Sorry, but don't call me again.
I stopped playing karuta.
Hurry up!
You're the one who showed up late!
It's not my fault!
I couldn't fall asleep last night.
Man, you're like a little kid on
the night before a field trip.
You owe me juice.
What?
This.
Can I get this and also the manju?
Hmm?
I already bought a gift for him.
I'm going to eat these.
Thank you very much.
I don't think it was
worth borrowing money from
your sister to make this trip.
Are you really that worried?
Sorry, but don't call me again.
Huh?
I stopped playing karuta.
An unfamiliar deep voice...
with a Fukui accent.
If I don't go see him now,
I'll never see him again.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 5
The Sight
of a
Midnight
Moon
Hey, Chihaya!
It's Mt. Fuji!
Sure is beautiful.
Ow!
What was that for, Taichi?!
Sorry, my legs are too long!
Mine are even longer!
We're on a trip!
Why don't you take in the scenery?
Arata probably found a different hobby.
Ginza Superstar Sablé
That's normal.
It's not a reason to go see him.
Y-You heartless bastard!
Men don't get touchy-feely
with each other.
So, Chihaya...
Huh?
Is there someone you like?
Dr. Harada!
Hah?!
I try to give him chocolate on
Valentine's every year, but...
No, I have my wife!
You shouldn't be giving her
a serious reply, Dr. Harada.
That wouldn't be considered love!
What would be love then?
Love is when...!
It isn't fun to be with that person.
What?!
You don't have fun when you're
with your girlfriend?!
I have fun.
She listens to me, and she's sweet.
So you just wanted to brag?
You should have taken
her on a date then.
Instead of wasting a day
off on a trip to Fukui.
What?!
She's ticking me off.
You can't even buy a train
ticket by yourself!
Oh!  I forgot about that!
It's when nothing goes
the way you want.
Hurry up!
There's no need to run!
Shirasaki
Kanezawa
You're not having fun...
I wanted the window seat!
Pipe down!  What's the difference?!
And yet...
You still want to be with her.
We're here!
If Arata's still living at the same address
that was on his New Year's
card from two years ago,
it shouldn't be that far-
Chihaya?
Huh? What?
Let's find a taxi.
This is Fukui.
This is where Arata lives.
Arata.
We're finally here.
Wataya
G-Go on, Chihaya.
Y-You go first.
You're seriously starting
to piss me off!
Why are you so quiet now?!
You said that men don't get
touchy-feely with each other!
I-I'm still nervous!
Huh?!  Why?!
Mashima, you're...
...a coward.
Coward
A little girl wouldn't understand.
What's that?
Stop trying to act all tough!
She looks like a supermodel.
Excuse me!
Is something wrong?
I live next door.
W-We're from Tokyo!
Arata?!  Are you Arata's friends?!
Yes!  We were friends when
Arata lived in Tokyo!
Arata works at the bookstore by
the station during this time of day.
The station!
Let's go, Taichi!
Back the way we came!
The station wasn't that far away!
Let's run!
I guess it's faster than
calling for another taxi.
And we have to save money
for the train ride home...
Oh, I'm Chihaya.
Thank you for telling us where he is.
Okay, Taichi.
Let's go!
Hey, Chihaya!
Thanks.
Chihaya!
There's no need to run!
But we have to hurry!
You're just gonna stand
outside the store anyway!
Anyway, Fukui's really something.
April's almost over, but the
cherry's are still blossoming.
Do I want to see Arata?
Or do I not want to see Arata?
I don't really care either way.
We can go home right now.
Huh?
Are you okay, Chihaya?!
Chihaya?
I've missed you!
I've missed you...
I'll leave a change of clothes here.
Oh, okay.
What am I supposed to do with this?
Arata?
I'll be going home now.
Okay.
Sorry about this, Yuu.
U-Uh...
Uh, this is a Tokyo specialty.
Please take some.
Thank you...
Bye.
You've grown quite a bit.
How tall are you?
173.
I lost by a centimeter!
O-Oh, what a coincidence.
I'm also 173.
Sure you aren't rounding?
You were always a coward.
Th-Thank you for letting
me use your bath.
Huh?
Why did you wash your hair?!
The back of my head
was covered in dirt!
But my panties were okay!
Don't mention your panties!
Are you still in grade school?!
Huh?  What's wrong?
They're my panties!
My point is...
You can wear those clothes home.
Once your hair dries, leave.
Huh?
Chihaya, let's go.
Wait!
I wrote a letter for Arata!
A letter?
When we came all the way up here?
Well, I figured that I
wouldn't know what to say,
so it would be easier if I had
something to read off of!
Here it is!
Let's play karuta together
with the three of us!
Can we use this room?
Chihaya?
My favorite moment when playing karuta
comes right before 25 cards are given
to each player and they're revealed.
I get so excited when I picture
the good things to come.
I picture myself winning.
Isn't it the same for you?
We were split up when we
started middle school,
but I'm sure that you still
played karuta by yourself.
You were getting better every day.
I always believed-
Don't you understand Japanese?
I stopped playing karuta.
I can't play.
Huh?
Glasses's grandfather
is an Eternal Master
who's famous in the karuta world.
I immediately knew that his
grandfather had taught him the game.
Arata...
That's a load of crap!
Taichi!
Let's leave!
There's no point in
trying to talk to him.
This isn't the Arata we knew.
That's not true!
He must have a reason!
I believe him!
If you believe him,
don't press the issue!
We didn't come here to see
you kick karuta cards!
We won't come back!
Wait!
Wait up, Taichi!
Taichi!
Chihaya!  Hey!
Don't leave these behind!
Take them with you!
I was never good at anything.
I never had any dreams...
But Arata told me that if I become
the best karuta player in Japan,
I would be the best in the world.
If I can be the best in
the world at something,
I think it's worth a shot.
Why...
as my sleeves are wet with dew
Why did Arata stop playing karuta?
Did he really quit?!
What happened?!
Tell me!
Arata's grandfather, Mr. Wataya,
was an Eternal Karuta Master,
and he was the one who taught
Arata to play karuta.
Arata loved his grandfather so much.
Then, four years ago,
his grandfather had a stroke.
Arata was there to take
care of his grandfather.
He worked hard to help
with rehabilitation.
But one day, when Arata
was supposed to be home,
his grandfather suffered a relapse.
Wataya-kun!
Hurry home!
Your grandfather suffered an attack!
Grandpa...
Champion  Wataya Arata
Arata had gone to a tournament
to reach Class A!
Arata hasn't touched a card since.
He can't do it.
Hey, Grandpa.
How come you can take cards so fast?
You move for the
"Would the" and "Would this"
cards after hearing "would"?
Why?
Come on, how can you tell?
Well, I suppose it's thanks
to the karuta god.
The karuta god?
If you love karuta and
play it every day,
the karuta god will sometimes whisper
the next syllable in your ear.
You see, my love of karuta is still
just as strong as yours.
If there truly is a karuta god,
he would look just like Grandpa.
Wait!
I wrote a letter for Arata!
If Arata has a cell phone, get his number!!
Important!
Ask if he received my New Year's card this year...
The one I screwed up
Ask if he received my New
Year's card this year.
Dr. Harada wants me to send
him a picture of Arata.
Will I be able to meet Arata
at a Kyoto tournament?
My sister's going to be on a quiz show.
But only mention this if I
have nothing else to say.
This is the letter?
I believe that Arata
is like a karuta god.
The longer we're apart,
the more you seem like a god.
I'm no god.
I'm nothing special.
Dr. Harada wants me to send
him a picture of Arata.
Will I be able to meet Arata
at a Kyoto tournament?
But I want to be your friend.
Chihaya!
Trains are considered public places.
Can you act like a human being?
I shouldn't have come.
Sorry, Taichi.
We shouldn't have come to see him!
Chihaya?
Chihaya!
Taichi!
Arata!  Arata!
Arata!
We can't open this?!
I didn't want you to come see me...
I didn't want you to
see what I've become!
But...
I really missed you.
Chihaya?
I'm so glad...
Huh?
He doesn't hate it!
It's not that Arata hates karuta now!
Don't sit down on the floor.
And stop babbling Arata.
But...
And don't get snot everywhere!
Suck it up.
Could you hear Arata's voice?
If I can be the best in
the world at something,
I think it's worth a shot.
I'll help you start a karuta club.
Huh?
If Arata's coming back,
we'll need to make the best
karuta club in Japan,
and wait for his return.
Let's start a competitive karuta club!
Please come see Ayase Chihaya in class 1-2!!