I can't take the sun...
Looks like we're in the Zuland Plains.
Um, we should see it soon.
Oh, there!
Wow! It's Mt. Fuji!
Huh? Where?
It's the spirit mountain of Fuji!
It really is huge!
Look!
There's something over there
that looks like a cow!
Really? Where?
Ah, I think that's a green elk herd.
Are they dangerous?
We'll be fine.
There's some distance between us,
and they're said to be calm.
They're so cute!
They really look just like cows.
I've heard they're delicious.
The Midday Vampire
The Midday Vampire.
The path here seems to be curving a little.
It runs along the coast.
There's so much grass,
I can't see the ocean at all.
But you can kind of smell the salt air, can't you?
I'm not sure, honestly.
Hey, didn't Shiroe say this road was...
The East Sea Road.
That's what this used to be called.
It was one of the Five Routes.
It began in Nihonbashi, Tokyo, and it
became an important trade route.
Today, the East Sea Road
is called "National Route 1,"
and many roads branch off of it.
If you follow it all the way,
it'll take you to Osaka.
Osaka!
Oh, you mean Minami.
So the roads are connected in this world, too.
Yeah.
This might be the fastest route
to the Redstone Mountains.
I've never really thought about
the roads that way before.
Me, neither.
Shiroe is so amazing...
He knows so much stuff.
Okay!
While I'm here, I'm gonna have an adventure,
and learn all kinds of things!
Think it's about time for lunch?
Sounds great!
This is good!
The chief's ham sandwiches are so good!
No objection, whatsoever.
Hey, you two!
Leave some for us, okay?
That's right.
Hey!
We're almost to Kalbe.
What should we do?
Stop there?
Let's keep going.
The weather's nice.
Let's have Danish and Croissant
work a little harder.
They're up for it.
We can keep going!
Let's do our best!
Yeah.
The path opens before Rundel Haus Code!
Okay, let's get going before it gets dark!
Yeah!
Wh-What happened?
The time limit ran out!
For the Twin Horse Flute of Lyman!
Oh, right...
It was six hours a day, wasn't it?
Why didn't anyone realize that, anyway?
You're right.
Still, just because the time limit ran out,
they didn't have to run away so fast.
That's right.
They ate carrots out of my hand.
They ate my cabbage, too.
They really have no sense of human gratitude!
Well, they're horses.
Even horses...
Horses?
Then would they have horse gratitude,
rather than human gratitude?
The horses ran off, but this is kind of nice.
Yeah.
Hey, where are we?
Somewhere between the
Kalbe Inn and Wilistoria Village.
Without them, we can't go on...
We'll have to camp.
Yeah, we'll just have to do it.
Leave the cooking to me.
This is where an adventurer really shines.
Being an adventurer has nothing to do with this.
We're camping out!
Yeah!
Let's eat!
This is good.
Yeah, it's really good.
It's just a little...
The salt flavor is...
Also...
Rudy!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
When I'm with Nyanta, I can make it just fine...
You just haven't practiced enough.
Don't worry about it.
The chief would say, "You simply
need to improve, little by little."
Right?
He's right, Serara.
I wish we had a cooking skill.
Sorry to keep relying on you, Serara!
That's right.
I need to keep a hold of myself.
I've got the Newlywed's Apron Dress, after all!
I need to do my best for Nyanta
and for everyone else!
Looks like the next place we
can stop is the town of Sazan.
How long will it take to get there?
If we can only use the horses for six hours a day,
it could take about three days.
Why is this road so twisty?
I wish it would just go straight.
Yeah, but as long as I get to
travel with everyone like this,
I don't care if it takes a long time.
I think Shiroe and the others sent us
on this trip to teach us this stuff.
You're great, Minori.
I feel like you've really grown up
from the person you used to be.
Have I?
I thought I'd grown up with you,
but I guess I have a long way to go.
That's not true.
You saved me back there.
I can do my best because you've always
been with me since I came to this world.
Well, I'm your big brother.
I'm your big sister!
No, I'm older!
No, it's me!
No, I am!
And I'm taller!
That doesn't matter!
It's been three days since they left on their trip.
I hope they aren't getting homesick.
Aww...
I'm sure they're having a great
time, like it's a field trip.
They may be saying they don't want to come back.
That would be a problem in itself.
You're looking pale again.
Am I?
Yes.
You're also glaring, Rieze.
You look just like my lord.
Don't get too stubborn.
Right.
Is it hard without the scary glasses guy?
Yes, it is.
I realized how much I depended upon my lord.
For the moment, D.D.D. is stable,
but we don't know what will happen in the future.
I'm sure I'm causing a lot of problems for people,
and I will probably cause more.
You don't need to worry about it.
Everyone knows it's rough.
Shiroe will do something.
My lord won't think of it as a bother.
He'll help you of his own free will.
Of course, so will I.
That's right.
You don't need to worry about us now!
We're friends, after all.
Why are you laughing now?!
Isn't that what being friends is?
It's kind of strange...
If we were in the old world, I'm sure
we never could've been friends.
You might be right.
No,
that isn't true.
It's said that the cute are drawn to one another!
I would've met you two, no matter what!
Henrietta, stop rubbing your
cheek against mine!
We didn't need that kind of assurance!
Akatsuki!
Oh, no!
Is that a Teaching for a ninja
body-swapping technique?
It's just a doll.
The sunset!
It's so pretty!
I can see it.
That's the town of Sazan!
We're almost there.
Our musician says she'd like to play here tonight.
We won't cause any trouble, so can
you provide a place to perform?
A forty-two, huh?
But adventurer bards are pricey...
I don't need any payment!
If you'll just let me play here, that's enough.
Please.
Please!
Nice job, Rudy!
We get to perform, and we can
stay free for the night!
This is what I am capable of.
...is what I'd like to say, but it's
thanks to Miss Isuzu's passion.
Rudy...
Don't worry about me.
You guys perform to your hearts' content.
Okay.
I really have learned a lot on this journey.
Even about the road we took to get here...
I wondered why there were
so many twists and turns.
But when I traveled it on a carriage,
I saw that there were forests and hills,
so we couldn't just go straight.
The road goes around all those things
to make it easier for people and carriages.
And this town was born so that, when you
started to feel tired, you could rest.
It was probably inevitable.
Don't be afraid of the boredom.
Let's... Let's... Let's go outside!
I think Rudy is amazing.
When I wasn't able to play soccer with everyone,
I couldn't just watch with an expression like that.
Will my twisty path culminate in a city somewhere?
I'm so tired...
They loved it!
The customers kept asking for another song.
The encore calls wouldn't stop.
Fantastic!
Yeah.
I knew it...
They have a lot of energy.
Too much energy.
I wonder what they're talking about.
Are you curious, Rudy?
Not at all.
I'm not such a boor as to be interested
in a secret chat among ladies.
I'm simply impressed that they never
run out of things to discuss.
That's because they're girls.
I see... Because they're girls... I mean, ladies.
Then is the reason that Miss Isuzu is so
pure and innocent because she's a lady?
Huh? Is she?
She always wants to hug me and rub my hair!
O-Oh...
I think she's just treating you like a dog.
Miss Isuzu doesn't act that way toward you.
Does she simply not think I'm important?
Don't laugh, Tohya!
I'm serious!
I'm sorry! Sorry!
I think it might mean you're special.
Special?
Yeah.
Paw.
You're my doggy, so you're special.
Hey! Why are you laughing?!
When Isuzu thinks it's fun to be with you,
that's what she does.
Is that so?
Yeah, yeah.
But I think that's different from
being especially beautiful,
especially amazing,
or especially magnificently strong!
What does she think about me?
If thinking about it won't help,
let's get some sleep.
That's not fair, Tohya!
I'll get some sleep, too. Goodnight.
Goodnight, Rudy.
Today, we're going to cross into the Sakawa region.
Sakawa?
In the modern world, that's Odawara.
They're famous for their fish paste.
Oh, I see.
We're going to follow this road
to the ruined castle of Ariba.
To get to our goal, the Redstone Mountains,
we'll either go off the Sea Road past the
Ariba ruins and onto a smaller road,
or take a route that involves climbing mountains.
Since this area is a rice paddy zone,
there are nature-type monsters.
Wild dogs, boars, and plant monsters
live in the forests and mountains,
Wild Dog
Rank/ Field
Boar (Mushroom)
but they keep to themselves.
Triffid
Rank/ Normal
And Shiroe said the monsters along the road
have their levels kept way down.
Then, even if we do run into one, we'll be fine.
Let's just keep going.
Okay, let's go!
Yeah!
Will this work?
Yeah, it's fine.
Sorry to have you take charge.
I don't care.
Isaac's actually looking forward to it.
Don't talk like you know me.
Anyway, so we have to train all the knights.
How many levels should we raise them?
Part of this is to forge friendships,
so two or three is fine.
That isn't very greedy.
They're People of the Land.
We can't be reckless with them.
What a pain.
Isaac...
Were you planning on power-leveling?
Yeah, that's easier.
If we take the lead and fight high-level monsters,
the lower-level guys will rise
in level automatically.
Their levels will go up,
but they won't get stronger.
You're so hard-headed, villain.
We can just alternate between
power-leveling and combat training.
No, I'll even focus on training!
This is starting to sound really macho,
but I guess it's okay.
Um, you still can't reach Crusty?
No.
He isn't responding on his Friend List, either.
What is he doing that's so important,
he'd ignore his guild?
It could fall apart.
Lately, lots of people are leaving D.D.D.
Of course, it's actually surprising
the guild's managed to stay on course
for these past three months.
Are you worried, villain?
What about you, Isaac?
I know him.
He's either off playing somewhere or fighting.
I'm worried about D.D.D., but...
The number of people in
Honesty has exceeded 1,250.
This is above our previous record.
But...
The majority of the new
members are basically leechers.
They don't hunt or gather outside of Akihabara,
and they don't do crafting or
trading in town, either.
Damned parasites.
Th-There are people like that. But...
These "people like that" are joining
our guild and taking it easy.
People in Akihabara and the guild
are getting angry with them.
It's only a matter of time
before that rage explodes.
Of course, I've shared our opinion
with the Round Table.
What can they do?
I think we simply have to kick them out.
Why not just limit who can join?
We can't do that.
The only reason Honesty maintains its influence
and position on the Round Table
is because we're the
third-largest guild in Akihabara.
If we lose that influence, we'll lose our
ability to influence Akihabara politics.
But I think it'd be healthier if the guild...
No, the whole town of Akihabara went on a diet.
Those are cherry blossoms, right?
Nope...
They're plums.
They smell so nice...
A river!
Oh, boy...
This won't be easy to cross.
Let's look for a way around.
Save us!
That's...
They're being chased by ogres!
Get over there and keep them safe!
Understood!
Man-Eating Demon
Rank/ Normal
Enemy levels are 21, 22, and 21!
Tohya!
Right!
Leave it to me!
Frost Spear!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Don't let your guard down!
There are fifteen adds!
Nightshade Serpent
Rank/ Normal
Nightshade Serpents.
Their average level is 40!
And there are fifteen of them!
They're a spirit-type monster.
Dark spirits have either evil poison,
or resistance to mind attacks and insta-kills.
Not only might we get hurt,
but the People of the Land could, too!
I'll go!
I'm not even touching them!
Tohya!
Servant Summon...
Princess Wraith!
Wow...
Um, who are you?
My name is Roe 2.
A summoner.
A traveling vampire, heading south, I suppose.
Roe 2
Race/ Half-Alv
Summoner, Lv. 90
No Guild
A new person with glasses...
I can't take the sun...
"Call me 'big sister.'"
Roe 2, a mysterious big sister who takes
joy in being called "big sister."
Tohya and the others enjoy their journey,
even with the chaos she causes.
They encounter a group of adventurers who fight
to protect People of the Land from monsters.
Next time: Odyssey Knights.
Odyssey Knights
I have friends to run with me.