How irresponsible.
You don't care if she dies or succeeds?
She won't die, and I don't
intend to let her.
She was expensive, after all.
You can neither become human, nor return
to being a fairy, you filthy creature.
Do you really think you'll be
forgiven for buying a human?
It seems you're still as much of
a human supremacist as ever, Renfred.
Why do you know about Chise?
You've never liked auctions, have you?
That event is strictly private.
What happens there is to be kept secret.
Besides, what use do you have
for this mass of human rage and regret?
I see.
Who took that arm of yours?
Good work, Chise.
Elias.
Flowers, huh?
You're safe!
That was clever.
Chise isn't all about
destruction the way you are.
He looks relieved.
Let's go, Alice.
Master...
Are you leaving?
You still haven't told me anything.
The corruption is gone. I have
no further business here.
I don't care how you use the girl.
Be careful.
There are countless people
interested in her.
You knew them?
That sorcerer is famous for
his distaste for mages.
He's always liked picking fights with me.
He still had both of his arms
the last time I saw him, though.
Something's going on.
Are you okay, Chise?
Her magical production circuits
must be exhausted.
You can get some sleep.
Thank you.
Elias...
When am I going to die?
You hadn't forgotten, huh?
In three years, maybe,
if nothing's done about it.
I've thought of a way to prevent it.
You don't have to worry.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because there was no reason to.
Your death isn't a part of my plans.
So your experiment is to
see if you can keep me from dying?
Sure.
To see what will happen if I have a Sleigh Beggy
around me, a reservoir of limitless magic.
But you don't need more magic, do you?
So, why me?
I'm half-baked—neither
human, fairy, nor spirit.
I've lived for a long, long time,
and seen many humans,
but I still don't quite understand
any of them, including you.
I can comprehend your thoughts,
but I can't empathize.
I can understand the reasons behind
your tears, anger, and laughter,
but I can't make them my own.
I bought you because it was
advantageous for me.
That's all.
Because you had nothing, and you couldn't
part from the non-human that is me.
I let you hear the words that I suspected you
would want to hear, and gave you shelter, food,
knowledge, and attention.
I thought I might learn something
if I raised one of you myself.
I did plan on telling you after you'd
become completely attached to me.
It's strange.
Though I had to do it
earlier, thanks to Renfred.
His facial expression doesn't change.
I know.
If you don't need this memory,
I can destroy it for you.
Yet the glimmer in his
eyes is like a child's.
There's no need to be scared.
Until you don't need me anymore...
I'll stay by your...
side...
Look at that quality male, being
confessed to by a female.
You've impressed me, mage.
I think she meant, "You're so
pathetic, I can't just leave you."
She touched me for the first time.
It looks like you'll finally have what
you've sought, after your long journey.
I'm glad for you.
Shall we return to our home, Chise?
Is this all for today?
Indeed, I hope she wakes up today.
Her breath and her pulse are stable.
It hasn't hurt her physically yet.
Chise may be more capable than I thought.
You're back, Simon?
At least let me worry about her.
Two weeks you've returned from
Ulthar, and she's still not awake.
It's to be expected.
She's keeping her physical
functions to a minimum,
so she can focus on replenishing
the magic she used.
Recovery is faster in the forests
or under water than in the city.
She'll awaken soon.
I don't approve of you letting
such a child be so reckless.
You're still hiding something, aren't you?
You can tell, huh?
It's been ten years since I was
assigned to keep an eye on you.
I can tell when your bony
face is pale under your cloth.
Sing, sing, sing.
Ruffle, trees, in the wind,
let not the sunlight pass.
Dance, flowers and grass,
let not your scent be lost for direction.
Sing praise, homeless bird,
that the mistress of the night
shall not tear off your wings.
Return to the earth, and sing,
flutter in the skies, and sing,
bow your head to the noble garden and sing,
for the great Gealach of Tir na nÓg has arrived.
Well, well, two strapping
young men to greet me.
How kind of you both.
My queen, you ought not speak
directly with the commoners.
You're so strict.
He is one of my own, Spriggan.
I have no respect to show a being of flesh.
Who is she?
Try not to talk to her too much.
She's the Queen of Faeries.
She commands all of the creatures
of the night in Britain.
Titania.
You're perhaps the only one besides my
husband that calls me by my name, Thorn.
Where's the king?
He gets rambunctious, so I left him behind.
I wanted to see you and
your hatchling today.
Oh?
You worship that foreign god.
You're called a "priest," are you not?
Y-Yeah.
Yes, though the scent is faint...
Those who kneel to the one who condemned
the fruit of paradise as evil are not welcome.
Be gone.
That was uncivil.
He'll merely wander the woods for a while.
I'll return him after the hour of honey mead.
Now, Thorn, would you
introduce me to your wife?
Wow, a redhead.
She'll become a great mage.
Oberon... What are you doing?
Shucks, you found me.
You weren't even trying to hide.
Faerie King Oberon.
She's neither a toy nor a doll.
Stand back, please.
What, are you jealous?
You've finally come to that, huh?
I like it.
How manly.
The one who wears a shell of flesh...
Seeing change in a halfling
like yourself is splendid.
You'd only been watching
from the shadows until now,
but you're trying to end your wandering
by having a human nearby.
Watching you act as though you were
her parent or mate is quite fun.
Although...
I wonder how long you can keep
up your false kindness for this one person.
Ow, ow, ow!
You mustn't bully children, dear.
You're here to see his
mate today, aren't you?
You're so soft when it
comes to kids, Titania.
Unfortunately, I'm not as
unscrupulous as you are.
You're so mean!
Fine.
Let's just hurry up and
wake this sleepy-head.
Magic power.
I knew it.
Our robin is beautiful
when she opens her eyes.
Good morning, sweet maid
who bears the name of birds.
Did you have sweet dreams?
U-Uh...
Who are you?
Morning, Chise.
Elias.
Rejected.
A hatchling's imprinting sure is strong.
She just caught on to how
terrible a person you are.
Um...
You were asleep for a while.
How do you feel?
Are you tired or in pain?
Uh, I'm not.
Good.
Sorry to scare you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Titania, queen of all faeries who
live in Albion as well as Tir na nÓg—
And I'm her husband, Oberon!
Nice to meet you.
Albion?
Tir?
An old name for the island of Great Britain.
Tir na nÓg is the land of fairies—
Hey, girl, Chise, was it?
You aren't afraid of him?
Are you okay?
Not distressed?
Sure.
Yes, I'm fine.
Oh, yeah?
I'm glad.
Yup.
As long as you aren't scared.
So, do you have kids yet?
Huh?
You're married, aren't you?
Maybe you're too little still.
I bet your child would be an excellent mage.
Kids are cute.
Especially blondes!
Seriously.
We really love blondes.
Spriggan.
Go.
Ow, ow, ow!
Not there, stop! Ow, ow, ow!
I guess he's kind of really stupid.
Pay him no mind.
Do forgive my fool of a husband.
I-Is he all right?
Don't worry.
He's enjoying it.
No!
Oh.
He's one of those people.
Kids?
By kids, does he mean...
Is something the matter?
No.
It's nothing.
Elias?
Nothing, my gut just...
I don't know.
Oh dear, oh dear.
This good-for-nothing makes
himself useful once in a while.
I'll be excusing myself now,
especially since this idiot is here.
We'll talk another time.
I'm glad I got to meet the hatchling mage.
Come visit us someday.
We'll hold a banquet.
I'll go, if you intend to let us come home.
We'll see.
Every being of the night, including she
and you, are my adorable little children.
Well then, good day.
Toodles!
Don't you dare think of setting
foot there, even if the queen allows it.
It's no place for a half-baked
creature with a shell of flesh.
Those with shells bring only calamity.
I know.
I would never ask to be invited.
Elias?
You sure are harsh to everyone
that isn't a fairy.
Damn shelled being...
Think of all the people and spirits
that were lost because of him.
The humans were guilty back then.
It's always those of us in the humans'
shadows that get the short end of the stick.
Well, then, why don't we bet on whether or
not it'll work out between those two, Titania?
Far wiser to bet on the number of children.
True.
I'm finally out of the forest.
Fairy magic is such a pain.
Simon-san.
Chise-kun!
You're finally awake.
We were worried about you.
Sorry.
Shoot, the sisters are going to yell at me.
I'll be going now.
Too bad I can't stay for dinner.
Are you really my watchdog?
I'm kidding.
Well, then, Chise-kun,
take care of yourself.
He's a good person.
He's just stupid.
He hasn't changed at all in ten years.
Ten years...
I wish you'd bought me ten years ago.
Even though we're going to be spending
far more than ten years going forward?
I hope your experiment succeeds.
It will.
Will it?
We'll make it.
Now, Silver is waiting.
Let's go home.
What's this?
It's out of season,
but it's a Christmas pudding.
She's aged it since the day you came home.
It's good.
Isabelle...
The girl and the mage set out
to fulfill their final task.
The sorcerer Joseph's schemes are set in
motion in pursuit of the masterless black dog.
Don't mess up next time.