I can see it. The reconstruction
of this world is already underway.
Wha?
A dark being utilized the
opportunity to infiltrate...
...while we were away at the battlefield.
This place is an utterly different world!
Either way, it's the same.
No. It feels alien.
Has the dark world already
eroded so far into this world?
I know what I must do.
Schwartz Shield!
Togashi and Rikka, welcome back!
How was your field trip?
It had its ups and downs.
Wasn't it fun?
You two wandered around
the city together, right?
Hey, you got a new one!
The Schwartz Z/X Perfect
Customized Ghelzonianses!
Don't mix that in!
Ghelzoni?
Good morning!
Oh, if it isn't Ghelzonianses and my master!
I said, don't mix that in.
Dekomori.
Why are you acting so surprised, Master?
The dimension really has warped!
EPISODE VIII THE FALSE... MORI SUMMER
[OR "HOLY SPIRIT MOTHER"]
The real Mori Summer?!
Ssh, not so loud.
What do you mean?
There is no real thing. I'm right here.
But she told me she met her.
I think they became acquainted
through her home page
while you were away on your field trip.
She's here.
H-how do you do?
I have been expecting you,
Mistress Mori Summer.
How do you do?
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting, Sanja.
Did she say "Sanja"?
But look at the gemstones on her left hand.
Those are the Mori Summer trademark.
I, the Magician Mori Summer,
have come here once again
to deliver my words of guidance unto you.
Yes, ma'am. Thank you.
I will begin with a purification
I and the soul spirits will perform.
Please place your hands together
and close your eyes peacefully.
Yes.
I am done.
What the heck was that?
I suspect that was a magical
purification device.
What?!
That was obviously a digital camera.
Who does that woman think she is anyway?
And so, you informed them of
my existence upon their return?
Yes, ma'am. I intend to inform
Fake Mori Summer
of your existence as well,
Mistress Mori Summer.
Then she'll be sorry!
Sanja, you mustn't approach others
with such evilness in your heart.
Yes, any commoner who would assume
the name of Mori Summer
is undoubtedly a thoroughly
twisted individual with an ugly heart.
What?!
However, if you entertain
hatred for such a person...
that hate will only taint
your own purity, Sanja.
Love is most important!
A foolish, worthless commoner
who thrives upon deceit...
is precisely who so desperately
needs our guidance!
Oh!
Oh, really? That woman is very interesting.
Hey!
It's you, Fake Sum...
I told you I'm not a fake.
Oh, dear. Are you the one
who has been using my name?
Deko!
You're the identity thief!
How dare you make a home page?!
Oh, my. Sanja told me about you,
but I had no idea the pretense ran so deep.
You must be extremely impure of heart.
It's easy to see.
Oh, really?
Mistress Mori Summer!
You stand back!
Deko!
Sanja!
Who are you calling Sanja?! Now listen up!
I utterly despise women like you
who hide who they really are...
...behind a facade of goody-goodiness!
Like you can talk.
You butt out.
Then are you suggesting that
you are the real Mori Summer?
I am!
If so, why do you hide who you really are?
I have been told that you attempted to burn
the scripture of the Mabinogion.
Th-that was because...
That's right! You would only do that
because you are the imposter!
That isn't true!
Then why did you?
Because...
Well...
It's complicated.
Just be quiet.
Was it wise to tell her you'd
bring the proof tomorrow?
I couldn't exactly back down.
I disposed of my dark
history very thoroughly.
There is nothing left.
The hand accessory isn't enough proof.
Now what?
It's time for my last resort.
Spirits, I order you.
Please honor my request.
That's your last resort?!
I feel the power.
It will be fine. This locating method
has a 100% success rate.
As they say, fortune telling
can be unpredictable.
Be quiet. You're distracting me.
So, she found nothing.
Is Nibutani really the imposter
as Dekomori claims?
No, not at all.
But I don't really see the issue
no matter who's the real thing.
Yuta.
Yeah.
So, you have no proof then?
You could say that. But I am the real one.
This is what you get for competing
with the real thing, Fake Summer!
You don't know the sheer scope of your folly!
Oh, be quiet! I will also add that
I'll bet you don't have any proof either.
You are truly appalling. The proof that
I am indeed Mori Summer...
...is I, in-of-myself!
Pardon?
I am the very visage of the magician
embodied within the Mabinogion.
My true identity is obvious to one
with magical power such as Sanja.
That's right!
I knew it was her the moment I saw her!
I knew this was truly the real Mori Summer!
Do you recall how you claimed
that I was the real thing too?
Don't act so conceited!
That was an advanced tactic
designed to throw you off guard!
So that's what it was!
Don't fall for that.
I will be blunt.
We are all now fully aware
that you are am imposter.
No one with such a disgraceful countenance
could possibly be Mori Summer.
Now, repent the error of your ways
and part with Sanja.
That shut you up good.
I knew you were the imposter.
Fine.
Huh?
So what if my old, dark history
was dragged out into the light?
I just have to ignore
it, and it will go away.
I no longer have any proof
that I'm Mori Summer.
I'm relieved to finally be free of you.
So long.
Mori Summer?
Hey, Nibutani.
F-Fake Summer?
Now she and I are both finally free
to take our proper paths uninhibited.
Mistress Mori Summer.
I'm relieved to finally be free of you.
As if! I know you hate to lose.
Sanae, what's wrong?
You don't look very happy today.
I'm fine.
You're sure?
SENDER: MISTRESS MORI SUMMER
TO: DEKOMORI
Come to my house after school and
we will read the Mabinogion together.
Are you really okay with this?
It has nothing to do with me.
Of course it does. She's impersonating you!
Whatever. I just won't let it bother me.
Ow.
Dekomori.
Yesterday was a true work of blunder!
Your fakeness was finally exposed
for what it really is...
...along with your foolishness!
W-wait!
Why?
Why do you sulk? Did it hurt
so much to be beaten by me?
To be exposed for the
imposter you really are?
Not really.
Go on, class is starting.
Well, hmph! This is what I get
for exercising tact.
Are you sure?
About what?
And then Deko went home?
Yes.
That's no good. That's
where you have to shine.
You are Ghelzonianses, aren't you?
Please don't memorize that, Senpai!
I did ask them both to come to the club room.
Dekomori is useless to me now.
I must find a temporary servant.
And then there's you!
Do you really think Deko will be okay?
Whoever that person is, she scares me.
Why is that?
Listen.
Love?
Yeah. According to Kumin-senpai...
...that person looks at Dekomori amorously.
Don't be ridiculous.
I actually thought the same thing.
When I look back at it...
...she does look different
when she looks at Dekomori.
You really should tell her.
W-why? Assuming that's true,
if that's what that idiot truly wants,
then leave it that way.
Hey, what's the point of
being stubborn about it?
Dekomori is only into her because
she believes she's Mori Summer.
That is exactly what ticks me off.
How could she be taken in
by that imposter so easily?
But is she really?
What?
I think Deko is only doing it
because somewhere deep down...
...she still wants you to
be the real Mori Summer.
She's too stupid to think
something that complex.
What is it?
Ssh.
What is she doing?
I bet that's a photo of Deko!
Battle?
Yeah. You will challenge her to battle
in front of Dekomori.
Defeat her, and prove
that you are Mori Summer.
That is the best way to do it now
there's no more proof
that you are the real Mori Summer.
Excuse me?!
You've done it before, remember?
You must fully become
Mori Summer and fight her.
That's how I earned Rikka's trust!
Infatuated much?
No!
Even I get embarrassed!
But there's no time to think.
He's right. You can't let her take
Deko away from you.
W-why should I care?
Argh, this is too much trouble!
Go, Rikka!
Understood.
W-what?
You need a crash course!
I will engrave you with the power
of Wicked Lord Shingan!
Be destroyed, real. Blow up, synapses.
Vanishment, This World!
Huh?
What's wrong?!
Vanishment, This World!
I think I'm incompatible with this shrine.
Incompatible? Get real!
Now what do we do?
Rikka can't do it, and Deko isn't
around to help either.
Togashi?
I'm through with all that.
We need the magical devil girl.
Who, Shichimiya? But you...
The magical devil girl told me.
She said would remain
a magical devil girl forever.
And the contract between
you and I is absolute.
It will work.
I summon thee!
I am magical devil girl,
Sophia Ring SP Saturn VII!
I will smite the angel!
Sorry for calling you out so late.
That's okay. You guys helped me out
on my school field trip.
I'm really glad things seem
to be working out for you two.
Huh?
So, you want me to give Mori Summer
a crash course in combat?
What? You're serious?
Yes, please.
Leave it to me. I was her partner...
...back when she called herself Mori Summer,
so I know her well.
Do you see the medicinal plants over there?
You always picked and ate them.
What? S-stop!
You would put a notch in
a tree and drink its sap.
Stop!
And you would spend entire days
trying to talk with small birds.
Embarrassing! Embarrassing!
Discard all shame!
You are Mori Summer, the magician
who has lived for 1,200 years!
You are here to spread your message of love!
No!
Is she okay?
We have to. Do it.
Okay, here it comes!
No!
I knew she was genuinely an imposter.
Although I knew that all along.
MAILBOX
Now delete that web page
or I won't get you a souvenir.
And what is that?
Mistress Mori Summer!
Y-you startled me.
It seems as though your
heart is still tainted.
What? Mistress Mori Summer?
I will purify it for you.
I will embrace your entirety with my love.
Mistress Mori Summer,
you're standing too close.
Let me take care of it.
Wha... What?
Stop it!
Sanja!
Your thingies here are as cute as a baby's.
Stop! Stop it!
Help me, Fake Summer!
That's far enough.
I have lost my memory, however...
I have lived for 1,500 years.
I am the greatest and
most real magician alive.
I gather together the threads of the story
with the spirits to guide me.
My name...
...is Mori Summer.
What?
Are you here again?
You, who call yourself Mori Summer.
I propose that we settle who the real
Mori Summer is here and now.
What are you talking about?
We have already discussed this.
If that is so, use your love
to purify me and obliterate me
for now and all eternity.
We will have a wizard's duel
on the horizon of permanence.
Take flight, elves! Whisper
to me, soul spirits!
Spiritual Caricature!
Get her, Nibutani!
I know.
I've taken it too far to get embarrassed now.
What is the meaning of this?
Do you want Sanja that badly?
Get real.
I can't stand the idea of you using
the name of Mori Summer, that's all!
I am the true one. Come to me, soul spirits!
Fairy spirits, lend me your strength!
Nothing embarrasses me
more than my dark history...
...but Mori Summer is still my creation!
Fake Summer.
I will not allow her to be
used by a creep like you
for your own despicable ends!
She was my own twisted love...
I aimed at myself!
Yes!
Critical hit.
Got that? Good. Now get lost.
What was that attack supposed to be?
Is that your so-called power as Mori Summer?
Sorry to disappoint you,
but I have exhaustively
studied the entire content of the Mabinogion.
I am the greater incarnation of Mori Summer.
The girl is mine.
She is my angel
I fought so hard to find.
I have been following her ever since
I first saw her in the city.
I waited so long to approach her.
You will never have her!
Mori Summer!
Nibutani!
Apparently I have the greater power
of imagination, Miss Faker.
It's time for you to disappear
for good this time.
Begone!
You're tough. Just let go.
I should mention that even
if you do get what you want...
...and get the moronic freshman for yourself,
you'll only live to regret it.
What?!
She's the worst. She
never does as she's told.
She has no intention of
respecting her elders.
She's spoiled, and violent, and annoying.
But she gets lonely, and she can be
such a coward, and she's a crybaby.
And she makes these really cute smiles
when you least expect it.
Fake Summer.
She's no angel.
She's more trouble than any devil.
She's the best idiot ever.
Did you call her an idiot?
Do not defile my Sanja!
Nibutani!
Mjolnir Hammer!
Sanja, why?
She is definitely the imposter.
She is Fake Summer, however...
She is a genuine imposter,
fair and square! Unlike you!
What?
You are not Mori Summer either!
The real Mistress Mori Summer
would never do this!
What?
You are a wolf in sheep's clothing!
I, Dekomori, will vanquish you, Fake Summer!
Ultimate End Of The Great Hammer...
...GX!
I loved you from the moment I saw you.
I thought you were angelic.
I wanted to make you look my way.
That's all.
What's so great about someone like her?
"Someone like her?" Sanja is an angel.
A pure and innocent angel.
She has never loved or been with a man.
She has never held hands,
never mind kissed anyone.
She actually has had her first kiss.
What?
On Christmas.
Th-that wasn't...
You're kidding. But I...
But I thought she was the one.
Victory!
You had no part in it.
I'm so glad they seem to be back to normal.
By the way, that kiss was an accident.
That goes without saying!
Why are you blushing?!
I am not blushing!
You're the one turning red.
I am not!
TO BE CONTINUED
You are so unlovable!