Number 18684, Sister Krone.
We hereby appoint you
to be Mom for Plant Four?
I'll be a Mom?
Yes.
There was a sudden opening
at Plant Four for a Mom.
I've been recommending you for some time,
which is why you were selected.
You've been recommending me?
Grandma is at the gate to pick you up.
Pack up immediately
and go back to headquarters.
Immediately?
Goodbye. Please do your best
at the new plant, too.
What's wrong? You don't look happy.
Oh no, this is an honor. I'll get ready.
That woman. She intends to get rid of me!
It's all or nothing, but I have to try.
I will not let everything go her way!
Mom!
Krone! The food's ready!
Huh? Where's Krone? Wasn't she with you?
Is she in her room?
No. She has some work to do.
We should start eating first.
Grandma.
There's something I'd like to report.
I'm so hungry!
Huh?
Krone's not here.
Where is she?
Mom said she has work to do.
So, is this what you mean?
In addition to the facts on this note,
the other perfect scorers know about
the secret and are trying to escape.
And the two high-quality ones below them!
I don't have evidence regarding their escape,
but please believe me!
If we leave this alone,
it'll get dangerous! At this rate—
However...
they are being kept under control, right?
If they are kept under control,
then there are no issues.
Just like how it was back in my day.
This is troublesome, Sister Krone,
that you get in Isabella's way.
They are special.
Isabella and her plant.
Isabella is a necessary pawn for me.
You are insufficient to take her place.
It will become troublesome for me.
May we offer the best plate at the Tifari.
May the farm have maximum profits.
Ah, I see.
They were in it together.
I had no chance of winning
from the beginning.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food!
You brats better escape.
You're good at playing tag, right?
Run...
and run...
and survive.
Then destroy this damned world we live in!
Thank you, that was delicious!
Let's start switching out the chemicals.
Let's go over the plan.
Norman and Emma will climb the wall
to inspect the vicinity.
Don and Gilda, stay outside where you can see
the south window on the House's second floor.
Just in case I fail to distract Mom,
I'll signal you.
Let Emma and Norman know
to cancel the inspection immediately.
Please let this go smoothly.
I eliminated her.
I eliminated Sister Krone.
I didn't need her anymore.
That's why I eliminated her.
You too.
Our deal is over, right here and now.
Am I fired as well?
Why? You need me, don't you?
Don't you want to use me
so you can control them
indirectly and peacefully
from behind the scenes?
That's exactly it.
I was doing a good job. To you...
Yes, you were a useful dog.
That's why I kept you by my side.
Even if you're a lying traitor.
Even so, there shouldn't be a problem, right?
As long as I'm useful!
Yes. It's true that there is no fault with you.
This is an unfair dismissal.
It's also unfortunate for me.
This was unforeseen.
I didn't want to let you go until the end.
Then—
But I have no choice.
The situation has changed.
From now on, I'll control them by myself.
I'm sorry, Ray. Please forgive me
for the things I'm about to do.
Mom!
Stay there for a bit, okay?
I'll let you out when I come back.
Let's see. From the speed of the two signals
running through the forest,
it must be Emma and Norman.
They're heading straight for the fence.
I wonder if it's for inspection?
Oh, and I don't care about the chemicals.
That's because you'll protect me.
For their sake, you won't get me killed.
That's why if you wanted to suppress me,
you'll definitely use a different method.
Goodbye, Ray.
Thank you for all your hard work until now.
Damn it!
In any case, I have to get out of here!
This is the worst!
There's no signal.
Hopefully things go smoothly.
What's going on?
Ray hasn't signaled us, but Mom came out!
What should we do?
Gilda, you stay here.
Don!
I'll check inside the House!
Please, just open!
Ray? Is that you?
Don?
Stay back!
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
Besides that, Ray...
That's right!
Gilda, let's go!
Is inspection canceled?
Are we stopping Emma and Norman?
We're enforcing the inspection!
We have to stop Mom!
Mom?
This is now our only chance!
We need to let them inspect no matter what,
before Mom gets to them!
Okay!
Emma.
Yeah.
Why...
Mom.
What's wrong?
Ten years.
We've been living together for ten years,
but this is the first time
talking to you without the acting.
Nice to meet you, Emma.
Nice to meet you, Norman.
Come on, please be at ease.
Don't worry. It's just us.
No one else is here.
You don't have to pretend to be good kids
who don't know anything.
Right now, it's just the caretaker
and the children meant to be food.
But please don't misunderstand.
I love you children.
I adore you. Truly.
I love you as if you were my own children.
And that's why I'm here.
I want you to give up.
Give up?
Give up what?
Give up resisting.
Because I love you, I don't want you to suffer.
I don't want to have to make you all suffer.
It's a happy life, isn't it?
A warm home
filled with love and delicious food.
Without knowing hunger, coldness, or the truth,
you can die with a satisfied feeling.
What part of that is unhappy?
A happy life?
Is the happiness you speak of
similar to the end that Conny met?
Death happens in an instant.
Until that moment,
Conny lived a rich life full of smiles.
I don't need any fake smiles!
Even if I suffer, I will live freely!
I will decide for myself what happiness is!
Emma.
Norman.
It's impossible to escape.
It's dangerous outside, too.
It's full of despair.
Okay? Let's all live together
happily inside our home.
Until the end, when your time runs out.
I want the five of you to be happy.
Five? Not three?
Okay, Mom.
I'll quit being a good boy.
Go, Norman!
Emma!
There, there. It's okay.
It doesn't hurt. It doesn't hurt.
You poor thing. My adorable Emma.
That's why I said to give up.
But you haven't hugged me in a while,
so that made me happy.
Norman, you realized it too.
That's wonderful.
That's right. I'll control you until the end.
That's how special you are.
A special meal
that only a special One can eat.
The highest quality children that I have raised.
Then...
That's why I have to protect you.
No matter what.
I had to do this
because you weren't going to give up.
Mom!
Mom, what happened to Emma?
Did she get hurt?
Hey.
You can't move for a while now.
You can welcome tomorrow safely.
Tomorrow?
Yes, tomorrow.
Stay put and celebrate, Emma.
I got a notice from the higher-ups.
Congratulations, Norman.
Your shipment date has been set.