Up you go!
And, again!
Hang on a minute.
I'm almost done.
Get off the counter!
Morning.
Good morning.
And down you go.
Wakana, can I get some food?
In a sec. I'm feeding Dora first.
For you.
And you.
What is this?
Leftovers from last night.
Hey.
It's because you always make
too much for dinner, Dad.
You could at least jazz it up with
some egg or sauce, or something.
I have to go now,
so please wash the dishes
when you're done.
What?
Don't "what" me.
And you should get up earlier.
Don't click your tongue at me.
I'm off.
Huh?
Hey, do you know what happened
to the flowers I left here?
I planted them.
You planted them?
In the garden.
Why?
You looked busy.
I told you I was taking those to school!
You did? When?
I can't believe this!
Have a good day.
Bye!
Episode 1
Running and Inviting
Sabure, whoa.
Miyamoto!
Oh, good morning.
On your way to practice, too?
Yeah.
Isn't it kind of sad to play
batminton by yourself?
It's badminton.
Good luck, forever alone!
Shut up.
Are you okay with taking the train home?
Yeah. See you later.
Shirohamazaka High School
Thank you so much.
Anything for our best customer.
It's Saturday, so I'll be home early.
See you in the evening!
If you keep eating like that, you'll get fat.
I'm off, Sabure.
Bye!
...even on a narrow path.
Running out, headlong
toward a miracle.
Looking up, waving at the light.
Connecting our unstoppable feelings.
Stop there.
You all need to listen to the other sections.
Sopranos, tone it down.
Tenors, mezzo-forte.
I shouldn't have to keep telling you this.
There's only a month left until the recital.
We'll work on the sections after school.
Dismissed.
Miyamoto-san.
Bow.
Thank you very much!
You want to sing, don't you?
Huh?
I have the song memorized,
so you don't need to turn
the pages for me anymore.
Oh?
This is our last performance this year,
so why don't you talk
to the vice principal?
Great idea! I will!
Good morning, Sakai-san!
Morning.
Oh wow, your plant is really cute!
Are those fresh flowers?
Yeah.
I snipped some hydrangeas from home.
Home?
Morning!
Hey!
Good timing, Konatsu. Help me wrap these.
Hurry, before Miss Takahashi shows up!
You should have done that at home.
Sawa, I need your help over here, too!
Sure, one second.
Konatsu, can I see your math printout?
Ta-da!
You guys are my slaves today.
Where in Austria did you live?
In Wien.
Wien? Oh, you mean Vienna.
I'm sorry I wasn't able
to get a uniform on time.
Don't worry about it.
It must be very hard to move back here
in your third year of high school.
I'll have someone show
you around after school.
Thank you very much.
Tanaka! Late again?
Wait right here. I'll call you in shortly.
Okay.
All right, class, take your seats.
Today, we'll–
Present bouquets!
Miss Takai
Thank You So Much!
Have a Healthy Baby!
Boy or Girl?
Thank you! Congratulations!
It's just maternity leave,
but if I'm not back by
graduation, I'm sorry.
Could we do our graduation ceremony right now?
Hey.
What, you wanna sing "Pomp and
Circumstance" with everyone?
Sakai-san, would you sing it?
Yeah, could you?
You've been studying music, right?
I want to hear you sing!
All right, all right.
You all know who I want
to hear last today.
Our repeat offender.
Tanaka Taichi!
Huh?
I come early every morning for practice!
I wasn't late today, either!
Excuses, excuses.
Oh, men.
Fine, then I'll sing.
I will now perform Shirahamazaka
High's school song.
I want to hear the voice
of the white beach,
so let's climb that winding slope.
Oh, no!
My dear friends...
I'm so sorry!
I've been away from Japan for twelve years,
but I'll try my best to get
used to everything quickly.
Right now, as my only friends are books,
I beseech you to bless
me with your favor.
Kneeling?
It is now noon.
Tanaka, please show him around.
Okay. Let's go.
Thank you.
Sakai, can you help me carry these?
Sure.
Have you gotten used
to the general curriculum?
Yes.
And you've made some friends?
I guess.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Can you please drop this?
If you hold out a little longer,
I'll set you up with my kid.
You're having a boy?
Does it have to be a boy?
Of course.
Hang on.
I'm going to grab my car keys.
You came all the way here
to talk about this?
Well...
I'm well aware Ueno-san has
the music memorized.
Her focus is piano, after all.
Then why do I need to
turn the pages for her?
Music is not a game.
This joint recital is an
event with a rich tradition,
featuring not only the high
schools of this district,
but professional performers
are invited, as well.
35th Joint Recital
Professors from music colleges
will also be coming to listen.
For music students, this
is a priceless opportunity.
Remind me, what did you do at
this function last year?
But that's why I've been...
Anybody can love music.
For music to love you, however,
is another story entirely.
It takes a special something
to move people's hearts,
and you don't have it.
Abandon your aspirations
to sing on stage.
Once the recital is over–
Then I quit.
Excuse me?
I quit!
Miyamoto-san.
If you're serious,
submit a formal request.
What gives you the right
to act like you know me?!
Nobody knows if they can sing, until they try!
Don't underestimate me just because I'm a general–
Blergh! You cow!
What are you doing?
That's it. Thank you.
That reminds me.
Do you have your phone on you?
Huh?
That's my address.
Contact me if anything comes up.
Like what?
Like if you find a boyfriend.
And come see the baby once it's born.
Sorry, but I want to eat
before I go to club.
What club?
Badminton.
I'm the only member right now,
but today I get to practice with
my sister at her university.
"Sister" is for a girl?
What was the word for a male sibling?
Brother.
Oh yeah.
I tried brushing up through books,
but I've still got a lot to learn.
Do those books explain how
to eat ramen, as well?
Of course!
You can't be serious!
You shouldn't have to quit!
She's doesn't understand anything!
I'm going to go have a talk with her.
W-Wait, Sawa!
Wait! Stop! I said, stop!
It's just, I'm already a senior...
Singing might be the most important
thing in my life right now,
but soon I'll be graduating,
going to college, getting a job.
These days are almost over.
So if she won't let me sing,
I should just quit.
But then what?
I know, I haven't had a chance to sing!
I really want to sing,
so I'm going to start a new choir group.
So...
So you have to sing with me, Sawa!
Me?! But I have a terrible voice.
Not true!
You have a powerful voice.
But I'm already doing archery.
Do both.
Are you allowed to start a new club?
I think so.
How?
You put the name of the club
and what it's for here.
Here, you put the president,
and here the advisor.
You need the principal's seal here.
Then, you submit this
to the student council
with the club members' applications.
Okay.
You need at least five people to start.
Do you think you can do that?
I've got myself and Sawa,
and I was thinking I
could invite Sakai-san.
She'd be great to have on board!
Yeah...
This might not be a good time, though.
Why's that?
Well, she didn't have enough
general credits,
so she's taking supplementary classes.
But a girl like you might be
a good catalyst for her.
A girl like me?
A cheerful, nice, and pretty girl.
Thank you!
An earnest girl who's
easy to understand.
I hope they don't have a weird
chemical reaction and explode.
Good luck to you, too!
Oh, thank you.
To the left, there's the
general studies building,
and to the right is the music building.
On the left is the general studies...
This is the inner courtyard.
If you're out here eating,
watch out for black kites.
Okay.
Watch out for black kites.
And that's the gym over there.
That is the gym.
Do you bike here?
Do I what?
Do you ride your
bike to come to school?
Oh, no, I come by train.
Then I guess I don't have
to show you the bike rack.
My club starts soon, so I have to go.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
I think you should look into
getting a different book.
Ki no Tsurayuki wrote about
a ficticious woman who,
on her travels, met many...
All right, then let's stop here.
Starting next week, a new
student will be joining our class.
Yes.
Thank you.
Sakai-san!
Let's walk home together part way.
The uniforms for the music
students are really cute.
You think so?
Do you ride your bike when it rains, too?
Usually.
What's this about?
Huh? What do you mean?
We've never walked home together before.
Yeah, well, I've been
wanting to get to know you better.
You quit the choir club, didn't you?
How do you know about that?
Sorry. I saw it.
Really?!
That's so embarassing!
What are you doing?
I overwrote the shame,
so none of it would be left.
Now, we're even.
What are you talking about?
I want to start a new choir club.
Our school is coordinating the joint
recital this year, so I think if
I talk to the principal directly,
I might have a chance.
I was wondering if you'd be interested in–
No.
Huh?
Absolutely not. I stopped singing.
Huh? Is this because of your
supplementary classes?
We don't have to have
rehearsals every day,
so I'm sure you'd be fine.
I know it's a crazy challenge,
but I think if we sing together,
it could lead to something incredible!
Please?
It would be so much fun!
Starting to sing now?
I'd never enjoy it.
Why not?
If you pretend it's fun, it might
actually become fun after a while!
If you just want to sing for fun,
why don't you go to
karaoke or something?
Don't involve me in your games!
It's not a game.
Then what is it?
What do you sing for?
Well, that's...
Whatever! Just because you're having fun,
it doesn't mean you're not serious!
That doesn't answer my question.
I'm dead serious about this!
Maybe so, but don't get me involved.
I don't want to regret
giving up before I even tried!
By the way, I heard that
you're crazy about sweets.
That's right! Especially homemade ones.
Honestly, Dora.
Makoto, you're not in any clubs, right?
Don't just barge in here, you hag!
I'm making a choir club.
You'll join, right?
What?
I left the application form on your desk,
so just fill it out and
bring it back to me.
Stay out of my room!
If you don't bring me
back that application,
I'm going to tell mom about
your secret porn stash.
Huh?
Dear Yang:
I've started at my new school.
I tried to prepare as
much as possible, by reading books,
but Japanese customs
are quite complicated,
and it's not easy to avoid mistakes.
I'm going to try hard to make Japan
feel like my home again.
I hope I can show you Japan, someday.
When that time comes...
Two more people, huh?
Starting a club is fine,
but are you really sure you
want to perform at the recital?
It's going to be hard
to find members now.
You know that, right?
Is this because you made Sakai-san mad?
Or is it what the vice
principal said to you?
Ah, both.
I guess you really did screw
up at last year's recital.
It's not funny!
That's why I've been doing
all this different training.
I'm not that person anymore.
Can I have some cream, please?
Listen to me!
I hear you, loud and clear.
You're going to go practice
today too, right?
Of course.
This one's on you.
Why?
Because you laughed.
Tasty Croquettes
Fly, fly, fly!
What you really need, is a sparkle in your eyes.
Using my body, I'll run
as far as I want, my way.
The soul forever believes
in something we can't see.
Isn't that all right?
Even yesterday...
Sakai.
Whatcha doing here?
Oh, Tanaka-kun?
I'm back.
Even then, I just want to laugh it off.
People will be people.
Huh?
Was she singing?
Today a holiday or something?
Why?!
Were you just singing?
So this is sukiyaki?
Two cakes, please.
This is our last chance!
Episode 2
Gathering and Struggling
Sakai-san, I'm going to find
the answer you wanted last time.