I am not about to be stranded
by something such as rain!
We are leaving, Sophia Ring!
What's your plan?
My dark barrier renders
all attacks ineffective!
No. Don't think about him.
Don't think about him. Don't think about him.
This is emotional turmoil.
The angel must be nearby.
It's okay. I still have my power.
It hasn't disappeared.
I have to do something before it does.
It's you, Shichimiya.
I thought Rikka had come home.
She's been staying out late every night.
I know it's summer vacation, but still.
I see.
Shichimiya, your sticker is coming off.
What?
Darn you, angel! It will take more
than these cheap illusions...
...to faze this magical girl!
What the...?
You haven't been getting enough sleep.
Where were you out so late yesterday?
EPISODE X GAUNTLET OF RAIN [OR]
A MIDSUMMER NIGHT'S... RAIN AND WHIPS
As I have told you many times,
to speak it means death.
Knock that off or you're grounded.
Due to the proximity of the Priestess...
...you may have been mentally contaminated.
You are even starting to look like her.
Shut up!
Wicked Lord Shingan!
Ha!
Miss, no diving please!
Is that Togashi?
Who are you?
It's me, me!
Oh, Takanashi.
Who are you?!
Can you defeat me within the water,
Wicked Lord Shingan?
Take that!
P-please, not there!
Stop making weird sounds!
Cento, we're not allowed to jump
into pools in Japan!
Agreed!
And Toka is the same as always.
Yuta, look.
Forget. You must forget.
Make it all disappear, in the Devil's name!
Shichimiya?
In the profane name of the Angel Lucifer,
rid me of my memory!
Shichimiya.
It's still not working!
I can hear his voice!
One more time!
Shichimiya?
Hero!
I didn't know you were here.
That is an excellent meditation spot.
Huh? Oh.
That's right! As a magical devil girl,
I meditate daily!
Shichimiya, your shoulder!
Get with it!
The attacks are getting
more vicious every day!
That was freaky.
What got into you?!
I don't know, but I am a
veritable feast of rage.
What are you blithering about?!
Okay, Rikka and I will be at the library
doing our homework.
Right.
Yuta, increased body temperature confirmed.
I hereby request supplementary
cooling components.
Ice cream?
If possible, soft.
Hey.
Yes?
Where's Scarf gone?
You mean Shichimiya?
I think she went home already.
What about her?
No, never mind then.
So, only Rikka can see it.
What is this?
There's nobody here!
It doesn't happen till nightfall.
Would you like to take turns napping?
I brought pillows.
I'm leaving.
You can't. The neighborhood
association director said...
...that if we stay here until night time,
they'll pay us for our time.
Then they should put us to work!
I can't stand wasting time like this
without any sense of accomplishment!
It sucks to be you, Morisummer.
Don't call me that!
It could definitely use more momentum.
Now see here.
Schwing!
Must you always insist upon
interfering with my plans?!
I didn't ask you to follow me here!
I am compelled to send you beyond
the reaches of the parallel world.
I was feeling bored anyway.
It couldn't hurt to play
along once in a while.
I am buying all of these water yo-yo's!
Thank you, come again!
I take this to mean you
will do battle with me?
Do battle nothing.
I am going to crush you without mercy!
Nice try!
Ugh!
Ow!
This is your fault!
You're to blame for this!
What did you want to talk about?
Yes, I have a favor to ask.
I, Dekomori, am my master's servant!
I will happily obey her sister!
Why are you sucking up to her?!
I wanted to do something
about it myself if I had the time...
...but I have to head back to Italy soon.
What?
MUNICIPAL LIBRARY
You have no intention of doing your homework.
But we did just get out of the pool.
INCOMING TEXT - TOKA
Toka?
SUB: GOING BACK TO ITALY
Find the answer for yourselves.
Contact me if there's trouble.
That is all.
Yes, that's right. I'm on
my way back to Italy now.
Don't worry. I've checked in on Rikka.
I see. Thanks.
The next time you come back...
...we should sit down for a meal together,
just the three of us.
Yeah.
Disappear! My netherworld
barrier is active...
...so none of your attacks
will affect me, Angel!
I think this is an extremely formidable foe.
YOU'VE GOT MAIL
WICKED LORD SHINGAN
UNSEAL
I am completely restored!
HP/MP are topped up!
You're pumped up with magical energy!
The barrier on this room is impeccable.
As I would expect from a magical devil girl.
Tonight I will once again attempt
to locate the parallel world.
What did you want to talk to me about?
Regarding the whereabouts of
the key to the Dark Flame Dragon.
You're still looking for the last one then?
Naturally, for I am bound by contract
to the Dark Flame Master.
It is Wicked Lord Shingan's mission.
Only I can locate it.
But...
You just can't find it?
Magical Girl TWIRLY CURLY KURI
Someone is interfering. Perhaps
it is the Mage Association's doing...
...out of fear the evolution
of Dark Flame Master.
The night of the blue moon
could be upon us at any time.
This is tricky. Why don't you ask Hero?
Maybe he remembers something.
That I cannot do.
That will not hold
as proof of our contract.
Really?
Yes.
Yuta, that hurts.
I said you'd be punished the next time
you left without saying anything!
Where were you?
That I cannot say.
Yuta, this is a time of
repose for Dark Beings.
The attack of the Light Beings
is taking its toll on my barrier...
...and I am so sleepy.
No sleeping!
Honestly. You and your sordid hobbies.
What other choice do I have?
And I never asked you to tag along.
There's Shichimiya now!
She looks out of it.
She sighed!
She looked at Togashi's apartment!
It looks like Toka was right.
She's in love...
...with Togashi?
Exactly!
Tell us if it isn't so.
Well?
What are you talking about?
I am a magical devil girl!
I am charged with my
eternal battle against the angel.
I am not like your average human being.
She averted her eyes!
I want you imagine the following:
What?
You are alone in a classroom with Togashi.
You are alone in a movie
theatre with Togashi.
You are alone on a desert
island with Togashi.
Activating Devil Barrier!
This renders any psychological
attack ineffective!
She even reacts identically to Takanashi.
Because she's in love.
So you're in love with Togashi, huh?
Are you in fact a marauder
who showed up on this land...
to wrest Ghelzonianses away from my master?!
Are you a homewrecker?
N-no! I'm not! Please believe me!
But you've always had
a thing for him, haven't you?
I admit, there once was a period of time...
...when I experienced emotional
instability towards Hero.
But that was then that I made
my decision to live my life as a
magical devil girl for eternity!
I'm saying that everything is resolved.
In accordance to the logic of the world
and its natural laws.
What's that?
That makes sense!
Deko seems to get it.
Don't worry. I have defeated
the enemy within once before.
I will stamp it out thoroughly this time.
Yuta, over here.
There is a shortcut through this park.
It's Master!
Hide, you idiot!
Is that the festival of the living dead?!
Don't talk about it like that!
It's the Bon Festival dance!
The ceremonial dance performed
by a myriad of people...
to summon the dark follower
converts to this world.
I said, don't talk about it like that!
Now come on. Let's go!
Yuta, wait!
I'm glad they didn't see us.
That's because I put up a barrier.
I am tops when it comes to barriers!
Shichimiya.
What are you gonna do?
Nothing changes for me.
I am and always will be the devilish girl
who rules the magical seven holy lands.
That's all.
I doubt it.
I doubt it's that easy.
I am at war with myself...
so naturally I've factored in
the personal damage!
Kuzuha, are you done yet?
Yes, almost.
That ought to do it. There, done!
You look so cute, Rikka!
What do you think? Not too tight?
It is difficult to access my weapon.
Weapon?
The Schwartz Z/X Perfect
Customized Ghelzonianses!
You can't take that with you.
No. I must keep this on
my person at all times.
To Wicked Lord Shingan, it is essential.
Oh, I see. That's because
my big brother gave it to you!
You two are so lovey dovey.
Ow, ow! That hurts, Rikka!
What should I do?
Huh?
My power is now gone and
I've lost everything.
What am I?
Wha-?
What?!
I split my magic with you.
You got a job, Kuzuha?
Yeah. The neighborhood association director
urged me to come...
saying they'd pay me for my time.
You'll be busy.
Where is Satone?
I think Rikka invited her to come...
...but she was too busy to make it.
Yuta!
What is it?
The deathly ghost planet!
You mean Venus?
It's red! Fire attributes?
Then it can't be Venus.
Why am I hiding?
Get a grip! Fight, Sophia!
I am a magical devil girl!
COTTON CANDY
Step right up!
WATER BALLOONS (1 TRY 100 YEN)
Yo-Yo fishing is so much fun!
Morisummer is such a hard worker.
She is just plain noisy.
Good work.
You're at it.
Master! Your dark plumage
does justice to your dark being!
Where's Kuzuha?
She's been captured by
the neighborhood association.
She has it hard.
Then why did she bother coming
to the festival in a yukata?
I think she finds it fun in her own way.
What is that?
I am magical devil girl,
Sophia Ring SP Saturn VII!
I am the magical devil girl Sophia
the whole town is talking about.
AKA the devilish girl who rules
the magical seven holy lands.
And don't you forget it!
Shichimiya.
So you did come after all.
Well, my schedule opened up.
Hey, where's Rikka?
She sensed a dark presence
a moment ago and went that way.
What? For crying out loud.
I told her to stay put so she
wouldn't mess up her yukata.
What's the big idea?
I came to make war with the enemy within.
Make war, you say?
Yeah. The enemy is inside me,
so I can't escape it.
That's why I've decided to fight it.
But how?
I have a plan!
Stand by for my report of victory!
Will she be okay?
Rain?
Surely it can't have gotten this far.
Yeesh. Where the heck is she?
Hero!
Shichimiya. Have you seen Rikka?
No, but I suspect she has
spotted a dark follower.
Yikes, it's really coming down now.
Are you dry enough over there?
I'm fine. I have put up a barrier.
A barrier, huh?
Be careful to give the deities
behind you their space.
Well now, let's start the hostilities.
Huh?
Say, Hero?
You have entered into a
lover's contract with Wicked
Lord Shingan, haven't you?
S-sure, sorta.
Have you done it? I mean...
...have you kissed and stuff?
Why are you asking that?!
Answer me.
Why should I?!
Because this is a battle.
You won't get angry no matter what?
Why would I get angry?
For some reason, Nibutani gets angry
when I'm honest with her.
That's because Morisummer
is mentally unstable.
I practice self-discipline, so I'll be fine.
You're sure?
Yeah.
Not yet.
I see.
But I should mention that we've held hands.
We've even touched noses thanks to you.
What's wrong?
Never mind me. This is my battle.
Please continue.
What battle?
Just tell me.
Do you love Wicked Lord Shingan?
Would you just drop it already?
Just tell me!
Yes, I love her.
What do you love about her?
There's more to it than that.
I guess I love everything about her.
Hey, you'll get wet.
That attack was harsh.
Its power is impressive.
That one registered as critical.
What are you talking about?
Pay me no mind. I'm fighting a good fight.
For me it's just embarrassing!
There's no way around
it, because this is war.
This is a matter of life or death.
Please continue.
You still wanna do this?
Yes. I should be able to
move in for the kill soon.
Honestly.
You know, Rikka was
watching me the entire time.
She watched me and kept on believing...
even after I had stopped
believing in my own power.
I have mostly given up on it,
but she keeps encouraging me.
She said I was incredible.
She said I had unique power.
I see.
Are you satisfied?
Why are both you and Nibutani
so keen to hear stuff like that?
INCOMING TEXT - RIKKA TAKANASHI
Rikka?
The water mage's attack has intensified.
Rescue requested.
Trust her not to have her umbrella
when she needs it.
Go to her.
But...
I told you. I'm fine
because I have my barrier!
You're hopeless.
Huh?
You don't accept goodbyes, right?
Uh, yeah.
I successfully held back the tears!
I am victorious!
It was a formidable foe,
but it will take more than that
to shake up the rock-steady
Sophia the magical devil girl!
Here.
I found something you can use
abandoned over there.
That's not fair.
Huh?
Only a coward resorts to surprise attacks.
Shichimiya?
You can't do things like this.
You just can't!
TO BE CONTINUED