Let's follow him.
Zelada?
He's gonna use that bomb. And right now, too.
Stay close to me, Kei.
I'm the only one who can
spot the enemy's ambush.
If you're my partner, trust me.
Got it.
Leahyah!
Wait! It's a trap!
But I have to go!
You're right but... Damn it!
I don't know what the hell
to do with this thing.
Then smash it!
It may blow up if I mess with it.
How do I disarm this?
Is it even a bomb?
What a reckless effort!
I can assure you,
for your own safety, it's best to run.
Damn you!
When I see a guy with a grin like yours,
nothing makes my day
more than messing up his plans.
Oh, my... You know you're helpless.
Shut up!
See? You're helpless.
It's an illusion!
Above!
Kei!
Too bad, Sir Matoba!
You've lost once more.
Now, on to the next one...
This is so much fun!
Where is he? Damn it.
I can't see him.
No, don't rely on your eyes.
Sound. Focus on the sound.
The sound...
Over there?
What?
Oh! The pain...!
Well done.
It's been 103 years since
I've been wounded like this.
Stop talking and prepare to die, monster!
No, I'm afraid it would bring shame
upon the Marzaney Sect
if I were to die at the hands of a mere barshe.
And thus...
Farewell!
Kei!
I defeated Zelada.
But I don't have any elixirs to heal you.
I'm sorry.
R-Run...
There's no time.
I'm going to spend the last
moments of my life with her.
You should be grateful.
I've decided to die next to an uncouth,
boorish, and sarcastic man like you.
I'd rather... you didn't...
"My dear Leahyah..."
Like I promised, I've come to save you.
When I was a child, lost in the forest,
you saved me and showed me the way home.
Remember what we promised then?
That we'd always be friends.
That's why I came.
I came, like I said I would.
I didn't let you die alone.
So Leahyah, don't be scared.
Let's stay together.
Leahyah? No! Don't do it!
Stop! Leahyah!
Leahyah!
"Peaceful color..."
"Powerless color."
"I beg you to give them more time."
"Rarest of colors."
I'm alive?
What is this?
I used a healing spell.
I needed an elixir to heal
the damage the poison did.
An elixir with powerful latena.
An elixir?
I used her body to make it.
That fairy died?
Yes.
The catalyst for the psychic
bomb was a living fairy.
She knew that, it seems.
And she sacrificed her life to save me.
Kei Matoba, thank you for everything.
Um, well... You too.
I may be returning home in shame
instead of dying with honor,
but I learned that there are
some good warriors on Earth.
Oh, you forgot something.
That's...
I got it back from O'Neill.
It's expensive, right?
Too expensive to give to a tour guide.
But...
Just take it.
Bye.
Farewell, gallant doreany soldier!
Kuroi, I'm home.
Amazing! Two three pointers in a row!
What is this?
A sports show.
No idea what the rules are.
No, you! You!
What are you doing here?
Oh, that?
I changed my mind.
We're not sure that Zelada's really dead.
And this city is filled with villains.
I figured there's more I can do.
What?
You're being treated as a detective?
And working in my department?
Yup.
So I'll be staying here for a while.
Any questions, partner?
Part... ner?
Tomorrow's gonna be an early morning.
Time for bed.
Got it.
Goodnight, Kei.
"Night, Tilarna."
This is the police! Open up!
Shit! It's the cops!
Who tipped them off?!
Go! Go! Go!
Make the slightest move and you're dead.
Got it.
Matoba! Exedilica! Get over here!
Now!
Chief Zimmer, is there a problem--
Matoba, they tell me you chopped off
one of the gang member's arms.
It wasn't me! It was her--
Quiet! I don't care who it was.
You two are a pair.
If that alien there rapes a 100-year-old man...
...it'd be the same as if you did it!
I'd be calling you a pervert
for the rest of your life!
--That's not--
--Don't worry.
I'm a fair boss.
So if your shit spills out of the toilet bowl,
I'll make the alien there
clean it up with her tongue!
We clear?
Yes, sir.
So, why did you chop off the guy's arm?
His lawyer's gonna be overjoyed.
It wasn't an arm. It was a finger.
And Inspector Zimmer...
Don't call me an alien.
That's racist!
Oh, is it?
I'll keep that in mind.
You know Gardner down at
the prosecutor's office, right?
I'll talk to him, but I need a report
on my desk by 9:00 AM tomorrow!
Don't even be a minute late!
Uh... roger.
That goes for you too, alien!
Ask Matoba how to write it!
He's pretty brutal.
So that's Roth's successor, huh?
Why is he yelling at me?
I was carrying out justice!
You went too far.
It's because you let your guard down!
It's your fault!
I didn't ask for your help.
I don't know how you can even say that.
Would it kill you to say, "thank you"?
--In the name of the great god Kizenya...
--Kei!
Over here!
We're being called.
You can pray next week.
He's such a jerk!
That hurt! What was that for?
Shut up!
Stop it! You're embarrassing me!
Rakebye!
Why are you flirting with her?
I am not.
Did something happen?
We don't know.
This garage belongs to the guys we just cuffed.
A coffin?
It's a little too strange for that.
Does it belong to a Semanian?
I don't know.
I've seen these letters in an old book.
Moon... Forbidden... Blood.
That's all I can read.
What's inside?
What if it's some valuable work of art?
We need to be careful with it.
Who gives a shit? Smash it open.
Is that...
...a mummy?
It looks like a princess or something to me.
I can't be sure, but it looks
like a Semanian woman.
Of course it is.
It's a mummy in Semanian clothes,
found in a Semanian coffin.
They have a different number of teeth.
Humans have 32 teeth.
But Semanians have 28.
I'll give her an autopsy if you want, I guess,
but we deal in fresh corpses, not mummies.
You'd be better off giving her to
an archaeologist, don't you think?
We can send her to a lab when you're done.
Time of death. Age. Cause of death.
I want to know all of that tonight.
Kei, I've been on the clock since this morning.
What a coincidence! Me too.
You're such a jerk.
I agree.
Right?
I'm amazed you decided
to stay here and work with him.
I think it was temporary insanity.
I deeply regret it now.
I know, right?
He's cold and mean.
But once in a while, he's nice
and it catches you off guard!
Make sure you don't let him fool you.
I don't really understand,
but I'll remember that.
Hey.
You wouldn't believe what
happened the first day we met.
He brings me the body of
some gang member he just killed,
and then do you know what he says?
"Don't steal the change out of his pockets"!
I know what you mean!
I saved his life today, and he said
he didn't ask for my help!
Next time something happens,
I'm just going to let him die.
Smart.
When he dies, why don't we dissect him together?
We can slit open his stomach and take a selfie!
I love it, Bozah Epps!
Make sure you invite me.
Call me Cecil, Miss Exedilica.
Cecil, you can call me Tilarna, too!
You're sure getting friendly fast.
Dr. Epps, the results of the lab test are in.
There's nothing wrong with
being friendly with our clients,
but don't forget to do your job.
Okay. I'll be right there.
What's his problem?
He's your apprentice, right?
My assistant.
He doesn't like me.
It might be the other way around.
He may have a crush on you.
Oh, are you worried?
Quiet.
I'll wait to hear from you, then.
I'm a little worried.
Bodies like that aren't something
to be touched lightly.
If you're worried about bacteria, don't be.
Cecil's a pro.
No. The spirits of the deceased
are drawn to corpses.
It's best not to touch them.
That's not an option. She's evidence.
And she might belong to some noble somewhere.
Anyway...
Are you close to Cecil?
I explained this before, didn't I?
That "ex" word, was it?
It wasn't in the dictionary.
Don't worry about it. We're still friends.
Wait.
Still? What does that mean?
Forget it.
I ain't talking to no cop.
Bring me my damn lawyer.
Villain! Start talking!
Do you know what happens
to criminals who defile corpses?
Their limbs are cut off
while they're still alive
before they're stuffed into a barrel
filled with poison insects
and left there overnight,
and then thrown into the Obiza swamp!
If you don't want that to happen to you,
start talking about that coffin!
I thought you'd do that...
A body of unknown origin,
kept in a Semanian coffin.
The teeth and cervical vertebrae
suggest that she is a Semanian female.
Simultaneous signs of desiccation and aging.
It's a strange form of mummification
that you don't see on Earth.
This is an archaeological examination
that does not require autopsy.
Chapman!
Yes?
Can you take a CT scan of the body?
Sure thing.
Right now.
Please don't hurt me...
We stole the coffin.
We heard it was worth a lot, so...
Where did you steal it? Tell me!
Doras Derill. A graveyard in Doras Derill...
What?
A corpse from Doras Derill?
What's up?
Cecil may be in danger!
What?
Hurry!
Hey!
Shit.
Did something happen?
Chapman?
What's going on?
"Shield of law, protection of the war god."
Cecil!
Tilarna?
Tilarna... The body...
Chapman...
Cecil, run!
B-But...
Hurry!
"Vampire."
The old language...
Did I get her?
"Next time"
Next time on COP CRAFT.