Okay!
That should be all of the large boxes!
Let's go say "goodbye" to the landlord.
Yeah!
Team Chihaya Furu
The next time we meet will
be at the nationals!
Yeah.
Watch me become a Class A player!
You won't beat me next time!
Yeah.
I'm going to become a Master.
I'll be the Queen!
Guess this is it.
Promise!
We'll meet again when we
become Class A players!
Yeah.
Chihaya Furu
A Whirlwind
of Flower
Petals
Descends
Verse 4
Chihaya, this is our stop!
Were you daydreaming or something?
Hey, have you been in touch with Arata?
No.
I see.
Arata must be incredibly strong now, right?
Do you think we'll see him at this
year's Omi Jingu tournament?
What do you mean?
You want to play against Arata
in the national tournament?
Uh-huh.
What class are you right now, anyway?
I made Class B in the
tournament during spring break.
At this rate, it'll take you another
three years to make Class A.
Why don't you just stick with track?
Instead of hanging around in
Class B for three more years...
What was that for?!
You're just as violent
as you used to be.
Ta-kun!
You're late!
I came all the way here
to show you my uniform!
Sorry.
She calls him Ta-kun?
Ta-kun?
Wanna go somewhere?
Taichi!
If I win the tournament on
Sunday and make Class A,
you have to help me
start a karuta club!
Wh-What are you talking about?
Do you have any idea how hard it
is to make Class A in Tokyo?
Promise!
Hey, wait!
Umm, who is she, Ta-kun?
Hey!
I'll make him pay for getting
himself a girlfriend!
I need to tell somebody!  Anybody!
She was calling Taichi "Ta-kun"!
Wataya Arata - Home in Fukui
Bunkyo City
Otsuka Karuta Memorial Hall
And here I am.
I couldn't forget.
Eye!  Eye!  Eye!
Eyebrows!
Dr. Harada, I can't believe
you actually recognized me.
You've grown so big!
Are your armpits and
pubes all bushy now?
But not as bushy as your eyebrows?
Excuse me.
Could you be quiet while
they're memorizing the cards.
Oh, my bad.
You already started.
I see.  You're here to
cheer for Chihaya-chan.
Yeah, I guess.
Looks pretty tense in there.
They have to win if they want
to advance to the next class.
Yes, it's especially hard
on the Class B players.
There are many strong players
who spend years in Class B
because they can't rack up enough wins.
Everyone's trying as hard as they
can to reach the next level.
If I win the tournament
and make Class A,
you have to help me
start a karuta club!
It's gonna take you a
while to make Class A.
Eyebrows, I heard that you're in the
same high school as Chihaya-chan?
Yes.
There isn't a karuta club, is there?
You should come practice
with the Shiranami Society.
No...
Well, I'm thinking about
joining the soccer team.
Please be quiet
during matches
Eyebrows!
You don't want to turn into
a two-timing bastard
or you'll never become a Master!
Stop it.
That's not my goal.
Doctor...
I played karuta in middle school.
It was just a small club, though.
I practiced and became
better little by little,
but I always knew, deep down,
that I could spend my
entire youth on karuta
without ever becoming
better than Arata.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
They're starting.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
So spring ends...
Yes!
Why is she yelling?
Did you teach her to do that?
Not under normal circumstances,
but I gave her a few tips since
she wanted to win so badly.
If someone challenges her,
she's supposed to complain
loud enough that everyone in the room can hear.
The hazy early morning light comes not from the moon
The point is to overwhelm her opponent.
Is she really so obsessed with winning?
When Chihaya-chan entered middle school...
Why track?
There a reason for choosing that.
You know how you're supposed to start
running when you hear the starter pistol fire?
It reminds me of karuta.
Huh?
It'll also help me get in shape.
Everything is for karuta.
"Spend your entire youth
without becoming stronger"?
Eyebrows,
hold that thought for now.
The night was young...
Yes!
She's made it past the third round!
Thank you very much.
I apologize for raising my
voice during the match.
What?
An okay sign?
That's the chocolate sign.
Chocolate sign?
Eyebrows, run down to
the convenience store
and buy some chocolate!
Huh?  What?
Hurry!  Go!
Temporarily Closed
Sorry!!
I don't believe this.
"Convenience" my foot!
Are there any other shops around here?
Go-Godi—
Temporarily Closed
Sorry!!
Welcome!
Hey!
Savor them, will you?!
Don't eat three of them at once!
These are good, Taichi.
So many different flavors!
Karuta tournaments are
long and grueling.
You have to memorize the
positions of fifty cards,
then forget them.
Memorize, then forget.
The longest tournaments require
you to play seven matches,
from morning till night,
before there can be a winner.
Your brain will burn through
the sugar in your body,
and you can lose up to three kilograms.
So players eat chocolate
to recharge themselves.
Right, Chihaya-chan?
Anyway, you've gotten a lot better.
I was actually surprised.
Huh?
She's already asleep?!
What's scary is that Chihaya-chan
sleeps with her eyes open,
Open
but that's what I like about her.
You're so kind, Taichi.
I-I'm just making sure that nobody
has to see your ugly mug.
You're so kind...
Taichi.
Hmm?
Sorry about forcing you into
making a karuta club with me.
But watch.
I'm going to win, so watch me.
Eyebrows, we're allowed to
watch the final match inside.
I'll pass.
I can't do anything if I'm inside.
Then I'll join you outside.
I'm already sick of looking at
her opponent, Yasuda-kun's face.
However, he will be a formidable foe.
He has the ability, but he's been
stuck in Class B for three years.
He's fired up this time.
I dare say that his card
positioning is perfect.
Yasuda-san's gonna win this.
I don't see him losing to some
random high school girl.
Just look at the way he's
spreading out the cards
that start with the same syllables.
How many cards will he beat her by?
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Team Chihayafuru
Please be there for me.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Okay.
Let's do this.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
In order to restore...
The emotions experienced
after a long-awaited reunion
Im—
the red that is the Tatsuta River
—passioned vows exchanged
over many a tear shed to last
until the day waves crash
over Mount Suenomatsu
As soon as he heard "Im,"
he went for the
"Impassionate gods" card
on the opposite side.
Once he heard it was "Impassioned vows",
he switched to the correct
card on his own side.
Yasuda-kun is known for
his precise aggression.
He's putting pressure on Chihaya-chan,
since she usually starts slow.
Chihaya.
I know you well, Ayase Chihaya-chan.
"Impassionate" is your best card.
Once I've taken away
your favorite card,
it will be easy to break
your 15-year-old spirit.
until the day waves crash
over Mount Suenomatsu
But I don't want to look her in the eyes.
Since I could not hide...
Yes!  She took a card from
the opponent's side!
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Doctor, she gave him
the "Chihaya" card.
It makes perfect sense, Eyebrows.
Huh?
I teach aggressive karuta.
The objective is to take cards
from the opponent's side.
But isn't it risky to give
a strong opponent her best card?
That's the one card Chihaya-chan
will always win.
I'm going to win,
so watch over me,
Taichi,
Arata!
All alone...
That was fast!
Wow.
Would the mountain...
the red that is the Tatsuta River
He passed it back!
As the first frost...
the red that is the Tatsuta River
My fear is that you...
They keep passing around
the "Chihaya" card.
Yasuda-kun is being really stubborn.
I guess he doesn't want to let
Chihaya-chan have an advantage.
The sight of the lonely...
Such intensity!
That girl is holding her
own against Yasuda-san!
While autumn leaves...
I feel that my...
He took another card!
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Chihaya...
Huh?
He's good.
And that's not all...
He truly loves karuta!
Since the dew atop...
For you, I would have given...
A mountain village...
It looks fun.
It looks like you're
having fun, Chihaya.
Is it because you're
the one who's playing?
Was it fun because we were the
ones you were playing with?
the red that is the Tatsuta River
are joined at river's end
Impassionate gods...
the red that is the Tatsuta River
She beat him!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Let's play!
Let's play karuta, Taichi!
We can improve together!
If we have each other,
we can become strong!
Okay.  Stay right here, Taichi.
Huh?
It's okay for me to
call Arata now, right?
Huh?
I have to tell him that I made Class A.
Arata...
Arata, guess what?
I...
Listen up, Arata.
Hello, this is Wataya.
Arata?!
It's me, Chihaya!
Ayase Chihaya!
Taichi's also here!
I made Class A today!
I worked so hard!
There are so many things...
Taichi and I are at
the same high school!
He got himself a girlfriend
who calls him Ta-kun!
Can you believe it?
Oh, Dr. Harada's doing great!
...I have to tell you, Arata.
Hey, Arata...
How strong are you now?
Could you stop?
Sorry, but don't call me again.
I stopped playing karuta.
Huh?
What did Arata say?
Hey, Chihaya?
the red that is the Tatsuta River
My dream is to become
a karuta Master.
I-I won't let anyone take
a single card off me.
I wouldn't show mercy if I
were playing a 5-year-old.
Thank you for playing karuta with me!
Chihaya, Taichi...
I stopped playing karuta.
I always thought that the three
of us would be reunited.
I thought that we would never change.