Kiss!
Wha...
Wh-What are you saying?!
What am I saying?
Oh!
N-No, that's not it!
I'm saying that you
should kiss Manaka-san!
Wha?! Either way, why would I do that?!
Because it's needed for her to wake up!
That makes no sense!
And why would that need a k-kiss?!
I already told you!
That's not a reason!
Hii-kun!
You're not supposed to
get that mad at girls!
Shut up!
It's because she—
Who are you?
Huh?
Hii-kun.
M-Mom...
Mom!
Episode Twenty-One:
The Messenger from the Bottom of the Sea
I'll be going now.
Are you going out, Miuna?
Oh, she already left.
What the heck?
She's not gonna come with us?
She left in a pretty big hurry.
Huh.
Hii.
Hii-kun, wait!
Don't leave me behind.
Why would I leave you behind?
See ya.
I go...
We'll be off, now.
We're going out for a little bit.
I go...
Hikari, don't push Manaka-chan too much.
I won't.
Don't drag her around everywhere.
You always go running ahead.
I won't.
If she starts not to feel well—
That's enough, already.
Manaka-chan, you can make Hikari
do anything you need him to, okay?
Okay.
Namaka, I go...
It's been a while,
so you can take your time today.
Akira, you're staying home with mommy.
Namaka...
Namaka... I go...
We'll be back soon.
Namaka! Namaka!
Namaka!
He seems to like you a lot.
Like?
Let's go.
Yeah.
Saya Mart
Seriously?
Looks like you're back together...
Huh?
The Four from Shishio.
Good for you guys.
The four of you together are one unit.
So anyway, a present for you.
Always Smiling
Saya Mart
Eat up.
See ya!
Tell Mukaido I said, "Hi."
Oh.
There are five in here.
We'll have one left over.
Chii-chan!
Kaname!
Manaka...
Chii-chan, it's cold today, isn't it?
We haven't seen each other in forever and that's what you have to say?
Huh?
But it's cold, isn't it?
It's supposed to be summer.
Well, yeah, it's cold, but...
This feels so weird.
I know, right?
No, I mean,
usually people would be more surprised.
Considering how grown up
some people have gotten.
Huh?
But isn't Chii-chan just Chii-chan?
Tsumugu's not coming?
He's doing field work right now.
So he's on top of the ice?
Want to go see him?
He's busy, isn't he?
We can do it another time.
More importantly, let's
go to the harbor.
S-Sure.
Hurry! Hurry!
Oh...
Sorry, Sayu.
My body got all crackly.
So cold!
It's fine.
So when your Ena gets
dried up, it gets crackly?
I don't know if it's crackly,
or hard to breathe...
This is the first time it's happened.
Sounds like a real pain.
Didn't Hikari and the others
tell you about that?
They did, but...
You should have just gone
with Hikari and the others.
He invited you, didn't he?
I can't.
Why?
I don't have the right to.
Right?
The right to do what?
The... right to go.
Course you do.
You're the one that was
doing all that research.
What?
You're not happy about Manaka-san?
I am!
She finally...
I thought, "She finally woke up..."
And I was happy that I was
actually happy about it.
But something was different...
It was different from what I imagined.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I don't know.
I don't know how I'm
supposed to talk to her.
You look totally surprised.
Jeez...
What the heck?
Cold!
Hey! I don't have any Ena!
Wow...
It really is frozen.
You saw that from the house...
Huh?
But if you see it up close,
it's really surprising.
Right, Chii-chan?
For you, the Ofunehiki was
just the other day, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Whoa!
What?
There's so much salt-flake snow!
There wasn't this much before!
Yeah, you're right.
It's like playing spot the
difference or something.
Spot the difference?
Yeah.
So cold...
Closing my eyes and then opening them,
I keep finding things that
are different from before.
Salt-flake snow.
Salt-flake snow!
And even more salt-flake snow!
What the hell?
You just keep pointing
out the salt-flake snow.
Manaka!
What are you doing?
Hii-kun.
Hii-kun's being nice...
Wha... I've always been nice!
Hii-kun, your face is red.
Shut up!
Save me, Chii-chan!
Hey, there's salt-flake
snow over there, too!
Manaka, it's dangerous if you run.
What were we even trying so hard for?
Huh?
I mean, Manaka woke up even without
the help of Uroko-sama's powers.
It all worked out in the end.
Yeah, but it was sort of anticlimactic.
Considering Manaka's like that.
Manaka!
She's so full of energy...
Chii-chan, look!
And she just woke up yesterday.
How were you, Hikari?
When you first woke up.
I was scared.
The town looked familiar,
but everything was just slightly off.
I didn't know what I was going to
do if everything looked the same,
but I didn't know anyone.
I was really scared.
I don't want to see any more
things that've changed!
I don't want to think about all of this!
I don't want to know!
There!
I wonder how she can laugh so much.
I think it's because
you're here, Hikari.
Huh?
And we are, too.
And I thought she'd want
to go see him first.
She says she doesn't remember.
Wake up Manaka
You...
Right before the Ofunehiki...
No. What happened after the Ofunehiki?
You were pulled down to the
bottom of the sea... after that.
Um...
I think... I heard someone's voice...
A voice?
Whose voice was it?
Was it Uroko-sama's?
It wasn't Uroko-sama's voice...
Was it the Sea God?
It could have been...
Did you see him?
Did you meet him?
I don't remember.
I think they said they'd
give me something
or they asked me to
give them something...
Give them what?
I don't know...
Wait! Manaka, wait!
The school's...
...covered in salt-flake snow, too!
So fluffy!
She doesn't have Ena anymore...
She can't go back to the sea... so why?
Hikari...
But it's true.
So why is she...
That's Manaka for you.
Yeah...
You're right.
This part is my side!
Hey! Then I'll do it, too.
Nope! You can't have that part anymore!
This, this, this, and this are all mine!
No! You can't have all of it!
What are you doing?
Huh?
Huh? You...
What the heck?
Coming to school on Sunday
doesn't make any sense.
Look who's talking. What
are you doing here?
What?
S-Studying!
Wha?
I thought I'd study for some tests.
Didn't you know? Finals are next week.
You're talking about
tests all the sudden?
Well, studying is important!
Very important.
What were you guys studying?
In math, we're learning simultaneous equations,
and in English, we're learning
conjunctions and verbal nouns.
Wow, I suck at both.
Man, talk about a downer.
Other than arithmetic,
you don't really use math anyway.
Yeah, that'd be the idiot's excuse.
Wha?!
Yeah, definitely an excuse.
What?
I think studying is important, too.
You're gonna say that?
What?
It is important, isn't it, Chii-chan?
It probably would be
better to study properly.
See?
It'll be too late to regret it later.
Too late.
Oh, I have to start heading to the hospital.
The hospital?
Tsumugu's grandfather
is in the hospital.
What?
He's pretty old now,
and a lot's happened...
Oh, yeah.
Eat these. Sayama-kun gave them to us.
Salt Cream Puffs
Full of Minerals and made with salt from Oshiooshi
Wow...
There's just enough.
Chisaki-san's so nice!
Yeah.
Who wants one?
I do! You want one, too, right?
I do.
I do!
Totally!
I didn't think you were here yet.
Oh... well, I had a little time.
What about you?
Yeah. I finished up early.
Then you should have gone to see Manaka.
I thought if she saw too much,
she'd probably get tired.
What's that supposed to mean?
How was Mukaido?
She's good.
She was so full of energy it surprised me.
She said she'll come visit soon.
I see...
Want a tangerine?
Sure.
There's coffee jelly, too.
You were awake?
Gramps remembered my favorite foods.
It's so good.
I might like it more than cream puffs.
Why cream puffs?
Just because.
Around the end of the month...
I think I'm going back
to the university.
The university's telling the professor
to hurry and put together our findings.
I see.
When's that?
I just said the end of the month.
What's wrong?
I screwed up.
When you eat something sweet
first, it becomes sour.
I'll send tangerines to your apartment.
Eat them with all the
people in your lab.
Yeah.
It's not that far.
I'll come back as soon as I can.
Yeah.
And I'll call.
If I find something out, I'll
contact you immediately.
What, Tsumugu? Are you lonely?
No, you are.
Wh-What are you talking about?
I'm busy too, you know.
You okay?
I mean, everyone's back now
and I'll have to watch over Manaka.
I can't leave her alone.
Manaka really hasn't....
So you don't need to worry
about trivial things.
Do your research at the university!
You and Professor Mihashi are
the only ones able to do this.
There's still so much we don't know.
Even though Manaka woke up and
Hikari and Kaname seem fine,
there's so much we
don't even understand.
Like what's going to happen in
the sea or on the surface...
the world's future, the
weather, and the tide.
If only we could just ask Uroko-sama.
Uroko-sama? Why?
Because he seems to know
everything about the sea.
You think so?
I have a feeling he'd just
say something random.
But he is the scale of the Sea God.
Tentatively.
So it's tentative.
I don't know if he'd say
anything even if I saw him.
He's always so contrary,
not to mention he's perverted.
Maybe we can bribe him.
"Bribe"? You mean money?
No... like porn mags.
What are you...
Actually, that might work.
That might work really well, actually.
I knew it.
Sorry I'm late.
Welcome back.
Perfect timing.
Huh? Why?
Well, I won't push you
guys if you can't, but...
Dada, where's Dada?
All right, I'll spend the night.
Hey, watch out.
Dada's going to be late at work tonight.
Hey, you can't put the
fish in all the sudden.
What? It's fine.
The flavor comes out that way.
What'd Tsumugu have to say?
Both of them can't make it.
What?
That's too bad.
Why?
Crab!
Hey, no touching the
crab. It'll be an owie.
Something with Tsumugu's grandfather.
They apologized.
Chii-chan must be busy.
Tsumugu, too.
Both of them are actually studying.
What do you mean by "actually"?
You're making it sound like I—
You're not studying at all.
It'll be time for entrance
exams in no time.
Dang, I think I'll go hibernate again.
Don't be stupid.
Sayu-chan, help Hikari with
his studying, will you?
You're the smartest in class, right?
Oh... sometimes...
It's not sometimes, it's all the time.
That's amazing.
Not really...
Everyone's applying for
Hama High School, right?
Well, Shishio doesn't
have a high school.
But I'm fine with how things are now.
Here's some crab.
Make sure you blow on
it before eating it.
Akira!
Is it still hot here?
Nope.
Are you okay? It doesn't hurt?
Nope. It's cold.
Sorry for the commotion.
Could it be that the Sea God is angry?
Manaka!
Come here a sec.
Huh? Huh?
Just come here.
Hii-kun?
Hii-kun? Hii-kun, what's wrong?
Are you mad?
The thing you said you'd tell
me after the Ofunehiki...
The Ofunehiki...
After it's done, I'll tell you.
I'll hear it now.
What did you want to say?
Don't make that scary face.
Is it about Tsumugu?
Huh?
Isn't it about Tsumugu?
What are you talking about?
Hii-kun?
Good morning.
Huh? Oh...
You're here early, Tsumugu-kun.
Is Mukaido here?
Good morning.
Everyone's up early.
Huh?
Tsumugu, what's wrong?
Fishy!
Tsumugu-kun, that's...
I was cursed by Uroko-sama.
"Cursed"?
He a person that curses people.
He's not actually a person, but...
Which means...
Uroko's somewhere close by.
You pushed a lady and you're
just going to leave her?!
I told you not to come!
It's no good...
I think I'll try asking her out again.
Episode Twenty-Two:
Something Lost
Asking out, huh...