All of the various economic
powers are hastily preparing
to launch their forces.
So I see...
These AHSMB units will
be our primary fighters!
Make sure they're in tip-top shape!
Yes, Boss!
Got it!
Our fleets against
theirs? Sounds exciting!
Accurate instructions are a must to
keep our allies from
falling into disarray.
You're always so uptight!
You'll never get anywhere like that...
with the enemy or women.
If you have time for idle chatter,
work on memorizing the
enemy's formations!
Yeah, yeah.
I have no idea what to
expect from the Wulgaru.
After all, they consider this "hunting".
We need be prepared for an attack
if they strike while we're on the move.
Come what may, our
primary goal is to reach
the gate in one piece.
Right.
But how will we power the
gate-destroying Straggle Laser?
Weren't the flagships
from the economic powers
supposed to supply the power?
That's the plan,
but the charge time upon reaching
the gate takes too long.
If the enemy opened fire, they'd
have no choice but to sit it out.
You're making Izuru participate
in this operation?
As his primary physician,
I can't permit this.
I understand,
but the fate of Earth rests on
the success of this operation.
I am aware of the position
you're in, but I am a doctor!
It is my job to protect my patients.
You still haven't been discharged
from the hospital, have you?
"Night before the Decisive Battle"
I have to participate in this operation!
Stay and get your rest!
Wow! Just now, didn't you
sound kinda big brother-ish?
Izuru!
No, no! You're supposed to take it easy.
You should stop him, Asagi!
I'm trying to!
Yep! Big Brother hasn't
done anything wrong.
I've already told you,
stop calling me that!
Huh? What's the big deal?
We merely inherited DNA
from the same human.
And it feels weird for him to
suddenly start calling me that...
But it doesn't change the fact that
you're Izuru's brother, does it?
I should have kept this to myself...
I'm kinda jealous! You've got a brother!
In that case, Suruga, you're
free to call me "Big Bro".
No freaking way!
But isn't everyone here
sorta like family?
That's how I think of you guys.
Tamaki...
Asagi is my big brother,
Izuru is my little brother,
and I guess Kei is like my mom!
Who are you calling a mom?!
What 'bout me? Well? Well?
Commander Simon!
Izuru Hitachi, I need
to have a word with you.
Well, we'd better be going.
Izuru Hitachi, submit your
resignation papers immediately.
Is that clear?
A moment, sir!
That was an order!
I am going to fight!
Not happening.
Why not?!
In your current condition, you
could jeopardize the operation.
I'll do my best to see that I don't!
Waiting for everyone alone
at a safe distance...
That would be far harder on me!
I've fought along their
sides this whole time!
Please, sir!
Even if... piloting an AHSMB
again could prove fatal?
We were born for the
sole purpose to fight.
That's what we were raised to do;
why our memories were erased.
But... But despite all
of that, I made friends
and had some fun times.
So I want to be with everyone!
If they are out there fighting,
then I want to fight, too!
I will grant you permission
to board the Godinion.
Thank you, sir!
I will fight with all of my might,
so that Izuru doesn't have
to enter the frontlines.
I will protect him!
Izuru is my friend... as
well as my little brother!
Uh, I'm still the only one who
knows about our DNA donors.
I see.
COMPOSURE
Welcome back!
Everything okay?
Yeah.
What about Izuru?
He'll be able to board the Godinion.
Is he all right?
Ange, have you finished
your medical exams?
They said I should be able to fight.
I see.
But how about Izuru...?
Let's do our best to
make sure he doesn't
have to enter the fray!
Yeah!
I'll do my very bestest!
Right!
I feel as though they have
taught me that new lives grow
and develop on their own.
In that case, it is our job to do
all we can to protect those lives.
I will personally participate
in this operation.
But-
I have made my mind.
We won't be using Red 5.
What?!
We can't reliably count
on him in battle.
So please devise a plan
that doesn't require him.
Very well.
Losing Red 5 hurts, but I'll
come up with something.
In exchange, Imperial Princess
Teoria will be accompanying us.
Have you reached a decision?
I have.
I see. Thank you.
As of right now, you are
the Supreme Commander presiding
over this operation.
In exchange, I have a
favor to ask of you.
There is something I'd like to use.
With our next strike, we will
bring this shikaara to an end.
We shall overtake Earth in one bout and
seize the genes that
Klein failed to obtain!
The final shikaara...
I can hardly wait.
Fight with all of your might...
...for our great ancestors
and descendants!
I am bewildered by these lamata
whom we refer to as "Earthlings".
Sir?
There are times when they prioritize
the life of another over their own.
That is not the correct action
for any living creature to take.
Thinking back on the prior
species we've hunted,
the individual beings always
prioritized their own lives.
However...
No, we must hunt them down.
We have continued the shikaara in
pursuit of increasingly advanced genes,
believing that such measures will
help us survive in this universe...
Is that not so, Lumes?
Yes, sir. That was what
the oracle proclaimed.
Prince Jiart, the final
shikaara is about to begin.
Was this my brother's decision?
It was.
Have you heard word from Teoria?
Nothing as of yet.
Either she has already passed away...
...or she has no desire to return to us.
Once this is over, we should be
able to find Princess Teoria.
True enough.
Cheers to the shikaara!
I repeat: All civilians
residing on Star Rose,
please evacuate to Earth
with all due haste.
I repeat: All civilians
residing on Star Rose,
Why does everyone suddenly
have to leave Star Rose?
Probably 'cause it's dangerous up here.
Does that mean the enemy could
make it this close to Earth?
That's a possibility.
Oh, guys! So this is where you went!
They're about to hold a general
briefing for the upcoming operation!
Once that's over, you're
supposed to board the Godinion.
Great Chinese Alliance
Organization of the
Bela-Russian Conference
United Provinces of Africa
GDF General Headquarters
Now then, I am going to brief
you on Operation: Heaven's Gate.
The primary goal of this operation
is to destroy the enemy's gate.
At a pre-determined time, all fleets
will begin heading toward the gate.
We will instruct you on how to handle
any battles along the way as we see fit.
Upon reaching the gate, you are
to swiftly enter formation
and prepare for the enemy to strike.
I will explain the fleets' strategies
at a different point in time.
The MJP's Team Rabbits will
fight in the frontlines.
All armies are to offer
their full support.
All AHSMBs will be equipped
with the markers needed
for when we fire the
Straggle Laser at the gate.
Blue 1, Rose 3 and Black 6 will upset
the enemy formation while
moving toward the gate.
Gold 4 will offer support.
Purple 2 will issue
orders from the rear.
The AHSMB units will take whatever
formation is necessary to
launch the markers, while all fleets
will offer their full support.
As soon as they've launched the
markers, we will fire the Straggle Laser.
That is all.
Did you understand the
outline of the operation?
Yes, ma'am!
We plow in and ka-boom!
Exactly.
Excuse me!
What about me?
You'll remain on standby
with us on the bridge.
Standby?!
We aren't dispatching you.
I feel fine!
Red 5!
Really, I wish I could leave
you and your unit behind.
But there isn't room for
mistakes in this operation.
As such, there is a possibility that
I may end up ordering you to sortie.
However, that is a last resort.
Understood?
I can't believe I'm stuck on standby...
I'm relieved.
Now I don't have to worry about
your health while I'm fighting.
You didn't have to put it like that!
That was cruel, Asagi.
Huh?
But Asagi's absolutely right!
We'll do our best out there,
Izuru, so cheer us on!
Please leave this to us.
Not you too, Ange!
I'm sorry...
In that case...
Everyone, fight!
You literally cheered for us, sheesh...
Huh? Isn't that your pit crew, Asagi?
Huh?
Asagi!
What's the matter?
Anna has gone missing!
She's gone missing?
We can't bring her with us
on this upcoming operation.
And since all civilians have been
ordered to evacuate Star Rose,
we tried to send her down to Earth.
After she threw a tantrum
saying she wouldn't go,
she ran off somewhere.
Anna!
Anna dear!
The Shopping Arcade that Floats
in Space: Star Rose Galaxy
She isn't here, is she?
This place is a total ghost town, huh?
It seems rather forlorn, doesn't it?
We can't find her after all of this.
I bet she must have
taken the last pod down.
I'll check the list of passengers, so
please make your way to the Godinion!
Asagi, do you have any idea
where she might have gone?
Star Rose Galaxy Rest Area
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
I wanted one last ice cream cone.
Come on. We're going.
No!
Anna!
I wanna stay with Papa and Grandpa!
Even if I went down to
Earth, I'd be all alone.
You still can't come.
We can't take you with us.
Your dad and grandpa don't
want to put you in harm's way.
I know how they feel.
This is what it means to be family.
I don't want to see
him get hurt, either.
My family, I mean.
I wonder why...
It's so strange!
We merely share the same DNA,
so why do I feel this way...?
Asagi, you have a family of your own?
Yeah, I do.
When I heard that he wouldn't
be participating in operation,
I felt relieved... big time.
So let's go.
Uh-huh.
Big Brother, fight!
Fight!
Lady Teoria, I will protect you.
Please protect Izuru and
the others instead of me.
Why do we allow genetics to have
such a strong hold over us?
It feels as though we
are slaves to our genes.
Lady Teoria...
But I cannot help but wonder,
"Why was I drawn to Earth?"
I believe that while humans
are slaves to their genes,
they are also capable of
surpassing their genetics.
Genetics are what connects families,
clans and nations and
allows them to survive,
but occasionally people are able
to protect others due to
"love" and "friendship".
That is true.
Sometimes the humans defy their
genetics and follow their hearts.
It was worth abandoning the
Wulgaru simply to learn that.
I appreciate everything
you've done, Daneel.
Ninety-five percent of Star
Rose has been evacuated.
Is that right? Thank you.
Why did we need to clear out Star Rose?
The Supreme Commander issued that order.
The Supreme Commander?
Not the GDF's Commander-in-Chief?
Right. He is finally making his move.
They said that this is the
last pod going down to Earth.
I'm glad we made it in time!
Yeah. Anna's dad and
grandpa were able to
put their minds at ease
and return to the Pit.
Now we can finally head
on out to the Godinion!
Yep! Please hurry on over!
Asagi!
Hey, kid!
What were you thinking?!
I'm going with you after all!
What are you talking about?
How am I supposed to
explain this to your dad?
I'm going anyway!
Hey!
I don't... want to wait...
alone on Earth worrying about everyone!
You win.
But let's beat those Wulgaru!
Yeah!
I'm sorry...
C'mon! We're down to the last lap!
Let's give it all we've got!
Miss, we have her running
perfectly for you.
Thank you.
Um... I made this for you!
Let's eat it together...
What is that?
It's a cake...
Is it edible?
It might be a bit sweet.
All right. We'll give it a try.
Too sweet!
This is awful!
I'll teach you how to bake a
cake once this mission is over.
I'll kick their butts,
so lend me a hand!
You're welcome to call us "Bro"!
Huh?!
We heard that you're
lookin' for a big brother.
Nah, I'm cool...
Let's hear it!
Say it nice and loud!
No, I'll pass! I don't
need any brothers!
I need to watch what I say
when I'm piloting you...
Otherwise all of Earth
will hear my potty mouth.
You locked it?
Sorry 'bout that!
I heard those were Captain
Suzukaze's orders.
That way you won't take off
without permission, Izuru.
But maintenance-wise, it's good to go.
Everyone, all of the fleets
will be launching soon!
Izuru, please go to the bridge.
Huh?
You are on standby.
Izuru...
You weren't born for the
sole purpose to fight.
The way Rin-Rin locked Red 5 shows
that she feels the same way I do.
The designated time for
launch will be in 12 hours.
Kei?
Is something the matter?
If it's about Izuru, he'll be fine.
I'll make sure he doesn't get sent out.
Asagi...
I'll do my best to make sure
he doesn't have to fight.
You can count us in on that, too!
All of us will do our best out there!
I will do the very best I possibly can.
Ange...
I'm counting on you, Ange.
Right!
Guys, we've got to strive
to become heroes!
And amazing enough to make
Izuru green with envy!
Asagi,
don't push yourself too hard.
Right.
Make sure to take some antacids.
Actually, I don't need antacids anymore!
You still have the residual
airs of a failure...
True enough!
Seriously!
Shut up!
Informing all fleets:
I am hereby transferring
all authority of command
over the current operation
to the following individual,
Simon Gato of the MJP.
I am Simon Gato.
I will be issuing all
commands from the Star Rose.
The Star Rose?!
Operation: Heaven's Gate, activate!
Cables, purge!
The Star Rose will carry
all of the fleets' ships!
Captain Amane, it's from
Supreme Commander Simon.
Upon retrieval of the fleets'
vessels, I will take off.
Sir, how are you navigating
the Star Rose?
The Star Rose's core is a
refined version of the Wulgaru
ship that Teoria used to fly here.
We will use the Star Rose as the
energy source for the Straggle Laser.
Have the troops advance!
Star Rose, blast off!
"Operation: Heaven's Gate"