We have an update on the Neo Hundred,
who are believed to be
behind the destruction of
Kasumigaseki earlier this morning.
Following the destruction of
the Ministry of Defense,
they seem to have taken
no further action.
Meanwhile, reports continue nationwide
of unexplained incidents
such as merchandise vanishing
in front of eye witnesses,
and women being molested
on trains and streets.
It remains unclear whether these events
are also related to the Neo Hundred.
Next, we...
What a waste!
This is a revolution.
What're you all doing?
There are still government
buildings left standing.
Who are you?
Are you Future GALAX-san?
No one's really listening to you, though.
Everyone has things they'd rather do.
Damn it...
I wanna do... Oh, abduct a celebrity!
Nice.
But don't you get tired when
you use the CROWDS ability?
I agree.
Yeah, definitely.
I want one that doesn't
make me tired next time.
Yeah, seriously.
Yeah.
Totally agree.
If the Neo Hundred can't do it,
the world's seriously not gonna change.
The Neo Hundred's a lame-ass.
I'll go help with land-mine removal.
Maybe they really don't
care what they do...
Liar, you hypocrite!
I wish there'd be an even
more awesome festival...
"An even more awesome festival"...
There must be something...
Something more.
X, what do you think?
Katze-san!
Katze-san, where are you?
Oh, Hajime-tan!
Right here!
What?
Where?
Oh, I saw your Gatchannel.
I like how you're honest, Hajime-tan!
Thanks.
Oh, are you the one controlling
the Neo Hundred?
What, what?
I don't know anything about that.
Oh, okay.
Sorry to ask.
But from what I heard,
the CROWDS are people,
so you can't attack them.
I hear they'll just go into a coma.
Oh, we've got that covered.
Oh?
Sounds fun.
I wonder what you'll do next.
Yeah, I want you to look forward to it.
The lord of the pinnacle of folly
shall descend upon the promised land.
What? A poem?
What's it mean?
We'll continue this online.
Walky walk!
I couldn't see Katze-san again.
I wonder why.
Woot!
Hajime-tan is looking
everywhere for me.
So cute!
I wanna kiss her!
Rui.
What is it?
It is a beautiful sunset.
So it is!
It looks just like the scarlet blood that'll be
gushing through this planet!
It does not look that way to me.
It is very unfortunate...
Oh, it's already out of juice.
Charge it up for me.
Yes, sir.
I'm so unlucky.
The CROWDS, the Neo Hundred...
Update the world, my ass.
Found fuel!
What can they do?
Sugayama Escaping to Tachikawa!!
Even though they now have power,
they only use it for useless things.
Declaration of War to Neo Hundred!!
They're just a pack
of losers in denial!
Oh, where are we headed?
The Tachikawa Wide-Area Disaster
Management Base, sir.
Okay, Tachikawa's finished!
My dear Neo Hundred,
the final boss of this nation
has appeared, at last.
Let us assemble
in Tachikawa for the final battle.
To the one who succeeds
in capturing Prime Minister Sugayama,
I will present the ultra-rare
CROWDS version 2.0,
which will not tire its user out,
no matter how long it is used.
Really?
I totally want that.
Just wait, Sugayama.
But why Tachikawa?
Because the National Diet Building,
the Prime Minister's office,
and the Ministry of Defense were all destroyed.
The Prime Minister is evacuating
to the Tachikawa Wide-Area
Disaster Management Base.
What's going on?
What's wrong, Papa?
The number you dialed
is no longer in use.
Damn it.
Mana, we're going home.
Hajime-tan!
Oh, Katze-san?
What's wrong?
Hey, Hajime-tan.
I think Tachikawa's gonna be in crisis.
Looks like the destruction of Earth
is gonna start in Tachikawa.
I thought that might be your move.
You ready?
You still look like you're having fun.
I am!
I'm bursting with excitement!
Wait! Where are you, Katze-san?
Katze-san?
Wake up, Newbie!
Tachikawa's in serious trouble!
Uh, oh.
Here they come.
They're after Prime Minister Sugayama!
Katze told them where he is.
I see.
Is everyone ready?
We have urgent news.
The Neo Hundred has just
released a declaration.
We declare to Prime Minister Sugayama
that we, the Neo Hundred,
will assemble in Tachikawa
in order to take you into custody.
You've got to be kidding me.
What? What's happening?
The CROWDS are right there.
Mayor.
Prime Minister!
Prime Minister, please issue orders ASAP.
Orders?
How can I issue orders
to attack something invisible?
It'll be fine!
Hajime-chan.
"Hajime-chan"?
Nobu-san.
I am the one running GALAX, Ninomiya Rui.
So you're Rui-kun.
I'll make it possible to see the CROWDS.
Hajime-chan.
Okay!
Amnesia Remind!
That's the CROWDS?
Yep.
Everyone's hearts are going berserk!
"Hearts"?
What is your command, Prime Minister?
The CROWDS are controlled by humans, right?
People will go into a coma if we attack, right?
It'll be fine!
We'll catch them alive without hurting them!
Delivering a certain amount of shock
to the CROWDS will freeze them.
This should minimize harm to its human users.
Reveal your names!
If you will not, then listen!
Who are they?
Could they be...
We are...
the wings that protect this planet!
We're the Gatchaman!
Rending Gale Blade!
Awesome, Senpai!
I guess I should get going, too!
Go, Bird!
Petits Ciseaux!
Gatchaman really exist?
The CROWDS!
O-Over here, too!
What should we do, Commander?
Go, Bird!
Gatcha here!
We can win.
CROWDS are approaching in massive
numbers from the south!
We must do something.
Evacuating the citizens from the city
at this stage carries too great a risk.
First, let's evacuate them
to areas within the city first.
Then use GALAX to issue evacuation orders.
Wait.
GALAX is still under Katze's control.
The internet is too dangerous.
Please refrain from using it, for the time being.
Tell people to stop using the internet
through the Disaster Prevention
and Community Safety divisions.
Roger!
I'm so sorry!
I swear I will take Director X back from Katze.
When you do, Rui-kun, we'll follow your lead.
Why would they listen to that brat?
We'll be running point defense!
Assign all Tachikawa citizens
to strategically defensible
locations and evacuate them!
Whoa!
Use the local schools,
Huh?
the Tama River area, and Hanamidori Park!
What?
Police and riot police,
evacuate the citizens ASAP!
Hey...
Roger!
Firefighting squads, assist them!
Hey.
Roger.
The disaster prevention division
will go with them, too!
All right!
Coordinate your efforts to deal
with anything that may happen!
Roger!
Hey.
Self-Defense Force, deploy a chopper
and scout the CROWDS' location!
Help defend the citizens!
Roger!
Hey, wait!
The Self-Defense Force?
Who gave permission?
Did you go through
the proper channels?
Now's not the time for that!
What? Who do you think you are?!
A situation is already underway.
Now's not the time to be worrying
about regulations and protocol!
Open your eyes and think about
the appropriate course of action
for what's happening here!
How dare you speak to me like that?
It was you GALAXters acting up
that led to this in the first place.
Do you get that?
Don't put us on the same
level as an online hack job!
No Self-Defense Force!
That's an order from the Prime Minister!
Please, let us go, Prime Minister!
The Self-Defense Force has
a duty to protect the people.
We can't just stand by and
watch as a tragedy unfolds!
Prime Minister, Tachikawa is capable
of functioning as a second capital.
All of us here have undertaken
our responsibilities
with great pride, until now.
Please believe in us.
We will protect the citizens, without fail!
I approve the deployment.
However, I am accountable, as well.
I do not condone an attack of any sort!
Harm no one.
Understood.
Listen up.
We've been approved to carry weapons.
Squad one, provide recon from the air.
However, the CROWDS
aren't an approved target.
Harm no one.
Evacuate 180,000 citizens in under two hours!
Yes, sir!
Out with Sugayama!
Let us handle it!
You're hitting too hard, Senpai!
This isn't a war!
As if you can even win...
Don't bother.
Let us evacuate while we can!
The Left Arm of Life.
Only stunning blows.
He's okay now.
Thanks, Utsutsu.
What?
Gatcha!
Pai-san?
Huh? What?
Leave it to me!
Who are you?
Thanks, Pai-san!
You're Pai-san?
Come, Earthling!
Sayuri?
Sayuri?!
Kou-chan! Mana!
Mama!
I'm so glad you're both okay.
What's happening?
Don't worry.
I'll protect you.
Why?
Why Tachikawa?
We demand that the Japanese
government surrender
and hand over Sugayama immediately!
The CROWDS will be ordered
to withdraw once that occurs.
Do it, now!
They don't understand anything.
Killing me won't change this nation.
I finally understand, now that
I've become the Prime Minister.
No one's thinking about the nation.
They just want to gang up on the leaders
and make them into a laughingstock.
You get it, don't you, Pai-san?
In times like these,
I've always asked myself,
"Do you love this planet?"
What about you?
Do you love this country?
I'm not sure.
To be honest...
You're the top dog
in this country, aren't you?
Y-You guys don't know anything.
I wanted to change the world, too.
But everyone's all about self-preservation.
No one listens to me.
Even if I slave away by myself,
nothing'll happen!
I want a revolution, too.
I want to say everything I've got to say
and remake this country from square one.
But...
In the end, you're scared.
You're too scared
that you'll lose everything.
But at some point, you have
to be prepared for that.
The same goes for us.
Come on, hurry!
Run!
Hurry!
Help me!
Help!
Hey, don't ignore our instructions!
X, what should I do?
Follow evacuation orders!
Wait a minute...
Senpai!
They just keep coming!
We can't do this alone.
Help us,
Jou-san...
Hey, give us a hand here, too!
This is how it should be...
I am no one special...
There are millions of guys
who are better than me.
There's no way I can win...
Please stay calm!
Don't panic!
I'm just...
Keep calm!
Please watch where you're going!
Just keep calm!
Please hurry!
This way, please!
Please follow instructions!
Jou-san, I owe you a lot.
Do you remember what happened?
Help!
Don't cry.
You're a man, aren't you?
I still remember what you said.
Make sure you save
someone, too, someday.
Thank you, Jou-san...
I'm not scared of anything anymore.
We're not caged birds.
We are the great wings
protecting this planet!
Go, Jou!
Alan...
Make your dream come true!
Hup!
Gatcha!
Lame.
I'm so lame.
Way too...
lame!
Thanks, Sugane.
I'm dying from the heat...
Jou-san?
You'd better be waiting for me!
Go, Bird!
No way!
Go, Gatchaman!
I'll light a flame...
...in this dark world!
I still remember what you said.
Thank you, Jou-san...
I'm not scared of anything anymore.
We're not caged birds.
We are the great wings protecting this planet!
Thanks, Sugane.
Prime Minister Sugayama
has yet to make an appearance.
At this rate, Tachikawa City will be destroyed!
Please! Do something.
Isn't it an alien who's controlling them?
Then the Gatchaman should just...
You bastard...
Are you saying my subordinates should
be the only ones to sacrifice themselves?!
It's not like I know what to do, either.
But most things in life
are unexpected, aren't they?
You should think about what to do, too.
This isn't just a problem among us aliens.
It's a problem for you Earthlings, too.
If this city is destroyed,
next will be this nation.
If the nation is destroyed,
the world, the Earth will be next!
That's the kind of being Katze is!
Damn that bastard!
We have just received reports that
the CROWDS have appeared
in front of Fuji Kindergarten!
Come on! Bring it!
Call Gatchaman!
Don't mess with me!
I...
I am the leader...
of the Gatchaman,
protectors of this planet!
Sorry, Pai-Pai.
Please hang in there.
Berg-Katze is nothing to fear!
Bow down before my courageous wings!
Go, Bird!
Oh, Ume-chan!
Please stop the CROWDS.
How can you say that now?
You're the one who said
we should go ahead with it.
But not this city!
My wife and daughter are here.
That's not my problem.
It was just fate, right?
Are you the devil?
No, I am you.
What do you mean?
I don't know why,
but everything pisses me off!
The IRL name of Neo Hundred's leader is Umeda Kouichi. Lives in Tachikawa,
address 700-20 Aomidori-chou.
He's all teary-eyed that his own city's getting attacked. lol!
What?!
My real name and address?!
Umeda finished.
Tear off his mask!
This guy, right?
I didn't care who,
as long as it was an idiot who
wanted to blow up this planet.
Idiot!
Umeda-chan!
Help me...
Someone...
Someone, please help me!
Fuji Kindergarten
Bite and Build!
Transform!
You're so cool, Panda Man!
Run, kids!
Okay!
Dibs on panda
Panda lollll
The Right Hand of Death.
Burning Hammer!
Jou-san!
I made it so they're only done rare.
All right!
Let's all work together
to protect Tachikawa.
Three, two...
Gatcha!