Hmm...
Blanc et Noir.
S-So cute!
Newbie!
Rending Gale Blade!
Evade, newbie!
S-S-S-Snip!
Sni—
Petits Ciseaux!
Balles Pastels!
Storm!
Snip, snip, snip.
Snippity snip!
Huh? This is how you respond?
This is kind of different.
Maybe it's not what I thought.
Wh-What the...
You idiot!
Tachikawa Station North Exit
You've got to be kidding me!
Human lives are at stake!
Do you understand what
your intervention means?
I guess we go back the normal way?
C'mon, give up your seat.
Senpai, maybe everyone's tired.
Huh?
Someone might feel awful,
but can't skip work.
Someone might be sick, too.
We've leased this thirteenth floor.
Oh, okay.
Then Jou-san and OD-san are here, too?
OD-san and Utsutsu
are in Apartment #2.
Jou-san rarely comes home.
OD-san, Utsutsu-chan!
I safely completed
my first combat mission!
What do you mean "safely"?
Man, I'm exhausted.
Does this place have a bathtub?
When are you going to stop
following me around?
Oh, but this is my apartment!
Apartment #1!
Hey, newbie!
Your luggage is here.
Thanks!
Giraccho, you got here in one piece!
Honey Karintou
Oh, what's this place?
Hey, don't come in without permission.
Oh, I knew you actually liked them.
No, this is just a strategy
to throw people off!
The Kamoshida Cabinet continues
to be rocked by bribery allegations.
In response to recent allegations
by certain news weeklies that
I love guys who cook.
Pai-san, you don't cook?
not only Finance Minister Asada,
I'm your leader!
but also Justice Minister Niigaki
may have accepted payoffs,
So stop calling me Pai-san, too!
Prime Minister Kamoshida
appeared to defend his staff,
dismissing allegations
as mere media accusations.
Man, humans are so inferior.
Prime Minister Denies Bribery Allegations
He has, thus far, rejected any calls
for his resignation, as unnecessary.
No wonder they're still under
surveillance by the rest of the universe!
Opposition to Boycott Diet Deliberations
Thanks for the meal!
Thanks.
How is it, Leader?
Oh, good.
Thank you, as always.
Senpai, this is beautiful!
R-Really?
But...
I might want to fiddle
around a bit more.
Done!
Here you go!
Come on...
This is so messed up.
It can't possibly taste good.
Delicious!
Yay!
It's good...
Sudden Death of Popular Idol
Miss Kiritani Noa,
a member of the popular
idol group, Goo Goo Pamore,
has died after jumping
from her agency's rooftop.
Man... That's so sad.
Although no suicide
note has been found,
I struggle to understand why
anyone would take their own life.
sources close to the idol believe
it may have been triggered
by rumors of an affair
being circulated online...
But...
maybe she was having
a really tough time.
No, it's because
she didn't value her life.
You, too.
What? I'm not gonna die.
You don't value people's lives, either.
That's why you can't
finish off the enemy!
That's not true.
Hey, newbie.
Oh, I'm Hajime.
Why did you interfere?
I didn't interfere.
It was different!
What was different?
We just shouldn't go
"Wham!" like Senpai.
That's not what we're about.
Why, you—
Newbie, you should just follow
Sugane's orders, for now!
Boo!
D-I-Y.
Do-It-Y...
What's Y stand for again?
What are you doing?
Huh? What?
First, stop drilling!
Oh, oops.
Hey, are you listening to me?
Oh, that's not it.
I forgot to tell everyone
what time to meet tomorrow.
Tomorrow, at 5:00 PM...
What does she want to do?
At the Tachikawa-Kita monorail station.
Guys, meetup's tomorrow 5:00 PM
at the Tachikawa-Kita monorail station.
What's that?
Oh, it's GALAX.
You don't know about it, Senpai?
No.
I only use my cell phone for calls.
Seriously?
Are you a fossil, Senpai?
Who're you talking to?
Besides, you can use the
NOTE to make contact!
But that's only with other Gatchaman.
Do you have any friends, Senpai?
GALAX is fun.
That's me.
Aren't my clothes cute?
I designed them, myself.
Cute.
They've become sort of popular.
See, she's wearing them, too.
Hi, Rei-chan!
So it's just playing dress-up.
That's not true.
GALAX is amazing.
It celebrates birthdays, too.
It's just a game.
There are bars and gyms, too.
I got a huge workout last week.
It's a game.
You can catch pervs and stalkers, too.
It's not like we only
interact on GALAX.
During the disaster,
GALAX was a huge help.
Haven't you seen the news, Senpai?
Everyone's been working
really hard since then.
I went to help out just
the other day, too.
Did you?
The stars are awesome.
I see...
Decline                Answer
Mom
Incoming Call
Hello.
Yep, I'm fine.
I fought.
Huh?
I didn't get hurt.
I'm fine, okay? But my new home...
Tachikawa City Hall
Okay, I'll be leaving now, then.
Hey, hey.
Jou-san, is it true that
you're a Tokyo University graduate?
Maybe. I don't remember
things that far back.
Why are you working at City Hall?
You're so efficient.
Maybe for the downtime?
I heard Jou-san was asked
by the mayor if he'd like
to become his secretary.
That's a great opportunity!
I'm not interested.
Major terrorist attack.
Major Terrorist Attack
[Drill] Major Terrorist Attack in Chiyoda Ward
Please evacuate.
Major terrorist attack.
Oh, was the drill today?
It'd be so scary
if we actually had one.
This area may also be
in danger of a terrorist attack.
It's actually already happening...
Tama Monorail
Senpai!
Hurry!
Chartered Monorail Ride
18th
GALAX
Collage Community
Meetup
"GALAX Collage Community Meetup"...
"Collage"?
What's with this gathering?
Does everyone have
too much time on their hands?
Are they unemployed?
Senpai, you haven't done anything yet.
What would I know
about this collage business?
Anything goes. Just give it a try!
Here, use this maste.
"Maste"?
Masking tape.
Like this...
And ta-da!
Isn't your sword pretty?
C'mon, let's go join everyone.
I'm Kuwabara.
Senpai, he's Baracchi.
Hi.
This guy isn't just anyone.
Who is he?
Baracchi's a fire chief.
Huh?
That man is Nobu-san,
the mayor of Tachikawa City.
Th-The mayor?!
She's right.
Hey, look.
Sir?
These are pictures
of my daughter growing up.
Nice, right?
Right...
I apologize for not recognizing you.
I am her, I mean
Ichinose's, classmate—
Oh, your surname is
Ichinose, Hajime-chan?
Really?
You don't look like an Ichinose.
Hey!
You should've told me beforehand
that they were the fire
chief and the mayor!
But they're all just normal guys.
They're totally harmless.
Who is she,
really?
You have a great kouhai.
Sir?
This meetup began after
Hajime-chan posted on GALAX.
She said we should make
collages to send messages
to the disaster zones.
I see.
Over time, we just got into collage.
Now, my daughter and I show
each other our planners.
They say how young'uns
these days are no good,
Smile!                                                             Let's have fun again.
Together Forever
Cheer is important
Cheer is the best!
but you never know until you
actually get to know one.
Hey, it's not bad.
I'm not cut out for this, after all.
It's fine.
Everyone's is different.
I see...
Man, I hope the whole
world gets this way, too.
Huh? The world?
Kind of like this.
Lots of different things
coming together,
but everyone still smiling...
That'd be great.
Being a civil servant is great, no?
You can start drinking early.
I guess.
Hey, you should compete once.
You have a chance at winning.
No way, Alan.
There are tons of guys better than me.
You've changed, Jou.
Have your dreams changed, too?
Nah.
I see.
Still the same old:
world peace.
U-tsu-tsu-chan!
I'm dreamy.
You're on GALAX, too, D-san?
OD.
I heard, Hajime-chan.
You let a MESS go?
No, that's not it.
Senpai got super ticked off about it!
"Not it"?
How was it, then?
Well, like...
There's no point in cutting them down.
Oh, more importantly,
it's like, I haven't really met them!
Yeah, that's it!
"Met them," huh?
Besides, why are we
fighting them, anyway?
Whoa!
Are you trying to reject
the basic premise of Gatchaman?
You're way too fierce!
You're scary, newbie!
No, really—why?
"Why"?
Because that's our duty!
Oh, you were here, Senpai?
You don't understand anything.
Listen, Gatchaman are—
Aww, you're starting to sound like him!
Huh?
Like Pai-Pai!
Who are you calling "Pai-Pai"?!
Pai-Pai, are you on GALAX?
Don't be ridiculous!
Of course, I'm all over it!
Listen up, newbie!
Ha-ji-me.
I'm Hajime.
What's with you, too, OD?
Listen. Don't bother thinking about
why you fight or anything else.
Just carry out the mission!
There are casualties every day!
Protect them!
Whose planet is this?
"Yours, isn't it?!"
Right, you do get it! Good!
Huh?
You!
What the hell?!
Oh, isn't it cute?
The NOTE is the lifeblood of Gatchaman!
It is a sacred, physical manifestation
of each member's soul!
But see, Hajime-chan,
the NOTE becomes our Achilles' heel
when we transform.
If anyone destroys the NOTE,
then you might die, in the worst case.
Oh, I see.
Hey, I was just about to say that.
The physical materialization
of each of our souls...
I get it.
That's why our gear and
weapons are different.
That's right!
How dare you paste
senseless decorations on them?!
Okay, question:
Why is it the sword for you, Senpai?
That... I don't know.
I wonder why.
And why is it scissors for me?
But you're a sword kind of guy...
Like... Straight as an arrow, and stubborn.
Newbie!
Senpai!
Here I was... just listening
to you, and now this?!
Th-That's my line!
I was the one listening!
Like I said, I'm Hajime!
What? You are the newbie!
Man, that's all you say.
You know the kind
of person you are, Senpai?
You just look straight ahead like this,
and walk in a straight line.
But that means you'll miss
seeing a lot of things,
like Giraccho, maste,
and pretty and cute MESS-chan!
If you can't see all
those kinds of things,
as a Gatchaman...
as a person...
you're not at all... you know?
What's she talking about?
You!
Like I said, I'm not "you!"
I'm Hajime!
I'm here.
I've been right here
next to you, Senpai!
C-Cut it out already!
Wings of Six, gather at
the Spiritual Precipice.
"A bird with sundered
wings has wandered in."
"The bird is no longer sane."
What does this mean?
Hey!
What are you doing?
You have to be kidding me...
I'm dreamy...
Oh, hey, JJ.
There's something I've
wanted to ask you.
Wow! Amazing!
I think I saw something...
"Chaos will stand above
the head of a demon"—
"The head of a demon"
sounds pretty interesting.
Cut it out.
We're not here to play a game.
It really is above the head of a demon!
This time, you will not escape.
Let's go!
Amnesia...
Amnesia Effect!
Let's go, Senpai!
A-All right.
Go, Bird!
Relinquish the innocent to us!
Maste?
Sorry, Senpai!
Grands Ciseaux!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Wings de l'Avenir!
I'm not going to go snippity-snip!
MESS-chan!
Good morning!
Wait, no.
Good evening!
Yeah!
Nice to meet you!
She's not attacking it?
MESS-chan, I've wanted to meet you.
What have you done?
I think we've now met!
Hey, it's not safe.
Stop.
Maybe, but...
Maybe it isn't?
Huh?
C'mon, Senpai! Now's the time.
What?
I'm sure it'll tell us now
where the missing people went.
You...
So cute.
What?
Don't stare! Damn it!
Who are you?
Aww, no way.
C'mon.
Should I drop fuel?
Hey, don't stop.
Imma kill you! You're in the way!
Who you talking to, huh?
Outta the way, man.
Let me go!
Apologize!
Don't get ahead of yourself!
You started it!
Y-Yummyyyy!
Crap!
There's blood!
Get an ambulance!
You make the call.
I'll try this route.
Hey, we have someone injured
here who fell down the stairs.
It will be fine.
Let's stay calm and deal with this.
There are three GALAXTERs
in the vicinity with first aid experience.
Yes, stairs in front of the taxi stand
at Tachikawa Station's North Exit.
I'm a nurse!
I can help.
Where do you hurt?
I called the ambulance.
Maybe we don't need one?
GALAX is far more useful.
Maybe.
There's a nurse nearby.
Looks like it'll be okay.
Congratulations.
The world has been updated.
Maybe I'll go for another round.
It's not heroes who'll update the world.
It's us.
Home!
Welcome back, Rui.
Here is my report.
There were 228,434 new GALAX
app installations today.
There are now over two hundred
million registered users.
Sounds good.
87.5% of them are active users,
up 0.5% from yesterday.
But there's still a long way to go.
Man, I'm starving.