Tsuritama Episode 2
The day I moved to Enoshima,
I met the self-proclaimed alien, Haru.
I don't have any interest in fishing,
but he forced me into it with
his mysterious water gun.
The fishing prince, Natsuki,
was super harsh...
and for some reason,
I'm living with that alien.
Haru Yuki Keito
Thanks for the food!
The Frustrating Uni Knot
Haru, you shouldn't make so
much noise when you eat.
Okay.
I didn't realize aliens
also ate miso soup
We can. I like red miso.
I'll make that tomorrow.
There's whitebait in here.
Whitebait's everywhere on Enoshima.
Why is he eating like he belongs here?
I'm glad you're here, Haru.
Whitebait!
Grandma does some unbelievable
things sometimes.
Your cooking's delicious, Keito.
She won't listen to anything I say
when she gets like this.
Who is this guy?
And his water gun...
What is that thing?
Yuki, it's a scary cat!
You're way scarier than the cat.
Stop it.
Stop it!
Is that the duo I've heard about?
The alien and the demon-face?
They're real weird, aren't they?
Yeah. Maybe they'll
put on a show for us.
Please don't associate
me with this weirdo.
Yuki, no.
It happened again. Why am I dancing?
I just wanted to have a normal
school life this time,
but now everyone thinks I'm a weirdo!
Wait up, Yuki!
I can't take it any more!
Huh? Where am I?
Thank you for looking after my brother.
His little sister?
Yes.
I'm sure my brother
has already told you,
but there's a fish we've got to catch...
and we want your help.
Her accent's ridiculous!
But I can't fish.
You can do it!
That was just dumb luck.
I don't care what it was.
If you don't catch it soon,
we can't return to our planet.
Careful!
If you won't help us,
you'll be in big trouble.
Big trouble?
The Earth will be destroyed.
You're the only one who can save it.
You gotta be kidding me!
Why do I have to save Earth?
Fine! I'll do it! I'll fish!
That's the spirit.
Then go catch one for the day.
Fine, one! I got it!
It's a promise.
If you break it, the next time
we meet will be on top of the Sky Tree.
I wanna go to the Sky Tree!
I've had enough.
Misaki, we're here.
Good for you.
I definitely thought you'd quit.
I couldn't quit even if I wanted to.
We meet again.
Hey, teach us to fish, Prince.
Say that again, and I'll kill you.
You really should listen to him.
Please, Prince.
Can't this guy follow a conversation?
And why isn't he talking?
Between this and breaking out
into the Enoshima dance,
he's a creeper.
Just teach them, Natsuki.
Why don't you go for some sea bass?
Sea bass?
"A saltwater bass.
In the Japanese lure fishing community,
suzuki is known as sea bass."
Just call it suzuki!
I wanna catch sea bass.
Prince, teach us.
Sorry, but I'm busy.
Onii-chan.
Sakura.
Sakura-chan, welcome.
You're his little sister?
Yes. I don't usually see
my brother hanging out with his friends.
No, they...
Yes.
We're Natsuki's friends.
No, they're not. They're just...
He's a completely different
guy in front of his sister.
Sakura-chan, Natsuki's gonna
teach us how to fish.
You...
Really?
My brother's really good at fishing.
I'm sure you'll catch something.
Right?
Right, Onii-chan?
Uh, yeah.
He smiled?
Prince, what's this?
It's a life vest.
Even if you fall in, you'll
float if you're wearing that.
You wear it when you go sea fishing.
Oh, right. Humans can't swim.
What are you, then?
Let's catch some fish!
It's not that easy.
It's a mess.
Fishing starts with
assembling your tackle.
Tackle?
"Necessary equipment for fishing."
We're supposed to put
together all of this?
Sounds like a lot of work.
Fine. I just have to catch one, right?
Listen up, because I'll
only say it once.
First attach your reel to your
rod, and open the bail arm.
Pull out your line, and thread
it through the guides.
Wait. Your explanation's too fast.
This is hard!
Then, attach the lure to the
leader on the end of your line.
You can borrow one of my lures.
I choose this one. It's so cute.
What the heck is he doing?!
Tie this with a uni knot.
Uni knot?
It's a way to tie your line.
I'm only going to show you once.
Pass the line through the
hole in this metal snap.
Make a ring, and go around three times.
And pull.
That won't work.
See?
It is different.
Mine's sort of lumpy.
If you don't tie it right,
it'll come undone right away.
No. This'll break right away.
Damn it!
Something's wrong.
Natsuki, one more time.
I said I'd only show you once.
Hey!
Prince, do it.
Yuki, make sure you remember this time.
What is this?
Is this how he's been
controlling me, too?
This guy's seriously scary!
What am I gonna do if
I can't catch a fish?
Tada!
I'm surprised you're
such a fast learner.
What can I say?
He didn't get it at all.
And why's he so mad?
Hey, do you need me to explain it again?
What am I gonna do if
I can't catch a fish?
Hey.
Huh?
Do you want me to explain
it to you again?
Did he really get it?
It's no use.
I know, I know!
Oh, good enough!
Prince, I caught another.
Yuki, why can't you catch anything?
Heck if I know.
Besides, there's no way an
amateur could suddenly catch—
You're kidding!
Another hit. Is he even holding it?
Um, what am I supposed to do again?
I told you before!
Raise your rod and calmly reel him in!
What am I gonna do? What am I gonna do?!
Is that a sea bass? Yuki, it's huge.
It's that feeling again!
Calm down!
I have to catch it. I have to catch one!
Hey, don't panic!
I'll catch one!
It's jumping!
Sorry. I'll pay you back.
Don't worry about it.
Did you tie your uni knot right?
I'm asking if you tied your knot right.
No, I winged it.
Who do you think's going
to suffer if you do that?
Fishing's not something
you can just wing.
I refuse to fish with
someone who does that.
Oh, he's super pissed!
What should I say at a time like this?
I bet you didn't even listen
to anything I said!
Think about others a little more!
I'm teaching you because
you asked me to teach you!
Guys like you can't do anything.
What? If you have something
to say, say it!
Yuki!
What's wrong with him?
He'll never catch anything
fishing like that.
You're giving up?
I can't do it.
You're Haru's friend.
Friends don't break promises.
I'm not his friend.
That's no good.
Onii-chan, is it done yet?
Soon. Just wait.
I want to eat your curry now.
I'm home.
Dad, good work today.
Good work.
Mari-chan, good work.
Natsuki-kun, good work today.
Hey, Natsuki.
See you tomorrow.
Okay.
Natsuki, good work.
Did you have some of this?
It's a cheese roe whitebait ball.
It's my new recipe.
What do you think you're doing?
It hasn't even been two years.
It's been two years.
Natsuki, you...
You should cut your hair.
Stop it.
What're you getting embarrassed about?
You'll feel a lot better
with short hair.
I didn't ask for your opinion.
There's no need to get so angry.
Time for some beer.
Why won't you fish?! Why, why?!
Come on! Come on!
Yuki won't come out.
He'll come out eventually.
Yuki said he doesn't
want to be my friend.
Does being with Yuki make you happy?
Happy?
When your heart feels like this.
Yes. It jumps.
Then you shouldn't bother him.
Bother?
When Yuki wants to be alone,
you should leave him alone.
Why?
When he wants to be alone,
he's thinking about something.
About something important, I'm sure.
If I leave him alone,
will Yuki be my friend?
Yes. I'm sure he will.
Okay, I got it.
What's this?
It's nothing. Don't do
it in front of Yuki.
Okay.
Who do you think's going
to suffer if you do that?
Guys like you can't do anything.
What? If you have something
to say, say it!
What is this feeling?
You don't have to go that far!
Oh, right. I was frustrated, but...
I might have been winging it.
Yuki, where are you going?
Yuki!
Yuki, this is hard.
Shut up and do it.
Yuki.
You're pissing me off!
What am I doing?
Hey Nii-chan, why do you
like that Yuki kid?
I don't know, but I like him.
He's hopeless.
He's always making that weird face,
and he breaks his promises.
I don't think you should fish with him.
It's okay. I won't bother Yuki.
What?
If I do that, we'll be friends.
If we're friends,
I know we can catch it.
It won't be that easy.
All right.
This again. Why does
this keep happening?
No. This'll break right away.
What am I supposed to do, then?
Could it be?
Of course.
This'll reduce the friction
and keep it from breaking.
I did it.
I did it!
All right.
But I need to be able to tie it faster.
Yuki!
Haru.
What?
Stop doing this.
Why?
I just don't like it.
Does this bother you?
Yeah, it does.
Okay.
Nii-chan!
I'll do it.
I'll fish.
I'll catch something this time.
Yuki!
Something's not right, Tapioca.
See you later.
We'll see you later!
Whitebait curry? They'll serve anything.
Not everything.
Not everything?!
Good morning, Prince.
Prince?
Is he talking about Usami-kun?
Bastard.
What?
It's a uni knot!
Is that all?
But I did it.
He talked.
I won't...
I won't wing it any more.
There's no reason you
can't do at least that.
Hey.
Teach me to fish.
I want you to teach me to fish.
Good morning.
Hello. I am Akira Agarkar Yamada.
I am transferring into this class today.
I may be 25 years old,
but don't let that stop
us from being friends.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
The duck's so cute.
Is Enoshima all right?
The four of us came together
for the first time that day.
The story began that day.
This little island's...
great big story.
Continued in #3