Miss Kobayashi, your coffee's ready.
Oh, thank you.
Kanna, if you don't eat quick,
you'll be late.
Yeah.
Here's your hot milk, Kanna.
Oh, Miss Kobayashi!
Hmm?
What would you like for dinner this evening?
Hmm, well, anything works.
Or maybe not.
No go?
Is there anything you'd like to eat, Tohru?
Me?
Omurice, I suppose.
Oh! Nice! Let's go with that, then.
Make us good ones, please.
Roger that!
Leave it to me!
When do you think you'll
be getting home tonight?
Hmm, I want to be home by ten.
Understood.
Lady Tohru, I'm heading out.
I'm heading out, too.
Yes. Take care!
All right!
Time to give my best again today.
Cleaning, cleaning.
Lalala.
Beat the dust,
crush it,
and leave no dirt or grime!
Wipe it out,
wipe it out!
Huh?! Bring it on!
Bathroom, check!
Bedrooms, check!
Entrance, check!
Rooster, check!
Living room, check!
Perfect timing on the laundry, too.
The weather's nice today,
so they should dry quickly.
Coming.
Please stamp here.
Thank you for all your work.
Thank you.
The cushion to help with
Miss Kobayashi's lower back pain, huh?
Well, the laundry's finished.
All that's left is the omurice for dinner.
It's all for Miss Kobayashi.
Make us good ones, please.
I must prepare the best omurice ever!
First, some trial runs.
Finished!
How's that?
Fluffy, juicy eggs, hot rice with
ketchup, all at restaurant quality!
And the taste...
is average?!
It's not that it isn't good, but...
Hmm...
Make us good ones, please.
Ah!
I want it to be a little more special.
Though she already warned
me not to add tail...
Yes?
Hey.
Oh, it's you, Miss Lucoa.
I brought some snacks. Want some?
Thank you very much.
What's with that outfit?
Everyone was always saying something to me,
so I tried toning down the exposure.
How is it?
You should change your body next.
Huh?
Please, come inside.
Yeah. Pardon me.
No wonder that shop receives such praise.
I'll put on another cup for you.
Oh, but I need to be going.
Right!
I was in the middle of making trial batches
of omurice for Miss Kobayashi to eat.
Do you know any techniques
to make them taste good?
Oh, omurice, huh?
Hmm...
The quickest way would probably be
to use good ingredients, I think?
I see.
Later! The tea was delicious.
It was nothing.
Ingredients, huh?
Oborozuka Shopping District
Prime Free-Range Chicken Thighs
It's expensive.
If I gather good rice,
vegetables, and eggs...
Yeah, all right.
Over budget?!
Shopping for dinner, Tohru-chan?
Oh, Mr. Tatsuta.
This chicken is expensive, isn't it?
Well, that's the best free-range
chicken from Akita, after all.
Could you give me a discount?
Hmm, it's already priced as low as I can go.
Could you please?!
If I go any lower,
it'll hurt my own livelihood.
I see.
But I wanted to thank you
for the other day, too.
I could give you extra on these cuts.
Chicken Thighs
They're average!
That would defeat the point.
It would?
Make us good ones, please.
I don't have a choice.
Hereabouts should be good.
I'm home!
Welcome home, Kanna!
Lady Tohru, what's this?
Ingredients for our omurice.
You went back again?
Only for a moment.
What eggs are these?
They're Gullinkambi eggs.
The one serving as Valhalla's alarm clock?
Yes.
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
They're damn good!
Really?
An einherjar told me they're
incredibly delicious.
And this?
That's...
spring water from an elf village.
I was planning to cook the
rice with it. Just...
I've fought with the elves
before, so I took it in secret.
You couldn't complain if
they killed you over that.
There's also meat from bull demons,
and fruits that only grow in that world.
What about the rice and vegetables?
I thought it best to use rice
and vegetables from this world.
True, the rice in this nation is delicious.
Apparently they use some magic
called "selective breeding."
I should have them teach me
the incantation some time.
Now, then.
Time to get cooking!
Kanna, could you help me, too?
Yeah!
Roar!
Demons out! Blessings in!
Roar, roar!
Roar, roar, roar, roar!
Demons out! Blessings in!
Lucoa!
Huh?
Oh, were you worried about me?
I-I wasn't!
Huh?
Episode 12
Tohru and Kobayashi's Impactful Meeting!
(We're Raising the Bar on Ourselves)
Ah, I'm beat.
Oh, right, tonight's dinner is omurice.
If I recall, the first normal meal
she cooked was omurice.
It's done, Miss Kobayashi!
She set it out with such confidence...
And it was damn good!
Normally, she always made
weird things, though.
Thinking about it now...
It's been a long time since I had
someone willing to cook for me.
Two's better than one!
Three's better than two!
Family's great!
Back then I told her it was so-so, but...
Today I'll tell her...
it's... good...
Hey, hurry up and pass that my way!
Forget about that,
hurry up and fix this error!
Make sure you're making backups!
Help me out here!
Kobayashi!
The deadline's almost here!
Yes!
Kobayashi! We've got errors!
I'll fix them at once!
Kobayashi! Help out over here!
Coming right now!
Kobayashi!
Shut up!
Another, man!
Coming up.
That's my stop!
Express
Where am I going now?
The mountain... sounds good.
The air's nice here!
Huh?! A bear?!
Caution! Bears in Area
Bear...
Tasty bears!
Bring it on!
Dragonslayer
It's pitch black!
Ow.
What?
Where did you come from, human?
Whoa! It's a dragon! Hug me!
Ow!
Leave, you insolent human!
Or I'll eat you!
Well, either way, I'm going to die, too.
How pathetic that the last
being I meet is a human.
Hey, don't you get tired
of talking that way?
Huh?
It has to wear you out.
Why, you!
You need this pulled out?
Huh? Well...
Hey!
You fool! If a human touches God's
sword, their mind will be torn— Ahh!
Don't know about that.
If God exists, then... Hngh!
He should try...
extending my deadline right now!
No, no, no, no!
Dragonslayer
Even if we are in my dream, that's no
reason a dragon should be so servile.
I'm sorry.
Yet you saved me...
I was defeated in battle with the
gods, and escaped to this world.
I imagine you managed to remove
that sword because you lack faith.
I'm truly grateful.
Who gives a damn about that?!
Huh?
Drink!
Drink with me!
Dragon, listen to my story!
Huh? Uh...
Drink it!
Oh.
So you're a girl, then.
Yes, I am.
I don't like using this spell though.
Oh! You're a good drinker!
All right! Let's drink
together, just us girls!
Hehehe
Girls?!
D'oh
I'm a girl!
Oh! I'm sorry.
Jeez, now I'm mad! Drink!
Let me fondle your tits!
Sure.
Huh? I can?
- Several Hours Later -
Dragonslayer
This whole world's unfair!
I'm out there working so hard, for what?!
That's right, you tell them!
Let me bring an end to it all!
And what the hell?! Don't make me cover
for your subordinate's mistakes!
Don't assume all dragons are those lolicons
who demand a village's virgin daughters!
Dragonslayer
Why am I all alone?
Same.
I'm all alone in this world now...
Do you have anywhere to go?
No. Though I've been alone from the start.
Then...
Want to come to my place?
I-I do!
Then be my maid!
What?
Listen! A maid isn't just a simple servant!
Normally they're divided by their
roles into house maids, laundry maids,
and so forth, and it takes training to be
one, unlike those girls at maid cafés—Oh!
I'm Kobayashi.
I'm Tohru.
So, Tohru.
I'm not out to deny the
existence of maid cafés.
Those are good in their own way,
but they're a problem that
helps contribute to the growing
trend of the maid profession
being taken lightly...
Oborozuka. Oborozuka.
Oborozuka
I feel like I dreamt about
something important...
I'm home.
Kobayashi!
Miss Kobayashi, welcome home!
We just finished the omurice.
I helped, too.
I'm confident in it!
The omurice was delicious,
but because I had to point out so many issues,
I again failed to tell her they were good.
I can't believe it's raining all of a sudden!
I'm home!
They said there was no chance of rain.
Help me, Takiya.
It's a guerrilla event.
Time to grind.
Coming, coming!
Hmm...
I guess we'll be having
this for lunch for a while.
So cute!
Is it okay if I pet him?
Sure!
World Wide Dogs
Entertainer Special
Entertainers' Pet
Gathering
Ridiculous.
Oh, hey, it's cramped.
What mere pets, acting
affectionate with humans.
You're one to talk.
Kanna.
No.
Speaking of which, were there any humans
you were close to in your old world?
Humans?
Well, if I had to say, there was one
human I associated with for a time.
Oh? What were they like?
Well, allow me to talk about
my former self a bit.
I first met that human in
an empty, ruined village.
Hmm, guess I'll make this
place my home for a while.
Hmm?
It's rare to see a dragon
in a place like this!
I was just lying low for a bit.
Let me stay with you for a while!
A bandit?
Uh-huh.
I mistook a noble for a merchant and
attacked them, now I'm on the run.
All my comrades have been captured,
so I'm all alone now and I
was wondering what to do next.
I'm not interested in you.
If you don't get lost, I'll just kill you.
How dare you... Why do you laugh?
Oh, sorry!
This is the first time I've
ever heard anyone say
they'd kill me with so little
intent behind the words!
Miss Dragon, you're not used to
threatening people, are you?
It's not just a threat!
See?
So it's okay, right?
Let me stay for a while.
Do as you please.
Yeah.
Thinking back on it now,
I could've just left myself.
But at the time I couldn't
let myself yield to a human.
Hey, hey, what's it feel
like being a dragon?
What do you mean?
You can fly through the sky, and possess
such power you'll never lose to anyone.
I want to know what it feels like to
be able to live freely in this world.
Huh? You're ignoring me?
No way!
At the time I found myself thinking.
You responded to me! Hey!
What was my freedom like?
I never thought of myself
as free before then.
I was born with the chaos faction,
lived with chaos, and fought the divine.
If that all ended, would I be free?
Would it ever end?
Even if it did end,
and I was free, what would I...?
What would you do if you had freedom?
Hmm?
Be a maid!
A maid?
Yes. A maid.
I'd wear a cute maid outfit,
greet guests with my best smile,
fall in love with my master.
You'd just be enslaving yourself.
Yes!
But it'd be my choice.
I would have a choice.
If I had a choice, I think
my life would be different.
If I could choose my own life,
and my only two choices were becoming
a bandit or becoming a slave, then...
I see.
Yeah.
Thinking back on it, I had
never made my own choice,
and I thought that was fine.
There wasn't anyone I wanted to see anyway.
So I chatted with that girl
for a while after that.
I think I should be good now.
You're leaving?
Yeah.
I'm going to cross the mountains and
try heading to the next nation over.
I'm sure there'll be something there.
Oh, Miss Dragon, let me ride you.
Bug off! I'll never let a human ride me!
Cheapskate.
I'll die before I let a human ride me.
Well, later.
Thank you, Miss Dragon!
For what?
For being with me.
And so I parted ways with
that annoying human.
At least, that's how I should have felt.
Yet I felt a little sad...
and uncomfortable.
Then maybe that person had something
to do with why you're my maid now.
You're right.
It's rare of me to say this, but I
wouldn't mind seeing that human again.
I see.
Yes.
By the way, Tohru.
Yes?
The way you used to talk
sounds like an old man.
Huh?!
But it's cool!
Huh?
All right!
The weather's nice.
Super Entry Level
Object-Oriented Programming
Learn the skills yourself
I see...
I've sure blended in to this world...
Oh, well.
Next Episode
Tohru, do you think that
bandit girl is still alive?
Who knows?
But if she is alive, I bet
she's serving as a maid.
Same as you, then.
Indeed.
I hope she's getting along well.
Episode 13
Emperor of Demise Arrives!
(It Was the Final Episode Before We Knew It)
I hope so, too.