The land of Flonyard.
On this continent,
bathed in protective light,
the people are joyous
and live in peace.
However, this last spring,
something unfortunate happened
in the south of the continent,
in the Biscotti Republic.
Thus, Princess
Millihiore of Biscotti
summoned a champion
from a faraway world.
The person who answered
her summons had a smile
for every person he met, and
brought happiness into their hearts.
Even though this hero returned to Earth
once his mission was over...
...he promised we would
meet again in summer.
Now, summer has come.
That's why the tale of love
and bravery of the hero,
and of us, will begin anew.
7/22/2011, 7:05 AM
Earth / Japan, Kinokawa City, Tokino Ward
So, Sink, are you going to tell me now?
Kinokawa International School, 2nd year Middle School student
Placed 2nd in the "Iron Athletics" tournament last year
Sink Izumi
What exactly?
Kinokawa International School, 2nd year Middle School student
Rebecca Anderson (Sink's childhood friend)
The destination of the upcoming trip!
I already told you.
I can't tell you until we get there.
Same day, 11:09 PM
Earth / Great Britain, City of London
Hi, Sink. It's me, Nanami.
Where are you?
Winner of the "Iron Athletics" tournament last year
Takatsuki Nanami
(Lives in London, Sink's cousin)
Almost at the station.
I just have to wait there, right?
Yes.
The guide will escort you from there.
Roger.
What are we doing here?
Tatsumaki!
Sink!
I haven't seen you in forever.
Sorry I kept you waiting, Becky.
We're leaving for our trip from here.
Here, kitty kitty.
For me?
H-hey, Sink...
Here we go.
Becky, the view is really great.
Open your eyes and look!
No way!
It's in the afternoon...
Is that the sea?
Wait, I'm in the sky?!
I'm sorry, Becky.
Wait here for a sec, okay?
Sink...
Yes, Princess.
Sink! Sink! Sink!
Princess! I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
I'm back, just like I promised!
Yup!
Thank you for summoning me again.
But of course! Thank you for answering.
I'm so glad you came again.
Me, too.
It's not just me though.
There's also Nanami and Becky...
How is Rebecca-san?
Oh!
I think she was a little too startled.
Let's take her somewhere
where she can rest.
Is Nanami doing okay?
She is.
I asked for her to be summoned
onto the Galette premises,
so I'm sure Leo-sama is giving
her a proper welcome.
So everyone's already...
As you can see.
Our hero!
Sink! Welcome back!
Jeez, you took too long.
Our hero!
I am overjoyed that the summoning
worked again without any problems!
That's because you did all
the research necessary.
Thanks, Rico.
Rico, stop hogging him!
I'm going to hug him, too!
Certainly.
H-hey, Yukki, Yukki!
Eclair!
It's good to see you again, Eclair.
I came back earlier,
just like I promised.
I hope you'll train me in all
sorts of subjects, again.
It's going to be tougher than last time.
Hero, hero!
Rebecca-dono is waking up.
Good morning, Becky.
Huh? Sink?
Isn't it beautiful?
I wanted to bring you here so much.
Um, yes, I do think that
it's very beautiful...
but the islands are floating
and the sky is violet.
Well, you'll get used to it...
So, can I introduce you
to my friends here?
Sure.
Princess! Everyone!
Yes!
It's so wonderful to
meet you, Rebecca-sama!
Nice to meet you.
We welcome you.
Hello... it's so nice to....
Welcome to Flonyard, Rebecca-san.
Thank you for coming to Biscotti!
Uh... yes, I mean... thank you...
Looks like it's about to start.
Yeah.
Then let's go back to the hall!
Yes!
Let's go!
Sink!
I've got so many questions!
Don't worry, I'll explain everything.
We're off, then!
Our destination is Fournette,
our battle-ground for the day!
Let's go!
The sky is clear and it's
another day perfect for war!
The main players have yet to arrive,
but the Biscotti vs Galette
army battle has already begun!
We're your hosts today,
and we'll be bringing
you all the action live!
We are Framboise Charley from the
Galette National Broadcast and...
Percy Gaudi from the
Biscotti National Broadcast!
Now, all of our wonderful guests
we invited from both countries!
General of the Galette Lion Army
Leader of the Knights
Bernard Sabrage
From Galette, we have their leader of
the knights, Bernard Sabrage and...
Thank you.
Next to him, is Leo-sama's
personal assistant, Violet-san.
Leader of the Galette Lion Army's Imperial Guard
Violet Amaret
Hello.
Knights of Biscotti
Leader of the Knights
Rolan Martinozzi
From Biscotti, we have their leader
of the knights, Rolan Martinozzi.
Hello.
Mistress d'Arquien,
leader of the Secret Squad.
Knights of Biscotti
Leader of the Secret Squad
Brioche d'Arquien
Thank you for having me.
With these members on board,
we'd now like to bring
you the battle live!
That's right!
And today's battle is
"Welcome back, Hero! Special
Welcoming Battle", is that right?
Yes.
Today's main character,
the hero of Biscotti,
should be arriving shortly.
Our princess and the leader of the
bodyguards are with them, as well.
Leo-sama is on his way, too.
And, of course, Prince Gaul.
To everyone fighting in
the battle right now;
to the knights, warriors,
and regular participants,
once the Hero arrives, this arena
is going to absolutely explode!
We recommend that you gather
all the points you can now!
Knights of Galette, Gaul's personal guard
Imperial Guard Unit "Genoise"
Jaune Clafoutis
All right, you've been
waiting long enough.
It's our turn now!
Unmatched in battle,
Gaul-sama's personal guard!
Knights of Galette, Gaul's personal guard
Imperial Guard Unit "Genoise"
Noir Vinocacao
Who called us? Who named us?
Knights of Galette, Gaul's personal guard
Imperial Guard Unit "Genoise"
Vert Far-Breton
The three of us are:
Genoise!
And no matter what they
say, he's our prince!
Everybody, call him!
And a-one...
Prince Gaul!
Yeah!
I'm here!
It's me!
So guys, I heard
that stupid hero was coming
back to Biscotti today,
and I decided that I'm going
to fight him personally!
But he has absolutely no intention
of letting him win because
it's a welcoming match.
We're gonna give it to both
the hero and the knights.
Today's victory's going
to Galette again!
So, all you Biscottians—
come and get it!
So this is... a war?
That's right!
Or, as you would say on Earth,
it's "an athletic event
sponsored by each country
and involving the
general populace."
Sink did really great things
in these events when he
was here last spring.
He's our, that is to
say Biscotti's, hero!
Sink... a hero?
That's right.
And as Biscotti's hero,
he saved Biscotti.
I can see Sink being able to
do well in events like these.
Yes, he proved to be an excellent hero.
That's so great.
It looks like so much fun!
Then why don't you join?
Can I?!
To be perfectly honest, that is
why we summoned you to our land.
Takatsuki Nanami, would you like
to try being Galette's hero?
Booyeah, we've cut
through their defense!
Now it's a straight shot
to their stronghold.
Troops, charge!
It looks like His Highness Gaul
and Genoise are advancing fast!
The stronghold is right there!
It looks like the Biscotti
camp is in trouble.
Emi-rin!
Are the captain and the
hero still not here?
Don't despair, Ange!
I know they will come.
Gaul-sama, we're going ahead!
Took you long enough!
I'm here now!
H-he...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I have answered the princess's
and your summons....
Sink, reporting for duty!
He's here!
The hero, Sink, has appeared.
Sink...
Sink-kun...
Sink, welcome back.
Jaune! Noir! Vert!
It's good to see you again.
As promised, I trained hard.
In one moment?
I didn't even see it.
He's been training too much.
It's really something.
It is, but that's not
enough to defeat us!
It looks like the Genoise
are out of the game for now!
That's what happens when you
try to upstage the hero!
It looks like the leader
of Biscotti's Secret Guard
and the Chief Researcher
are both here, too!
And...
the captain of our imperial guard,
Eclair, has arrived as well!
It's been a long time,
Sink, Hero of Biscotti.
Your Excellency!
Oh, it's Leo-sama!
I'm glad to see you've
come back stronger.
However, we won't be defeated.
If Biscotti is using a hero,
might we not do the same?
Behold!
This is the hero of the
Galette Lion Army!
I was summoned by Leo-sama.
My name is Takatsuki Nanami,
here to fight as Galette's hero!
I suspected Nanami-san would
join the battle right away.
Would you like to participate, too?
You could be on artillery or archery!
Oh no, I'm not good at this
type of thing at all!
That's it!
Why don't I introduce you
to everyone, since you
came all the way here?
Oh, I am getting a message
from Princess Millihiore!
Hello!
I'm Millihiore, speaking to you
from the Fournette fortress.
It looks like you're all having
a lot of fun over there.
Here, we've got childhood friend
of both heroes: Rebecca Anderson!
Um, well... uh... hello!
Hello!
Becky!
Yes, yes...
Principality of Pastillage
Castle Eschenbach
Both armies have resumed their advance!
Is a direct clash imminent?!
They're really getting into it.
Quite so.
Both countries summoned a hero...
Millihi-nee and Leo-nee
are both unbelievable.
First Princess of the Principality of Pastillage
Feudal Lord of the Eschenbach Lands
Couverte E. Pastillage
Pastillage Crystal Technique Knights
Callaway Risler
Everybody seems to be
enjoying themselves.
True...
Truth be told, I'd like Pastillage
to join the fray with gusto, too.
I concur.
On the other hand, I'm not that...
This girl...
Yes, I hear she is the
friend of both heroes.
A visitor from the other world.
I see.
So she's not the hero of
either country, right?
Yes, I believe so.
This girl... she's good.
My senses are tingling!
I'm going to go meet her!
Since we're going anyway,
let's crash their battle, as well!
Certain— What?!
I'm coming to pick you up right now!
Just wait for me, my hero!
A Hero Appears!
Our hero's finally returned!
Since he's brought Rebecca-sama
and Nanami-sama as well,
it's going to be even more fun!
Pastillage Joins The Battle!
Let's get fired up
together next time, too!