Suicide?
That idiot...
Kei?
I'm sending you the info on this
Elbaji guy and his company.
Cammy, I'm not seeing it.
Don't you have something to say?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What happened to that Tilarna girl?
I haven't seen her...
Oh, she's in the sleeping room.
She's in a new city. It's tiring her out.
So what's with the sword, then?
Sorry. I took my eyes off her
for a minute and she split.
Bring her back. Now.
I don't want people complaining
about the investigation.
Fifteen years ago, a hyperspace gate
appeared in the middle of the Pacific.
Beyond the gate lay a strange world
filled with fairies and monsters.
Kariaena Island. The city of San-Teresa.
This city is Earth's "front door."
Over two million citizens
from both worlds live here.
A mixture of different races and
diverse cultures, haves and have-nots...
The world's newest "city of dreams."
But in the shadows of all this
chaos lurked countless crimes.
Drugs. Prostitution.
Weapons smuggling.
The San-Teresa Metropolitan Police maintained
a special unit to deal with these crimes.
Well?
Without my help, you'd have been turned
away at the front door, Sister Tilarna.
Be grateful to the God of Earth.
Does your "God" help with fake IDs?
I would've preferred
a more normal outfit, though.
Don't let it look like it's bothering you.
On Earth, high-ranking women walk like this.
Now try it.
Like this?
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
Don't you think that's wonderful, Brother Kenny?
Cute...
I can't stand this stuff.
Play some damn disco music.
This isn't that kind of place.
This is far enough.
Here's your payment.
That was easy. Thank you.
You sure about this, miss?
Isn't this important to you?
My mother gave it to me.
But I don't need it anymore.
But...
Thanks for everything.
Okay, Brother.
Let's have some fun while we're here.
But Father, she seemed like
something was really bothering her.
Kids that age have a lot on their mind.
Let her get some experience
with different things.
Like O, or V, or A.
I'm worried...
Give me water.
Water.
Hey, having fun?
--Get lost.
--Aww, lighten up.
You're a noble from the Tiburani area, right?
Surprised?
I'm from your world, too.
Then why didn't you speak to me in Farbani?
Apologies.
I thought the language of the doreany
would be more suited for a place like this.
Speak as you like. I don't care.
Really? Great, all that fancy
noble language tires me the hell out.
Can we talk like this instead?
Tell me what you want.
I'm hitting on you.
I love girls like you.
How about we go have a good time?
I'm looking for someone. Bother somebody else.
Who are you after?
Dennis Elbaji. The guy who runs this place.
Oh, Dennis?
Dennis... Dennis. Oh, Dennis!
Dennis Elbaji's a friend of mine.
Want an introduction?
Don't make that face. Just come with me.
Now...
Actually, I'm Dennis Elbaji.
Surprised?
Not really.
Well, that's no fun.
So, what do you want, miss?
I am Tilarna Exedilica.
I was sent here by the Knights of Mirvor.
A knight, huh?
I know what you're up to.
Give back the fairy.
Oh, that?
No way. That's product.
I thought you'd say that.
You seem like you're ready to die, huh?
We're done talking, then.
Incompetents.
That's what happens when
you rely on doreany weapons.
Agreed.
Kids these days are just wimps.
It's a real problem!
I guess I should ask.
Who's your teacher?
I have no intention of answering.
I see.
He's...
I can see your panties, Tilarna.
I won't kill you yet.
I have lots of questions, after all.
This area hasn't been developed yet.
There're still traces of the other world.
Nobody lives here anymore.
They all moved to the doreany town.
Can't make a single dollar
raising crops, after all.
Do you know the name of Earth's god?
"Money."
Simplest thing in the world, right?
I've converted to its religion, too.
I've been waiting for you, my master.
Zelada, the goods are ready, right?
Yes. If you'll follow me...
Who is this lady?
One of the Knights of Mirvor.
She found my club somehow.
Ask her all about it.
Leave it to me.
I'll make her tell you everything.
Now, Mr. Kareem, let's finish the deal.
What a mess.
What's the situation?
An old temple in the Hightails.
Matched the records the delivery people had.
Keep watching.
SWAT's on their way.
When will they get here?
Thirty minutes.
That long? Make them hurry!
Stay put.
We need to move up the schedule.
I'm sorry. Please keep an eye on her.
What about the questioning?
I'll be right back.
A fire?
Shit!
Damn it, now I'm Don Quixote.
Arms of great strength.
Protection of the war god.
Hey, you need to stay put!
What are you doing?
My job.
I guess I'll say it.
This is the police. Throw down your--
Yeah, thought so.
Where's the fairy? Tell me!
How awful...
It's worse for me.
It takes cash to make
the drugs I turn them into.
And then there was the investment
to make my new product.
And now the place is going up in flames.
It's depressing.
Shut up!
Oh, you mad?
The fairies are holy and inviolable beings.
But you...
This is my new product.
I can use a fairy as a medium
to turn everyone within a few kilometers
into fairy dust addicts instantly.
A psychic bomb, you could call it.
I'm trying to come up
with a cooler name, though.
That's terrifying...
You're no longer even human!
Human... Human, huh?
I grew up in the same world you did.
My family were warriors.
Sword fighting. Mounted combat.
Etiquette. Magic.
I was forced to master it all.
Then I was gonna spend the rest of my life
being bossed around by incompetent nobles
before dying in some
stupid fight over territory.
Thus ends a life lived with honor.
Disgusting, huh?
But Earth's different.
It's the American dream, you know!
Remember what I said? Money.
With money, you can have whatever you want.
This place is much more human!
Shut up!
So you're another one of the morons, huh?
That's a shame.
There'll be no holding back!
Dance, dance!
Come on! A little more and
your boobs will come spilling out!
If I only had my sword...
Tilarna!
That stance. That sword. Vreideni style, huh?
I told you. I'm not giving you a name.
This'll be fun!
Want some help?
No! I'll kill him myself!
Okay! Get him!
My deepest thanks!
You bitch...
I'll tell you before you die.
My teacher's name is Lord Garada Vreideni.
Tell it to the demons in hell.
Screw you...
Nicely done. I would turned tail and run.
He was a scary dude.
He was a fierce enemy.
What's with the outfit?
D-Don't stare at me!
It's not the kind of clothing I like!
Sure. Let's get out of here.
Wait. She's still...
A fake?
What?
It's just a doll.
I don't sense any latena.
The real one is getting further away.
So somebody took it?
Quiet. I can't concentrate.
Here.
Those footprints are new.
That red wizard took the bomb
she was trapped in and fled.
I'll explain on the way.
Let's go, Kei.
A psychic bomb, huh?
I don't know if I understand the particulars,
but that explains what happens
to the guys from Precinct 22.
That wizard, Zelada, took it.
If he uses it, the results will be horrific.
Tens of thousands of people
turned into addicts in an instant.
And he can make them do
whatever he wants, huh?
Quiet. She's very close.
Stop!
Hands up. Slowly.
Oh, you're the undercover
cop from the other day.
Hello, there...
Careful, Kei!
You're gonna pay for what you did to Rick.
You're spending the rest of your life in jail.
How could you do that to an old man?
Show a little mercy.
Shut up. You're under arrest.
Matoba, looks like you caught the guy.
Chief?
SWAT's cleaning up.
They caught the terrorists
who were buying the bomb, too.
Good to hear. But why are you here?
This is why.
Don't move.
Let him go.
Use my car.
My deepest thanks, Sir Roth...
Wait!
Throw down the gun, Matoba.
Chief...
Do it.
Oh, right... Sir Matoba, was it?
You've grown so handsome.
I barely recognized you from
the time we met in that swamp.
It was you?
It was you, wasn't it?
You wiped out my unit during the war!
Have a lovely evening.
Don't move, Matoba.
He killed Rick!
Were you the one informing him
about the investigation?
Yeah. It was all me.
I'm the one who gave you an inexperienced
Semanian to slow you down.
The one who had an assassin sent after Alvarez.
And told Zelada that the temple
hideout had been found.
And killed Rick, too?
Answer me!
Fury had almost found me out.
I couldn't help it.
I don't get it...
Roth, you of all people...
Why?
He and I want the same thing.
That man, Zelada, hates Earth's civilization.
He wants terrorism to sow hatred
between Earth and the Semanians.
And so do I.
Coexistence and peace
are lies the idealists tell.
We can never understand each other.
We have to be separated.
Some people are adapting just fine.
And their ability to adapt is what scares me!
Look at their vitality.
Three generations from now,
they'll be ruling the Earth!
The invasion will be over
before anybody realizes...
Yes... Even the invaders
don't know they're doing it!
The world needs to know
how dangerous they are.
And that psychic bomb can make them afraid
without damaging the infrastructure of society.
And you call yourself a police officer?
An officer? But more importantly,
I'm a human living on Earth.
Kei Matoba, I thought you might understand.
You want me to join you? Screw you.
I'm sorry to hear that.
You always hide a revolver at your ankle, right?
Give it a try, if you want.
You were like a dad to me.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Kei...
No, I'm fine.
I'm amazed you survived.
I can't believe it.
Neither can I.
Let's follow him.
Zelada?
He's gonna use that bomb. And right now, too.
We found the chief's car.
Forest Tower, in Queen's Valley.
Thanks.
Kei. About the chief...
We'll talk later.
Get some officers there.
Forest Tower is one of the
tallest buildings in the city.
He's going to use the psychic bomb there?
It may be more effective
there than on the ground.
I see.
Just like a nuke, huh?
What's this place like?
Loaded with rich folks.
Common folk never go there.
Maybe it's not even worth stopping him.
I know. It was a joke.
Good, then.
Kei.
What?
That wizard... Zelada... You know him?
Who knows? To me, he's just another perp.
It's that wizard Zelada's doing.
Above!
Is he dangerous?
A wizard's power is something to be feared.
They can blind a warrior
or create poisonous flames.
Your weapons are no match...
Even this thing? It's a good gun,
and I've been using it for a long time.
Your doreany weapons have no soul.
No... I feel a faint latena from this gun.
Feelings put into an object,
no matter what it is, will create latena.
Stay close to me, Kei. I'm the only one
who can spot the enemy's ambush.
But...
If you're my partner, trust me.
Got it.
Get back!
Ahead! Run!
That fire will burn your lungs.
You won't be able to breathe...
So you'll choke to death, huh? Damn.
That's her!
Leahyah!
"Next time"
Next time on COP CRAFT.