Yes!
Matsuoka Rin
Nanase Haruka
Haru lost...
Haru!
I win.
This means I'll never swim with you again.
Huh?
Never.
Revenge in the Medley!
Set.
Go!
Oh, there you are!
Sorry about being late.
Coach Sasabe...
Where were you?!
You're late, Goro-chan!
Thank you for your help the other day.
And I appreciate you taking time
from work to come support us.
Oh, it's no big deal.
I really think we've met before.
No, I don't think...
Jeez, did you come here to hit on girls?
I wasn't hitting on her!
Haruka-senpai already
swam his freestyle heat.
Darn, I missed the prelims.
But I can still watch the final.
He won't be in the final.
Huh?
Haru... didn't pass the prelims.
He lost?!
I thought I didn't care about winning.
Wasn't I...
Wasn't I supposed to become
free after racing him?
Matsuoka-senpai!
You did it!
You qualified for the final!
And you beat Nanase-san!
Yeah, well.
You go kick some butt, too.
Yes!
Samezuka Academy
Mikoshiba-kun in lane 4 has just
set a new tournament record.
Way to go, Mikoshiba!
Wow, that's impressive.
Isn't Mikoshiba...?
Oh! Samezuka's captain!
I thought he was just
an enthusiastic person,
but he's actually a good swimmer.
Right, Gou-chan?
Y-Yeah...
What's wrong?
Haruka-senpai isn't back yet.
Oh, you're right.
He's probably taking a shower.
He's taking a long time though.
I'll go check on him.
Rei! Wait up!
Hold on, Mako-chan! Rei-chan!
Wait up, Rei!
Don't dwell on it.
That's how sports are.
That's not it.
Huh?
I wanted to watch my brother and
Haruka-senpai swim together.
But that wasn't what I was expecting.
Wait, Rei!
Why are you stopping me?
Well, it's because...
Calm down, Rei-chan.
Aren't you worried about Haruka-senpai?
Rin-chan!
You guys.
Right, you're all swimming
in the tournament.
Hey, Rin-chan.
Have you seen Haru-chan?
Haru?
He hasn't come back yet.
Was losing to me that big of a shock?
He's the one who said that
he didn't care about winning
or improving his time.
He's not upset about losing.
There must be some other reason.
What?
What else matters in swimming
other than winning?!
There is more.
At least, Haru thought there
was something more.
That's why he wanted to race you.
And I'm pretty sure you're
the one who taught him
what that something was.
When we swam in that relay
in grade school, you—
What do I care?!
I beat Haru!
That's all that matters.
A relay?
Did you guys swim in a relay
with him in the past?
We didn't mention that?
You only told me that things
happened in the past.
If you were that close, why are you—
Now, now. Calm down, Rei-chan.
We need to look for Haru-chan right now.
No, we should let him be.
Knowing Haru,
he probably doesn't want to
talk to anyone right now.
And we have our own races coming up.
Let's focus on what
we can do right now.
Yes.
Where's Haruka?
Oh, we couldn't find him.
Man, what's he doing?
Makoto's about to swim.
I'm gonna go get him!
I want Haru-chan to watch us swim!
Nagisa-kun?!
Back then...
If Rin had won,
would I feel differently now?
Rin is swimming to compete
in the Olympics.
What about me?
Why do I swim?
Hey! Haru-chan!
There you are!
Mako-chan's race is about to start!
Hurry up!
I'll pass.
I don't think so!
Let's go!
Go, go, go, go, go, Makoto!
Swim, swim, swim, swim, swim, Makoto!
Not loud enough!
You've gotta shout from your belly!
Especially you, Rei! Don't be shy!
Yes!
Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, Makoto!
Go, go, go!
Go!
Go, go, Makoto!
And turn!
That's it!
Last spurt, last spurt, last spurt!
Good job!
Tachibana Makoto (Iwatobi High School)
Man, Mako-chan was so close!
He almost had a fast
enough time to qualify!
He was so close to making the final!
Okay! I'm up next!
Yeah, go get 'em.
Set.
Go!
Go, go, go, go, go, Nagisa!
Swim, swim, swim, swim, swim, Nagisa!
Haru thought there was something more.
That's why he wanted to race you.
And I'm pretty sure you're
the one who taught him
what that something was.
I couldn't do it!
It was close.
You made a huge push at the end.
I believe it's finally my turn.
Will you be okay, Rei-chan?
I've got this.
Despite how I may look, I'm
better in actual competition.
Set.
Go!
Wow, his form is perfect.
Huh? Look at Rei-kun's goggles.
Ah! They slid off!
It must have happened when he dove in.
Go, go, go, go, go, Rei!
Swim, swim, swim, swim, swim, Rei!
Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, Rei!
Go, go!
I apologize.
I wasn't good enough.
You shouldn't say that.
You were able to swim a personal
best. That's a great thing.
You might have qualified if
your goggles hadn't slipped off.
Er, that seems a little far-fetched.
In any case, everyone performed well.
Excellent work.
There's a sense of
accomplishment, right?
Yeah.
Let's start preparing for
the next tournament.
Oh? Where's Nanase-kun?
It looks like he left without us.
What? Really?
Yeah, he wasn't feeling well.
Oh... I guess that can't be helped, then.
Matsuoka-san, can you
take it from here?
Yes.
Then I'll be leaving now.
It's been a while since
I got my blood pumping.
Nice job! See ya.
He came here on that?
Is his work gonna be okay with this?
It's over.
Yeah.
It would have been nice
to go to regionals.
After we practiced so hard,
I was thinking at least one
of us might make it through.
But it's not that easy in reality.
There's more to swimming than I realized.
Understanding it in theory isn't enough to win.
I'm getting fired up.
Well, it's a little late for that.
No, it's not too late.
There's still the second day
of the tournament tomorrow!
But the events we entered were all today.
The second day is the individual
medley and the relay...
Gou-chan, don't tell me that...
I'm sorry!
I signed you up for the
medley relay in secret!
What?!
I told Miss Amakata about it.
So if we win the relay...
We can go to regionals!
That's crazy. This is too sudden.
We didn't practice at all for the relay.
Why didn't you say something sooner?
Because it sounded like Haruka-senpai
didn't want to be in a relay.
Let's do it.
Huh?
Rei-chan?
This is our final chance!
We haven't practiced for the relay,
but it's still worth a shot!
No luck. He isn't home yet.
I don't think.
We can enter upstairs!
Got it!
Uh, wait! Is this really okay?!
He's not on the second floor!
He's not in the bath!
You shouldn't run around someone's
house when they're not...
Haru...
Let's wait for him to return.
Will Haru-chan agree to swim in the relay?
What was it I really wanted?
What was I trying to do?
What was it all for?
He's still not home.
Where'd he go?
What if...
Rei-chan! Don't say scary stuff
with that look on your face!
I didn't say anything yet.
But...
Don't worry.
Haru's not that weak.
Oh, his cell phone!
Let's call him!
Haruka-senpai has a cell phone?!
Why didn't you say something sooner?!
Well, I never see Haru-chan
actually using his cell phone...
Anyway, let's call him!
You have reached the voice mailbox.
He's not answering.
Please leave your name and
a message after the tone.
Leave a message.
Haru-chan? Where are you right now?
Please hurry home.
We're all worried.
I'm sorry, Haruka-senpai!
I signed everybody up
for the medley relay!
Yeah, so let's swim together
tomorrow, Haru-chan.
I'll be fine!
I'll have the theory
memorized by tomorrow!
Rei-chan, that's a sure sign that you'll fail.
I just have to memorize the
theory for how not to fail, also!
Your message has ended.
Will Haruka-senpai come home after
listening to that sloppy message?
It'll be okay!
Our chaotic message has
what it takes to touch
Haru-chan deep down!
Wait...
Haru-chan left his cell phone here!
What?!
Haru usually doesn't carry
his phone around with him.
It's getting late.
We should head home.
But...
I don't think Haru will swim tomorrow.
We'll have to forfeit.
Makoto?
Playing new message.
Haru-chan? Where are you right now?
Please hurry home.
We're all worried.
I'm sorry, Haruka-senpai!
I signed everybody up
for the medley relay!
Yeah, so let's swim together
tomorrow, Haru-chan.
I'll be fine!
I'll have the theory
memorized by tomorrow!
Rei-chan, that's a sure sign that you'll fail.
End of message.
Let's swim together, Haru-chan!
I'll have the theory memorized!
It has to be you!
I want to swim with you!
Makoto, Makoto.
Haru?
We have a relay to swim, right?
Yes, hello?
What?! Haru-chan did?!
He's going to swim?
That's great!
I'll call Miss Amakata right away!
Are you sure about this?
You haven't practiced for
the relay at all, right?
I don't know how we'll do, but
we'll give it our best shot.
And this isn't our first time.
But it is for Ryugazaki-kun.
Nagisa-kun and Rei-kun aren't here yet.
Sorry we're late!
I'm sorry!
Man, what were you guys doing?
You're late!
Actually...
We were practicing the exchange
in the pool at school.
That eliminates the possibility
of Rei-chan completely failing!
When did you...
Haru-chan...
I'm thrilled that we get to swim
in a relay together again.
Let's do this together, Haruka-senpai.
Okay, time to show everyone
that our training paid off!
Yes, that's why we're here!
So much enthusiasm.
Okay!
Let's give it our best shot!
Yeah!
Matsuoka-senpai!
Come with me! Quick!
What is it?
It's not time for Samezuka's relay yet.
No! Nanase-san's club is in the relay!
Huh?
W-Wait for me, Matsuoka-senpai!
They signed up for the relay?
Mako-chan, you can do this.
Fight.
Yeah, wish me luck.
Set.
Go!
His stroke...
A rough but dynamic stroke that
leaves everyone behind...
It hasn't changed at all since then.
That's Makoto's stroke.
And I can't forget Nagisa's stroke.
How he speeds up after the turn...
And how he creates the illusion that
his arms extend when he swims...
And him...
Is that supposed to be butterfly?
Pathetic.
Why is someone like you
swimming with them?!
I don't need an answer right away.
For now...
Hey, have you heard of
the Squid Festival?
Hold on, Nagisa-kun.
Why are you talking about a festival?
We're in the middle of an
exciting medley relay.
The Squid Festival is held around this
time every year to promote squid.
I want fried squid!
I'm looking forward to squid ink soba.
Next time: Hesitant Loosen Up.
Hesitant Loosen Up!
This doesn't tell me what
the next episode's about.
Should I go with thick or thin noodles?
Doesn't tell me a thing...