Pardon me...
What day is it today?
We're home.
Miuna, Hikari!
What's wrong?
Kaname-kun woke up!
Where is he right now?
He's at the Fishery Cooperative.
I'll watch Akira, so Akari,
you can go with Hikari-kun...
Hikari!
Kaname!
Wait up, Hika—
Hey. Good morning.
Episode Seventeen: The Sick Two
Kaname?
So you really did stay on the surface.
Kaname...
You look well, Chisa—
It's been a while, Kaname.
Tsumugu?
Yeah.
Kaname? Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Good morning, Chisaki, Tsumugu.
The truth is, I don't really remember.
When I came to, I was being
carried by the current.
So you don't know how the
rest of the village is doing?
Yeah.
Manaka...
Was there anything else you noticed?
Now that I think of it,
I might have heard a sound...
Huh?
A sound? What kind?
Something like sand flowing.
I didn't hear anything like that.
I heard it, too.
Wha?
When?
Today. I accidentally
fell into the sea...
I heard it then.
Were you okay?
Well, apparently she's able to swim now.
What?
It wasn't hard to breathe at all.
You were able to breathe underwater?
I think so...
Your mom was from Shioshishio, right?
Her birth mother was, yes.
I see...
Does that mean something?
No, I might just be overthinking things.
I'd like to talk to your daughter
at another time if that's all right.
Sure...
All right, Tsumugu.
That should be enough for today.
Right.
Thanks, Kaname.
You helped a lot.
I'm not sure if I was any help.
You helped plenty.
After Hikari-kun came back,
you came back as well.
The awakening of everyone else in
Shioshishio may be drawing nearer.
Really? Does that mean we'll
be able to get into Shishio?
There isn't a sure way yet.
But I believe to solve the mystery
surrounding the various adverse
weather phenomena in the past few years,
we'll need to go to Shioshishio.
And to do that, we've
gathered quite a bit of data.
Please wait a little longer.
We're counting on you.
I want to know if everyone
in the village...
my dad, and Manaka are all safe.
It's best not to forcefully awaken
the ones that are still asleep.
There's still a lot that we don't know.
I know that.
Are you okay, Kaname-kun?
Yes.
Or rather, none of this
really feels real yet.
A lot's changed, so it
must have been surprising.
Right...
But, there are things
that haven't changed.
Mementos Distribution List
Kaname: Gloves and the
four-leaf clover I found by Miuna's
Long Hair: Sea Slug Pendant
Boobs: Dolphin Pencil Board
Good girl.
Precious Notebook
Sayu, Miuna-chan's on the phone!
Okay.
Sit wherever you'd like.
Right.
So you really are living
here, Chisaki...
I said that, didn't I?
You guys came to the Fishery
Cooperative together so I was surprised.
And I just assumed things.
Idiot.
Come on, sit down.
Thanks.
You'll be sharing a room
with Mihashi-sensei.
That's fine.
The tea will be ready in a sec.
Huh?
Here.
My pajamas should work, right?
I've already laid them out.
Kaname, yours is the blue one.
Okay...
You okay?
What do you mean?
Well, Mihashi-sensei is here, too,
so I thought there might be a lot to do.
I'm perfectly fine.
I see...
Yesterday, another student
from Shioshishio awakened.
I know! It's Isaki-senpai, right?
He's good looking, isn't he?
And totally cool.
Hold up!
Didn't you guys say that I was
cool wearing the happi coat?
Is Isaki-senpai joining this class, too?
When's he coming?
You're ignoring me? Hey!
Man...
I decided I'd live the
rest of my life alone.
And now even though
he came back suddenly...
I see...
But...
Yeah... you're happy, right?
Back then, I was just
looking at him from afar.
Even though we were together,
he felt so far away...
And the closer I got to him,
the farther away he felt...
What?
Oh.
Well, I guess you were feeling
the same thing I was.
But now we may be able
to get into that circle.
Now...
Hey, do you want to go see Kaname-san?
Huh?
After a little while when
Kaname-san's settled down a bit.
Oh, b-but...
Sayu.
Oh, r-right.
I wonder if things haven't changed...
See ya.
Let's do our best, Sayu.
Yeah.
Do your best in what?
It's a secret.
That's rude.
I'll do my best...
Come here.
Hey, Kaname!
I heard you were back!
You haven't changed at all, of course!
Um, could you be...
What? You can't tell?
It's me, Sayama. Sayama from Saya Mart.
Oh, it is you.
Once you get a little more settled,
let's meet up with everyone.
See ya later!
Oh, uh...
I guess you wouldn't know.
Oh...
Could it be...
Kaname?
Is something wrong?
No...
Is school fun?
Yeah, I guess.
I had no idea that you
wanted to be a nurse.
I wasn't considering it that long ago.
So it was while I was sleeping...
What were you up to today?
I thought I should see various things.
Things that changed...
things that haven't changed...
Have you changed, Chisaki?
I did age five years.
That doesn't matter.
I like older women.
What the heck?
What about you, Kaname?
I've liked you, Chisaki.
For quite a while now.
Have you changed, Kaname?
I haven't changed at all.
I was just sleeping.
I see...
There's no way I'd change.
It's been a few days since
Kaname-san came back.
Huh?
Miuna has Ena?
After close examination,
it's become clear that
she has about a 50-micron layer of
membrane above her normal skin.
We aren't certain yet,
but it appears to be Ena for sure.
But don't kids born between someone from
the surface and someone from the sea lose their Ena?
Right.
This would be the first time
I've seen a case like this.
I'd like to examine
Akira-kun once, as well.
I still don't get it.
Hey, stop that.
But to think that Miuna has Ena...
Miu? Ena?
Yeah, just like me.
She's just like me.
Ena, Ena.
Good morning.
Good morning!
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
You seem down.
Not really.
I see...
When do you want to go see Kaname-san?
I'm not going.
What?
Sayu?
I wonder where Sayu went.
Miuna! Let's go home!
Sorry, could you go ahead without me?
Jeez...
I really don't get girls.
Seriously.
I thought I'd head back to school
finally and come to check things out,
but apparently things haven't...
Oh!
They apparently kept it around so
we could still use it at any time.
Apparently Miuna and the others
have been keeping it clean.
I see.
By the way, Miuna-chan's
grown up quite a bit.
Not so much on the inside.
I see.
Seriously.
But I guess it can't be helped.
She looks like she's changed.
A lot's changed,
and a lot hasn't changed...
Honestly, it's pretty overwhelming.
Could it be you're
trying to cheer me up?
Well, I am the senpai
that woke up before you.
You've matured, too, Hikari.
Shut up!
Though I've been prepared,
ever since we knew we'd
be falling asleep.
But once it happens,
it's actually rough, isn't it?
You really have changed, Hikari...
Even though you woke up
just a little before me.
You think so?
Yeah.
You only woke up a few days
before me and changed.
So if five years have passed...
I see...
I guess that might be.
Then I won't change anymore.
If I change anymore,
once Manaka wakes up,
it'll surprise her.
Now that you've woken up,
that means Manaka...
She probably hasn't changed since then...
Her feelings for Tsumugu...
But even then, I won't change.
No matter what...
Hikari...
Sayu.
Do Not Enter
I thought I was able to
get a little closer...
But we're still so far away. Man...
I guess I am on my own.
But you know,
there's no way a childhood
crush bears fruit.
I'm bound to forget
these feelings one day.
You think so?
Yeah.
Even though I try to be
tough and live on my own,
as time passes,
I'll probably like someone else.
Or be with someone I don't
like just to avoid being lonely.
That's how it is.
It's not possible to keep feeling the
same way for one person
from when you're a kid.
That's like a manga or a drama.
To feel this way for five years...
I'm just drunk from myself.
It's gross, it's pathetic, horrible.
I'm sick.
That's...
That's not true!
It is true!
It is not!
It is!
It's not!
I've decided. I'm not going to change.
What?
I don't care if I'm sick.
I don't care if it's a manga.
Even if it's gross,
even if it's pathetic...
I'm not changing!
I'm not!
You're not changing? What?
That's not right, Miuna. You're wrong.
Oh, you're alone today, too?
Come here.
I guess you still won't come near me.
Sayu-chan.
Wh-Who are you?
It's been a while, Sayu-chan.
Uh... U-Um...
R-Right. It's been a while...
or maybe it hasn't...
You haven't changed.
Oh, sorry.
We're the same age now.
I'm sick, too.
Hikari, wait!
Whoops, sorry!
Hey, Hikari, where are you going?
I might be able to get
back to Shioshishio!
Jeez...
The key is the sound that Isaki-kun
and Shiodome-kun said they heard.
I believe that this might
be an unknown current.
With that data,
after rewatching the video footage
of the deep sea diving expeditions,
we were able to pinpoint
a weaker current.
It originates somewhere around here.
Right around where
Shioshishio village was.
If this current
has something to do with the mysterious
power that is surrounding the village.
If we're able to get through
the current, we can get in?
This is just a theory though.
Meaning we won't know if we can get
in or not until we actually try, right?
Right.
So we were wondering if you
and Hikari could help out...
Totally! Leave it to us!
Sure, but...
that sound is an important
key to all this, right?
Hikari's going to Shioshishio...
But we don't know what that
sound actually means yet.
The world Hikari was in...
You heard that sound, right?
I'll leave it to you to lead us.
I didn't hear it that clearly, though.
Wha? Then what are we supposed to do?
Where Manaka-san is...
I'll go, too!
I heard the sound clearly.
I think I'll be able
to follow that sound!
I have Ena now, right?
I'll be okay in the sea, right?
Yes, but...
Miuna.
I appreciate your concern,
but isn't it dangerous?
Your Ena's not complete.
I think it'll be fine.
Kaname and I will be with her.
There's nothing to worry about.
We're counting on you, Miuna.
Okay.
Are you sure I don't need to go?
It's up to you.
See ya.
The water temperature's pretty low.
Our Ena is the best. We'll be fine.
Make sure you come back immediately
if something happens.
Yes.
All right!
Are you cold?
I'm fine.
You sure you can breathe
okay down here?
Yeah. I practiced a lot of times.
But make sure you don't
push yourself, all right?
Okay.
So do you hear it?
I don't hear anything.
I don't either...
I hear it...
I can hear it.
Over here!
Wait a sec, Miuna!
A world that I don't know...
Hikari's world that I don't know...
We're home...
This is Shioshishio...
What are you so afraid of?
The Shioshishio I don't know...
This isn't how it really is.
We're in the sea.
I wanted to show her...
The Shioshishio that I dreamed of...
Episode Eighteen:
Shioshishio
Our Shioshishio.