Wow, so pretty!
Such beautiful flowers, Sister!
So glad we still have these kinds of places.
Purple flowers all over the place.
Do you know what this flower is?
Hm... I wonder what this is.
I'm not so good with flower names.
That flower is myosotis.
Huh?
Hm... This is how myosotis look?
Its floral phrases are "Forget-me-not"
and "True friendship."
Thank you, Mr. Robot!
You are welcome.
My name is SEEK.
Mine is Touka.
This here is my sister, Karen.
Touka-san, Karen-san, hello.
I am property of city hall.
I provide nursing, mowing,
and street cleaning services.
I provide useful services
through continual study
and the acquisition of new information.
Keep up the good work, SEEK!
Yes.
Excuse me, would you please be my friends?
I have not any friends yet.
Sure, sounds good!
Here.
I am your friend, SEEK.
Thank you.
In five years, the machines
took down human society.
They sifted through the humans killing some
and allowing others to live.
My sister, Touka, was killed by the machines.
But she is always with me.
Come to think of it, Sis,
you always get strawberry.
Do I?
I like the color red.
Can I have some?
Sure.
Really?
I believe this will be remembered as a
tale of those who threw down
the gauntlet against the machines.
Don't wreak too much havoc.
I can't fight trying to
be nice to the machines.
You only need water to grow...
Thanks as always.
I gave you a little extra.
Gee, thanks!
Huh?
Sorry.
I'm always causing trouble.
Bye.
That's okay. Don't die young.
Thank you!
Good evening. Sorry to keep you waiting.
My, it sure has been a while.
Hi.
Haven't you forgotten something?
No, I haven't. Here it is.
You remembered! I'm so happy!
It's a device to enhance your emotion functions...
This will make you feel so much
better, though it is illegal...
Well, now it's time for
a little compensation.
My killer bra-removing technique.
You're so impatient.
Ah, so nice.
These curves, they're godly.
I simply can't resist what's in front of me!
Cappeli D'angelo.
Cappelini, Fedelini.
Spaghettini, Spaghetti.
Boil water in a large pot.
Add a little salt...
Al Dente.
Boil until it has the firmness of hair.
Cappeli!
It's rude not to knock.
Oh, you're there.
Yes, this is Jack's Corporation.
Right now?
I'm currently busy with something else.
Right... Right, I'll call you
when I'm finished here.
Just get here quick!
Yeah, I want to rush over right now!
Yes, but could you wait just a little bit?
Come quickly or I'll kill ya!
Ta-da!
Super hot stuff, indeed!
You'll get lots of money for these!
That's all you got?
Oh, not again!
You scratch my back, I'll scratch yours.
What if they found out we strip them down?
That'd be it!
It's going to be the end
of me, end of you...
Whatever! Just take them away.
Really?
Okay! Thanks for the business!
Secure and trustworthy, Jack's Recycle Corporation!
Looking forward to working with you again.
You can call me without business, too.
Hey, hey, hey!
Can't you move them with
a little more care?
Time to move out of this place, too.
Awful!
Shit!
Hi, Eleanor. It's me!
Just got replacement parts for
the Regeneration Device.
Oh, really?
Right, I'll deliver it tomorrow.
Right, absolutely.
Oh, really? Thank you so much!
By the way, you know Karen?
She's no good...