Mongolia
Pub
But, wow... To think we played over
sixty sets and only won three...
Manabu! Come on, drink up.
We've definitely gone down a thorny path.
No, thanks. If I drink any more,
I'll definitely feel it tomorrow.
That's for sure.
Well, if they were like they
were during the Seijoh match,
they could have probably won a few more.
Manabu, are you saying you're
too good for my liquor?
The team's offense was styled around
Hinata and Kageyama's
weirdo quick and their bait routine,
and they executed them well.
No, um...
I'm just kidding!
But we could see the limits of that strategy.
The truth is that they lost to Seijoh,
and that's why they started changing things up.
I know.
They're all developing their own cogs.
There's no way they could beat
the powerhouse schools of Kanto
while they're still incomplete.
But... Once all the cogs fit together...
Hey! Don't think that you can
beat Nekoma that easily.
I certainly didn't mean to say
that it would be easy!
But we'll still do our absolute and win.
You sure talk big now, Sensei.
You, too, Ukai-chan.
Karasuno               Fukurodani
This is the final set...
of our losing streak at these away games.
Let's at least try to
win this one set against
the strongest school at the
training camp, Fukurodani,
before we go home.
Yeah!
I'll show you my progress
from the training camp!
Haikyu!!
Episode 10: "Cogs"
Karasuno               Fukurodani
Let's play!
We're gonna get this one!
Yeah!
All right! Bring it, Karasuno!
Asahi-san, nice serve!
It's a bit off!
Bokuto-san!
Right!
Left, #4!
Tighten up for the straight.
If there's even the slightest
gap, it'll get through.
Out!
A wipe, huh...
So close!
Don't worry about it,
Tsukishima! You were close!
You guys keep getting better
every day, and it's annoying.
Right.
Karasuno               Fukurodani
Left, left!
Whoa, he got it!
But it's off!
A quick from there?!
Even if the receive is a little off,
they confidently pull off a quick.
Their setter's pretty skilled, as well.
Nice serve.
Break it off after the first one!
Their #4 is up front now.
Now I can finally hit up front.
Nice serve!
Nishinoya!
Nice receive!
Nice, monkey!
Give me the last one!
Right now, our front row is in the rotation
where the wall is at its highest.
Make sure you stop the ball!
That's an insane cut shot...
Hitting at a sharp angle against
three blockers is really tricky.
It can be hard on your shoulders
if they're not flexible, too.
All right!
Did you see that, Akaashi?
Hey, did you see my awesome
cut shot right now?
I did. Amazing.
It was pure luck, though!
Bokuto is so annoying.
That's amazing, even if it was luck.
I'd love to hit something like that.
Fukurodani's Bokuto-kun is a real puzzle.
Hey, can I try hitting that again?
Even when he's your opponent,
you kind of want to cheer for him.
I wanna do it again!
The other team's completely
on to you, Bokuto-san.
Though that might be because I think he's
a player on a completely different level.
Oh, crap! My bad.
Then maybe I'll go for a straight.
True...
He might just be a player
who lifts the spirits of both
his teammates and his opponents.
Karasuno               Fukurodani
Yeah!
Tsukishima, nice serve!
A special attack?!
Yup!
Listen up. The best way
to describe this attack
is something born from upsetting the
balance of stillness and motion.
Whoa! Whoa...
There he goes, trying to sound cool again.
Do you have any idea what he's talking about?
I have an idea.
This isn't a move that you use to run away.
You have to have the perfect
timing, the perfect toss,
and look like you're about
to hit the perfect spike.
When everyone thinks you're
about to hit a powerful spike...
More than anything, it works best
when you think you're about to
hit a powerful one yourself.
Leave it to me!
Nice receive!
Just like you're sneering...
Let them have it!
Ah!
Hinata just...
...did a feint?!
When you get a feint in,
there's a completely different sense of
satisfaction than you get from a good spike.
You know how a handful of receivers
will dive for the falling ball?
Yeah.
You're usually eye level with them or above,
but the moment they try to reach
for the ball, miss, then look up...
It's the best feeling.
A feint?!
You're the one who taught it to him.
You actually used your head?
You're gonna get a fever.
You are the only person who doesn't
get to say stuff like that to me.
Hmph! I'm not gonna let them
get any more points.
I don't think that's going to be possible.
Akaashi, back me up once in a while!
Damn that little Shrimpy!
We're not gonna lose!
Karasuno               Fukurodani
#2! #2!
All right!
Ready and...
They all seem to be enjoying themselves.
One touch!
Got it!
I wonder if it's because
of Bokuto-kun's influence.
All right!
Wow, a dump!
Kageyama-kun's doing very well.
He hasn't missed a jump serve today, either.
Yeah, Kageyama today is like...
Calm and collected.
He gives you the same uneasy feeling
as the calm before a storm.
One more, Tsukishima! Nice serve!
I feel like everything I ate this
morning is gone from my stomach,
but I'm still not hungry.
My body's more responsive than usual,
and I can see everyone moving around me.
I can tell how well I'm doing, too.
All right!
The same goes for everyone else.
Nice, Daichi-san!
Is this because of the barbecue?
Hinata's doing well, too.
He's not making any unnecessary movements.
We just might...
...be able to do the new quick.
But...
Asahi-san, nice receive!
Is he planning on doing the new quick?
But if we miss, the good atmosphere
surrounding the team might shatter.
We should just hold off on the new quick
until the chance of success is higher...
You're not gonna do it?
The ball's coming...
And...
It stops.
You've got to be kidding me!
If you're gonna do that,
let me know sooner!
I just felt like we could pull it off! Didn't you?!
What the heck? Is the weirdo
quick making a comeback?
I did, but it was too sudden!
Not quite.
I've got to mentally prepare, and stuff!
That was... different from the quick
they were doing in the beginning.
Who cares?! We actually did it!
The first...
...cog.
Haikyu!!
The ball's coming...
And...
It stops.
Karasuno               Fukurodani
All right!
What the heck was that?!
That was awesome!
Nice, Hinata, Kageyama!
Hey, Akaashi. Was that really that amazing?
Could we do it, too?
That's something we should never try.
Hinata hit it like it was nothing,
but I believe it would take a lot of
practice to hit a toss like that.
Not to mention...
Making a toss float at the point of
impact is an incredible move.
At my skill level, that's impossible.
You're not gonna do it?
He encouraged me again, damn it.
What? You wanna start somethin'?
But that was awesome! So cool!
It stopped right before my eyes!
It was like shoop!
I totally thought it was coming this time,
but when it actually stops right
in front of you, it's sorta scary!
You really are awesome!
Wh-What... You dumbass...
Awesome! So awesome!
Kageyama's expression
right now is indescribable.
You're so awesome, Kageyama!
What happened to his mimetic muscles?
It's not often that Hinata
compliments Kageyama
in such a straightforward way.
I'm glad we actually believed
in this and waited.
Yeah.
Anyway, next time, make sure you—
You did it!
You did it! You did it!
Nice kill, Hinata! Kageyama-kun!
Finally, after three weeks...
Ever since that fight,
Hinata and Kageyama-kun stopped
talking to each other.
But both of them worked
hard on improving.
And, now...
The weirdo duo is back in action!
One more time!
I'm so jealous!
Let me look cool, too!
We can't let them beat us.
Let's keep up!
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't get cocky, you guys!
All right!
Shoyo...
...always does something new.
Maybe if Shrimpy came to our team,
you'd feel a bit more motivated.
I wouldn't be able to be
on the same team as Shoyo.
Huh? Why?
If I'm not able to keep doing new things,
I wouldn't be able to keep up with Shoyo.
No matter how well I were to play hookie,
Shoyo would probably find me out.
Even that genius first-year setter
hesitated for just a second
and Shoyo figured it out.
That'd be exhausting.
Huh...
Then maybe Shrimpy should
just stay as our opponent
and practice partner, and then
you'd feel a bit more motivated.
Why?
Because whenever you watch Shrimpy play,
you have the same expression on
your face as when you're about
to play a new game you just bought.
No, I don't.
And what does that face look like, anyway?
Really excited.
What does that mean? I don't know
what you're talking about.
I don't make that face.
You do.
I do not.
U-Um, Ukai-kun...
Hm?
To be honest, at first glance,
I can't tell the difference between
this and their previous weirdo quick.
Ah...
In the previous quick,
the toss would go right through
Hinata's point of impact.
Point of Impact
Conversely, with this new quick,
they're trying to make it so that
the spiker's highest point of impact
equals the ball's point of arrival.
Once the ball's forward momentum reaches zero,
there's a brief moment that you wouldn't have
if the ball was going straight through.
The difference is ultimately that one moment.
It means that Hinata has more
options while he's in the air.
Oh!
I need to make sure
I bring that geezer to the spring tournament.
I'm gonna show him their quick in person.
Nice receive!
Kill the ball's momentum...
Kill it...
Damn it! I'm visualizing the
same thing as last time, too!
All right!
Oh, my.
Lucky! Lucky!
Did he lose his incredible
concentration from earlier?
Don't worry about it, Kageyama-kun!
Damn it! That pisses me off!
Why?! What else am I supposed to say?!
Well, this isn't something
that happens easily.
And what better time...
...for the senpais to shine!
Karasuno               Fukurodani
One blocker!
One touch!
Got it!
There's that weird sound!
But a double hit wasn't called!
From the libero's toss...
It's the ace's...
...back row attack!
The second...
...cog!
It's an out?! So close!
Sorry, my toss was a bit low. Damn it!
I-It was fine!
I actually think it was my mistake.
You need to be honest when
I mess up, Asahi-san!
Oh, okay...
I-I'd appreciate it if you could
toss the ball up a bit higher.
They changed this much in a week?
I know that!
That's terrifying.
That's it! Keep it up!
We still don't have enough experience
to be able to go head-to-head
with a powerhouse school
while they're on guard.
Got it!
Left! Left!
Karasuno               Fukurodani
Two blockers!
Our team might not be good at winning right now,
Chance ball!
Got it!
but we'll focus on honing our new weapons.
Now!
Spikers from all directions
head up about the same time...
A synchronized attack on first tempo!
Don't let the blockers pinpoint the target!
All of you, jump up and strike
like the toss is going up for you!
All right!
It feels so awesome when
a spike goes through...
He's crying...
All right!
He's babbling...
Well, it's been so long since
I made a spike this awesome.
Damn it! Where do you guys get off
using a synchro attack like that?
Kageyama, nice toss!
Thank you!
Tanaka-kun, nice kill!
Thanks!
Always something new, huh?
Don't look the other way!
The third...
...cog!
That was a synchronized
attack on first tempo...
It went through so smoothly!
Yeah.
Against their three blockers,
our attack, including the back row attack,
had four players advancing at once.
They weren't able to mark all of them.
Is something wrong?
No...
There's just something I want to try out now.
Damn it!
All right!
Karasuno's at the top of their game.
The messy attacks they were trying
on the first day are finally succeeding.
All right!
Karasuno               Fukurodani
Yes, yes, yes!
We're actually neck-and-neck
with Fukurodani at the last part of the game.
Yeah!
That doesn't mean you
should get too confident.
The real battle begins now.
Right!
It's true that we should be on our guard,
but it's also true that all
of the cogs you have created
are now starting to fit together.
Please continue to perfect them
while you're playing this match.
Right!
Also, just as planned,
you haven't been letting
their ace spike too freely.
Though there was that one
ridiculous cut shot...
But that was because Tsukishima
was able to put in one touch.
Oh, right.
If you can keep their #4 back,
we just might be able to do this.
Let's finish this!
Right!
We're having a difficult time,
but let's stay calm.
We can't Karasuno's attacks faze us.
Yeah!
Right.
Bokuto-san? Were you listening?
Wha? Yeah, I was listening.
Come on, let's do this already.
Could that mean...
Karasuno               Fukurodani
All right!
Damn it! I'm sorry!
It was our chance to turn things around...
Don't worry about it!
Nice try, Noya-san!
All right! I'm gonna blow
them away with my serve.
Bokuto, nice serve!
Bokuto-san, stay calm.
I am calm!
This isn't good. He's losing his temper.
All right! Here I go!
Damn it! I'm sorry!
Calm down.
Don't worry about it...
I'm sorry!
Karasuno               Fukurodani
Hey, Karasuno caught up with them again.
Yeah...
Are they actually going to turn
the tables at the last minute?
Their #4 can hit from anywhere.
We're gonna use our serves
and try to keep him in check.
Right.
Crap! I aimed too far for the corner.
You jerk!
Whoa...
It barely made it in. Lucky!
Give it to me!
I'll finish this in one hit!
Seconds
There are few possibilities
when giving a toss to Bokuto-san
while he's a bit angry.
Seconds
A: If he scores normally,
there will be no problems.
All right!
B: If he misses, or he's blocked again,
he may start to feel even worse.
C: If I don't give him a pass...
Hmph! I don't care anymore!
he may become uncooperative.
C is the most annoying.
Bokuto-san!
Three blockers!
All right!
Got it!
One more time, Akaashi!
Here.
All right!
This time, we're gonna stop it!
Ready, and...
Ah...
Gah.
All right!
Karasuno               Fukurodani
Wow, Karasuno turned it around!
Isn't this the first time this week
Karasuno has taken the lead?
It could be.
W-Was that a block?
No... It didn't seem to make it over the net,
so it was a spike miss.
Oh, could this mean...
Aw, man... Is this happening now?
Seriously? Isn't it a bit early?
Wow, already?
It's early...
Jeez, here it comes...
Akaashi...
Don't toss to me anymore!
There it is! Bokuto's emo mode!
What the...
All right.
Huh?
Then please calm down in the time
that I'm not tossing to you.
Does this mean our chance has arrived?
Yeah! We can win this match!
I don't know what's going on,
but their ace doesn't seem to be doing well.
Let's keep it up!
Yeah!
Hinata, we're gonna use that quick again.
I'll give you the toss that you want.
Trust me, and jump.
Yeah!
We're going to take our new weapons
and defeat Fukurodani!
We might finally be able to beat Fukurodani!
Their ace even said not
to toss to him anymore.
I wonder if we'll be able
to eat more meat if we win.
But does that mean we won't
be able to eat any if we lose?
We're gonna win no matter what!
Episode 11: "Above"
Next time on Haikyu!!: "Above."