The Master was as cute as always today...
She truly is an angel from Heaven.
Yo. Welcome back.
Close the door already! I'm in my boxers.
Oh, and the folks will be visiting
Mom's hometown over the weekend.
As of tomorrow, it'll be just the two of us.
You wanna get some food delivered?
A-and so...
When I go back home today,
it will just be me and my brother!
What's so bad about that?
Our house is Hell as it is, but now it will be Hades!
How is Hades different from Hell...?
Hey, you should just stay here tonight!
WHAAAAAAAT?!
I-i-i-is th-th-that okay?
Yeah. I'll have to ask my brother, though.
Sure, that's fine.
Score!
I guess I'll head over to Bomba's place later.
I'm sure he'll be lonely without you around.
Huh? You already knew about this?
Huh? Yeah, he'd mentioned it at the Enoshima aquarium.
That was so long ago!
Well, guess I'll make dinner.
So full...
It was quite filling, wasn't it?
Well, I'm going to Bomba's. I'll be back tomorrow.
U-um, about me being here...
You'd rather I not say anything?
No, it's all right. I get the feeling
he'd be worried otherwise...
'Kay.
Well, I'm off.
See you!
S-see you later.
Master... your brother is kind, isn't he?
Yup!
Kindness like this...
It sort of reminds me of Ebina.
Kirie, let's play a game!
Yes, Master!
It feels a little strange being under someone else's roof...
Well, what's YOUR house like?
It's pretty old and rundown.
Our house, huh...?
Big Brother! I'm back!
What the heck, Kirie? You're so late,
that I was worried you'd gotten lost!
I-I took the long way home.
You don't say.
Big Brother!
Give me a piggyback ride! C'MON!
Sure. No problem.
Kirie...
Kirie!
Th-the Master is calling out to me while she's dreaming!
You're riding a fish...
A fish?! Don't tell me she's
formed a bond with my storybook!
Kirie, you're gonna fall.
Fall?!
Well then, Master, I'll be on my way.
Sure. See you!
Woo-hoo!
That Kirie, I'm tellin' you...
Up until the start of elementary school,
she'd be all like, "Big Brother!"
Are you listening, Taihei?!
Y-yeah. I'm listening...
Are you? Are you listening? You gotta listen!
But now, my Kirie...!
She's gone off and made some great friends,
like Tanukichi and Ebina, and I... I...
Are you listening, Taihei? Well, Taihei?! Taihei!
Are you listening? Hey, are you listening?!
H-hey! I am!
Are you listening, Taihei? Well, Taihei?! Taihei!
Are you listening? Hey, are you listening?!
Taihei?
Don't abandon me!
Taihei!
TAIHEI!
My, my... reading manga indoors on a hot day
with the AC blasting sure is great, huh, Kirie?
Huh?
Kirie?
Huh? What did you just say?
I...
I love you!
They're ending it HERE?!
I can't stand it, Master!
And I bet it'll follow the standard pattern of him
not hearing over the sound of the train!
It's kinda vexing, but you want to root for them because
a romantic comedy needs a happy ending, huh?
Root for them...?
Say goodbye.
Kirie, what's got you yelling all of a sudden?
Th-that vision just now was my dark side...
and that was something I would've said up till recently!
It looks like those two are a couple now!
So, for our next girls' day out...
If you two start dating...
What kind of boy would you like to...?
Umaru sure is cute, huh?
She's got a great bod, and she's smart too.
And good at sports!
She's perfect!
"Umaru"? That's MISS Umaru to you, punk!
I'm so embarrassed!
Kirie, what's got you crouching all of a sudden?
I didn't want to admit that I just can't get used
to being part of a community.
All I would ever do is despise the people around me.
Master.
Huh?
I've... made an enemy I must defeat.
Kirie?
M-Master!
I... cannot root for love!
Huh?!
She sure gets emotionally involved with her manga...
You don't have to get that worked up about it, you know.
Wait a minute.
Kirie wants to be a storybook author, so maybe
that's why she's taking this manga so personally.
In that case, I must give her
a definitive answer, as her Master!
Kirie.
Y-yes?
There is no need to overthink this.
Only one thing is important...
you should just believe in what you want to believe!
What I... believe in?
Huh? Kirie!
H-hello.
What's going on? You're in your school uniform ...
There is something that I would ask you!
Huh?
You like Taihei Doma, don't you?
Whaaaaat?!
It was obvious from your reactions the other day.
I-I...
That is what I wish to discuss with you.
I have decided on something this day...
Huh?
You want to root for them because
a romantic comedy needs a happy ending, huh?
I shall root for your love with all my strength!
Whaaaat?!
You should just believe in what you want to believe!
And what I believe in... is my Master.
U-um...
O..okay!
Please leave this to me!
My little sister, Umaru...
is renowned for her beauty.
She's kind and smart, and graced with many talents.
She's loved by young and old, men and women.
She's flawless, the perfect high school girl.
Well... that's what everyone seems to think.
This is Umaru when she's at home.
My lazy, dried fish of a sister... a himouto.
HEY! Get up, Umaru!
Gah! What, what's going on?
Now look here, Umaru:
summer vacation isn't just for lazing around!
It's a time for you to do and experience things
you don't usually have the chance to at school.
Are you listening?
Don't you worry, Big Brother.
I may not look it, but I've changed.
See?
I always read Jumpu, but today I got Jumpu SQUARE!
Still, I'm not so sure what "Square"
is supposed to mean...
This is not good. I have to at least get her outside!
Oh, yeah...
Umaru! There's a fireworks festival today!
You want to go?
There will be lots of big, beautiful fireworks!
Huh?
The first thing is to try to get her
to an event that she'd like.
Nah, no thanks. There's too many people,
and insects, and it'll be hot.
This isn't working.
Man, I was thinking we could buy some food
from the stalls there...
Stalls!
I'm not buying all that! How greedy can you be?!
This is no time for sitting around! Let's go, Big Brother!
The festival's at NIGHT!
Don't sweat the small stuff.
Umaruuun!
She really is a different person outside...
We should invite the others. Let's start with Ebina!
Oh, so she wanted to go with her friends?
Put simply...
You invite Taihei to the fireworks festival.
That will create just the right mood.
Fireworks?
M..mood?!
Wow...
It's great, isn't it, Ebina?
Oh, sorry.
I-it's fine!
N-n-no!
That's too embarrassing!
What are you talking about?
We've already been to the beach together, right?
Huh?
I wonder who that is...
Taihei and Umaru!
H-hello, Umaru, Taihei.
Ah, Kirie. You're visiting Ebina, huh? Perfect timing.
What do you say we all go to the fireworks festival?
The fireworks festival, you say? Of course I will go!
I'm glad. Now we can all go together!
Shba!
Well, come on in, everyone.
Huh? You don't want to go yet?
There are preparations to be made! And you too, Taihei.
Huh? Me?
Yes, indeed! A fireworks festival
means one must wear a summer kimono!
Well, let us depart!
Yeah, let's go.
No reaction!
You still have a lot to learn, Big Brother.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Indeed, the stalls!
The stalls!
There are so many!
We shall visit them all!
What can I get you all?
Huh?! No, I can pay for myself.
You don't have to worry about that today.
O-okay...
Keep it up, Ebina.
Shbababababa!
Shugaan!
Okay, let's sit here and watch.
This is an especially large star mine, indeed!
Amazing!
They sure make a lot of sound, huh?
Wow...!
So pretty.
Impressive fireworks, indeed!
I may not look it, but I've changed.
We should invite the others.
My younger sister is a "himouto," but...
while some things don't change,
little by little, some things do.
Hey! Get up, Umaru.
G'morning...
It's time to go to school. Summer vacation's over.
Don't keep Ebina waiting.
Huh? Do you have the day off today?
Yeah, to make up for lost vacation time.
Are you gonna go somewhere?
Hmm... to go buy groceries, I guess.
Ah! Then buy some potato chips!
Yeah, sure.
Thanks, Big Brother!
It's lunchtime!
And we shall all eat together!
Oh, Umaru, the teacher was looking for you earlier.
Huh? What for?
To give you your certificate from that awards ceremony.
Oh, yeah. It always takes a while
to actually get your award, huh?
It's been on display in front
of the staff office this whole time.
I heard that the last time two people got awards
at the same time was 10 years ago!
Hm? 10 years ago? That might have been my brother.
Huh?!
Apparently, he always had
the top grades in his school year.
That's what Bomba said.
This brother and sister have some impressive specs!
Oh, really? Your brother is amazing!
I like Umaru's brother, indeed!
This bread is cheap! Maybe I'll make cream stew today.
After all, he is SO kind-hearted!
He brought souvenirs and bought us
so many things at the festival!
That was a shock!
What's more, he's kind
and makes you feel at ease somehow.
Yes. That he does...
Ah! No, Ebina, I was just thinking,
I'd like a brother like that!
Y-yeah.
Really, that's all!
Y-yeah!
I have to go to the principal's office,
so you all go on ahead.
Very well!
Okay. See you later, Umaru.
U-until tomorrow.
Taihei Doma sure was something else.
"Taihei the Demon," they called him.
Takes you back, doesn't it? He was an excellent student.
Your brother is amazing!
I like Umaru's brother, indeed!
And makes you feel at ease somehow.
He was an excellent student.
Big Brother!
Looks like he's just come back from shopping.
I know! I'll scare him from behind!
This is sure to give him a shock!
Here goes!
Biiig Brothe-!
Big Brother!
Huh?!
Um, I think you've got the wrong person...
Huh?
B-Big Brother?
Oh, Umaru. Welcome back.
Huh? I feel like I've seen this girl somewhere before...
That's it, at the awards ceremony.
She's the girl from the AP class.
Oh, I see. She's a friend of yours, huh?
W-well, we go to the same school
but I wouldn't say we're friends...
I don't like the outdoors... I want to go inside!
Oh. You want to come in?
Huh?!
Just make yourself at home.
U-um, your name is Kongo, isn't it?
What brings you over today?
This is the first time we've talked, isn't it?
There's no need to keep up appearances,
so just lounge around as always.
Huh?
Gah! She knows about me!
Sensei is always lounging around.
Always lounging...
Wh-who is this girl?
I've never even talked to her before,
but she's fixated on Big Brother...
She's way too mysterious!
Big Brother is MY big brother.
Huh?
He's my big brother.
I do feel like I know her from somewhere...
I heated up some bread. Would you like some?
Thanks very much.
Ah! My bread!
What is it, Umaru? Ah! You've eaten it already?
This girl ate it all! In, like, a second!
There's no way a little girl like this
could eat THREE of them.
It's true!
H-Hikari?
It is! It's Hikari!
You're Kanau's younger sister, aren't you?
You sure have gotten bigger!
Huh? You know her!
You remember that girl
from when we went to Hamamatsu?
That was my boss, Kanau.
And Hikari is her younger sister.
It's been a REALLY long time since I've seen her,
but I remember now.
B-Big Brother...
No, no, no, no, no no no! That's MY big brother!
Well, I'll be leaving now.
Will you be okay? Do you want me to walk you back?
No, I'll be fine.
I've got some cream stew that will be ready soon...
I-I'll come back again sometime.
You will?!
B-bye.
Yeah.
Say hi to Kanau for me.
I will.
It is! It's Hikari!
Why does she call you "Big Brother"?
I'm not sure... she did used to call me that, though.
He's my big brother.
Why did she suddenly show up today?
Huh? To hang out with you, right?
I've never hung out with her! That girl's just fishy!
It had been so long since I'd seen my big brother
and we were able to talk. I'm so happy!
No, no, no! Like I said, he's MY big brother!
If you're determined to call him that, though,
then you can call me "Big Sis"!
I refuse.
That was fast!