Welcome.
Man, don't come to show off
every time you buy a new slave.
That's not it.
Another young girl?
You really are a lolicon, huh?
Wrong!
Master, I'm hungry.
Want a bite?
Yeah, thanks!
Hey, Filo.
It's fine, missy.
How big a bite could she take, anyway?
Time to dig in!
That was so-so, I guess.
The Rising of the Shield Hero
A New Comrade
So, what's her deal?
According to the slave merchant,
filolials have a king or
queen leading each flock.
Isn't that just a myth?
Those kings and queens are highly
skilled at transforming,
and they blend into the flocks by
disguising themselves as normal filolials.
And they can transform into humans, too?
That's nuts.
What's more, it turns out they need
a special crest to be tamed.
I hadn't budgeted for that.
Things got crazy while
giving her that crest.
Filo started resisting with all her might.
And that was at Level 19.
Who knows how strong she'll
be at Level 70 or something?
And? You didn't come here just to
show off this filolial queen, right?
Sell us some clothes.
Clothes?
If she rips them apart each
time she transforms,
I'll go broke in the blink of an eye.
There are outfits made for
transforming species, aren't there?
Those are special. I ain't got any.
Go see a dressmaker.
But I guess you can't have her walking
around in public looking like that.
Take this. Another customer left it here.
Wow, cute!
She's cute, like an angel!
Wait, she has wings on her back,
so maybe she really is one?
Am I cute, Master?
Don't ask me.
You mustn't be like that, Father.
Fath—?!
Compliments help girls grow ever cuter.
Master, are you my father?
No, I'm your owner.
What about Raphtalia-oneechan, then?
She's like my daughter.
I am not!
Anyway, that doesn't matter.
It doesn't?
We want clothes that don't rip when you
transform and can go back to normal later.
Oh, that's what you're looking for?
Did you bring magic thread?
Magic thread?
Transforming clothes are always woven using
thread made out of the wearer's own mana.
So, they're custom made?
Indeed!
If you give me the magic threads,
I'll make you the cutest dress ever!
Magic thread, huh?
You certainly could spin it here,
but not right now. My magic
gemstone broke recently.
Is that gemstone expensive?
It is, but the bigger issue is
that it's always in short supply.
Well, that's a problem.
I'll talk to people and try to
procure one as soon as possible.
Could you give me some time?
Hey.
What is this?
A crystal ball. It measures
one's magical affinity.
Let me check yours, too.
No outfit for a while, huh?
Filo has wind affinity!
I blow away all the enemies!
My job is draw the carriage.
Well, she's in a good mood.
To where my Master says!
If I find the spear guy,
I'll send him flying with a full-power kick!
It'll be a while before we get her clothes.
In the meantime, let's travel
around and make some money.
That trade pass we got from the
village lord will come in handy.
Master, there's someone up ahead.
Is something the matter?
P-Please, give me a ride on your carriage.
Huh?
I need to get this medicine to the
village past the mountain at once!
Filo, how long will it take
to get there at full speed?
Not long.
But we can get there even
sooner without the carriage.
I'll take you there for one silver.
But I already spent all my
money on the medicine...
You can pay me in goods,
or even pay me later.
Don't you dare try to
weasel out of it, though.
Th-That would be fine.
Give me the reins, Raphtalia.
Here.
Thank you.
I don't need your gratitude.
Just make sure to pay me.
Go, Filo!
Right-o!
Halt! Pay the toll!
I'll come back for it later!
Mother, I got you the medicine.
You go boil some water.
I'll give her the medicine.
But...
Relax. I won't charge you.
Potion Enhance
Why, thank you.
Mother!
The medicine's helping already?
Yes. The pain went away in an instant.
Thank you.
Um... What kind of magic spell did you use?
Quit asking questions you don't need to ask.
That aside...
Oh, here. This should be
worth one silver in total.
That works.
Later.
Thank you so very much!
On top of selling goods, I can even
provide transport for people.
Traveling trade may actually be
more profitable than I thought.
I can't believe I get to ride with
Our Savior of the Heavenly Fowl.
"Our Savior of the Heavenly Fowl"?
You've become quite famous
around these parts.
"Traveling in a carriage drawn by
the god of domesticated birds,
Our Savior crosses the land to treat
the sick with his special medicine!"
Am I a god?
Hey! Didn't Naofumi-sama tell you
not to talk with strangers around?
Sorry.
She can talk, too? That's the
god of domesticated birds for you!
She's not a god or anything.
Naofumi-sama, there are
people blocking the path.
Whoa, stop right there!
Strange bird you've got there.
We heard an accessory seller
was hitching a ride with you.
We know you're in there!
He was a client with baggage, huh?
Quietly hand him over, and we'll
spare your lives, at least.
You mean you'll take
everything but our lives?
You're a sharp one, lad.
That girl's pretty hot for a demi-human.
Looks like we can have
ourselves some fun tonight.
Naofumi-sama, may I cut him down?
Not like you'd listen to me if I said no.
Me too!
Don't bother.
We've got a class-upgraded bodyguard.
We're counting on you, Sensei!
Class-upgraded?
Yet another unfamiliar term.
If nothing else, I can tell
he won't be easy pickings.
If only I could use support
magic right now...
As source of thy power, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature and
conceal me in a haze.
Hide Mirage!
Fast Tornado!
Some other trader told us to
mug the guy riding with you
because he was carrying
a bunch of nice stuff!
One of my own sold me out, huh?
Well? What do we do with these guys?
Usually, you'd hand them
over to the local guards.
Aren't you the Shield Hero?
It was obvious since you had
no weapons, only a shield.
"We're unlucky adventurers who were
attacked by the cruel Shield Hero!"
Is that what you'll tell the guards?
Exactly.
They'll surely take our word
over the Shield Hero's.
Then you leave me no choice.
You'll have to die.
Filo, are you hungry?
I am!
Food!
She's an omnivore, you see.
And she'll gulp anything down in one go.
Aren't you Our Savior of the Heavenly Fowl?
Do you really want to commit murder?!
I'm no savior, and I need to
act in my best interests.
You must've killed plenty of people so far.
Just consider this your turn, and give up.
W-Wait, please! Anything but our lives!
Got it.
I'll spare your lives, at least.
However...
We're looting the bandits?
Doesn't this make us more
evil than the criminals?
You're wrong there.
They offered up everything they had to
purchase their lives from Our Savior.
He's treating even lives as merchandise.
Sir Hero's a shining example of the
trader's spirit that's so rare nowadays!
I'm pretty sure this is just intimidation.
You two... Less talk, more work.
Also, how are you going to compensate
me for all this trouble you caused?
I offer you all the knowledge
and connections I possess.
Knowledge and connections?
Yes. I've taken a real liking to you.
The first things the accessory
seller taught me
were how to process precious metals,
use the tools required,
craft gems, and imbue them with mana.
I even managed to pick up some spells,
thanks to getting a feel for mana.
And so, I gained a new
business venture: crafting gemstones.
Then I gained an in with
the traders' grapevine,
where I heard rumors of the other heroes.
Apparently, Motoyasu saved a famine-stricken
village to the southwest
by introducing a legendary crop.
I bet that goddamn slut put him up to it.
Ren's apparently southeast,
looking for vicious monsters to slay.
I even heard a rumor that
said he took down a dragon.
But the information regarding Itsuki,
the Bow Hero, was all over the place.
Some said he's training up in the mountains,
and some said he went into a
dungeon on a quest for treasure.
There were even some tall tales, like him
joining another country's resistance,
but none of them were credible.
That seller certainly did provide us
with ample knowledge and connections.
But one thing he offered helped
me more than any other.
Yes, this deed is genuine.
I'm amazed that grumpy money-grubber
actually gave this to you.
Anyway, if there's a gemstone you want,
I can arrange getting it for you.
At a discount, of course.
What would you like?
I want the gemstone used
to make magic threads.
I'm amazed you learned where to
find that gemstone so quickly.
It's not all good news.
It seems to be in a rather dicey location.
Naofumi-sama...
This temple was once a notoriously
evil alchemist's base of operations.
I never knew there was a tunnel here.
According to the mining chief,
nobody's dared approach this place
since some monsters nested here.
Stay on your toes.
It's empty.
That's ancient writing.
"We pray this seed never
makes it out of here.
It is a horribly twisted
manifestation of our wish
for nobody to starve."
Looks like some bandits already
released it into the world, though.
Master, there's a path down this way.
Let's go.
Hey, Filo! What are you doing?
Hurry up!
Oh, Master!
You see...
For crying out loud.
If you won't listen to me,
then I don't need you anymore.
Stop.
What is that?
A monster footprint.
It must be a rather large one.
But we have to keep going until
we get what we're here for.
Just be care—
Naofumi-sama?!
Stay calm!
Hey, witch! What's going on?
I'm sick and tired of being
Naofumi-sama's slave.
I only pretended to become his slave again
so I could kill him with my own hands.
I can stab him clean
through from behind now.
Don't let the voices mislead you!
The witch?
The monsters here provoke you by saying
the last things you want to hear,
in the last voices you want saying them!
How nasty is that?
Master is my food!
Hey, something cut me!
Do something about this!
As source of thy power, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature and
restore our sight!
Fast Anti-Bind!
If we can see them...
Filo!
I'm gonna blow you away!
Are you all okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I don't think this will come in handy.
Voice Gengar Shield (Bat Form)
Let's keep going.
You won't abandon me, right, Master?
I've got money riding on you.
I won't get rid of you easily.
Naofumi-sama...
Don't worry.
Naofumi-sama would never say mean things
like those hallucinations you heard.
Okay, I'll believe in him.
It's nothing. Never mind.
Something's in there.
That's the gemstone.
Yeah, but...
That's a nue.
It's on the small side, but still dangerous.
This'll be rough.
The gemstone's right there,
but we can't get it.
We're going!
Those two!
Cover us, please!
Zweit Fire Blast!
Naofumi-sama!
Can I hold it off?
Don't!
Hey!
That was close...
We need to avoid that at all costs.
But then how do we attack it?
Watch out, Raphtalia!
It can see her?
No. It hears her.
It's really sensitive to sound.
Sound?
Filo! Yell in here as loud as you can!
Okay!
Everyone, cover your ears!
Now!
Zweit Fire Blast!
We won!
Are you unhurt?
Yeah!
You?
I'm fine.
Don't charge in so recklessly.
But...
What if you got a scar that never faded?
You're worried about my...
Are we clear?
Y-Yes.
Wow, so pretty!
It really is beautiful!
This is making me tired...
It's because you're converting
your mana into thread.
Endure it for just a while longer.
I'll give you a snack once you finish.
A yummy one? Then I'll keep going!
How do I look, Master?
Very nice.
Yay! Thank you, Master!
I mean, sure, she looks cute...
Doesn't she?!
I did my very best to bring out every
last bit of Filo-chan's angelic charm!
I used white as the base color,
to go with her wings.
I added in plenty of frills as
a nod to her feathers, too.
And since it'd contrast
best with her blonde hair,
I went with blue for the ribbon!
R-Right...
The monster crest and magic outfit
add up to 340 silvers in total.
You'd better work hard to pay it off.
Yeah! I'll do my best!
Don't suddenly transform indoors!
The ribbon looks oh-so-cute
even in her monster form!
Don't you agree?
You agree, don't you, Father?
Don't ask me!
The Savior of the Heavenly Fowl