Huh? A person I love?
Yeah. Do you have someone special like that?
Um...
My dad, I guess?
Uh, that's not what I mean.
What about you, Rifana-chan?
Do you have someone like that?
You see...
I wanna marry someone like
one of the legendary heroes.
Like the Shield Hero?
I wanna meet him, too.
Look!
P-Please!
Spare my life!
After you killed so many demi-humans
in your underground chamber,
you think you can beg for your life?!
You can't be...
One of those villagers
I kept enslaved underground?
One of those demis?!
The Rising of the Shield Hero
Raphtalia
W-Wait!
You lot would've died like dogs in the
wild if I hadn't taken you in back then!
Shut your mouth!
Do you really think I've forgotten
the atrocities you committed?
I haven't!
I could never forget!
I was wrong!
I-I'll apologize!
I'm so sorry!
This scumbag took Rifana-chan and...
No! Please don't!
Raphtalia...
Will killing him help you get closure?
It's not just with the sword, right?
Haven't you grown stronger in other ways?
You're a terrible person who put so many
demi-humans through hell, then killed them.
I can never forgive you.
But if I kill you now,
I won't be any different from you.
So I won't take your life.
You will live and atone for
the sins you have committed.
Confound you...
Know your place, scum!
Curse you!
Demis don't deserve to live.
Idol-sama!
Idol-sama is dead!
Retreat!
Onee-chan, are you okay?
Raphtalia-san!
Naofumi-sama, I...
It's not your fault.
But I...
It's okay.
Sir Shield Hero...
Thank you. You saved me.
Reichnott! Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
First Aqua Heal.
Let's take this chance to run.
Yeah.
But first...
Idol imprisoned his demi-human
slaves underground,
and tortured them.
Why do you know that?
Because I was one of them.
It's not too late to turn back, you know?
There's no need. I'll be fine.
Always keep smiling and
play nice with the villagers.
And smile even more in hard times.
You must smile and help everyone
around you smile, too.
Dad... Mom...
I won't cry anymore.
Please watch over me.
Listen to me, everyone!
We're still alive!
And we'll keep on living!
As survivors, let's rebuild our village,
so it's the way it used to be!
I'm sure that's what everyone
who died would want!
Yeah!
Raphtalia-chan's right!
Yep! Let's do our best!
Yeah.
Let's rebuild our village!
Raphtalia-chan...
Your parents died, right? Um...
Aren't you sad?
I am sad.
But I don't want to cry.
Dad said I should keep smiling in hard times.
If you're trying so hard
with a smile on your face,
I should do my best, too.
Yeah.
Hey.
Look.
Help from the capital?
Finally!
Get on already.
Quit wasting time.
Raphtalia-chan!
Get in, brat!
Are you okay, Mel-chan?
Yes.
Raphtalia was trapped in a place like this?
It's easy to see what was happening here.
Just thinking about it makes me sick!
Damn it!
You bore me!
Scream and cry more!
Rifana-chan...
Eat up, Rifana-chan.
Don't worry. I'm sure the
Shield Hero will save us.
Rifana-chan?
You're burning up!
Hey, do you remember that flag?
It was a symbol of how we demi-humans
were allowed to build a village for ourselves.
Yeah... Yeah.
I remember.
I wanna see it again.
I'm sure you can!
Yeah...
Raphtalia-chan...
What?
I wanna go back to the village.
Yeah, let's...
Let's go home to our village together.
I wanna go home.
Is that...
I'm sorry I couldn't make it any better.
No!
I'm so happy. Thank you.
Rifana-chan?
Hey.
Out.
You're being sold off to a slave merchant.
What about Rifana-chan?
Tell me!
She's the only one being sold.
Get going.
What about Rifana-chan?!
She's done for.
...le... when times are tough...
Huh?
How do I smile again?
There's a survivor!
Let's go, Raphtalia!
You'll be all right now.
Naofumi!
Over here, too!
There's someone over here, too!
Keel-kun?
Keel-kun!
Why are you here?
Who... are you?
You were brought here, too?
I'm so glad you're alive!
Who are you, lady?
Did you forget? It's me, Raphtalia.
Raphtalia-chan?
No way.
You can't be her.
S-Stay away!
Do you remember?
That one time, you went
diving and nearly drowned,
and Sadeena-oneechan had to save you.
You ate a poisonous mushroom and ended
up with an upset stomach another time.
You were in pain and begged me not to tell anyone.
And when I said we should rebuild
the village after the Wave,
you were the first one to agree.
That made me so happy.
Raphtalia-chan...
It's really you!
Thank you.
I'm so grateful that you're still alive.
Who are they?
I'm with the Shield Hero right now.
What? The... Shield Hero?
Yeah. The Shield Hero is here to save you.
Let me see your wounds.
He's real...
The Shield Hero really exists!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I see...
Rifana-chan would've been
so happy to see him.
Keel-kun...
Where is Rifana-chan?
Is she also...
Say, Raphtalia-chan.
Do you think the Shield
Hero will come to save us?
I know he will!
I wanna see him soon.
See him and...
And?
Have him make me his wife.
Master...
I can't believe such monstrous
deeds were being done in Melromarc.
Melty-sama...
As much as I hate to say it, similar
things happen all across this country.
What?!
That's why we needed Seyaette.
But now...
Melty, I need you to do something for me.
Return to the capital
and admonish the king for
his unjust treatment.
Ordinarily, I would go myself, but...
I'm sorry I took so long.
Raphtalia, who is that?
Rifana-chan.
She was gentler and more graceful than me,
and she'd always say she wanted to
meet you... meet the Shield Hero.
Let's give her and the
others a proper send-off.
They can't rest in peace
in a place like this.
What's wrong?
I hate myself.
I couldn't protect anyone.
Before meeting you, I was powerless.
I couldn't do anything.
If only I was stronger,
I could've kept everyone safe!
They could have...
You did protect us!
If you hadn't come to help,
I probably would've died here.
And the only reason everyone hung in
there without losing hope was your smile!
We decided to keep smiling,
no matter how bad things got!
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Keel-kun.
I can't smile like I used to.
I mean...
I ended up killing someone.
You're wrong.
It was all wrong.
Everything I've done so far...
It was all a mistake!
That's not it!
Raphtalia...
I don't have the right to walk beside you!
You did nothing wrong!
If I hadn't met you,
I would've run from this world
without ever trusting anyone.
It's because you believed in me
back then that I'm here right now,
that I got to meet Filo and Melty.
Yeah. It can't have been a mistake.
I mean, you were so tiny,
and now you've met the Shield Hero,
become such a cool lady,
and come back to save us!
Look.
You were the one who kept those kids alive.
Naofumi-sama...
Stop crying.
I'm sure Rifana-chan's happy she
got to meet the Shield Hero, too.
From now on, we have to protect them.
Make sure nobody goes through
what you and she did.
Isn't that why you fought
with me for all this time?
Together with me, the Shield Hero?
Yes!
Lucky you.
You're in the Shield Hero's party.
You must be jealous, right?
You jerk!
I'll always be watching.
Okay.
And one day, let's go back
to a village with that flag.
Yeah!
Rifana-chan,
I promise I'll bring back
the flag from those days...
Together with Naofumi-sama.
What's happening there?
In order to take you back,
demi-humans from your
domain are rioting here.
Go let them know you're all right.
I will.
What?
Look there, Master!
That guy's still alive?
O Supreme God,
grant me the power to rend the Devil asunder!
No... Don't tell me...
What's wrong?
The heroes of the past built that
stone monument to seal a monster away.
Is he trying to release that seal?!
Go on and destroy everything!
You are free from your confines now, beast!
Bring divine judgment down
upon the Devil of the Shield!
Nobody can stop me now!
If I can kill the Devil of the Shield,
I will be eternally blessed by God!
Filolial Queen