My girlfriend found my porn.
Western porn, of all things.
K-Kana-san, you came here
to study for the exam, right?
"Study," my ass!
You were thinking about doing this all along!
Th-That's not entirely true.
Wh-Why don't you just do it
if you're so desperate?
Romantic Comedy
I-Isn't it a bit early for that?
When you don't try to do anything.
We haven't even kissed.
Because you never set the mood for that—
You scared, punk?
I am Chiaki, proud son of Keiko and Manabu!
Then come forth, I shall prey upon your neck!
O-Okay...
Kana's got pretty big boobs.
I wanna squeeze 'em.
I can, right?
Okay, here goes.
Hey, we haven't kissed.
Wait, never mind, forget I said that!
No, no, do it in order!
In order!
What do people do in this situation?
Oh, whatever, start with a kiss.
Does my breath stink?
My lips might be chapped.
I'm not sweaty, am I?
Which underwear am I wearing?
Wh-What if I fart?
Crap, shoulda plucked my nipple hair.
Sorry, gotta poop.
You just pooped!
Quit trying to get away!
N-No, I just wanted to get prepared!
Besides, you're not supposed
to rush this stuff.
I really hate the whole
"we kissed, so now we're dating" thing.
K-Kana-san, a lady ought not be
so quick to show her skin.
Shut up, you idiot.
It's not like I just want to kiss, either.
I, like, want to be closer to you.
So I want to learn more about you,
a-and I want you to know me better, too.
Kana...
Don't look at me!
You wanted me to know you better...
Shut up, you perv.
Turn the lights off.
Just so you know,
I don't have that nice of a body.
And I didn't get a chance to shower today,
so I might be sweaty and stuff.
You were super hot when I caught
a glimpse just now, though.
You idiot!
I just complimented you!
You poop!
Poop, poop, poop, poop, poop!
I haven't prepared for this stuff at all.
I-It's fine.
It's not fine!
I'll go buy some.
No.
My mom made me bring some
on my way out today.
Oh.
So we're all set, then.
Hey, Chiaki...
I love you.
I love you, too, Kana.
Hey, Chiaki, I brought snacks for Kana-ch—
Oh boy, pardon me.
I'll leave snacks here.
Have some when you're done.
Onee-chan, don't go upstairs right now!
Sorry.
Nah.
My family's like that, too.
Can we keep going?
Yeah.
Let's do that.
Remember to take your pill?
Need to take mine?
Dude, Mom!
Class 3-8
The student president caught me smoking,
and he confessed to me.
And he's making me quit
as a condition for dating.
Damn, I want a smoke.
Wait, why am I actually quitting?
Let's Find Out
I never even said I'd go out with him, did I?
Hello, Kaji-san.
What did you need from me—
Akagi.
Listen up, and listen well.
You might have my weakness—
Weakness?
How you get shy when praised?
No!
My smoking thing!
I never said I'd go out with you!
Ah.
Let's make it official.
Hell no.
One kiss doesn't mean we're dating—
We kissed twice.
Shut up!
That wasn't even my first kiss or anything!
Don't think you can win a girl that easily.
What do you want me to do, then?
Wh-Why are you even, you know...
Love you more, you say?
All right, come.
Don't "come" me!
You don't even like me, do you?!
I can't say I don't.
Liar.
You don't know anything about me.
True, I don't know much about you.
See? I knew it—
Other than what I've seen at school.
You don't have many friends.
You're always sleeping in class.
You could go home after school,
but you stay and smoke.
I didn't catch you by coincidence.
You've been on my mind for a while.
You thought I'd let you do me if you asked?
Yes.
I thought you would sleep
with anyone who talked to you.
And I was right.
Had I been a player,
you would have been played.
Although, I do prefer thicker women.
I knew it!
Student president or not,
you're still just a horny bastard inside.
Yes, if I could sleep with you, I would.
I see.
Then why don't we—
So I wanted to take you for myself
before anyone else did.
D-Dude, what are you talking about?
I want to make you mine.
Shut up!
Why would you...
Why me?
Probably because I like you.
Wh-What do you mean, "probably"?!
I really don't know.
I've never liked anyone before.
But if this isn't love, then what is it?
How would I know?!
Let's find out.
If it's all right with you, of course.
I won't force you into it.
I...
Well? Want to go out?
N-No, but I...
You what?
I-I mean...
Say yes.
It looked so fluffy.
Minagawa-san confessed to me.
But I've been putting off answering
for months now.
I tried approaching slowly,
but it ran away when I got right near it.
I really need to give her an answer.
The Answer
Hey, Furuya-kun, I've waited long enough.
Can you tell me now?
W-We can talk about that later.
Your username.
So, do you have an answer for me?
I can't tell if you're serious
or just playing me, Minagawa-san.
Sorry, I'll ask seriously this time.
What's your answer?
Well, I...
So that's a no, huh?
All right.
I guess you aren't interested.
No, it's not that I'm not interested,
I just can't bring myself to answer.
I can't tell if you're serious
or playing me either, Furuya-kun.
I didn't mean—
Forget it.
I give up.
Class is starting.
See you.
I didn't think she would give up so easily.
Hang on.
What if she's acting,
and she's waiting for me to stop her?
Idiot!
This is my fault.
I made her wait so long.
I'll try talking to her again later.
She must be feeling at least some remorse.
No, that's not it.
She hasn't given up, she's lost interest.
I can't blame her. I'm so indecisive.
Minagawa Yuki
Why are you staring at me?
(¬_¬)
How could she tell?
Wait, I thought she was angry at me.
Why are you staring at me?
(¬_¬)
I'm not trying to!
Huh?! You were actually staring??
LOL
Just kidding.
I felt like teasing you a little.
I'm not in any hurry for an answer.
Besides...
Actually,
never mind lol
"Actually, never mind."
Thank goodness!
He was actually staring at me!
My friend handed me a love letter.
To be delivered to...
Sugawara-kun.
Yeah?
You're Beautiful
Sorry to do this during exams,
but we need to talk.
Do you have time after school?
Totally!
I totally do!
Anything for you, Takano.
He really is a nice person.
A letter? For me?
Yeah.
T-Thanks.
I never expected this from you.
No, that's from Yoshinaga-san.
Oh, really?
I'm flattered.
And she wanted me to ask you for your answer.
Don't worry about it.
This is more stressful
for you than anyone else.
You're so nice, Sugawara-kun.
Can you tell Yoshinaga I said sorry?
There's someone I like.
Really?
Are you going to confess?
I did,
but she didn't notice.
That actually happens, huh?
Aren't you going to try again?
Well, apparently, I'm just a nice guy to her.
She and I sound similar.
What would you do
if I confessed to you, then?
No way, jeez.
I don't know anything about that stuff.
You wouldn't have any fun dating me.
I think my crush would say the same thing.
Really?
She sounds like a pain.
What should I do?
Maybe you should be a bit proactive.
Try hugging her, maybe?
You know, like in dramas,
where the guy hugs the girl
and shouts that he loves her?
W-Wouldn't it bother you
if someone did that to you?
Of course it would.
It'd be creepy.
I know.
But you're a nice person,
so I might be okay with it.
Does that help?
We should go home.
Let's go.
We need to study for exams.
Y-You're right.
So, I've decided to give up on confessing.
Huh? Why?
I'd rather not end up getting friend-zoned.
You wouldn't know what to do
if I confessed to you, right?
But I'm not the person you like.
You said it would bother you,
so it's probably hopeless.
Should I not have said that?
Nah, it was helpful.
About my answer to Yoshinaga...
I'll turn her down myself tomorrow.
Really?
She had to go through you, but she had the
courage to confess, and I want to honor that.
Well, good luck on exams.
Yeah.
Sugawara-kun's so kind.
He's such a nice person.
If it were me...
I like you!
Not that that would ever happen.
Next episode: Watching You From Afar.
Watching You From Afar