Hmm...
Hey, are we really going...
Tohya?
Hmm...
Takoyaki!
You can eat later.
We still have things to buy.
You're so mean, Umeko...
You promised not to call me by that name.
Now, let's go.
What's wrong?
Akihabara really has changed...
But it's only been a week, hasn't it?
Since that conference.
If you're that insistent,
why don't you tell us specifically
what Log Horizon has in mind?
Grab It in Your Hand
Grab It in Your Hand.
I have two primary goals...
My proposal to restore life to the people here,
and to protect them, is as I've explained.
As for specifics, we'll begin with
bringing life back to the area.
Marie?
As I believe some of you are aware,
we've been running a restaurant
called Crescent Moon.
The secret behind its popularity...
You can do it, Marielle.
The secret of how we make
food with actual flavor...
I shall now reveal it.
This is the trick...
You get normal ingredients,
and you cook them just as in the real world.
And the cook must have a subclass set to chef.
And if their cooking skill isn't
high enough, they'll fail.
That's all.
The trick is that there is no trick.
So you just cook it yourself,
instead of using the command menu?
That's all?
I believe this discovery has a number of implications.
Without it, I never would have
thought to gather you all here.
Michitaka?
Yes...
In conjunction with the Roderic
Merchant Guild and Shopping Street 8,
our guild has successfully created a steam engine.
A prototype, to be precise.
It still has many flaws,
but it's a proof of concept.
It's amazing you did that in
fewer than twelve hours.
Wait... What does that mean, exactly?
It means the secret you've just learned about
cooking is not, in fact, limited to cooking.
When it was a game, Elder Tale
had no steam engines.
However,
a player with sufficient crafting skill
can take this world's materials and,
without using the command menu,
but with their own hands...
They can invent things that weren't
originally part of this world.
This is a Steam Engine!!
So now, there'll be a rush to invent things.
And that means a demand for new products.
And purchasing them will require earning money.
That will get the economy running...
In light of this,
we, the three major crafting guilds,
support the creation of the
Round Table Conference!
That's three...
Part of the reason the town feels
so dead is simple despair,
but another problem is that
people have nothing to do.
Surviving in this world costs too little money.
Wouldn't it be better to use some money,
then go earn more,
so you can then spend that?
To get money and crafting materials,
activities such as hunting become necessary.
That would give the combat
guilds more work, as bodyguards.
The next problem is safety.
The laws don't have to be that strict.
If you consider fights over
territory and hunting grounds
to be simply another form of competition,
there isn't any need to ban them outright.
That's right.
However,
certain things go too far, and will need banning.
PKing, for instance.
Why don't we forbid player killing within
the lower level zones around Akihabara?
Certainly, there's no point in fighting
players who are below level 50.
Our next issue is one of human rights.
I believe that, with death no longer an absolute,
kidnapping and imprisonment
are far more serious crimes than they
would have been in the old world.
And leaving or joining a guild
should be up to the individual.
I agree.
My final suggestion is this...
That these human rights apply
not only to us adventurers,
but also to the People of the Land.
Huh?
This isn't the Elder Tale that we knew.
The cooking and inventions prove that.
That's true, but...
It's certainly influenced by Elder Tale.
But this is a different world than
the one we used to know.
We must keep that in mind at all times.
And the People of the Land are
this world's original residents.
We're the outsiders,
and we're in the vast minority.
So they aren't simply non-player characters?
Correct.
Each has their own personality,
concerns, and dreams...
That's idiocy.
Have you ever spoken with any of them?
Why would I?
M-May I say something?
It isn't only adventurers who
come to Crescent Moon.
Many People of the Land do, too.
They desire good food, as well.
Many People of the Land work in
the market or the Guild Building.
We can't get by without them,
but they would probably be
perfectly fine without us.
If we cannot govern ourselves,
then before too long,
relations with them will be
damaged beyond repair.
Are you implying
there's a possibility of war with
the People of the Land?
I think that's a question for the Round Table.
D.D.D. agrees to the establishment
of the Round Table Conference,
and will participate.
As does the West Wind Brigade.
It's been a long time since I've seen
you in such total control, Shiroe.
I just wish you'd joined us.
We cannot split Akihabara...
The Black Sword Knights will also participate!
Honesty agrees, as well.
So does Grandeur.
And Radio Market.
W-We, too...
The Crescent Moon Alliance agrees with pleasure!
And so, that day, the Round Table
Conference was founded...
And the secret of the recipes was publicized.
This world is not the Elder Tale we knew.
We must accept this fact.
Regarding security and human rights...
Our next goal is to gather information
about the closed transport gates and
fairy rings, as well as other zones...
Um, well...
Let's all get along!
Each use of the Guild Building will cost one gold.
This will serve as a tax...
And this will be the first day
of a huge celebration!
Eat up!
Hamelin shut down, as well...
Shiroe denied them access to the Guild Building,
so for a while, they were locked in their guild hall.
And then they realized that
they could use Call of Home,
the return spell, to get outside the gate.
Some of them escaped by killing themselves,
so they would revive at the Cathedral.
Regardless, they can't use
this Guild Building anymore.
Every last one of them has left town.
Yeah...
But all the children who fled
Hamelin said they want to join us.
We had to move into a larger guild hall
to accommodate all the new members.
During the escape, Shouryuu may
have been a bit too impressive.
Like a newborn chick that confuses
the first toy it sees for its mother,
they're imprinted on him.
I wonder what Nyanta's up to...
I can't believe Shiro kept all that in motion
behind the scenes at the conference.
I had no idea, either.
He really did destroy an entire guild...
He can be such a scary boy.
He's dangerous!
Come to think of it, I haven't seen them today...
Actually, they're moving today, too.
Oh?
Hey, Shiro...
Where do you want this?
Over there, please.
Wow... It's looking pretty good.
Karashin?
What'd he say?
He suggested hiring People of the Land
to handle the Round Table's paperwork.
He's right that it'd be cheaper than hiring players.
They say that People of the Land
have come from other cities after
hearing rumors about our cooking.
My lord,
I have already seen several of
them infiltrating Akihabara.
So it would seem.
Shiroe, from Log Horizon, said
that the Round Table would decide
if we go to war against the
People of the Land, but...
The People of the Land may end up deciding.
They appear to have begun already.
What will you do, Villain in Glasses?
We should assume they've already started...
This place is huge!
This hairstyle is adorable, too!
I'm in the middle of cleaning...
I've brought you a moving present!
Now, we take this...
Stop...
Isn't that...
A children's festival kimono?
Shiroe, Naotsugu...
This is a moving present!
Takoyaki...
Okonomiyaki...
And crêpes!
Even the dessert's a fried food?!
Th-There's so much—
Don't be modest.
You have to eat a lot, or you won't
grow up big, like Naotsugu.
Right, Naotsugu?
Huh? Wait, Naotsugu...
Have you gotten bigger again?
No way...
Put it on!
That's a suit of armor.
I refuse!
Hey, everyone's here.
Put it on!
Shiroe... Naotsugu...
Hi, there!
Souji! Nazuna!
Welcome.
Hey there, Chief.
Do you know them, my lord?
Yeah.
Nazuna was also in the Tea Party.
This is for you.
Cherry sake from our brewmaster.
I can't wait to try it.
This guild hall is amazing...
Really...
It must've cost a fortune.
Not at all.
Look...
That tree destroyed the elevator hallway and
stairs, so it was abandoned and quite cheap.
It's far from the city center, too.
What did you do about the stairs and flooring?
I asked Michitaka...
I see.
Then if we remodel them,
all the previously uninhabitable abandoned
buildings could be used for new things.
So, about the remodeling cost...
Hey, don't rip us off, okay?
To be honest, I have no idea how to price it.
Huh?
The crafting and construction processes
are so different than the real world.
In other words,
they don't know the appropriate
prices for anything in this world?
Our economic system still has many holes.
Isaac, from the Black Sword Knights, was also here!
This place is pretty big.
Isaac!
Hey, Villain in Glasses...
It's perfect. Let my summoners train here.
W-Wait a second, Isaac—
Do it!
Cosplay?!
Later.
So, the Black Swords came here...
They aren't all that bad.
We're making a huge bath area now.
Come over when it's done, okay?
Yeah.
See you soon, Akatsuki...
When we can take our time!
Shiro, you've built a lovely house.
See you!
We'll be going, too.
Oh...
Are Tohya and Minori doing well?
Eh? Ah...
Haven't they told you yet?
Nothing!
See you soon, Shiro.
Sure...
Are you going shopping, master?
Buying stuff for dinner.
Tonight, it's everyone's favorite, curry.
My lord, we're having curry tonight!
What? Curry?!
I love curry!
Hey, Naotsugu...
It's curry tonight!
Seriously?
Yahoo!
Bye.
Bye!
Curry... It's been so long...
Curry!
I'm honestly not sure which is better...
Curry or bo—
My lord, may I roundhouse kick this pervert—
For once, let me finish!
Don't compare curry with something perverted.
The chief's curry is for grown-ups... It's spicy.
Can you eat it, shrimp?
It is?
I'm starting a new guild.
Will you join?
What's this, Shiro?
You finally got around to it?
I thought that from here on out, we were
just going to be a nameless guild.
It is a ninja's task to follow her master.
Just give me your orders, my lord.
Spicy, grown-up curry, huh...
Maybe I should've thought of
a better way to phrase it.
Wait, don't call me a shrimp!
Looking for party members!
We're leaving tomorrow morning!
We'll Take Anyone     Recruiting Now     Weak Players Welcome
I'd like to have one more...
Then join my party.
I'm alone at the moment.
This is perfect. Our meeting must have been fated.
Nice timing.
Huh?
What level are you?
20... Why?
We only want people over level 40.
Wh-What?
No mild curry!
Spicy is out of the question.
I'm back.
You're back already, master?
Is the curry party off?
I found them wandering around the
building, so I brought them up.
Tohya! Minori!
I heard that the Crescent Moon
Alliance was moving today.
Um...
Actually, mister...
Um, well...
We've come to join your guild!
We'd like you to teach us.
This past week, the Crescent Moon
Alliance was very good to us,
but we haven't joined them!
We made it this far thanks to what you taught us.
If you've made a guild, we want to be in it!
I may be weak now, but I'll get strong!
Me, too!
I may slow you down, but...
But I decided not to use that
as an excuse anymore!
Let us join you!
Well... Uh...
Shiroe...
Don't just stand there.
You're a guild master.
A guild master... A guild master?
The leader of a guild...
Right.
I am.
Now...
It's my turn to lead everyone.
Okay, Log Horizon welcomes you,
Tohya and Minori!
As new members, your first mission
is to eat curry with the leaders.
Got it?
Mister...
Yeah!
Actually, it isn't done yet.
It's great!
Yeah, nothing beats curry under a night sky.
I just wish I had something to go with it...
Next time, I'll make some curry relish.
I love you, Chief!
A Round Table Conference?
I see.
The adventurers of Akihabara...
Lord Sergiatte...
I've brought Lady Lenessia.
Peace has come to Akihabara.
Minori and Tohya join Log Horizon,
and train every day.
Shiroe decides to hold a training
camp for new players.
Meanwhile, a letter comes to the Round Table.
It's from the People of the Land.
An Invitation from Eastal
Next time: An Invitation from Eastal.
Always look thirty seconds ahead.