He's overworked.
He had an anemia attack, but he didn't faint.
He's sleeping.
Sleeping?
Run with the Wind
Thank you.
Being stuck with a syringe didn't wake him up.
He must be really exhausted.
It's hard to tell when he actually sleeps.
I thought he was fine without sleep.
It's not just practice.
He was doing all the cooking, too.
It's my fault.
I made him worry.
You know that's not true.
I caused him much more concern.
No, I...
It was everyone.
All of us can think of something we did.
Coach.
Please stop. It's ominous.
I don't know what to do in times like these.
You don't need to do anything.
We should run practice
ourselves tomorrow, right?
I agree.
Come to think of it, clerical procedures
like registering for meets
were all Haiji's job, too.
Supervisor-cum-coach-cum-
manager-cum-dorm leader, huh?
We should at least take turns cooking.
Yeah. All I can cook is ochazuke, though.
Me, too. I've only ever boiled pasta.
Can we survive without Haiji?
Why don't you reconcile?
I mean you guys.
Quit the team if you can't run fast enough?
This is no time to be saying that.
I'm not the one who suggested it.
You're his senior.
I was just expressing my misgivings.
Hey!
If that's what you hurled at me,
then you're being a nuisance.
Earlier, you said you made him worry.
You are making him worry, aren't you?
That's enough!
Don't ruin what Haiji entrusted to you.
You make it sound like he's dead!
You guys sure you don't actually get along?
That's not good enough, Prince.
Our Speed
What? Give me a break.
Please.
I can't even be a substitute captain.
We never decided who'd do it.
I believe that, as the eldest
and most experienced,
you're the most suitable candidate.
I just can't. I can't afford
to look after others.
Then... Yuki.
I thought you'd ask.
But I refuse.
Heart
Was that...
Aw, shucks...
What are you doing?
You mean you don't know about "but I refuse?"
Just so you know, I still don't
think we can make it to Hakone.
I wouldn't know how to lead the team.
You're still saying that?
After participating in all these practices?
Shut up. No. Ask someone else.
Then...
Kakeru, how about you?
Hey! What about me?
If you go in order, I'm next.
There's no way you'd want to do it.
I still want to be asked.
Be asked and decline.
Give me the chance to act like your senior.
I can't respect him, at all.
Yeah.
I don't mind.
What?
I may not be gentle.
Complete and
Total Rest
Joji & Jota
Plum Ochazuke
Get well soon!
I'm sorry
for always relying on you
for everything!
Get well soon.
Sugiyama Takashi
This African mask
will protect you
from evil!
Musa Kamara
You need to rest!!
They said eating meat when you're sick
is good for you
King
Sorry. Get some rest!!
Sleep well, rest well.
Yuki
Take care.
Kurahara
I'll lend you
some of my comics.
Kashiwazaki
Have some porridge!
Jota & Joji
Is this torture?
You don't have to do this.
What?
You don't have to do what Haiji does.
If I leave you alone, you'll fall
farther and farther behind.
Everyone else's pace is increasing.
Their efforts will be ruined because of you.
Buck up and take this seriously.
Since when have you been fast?
Huh?
Since you were a child?
Probably. After all, you're a prodigy.
That's not true.
Then try talking at my speed.
What is this?
Hey, twins!
What is it?
We made lots. Eat all you want.
Why did you start reading comics
as soon as we got home?
You should get changed first.
I need to read the magazine that
came out today by the end of the day.
Your comics aren't going
anywhere. Get changed.
Freshness is everything!
What?
He's right!
Freshness is everything!
I heard Haiji collapsed,
so I brought you something.
Hana, perfect timing!
I missed you!
Huh? Uh, um... What?
Can you cook?
Huh?
Bathroom
Musa!
Hurry!
Hurry up!
Bathroom
S-Save me...
Musa!
I-I'm sorry. Maybe it wasn't to their tastes.
What do you two think?
It's good.
I'm glad.
Whenever I cook at home, everyone says it's good.
My dad cries every time he eats it.
Really?
He must be better after a full day of rest.
Complete and Total Rest
Joji
&
Jota
Excuse the intrusion.
Haiji?
He vanished?!
How?
We missed something.
Unbelievably enough,
there was a window in his room!
Oh...
In other words, Haiji opened the
window and used it to get outside.
His room's on the first floor.
It must've been easy.
We were stupid to let them handle it.
What? Why?
Where did he go?
I don't know.
He finished the ochazuke
we left in his room this morning.
So, he's well enough to eat
and escape through a window?
Then he must be fine.
It's over.
You didn't need to come all the way here.
It's fine. Thank you.
Hey. I came to thank him for yesterday.
You're a fine man.
Right?
What? Oh, no.
You totally lost that argument.
It's no laughing matter.
There's no beating Prince
when it comes to sophistry.
Not that it is.
Try talking at my speed, huh?
Will he be all right?
Prince.
I got a proper look for the first time
today, but he has no form at all.
He needs to be corrected.
You got a proper look for the first time, huh?
I...
I'm not criticizing you.
You had your own problems.
But I think he was watching you and
waiting to see when you'd look his way.
You're always facing forwards.
Prince isn't the only one.
Everyone else is running behind you.
Until you turn around, you'll never
see them from where you are.
You won't see who is running where and how.
Let's go home.
I've only had ochazuke to eat today.
I think I might get even more sick.
We can finally eat a decent meal.
Sorry for making you guys worry.
Don't be shy. Eat all you want today.
Haiji!
Welcome home!
By the way,
I heard Hana made breakfast.
She even brought her own ingredients.
I'd better thank her later.
Huh?
What's wrong, guys?
Do Not Enter
What?
I said, could you lend me some
comics you recommend?
No, I—I don't have anything in my room.
I thought once in a while...
Do you mind romance?
What?
You're really good at that.
Really? It's pretty hard to keep it steady.
That's it!
Huh?
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
No, I'm serious.
What? You're going to run like that?
It's dangerous.
It'll be fine. I just want to try it for a bit.
Then, I'll lead the way.
Please do.
That's it. That's it, Prince.
Hijiki
Normally, you look down when you read comics.
But when you're on the treadmill,
you naturally look forwards
since your comics are in front of you.
You stand up straighter than
you do when you're just running.
It brings your center of gravity forwards.
What?
Good pace, right?
Maybe.
Then could you turn the pages, too?
And could I try something else?
This is amazing, Prince.
It's totally different.
You're totally different.
With my bangs out of my face, I can
see what's in front of me a lot better.
Yes.
What have you been looking at until now?
Try imagining a comic
in front of you as you run.
There's a lot I'd like to say about that.
I bet it'd be fun if you
put bells in his hands.
Why does he do that?
I know! It's like when he's reading comics!
Oh!
Yes. Prince's arms are fixed in a reading
position even when he's running.
Now that I think about it,
I'm amazed he could run like that.
Since we're not short-distance runners,
there's no need for sweeping arm movements.
But I'd like to fix his habit
of holding them in place.
Hey, it's starting to look right.
"I can't wait to go back to my room and read!"
Imagine that as you run.
I can't wait to go back to my room and read.
Yes, that's it. Keep it up.
You've got your color back.
Huh?
I've been eating.
I don't want to make you worry unnecessarily.
Thank you.
You don't miss a thing.
What about them?
You could've intervened anytime.
Did you stay out of it because
you knew this would happen?
No way.
I intended to fix things if I had to.
But I didn't think it'd ever really be his
if he'd learned to run that way.
It's truly a fortunate error.
"I wish I could go back to my room and read!"
Now you!
I wish I could go back to my room and read!
Ow...
Go, Prince!
Final spurt!
Prince!
Whoa!
This is amazing.
Is Kakeru going to break 14:30?
Prince!
Forward!
Face forward.
Hey! Why's he slowing down?
He was going to get a good time, too!
Kakeru...
Prince!
I am... facing forward...
You never... shut up!
I'm fine.
Go!
Prince!
Hey, he might make it.
Yeah, he just might.
You can do it, Prince!
Prince!
Final spurt!
Yeah!
Prince!
You did it. You made it.
Don't make such a fuss.
I still have a long way to go.
Yes, you do. You can go much faster.
Shut up!
What's so great about that?
Who knows?
Yeah! To celebrating breaking 30 minutes...
Ready, and...!
Next time: "Overflowing Drops."
Next time: Overflowing Drops