Your High School National Ogura Hundred
Poets Karuta Team champions:
Mizusawa High School from Tokyo!
Congratulations.
Champions
1st: Fujisaki High School
2nd: Fujisaki High School
3rd: Fujisaki High School
4th: Fujisaki High School
5th: Fujisaki High School
Chihaya-chan.
Go on
It's heavy.  Be careful.
My goal is
to win the team High
School Championship...
We finally have new members...
Two of them stayed.
Compared to becoming Queen, becoming
the strongest woman in Japan,
it's much harder for us to
become best in Japan together!
Like a boatsman adrift...
Chihaya Furu
Episode 20
The
fall
paddy
shacks
Everybody have everything?
We're good.
I'll have the trophy and other
awards sent back to the school,
so place everything here.
Oh, I need to write out an invoice.
How many are there in all?
Ms. Miyauchi?
What is it, Ayase-san?
Um, is there a hospital still open nearby?
Huh?
Wait, it's swollen!
Why didn't you say something sooner?
I know of an emergency clinic.
We went there last year.
Oh, yeah...
Oe-san, should we get you
looked at too, just in case?
The swelling's gone down.
You're okay, then?
Mashima-kun, can you take over here?
Let's get going.
Will Chihaya-chan be okay?
The individual tournament is tomorrow.
Well, let's start packing the awards.
Should we put the medals inside, too?
Probably.
We'll need something
to serve as a cushion.
How about a towel?
Taichi.
I forgot.
Here's a gift.
Famous
Sake Manju
Fukui's famous sake manju...
What happened to Chihaya?
Arata, are you walking to the station, too?
No, my uncle's coming in
his car to pick me up.
Oh.
Hokuo!
Fight!  Fight!
Third Place
Tokyo    Hokuo Academy
We're sprinting to the station, wimps!
Boys' schools are full of idiots.
Fourth Place
Hyogo Prefecture   First Akashi Girls' High School
I'm dying for a bath.
Did you call for a taxi, Coach?
I'm starving.
We need to save our energy for the
individual tournament tomorrow.
What?!
Wataya-san, Mashima-senpai, and
Ayase-senpai are childhood friends?!
Well... Yeah.
When you put it that way,
No way!  What kind of balance is that?!
I'm childhood friends
with Retro from Hokuo...
I smell a love triangle in the air!
Childhood
Friends
She's not listening.
Is your school co-ed, Wataya-san?!
What's your type?!
Do you have a girlfriend?!
But!  But!  This is very important!
Show some restraint!
But!  But!  But!
We're going on ahead.
I understand how you feel!  I do!
I'm hungry.
What's for dinner?
I wanna know!  I wanna know!
That's amazing, Taichi.
That girl also plays karuta?
She's a beginner.
Chihaya worked hard to recruit them.
Really...
Team...
Taichi, in my mind,
the only team for me is the one
I had with you and Chihaya.
I sound pretty creepy.
Especially since I was
looking up at the moon.
Oh, never mind.
On a different subject,
Tokyo
I'm planning on going to college in Tokyo.
What?
Wh-Which college?
Any place I can get a scholarship.
I'll win the individual tournament tomorrow
and go to Tokyo.
Tokyo...
Arata's...
coming to Tokyo.
Oh, that's my uncle's car.
Bye, Taichi.
See you tomorrow.
Arata...
Chihaya wants to be on
a team with you again,
but I don't.
You're my enemy.
Did you say something?
No.
See you tomorrow.
What is this?
Huh?!  What do you mean, Doctor?!
It doesn't look like
any bones were broken,
but there appears to be a chip fracture.
Chip fracture?!
But a fracture would hurt more,
and the swelling isn't that bad.
I'll write up a referral,
so you should go to a bigger
hospital for a second opinion.
What?!
She has a competitive
karuta tournament tomorrow.
Can she participate?
Karuta?
Wow, you're good
Got it
If you mean this, it should be okay.
It's a little more intense.
She should refrain from
any intense activity.
The bone has been weakened.
And it'll be painful if you hit it.
I would recommend that you give up.
Oh, Chihaya-chan.
How did it go?
Oh...
Um, are you about to take a bath?
Yes.
Go on, then.
We can talk about Ayase-san later.
Oh, Ms. Miyauchi.
If you talk to the inn staff,
they'll serve dinner.
Okay, I'll go ask them.
Thank you.
Go take your bath, now.
Let's go, Senpai.
Oops!  Boys' room!
We'll win every match
and become number one in Japan!
Though I prayed...
Note that though...
She moved the instant the reader spoke.
She moved faster than sound.
The sound of birds...
Okay.
One card at a time.
Okay, I won!
One win for First Akashi Girls'!
One win for Pizusawa!
Oe-senpai held on to win!  Amazing!
Two wins for Mizusawa!
Thank you very much.
His opponent has "The sight of Mount,"
while Komano has "May my lonely"
in a luck of the draw.
There are four more dead cards...
I'll always have...
The sight of Mount Arima...
Good thing it wasn't Chihaya-chan
jamming her finger.
What are you talking about, Kana-chan?!
We should consider ourselves lucky!
It wasn't our ace who got hurt.
We have first-years to sub in!
Luck is on our side.
Mizusawa is set up to win.
While
I sigh and lament how the one
I love does not feel the same,
Wh-What is this?
She's different.
Completely different.
Her reflexes...
Her sense...
My only thought as
I don't think so!
Chihaya?!
Is she hurt?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Ayase, you can't hide it from me.
I'm right next to you.
Excuse me.
Win, Rion!
Thank you very much.
Tsukuba-kun...
Thank you very much...
Two wins for Fujisaki!
Mizusawa's down 0 to 2.
Fujisaki's got this in the bag.
They're strong.
That makes it a five-peat for Fujisaki.
Three wins.
We're getting three wins, guys.
Thank you very much.
It's down to luck-of-the-draw.
In both games...
I beg you...
I don't care if my card is never
read in a luck-of-the-draw again.
So please...
Just today...
Just this once...
This one time...
Like a boatsman adrift...
Hey.
You've got tatami marks.
Thank you.
Thank you!
The doctor wasn't sure what's
wrong, but told you not to play?!
Metal guard underneath
It was more than a jammed finger?!
Why didn't you say something yesterday?
I was hoping it might be
healed when I woke up.
You can't play like that.
That's right.
You should forfeit, Ayase-senpai.
It'll hurt even more if you hit it again.
Ayase-san,
I understand how you feel.
But...
You won the team tournament.
You've done very well.
Get some rest.
Huh?  Sis?
Man, what's with her?
Congratulations Winners
I wanna play.
I wanna wear this and play.
Hilarious.
You got hurt yesterday?
Wild animals are slower
when they're injured.
However, if you force the
issue and play poorly,
The S in Sudo stands for sadistic!
they'll say that the team
champions are weak individually.
I haven't forgotten.
My goal is
to win the individual High School
Championships in each class.
gulp
As the team high school champions,
we'll do all we can to make it happen.
Class A
Our goal is
Class C
to win the individual
tournament in each class.
Class D
What?  We count?
Class B
Win.
Class A
Today is the day we show
Fujisaki's true power.
We will dominate the rankings.
Yes!
Class B
If you lose, I'll throw you in Lake Biwa!
Class B     Class B     Class B     Class A     Class A
If you don't want that to happen, win!
Yeah!
Class B     Class A     Class B     Class B     Class A
We have to avenge our loss, girls!
Yes!
Well, the team tournament
was exciting as a new
school emerged triumphant.
I expect this to give the
karuta world a jolt, Chairman.
No, in the team tournament, players
rely on strength to take cards.
All Japan Karuta Association Chairman
Mashita Yoshiaki, grade 10
The matches are very messy to watch.
However, in the individual tournament,
we can expect battles of wit and strategy.
Super Class A
It'll hurt if you hit something.
How are you gonna play like that?
I-I'll use my left hand...
Huh?
I'll do what I can with my left hand.
What?!
We're all playing to win.
The individual tournament
is about to start.
Class A
Ayase Chihaya
Yuube Keiko
You don't have a chance!
She's aggressive enough to blow you
away, even using your right hand!
What are you going to
do with your left hand?!
But!  But, but, but!
What's with that scarf?
Stare...
Why is the Queen so interested?
The first round should be a cinch for her.
They should just seed her, for our sake.
How did she lose all that weight?
It's probably because they stopped
selling Snowmaru daifuku.
You know the reason?
It's so sad...
Wataya Arata
Kawauchi Shoji
Wait,
I'm
playing
him?!
Oh, Arata.
I lucked out.
It's a good thing I didn't get paired
against Arata in the first round.
I would've had a taste of how
much stronger you've gotten
over the past few years.
It's not just Arata.
Everybody here.
I'll make them admit that the team
tournament is nothing serious.
I'll crush them all.
The Queen looked so lame.
Was that a cooling scarf around her neck?
Oh, Chihaya.
Will the players please step inside?
The first round will soon begin.
Class A will be on the second floor.
Will the players please step inside?
Chihaya, aren't you coming?
Oh, I'm coming.
It's Arata.
Arata's here.
Arata and I are standing
on the same tatami floor.
Today is the day...
Today is the day I win it all
and start the Legend of Retro!
Kinashi Hiro's Road to Master Project
Classified
Retro
What's wrong, Mashima?
Today is the day I win!
Retro...
Why am I here?
I-Is he burned out from
the team tournament?
That's not like him.
It's not like him, but that
means my greatest rival is out!
My victory is assured!
The two first-years in Class D
are in a separate hall.
Komano-kun and Oe-san in
Class C are in the office.
Mashima-kun will be playing the Class B
first round on the first floor.
On the second floor is Class A,
Nishida-kun and Ayase-san.
You can tell this is the
national tournament.
The parents are here
to support the players.
Arata's dad
Arata's mom
Ayase-san...
It's time.
We will now begin the first round of
the Class A individual tournament.
Thank you very much.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
Here we go.
Gust of wind...
Yes!
I won't lose.
Not until I get to play Megumu.
...fall leaves
The sound of birds crossing...
What do I do?
I can hear everything.
I can hear the sound,
but my body, my left hand won't...