It's been a long time, kid.
I'm taking Hana back.
Daichi Manatsu,
do you realize what you're about to do?
Sleeping within this ship are
thousands of young men...
Young men entrusted with humanity's future.
You're trying to destroy their
lives and humanity's future.
No!
The captain is trying to save their lives.
What is the "life" you speak of?
The boys sleeping within this ship
will face a future where only they
survive, locked in this iron box.
They'll sleep for thousands,
tens of thousands of years,
perhaps forever, inside a spaceship.
That isn't life.
The way I felt in that cold spaceship,
just watching time pass...
I don't want anyone else to experience that.
It's miserable.
I'm sure they all want to run around,
full of life, on that blue planet below!
I'm sure the captain will make that happen.
I cannot imagine that kid is prepared for that.
Put down your gun.
Pull that trigger, and you'll blow
up the whole Tenkaidou.
This is a detonator.
If my vital signs stop, it will activate.
Don't forget that I hold hostage
all the lives aboard the Tenkaidou.
I can't imagine a member of the
Ark Faction like you would destroy
all the young men sleeping here.
With humanity's future at stake, you really
think we wouldn't have a spare on hand?
We're prepared to make some sacrifices
to save humanity from extinction.
Don't underestimate us, kid!
I've run a trace simulation on the enemy's actions
to predict where the bombs are.
But given that he's been moving about freely,
we should assume he has inside help.
There are other bombs, too.
Give the bomb disposal team
the estimated locations.
Roger.
Don't move.
"Midsummer's Knights"?
Those lacking resolve cannot save this planet,
Daichi Manatsu.
Especially not you.
Hana!
We've no intention of unnecessarily
hurting those aboard the Tenkaidou.
Our primary objective is securing Hana Mutou.
And if Pointer screws up?
If nothing else, he'll be able rid us of our problem.
We'll stop Operation Summer, whatever it takes.
Yes, the Blume belongs to us.
The Meaning of a Captain
Sorry, but today's concert isn't an abreaction.
The Blume is in orbit.
If they attack us, it'll pose a bit of a problem.
If they convert their Orgone energy
into pure physical energy,
destroying an Ego Block is theoretically possible.
There's a good chance
they'll use the Blume's Entangle Link to
destroy the cocoon inside Oberon.
That would be bad!
You're right...
If we can, we should stop
that disaster before it happens.
Ai, go up there and defeat them.
Why Ai?
She's the only one whose face they don't know.
I can't believe it...
Using an idol who hides her face
with sunglasses for a terrorist act?
Zin's singularity will be helpful.
Have him share it with you by telepathic kiss.
I can't believe it!
If the press sees that, there'll be total chaos.
Hey, Ai?
I think I like the way you try so hard in this video.
Well, you know...
It's my job.
Kiss scenes are also part of my job, huh?
I found a good one.
What's wrong, Pitz?
This is Manatsu.
What's wrong, Captain?
Hana's been kidnapped.
It was Hirosue, from Salty Dog.
He has the detonator for the bombs
placed on the Tenkaidou by Salty Dog.
Governor Yomatsuri, I'll send you
the route we expect him to take.
Roger.
I'll forward it to security.
Security, you hear me, right?
From the estimated escape path,
he likely escaped into the engine block.
The detonator is connected to his vital signs,
so firearm use is prohibited!
Also, he has kidnapped Hana Mutou.
What now?
A meteoroid is approaching the Tenkaidou.
Spectral analysis has identified its constitution.
Inconel... Probably the remnants of a spaceship.
I don't see this debris in our catalog.
It isn't in our catalog?
Bearing: 736.
Relative distance: 300,000.
Relative speed: 400.
We can't dodge it.
Collision in 750 seconds.
Estimated mass: 1,200 kilograms.
Impact energy: 96 megajoules.
That's enough energy to penetrate
the debris bumper!
Akari?
A large piece of debris is heading for us.
Debris?
Just get Hana back as soon as possible.
Otherwise, I won't know what Pitz is saying!
What's going on with Pitz?
Just before we found the debris,
Pitz started freaking out.
Because Hana was kidnapped?
No, this is just my intuition as a magical girl,
but something else is going on here.
I'll handle the debris.
You follow Hirosue.
Roger.
I'm counting on you, Daichi.
Governor, Teppei is headed
for the Nebula Engine.
Have him launch as soon as he's ready!
Roger.
Target sighted.
I'll destroy it now.
The target has vanished.
No, there's more.
A new meteoroid is incoming.
Bearing: 927.
Relative distance: 350,000.
Relative speed: 420.
Impact in 833 seconds.
There's no record of this debris in the catalog.
Estimated mass: 2,800 kilograms.
There's no way we couldn't detect
the orbit of debris this size...
Footage incoming.
I'll destroy it.
The target has vanished.
A second one?
Oh, did my test attract too much attention?
But... But...
There's lots of debris in orbit!
I have all kinds of toys ready
to give as gifts my fans!
Violent...
Attacking...
Ticket to hell!
More debris incoming.
Thirty-five in total.
Thirty-six.
There's still more!
What?
What's going on?
Relative distance: 320,000.
Relative speed: 420.
Impact in 780 seconds.
I'll destroy them.
Not bad...
But how about this?
They dodged?
No!
This is the Nebula.
Some of the debris is heading your way!
Tenkaidou, can you hear me?
Propulsion, communication, and
ejection systems are all down...
The Nebula Engine has been hit.
The debris has passed the Nebula,
and is heading for the Tenkaidou.
More debris!
Are you okay, Teppei?
Teppei?
The communication system is offline?
Captain, come in!
This is Manatsu.
The Nebula has been damaged and
knocked out of commission.
Teppei?
The debris is on course for the Tenkaidou!
Head out in the Earth.
But Hana...
At this rate, the Tenkaidou itself is in danger.
Understood.
Even more debris has appeared.
What is Pitz saying?
Forty-seven... Forty-eight... Forty-nine...
It keeps coming!
It can't be!
Bingo!
MM bus signal detected.
Epicenter identified.
It's...
Inside the transport ship Nipper?
Security Team 64, get to space port Nipper.
There's no end to them.
Governor, there's even more debris coming.
Of all the times for this to happen...
What's going on?
The main event's just starting.
Over five hundred pieces of debris incoming.
They're coming in at relative speed: 620.
We can't stop them all...
Captain, we'll use the boosted plasmagnum.
But we haven't even tested it!
There's no other way to survive this.
You can do it, right?
Understood.
Boosted plasmagnum, stand by!
Boosted plasmagnum, scramble!
The Marine Gate...
Target confirmed.
Boosted plasmagnum, ready to go.
Wait, Captain...
We need to get the Nebula out
of there, or Teppei-kun will...
The Nebula can't move.
Its propulsion system has been
destroyed, and we can't contact it.
The ejection system is probably damaged, too.
But...
If we don't fire now, it's over.
It's impossible!
He can't do it!
You go to the Blume,
and promise me you'll save humanity's chosen ones.
Hey!
Wake up!
Only those with the necessary
resolve can save humanity!
You understand, don't you, Captain?
Don't hesitate!
Fire!
He fired.
An amazing amount of energy...
Is this that boy's power?
It may be just as King said.
Indeed.
We can entrust our hopes to that team.
All objects in the firing radius
have been annihilated...
Teppei-kun...
What is this?
There's a signal where the Nebula was destroyed.
Is this...
The Nebula Engine?
Teppei...
I'm alive?
DC?
What is that machine?
What is that Orgone energy light?
This is Matsui, with Security Team 64.
We've found a suspicious object
in the Nipper cargo room.
A Machine Goodfellow?
And it's active!
Destroy that capsule!
Hurry!
R-Roger!
I hate it when my fans ambush me.
The event's over.
This is Security Team 64.
We destroyed the capsule, but the object fled.
We will continue searching for the bombs.
Had our positions been reversed...
I would have fired 2.5 seconds faster.
You still aren't strong enough, Captain.
Let's get Hana back.
Yeah.
My mission is to kidnap Hana Mutou
and eliminate you.
Answer me one thing.
Did you know Teppei Arashi would survive that?
Or are you the kind of man who
would let one of his friends die?
Answer me!
I thought I was going to kill
Teppei with my own hands.
I wasn't going to "let him die."
If he'd died,
it would have been because I killed him.
But I couldn't afford to hesitate there.
I don't like you.
I hate you!
But...
Can you really defeat the enemy?
Can you really save Earth?
If you really can...
Please.
My dad and my brother...
Save the planet where everyone lives.
If you really can...
Please save them, Captain Earth!
At last, the time has come to destroy
the enemy fortress carrier Oberon.
That very moment, Alonzo tells
us the Planetary Gears are
launching an all-out attack.
We're running out of time.
But Salty Dog's ultimate weapon stands before us.
Why are you getting in our way?
This plan is for the Earth's protection!
Next time, on episode 22 of Captain Earth:
The Operation Summer.
The Operation Summer
Earth Engine, expand!