Closed for the day.
Hokubi News Online
Cloudy weather expected during
largest meteor shower of the year.
I'll never forget.
Morning.
Night of the Meteor Shower
Morning, Dad.
I could have cooked.
I can do it for a change.
It's not burnt!
I'm improving, too.
Noel, was it?
Is she okay now?
Yeah, thanks to you.
Next time she's here,
she'll have to try my awesome cooking.
You're right.
Hey,
I might be late tonight.
Is that okay?
As long as I can contact you.
Thanks, Dad.
Komiya Shuichi
Kaori
Nonoka
I'm leaving.
Nonoka!
Oh, good.
There's something we need to talk about.
Yuzuki.
Hey, morning.
Clouds, clouds, go away!
I see, the olive oil—
The meteor shower this year, unfortunately—
Wait.
Didn't this happen before, too?
No, it hurts more than last time.
Because I know you're forcing it.
Yuzuki!
Let's meet at the
observatory tonight!
We're all watching the
meteor shower together!
Hey, Souta, what's your plan now?
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
No,
it's nothing.
Nonoka.
Gathering at the observatory?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Koharu, I...
Okay.
It's what you believe, and decided.
Yeah.
One more fresh ginger ale.
Shione, listen to me.
I decided.
I want to make Noel smile.
So let's all go to the
observatory tonight.
Let's watch the meteor shower.
Get in.
I'm back.
Why won't you leave me alone?
Don't involve yourself.
Please, Nonoka.
Stay out of my life.
Friends
Understand!
We're friends, please understand!
You have to understand!
I do.
Then—
This girl, Yuzuki,
loves her brother.
Friends
Souta cares for his sister, too.
When people hurt each other,
this girl, Koharu, feels just as hurt.
And then, there's Shione.
She's more lonely than anyone
else, yet she's stubborn.
She thinks everyone will be
happy so long as she endures.
I'll take a picture of you, now.
Me? No thanks.
I'm okay.
I want a picture of you guys.
What are you talking about? Here, gimme.
Nonoka, catch her!
Right.
My wish is for everyone to smile.
It's the wish that Noel said was beautiful.
And it includes your smile, too.
I...
Talk to Noel.
I'm thinking of coming to the
observatory with the others tonight.
I can't wait for the meteor shower.
I wonder when they're coming.
Yuzuki.
Yuzuki!
Hey, don't just barge in.
Shut up.
We used to be in the same room.
Not anymore.
Right.
Was it when I got injured
that we changed rooms?
Go away already.
I can't talk to you anymore.
You don't care?
Of course not.
I don't need to talk to you.
It's
tougher than I thought for me.
Me, too.
But Noel...
Do you remember the day
we called the saucer?
We had a stupid fight that morning.
We did.
We'd never even gotten
into a fight until then.
We had no idea how to make up.
So I made a wish to the saucer.
Please grant my wish.
That I'd be friends with
these guys forever.
With you, too, of course.
The saucer we saw on the dock...
Maybe that was Noel
granting my wish.
That's my guess.
Me, too.
Because my wish was...
Please grant my wish.
That I would be able to make up
after I fight with my brother
or with my friends.
Then maybe it's our turn
to grant Noel's wish.
Thanks, Koharu.
Not at all.
When we called the saucer, I made a wish
that we'd always be friends.
I think it might be thanks to
Noel-chan that we can still
be so close that we
know how each other feels.
I'm borrowing this again.
Shione.
I know they're waiting.
At the observatory.
Let's go.
Noel.
Are you lost?
I might be.
I'm going ahead.
I'll be waiting.
Shione, let's go together.
Why?
You're going to vanish, aren't you?
We won't be able to
see each other anymore, will we?
So
how can you look like that?
Aren't you sad?
You won't see Nonoka
and the others anymore.
Don't you feel lonely?
I feel
really warm here when
you're all happy.
When you're all sad, it tingles.
When you're all smiling,
I think I granted your wishes, right?
Shione, let me part with my
beloved friends with a smile.
That's not fair.
Saucer-san, Saucer-san,
please grant my wish
that I will always love
Nonoka and the others.
How could you refuse
after you granted my wish?!
Do Not Enter
Nonoka!
Where's Shione?
She'll come.
Yeah.
I know they're coming, too.
You're late!
We just got here, too, though.
You didn't need to give it away.
There, there. We have tea.
Nonoka, Noel-chan, come here.
Nonoka!
Why are you just standing there?
It's nothing.
What's wrong?
Thank goodness, you're all here.
What makes you say that?
There's someone I want you to meet.
Nice to meet you,
my name is Togawa Shione.
Hey...
We have some time,
with the weather being how it is.
That's true.
Let's all take pictures.
Gimme.
I'm going to take a ton!
Us too.
Don't move.
I can't get a good picture.
Okay.
Damn it.
I'll do it.
Smile, you two.
Noel.
I have to go home.
Shione.
We're friends now, right?
Yeah.
I'll cherish what you gave me forever.
It was fun at the hot springs.
Yeah.
It was huge and warm.
Someday, with the others.
Yeah.
Thanks to you,
I can smile with Nonoka again.
Because you watched over me.
Really?
Yeah.
Koharu, I'm glad Monster-san
is feeling better.
Yeah, because you never gave up on him.
Souta!
It's thanks to your help.
Monster-san got better
because you helped.
Right...
Say thanks to Souta, too.
I know.
I know that.
Yuzuki.
Go away!
You and Souta made me understand
the true meaning of your wishes.
I said nothing but awful things,
like getting rid of the saucer.
Noel.
I'm sorry.
Noel, I'll never forget about you.
I won't forget either.
You gave me lots and
lots of beautiful things.
Nonoka.
I'm sorry.
I have to smile.
I really, really have to.
Sorry, Noel.
Don't apologize, Nonoka.
Nonoka,
do you remember what
your mother said?
Shione.
Yeah.
Nonoka.
Shione.
Yuzuki. Souta. Koharu.
I love you all!
This is a meteor shower...
Come on, Noel.
Let's watch the meteor
shower together.
Huh?
I'm happy.
I'm supposed to be really happy.
You're all smiling.
And I...
Why won't it stop?
Why does it keep overflowing?
Noel!
Nonoka!
Thanks.
Nonoka.
Nonoka!
Are you all right?
Noel.
Is she really gone?
Why?
You were prepared, weren't you?
Yeah, but still.
The saucer!
Is this what you really wanted?
Noel?
Saucerless City
Next episode of Celestial
Method: "Saucerless City."