I've found you, weretiger.
Akutagawa!
Looks like you've improved your
acrobatic skills, weretiger.
Why are you here, Akutagawa?
To kill you.
Don't you understand the
situation we're in right now?
We may no longer have a place to live.
I don't understand you one bit.
I don't remember ever asking
for your understanding.
Oh, dear.
Akutagawa-kun still has a
terrible habit of going solo.
All right.
Atsushi-kun, we don't have
time to deal with him.
Let's move on.
But...
Don't worry.
Just do as I say, and you'll make it.
Understood.
Akutagawa, I'm speaking to
Dazai-san on this intercom.
He wants to talk to you.
Dazai-san!
Well hello, Zelda.
How have you been?
Yeah, I apologize for calling you so late.
I heard the news.
You laid off another chef?
They came all the way here from
a top-notch European restaurant.
No, I don't blame you.
It's true.
Any cook that doesn't know of your distaste
for cream cheese ought to perish.
Yes, she's still studying in London.
I wouldn't forget it for a moment.
Sorry, it appears I have a guest.
I'll call you back.
I love you, Zelda.
That was a brief farewell, boy.
Is this what you're looking for?
Are you the one guarding
the control terminal?
Here's the first secret
to how I got this far.
The most important part of any job is to
not leave anything for others to handle.
By the way, do you know how
much the Moby Dick weighs?
It has a total mass of 29,000 tons.
Dropped from an altitude of two kilometers,
it would explode with the force of 140 tons of TNT...
Right in the middle of the city.
No one would allow such an atrocity.
The second secret to how I got this far is:
don't let the values of others affect you.
With that said, you and I are both busy.
If we have to fight over the control
terminal, let's keep things simple.
We'll both run towards it
on the count of three.
The first of us to take it is the winner.
If you win, you can do as you like
with the Moby Dick.
But if I win, you'll serve me
in helping with my search.
One...
Should I take his challenge
and run when he does?
Two...
No, I can't trust anyone from
the Guild to keep a promise.
I'll outsmart him and take it
before his signal, and run!
Three.
Secret number three: It's easy to predict the
behavior of anyone who's given an opportunity.
Oh? You aren't going down with that kick?
That's impressive.
Very well.
10,000 may have been insulting.
This is a portion of my securities.
There's 100,000 dollars worth.
I haven't introduced you
to my ability yet, have I?
Ability: The Great Fitzgerald.
My ability grants me physical
strength equal to the money I spend.
Be proud, boy.
I haven't used 100,000
dollars in a long time.
Of course, Zelda would spend
that much in a month.
Now everything is going according to plan.
With crashing the Moby Dick,
and with capturing you.
Me?
Our strategist has the
ability to make
limited precognitions based
on what information she has.
Now that I have you, it would
be a pain if you got away.
I should probably remove your
arms and legs for good measure.
Oh my, what an unusual guest.
Mister...
Agua?
Aguagar?
Akutagawa.
That's the one.
Episode Twenty-Three
Rashoumon, The Tiger,
and The Last Emperor
Hey, Kyouka-chan, can you hear me?
It's Dazai.
We negotiated with the
Gifted Special Operations Division.
We can bring you back down for now.
I'm going to teach you
how to pilot that drone.
No more.
To tell you the truth, the Agency
doesn't have a reason to rescue you.
You aren't an official member, after all.
The Agency has an entrance test,
and you haven't passed it yet.
The test is to see if you have the heart and
strength to help even complete strangers.
I don't think I'd pass.
I don't like that.
A former killer isn't qualified
to become a good person.
Do you truly believe that?
Well, Mr. Akutagawa, I'd love to welcome
you aboard, but as you can see, I'm busy.
Who gave you permission to lie around?
You aren't getting away this time.
Stand up and fight.
Things couldn't get worse.
I was never ready to begin with.
You said earlier that you
couldn't understand me.
To me, you're completely incomprehensible.
Those fearful eyes have no faith in
your own strength or gift,
yet you always involve
yourself in futile battles.
Where do you get that
incoherent self-respect?
That's enough, little guy.
I don't like being ignored.
Shut up.
My main course is the weretiger.
I'd like my dessert to sit quietly.
I hate being in second place.
I request our rankings be changed.
Fine.
Did he stop Rashoumon with his bare hands?
For your efforts, I'll teach you
the fourth secret to success.
I don't need it.
Rashoumon!
Black Torrent!
Black Torrent
500,000 dollars.
The fourth secret to success: Though
there are many forms of strength...
money and influence, gifts, social status...
it helps to have all of them, the way I do.
The tiger's gone.
Strength my ass!
Money and gifts don't
exist to blow up cities.
Human strength exists to be shared with
those who are in the depths of despair.
I'm not surprised that
you'd make such a mistake.
Strength doesn't exist to help the weak.
The very essence of money-making
is to extract value from the weak.
To then offer that to the
weak is to repeat a pointless act,
akin to swinging a door round and round.
Strength must be used more meaningfully.
Do you pretend not to see the lives
that are snubbed out to that end?
By the snubbed out lives of the weak...
Do you mean, for example, your past self?
I looked up your history.
You were nearly killed, twice,
in your early childhood
by the president of your orphanage.
When he kicked you and broke
your ribs, he said to you...
Compared to what your parents
did to you in your infancy,
this doesn't even count as violence.
We're slowing down, preparing for descent.
We have just over ten minutes until impact.
I understand.
What?
Stop!
He ran?
I take back what I said about not
being able to understand you.
I understand you.
Weretiger, you fight in order
to earn permission to live.
Even if that means
sacrificing your own life.
Disgusting.
Do you honestly believe, weretiger, that
someone is out there to grant you permission?
Did you think that if you put your
life on the line fighting for others,
someone will stamp a form certifying
that you deserve to live?
Where's the crime in believing that?
You're an utter disappointment.
I never expected you to be such a fool.
I could kill you hundreds of times, and I'd
have gained no accomplishments in battle.
Accomplishments in battle.
Indeed.
That is the only true measure of value.
Without any accomplishments in battle,
that man would never approve of me.
Not Dazai-san.
Dazai-san?
How does his name fit here?
I've found you, stray dogs.
Kyouka-chan, everyone has
strengths and weaknesses.
You clearly have talent in killing.
You think that, therefore, you can't
become a member of the Detective Agency.
That's foolish.
I'll prove to you in one second how
devoid of reason that belief is.
Kyouka-chan, how many people have
you killed with those hands?
35.
A mere 35.
Listen up, Kyouka-chan.
You don't know everything
about the Detective Agency.
You don't know everything about yourself.
No one can know everything.
That's what we call "potential."
Even Atsushi-kun, who's
given you another chance,
was originally a savage
beast, deemed a menace.
But now he's risking his own life to do what
only he can do, in order to protect this city.
That's it.
The cargo elevator.
His ability is way out of my league.
I don't stand a chance.
I need to think of a way to steal
the terminal when I have a chance.
You're as foolish as ever.
What?
This box takes us to the
inescapable deck service door.
We are the ones who have been cornered.
No.
Nothing could be more shameful than to have
been defeated once by the likes of you.
Especially knowing that you're so worthless
that you ask others for your own right to live.
You're right, I'm worthless.
But you're a murderer with no purpose
but to flaunt your strength.
I'm a hundred times better.
Say that again.
You have plenty of power and status.
You fight just so that people fear you.
That's way more worthless.
Take that back!
I have power and status?
I'll tell you why I called you disgusting.
It's because you're a fool who continues to
mope about old wounds despite having everything.
What?
What did you say I am?
You're blessed with your gift.
You're blessed with friends.
With no effort and with nothing but sheer
luck, you're revered and praised by Dazai-san.
You don't even understand how lucky you are.
You dwell in your own tragedy.
You're a disgusting fool!
Without any accomplishments in battle,
that man would never approve of me.
Not Dazai-san.
Dazai-san?
Don't tell me you've always been...
That's enough of playing tag.
In less than ten minutes, the Moby Dick
will enter into an irrevocable trajectory.
At that point, not even this terminal will
be able to stop it from falling into the city.
Only I will survive, as I've
strengthened myself with my ability.
Hey, nouveau riche, if I defeat someone as
strong as you, will I no longer be weak?
I'll guarantee it.
Then I won't regret dying
as many times as it takes.
Rashoumon! Demonic Armor!
Is he overriding my actions with his gift?
Akutagawa is so strong, yet
he thinks of himself as weak.
He's preposterous!
How many people has his selfishness killed?
Tiger, grant me strength once again.
Just like last time.
Get out of my way, weretiger!
You get out of my way!
Dazai-san, my ass!
You're even more worthless!
Nonsense.
You're more worthless than I am!
This is amusing.
You're both very much alike.
What?!
Don't...
...compare me...
...to him!
This technique makes my black
armor double as muscle.
My body is too feeble to last.
Taking a break, Akutagawa?
Shut up.
You're next.
The control terminal comes first.
If this ship hits the city,
Dazai-san will be obliterated, too.
That man wouldn't die so easily.
Tiger beetle, tell me, is
there anything in this world
aside from family worth
sacrificing everything for?
I'll take the book, and I'll bring
my daughter back into this world.
Your daughter?
My wife, Zelda, unable to accept our
daughter's death, became mentally ill.
To this day, she hides in her fantasy that
our daughter is studying abroad in London.
I'm going to make that fantasy a reality,
and reclaim my family.
No matter what the cost is.
My wealth is dispensable.
I'll pay all of it!
He's off the scales.
It's like standing in front
of a massive tornado.
This is the will of the Guild's leader?
Akutagawa...
What?
Am I a fool?
Is it worthless of me to want
to escape from those memories?
It is.
The words of your past are fundamentally
unrelated to who you are now.
I see.
I think Dazai-san already approved
of you a long time ago.
Come!
Beast Beneath the Moonlight!
Rashoumon Demonic Armor!
Episode 24
If I May Shed Away
My Burden Now