Hilda.
Oh, dear. You're here again?
You sure do like it there.
Yep.
The apple pie's ready.
Really?
Yay!
Eat up.
I love, love, love your apple pie.
Time to eat.
Hilda.
Hilda!
Mom.
Mom!
Please! Spare her!
Spare her!
She may be a Norma, but she's still my child!
She's my precious daughter!
Mom.
Mom!
Hilda! Give her back!
Give back my daughter!
Mom!
Hilda.
Hilda!
What the?
The Hometown of Betrayal
Forgive me, Angelise-sama, I—
Get some rest.
We move at night.
Okay.
I wonder if Hilda...
...found her mom.
Hilda!
Give her back!
Give back my daughter!
Mom.
Open.
Who's there?
Reika? Maki?
Akiho.
It's been a while, Akiho.
Angelise-sama...
You're still here doing maintenance?
You're as diligent as ever.
Yes.
You c-cut your hair.
It looks good—
Forgive me!
Help me!
Akiho.
Did you think I was going to hurt you?
No...
You believe it, too?
That Normas are violent, antisocial monsters.
No!
I may be a Norma, but I'm still me.
Nothing's changed.
I don't intend to harm you.
Akiho.
You're my friend.
Friend?
O-Of course.
W-We're friends.
Akiho.
I have a request.
Y-Yes?
Don't tell anyone that I'm here.
O-Of course.
I won't tell anyone.
I promise.
So, can we leave right away?
Yes, we can.
I thought so.
You're like them, too.
Don't come near, you monster!
Let's go to the imperial palace.
Right!
Angelise-sama.
It's fine. I knew.
Thanks, Momoka.
You're... you.
Angelise-sama.
Sylvia.
Mom.
Who's there?
Who might you be?
M-Mom.
I, I—
Ah, a friend of my daughter's.
No.
I-I—
Well, welcome.
Make yourself at home.
She'll be home soon.
Oh, right, my apple pie will be ready soon.
It's her favorite.
Apple pie.
Mom.
I'm really home.
Let's go, Angelise-sama.
The Dawn Pillar...
Left.
Okay.
Um, really?
We're getting further from the palace.
Don't worry.
An ambush?
Wh-What shall we do?
What else?
Go right through it.
Thank you for the report.
Please catch them.
Otherwise, I don't know what she'll do to me.
Don't worry.
There's nowhere for a Norma to run.
I knew this would happen.
Does she have no concept of stealth...
or infiltration, or modesty?
I guess not.
Well, that's definitely like Ange.
A restraint barrier?
Momoka.
Dammit.
Angelise-sama.
Momoka, get me a clip.
Okay.
Forget using Mana, use a net gun.
Momoka.
Okay.
Fire!
Over there.
Charge!
O-Okay.
Now we just follow the road.
It'll take us to the front of the palace.
I never knew of this secret passage.
Only royalty know of it.
I used to use it to sneak out at night.
Really?
I never heard about it.
Her tactics, eh?
Predictable indeed.
The palace.
What the—
Onee-sama.
Onee-sama!
Angelise-oneesama.
Help me.
Onee-sama.
Sylvia.
Let Sylvia go!
She wouldn't recognize me.
I've grown up so much.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Eat up.
Be careful, it's still hot.
Okay.
Um, I... I'm...
Hilda.
I'm home, Mom.
Welcome home.
School finished early, did it, Hilda?
Happy birthday, Mom.
You remembered?
Of course.
We're family.
Apple pie.
Can I have some?
Wash your hands first.
Your friend's going to laugh at you.
Fine, fine.
Hey, Mom.
Who is she?
Isn't she one of your friends?
Why?
Why... Why is she Hilda?
I'm Hilda.
Hildegard Schlievogt.
We were separated eleven years ago.
I'm your daughter.
You're alive.
Mom.
Why did you come back?
Wh-Why?
Because I missed you, Mom.
Leave.
Leave, now!
Don't ever come back!
Mom.
I'm not your mom.
This is my only child!
Your daughter?
She's alive?
You mean, she's my sister?
No.
She's a monster.
A monster?
A forcefield?
Norma.
Norma!
Hilda.
Hilda!
Mom.
Stay away.
I finally forgot about that nightmare.
I was finally happy.
Don't take my happiness.
Please.
You know, there are some things in
this world that just can't be helped.
Right?
That I gave birth to a Norma.
And that you're a Norma.
Leave, please.
I won't tell anyone you came.
I promise.
Mom.
How could you?
I told you to leave!
You... You shouldn't have even been born!
Get away from me.
Sylvia, come here.
Okay.
Sylvia-sama.
You came for me, Onee-sama.
You're my sister. Of course.
Thank goodness you're okay.
Angelise-oneesama!
Angelise-sama.
Get a hold of yourself.
Sylvia.
Don't be friendly with me.
You're not my sister or anything.
You monster!
Why?
Why were you born?
If only you were never born,
Mother, Father, Onii-sama,
and I would all have been happy.
If only you never existed,
I would have been able to walk.
Mother would have never died.
You took it all.
You destroyed everything.
Bring back Mother!
You monster!
I hate you!
Sylvia-sama...
Angelise-sama!
Angelise-sama.
You look pathetic.
A fittingly miserable end
to a fallen princess.
Julio-oniisama.
Yes, that's it.
I wanted to see that dumbfounded face.
It was worth trying to lure you out.
Now, let's begin the trial, Angelise.
For the crime that is you.
I wonder if Ange found her sister...
Preview
I caught Onee-sama today.
I was scared! She was so vicious.
I used to be her delicate sister,
but now I'm swinging a knife around.
It's terrible, as always.
Goodbye From the Gallows