"Graduation"
Captain Simon, congratulations
on successfully
destroying the enemy base on RA221.
Indeed, that was splendid!
We finally managed to land a blow
against the Wulgaru army.
There's hope yet that we can change
the tide of this war.
The real battle has yet to begin.
Until now, the Wulgaru
has taken us lightly,
but that strike will serve as an excuse
to launch a massive attack.
Precisely.
We must prepare for the
Wulgaru's counter-attack.
We have already confirmed signs
of enemy movement.
You are speaking out
of line, Deputy Amane.
My apologies.
But after this, I imagine
the MJP will be back
on track, training pilots.
If they pump out more
excellent students,
we might actually win this war!
Yes, indeed!
We need to increase the AHSMB
unit's production speed.
Yo!
See, that was a pretty
hard fight back there,
so maintenance has been killer.
Our Rhinos are just prototypes
for your AHSMBs.
But the way you fought with them...!
You guys should be able
to show us up easy.
You've just gotta get a
grasp on your units first.
Our DNA has been programmed
into our units,
which makes piloting them relatively easy.
But don't rely too heavily on
your machine's abilities.
If one side relies too heavily on the other,
the relationship is screwed.
So, did ya need somethin'?
I don't have any porn on hand
if that's what ya want.
Uh, no!
We received orders to return
to the academy again.
I just wanted to say "Goodbye" first.
That right?
Well, I'm sure we'll run into
each other again someday.
After all, the enemy
is already on the move.
Oh, right! Before I forget.
This contains the data
from our last battle.
I had it stored on my Rhinos.
One of our duties is to collect combat data
for future generations.
Thank you.
Hang in there!
After this, we'll be headin'
back to the frontlines.
See ya 'round.
Right!
Data from the Rhinos units, huh?
As far as the bigwigs are concerned,
all of us are just data.
Where is Doberman going next?
Back to the frontlines.
Is that right?
We'll see them again.
Huh? What're you doing here?
Why the heck did you come back?
Well, we're not sure why ourselves.
You're still lacking where it counts.
That's what makes you the Fail Five!
That last strike only worked because
those other pilots were there, huh?
Just try not to make the
rest of us look bad.
Asagi!
This place never changes!
Yep. It's kinda relaxing.
That isn't relaxing!
And here we're working our butts off!
Seriously!
Ah, sirs!
Instructor Suzukaze is calling for you.
Oh, thank you.
It was nothing.
Now if you'll pardon me, Team Fail.
Team Fail?
Did she do that on purpose?
She seriously thought
that was our team name...
Huh?
What does graduating entail?
In short, it means you have
completed your training
and will officially enter the GDF army.
The five of you will
be graduating early.
Likewise, I will be
transferring with you.
I will be the captain of the Godinion:
your superior commander.
Pack your belongings in your dorm rooms.
You will return to Star Rose tomorrow
and remain on standby
until tomorrow's mission.
Understood?
What Life Brought You
Now they're rushing
us through graduation?
Guess that means, "From now on,
we can throw you into as many
battles as we want!" huh?
Aren't you going to miss this place?
I never dreamed I'd feel this way
when I first came here...
We were practically
thrown into the school.
Boy was I shocked when I found out
we were on the same team...
Now for the next team.
Toshikazu Asagi,
Ataru Suruga,
Izuru Hitachi,
Kei Kugimiya,
and Tamaki Irie.
Ma'am...
Yes?
Everyone is younger than me...
Is that a problem?
So if you have any questions,
please feel free to ask.
Come to think of it, Suruga,
didn't you start out pretty quiet?
I had no idea what to talk about!
Our memories had just been wiped.
True enough.
Aside from class and the weather,
there was nothing to talk about.
Whoo, class!
Team Rabbits, you have excellent
offensive capabilities and mobility,
but you're getting E's in cooperation,
concentration and operational stability!
Cooperation is an outright E-!
That'd give her a fairly
large cup size...
What are you talking about?
An F would have been even better yet.
E is the lowest grade you can get!
Uh, guys...!
For some odd reason, everyone
started to open up after that.
All thanks to me, huh?
Not quite...
Keep out of this.
Doesn't it feel empty now?
Yeah...
Could I take this with me?
Sure, didn't it belong to whoever
stayed here before us?
It's a tattered mess, anyway.
It's the first manga I ever read.
NEW
SERIALIZATION!
BUDDY SPIRITS 3
Well, this is a load off.
It's nice knowing that we don't have
to come back here anymore.
Sure is!
I bet no one dreamed we'd be piloting
the high-tech AHSMB units
and graduating ahead of everyone else.
Not in their wildest dreams!
Hey, where are you going?
Gonna cry?
You're gonna cry by yourself, aren't ya?
I want to draw one last sketch.
FAIL
In the end, I never could
get this to come off...
What are you doing here?
Right back at you, Kei!
We came to clean out our desks.
How to Get a Wonderful Girlfriend
Learn how girls think!
Ways for 'meh' guys
to find romance!
That's a magazine for guys.
DANCING CAKES
Make dough for popular cakes,
simple baked sweets that make your mouth dance,
and French recipes you've always dreamt of.
Ladies, what were you
two doing during class?
You're not one to talk!
No wonder we were called the Fail Five.
It's seriously no wonder at all, huh?
So this is where you went!
What are you up to?
Uh, nothing...
Asagi was wanting to fly one last lap
around the campus.
I never said that!
Your AHSMBs are currently being
transported to the school.
Lieutenant Amane.
First Lt. Shirato.
Is something the matter?
Not really. The meeting just ended.
All of the economic powers
are squabbling over the
AHSMB technology and units.
After fighting a losing war for so long,
we had our first victory.
It's only natural for the MJP
and the AHSMBs to garner attention.
But they don't care about
fighting the enemy!
Each country merely wants to
stand above the others.
Fighting the Wulgaru isn't easy,
but Earth politics are no
laughing matter either.
They're so desperate for the technology
that some are asking to sponsor
Gurantseere Cosmopolitan Academy.
Others are trying to
volunteer new students.
Doesn't this fall outside
of your jurisdiction?
Yes, but with Commander Simon away...
Is he visiting the academy?
Are they ready?
Sir! They are already packed.
I believe they could leave tomorrow.
Very well.
I believe it is still too soon for them
to become official members of the army...
Your reasoning?
They have not fully
mastered their AHSMBs...
Plus they still seem uncertain
about the JURIA-SYSTEM.
Due to their innate personalities,
Tamaki Irie and Ataru
Suruga are adjusting to
the SYSTEM relatively well.
However, Asagi and Kugimiya both
deteriorate and freeze on the battlefield.
At times, Izuru Hitachi displays
bursts of power, but not reliably.
But there is nothing left
for you to teach them here.
I imagine the JURIA-SYSTEM
can only be mastered on the battlefield.
It requires situations where they
put their very lives on the line.
I will see to tomorrow's preparations.
What are those?
AHSMB?!
Awesome! Are they real?
They're nothing like our practice units.
Why the heck do we have to do
a demonstration?
Don't ask me!
Good morning.
You're here early.
This is just a demonstration.
It's hardly something
to stress out over.
We're stressed BECAUSE
it's a demonstration.
It could be scarier than a real battle.
Do we seriously have to
go through with this?
As I explained yesterday,
Blue 1 and Red 5 will perform linkages.
Gold 4 will fire while under 1G.
You'll be using live ammo,
so bear in mind the
gravity, wind, humidity
and air density while calculating your trajectory.
Purple 2 will issue orders and Rose 3
will offer aerial support.
That comprises this demonstration.
The one thing I suck at...
You failed once in front of
the entire universe, remember?
Shut it!
At least you get to show off!
All I get to do is shoot!
Don't tell me...
I'm issuing orders from THERE?
You're on stage!
That might be the most
embarrassing job...
Team Rabbits will hereby offer you
a demonstration.
I never expected a mission like this
before graduation...
Let's do our best!
This is a great chance to rid ourselves
of the name "Fail Five".
Dude, you're planning to become
an instant school hero, aren't you?
This really is a great
opportunity, isn't it?
Assuming we don't fail!
Blue 1, Gold 4, Red 5, take off!
Blue 1, Red 5, linkage!
Rose 3, blast off!
Tamaki, you went lower
than you were supposed to...
Gold 4, now!
No one was watching me!
Who was that applause for?!
That is all for their demonstration.
It's over...
I'm beat!
Hey!
Sorry for everything.
It won't be the same without you guys.
Although we'll be hitting
the frontlines soon enough.
Bye! Let's meet up again
sometime, Fail Five!
Of all the nerve!
Graduates, enter.
Come receive your medal
of rank, Tamaki Irie.
Ma'am!
Kei Kugimiya.
Toshikazu Asagi.
Ma'am!
Are you all right?
What a doozy...
What were you thinking, Asagi?
I'll regret it forever.
I bet that gave you three
holes in your tummy.
Did you get hurt?
Nah, I'm fine.
Asagi hogged all of the attention
back there, didn't he?
That's not the type of attention I want!
Hurry on!
We'll never come back
here again, will we?
Yeah...
That's kinda... sad.
From now on...
Wherever our team is,
that will be where our home is.
Let's strive...
...to do our best as Team Fail!
That's not our team name!
Really?
Don't gimme that!
Stoopy-poopy-doopy head!
Look!
"Stronghold of Lust"