Give it to me!
All...
...right!
Yes!
Well done!
That was no ordinary
prefectural qualifier match.
I got goosebumps.
All right! Let's do our greetings.
Right!
Now we're at one loss, one win.
Don't get on your high horse.
I won't.
Haikyu!!
Episode 25: "Declaration of War"
Thank you very much!
We did it, Sensei.
Yes.
It...
looked like he was actually able to
predict where Hinata was going to hit.
If it wasn't caught by the
block, changing the course,
That was a very heartwarming match.
he might have picked it up.
Karasuno           Aoba Johsai
Say what you will, but the
results are what you see.
There's no way your
disappointment will subside.
I'm sure there are even
some plays you regret.
With that in mind, let me just say something:
You fought well.
Let's go greet the people in the stands.
How can I be the ace when
I couldn't even make that?!
Thank you very much!
Rule the Court
Hey, hurry up!
Yeah!
We fell over!
You're way too worked up!
Hinata, you dumbass!
Don't ever forget this sight.
We're definitely going to pay them back.
Yeah!
Apparently we're about to head out.
Yeah.
Karasuno High School
Volleyball Club
Kageyama!
We're not gonna lose next time!
Apparently.
Right.
Hey!
You guys were awesome!
Yay!
Ne-san!
Ryu!
You did great, getting that last one!
You looked awesome!
Right...
Or rather, I appreciate the support,
but don't use my name so much...
Don't be embarrassed!
Ow, ow, ow! Seriously, stop!
Hey, your boobs!
Your boobs are in my face!
That was a great serve, Tadashi!
Thank you very much.
What? You can't handle
some boobs in your face?
The last one! The last spike was amazing!
Thanks!
Thanks.
I couldn't help but remember our last match,
so when I saw the triple block,
it was quite chilling...
Just like when Azumane faced the Iron Wall,
Kageyama might have thought
it was best to think ahead and have
Hinata's hand break through...
No... It might just have been instinct.
It's so amazing that you got
through such a high block!
That last part...
When the Great King reacted...
I thought he was going to get it.
The Great King really is amazing.
When the bus comes, will you load our stuff?
I'm gonna go get everyone else.
Right.
This is a warning, Oikawa.
Don't choose the wrong path again.
You chose the wrong path.
There was a place where you could
have realized your true potential.
Because of your worthless
pride, you didn't choose it.
So you're trying to tell me
that I should have gone to Shiratorizawa
instead of Seijoh, right?
No team is guaranteed victory.
If nothing else, I can say...
...that my team is the strongest one here.
Shiratorizawa Academy
Wow, I see you're still laughably confident!
Worthless pride, huh?
That's true...
Listen up, Ushijima.
I never thought my decision was wrong,
and my volleyball hasn't ended at all.
Don't you ever forget
my worthless pride.
Oh, yeah.
If you keep all of your attention on me,
you're going to get stabbed from
the direction you least expect.
What's that supposed to mean?
My junior...
isn't smart, and isn't even
close to my level yet...
But now that he's not
by himself, he's strong.
When crows flock, they might even
kill a huge, white eagle.
Hey.
What the hell are you doing?
Hurry up and load your
your stuff onto the bus.
What's the matter, you two?
Infertile soil will not
bring forth splendid fruit.
I'll show you just how much
we can grow from the concrete.
Today's Events
Ah, w-wait!
The Japanese National
High School Volleyball Tournament
Miyagi Prefecture Qualifiers (Boys)
Finals
Shiratorizawa vs. Karasuno
Haikyu!!
No surprise. They're fast asleep.
You can't blame them.
They fought two matches
with powerful opponents.
I'm thankful for you, Sensei.
Wha?! Where did that come from?
The fact that a team like ours,
which hadn't done well for a while,
got to do so many practice matches with
the powerhouse schools from Tokyo...
All I can say about that
is that we were blessed.
You need someone else to
become more disciplined.
No matter how hard you try
by yourself, there's a limit.
The fact that we were able to
regain our connection with Nekoma
is a much bigger deal than
you or the team realizes.
You did an amazing thing.
What? No, I didn't...
If we're able to win tomorrow,
please make sure you compliment me then.
Right.
All right. Get your things and head
straight to the gym for a meeting.
Right...
You totally drooled. Gross.
My drool isn't gross!
Oh, they're back.
Congrats on making it to the finals!
Oh, Michimiya.
How did you know?
They just announced it on
the school announcements.
That's amazing!
The fact that you were able to beat Seijoh and
made it to the finals is just... is just...
Amazing! It's insane!
Your lack of vocabulary is insane.
Wait, what happened to
your face?! That bruise!
Yeah... It happened at the match today...
It looks a lot worse than it actually feels.
I see...
Hey, boys' volleyball team.
That was amazing!
Congrats!
Hinata! Kageyama! Well done!
Sensei!
Thanks!
I'm going to cheer you on tomorrow!
You better win!
Do your best!
You guys all stayed late for us...
M-Sta Miyagi is gonna start!
Good day-evening.
Good day-evening!
Today, the Sendai Municipal
Gymnasium in Tomizawa
hosted the quarter and semifinals
of the Miyagi prefectural qualifiers
for the National High School
Volleyball Tournament,
otherwise known as the
Spring Volleyball Tournament.
Karasuno                                   Aoba Johsai
In the first match, Karasuno
High School defeated
the powerhouse school,
Aoba Johsai High School,
earning them a spot in the finals
for the first time in years.
Wow, that is certainly surprising.
To think that Seijoh would be eliminated.
Precisely. With Oikawa-kun at the lead,
they are an extremely well-balanced team,
so it's sad that we won't be
seeing them in the finals.
Come on! Show us a little more!
We actually won!
Yeah! Yeah!
Stop showing just Seijoh!
This happens every time.
The lost in the semifinals.
What do you expect?
Semifinals, Round 2
The Champions' Dignity
Next, we have the second
round of the semifinals.
In this match, the school garnering
attention rightfully won,
and moved toward the finals.
Now the headliner arrives.
It would be Shiratorizawa Academy,
that has won this tournament
the last three years,
but is led by Ushijima Wakatoshi,
who has played for the under-19 national team.
Shiratorizawa Academy           Kesenike West High School
Looks like they had no problems winning
straight through the semifinals.
Yes.
This year, they've gathered members that
might just promise them victory at Nationals.
I think we can expect great things from them.
It'll be interesting to see
how high Karasuno can climb
against the powerful Shiratorizawa Academy.
You can watch the finals live on this channel,
tomorrow at 11 AM.
Tomorrow: Volleyball Spring
Tournament Finals: 11:00~ Live!
The match that will determine the
Miyagi Prefecture representative...
Be sure not to miss it!
Now, then. We'll be going against
Shiratorizawa tomorrow, but...
In the three years since
Oikawa joined Aoba Johsai,
they have never beaten Shiratorizawa.
Not even once.
They are undoubtedly the undefeated champions.
Of course, there's Ushijima,
but there are plenty of others
that are top in the prefecture.
It's no fluke that they are top in the prefecture.
Shiratorizawa is far stronger
than you can even imagine.
No one actually thinks we're going to win.
Huh?
What is it, Hinata?
That doesn't matter!
I think...
Hey, don't talk to the coach like that!
Oh, uh... I didn't mean it like that...
Just say it.
R-Right.
No one thought that we were going
to beat Seijoh, either.
That's why it doesn't matter...
I think.
Tomorrow, we're going to
be the challengers again.
Let's turn the tables on them.
Right!
"The fallen powerhouse."
"The flightless crows."
There's no one to call you that anymore.
Birds with the wind in their wings are
flying across the great blue sky right now.
And all of you should be able to make it!
To the highest limit,
Karasuno High School
Volleyball Club
to the farthest limit!
Now, everyone. The time has come!
Let's win tomorrow and
make it to nationals!
Yeah!
All right. Now get home and go to
bed so you aren't tired tomorrow.
Right.
All right, dismissed!
Right!
Kageyama.
Throw me a toss.
Huh? They couldn't be...
I knew it.
Ah! Yachi-san!
Could you throw us some balls?
You guys had two matches today, so
you should just go home and rest up.
If I went home right now,
I'd be too worked up to sleep.
So, please!
Please!
Throw it, please!
Okay.
Yeah!
Give me one more!
Yeah.
One more!
What's the matter, Yachi-san?
Oh! I-I'm sorry!
I just remembered something...
What did you remember?
The time you two got into that fight,
I kept throwing balls to you like this.
Really?
What?! You don't remember?!
Hinata like charged you and
tried to fight with you,
and then Kageyama-kun started
punching and pushed you over...
I was super scared!
O-Oh...
Sorry.
Oh, uh, that's not what I meant...
I thought of this, watching the match today.
If I hadn't become a manager,
I wouldn't have been able
to watch today's matches,
wouldn't have been so excited and flustered,
or been so happy when you won,
and my heart wouldn't have felt so warm.
It's all because I watched
each of you work so hard
to do something that you
couldn't do before...
If I hadn't been here, I would have
never had that experience.
So, thank you.
No, no! We should be thanking you!
You stayed with us through all our practices!
If you weren't with us, Yachi-san, we might
not have completed our new quick, either!
Really? I was of some use, even
though I'm just a Townsperson B?
Of course!
You're the best Townsperson B
in the Tohoku region!
Is that even a compliment?
Of course it is!
If you're actually thankful,
too, you need to thank her!
Ah... Thanks.
Is that all you can say?
There are so many other ways to say it!
Shut up! I thanked her, didn't I?
N-Now, now...
What are you doing?
Sh-Shimizu-senpai?!
Resting properly is another important
part of preparing for matches, you know.
S-Sorry!
Come on! That's enough!
Let's clean up!
What?
Come on, hurry up!
Okay...
We got in trouble because of you.
You wanted to practice, too, didn't you?
I'm sorry for helping them practice.
No, it's fine.
Actually, thanks for practicing with them.
Right!
Hitoka-chan, it's already dark, so do you
want me to go to the bus stop with you?
O-Okay!
Hinata and Kageyama, as soon as you're
done, you need to go straight home.
Right!
I wonder how the Little Giant
felt the day before the finals...
I'm super nervous,
but...
Isn't it even more exciting now?!
We're going to win tomorrow.
Yeah!
But man... Who ever thought that
Karasuno would make it to the finals?
They beat Seijoh,
so maybe they're becoming a powerhouse again.
Hey, speaking of...
It's Ushiwaka.
H-Hey!
Hinata Shoyo. Kageyama Tobio.
We made it to the finals.
We, who grew from the concrete,
will beat you and go to nationals!
I look forward to it.
Let's meet on the court.
Damn it...
I wanna hurry up and fight him!
All right! We're gonna make it to the
spring tournament, no matter what!
Yeah!