Second Plate
Episode 6
This may as well be the famed
battle on Gojo Bridge.
A battle between the knife-wielding Benkei
and the knife-wielding Ushiwakamaru!
Here's my twist!
It smells spicy, but meltingly tender...
What a unique, smokey fragrance...
That's bacon!
But if he's trying to match Yukihira,
he'd be using oxtail in his stew.
What's the bacon for, then?
Bacon in beef stew can only mean one thing...
He means to use it as garniture.
Dawn Will Come Again
Yukihira Soma, your recipe is intended
for a beef stew that has been strained.
That'd make the dish a dull one,
consisting of only sauce and meat.
And that's why the garnish,
or garniture, becomes crucial.
Beef stew is said to have
evolved from beef bourguignon,
a stewed beef dish with red wine
from the Bourgogne region in France.
It also always comes with garniture:
usually croutons,
glazed pearl onions,
sauteed mushrooms,
and bacon.
The smell is sure mouth-watering.
It's mellow, yet so striking!
He used mesquite wood to smoke the bacon.
It's a tree in the legume family
originally found in South America.
It's virtually unknown in Japan
as a wood used for smoking meats.
In Texas, home of barbecue,
it's one of their favorite
smoking wood chips.
Because of its sharp smell,
it's used to smoke meats with strong flavor,
and imparts a bright, golden color.
In the brine,
I used sage, nutmeg, and bay leaf,
as well as my secret ingredient—brown sugar!
The umami will be remarkably enhanced.
Was Mimasaka that knowledgeable
about smoking and curing?
His knowledge and expertise
are on par with Ibusaki's!
What's going on?!
Asshole...
Yukihira-kun doesn't seem to be going
for anything unusual with his garnish.
He probably didn't think of it as
anything other than something on the side.
Huh?
Garnish, garnish.
The garniture is a critical component
of beef stews, too.
How disappointing.
Yukihira Soma cannot win!
Leaping to conclusions before even
tasting his dish... Oh, how distasteful.
Having someone like you as the head chef
must make the kitchen very tense.
Shut up, thirty-year-old.
I'm not thirty yet!
I'm in my twenties!
Cut it out with the cute act!
Tsunozaki, you can't
bring up age to someone's face.
'Kay, I understand, Fuyumi-senpai.
Why're you being polite
to Mizuhara-senpai?!
I choose who deserves my respect.
Oxtail, the critical ingredient,
was profiled by Mimasaka.
He then added a twist with his special bacon.
Yukihira is definitely between
a rock and a hard place now.
Wh-What should he do?
At this rate, Yukihira will...
Fine, I'll quit being a chef if I lose.
Yukihira-senpai...
Oh, you're Sotsuda Mitsuru.
You should be more careful with your passwords.
Using your birthday's a bit too obvious.
I'm going to tell the entire campus
about Yukihira-senpai's victory
with my special edition!
You saw my notes?!
You really made my work easy.
It's all thanks to you.
All the days Yukihira-senpai
spent testing his recipes...
All that time he spent
trying to be innovative...
Mimasaka got all that information.
And it's my fault.
That's...
Tsunozaki Taki-senpai, was it?
I think you've been saying
a lot of things about me,
but I'll hear your complaints...
...after I've served my dish!
Those are...
...a lot of different...
...meat...
...parts!
Beef cheeks.
Beef tongues.
Tripe!
Fillet!
So...
Dear judges,
I will now spirit you away
to a meat theme park!
Parboil the beef tongue and peel it!
He's fast!
Brown the meat with butter for mildness,
plus olive oil for freshness of flavor!
Marinate the cheeks with red wine,
parsley stalks, and bay leaves.
Season with salt and pepper,
dust the meat with a thin layer
of flour, and then brown it!
Use the oven to braise the fillet,
still in the pot!
What?!
What's he doing?!
It means he's improvising
everything on the fly.
Improv cooking...
The skirt steak's being...
Oh!
What the hell?
Is he running away?!
Oh!
He's coming back.
Oh, I'm glad I brought my clay
cooking stove to the standby room.
Using a clay cooking stove for beef stew?
What's his game plan?
He's really just putting
the dish together right now.
I see, Yukihira.
Like I thought, that's the
approach you chose to take.
Opponents who know about my perfect
profiling take one of two approaches.
One is to put up a front,
then try to deceive me.
Flan
They first announce what dish
they'll make before the match,
then try to confuse me by making
a different dish at the match.
The other one,
which is more likely the more confident
the opponent is about their skills,
is improv cooking!
Empty
They show up without a single plan,
then start cooking.
As long as they don't think of anything,
they think I won't read their thoughts.
Well, the majority of them
give in to panic
and lose without even
producing a finished dish,
but I bet you'd be able to
serve a pretty good dish.
You're not the type to panic midway.
Why're you praising me all of a sudden?
I have faith in you, you see.
I know everything about you.
I know you went by Aldini's
apartment this morning,
and I know you got
a ton of meat after that.
We will first evaluate
Mimasaka Subaru's dish.
Well, enjoy.
He used bacon, mushrooms,
and glazed pearl onions as the garniture.
The french word for glazed,
"glacé," means to freeze.
The glossy surface, like ice,
visually pulls the dish together.
Shut up!
Just dig in already!
I... I... I will.
The oxtail's viscosity and the mild white miso
hidden deep within are exquisite!
I think my tongue's melting apart!
And yet, the fragrance of mesquite
from the bacon strikes a powerful note!
It's unbelievably delicious!
I've predicted all your thoughts.
I knew you'd spring for improv cooking, too.
That's why I went for this special bacon!
It spent a whole five days in the brine!
Then I air-dried it for a whole day,
then smoked it for five hours.
This level of umami requires
this much time and effort.
Indeed...
The umami of this carefully-nurtured pork
serves not to undermine, but instead
to heighten the beef's flavor!
The time and effort this required...
the weight of it!
This dish possesses a strength
that can be considered the
total opposite of an improv dish!
It's just like what happened
in Takumi-cchi's match!
He even knew that Soma-kun
would try improv cooking...
He predicted everything.
He made a preemptive move!
So light! So tender!
This flavor goes far beyond the
realm of possibility with profiling.
This is as though...
...there is a fierce clash
between meats in the fighting ring!
This extreme deliciousness
shakes you to the very bone!
No! I can't contain it all!
The interplay between beef and pork...
Their cross-impact!
High praise!
Even the professional chefs are in awe!
How foolish, Yukihira!
Building a dish on the fly
as inspiration strikes you...
It may sound like a great idea at first glance,
but it's nothing other than blanking out!
Those who plan their cooking
right down to the last detail
and make the necessary
preparations always win!
No matter how many tricks you may try
to hide up your sleeve, it's useless!
It's all pointless!
Well, don't ever forget this moment.
It's the last dish
you'll ever serve to a customer.
You make me sad, Mimasaka.
See, I also had faith in you.
What?
I also thought about you all last week.
No matter what he may try to pull,
it should fall within
my range of predictions.
And yet... why am I afraid?
Well, here you go.
Enjoy!
It's the Yukihira-Style Beef Stew—
the Autumn Election Special!
What?
So many different meat parts!
This'd better not be a joke.
I've never seen a beef stew like thi—
What do you mean?
It is beef stew.
That's all just garniture.
What?!
That's all garnish?
The smoky fragrance of charcoal...
It's cooked just right.
Hmph.
Shoving random ingredients together
into a mish-mash...
Talk about a crude attempt!
It could hardly live up to my garniture.
I nurtured my special bacon
with the alluring smell of mesquite.
He can't compete with my
meticulously-cultivated flavor.
Hmm.
The stew itself is not that different
from the one we just had.
As for the garniture...
What?!
Right!
Left!
And a surprising loop!
Delicious!
The meltingly tender cheeks
fall apart when you bite in!
The tongue and tripe offer
great texture and mouthfeel!
The charcoal-grilled skirt steak
is unbelievably juicy
because of its thick cut!
Even when tasted with the stew,
the garniture adds a
great accent to the dish.
Indeed.
This may seem slapdash at first glance,
but each component
has been precisely prepared.
It is an attraction that
has been carefully composed.
It is perfectly balanced.
Impossible!
How could he improvise that?!
To be honest,
I was thinking along the same lines as you.
About using a strongly flavored garniture
like smoked bacon to strengthen the flavor.
But that wouldn't be right.
That wouldn't be my own cooking.
I wanted something where
a wide range of flavors and ingredients
would gather into a single dish.
I never thought beef stew could have
so much depth and range of flavor.
Oh, well, my thinking
was inspired by a certain dish.
What dish?
I only had that flash of inspiration
this morning, but yeah.
It was the Chikuzen stew.
Huh?
The dish is commonly
misinterpreted as a simple stew,
but when it's made by a professional,
it's something else.
Right, Hinako-senpai?
Yes.
By simmering each vegetable ingredient
separately for the optimal amount of time,
you can maximize each
ingredient's color and flavor.
Then you reassemble the
components into the final dish,
while paying minute attention
to the balance of ingredients.
This dish is the same.
Chikuzen stew... that's definitely
a dish of the people.
That's Yukihira's specialty!
Yukihira, weren't you just doing
improv cooking without any pre-planning?!
I never said it was improv.
I've been building this dish
for my entire life!
The path I had to take
to get to this point...
The countless flavor
combinations I've tried...
I called on everything I had
to create the dish in my head.
You've always only taken
the one step necessary
to discover and surpass
your opponent's dish.
I thought you wouldn't be able to do
what I was attempting.
An approach my perfect profiling
cannot reach?!
What he built is
a paradise decorated with all the
delicious flavors beef has to offer...
A land of dreams that makes
you want to stay forever...
Beloved by all!
Yukihee Land!
Hey.
Let's remember today forever.
Yeah!
Let's all be friends forever!
Let go of me!
Taki-chan, you have small, cute hands.
What?!
Why are you all teary-eyed?!
So cute!
It seems Yukihira was the one
who didn't blank out in the end.
Stop staring!
Go back to your seat already!
The long, long history
of pursuing your own cooking...
That is the depth possessed by
a professional chef.
Yukihira has concentrated all of that
most admirably into a single dish!
We'll now enter the final assessment.
This concludes round one of the
Autumn Elections' Semi-Finals,
and the Shokugeki!
Judges, please cast your vote!
Now, what is the outcome?!
Yukihira Soma
A unanimous vote!
Candidate Yukihira Soma
has won the Shokugeki,
and will proceed to the finals!
Glad you enjoyed it!
He won!
Soma-kun!
Impossible...
No one can escape my profiling!
If that's what you think,
you should taste this, too.
Yukihee Land!
Shit... why is it... so pleasant?
I'm starting to remember how it used to be
when I'd just started cooking!
Young Master Subaru,
you're so clever with your hands!
You can recreate any dish
just by glancing at the recipe!
You're your father's son, for sure.
What wonderful talent!
You're making me feel embarrassed.
Mimasaka Subaru (Age 12)
This is just me learning by imitation.
Would Dad praise me if he sees this?
Don't be so happy over this poor imitation!
A true top-notch chef will have originality!
This restaurant has no need for chefs
who have no personal creed!
A few days later,
there was a showcase of our new dishes
with a lot of VIP customers in attendance.
I didn't do it out of malice.
I just wanted his respect.
I added just one simple twist
to Dad's specialty dish,
and I won.
I was exiled...
No, that's not it.
Dad ran away from me.
Oh... cooking's easy.
Shokugeki
Just one step...
One small step is all I need
to surpass my opponents.
I have that talent!
Mimasaka Subaru
Look, see?
All the elites at Japan's
elite culinary academy
are at their wits' end and losing to me.
Top-notch? Creed?
Yeah, right.
Worthless chefs!
Mimasaka Subaru... you are useful.
Come work for me.
I'll let you wreak whatever havoc you want.
With this Shokugeki,
Mimasaka Subaru has lost
all rights to these tools.
Yukihira Soma, I understand you wish to
return all of them to their former owners.
Is that correct?
Yup!
Ah! One hundred knives
are being returned to their chefs!
Um, Yukihira-kun.
This knife belonged to my mom.
I got it when she passed away.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
It's time.
I'll leave Totsuki.
I won't cook anymore.
I suffered such a miserable defeat.
There's nothing left for me to be proud of—
Idiot!
Why did I accept your
Shokugeki challenge, then?
Hey, what's the matter?
Aren't you going to claim it?
The last one's yours, Takumi.
Aldini...
Mimasaka Subaru.
I lost to you.
It was total defeat.
But next time, I won't lose!
If you're one step ahead of me,
I'll take two... no, ten... a hundred steps!
I won't let things end this way.
Do you hear me, Mimasaka?!
The mezzaluna is now Yukihira's.
I will get it back someday.
After I beat you in a Shokugeki!
Until then, keep it safe for me!
See?
People who want to become professional chefs
are all really sore losers.
Listen up, Mimasaka.
Never plan to take your opponent's
entire pride in a single match ever again.
Even if all the confidence and pride
you've built over the years
is blown to pieces by a major failure...
Even if you've had a
soul-crushing experience...
In Preparation
...you still have to open shop the next day.
Open for Business
That's who chefs are.
Aren't you the same way?
Mimasaka?
Is he telling me to keep on cooking,
despite who I am?
My cold, hardened heart...
...is softening again.
I have cuticles like a girl!
You decided to put
your life as a chef on the line
to send a message about
starting over, even if you lose?
It doesn't make a whole lot of sense.
Yeah, you're right.
But it's something Soma-kun would do.
Hey, Nakiri.
I managed to get this far.
Just one more step until I get
to where I can face off with you
as the top first-year.
Know your place.
I am far above and beyond where you are!
Also...
...don't forget to bring me that book.
We'll now proceed to
Round 2 of the semi-finals!
We have Candidate Kurokiba Ryo
and Candidate Hayama Akira!
Food
Wars
The Second Plate
Next Episode: Beasts Devouring Each Other
Next time, "Beasts Devouring Each Other."