Why? Why did you...
This isn't like three years ago.
I've created a path.
I now have a country
to protect you.
Lieselotte...
Michael...
Allow me to abduct you.
Carmilla!
This is my way out!
My life was saved by you.
If it weren't for you,
I would be dead.
This is to repay me?
You have gone to such
lengths just for that?
No, not only for that.
Not only for that.
I... am in love with you.
Laugh at me if you like.
I have only met you twice.
And we haven't even spent an hour
in each other's company.
But even so...
I fell in love with you.
Michael...
You are very young, aren't you?
I've seen them in videos, but they're
quieter than I expected!
These use the Rave Engine?
Haruto, are you sure about this?
Your father, I mean.
Senpai...
I'm sure. We're done.
Walking away from such an
ideal environment...
As researchers,
they have a screw loose.
We're swimming in research funding,
and we don't have to obey
the Healthcare Charter.
And we can experiment on all the
human test subjects we want!
What?
I'm sorry, I'll let you
out later, I promise!
Hold it right there!
What did you do just now?
You're Saki Rukino,
the Valvrave pilot, aren't you?
I have more questions for you
than I can possibly ask.
It's over.
You're quite formidable,
aren't you?
No, I am weak.
It took me 10 years
to come this far.
If only I were stronger,
I could have—
L-elf!
Captain Cain said it would
be more fun over here.
Doing as he said
was totally the right call!
Let's have a knife fight.
I haven't done that in a while.
Death to traitors.
What was that?!
We're being shelled?!
They've found us out?
No way!
We're surrounded by Dorssian forces!
How did they know what
we were up to?
This is bad!
They've destroyed the runway!
You're kidding!
This shuttle can't take
off without a runway!
They saw through
our entire plan...
I had factored in the idea of using
the shuttle at the museum.
I would rather not destroy such
a beautiful building, though.
Takahi and the guys have been spotted!
We're not supposed to yet, but let's go!
What about this?
The fighting has started!
The time for hacking is over!
Oh, you're good!
I knew it!
You're amazing, L-elf!
This is the best!
If Q-vier is here,
that Cain is, too.
In which case, he must already
know about the shuttle.
This is no time to be distracted!
H-neun turned traitor!
Just like you, L-elf!
You didn't put him
up to it, did you?
L-elf! Get in!
Haruto Tokishima!
Hurry!
Never mind me!
Take her!
What about you?
This is about to become
a battle against Cain.
This time, I can't lose.
Lieutenant? Where are you going?
I can't fight that
with a knife, can I?
L-elf!
The bridge...
Haruto Tokishima, go to the museum!
Take good care of her!
Michael!
Let's go. It looks like
L-elf has a plan.
Very well.
Thank you, Haruto Tokishima.
The boy who is fighting
the whole world.
Who's that?
Who is that organism?
"Organism"?
Come on, this isn't the first
time you've seen a human being.
Human? No, that organism
is the same as me.
The same as you?
She is correct.
I am a Magius.
A lifeform that has
taken over a human body.
Lieselotte, I'm going to save you
for sure this time.
All combat-capable squads,
pursue L-elf.
Without him, the enemy is nothing
but a giant that has lost its brain.
Please explain, what in
the world is a Magius?
We Magiuses came to Earth
several hundred years ago.
It was a freak accident.
We could not establish
contact with our homeworld,
and had no means of getting back.
We had simply been waiting for
death on this unknown planet,
but then we transferred ourselves
into Earth's creatures.
Body-jacking...!
We have no physical form,
so we needed vessels, bodies,
to survive here on this world.
The same! The same!
You were marooned here, too!
Yes.
You are just like us, aren't you?
What am I, then?
Your kind seems to resemble us.
Artificially, I suspect.
The real goal of the Valvraves is
to create a new form of life!
Yes! You have surpassed humanity!
We have survived all this
time by passing from one
human body to another.
Then you're a super-old lady?
Otamaya, this thing is ready
to go at any time, right?
Assuming we can get out the front
door in one piece, yeah!
We're going to be destroyed
if we try to leave like this!
It's no use!
Let's just surrender!
Forget it! Don't give up
until L-elf comes back!
Way to go, Tokishima!
Just in time!
After a long, secret war against humanity,
we created an organization.
The Council of 101.
A group founded by selecting the most
influential humans and Magiuses.
Its objective was to
hide the existence of
Magiuses from the world,
and to allow for our food needs.
"Food"?
Runes!
Yes.
The only lifeform that possesses Runes
in large quantities here
on Earth is humanity.
I survive by devouring humans.
I am their enemy.
Haruto! You okay?!
Leave the rest to us!
Yamada, I can't—
Come inside for
the time being, Tokishima!
Take turns to keep your
heat levels from rising!
Inuzuka is here, too!
He says he has the prisoners
that they rescued!
Good! Let's open the hatch!
Otamaya!
It's no use!
The Impact Boosters' cooling
fins don't have enough cooling capacity!
We're out of spares!
Crap!
Ah, they are vulnerable to heat.
If we fly here on the surface,
we overheat in the blink of an eye!
Oh, these?
What are they?
They are the result of my refusing
the Council of 101.
It is my punishment for trying
to reveal everything and find
a way to coexist with humanity.
Punishment?
My Runes are siphoned off
at regular intervals.
It leaves me in a constant state
of barely clinging to life.
I am grateful I had this
chance to talk with you.
This is goodbye.
But you—
If I hadn't fled with you, Michael
wouldn't have left either, right?
Then you did this for L-elf...
Michael said that he
was in love with me.
But I am a Magius.
We cannot be with a human.
That's not right!
I'm begging you.
Don't arbitrarily write
it off like that.
L-elf wouldn't want that,
and knowing him,
I'm sure that he can make
both you and himself happy.
He's an amazing person.
He's so smart and level-headed that
it makes me mad. So please, don't.
Michael is most fortunate.
He has a good friend in you.
Damn it, they won't stand still!
Yamada, don't try to fly!
If you overheat, it's all over!
I already got bigger problems!
But if all they do is
provide cover, we'll never...
We wait for instructions
from L-elf!
Where's Professor Kibukawa?
In the hangar!
He's running a check
on the shuttle!
L-elf!
Has Unit 1 returned?
Yes! But we're pinned down!
Renbokoji. We're changing course.
Leave from the east side
and use the road as a runway.
We can't, there's a river to the east.
There's not enough room to take off.
If I lower the drawbridge, it will link
to the road on the far side of the river.
How will you lower it?
I'll think of something.
Just carry out your instructions!
Is the area past
the river safe?
It's a country road, but it will work.
Let's have faith in L-elf.
There's been a change in route.
We're using the road to
the east as a runway.
But there's—
L-elf will lower the drawbridge for us.
We'll use the road as our runway.
Turn it around!
Unit 5, smash through the wall!
L-elf... You always
think of something!
But... what about Michael?
I've beaten you, Cain.
The drawbridge is moving!
I see, that's what he's planning...
L-elf, you know this city like the
back of your hand, don't you?
Let's move! Can you fly?
I can fly! I'm good to go!
You're not getting away
from us!
It's fast!
Escape, Lieselotte...
Haruto Tokishima?
What kind of fool are you?
I know exactly how it feels
to want to save someone.
Löwenglitzen!
What the hell?!
This thing's aim is off!
No, it did enough.
Output falling!
We won't have enough thrust
to leave the atmosphere!
It's going to explode!
Detach us!
I can't! If we lose altitude now,
we'll be shot down!
What do we do?!
I don't want to die!
Can't you push it
with Unit 1?
I can't, I'm already on the
verge of overheating!
Michael... I feel the same way.
The curse of diffusion breakdown...
But that won't stop me!
That's the light of a Valvrave!
Is there another unit?
Michael.
It truly made me happy.
When you said
you loved me.
Hang in there!
We are not physical beings,
but rather spiritual ones.
But in spite of that, we
never quite understood
what the humans called "love."
And yet...
...now, thanks to you,
I feel as if I do.
That light... It's Lieselotte?!
Come on, reach!
Michael...
I wanted to...
...love you... in return.
Lieselotte!
Next time, episode 20.
"The Kamitsuki Exposed."
Valvrave the Liberator...
The system that will expose
the truth of the world.