You mean...
Don't worry.
I'm sure I'll grant your wish.
Nonoka?
Everyone
was together.
Yuzuki. Koharu. Mizusaka-kun.
And Togawa-san.
Nonoka...
Guys!
Look, Nonoka, everyone's here.
That means...
We're all here! We're all here!
We're all here!
There's something I need to tell you.
We should go back down the
mountain before it gets dark.
That's right.
Let's meet up with the teachers first.
Okay, Nonoka?
Wait!
I'd forgotten.
About the observatory, and about
the time we all played together.
And that I couldn't say goodbye.
And that we called the saucer.
Yuzuki, wait!
Hey, Koharu.
Damn it.
Sorry, I...
So what if you'd forgotten?
You thought we'd forgive
you because of that?
Huh?
A Fragment of Emotions
Sparkle!
All right!
Noel.
Nonoka.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I thought your wishes would come
true if we all came together.
But it wasn't like that.
I was wrong.
So, sorry!
Wait, my wishes?
I'll try hard.
Um...
So cheer up, Nonoka!
Nonoka.
Do we have a guest?
Dad.
Don't come out dressed like that.
Huh?
I did a good job cracking
the eggs today.
She'll try hard, huh?
It'll be a shame if my cooking gets col—
Sorry, I have to go out.
Hey!
Noel, right?
What's wrong?
It's so early.
I want to talk about something.
I...
Uh...
Oh, is it about Nonoka?
Then I don't intend to forgive
her or apologize to her.
She deserved it.
No, I want to talk about
Nonoka, too, but...
Then...
Did you call her?
I'm going home.
Wait!
What do you want now?
You tricked us, and then disappeared.
Do you even know what happened
because of the saucer?
I'm sorry.
That's why I want to know.
Tell me about this town.
Please, Yuzuki, tell me.
How could I...
I don't want to tell you anything.
I have things I need to be doing.
Are you going to keep doing that thing?
Of course.
I'm going to drive the saucer away.
Alone!
Yuzuki, listen.
Just leave me alone!
The saucer, Nonoka, Koharu, Souta...
I hate you all!
Yuzuki!
I guess
I'm not good enough.
Koharu, what's up?
Souta, where are you right now?
I'm heading home from school.
Oh.
I wanted to talk to you about
Yuzuki if you were nearby.
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
I just couldn't explain properly.
Don't worry too much about Yuzuki.
The bus is here.
Later.
Hey, wait!
Jeez, so rude.
It's the saucer's fault.
Mizusaka-kun!
Please!
Please help!
No Saucer
Please help us drive
the saucer out of town!
Please, help us!
Wait, please.
At least take this, please.
Please.
The details are...
No saucer!
Please help!
Please hear me out, just a little!
Please!
No saucer!
Please help!
Let's drive the saucer out of town!
Let's drive the—
Thank you.
Come on.
Please help!
Noel.
We promised.
Thanks.
Hip hip hooray!
Please!
Please help!
Dew of Kiriyako
Here.
Really?
My sister's causing you trouble.
It's my fault.
Thanks, Mizusaka-kun.
Were you at school?
About my career options.
There isn't anyone else
going to study abroad.
I can only talk to the
teachers about it.
You're studying abroad?
Just so you know,
it has nothing to do with the fact
that I don't get along with Yuzuki.
I-I wouldn't have...
I've always planned to go
overseas after middle school.
What?
You were fighting over steamed buns.
That was a long time ago.
But she's really doing all
that to get back at me.
It might be good for us to
be away from each other.
To get back at you?
She probably wants to bother
me because she hates me.
I don't think that's it.
There are still some things that
haven't gone back to how they were.
They used to launch
fireworks from the lake.
Fireworks.
Yuzuki still wants
to see the fireworks.
Fireworks?
Obviously we can't.
Why not?
We promised to watch
the fireworks together!
They were canceled
because of the saucer.
What do you want me to do?
Onii-chan, you idiot!
Stupid Yuzuki.
Shiihara Shop
Please!
Please help!
Don't look at the saucer!
Please!
Why not?
Because it's embarrassing.
No, that's not it.
It's because nothing good comes
of being involved with the saucer.
Come on, Noel, don't
say weird things.
But!
Thank you.
Saucer Palace
Excuse me.
Coming.
Thank you.
Hey, what's that outside?
I'm sorry.
Please!
Please help!
Yuzuki.
What?
Can I ask you to stop?
It's bothering the customers.
I'm not bothering them.
I'm getting complaints from customers.
You're saying that to try to
get rid of me, too, aren't you?
Like the other places.
Please, Yuzuki, don't make me say any more.
What's wrong?
Sorry for the trouble, everyone.
Wait.
Wait!
Please.
Um, here.
I'll help.
But are you sure?
Yes.
I'm always on your side, Yuzuki.
Liar.
Yuzuki,
where are we going next?
There's nowhere left to go.
I'll work even harder.
Forget it.
It's not worth it.
Thanks for helping me.
But...
Thanks.
What's wrong with that kid?
What is that Mizusaka-san person doing?
What?
We live in different towns,
but if this whole class cooperates,
I think we can get rid of the saucer.
What's with her?
Mizusaka hasn't changed,
even in middle school.
If only she didn't do that.
Come on, listen up!
Hey, don't you think so, too, Shiihara-san?
I know Yuzuki really well.
So I can't laugh.
You don't know her. How can
you say something like that?
Sorry.
Could you stop helping Yuzuki?
Why?
I don't want her to cause you trouble.
I'm fine.
I'm glad we talked.
It's nothing, really.
Besides, Koharu probably understands
Yuzuki better than I do.
Thanks for this.
Can't you make up with Yuzuki?
I wonder.
I used to know everything.
How can I help her?
Can you talk to her, too?
I will, too.
Why won't anyone understand?
I don't need anyone if
nobody's going to help me!
Yuzuki.
Yuzuki!
What are you doing, Yuzuki?
Let go!
Don't get in my way!
Stop it already.
You're just causing people trouble.
You're not accomplishing anything.
You're more worried about
your shop, aren't you?
How could you say that?
You're just like Souta.
You think what I'm doing is stupid!
But you know that what Yuzuki's
doing is pointless, right, Koharu?
Well...
You think it doesn't mean
anything, don't you?
You do, don't you?
Well...
Say it!
I do.
I hate you.
The one thing I can do...
We're closed for today.
Koharu!
Nonoka.
Are you all right?
Did you need something?
Lend me a hand, Koharu.
Next episode of Celestial
Method: "Flower of Light."
Enjoy.
Flower of Light