You're working hard.
Aoyama.
Surely you don't have
to hammer it that hard.
It didn't really need to be
fixed in the first place.
I know.
Sakura Hall
I just thought, this way,
it'll never fall off again.
You're right. Never again.
What about you, Aoyama?
Are you already packed
and ready to go home?
Yup.
That's all you're taking?
I'll be back again soon.
I don't want to give up.
My feelings have become much
stronger than they were before.
My desire to become a voice actress.
Aoyama.
Go home to Osaka.
Chihiro-sensei.
Don't mind if I do...
Go convince your parents.
What?
I'm sure you're thinking...
that you've been getting by on
your own these last two years.
Thinking your own thoughts,
making your own decisions...
If you think that makes you an adult,
you couldn't be more wrong.
That's something you do if you're
a kid who can't be bothered...
to listen to others' opinions.
Hey, Sensei. You're being too harsh.
It's fine, Kanda-kun. She's right.
When my father opposed my decision,
I think I chose the easy way out.
I just threw a tantrum because I
didn't get my way, and ran out.
I'm going to go home and talk to them.
I'll ask them to let me pursue my dream.
I'll ask them to let me stay in Sakura Hall.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll tell you one thing.
Your last two years weren't a waste.
Not at all.
Despite how she acts, she does
sound like a teacher sometimes.
I rented a van!
Load 'er up!
Okay.
There you are.
Thank you.
So heavy...
Thanks for everything.
If you invite me to your
wedding, I'll come running.
You're an infuriating brat to the very end.
Okay, let's go!
Thank you!
Chihiro-san!
Sensei!
I'm so tired.
Oh? Am I late?
Kazuki.
As a former resident of Sakura Hall,
I came to see off my successors.
Liar.
I suppose.
I figured I'd come fill
the hole in your heart.
I'll go get changed.
Do you want to go for drinks?
What? This early?
Is there a problem?
No, I'll join you.
Let's be friends forever.
Goodbye for today.
Until we meet again.
Kouhai-kun, I can't hear you!
Until we meet again...
First, Rita...
I don't know when we'll meet again.
Ryunosuke, please don't forget about me.
How am I supposed to forget you when
you're constantly coming to Japan?
That's different.
Well, Ryunosuke, it's time for
our touching farewell.
You're doing something
inappropriate again!
What's so inappropriate
about a handshake?
Oh, a handshake.
Okay.
There it is!
Rita-san!
You're as gullible as ever.
H-H-H-How shameless!
That sort of behavior is—
And one for you, too.
Waaaait!
Next, Jin-san and Aoyama.
Don't make that face.
I can't stand being away
from you, after all.
I feel anxious when you're not around.
Am I really that untrustworthy?
That's not what I mean.
I just wish I had
something more certain.
I see.
In that case, I'll take a
page out of Rita-san's book.
Th-They're demons...
If that's still not enough,
I'll leave you this.
To Jin
Is that a love letter?
C-Congratulations on getting hitched.
That's not funny, Aoyama-san.
It's the form from...
Once I get back from Osaka,
let's go submit it together.
Jin...
Jin!
I can't watch this.
Yeah.
Tell me about it.
I should get going.
Okay, get home safely.
No, Sorata.
Huh?
Nanami's home is Sakura Hall.
Mashiro.
She's right. Come back soon.
We'll be waiting for you.
Okay.
I'll definitely be back.
I won't give up. I'll be back.
I'll be waiting.
See you later.
Let's be...
I guess we don't have enough people.
The van feels kinda empty.
And finally,
Misaki-senpai.
Don't worry, Mashiron.
I'm going to Suimei University,
so we'll see each other soon.
For now, I've got to go home
and prepare for the move.
Okay.
Take care of Sakura Hall for me!
Farewell!
Hey, Akasaka.
What?
Can you make a game by yourself?
Watching Misaki-senpai made me think...
I should make something
just because I want to.
Even someone like me could start
working on something by myself, right?
Given your current programming abilities,
you're limited in what you can produce.
However, it's not impossible.
You could use a free game engine.
I see. That's all I need to know.
Since I made it through my presentation,
I feel like a door has opened.
But I learned that there's...
an unbelievably large world
waiting on the other side.
It may be frightening,
but I have to start walking...
in order to move forward.
Is that the time already?
I've got a meeting. I'll see you later.
A meeting?
But I thought you did all
your work through email.
Once in a blue moon, I have work
to do outside my room, as well.
It's just the two of us now.
Yeah.
Mashiro?
The cherry blossoms.
It's already been a year, huh?
Beautiful...
Yes, it is.
Two coffees.
Thank you.
You could use one, right, Aoyama-san?
Are you nervous?
Yes. It's been a while since
I last saw my father.
I think you've made the right decision.
We're just getting started.
There's no need for us to give up.
Not on Sorata, either.
What?!
Would you like milk?
No, thank you!
How grown-up of you.
So bitter...
We're home.
The first night I moved into Sakura Hall,
I looked in each of the empty rooms...
and I had a dream.
My dream was...
for all of Sakura Hall's
rooms to be filled,
and for days full of warm light
and laughter to follow.
Misaki-senpai.
Mashiro, what happened?
That painting...
I wanted to hang it up.
Oh, I see. You should've told me.
But it's a fabrication.
Hikari would never let you hold her.
She does sometimes.
Really?!
A kiss.
What? Hikari let you kiss her?
They were kissing all
over the place earlier.
Oh, you mean Senpai and the others.
You make them sound like perverts.
I want to try kissing, too.
I see.
What?!
I can't?
Is it... necessary for the
manga you're drawing?
I haven't decided yet, but probably.
I see...
I-In that case...
Do you want to try?
Um, I'd appreciate it if
you'd close your eyes.
Hikari?!
Hikari's jealous.
Hey, stop that!
Hey!
Not now.
Now?
It's interesting because there's
something to look forward to.
You're right.
My reservation for the future.
She's too much.
She's probably right...
Our futures will go on for a long, long time.
30th Suimei University High School
of the Arts Entrance Ceremony
What? Sakura Hall?
Don't do it, Hase-san.
The regular dorms have shared rooms.
I can't sleep in the presence of others.
Besides, my roommate
made a real racket.
Yeah, but...
Well, I need to take care of
the procedures to move in.
Faculty Office
Excuse me.
Hase Kanna
General Education Curriculum: Class 1-1
Kamakura Wada Public High School Graduate
Ah, so you're the girl.
Your friend's here.
This is the highest-scoring
freshman, Hase Kanna-san.
And this is the student exiled
from the regular dorms...
for sneaking a peek in the girls'
bathroom, Himemiya Iori-kun.
A Peeping Tom?
Your sister would cry if she knew
her younger brother had become...
a criminal immediately
after starting school.
Don't spread such scandalous
rumors about me.
I didn't actually see anything.
Now, now.
I don't know if you'll be able to
have a normal high school life,
but welcome to Sakura Hall.
Here! I brought you this from Osaka!
That sauce looks delicious.
We can turn half of this
into tuna cutlets.
That's amazing!
When I said I was throwing a
party for the new students,
the fishmonger gave it to me for free.
We can make hotpot with the head.
We've got to welcome them to
Sakura Hall with hotpot.
Just like they did for us.
You're really acting
like an upperclassman.
Nah, nothing. I'll help you.
It's okay. You just got back.
Why don't you go unpack your luggage?
Thanks.
Duty Board
Kanda: Mashiro Duty
Shiina
Akasaka
Aoyama
It's great your dad accepted your decision.
I'm not sure he accepted it.
I kinda forced it on him.
But I think he realized I
was serious about this.
Not going home for two years
really made an impression.
I plan to work part-time again
this year and save up money...
so I can attend a different training school.
So, we'll get to work hard together again.
Yeah!
Horror Adventure
Western House of the Dead
Is this your new pitch proposal?
Yeah.
By the way, Aoyama, could you
help me out with it later?
How so?
It's a horror adventure game...
that takes place in a
Western-style house.
I'm hoping to make a prototype
for the title screening.
Could you do some voices for...
You're assuming that your
presentation will be successful.
Maybe I'm getting ahead of myself.
It's good that you're more confident.
There are some lines here.
Hey, listen.
Why are you standing so far away from me?
I don't want to be near a pervert.
I told you, that wasn't...
Hello.
Blood! I want blood!
Young blood! Give me
your fresh, dripping blood!
Oh, welcome.
Hey, wait.
Hey.
A total hottie...
And a pigsty of a room.
A new person?
Y-Yes!
I'm Himemiya Iori, and I'm going
to be living here starting—
Take it off.
Huh? Wh-What's going on?
Take it off?!
Got it! If that's what you want,
I'm more than happy to oblige!
Mashiro, the new students...
Hey! What do you think
you're doing, you—
It's not what it looks like! I—
A painting of the new people.
You're going to add the new
students to this painting?
The skeletal structures of men are
varied and difficult to paint.
Sorry we scared you.
Why do I have to cut the grass, anyway?
Don't you want to welcome...
the new students into the
nicest possible environment?
Oh, it's fine. I enjoy a little excitement.
Where's Shiina?
She's still in her room.
Let's eat without her!
We can't do that.
Yuko?!
Why are you here all of a sudden?
I was even at the Suimei
High entrance ceremony.
Until yesterday, I was
Kanna-chan's roommate.
I wanted to surprise you, so I
asked Mom and Dad not to tell you.
Do you remember my exam number?
It was 99, wasn't it?
But! It was a fake number
meant to deceive you!
If you tell me it was actually
66, I'm cutting ties with you.
What? That's amazing!
How did you know?
I knew you could do it, Bro.
I refuse to acknowledge
we're related by blood!
I did it.
Whoa! That's me!
Amazing. In such a short amount of time...
You left me out, Mashiro-san!
Yuko, what are you doing here?
Make me a member of Sakura Hall.
I respectfully decline your request.
There's no space to paint Yuko.
I'm coming!
Yuko, we're going to talk about this later.
I moved in next door.
I came over to pay my respects.
I'm coming. Hold your—
Good evening!
I'm the newlywed who moved
in next door, Mitaka Misaki!
What? Mitaka Misaki...
What?!
Mitaka Jin
Mitaka Misaki
I couldn't wait until Jin graduated,
so I submitted the marriage registration.
What?!
Smells like hotpot!
You can save the moving soba for later!
Kamiigusa-senpai?!
Her tits are huge!
They're huge!
What was that graduation
ceremony speech about?
Sakura Hall still has a variety of colors.
Colors from before, as well as new colors.
We each have...
our own color shining brightly
on the canvas of Sakura Hall.
I'm going to leave this place!
I haven't decided what I
want to do in the future,
but for now, I guess I'm iridescent.
I will take off your underwear.
You're crazy!
He will send you a virus, lol!
Kouhai-kun, you're on Mashiro Duty!
I drew pictures.
The thing about talent...
is that it unconsciously
wraps up and destroys...
everyone around it.
Your scripts don't excite me!
I'll catch up to you someday!
Let's work hard together.
I think I wanted you to prove
hard work is rewarded.
I want to work hard with you, too.
You don't get it.
I'm telling you not to work so hard.
What's happening to me?
Is this...
love?
I love people who have goals!
I love people who work
as hard as they can!
I love you.
Love is simply a bug.
I love you!
So don't go!
It's not easy for me to tell
Misaki how I feel about her!
Your heart is pounding
because you're alive.
Your pulse sped up.
Leap into space!
Oh, man. I'm starting to have fun.
Don't stop running, Sorata.
All-out dash!
I don't know. I don't know
what this feeling is.
Are your precious friendships so fragile...
that you'd lose them just
because a building is torn down?
I told you, they're not!
I have to be prepared
to be with her forever!
I don't understand.
Why? Why am I not good enough?
My chest hurts, kouhai-kun.
Sakura Hall is Sakura Hall
because everyone is there.
We're all Sakura Hall.
How far do you think we can go?
We can go anywhere.
That's how I feel, living
at Sakura Hall.
Thank you for everything!
What color do you want to be?
Welcome to Sakura Hall