Antarctica, huh?
Antarctica, yeah...
It really is Antarctica!
Yeah...
High school girls!
Yes?
Within 100 kg. You're clear.
I ate so much while cutting down
on my sweets, but it didn't change!
You should think about that, my dear.
Is that really what we're taking there?
We can't go in the snow cat, I suppose?
Yuzuki-chan, you look like
you could die right now.
I certainly feel like it.
Look!
It really is a big boat, isn't it?
Right?
Yeah.
At least look first.
A Place Further Than the Universe
25 Likes
17 Comments
Partial Friendship
#JarGenie #IfYouTouchMeI'llKillYou #MessageRead
Challenge For Antarctic
Hey, lie down there!
Okay!
It's so cold!
Or not?
December is summer here,
so on warm days, it might not even
get below freezing during the day.
Really?
Hey, my hand's totally fine!
Cold!
I'll give you a quick tour before the
stuff arrives and things get crazy.
So this is Syowa Station?
That thing that looks like a stack
of cubes is the control building.
If this were a house, it would be like
the living room where everyone hangs out.
That's the generator building.
Those are the residence
building and the warehouses.
That's the Lakeside Hotel.
Lakeside?
It's what we call the lodging
house for the summer team.
Normally, the members who aren't staying
for the winter would live there.
But because there hasn't been maintenance
at the other building for three years,
and seeing as you're girls...
You get your own rooms!
We get to use all this?
The air is very dry, so be
prepared for lots of static.
But the floors are heated,
and if you open the blinds...
At last, I don't have to worry about the
things Kimari-san rambles in her sleep.
Do I really talk that much?
Yes, you do!
And you do it with your eyes open...
Emergency.
What is it?
The jar genie won't come out of the toilet.
He probably won't go through the ticket gate.
Like that.
What's the jar genie?
How should I know?!
Well, let's move on to
the control building...
Or that was my plan, but I bet the
stuff is about to start arriving.
Let's go back to the heliport.
Okay!
I'll have to replace this...
Ow.
Time for some cleaning up!
Okay, let's take a break
until the next one arrives!
You okay?
Yes.
I worked part-time at a moving company.
Okay, then rest for ten minutes and then
help me with the loading over there.
Oh? I got an email...
It might have arrived when
we were in the base earlier.
We get a cell phone signal
near the control building.
Shiraishi Tamiko
Wow, so we can use our smartphones,
even in Antarctica?
Penguins!
Keep your voice down!
Yuzu! The camera!
R-Right!
Just stay within five meters, okay?
Got it!
Pen...guin...
Hold it!
Okay, I'm filming! Yuzu, grab
the mike and do a report!
Hinata-chan, emergency!
What?
It's coming toward us!
It's coming... coming...
Wait, wait, wait! Stay within five meters!
Wait, wait!
No!
Never a dull moment, huh?
Something wrong?
Oh, no...
Is it really okay to drop
dirty snow in there?
They said it would get
filtered, so it's fine.
Don't take that off. You'll get sunburn.
But it's hard to breathe!
But it's just been one
job after another, huh?
No one's been here for three years,
so we'll probably be this busy for a while.
I see...
You don't like it?
Keeping busy is the best way
to speed the clock's hands!
Another made-up saying?
I thought that one up when I was
working at the convenience store.
I think I prefer to keep busy.
I'm exhausted!
I agree.
I think I like keeping busy, too.
What?
Well... we've been traveling
together for so long, haven't we?
Yeah! We have!
We talked about a lot of things
and had fun together, didn't we?
What's with you right now?
A drama?
I had an audition before we set out.
It's a morning drama. I'll be playing
the best friend of the protagonist.
No way! And you got the part?
Shiraishi Tamiko
It's decided! Well done!
You passed the audition for the morning drama!
Congratulations! Great job!
Love, Mom
Sent from myPhone
That's amazing!
It is great!
But when the drama starts shooting,
I'll have a lot less time.
We won't be able to hang out
together like this anymore!
You don't like that?
Well, even without the drama,
we'd be living separately again anyway.
B-But...
It's okay. We're all best friends already.
Best friends?
Are we best friends?
Don't cry.
But didn't you say before...
that you'd only just met?
Well, at the time, that was the case.
So when did you decide you were best friends?
Did it happen while I was in Hokkaido?
Well...
It did, didn't it?
Don't cry!
The three of you, without me...
Wait, wait, wait!
Without ever telling me...
Don't go outside!
Anyway, there's nothing we've
done without telling you!
Really?
You really don't trust anyone, do you?
Actually, there is one
thing we haven't told you!
But we are still friends. All of us!
Since when?
I don't know. No time in particular...
That's what being friends is, though!
But you never told me you
wanted to be friends.
Let's have another productive day tomorrow!
Yeah!
When did we become friends, huh?
You think she was waiting this whole time
for someone to say, "Let's be friends"?
We could just say it.
Hell no.
"You're obviously just saying
that because I made you!"
We don't have to do it.
How's Kimari doing?
I dunno. She said she could handle it...
But she's so bold about some things
and so timid about others...
Helmets good?
Helmets good!
Lunch Menu!
Christmas Antarctica Special
Chin straps good?
Chin straps good!
Health good?
Health good!
Feet good?
Feet good!
Let's have another productive day!
Let's do it!
Be safe!
They said we'd get to work indoors...
But it's colder in here than it is outside!
My nose is getting red!
They're conserving energy, remember?
We need to keep the indoor work short.
This is all of it, right?
Yes, thank you.
Next, take this.
A chicken?
Yeah, because it's Christmas.
I want you to find somewhere
warm to defrost it.
I had a few I set defrosting yesterday,
but it doesn't look like it'll be enough.
Somewhere warm...
I have an idea!
Go for it!
And you two can stay here and help me.
Yes, ma'am.
That'd be the best place!
That seems unspeakably dangerous.
What about here, in the sun?
It never sets here, after all!
I don't know...
They're both birds.
I don't think that matters to them.
There are penguins here, too.
Do they eat chicken, too?!
How should I know?!
There, that should do it.
Defrosting
Touch and
you die
Yeah!
But how are things going
with the other thing?
Oh, just perfect!
Okay, today's pick-me-up is done!
That's quite extravagant.
Well, it is Christmas...
Is Christmas that important?
Do you know the most important
parts of life on the station?
No...
Food and events.
We'll be living a spartan life in a
limited space for a long time, after all.
Is that right?
It's time for your pick-me-up.
Christmas cake!
Merry Christmas!
You don't like Christmas?
It's not that I don't like it...
But it's like a birthday, isn't it?
So?
It's not fair, is it?
Everybody has a birthday, yet there are
people whose birthdays get celebrated,
and people whose birthdays don't.
Isn't that your song?
You want to get the
external shots in advance?
Yeah.
Since they said we might not be able
to go outside if the wind picks up.
Um...
About that thing I mentioned before...
What happened?
I've decided to do the drama.
Really?
Yes. I gave it a lot of thought,
and apparently some people here
may be looking forward to it.
Yeah, that's right!
Yeah, yeah!
So, could I ask a favor of you all?
Could you fill this out?
What's this?
Friendship Contract
This way, even after our adventure is over,
and we're not around each other
as often, I know we'll be fine.
Oh, come on...
This won't mean anything.
I've been all alone before, so I know.
Even if you do this...
Kimari-san?
Sorry. I'm sorry.
You don't know, do you?
You can't know, can you?
Don't leave a scrap behind!
If you don't clean your plate,
you'll be denied bathroom privileges!
Let's dig in!
Cheers!
Still partially frozen.
Yeah, partially frozen.
It says "partially frozen
rice bowl" on the menu!
That's one way to put it.
Yuzuki-chan, want seconds?
No...
Kimari-san!
Um... after dinner, I was
hoping to talk to you.
Sorry, I have something
I have to take care of.
I see...
What should we do?
I don't know if I know what to say to her.
Then, should we lay off?
I didn't say that...
Yuzu.
Don't worry. She's not mad, or anything.
But Kimari-san cried.
I think she felt hurt.
It's all on you.
Don't ditch me!
Have I done something strange?
Well... I wouldn't say "strange."
If I were in your position,
I'd probably feel the same way.
It's just...
Merry Christmas!
Friendship isn't about lots of words.
I hear that a lot...
What is it about, then?
Give me a break...
It's about... feelings?
Feelings?
For instance, let's say you
tell Kimari you like her.
Kimari doesn't believe you, so she wants
you to write it down on a piece of paper.
You'd hate that, right?
You'd feel like she didn't trust you.
Well...
Seconds, please!
That's probably why she was crying.
Yuzu, Kimari already sees you as a friend.
But what makes us friends?
How do you become friends?
Well...
There's probably no real way to define it.
It's not like a parental
or spousal relationship.
It's more vague than that.
No one's to blame if it fades.
Oh, no...
That's the case for me, at least.
But that's what lets it feel unrestrained.
That's what lets us be together.
Merry Christmas.
We're back.
4. Antarctic Magic Show
5. Christmas Stories Two High School Girls
6. Golden Oldies Old Man Choir
7. Wrap! Wrap! Burp!
Are there good children here, too?
Why even bother with the performance?
That's why I didn't want to do this!
Why did you make us do it?
Forget it. Come on, let's go.
Kimari told us to, remember?
What does it mean?
I really don't think I understand...
Got it!
I'm on my way!
I'm sorry
Yes?
M-Merry Christmas!
What are you doing?!
It's Christmas, so...
That hurt!
Are you okay?
Could we talk for a minute?
Got it!
I'm on my way!
I'm sorry
It's hard to settle down when
it stays dusk like this, huh?
It's like the day never ends.
You're angry, aren't you?
You didn't write back.
Because you didn't have
anything to apologize for.
What's that?
Megu-chan has been my best
friend since kindergarten.
Right before I headed out, she said
she wanted to break things off...
Arrived in Singapore!
But I still think of her as a friend, so...
She doesn't respond often, does she?
Arrived in Australia!
I see.
But somehow, I can tell...
When I'm watching the screen,
and it pops up with the
little "message read" sign.
Message Read
She writes something back,
sometimes right away,
sometimes after a while,
sometimes half a day...
Each time I see it, I can tell.
"Ah, I bet she's at school right now."
"I bet she's in bed."
"I bet she's not sure whether
or not she should respond."
Send
I can tell just how she's feeling.
Is that weird?
I think that's what friends are for me.
It's totally vague, I know,
but that's what it is for me.
I'm sorry. I guess that
doesn't solve anything...
Merry Christmas!
And...
Happy birthday!
Yuzuki-chan, it's was your
birthday before, right?
But we spent so long being
seasick at the time...
We're sorry.
Kimari suggested that we should
celebrate it in Antarctica.
We had Yumiko-san set the ingredients aside.
Well, just fill in the parts we
messed up with your imagination.
Yuzuki-chan...
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday!
Go on, blow them out.
Again?
This is just like the first
time we met you, huh?
I'm not crying!
Blow them out before they melt.
Yuzuki-chan.
No!
Because...
it's the first time...
friends have celebrated my birthday...
Go on, Yuzuki-chan.
Hey!
Oh, dear...
I messed up my first time!
Time for a pick-me-up!
Right!
Sorry
Got it!
I'm on my way!
I'm sorry
Good morn
Thank you
But when the question gets put to
you, it's hard to express it, huh?
You mean, what friends are?
Yeah.
Wow, after you burn it,
there's so little left.
But they say when they take back a whole
year's worth of garbage it'll be like a mountain.
I'm Sorry
Thanks
Right?
I get it!
Thanks
I think friendship is this one little word!
Right?
What's with that quote?
But it's better than your quotes, Hinata.
I know!
Thanks
Right?
Right
New Year's Card from Antarctica
Time Table
Program
Introduction
Introduce the Syowa Base Post Office
~Japan's most southern post box~ by: Shiraishi Yuzuki
Recap episode of the girls' Antarctica report by: Shiraishi Yuzuki
Messages from Japan to the crew
Messages from family members for Tamaki Mari
Messages from Hanyu Daisan High School Track Team for Miyake Hinata
Messages from the National Institute of Polar Research
for the Challenge for Antarctic Crew
Introduce life in Antarctica