Episode 4   Umaru and Her Rival
Umaru-chan? What's the matter?
Oh, sorry. Let's go, Ebina-chan.
S-Sure.
Now in Stock!!
Menacing
Sir, that's...
Yes. I'm aware.
UMR!
Action, shooting, fighting,
and rhythm games...
She has conquered every game,
regardless of the genre.
On top of that, she is a prodigy
when it comes to crane games,
and can claim any prize with a single coin.
Empty~
She is the most dangerous gamer
known to this arcade: UMR!
She's already got her eyes on the
Fukigen Nyankoro items we just got in.
If she were to get a huge haul
of those, it'd be a problem.
We're ready for her.
What?
I've already arranged the prizes in that
machine so that they won't be easy to get.
Complicated
Placement
What?!
Th-That's a tag hook!
That's a cheat where you
hook the plushie's tag!
She just got three at once!
Do you think she'll get
one in a single try again?
No. It'll be fine.
Hatsune Migu
1 Angry Migu
Those are in boxes, so you
have to aim for that loop...
Here
But I lowered the arm's
strength as much as possible,
so it must be moved at least
fifteen times for it to fall.
I-I see...
Wh-What?!
It's lifted up!
Now she used the stab technique!
It's a high-level technique where you stab
the arm's claw into the crevice of the box!
Here
Excuse me...
I don't see the prize I want.
Could you put it in for me?
Sh-She's so cute.
S-Sure. Please wait a moment.
You understand, don't you?
No matter how pretty she is, we cannot
let her get any more prizes on one try.
I know.
I'm a professional.
I put it on the "hell" setting!
That's... the Niagara Drop!
No!
By breaking the center of the
the mountain of plushies,
they're all falling like Niagara Falls!
Stop explaining, and do something about it!
I'm sorry!
So... You got some more, huh?
I got a jolt when I passed by the
arcade on the way home from school.
It must be a disaster for them
every time you visit.
Also, you don't even need all of these.
They're all different colors.
Welcome home, Nyankoro.
Well, I guess it's all right.
You sure do love plushies, though.
Umaru, it's already midnight. Time for bed.
Aw, but I wanna watch the late-night anime!
You're recording them anyway.
Hey.
6 Types
1 Angry Migu
2 Ultra Angry Migu
3 Ultra Angry Grr Argh Migu
4 Migu on Fire
5 Migu on Fire Infernoooo
6 Ultra Angrystic Finaleality Migu Migu Dream
These illustrations are just samples.
They may differ from the actual product.
Umaru, time to go to school.
Aw, but I wanna keep lazing around.
Here. You have tennis
for PE today, don't you?
I don't wanna move.
Umaru-chan, you look great
in your tennis outfit, too.
That's not true.
Tired. Wanna go home.
Wanna play online games.
I only know about tennis
through anime and manga.
**zuka Zone
Umaru Zone
Let's start by getting used to the ball.
This is easy. It might actually be fun.
Umaru-san!
Shubaphyyn
T-Tachibana-san?
I'd like to challenge you to a match.
I will not lose to you in tennis!
Uh, but...
There aren't very many courts...
Not to worry! I have reserved a court.
What's going on?
Umaru-chan's going to have a match.
Wh-Why is this happening?
Kirie & Umaru
Um, I can't play tennis at all.
You think it'll be okay?
Shuba
Not to worry.
I shall be in charge of
all serves and smashes.
Huh?
Sylphyn & Ebina
Game start!
Th-There seems to be quite the audience...
But we can just have a light match, right?
Umaru-san! Today is the day
that I shall become number one!
Here I go!
Canzone Sylphyn Smash!
Huh?
Wow, what an amazing serve!
They're going all-out!
She actually used an attack
with her name in it.
This isn't light at all.
That's just how it goes.
Kirie-chan's actually pretty
good at sports
Wh-What is the meaning of this?
Service, Sylphyn and Ebina team.
I-I just have to throw the
ball up and hit it, right?
There!
Ebihara-san! Why did you close your eyes?
I'm sorry! Also, it's Ebina.
Looks like Ebina-chan's got it rough.
Service, Umaru and Kirie team.
It's dangerous since Ebina-chan
has her eyes closed,
so I'll hit a weak serve.
I've got it!
Yes, indeed!
Sylphyn-san, are you all right?
Th-There's nothing to worry about!
Yes, indeed!
Why is she trying so hard?
Um, Sylphyn-san...?
I'm fine!
Nothing less from Umaru-san.
That was a superb serve!
That makes you all the more
worthy to be my opponent!
Now, this is where the real battle begins!
Shupapaa
But we can just have a light match, right?
Yes, indeed!
You guys
Canzone Sylphyn Smash!
Seriously
I'll protect you!
I love you, Kirie-chan!
Ebimori-san!
It's Ebina!
You don't                          understand the rules, do you?
Sylphyn Smash!
Kirie-chan!
You can
Ebikura-san!
It's Ebina!
stop now
What's the matter?
I-I can't move...
Muscle
Aches
Taihei-senpai.
I just came from visiting my uncle
in Europe, so I brought you a gift.
Oh, really? You shouldn't have.
I found something I thought you
might like, so I couldn't resist.
Wow, thanks, Alex-kun.
Please take good care of it.
R-Right...
Apparently it's a cat figure
with a bobbing head.
The fact that it's porcelain
is totally not cute.
He said they were handmade individually
by some craftsman over there.
Anyway, it sure was thoughtful of
the guy I trained to give me a gift.
Nice to meet you. My name is Alex.
Maybe one day he'll be your boss.
Taihei-kun, this isn't right.
I'm going to put it in here. Don't break it.
It's not cute, so I won't touch it.
The Next Day
Let's Play Pocket Hamster GK
Shwing!
A wild Hamsaburou has appeared!
Metal Nyankos! I choose you!
Metal Nyankos bobs its head.
Hamsaburou's defense goes way down.
Hamsaburou's life is low.
Now's my chance to get him!
M-Metal Nyankos is so weak!
Let's Play Pocket Hamster GK
End                                    Watch Again!
This isn't the time for that!
Onii-chan's gonna kill me!
How many times did I tell you not to break it?!
I'm not buying you anything else,
since you can't take care of anything!
I will now begin the repairs.
There is no doubt that I will
get in trouble if he finds this.
In order to avoid that, I'll have to make
it so the destruction never happened.
Umaru Makes the Colosseum
My grade in art class is a 5.
I shall control fate with these hands
to achieve a future in which
I don't get yelled at!
How to make an Akabeko
The system that makes its neck move
is the same as an Akabeko.
I'll just have to stick the broken
pieces together with a powerful glue,
and I'll fill the cracks with putty.
After it dries, I'll use
sandpaper to sand it down.
I'll have to be careful with the touch-up
so that it doesn't lose its vintage look.
The damage to the head is pretty bad.
It'll be better to start from scratch.
I can't remember its face!
This is the problem with vintage!
I remember that it wasn't very cute, but...
Come back... my memories!
Pukka!
That's not it!
No matter what I do, I keep
coming up with the wrong face!
I have to somehow make it
before Onii-chan comes home!
I'm sorry.
So you broke it, and remade it.
Yes.
Well, I'm not upset that you broke it.
Since you actually felt bad and
apologized, I won't get mad.
Onii-chan...
Hehehe, I'm saved.
More importantly...
How did you buy all these tools
you used for the cover-up?
U-Um... I bought them
at the hardware store...
With your card.
How do you know my PIN?!
Pocket Hamster
Onii-chan
"Umaru, starting today, you're a trainer!"
Umaru
"Ugh, just 5 more minutes."
There! Take that!
This is the final blow!
Looks like I'm still a bit weak
on connecting the fifth combo.
I'll have to look over the pattern again.
I'm home.
Invitation
Dear UMR,
Thank you for participating in
the recent Plaza GAPCOM
game tournament.
A game tournament?
There's going to be a game
tournament at the same
arcade that had the
rock-paper-scissors tournament.
Oh, yeah.
You should come with me, Onii-chan.
Day of the Tournament
I'm going to go register.
You wait here, Onii-chan.
Tournament Area
Okay, got it.
Hey, it's Taihei-senpai.
Alex-kun.
It's rare to see you outside of work,
and in a place like this, no less.
Yeah, I'm here with my little sister.
What a coincidence. So am I—
Thank you for coming today, everybody!
We will now begin the Supe IV Number One
Tournament!
Th-Things got really intense all of a sudden...
Oh, you didn't know?
The world-famous fighting game, Supe IV,
had ranking matches in arcades all over Japan.
This tournament gathers all of the people
who placed first at those arcades
to decide which gamer is truly
number one at fighting games.
It's the tournament that all
fighting game fans wait for.
O-Oh...
Now, let's bring out
the champion who won through our arcade,
the most grueling battlefield in Japan...
UMR!
Huh?!
You can tell she's this arcade's champion.
Her aura's completely different.
Huh? Y-Yeah...
Umaru's that good at this?
Next, we'll introduce the other
challengers from across Japan.
The socially disconnected
convenience store worker gamer:
UZR!
We are aliens.
The genius grade school gamer:
JNB!
The old musician guy gamer:
DDT!
The boy gamer suffering from
delusions of grandeur:
CHJ!
The mysterious masked gamer
whose day job is a manga artist:
SKH!
Wow...
These challengers are all
famous in the gaming world.
This might not go as easily as I thought.
And lastly, the dark horse
of this tournament...
The player who got an unbelievable
score in the qualifiers...
I shall be the number one player!
I am TSF!
Shubaan
What?!
UMR has won the first round!
Why, I wonder?
Why is Tachibana-san from my
class in a game tournament?
Come to think of it, I guess
she mentioned that she's been
in all sorts of competitions.
I brought this from home.
I had no idea she liked games.
I hope she doesn't figure out who I am.
Sylphyn Kick!
Hey!
I, Tachibana Sylphynford, have won!
Um, TSF-san?
We'd prefer that you wear a mask
and refrain from using your real name.
You're leaking your personal information.
And now, it's already time for the finals!
I guess these things go pretty
quickly with fighting games.
We will now find out at last
who is the ultimate gamer...
TSF versus UMR!
Pleasure to meet you, UMR-san.
I am Tachibana Sylphynford.
I told you! Put on a mask
and don't use your real name!
Good. She hasn't realized who I am.
There!
Horizontality Sylphyn Kick!
TSF immediately busts out a super move!
UMR quickly dodges!
This is a high-level match!
She started right off with a difficult
command like Vacuum Ultra Blast?
Only people who have played
for countless hours could do that.
You did well to dodge that.
But now that you've jumped, you're wide open!
TSF goes in for a combo!
But UMR blocks all of them!
Now...
UMR goes in for the combo!
There's an opening before your fifth combo.
Looks like I'm still a bit weak
on connecting the fifth combo.
Sh-She read me...
Uh-oh! UMR was not able to
complete her combo against TSF!
Will this decide the match?
What should I do? I'm going to lose!
And this was the perfect chance to
show Onii-chan how strong I am...
UMR's movements have stopped!
This is a huge change for TSF!
How naughty of you to look
elsewhere during a match.
Shuba
What on earth are you looki—
Shubaduuum
Whoa! Now TSF has stopped!
I shall be the number one player!
I am TSF!
Now I've done it!
How embarrassing!
H-Huh?
U-Um, the winner is...
UMR!
UMR! UMR! UMR! UMR!
Alex-kun?
The Next Day
Sylphyn-san just ran out yesterday.
I wonder what happened...
Umaru-san!
Shuba
Wh-What?
We have an academics test today!
I, Sylphyn, will be number one!
Huh? R-Right...
Sylphyn is always like that.
I heard she enters all sorts of competitions.
I'm sure she just wants attention.
I don't think that's the case.
I am number one!
Next Time
Episode 5   Umaru and Summer Vacation
Now, let us compete in the
fifteen seconds of the preview, UMR-san!
You're asking for a bit much, TSF-san...
Wait, we already have less than ten seconds!
Then let us compete again in the next episode!
Wow.
That actually turned into a proper preview.