What is the Ideal?
There are any number of
answers to that question.
It is words,
it is thought.
It is the font of all meaning.
But if you were to ask me,
the answer to the question is clear.
Ideal
It is the word written
on my notebook's cover.
The Ideal...
Everything about me is
written in this notebook.
Ideal
My schedule, my plans, my goals...
This notebook contains the
entirety of my future.
I arrived a whole ten seconds early.
My name is Kunikida Doppo.
I am an idealist walking the earth,
and a pragmatist in pursuit of ideals.
It's time.
Good morning.
Kunikida-san, please help us!
What's going on so early in the day?
J-J-Just look at Dazai-san!
Oh!
Kunikida-kun, it's an emergency!
Just look!
Look at what?
At that!
I only see your idiot face!
I've finally arrived...
in the afterlife!
At Yomotsuhirasaka!
What's going on?
It's exactly as I'd imagined!
Blue smoke trailing along the ground,
Kunikida-san.
moonlight dashing against the windows,
I think this may explain it.
and pink elephants dancing
in the western sky!
Complete Guide
to Suicide
I knew the Complete Guide to Suicide
was a masterpiece!
Who knew I just needed to eat mushrooms
growing in the nearby hills
to have such an entertaining way out?!
So he ate poisonous mushrooms?
Well, he thought he was eating
lethal mushrooms, but...
Ah, I've finally caught you,
rainbow pillbug!
All right, let's eat you back home!
Kunikida-san!
I'm doing my customary paperwork
after arriving at work.
Wait till I'm done.
What?!
Kunikida-kun.
You should come to the afterlife, too.
It's amazing.
There are rainbow pillbugs, too.
You can drink all you want!
You can eat all you want!
You can look at all the sleeping
beauties you could possibly—
Shut up!
Why are two such incompatible
people a team?
Kunikida-san, the president
has your case for the day.
Dazai.
Quit dawdling.
Walk faster.
'Kay.
We only have two minutes and fifteen
seconds until the appointed time!
That's a concern.
Is it okay for me to come along?
This is part of your rookie training.
This case involves solving a series
of disappearances in Yokohama.
If I recall, it's the one
where visitors to Yokohama
keep disappearing one after another, right?
We have an anonymous tip.
The victims have been abducted and
imprisoned in a certain location.
An anonymous tip...
How suspicious and wonderful.
But we can't ignore it.
So we're going to check the place out?
No.
We're going to investigate the
anonymous tip's source first.
How goes it, informant?
Hey, four-eyes. Are you a slave
to your notebook yet again?
You think you can talk like
that to a detective agency
when you're a cyber criminal?
If you're arrested,
your deceased father will be most aggrieved.
Don't bring my father into this.
More importantly, you're late.
Isn't that unusual for you?
Why?
Were you on a date with a pretty lady?
No!
Dates should be with a chosen woman,
followed by marriage six years later.
That is what's written in this notebook.
Huh?!
You have someone you've decided to marry?
I will in another four years.
Is he new?
I'm Nakajima Atsushi.
Cyber Network Warrior
Taguchi Rokuzou
I'm called Taguchi Rokuzou.
I'm an informant.
For the right price, I can
dig up dirt on anything.
And?
Did you figure out who's
behind the anonymous tip?
The Azure Messenger...
What?
There was data left on the server.
And pics of the abduction victims, I guess.
The mole's not a bad guy, though, is he?
He told you where they're holed up and all.
I wonder...
I hope we don't go there, only to
find he's one of the kidnappers.
The Azure Messenger...
I want you to keep looking into it.
Sure, when I feel like it.
Episode 6
The Azure Messenger
I'm busy looking after my tropical fish.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I called a cab.
We'll go to the abandoned hospital
mentioned by the tipster now.
Kunikida-kun, why are you
looking after the Rokuzou boy?
What do you mean?
It's not like you to give a hacker jobs.
You could've just talked
to him over the phone,
but you took the time to
meet him face to face.
His father's deceased, isn't he?
Are you trying to be his dad?
We came here so that Atsushi
could meet our informant.
That's all there is to it.
Sure, let's leave it at that.
This driver's another one of our informants.
He was a stage actor in his former life.
I couldn't make any money,
so I switched careers.
That was the right decision.
He knows more about Yokohama
than anyone I know.
He also saw two of the eleven victims
right before they were abducted.
I just happened to drive them
from the port to a hotel.
Is this case really about
abductions, though?
There've been no requests for ransom.
Are you sure these two
were the ones you saw?
Yes, I'm sure of it.
They're even wearing the same clothes, too.
I see.
I have a hunch!
Look at these photos.
They're both wearing glasses!
That means this is a serial
glasses abduction case!
It's your time to shine, Kunikida-kun!
Some of the victims don't wear glasses.
You can't say it's a pattern.
Oh.
Too bad. And here I thought it'd
finally be your time to shine.
I can't let that remark pass.
Are you trying to say my glasses are the
only reason I'd ever be in the spotlight?!
Wh-What?!
We're here.
It's the abandoned hospital, as you requested.
What a nice atmosphere.
I think it might be haunted.
By what?
It is creepy, to be sure.
It's kind of nice.
It revs you up.
You'd better not have eaten
another weird mushroom.
Oh, are you scared, Kunikida-kun?
Are you afraid of ghosts or something?
I'm not afraid of ghosts!
Then keep up.
Fool!
In this sort of movie, those who are
careless and get ahead of themselves
are the ones who die first.
Look at these footprints.
They're still fresh.
Help!
That voice...
Did it come from the basement?
What's this?!
Thank you.
You saved me.
University Lecturer
Sasaki Nobuko
I am Sasaki Nobuko.
I'm a lecturer at a university in Tokyo.
So you're victim number twelve?
Did you see who abducted you?
I'm sorry.
I blacked out at a station.
When I regained consciousness,
I was drowning in the tank, as you just saw.
Dazai, what's your take on the situation?
Sasaki-san's looking super sexy.
Be serious!
Oh, right...
There should be others
who were abducted here.
I know I heard voices just as
I began drowning in the tank.
What?
Kunikida-san!
I found them!
They're here!
Help us!
Please!
You all right?
Get us out of here!
Get back, Atsushi-kun!
It's gas!
You, too, Kunikida-kun.
Hey, hang in there!
Hey!
Kunikida-kun!
Let me go, Dazai!
People shouldn't die like this!
Let me go!
"Victims of Yokohama's serial abduction case were found,
Series of Disappearances in
Yokohama Ends in Tragic Deaths
but perished when a civilian detective agency
conducted an independent raid."
Perished...
So this was the enemy's objective.
You're saying they were
trying to frame the Agency?
Maybe it wasn't my time to shine,
despite what Dazai said.
Kunikida-san...
Where's Ms. Sasaki?
Infirmary
She should be in the infirmary.
Oh, that's great.
Thank you so much for
saving me the other day.
If you hadn't come when you did,
I wouldn't be alive right now.
Not at all.
Not to mention, you even let me
stay at your residence last night.
Huh?
Where did you stay?
My place!
What?!
I'm... deeply indebted to Dazai-sama.
See?
I-Is that something detectives
are allowed to do?
It seems Sasaki-san didn't see who it was.
She apparently faints a
lot due to anemia.
That's why she fainted on
the day she was abducted, too.
I don't know how she was abducted afterward.
So she's your type?
I like all women.
But Sasaki-san seems like the type
who'd commit suicide with me if I ask,
which is nice.
But what about you, Kunikida-kun?
Is she your type?
She is a victim in the case
and a witness. That's it.
Well, that's how you would roll.
Oh, Atsushi-kun, want to read it?
Ideal
His ideal woman.
You bastard!
When'd you swipe that?
Ideal
Read? You mean it's
written down in here?
Kunikida-kun's notebook
has a wide range of schedules,
plans, and ideals recorded in it.
See, like here.
Whoa!
Ideal
Th-This is too much...
You have a problem with it?
No, I can sympathize with your
vision of an ideal woman, but...
You should probably not share
that vision with women.
Forget about me!
We're talking about the
abductions right now!
Have we picked up on anything?
Yeah.
In this newspaper photo,
you look pretty manly.
Is that your way of indicating
that you want me to punch you?
What's regrettable is this...
You should've picked
sexier eyeglass frames
if you were going to end up in the news.
They're so plain.
Hey...
Only a naturally flamboyant person
like me could pull off wearing them.
What do you think, Atsushi-kun?
Not bad, really.
They only scream "con man" to me.
Wait...
What's the matter?
Let's go, both of you.
I know who's behind this.
Sorry for the short notice.
You said on the phone that you'd figured
out who's behind the serial murder case.
You're on your way to arrest the killer?
That's right.
Then let's hurry.
Where to?
Here.
Huh?
This is where the abductions took place,
and you are the kidnapper.
You dosed passengers with sleeping gas,
and abduct them after they fell unconscious.
You wore a gas mask.
What were his reasons?
I can think of one.
Cargo.
Cargo?
He'd sell them off.
There's a black market for
organs in the underground.
The margin isn't great because of the exchange rate,
but if you're pulling it off alone,
it's a decent payout.
That's horrible.
Wait a minute.
Hang on.
If I'd used this taxi to abduct people,
the city police would've found me already
when tracing the victims' last known locations.
No, no one looked twice at this taxi.
Because all the victims would vanish and
become untraceable the following day.
When your targets boarded the taxi
and you made them unconscious,
you'd imprison them and take
their clothes and luggage.
That's why all the victims at the
hospital were in their underwear.
You would then wear their clothes
to disguise yourself as them,
then check into the hotels where
they'd made reservations.
You made sure you would show up on
security cameras for that reason.
The victims were all of approximately
the same height and build
because you were choosing passengers
you could impersonate.
Many wore hats and glasses
because that made passing
yourself off as them easier.
If the security feeds show someone
looking reasonably like the victim,
you can dupe the police easily.
By the time the last known sighting
of the "victim" was recorded,
the real victim had already been abducted.
Ms. Sasaki's abduction was
even easier, wasn't it?
After she collapsed at the train station,
a good Samaritan paid for her cab ride.
It's faster to hail a cab than call
an ambulance at a train station.
That's all circumstantial evidence.
I suppose.
You're right.
What now, Kunikida-kun?
Are you being serious?
Let's make a deal.
A deal?
If you agree to my conditions,
I'll turn myself in.
Please protect me at the
Armed Detective Agency!
I need to be protected for 72 hours while
the prosecution concludes their questioning
and arranges witness protection.
What's this about?
I was put up to this.
I was assured by a new-fangled
organ smuggling organization
that this was a great deal I'd
never get caught for, and yet...
So there's a group behind all this?
Where are they?!
I don't know.
I always meet them in the
Harbor Central Building.
So that's the place.
And?
Why do you need our protection?
Well...
It appears one of the people I abducted
was with the Port Mafia.
Well, that's not good—
The Port Mafia?!
Help me!
Hey!
I don't want to die!
Wait!
Kunikida-san.
I can't get a signal.
They must be jamming.
If we lose the driver,
the truth may never come to light.
Dazai, pursue the driver.
Brat, get a hold of the
police and request backup.
I'll distract them as a decoy.
Roger!
Let's go!
Ability: Doppo Poet!
Doppo Poet
Flash Bang!
Flash Bang
Now!
Metal is fragile,
and so is the human psyche.
What about you all, Armed Detective Agency?
You...
Akutagawa of the Port Mafia!
Indeed.
If you can't shoot straight,
there's no need for me to devour
the space around your bullets.
My hobbies don't include murder.
Trifling words of a weakling.
Doppo Poet!
Stun gun!
Come to heel, you aberrant dog.
It appears the Armed Detective Agency
is not merely a group of entertainers.
You're worthy of being Dazai-san's cover.
Interference.
Very well.
Our paths will cross again in the future.
We'll continue this another time.
Don't ever come again.
I turned the driver over
to the military police.
So this is the building the organ
traffickers used for their deals?
They've already flown the coop.
The wall's scorched black.
This is where the Azure
King blew himself up.
That's right.
What?
You mean, the one in the infamous
Azure Flag terrorist incident?
That Azure King?
That's right.
A terrorist who destroyed many
national and corporate facilities.
Azure Flag Terrorist Incident
From the time I heard the
term "Azure Messenger,"
I've been wondering if there
were ties to the Azure King.
I'd heard that the Azure King
blew himself up in the end.
So this was the place.
He committed suicide after the
police cornered him, right?
That's right.
I'd determined that this was his hideout
and reported it to the police.
You were the one who found
the Azure King's hideout?
But on that day,
the military, the public safety bureau, and
the police were all working in tandem,
so the chain of command was in utter chaos.
Only five detectives arrived at the hideout
in a timely manner upon receiving the report.
To add further insult to injury,
the Azure King got wind
of the police's actions,
so he holed himself up with a bomb.
After a conflicting set of orders,
a decision was made to raid.
But ordinary policemen without special
training or abilities didn't stand a chance.
Cornered, the Azure King blew
himself up and perished,
along with the five detectives.
I remember now, Kunikida-kun.
One of the detectives was that
Rokuzou boy's father, wasn't he?
He was a good detective with
a strong sense of justice.
I'm the one who reported the
hideout's location to the police.
I may as well have set the bomb off myself.
That's not true!
It's the terrorist's fault
for blowing himself up!
That's right, Atsushi-kun.
Yet Kunikida-kun can't stop trying
to look out for the Rokuzou boy...
in his deceased father's stead.
What is it?
Another job for the Agency.
The client...
Regards,
The Azure Messenger
is the Azure Messenger.
I see.
I'm starting to see who
this Azure Messenger is.
So? What's the job?
Disarming a bomb.
A bomb?
If we don't disarm the
bomb by sunset tomorrow,
several hundred people will die.
A bomb capable of that can't be easy...
The equipment here is for building a bomb.
With this setup,
you could build a very advanced bomb.
But...
Don't worry. We won't let the bomb go off.
We'll stop it for sure this time!
What should we do?
If we don't find and disarm
the bomb by sundown,
there will be hundreds of casualties.
If we cannot find the bomb
and lives are lost,
we no longer have the right to call
ourselves a detective agency.
Oh, President.
Think of this mission as a fight for
the Agency's existence and pride.
Begin the investigation!
Man, where'd Dazai-san run
off to now, of all times?
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs, Episode 7:
Love for the Disease Called Ideals.
Episode 7
Love for the Disease Called Ideals