I Can't Reach You
I'd better stop...
All these heights are gonna
give me a heart attack.
Oh, does that light need changing?
Could you maybe...
You can't reach, can you?
I'll let you ride my shoulders.
I mean I did it the other day,
don't be embarrassed.
Upsy-daisy...
Hurry up and change it.
Nonononononononononono-
L...Let me down...
Huh? Why?
Hey, what about the light?
Youngest hates me...? Why?
Did I do something weird?
No, I just lifted her like normal...
I barely even touched her...
Maybe she thinks I'm like everyone
else in this class
and she's better off not
hanging out with me!
But I'm not...I'm different!
Miya-chan, wanna play Kokkuri-san and
see what the spirits have to say?
He's the god of love, you know!
I don't think he is...
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san...
Will I ever find true love?
No
Man, Kokkuri-san's brutally honest.
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san...
Please go out with me!
That's impossible!
Don't contemplate it!
Kokkuri-san's a jerk.
You took another picture of
my panties, you pervert!
No, I-umm...
They're Miyashita's!
Wh-
Liar! Fine, let's see!
Kn-Knock it off-
I have proof she's a nympho!
Hey-delete that!
Why can't we have class?
Knock it off, stupid!
You can borrow my gym shorts today
if you forgot yours, Shin-chan!
I said knock it off! It's okay!
Put them on!
I don't need you to...
Stop, I said stop!
Come on-
He's got one.
He does not!
And that's why you're here...
I'm not like them, I swear I'm normal.
So why-
I can see your panties.
Listen to me! And I can see yours too!
Miya-chan...
Miya-chan, you like Youngest-san!
No, I-
Maybe a spirit possessed her-
No, no!
So why're you so worked up?
I'm not-
Worked up?
That's right, I need to calm down...
I might be scaring her off.
I should take a kinder gentler approach.
Kinder...gentler...
Youngest-san!
Let's change that light.
Who're you?
Miyashita, damn it!
This is because you're all a bunch of freaks!
Who're you?
Who is she?
Where's Miya-chan?
Yabecchi, I dunno what's going on but
we've got some weirdo in our class.
Don't call ME weird!
Stay positive.
If changing my hairstyle made
me unrecognizable,
I could probably get away with leading
a double life like people do in manga.
Gotta make things more fun!
Sorry, I had the wrong class.
What're you doing, Miyashita?
This a joke?
Why?!
Mitsudomoe!
Yabecchi's Room
I wish I could quit, but here we are
for another episode of "Yabecchi's Room."
Today's guest is the middle
child of the Marui triplets,
Today's guest - Marui Futaba-san
Marui Futaba-san!
What interesting topics will
we talk about today?
Thank goodness you're on the
show this time, Futaba-chan.
I think we can have a real conversation?
Really? That's great!
What should I ask you...
I know!
Futaba-chan, why are you so
incredibly super-strong?
Hmm? I dunno.
Ah ha! In earlier episodes
you used to wear a dogi.
Did you get your strength from martial arts?
I dunno!
If you wanna know the back-story
you should talk to the author.
Never mind...
Wh-What?
I saw a cockroach!
Wha-Wh-Where?!
Over there, I'll get it!
Futaba-chan, be gentle,
remember to be gentle!
Freeze!
Futaba-chan, I'm a renter, a RENTER!
Not bad, little roachie.
Huaya!
Stop it, Futaba-chan!
Look, your favorite kind of book!
Boobies!
So Futaba-chan, on to the next...
Umm, Futaba-chan...
Boobies, boobies...
I wanna eat them all up...
That's it, I quit! I mean is!
Yabecchi, get the next book ready!
How could you do this to me, Futaba-chan!
Yabecchi's Room - Fin
MITSUDOMOE!
7.53 seconds.
Wow!
He's fast!
Satou-kun's awesome!
But he's a pervert...
Just the breeze Satou-kun
made from running...
...Adds five years to your life!
Shin-chan!
I got 6.2 seconds!
Wow, that's great, you should
shoot for the world record.
You should try too!
Yeah right.
We've got some time left, so let's
play boys vs. girls dodgeball!
I'm in, I'm in!
If the girls win,
all the boys have to address me
as "Mitsuba-sama" from now on!
That again?
She thinks it's in the bag because
they've got Futaba on their side.
We probably don't stand a chance.
Okay, it's time for our boys vs. girls
dodgeball match!
Okay!
Try NOT to throw at Futaba!
Right!
What're you doing you stupid
pervert brigade!
DUH, we want Satou-kun to smash
his ball into our faces!
That'd add ten years to our lives!
And do wonders for our skin!
Then the game's on, who can get
Satou-kun's ball in the face first?
Uhh, hey...
We won't let you win, Futaba!
I don't really get it...
but I don't lose!
Oh not you too.
Umm...
Bring it!
What the heck...
Forget it.
N-No!
Dooooofus.
Why didn't you smash her?
I couldn't do it!
I'm gonna cave your skulls in!
Weak!
Not too shabby!
Shiori!
Someone besides Satou-kun hit
me...I've been tainted...
This is for Shiori!
Too fast!
You okay?
Nice...now I'm out.
I'd better sneak off the field before
things get any crazier.
Satou-kun!
"Careless"
doesn't begin to describe what a horrible
person I am for hitting you!
I'll repent in death!
H-Hold it!
She's trying to bite her tongue off!
She deserves nothing less
for damaging Satou-kun's handsome face.
But we're still friends...we'll
clean up your corpse.
Chicks, man...
Easy, this is just supposed to be a game!
It doesn't even hurt!
Actually it's a good thing!
Wha?
It is?
I'd rather be out.
Satou-kun!
Wh-What's going on?
He's happy he got hit in the face?
Shin-chan...
He IS a pervert.
I'll make you even happier...
Huh? No, that's not what I meant!
Besides I'm out now, I'm going to the field.
Headshots don't count.
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
Mitsudomoe.
The Hopeless Squad's Daily Routine
The Hopeless Squad starts its day early.
Satou-kun's shoebox!
All clear!
Satou-kun's desk!
Nothing.
Zip.
Nada.
You bring your books, slippers, recorder
and everything else home every day, huh?
Yeah.
A lot of scary stuff can happen.
And thus the Hopeless Squad's
day comes to an end.
You're good, Oga-chin!
I've been practicing soccer since
Satou-kun loves it so much!
You're one step closer to Satou-kun!
When I'm kicking the ball around,
It feels like my soul is one with Satou-kun's.
No fare, I wanna be one with him!
Me too!
Meee!
Toooo!
You'd need a million years
of practice before
YOUR soul will be one with Satou-kun's!
Soul? Not soccer?
Oh, Shin-chan!
Bu-
Damn Futaba,
she sticks to Satou-kun like super glue!
She'll pay!
Hey class 3, let's play soccer!
Class 1! Sure!
Yay!
Wait up!
Let me play instead of Futaba!
You don't need someone who's
headers pop the ball!
Oh, I'm sorry...
Fair point, but...
If they do that we'll be better off too.
As the goalie I'd feel like my life
wasn't in danger for once.
S-S-Satou-kun!
I've been practicing soccer
a lot lately, all for you!
I'll do my best!
Okay.
Yes! If I can just show him
how good I've gotten...
Oga-chin!
Satou-kun!
Let's roll, Oga-chin!
Right!
Twin Love Shot!
We did it, Satou-kun!
Yeah!
I got this.
Kickoff!
Now to show Satou-kun
something really cool!
If any boy other than Satou-kun touches me
my body will wither and rot!
Then what're you out here for?!
It's no use...I can't play like this...
Man, Satou's really awesome.
He's in total control of the ball.
Well he's played soccer since
he was two years old,
that's practically his whole life!
I hear he even goes to sleep
holding a soccer ball.
The ball's like his best friend.
Or his GIRLfriend.
But it's just a ball...
Just a ball..
Just a ball! I'll kill it!
Man, without Futaba things are so peaceful.
Wow, that was a sick slide!
What the heck, he's on our team!
Get away from that, you filthy ball!
Why are you stealing from
your own teammate?!
Whoa!
I'll get it!
She's gone!
You stupid ball!
What's going on NOW?
Who knows...
How dare they say...Satou-kun...likes
balls better...
No, the balls aren't what Shin-chan likes.
Wh-what'd you say?
No girl besides Futaba has
ever stopped my dribble.
She's not as bad as I thought...
Hey, you're pretty good-
Wh-What're you doing?!
He reacted!
So it's true, you like PANTIES most!
No, it's not...I mean, anyone
would've reacted to that!
They're just cloth...
Just cloth...
Just cloth!
You're just cloth!
Wow!
Everyone move out!
Don't let class 3 win!
Pan-ties! Pan-ties! Pan-ties!
Can't we play soccer?
Losing to mere cloth...
Losing to mere cloth!
I'll never wear panties again!
NEVER!
Okay everyone, move to a new desk.
Let's have fun, okay?
With what?
I'm just saying we should try to be friends
since we sit near each other now.
It won't work.
Why?!
We don't know a thing about each other,
I have no idea how we're
supposed to be friends.
We can GET to know each other.
Grow up
Let's see...my blood type's O, my sign
is Cancer, and I like basketball.
Grown-up (Futaba)
I actually play on a local team.
Grow up
What're you into?
That's a personal question.
Why's Youngest so anti-social?
Meh, it's just how she is.
Leave her alone.
No, I think she really wants to have friends.
I can see it in her eyes.
You can be a real pain
sometimes, Miyashita.
Now, now.
Anyways, I have nothing to start a conversation
about and I barely know her,
so I was hoping you could
tell me a little about her.
She likes superhero stuff?
Oh yeah!
She even snuck out to buy
one of those toy belts!
Hitoha's like a kindergartener.
That's so cute.
If you want info I demand your
fruit juice from lunch!
You could've told me earlier.
Gym is next! Everyone get changed!
Superhero shows, huh?
I've never seen one and I'm not into them,
how should I handle this?
Scenario I
So, Mitsuba told me you like
superhero stuff, is that true?
Don't go around trying to get
dirt on people, it's pathetic.
Scenario I FAILURE
Gotta play it cool...
Th-That...
She even snuck out to buy
one of those toy belts!
H-Hey!
Scenario II
Wow, it's the belt!
You recognize it?
Of course, I'm all about it!
So you're a fan too Miyashita-san?
I'm so happy!
Yeah, let's talk all about it!
Then I just have to be as vague
and general as possible.
Success
Yes! That's the ticket!
Everyone get in pairs and
we'll all stretch first.
Miya-chan, will you-
Be my partner!
Uh-S-Someone?
One, two, three, four.
Is this...
Five, six, seven, eight.
O-Ow-
Is this...
S-Stop-
It's okay...I know what this is.
I like it, too.
Stop it-
Miya-chan...
Oh, no, no!
I mean, Youngest's bel-
She even snuck out to buy
one of those toy belts!
Snuck out...
I...
I felt some kinda hard thing
under her stomach!
Youngest-san's a BOY?
N-No!
Let's see it, Youngest-san.
Stop!
I said let's see it!
That's not what I meant!
Let's see it, Youngest-san!
Youngest-
T-That's...
I'm tired of all these ridiculous
misunderstandings.
Go ahead and make fun of me, laugh at me-
but I love the Gachi Rangers and
there's nothing I or anyone
else can do about it!
Oh, I know them.
"We will end all hatred and anger," right?
Oh yeah, that's the one adults
get into too right?
You like them too Youngest-san?
The black ranger's my favorite!
I catch them once in a while.
The Gachi Rangers rock!
They're so cool!
Yeah I like...the...green one...
There IS no green one.
Wha-
Can we get back to stretching now, please?
What were they even talking about?
Next week is a the last episode,
but we're not doing anything special
so don't get your hopes up.
Yup, it's just your average
everyday Mitsudomoe!
Is the preview done?
Last Episode
A Day at the Marui House
Okay...
We're outta here!