It's me.
Vivian.
Yeah!
It happened again?
Are you hurt?
Tusk.
I thought we were above the water.
Where... are we?
Ange and Tusk
Angelise here.
Arzenal, please respond.
Arzenal, if anyone is alive, please respond.
Poke-poke...
Momoka. Hilda!
Anyone! Say something!
What's going on?
I'm not getting anything, either.
No response on any frequency.
No motion detected
within a five-kilometer radius.
Position sensors are down, too.
There's no place like this
near Arzenal, as far as I know.
Maybe it's some ancient ruin,
from when humanity was at war.
I've never heard of such
a thing still being around.
Then are you saying we've been
thrown into an unknown world?
With the Villkiss, that's possible.
Huh?
The light that the enemy emitted...
The Villkiss might have done
something to protect you from it.
The Villkiss is a special machine.
Nothing it could do would surprise me.
I guess...
...it's special.
Huh?
Nothing.
Can you fix it?
Somewhat.
I can get it flying again.
Please do, then.
And you?
Scouting.
There might still be enemies.
Got it.
Be careful.
Right.
Ange, Ange.
Get on me!
Get on you?
Yeah.
To think, you were a DRAGON...
It's a secret.
Where are we?
Vivian, look. Go over there.
Gotcha.
I knew it.
It's the Dawn Pillar.
We're in the Misurugi Empire?
The palace and city were gone.
But the Dawn Pillar was there.
I'll always recognize that.
But something's wrong.
Huh?
The Pillar and the city...
They looked like they collapsed long ago.
Maybe a few hundred years
passed while we were out cold?
Nah...
This isn't funny.
Sorry.
This is Capital City Defense.
Are there any survivors?
Capital City Shelter #3 is still operational.
We are taking refugees.
Survivors, please meet at the central park.
Survivors?
Let's go.
There?
There are survivors here?
Life signs detected.
Beginning reception.
Welcome to Capital City Shelter #3.
Capital City Defense welcomes you.
We currently have 1.7% capacity available.
Please choose an area.
Enjoy your stay.
What is this?
You from before! Where are you?
Come out and explain!
I am management computer Himawari.
State your query.
She's a computer?
What's going on?
Are there any survivors?
What happened?
What's going on?
Query received.
Beginning response sequence.
What is this? A movie?
These are visual records.
This was a large-scale international war
waged by the Unified Economic Federation
against the Pancontinental Alliance.
Known as World War Seven,
Ragnarok, or the D War,
it reduced earth's population
to 11% of its pre-war level.
In order to end the stalemate,
the Federation deployed the
ultimate weapon, the Ragna-mail.
That's...
A black...
...Villkiss?
What is it doing?
And so the battle ended.
But the Ragna-mail's
dimensional resonator weapon
caused the sympathetic detonation
of all of Earth's Dracunium reactors.
All regions of the planet
became contaminated and inhospitable to life,
destroying all civilization.
That is all.
Do you have any other questions?
The world ended.
What is this?
What kind of joke is this?
This is stupid. When did this happen?
Five hundred and thirty-eight years ago.
What?
Five hundred and thirty-eight years,
one hundred and ninety-three days ago.
No heat, motion,
or life signs are currently detected
in any of the 20,976 shelters
located throughout the world.
You two are the only living humans
that remain on Earth.
Five hundred years, huh...
I guess that's long enough for
writing to change, too.
You really believe that little skit?
I saw the decomposing bodies.
It could all be a lie.
Why would anyone do that?
How would I know?
I'll only believe what
I see with my own eyes.
Vivian, let me on.
All right.
It's impossible.
This can't be five hundred
years into the future.
It's bullshit.
Come on, Vivian.
We haven't gone up north yet.
Come on, wake up.
Get a grip.
Vivian. Come on.
Ange, you shouldn't force her.
Wake up, you useless thing!
How could you say that?
Let go.
You should get some rest.
What good would that do?
Are you saying we should
stay in this bullshit place?
I want to know what happened to Arzenal!
If Momoka and the others are safe!
If he's really dead...
Ange.
Don't you have to get back soon, too?
That woman's waiting for you.
Right, Knight of the Villkiss?
Yeah.
I'll protect you and the Villkiss,
even if it costs my life.
For Libertus, right?
You're just like Salia.
You're only interested in using me.
You're that woman's dog.
No.
I really...
If we can't get back,
then maybe that's good enough.
Huh?
That garbage strategy wouldn't work anyway...
Garbage?
Right?
Destroy the world and free the Norma.
You'd let as many people die
as you need to for that goal.
And what exactly are you freeing?
You make me laugh.
Then my parents...
...died for garbage's sake.
Is that right?
We Ancient People...
We always fought to free the world from Embryo.
Dad and Mom fought to create a
world where we and the Norma,
people who can't use Mana, can live.
And they died!
My dead comrades, and my parents' wishes...
It's all garbage to you, is it?
Well...
Whatever. He's ignoring me? So immature...
He's always...
He didn't have to get so angry.
Hey, this is cute.
Ange.
I thought it might look
good on you. That's all.
How is it?
I think it's good.
Thanks.
You must be tired.
Let's eat.
Hey.
I'm, um... I'm sorry.
You know how to apologize?
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm sorry for being so harsh, too.
Vivian.
Sorry about last night.
I said too much.
Thanks, Vivian.
No wonder I felt cold.
Tusk.
I found something awesome.
Hotel
Mulaflaga
We have a roof. And beds!
And a bath!
It's miraculously well-preserved.
It must have been a
prestigious aristocrat's castle.
I have to thank Vivian for finding it.
I'm going to take a bath.
Clean up, please, Tusk.
Sure, princess.
Thanks, Tusk.
For everything.
You know a lot of things,
and you're always rational and kind.
I can depend on you.
I'm no good.
I get emotional right away.
And I'm stubborn. And I panic.
I can't blame you.
Anyone would be that way
in a situation like this.
You were a princess,
and then you were a Norma,
and then a soldier fighting DRAGONs,
and you were dropped into a crazy weapon.
Next, it's five hundred years in the future.
You're right.
Too much has happened.
But it's not all bad.
I got to meet you and Vivian.
I learned a lot of things.
Even though some people...
I couldn't understand until the end.
Your brother.
Hey...
Yeah?
Who's Embryo?
He controls all of civilization
from the shadows.
He's the master of the world.
Our highest, greatest enemy. He was, anyway.
Was?
That was five hundred years ago.
Right.
We've come so far.
But we're alive.
So long as we're alive, we'll manage.
You're strong, Ange.
Are you mocking me?
I'm complimenting you.
Well, then. You get to enjoy
your first bed in a long time.
Sleep well.
What about you?
I'll sleep in the hallway.
You could sleep here.
There's a sofa and a bed.
Uh, but, um...
It's fine.
Okay. Thanks, then.
Jeez! What are you doing?
Why don't you come here?
I think that's a bit much...
What's that noise?
It's so quiet.
Yeah.
We're the only ones here.
How long has it been
since I've felt so at peace?
Maybe it freed us...
Huh?
The Villkiss.
To a world without fighting...
Aren't you...?
N-No, no, no, no, no.
I'm the Knight of the Villkiss.
I can't get involved with you.
Do you... not like me?
Of course not!
Then...
So, um...
Y-You're awe-inspiring.
Ten years ago...
Well, I guess, 548 years ago now...
Libertus failed.
Alektra lost her right arm,
and she couldn't pilot the Villkiss anymore.
My parents and friends all died.
I was left with nothing but my
duty as the Knight of the Villkiss.
But I was afraid.
To fight and die for someone
I'd never known, let alone met...
I ran from that duty into the deep forest.
I couldn't find a reason
to fight, or even to live.
I just ran.
That's when I met you.
You were fighting.
You were resisting...
...with your small body.
My eyes were opened.
What was I doing?
That's when I finally found
purpose in being a knight.
I stepped forward.
I wasn't forced into duty.
I chose it myself.
So if I can protect you,
that's good enough for me.
I mean...
Loser.
But you're pure, at least.
I'm blood-soaked.
I killed humans and DRAGONs,
and even drove my brother to his death.
I'm soaked in blood, crime, and death.
I don't deserve a protector like you.
That's not true.
Ange, you're beautiful.
No matter how blood-soaked you are,
I'll stand by you.
I'm violent, unpredictable, and fussy.
Even then?
Yeah, even then.
Ange!
Tusk, not again!
Sorry.
Are you the ones who sent that distress signal?
A DRAGON...
Welcome, false citizens...
To our world, the true Earth.
Preview
Ange, we're not alone anymore!
But we're in a preview together again?
They're just cutting corners
because the cast is so small.
Huh? There's lots of pretty girls next week?
Maybe I'll get a harem!
No, so just die this week!
The Other Earth