I've liked you, Chisaki.
For quite a while now.
Episode Eleven:
The Changing Times
Um, uh...
Here.
Th-Thanks...
I'm sorry for causing a stir
so early in the morning.
I just confessed my
feelings to your daughter.
Oh my...
How polite.
It's not that I want a reply.
It's sort of like a modest resistance.
Resistance?
Come on.
If you don't hurry,
we're going to be late.
R-Right...
What's wrong?
You're really far away.
I-I'm fine!
Really? Then good.
Looking back at it now,
I think that Kaname and Chisaki
were a little weird that day.
But at the time,
my thoughts were full from the
upcoming cold, the Ofunehiki,
and Manaka...
And I think Manaka was the same...
That's why Manaka and I could have
never caught on to those two at the time.
Hey.
You're late!
Good morning!
The fact was that, in the
few days that followed,
the world that surrounded us
changed at an unbelievable pace.
Every day...
the saltflake snow continued to fall.
When we realized it, our village
had turned completely white,
like somewhere from the snow country.
Along with that, the preparations
for our sleep were continuing.
Closed to Prepare for the Sleep
Everyone stopped eating,
and their Ena just kept getting thicker.
At first, "the moment" just felt like something
vague, but eventually it was right in front of our eyes.
There was no way to think of it
as some kind of joke anymore.
On the surface, the saltflake
snow had only fallen once more,
but because of the overly chilly summer,
I think everyone started to
work a little more seriously.
But...
According to Uroko-sama, with how
everyone's Ena is coming along,
we should probably fall
into our sleep on the 21st.
Wha—
Young Men's Coalition
The 21st?
That's the day of the Ofunehiki!
So on the day of the festival,
we'll be cheerfully saying goodbye
to everyone on the surface.
All of them will just have to
cool their heads off in the cold.
Those ungrateful, shameless jerks!
Though actually, right now we're
the ones with the thicker skin.
No doubt.
Young Men's Coalition
But...
The guys on the surface right now might
not be there anymore when we wake up...
Thanks for the meal.
Is something wrong?
I'll be going now.
Have a good day.
How are you feeling?
There hasn't been much change.
It might be because I've been
out of the sea for so long,
but it appears that it's
affecting me a lot less.
But I probably shouldn't
try to diet for a while.
Here. I filled it out.
Marriage Registration
Husband-to-be
Wife-to-be
Name
(Phonetics)
Sakishima Akari
You sure it's okay?
I may be inexperienced,
but please stay with me for a long time.
S-Same here.
Oh, and about the ceremony...
What do you want to do?
I was thinking we probably
don't need to bother.
Considering the times,
I'm pretty sure my dad won't
come even if I invite him.
Yeah, but...
don't you think that's exactly why
we should have a proper ceremony?
I'm sure your dad would like
to see you as a bride as well.
So let's think about it.
There should be a ceremony
that is suitable for us,
and I still don't want to give up on
getting your dad's blessing
on our relationship.
All right, Itaru-san.
This country originally had
a temperate humid climate.
The biggest characteristic of that
is the changes in the seasons,
and the thing affecting this
is called the seasonal winds...
And...
Apparently it's time.
Go on ahead.
It's still before noon.
Our Ena is fine.
But these are instructions from Shioshishio.
I think we should follow them.
Your hibernation is thought
to be a biochemical reaction
to special environmental factors adding up.
But this hasn't happened these past
few centuries, so we're not sure.
But Sensei, we're fine...
Huh?
Seriously?
See?
Your Ena's become thicker, and
it needs water more often.
Go on ahead.
Damn it...
It's already dry.
We seriously are going to sleep...
You don't want to?
I've been thinking, even if people
sleep at the same time at night,
everyone still wakes up
at various times, right?
So are we all really going to be
able to wake up at the same time?
Isn't everyone going to sleep
together and waking up together?
There's no guarantee.
After our hibernation, not only will the
surface be different, but so will we.
The only guarantee we have of spending the same time together is right now.
It's sort of ephemeral.
What did you guys want
to do about lunch?
Sensei asked me to ask
you guys just in case.
You really do have
amazing timing, Tsumugu.
I'm going to eat.
Y-You'll get in trouble.
Like I care!
I'm not just going to fall sleep helplessly,
when I don't even know
what's going to happen.
Manaka!
I...
I'm going to eat, too!
I mean... I don't want it to be like this.
I don't want to go to sleep and have
everything be different when I wake up.
Manaka...
All right...
Come on.
Okay, Hii-kun!
Manaka really is a fast runner.
She's usually really slow,
but sometimes we get left behind.
If you don't hurry, Egawa and the
others are going to eat it all.
Shall we?
Yeah.
Saya Mart
I really understand now
how much the people from
Shioshishio helped out our store.
Due to bad weather,
the produce and fish have all
been stuck at a steep price.
I guess the world really
could be ending.
Let's do our best, boss.
This is the time to put
good things on sale.
You saw, didn't you?
Go away!
Yeah, go away!
Go away somewhere, Aka-chan!
I said go, you fake mom!
Miuna!
That made Aka-chan mad, right?
This will make her go
back to the sea, right?
She'll go to sleep, right?
She won't die, right?!
Don't cry, Miuna!
We're red demons that cried!
We didn't have a choice!
Thanks...
But where I'm headed has
already been decided.
Um, Sakishima-san?
Yes?
We're from the Fishery
Cooperative's Young Men's Coalition.
We had a request for your brother.
For Hikari?
What?
Really?
Yeah.
Is there any way that
you'd do the Ofunehiki?
Come on, Dad.
I know...
Sorry about what happened
at our last meeting.
We, um...
let our tempers get the best of us.
That doesn't matter right now.
More importantly, are you being serious?
Yeah.
When you first told
us about the winter,
we weren't really sure what to think.
Because of the saltflake snow falling
and the weather being what it is,
everyone realized it might be true.
So please!
We beg of you!
You know, Hikari...
These people were laughing
at what you said,
but now that the fishing's not good
and they see what's happening,
they want to be on board with you.
You have every right to decline considering
how convenient this sounds for them.
But, if possible, please
accept their plea.
The surface is a very
important place to me.
Please.
So everyone on the surface is
going to help us out, right?
Of course we'll help
in any way we can.
This is the consensus opinion of
the Oshiooshi Fishery Cooperative.
All right.
Then leave it to me.
And so...
Everyone from the Fishery Cooperative
said they'd help with the Ofunehiki!
Oh, I see.
Very well done, indeed.
However, even if you go through with
the Ofunehiki, nothing will change.
What?!
But...
That's not what you said!
Oh? I was just asking
if you could move the
men on the surface.
Did I ever say that would
result in anything further?
Please!
Save the surface!
I beg you! Save them...
I am but the scale of the Sea God.
My powers will not extend beyond the sea.
There's nothing I can
do about the surface.
But...
Uroko-sama...
You knew all this yourself.
The fact that the Ofunehiki
had no meaning or power.
But...
Apparently the humans
weren't a total loss.
What am I supposed to say to them?!
After all of them worked so hard!
And they're still working hard as we speak...
Hikari...
I know that all those guys would never
have wanted to bow their heads
to a kid like me.
But they did anyway.
And I said that I'd do it and
that they could leave it to me...
You did your best.
It's fine. Everyone knows that.
Nee-chan...
Hey, Hikari.
There was something I
was thinking about...
I brought them.
Let me go!
This is a violation of human rights!
I'll sue!
Right, right.
Um...
Thank you all for gathering here today.
I had something I wanted
to ask of all of you.
I think that you are all aware by now,
but Shiodome Itaru-san and
I are going to be married.
And so...
I was wondering if it would be possible
to do the Ofunehiki
and wedding together.
Together?
I was wondering if you'd let
me take Ojoshi-sama's place
on the boat to be sent out to sea.
But does that mean...
You're going to be the sacrifice,
and try to calm the Sea God's rage?
But Uroko-sama said there was
no point in the Ofunehiki.
Right...
If Uroko-sama said that, I'm
sure nothing will happen...
and there may be no
point in me doing this.
But if there's nothing
else that we can do,
I want to try everything
we can just in case.
I'll be the Ojoshi-sama.
And when the Ofunehiki is over,
I will marry Itaru-san as if I
were going to marry the Sea God.
Will you... forgive me?
No!
Because if you go to sleep in the ocean,
you'll be able to keep living, right?
Then I want you to
keep living, Aka-chan!
But I need you and
Itaru-san in my life now.
There's no point in me living
if I don't have you two.
So, I'm sorry, but I definitely
won't go away.
I'm going to live my life in the same
place and time as you, Miuna.
Aka-chan!
I'm so sorry!
I don't care if it's futile.
I just thought I needed
to do something, too,
after seeing all of you work so hard.
Because I don't want to
say goodbye to all of you
without trying anything!
I...
I think that's a great idea!
I, um...
want to do this together!
The wedding!
Sounds good.
Let's do it.
It would suck if this just ended
with us being swallowed up.
Yeah!
Just watch, Sea God!
We'll put on such a flashy ceremony,
there'll be no way you can ignore it!
Yeah!
And so, the Ofunehiki
was put in motion again.
Just like the very first one our
ancestors put on for the Sea God.
With the assistance of the
Fishery Cooperative,
the fishermen started
helping us out as well.
We were able to use the shipyard,
so it wasn't just us anymore,
but the adults were helping out, too.
Thanks for your hard work!
Thank you, too!
See you tomorrow!
Thanks for your hard work!
Akari-san!
Could you check the fire and the door...
It's so amazing. It's very admirable.
No... not just Akari-san...
But Hikari, and Manaka, are
both trying hard to change,
and have changed, and started
changing everyone around them.
It's sort of like a modest resistance.
Kaname, too, probably...
Akari-san.
I'm going to confess
my feelings to Hikari.
It might not do any good,
but I can't let it end without
trying or without changing.
Because that's what I believe, too.
I love Manaka...
I don't understand any of that!
This is the best that I can do...
Don't talk to me!
I won't forget.
Episode Twelve:
I Want to Be Kind
We won't... see each other anymore...