Torrent
All right, now that Kiriyama
has joined us, shall we continue?
This is how I set up the board.
This is...
Last year, in the Lion King
challenger's tournament,
this is what the board looked like when I lost.
This just bothered me suddenly.
Tokyo
Nagano
Tokushima
Kyoto
This weekend, I have to head to Tokushima.
So I felt like delving into one of my defeats.
All right, continuing...
I'm telling you.
Black should go 6-a-Bishop,
and white should go 5-b-Pawn.
Then black should go 7-d-Pawn.
Wrong.
Black just needs to go 7-d-Pawn.
Why does the bishop need to be taken?
Are you the type who gets killed on a battlefield
right away from moving around too much?
Pffft!
What are you talking about?
What about you, Mr. Shigeta?
You sit there with pride
while constantly checking the situation,
and before you know it,
you're surrounded. The end!
Like the Battle of Sekigahara's Shimazu type?
If black goes 6-a-Bishop, and white
goes 5-b-Pawn, it'll just be a hardship.
The 6-a-Bishop being taken is a benefit.
Whoever takes a Bishop first will degenerate.
Black going with 7-d-Pawn is logical.
Black Cat Team
If black goes 7-d-Pawn and 6-d-Gold,
it's illogical to go with 6-a-Bishop.
Rumble
It makes more sense to go 3-e-Pawn
to take your 7-a-Bishop.
White Cat Team
So you'll leave my 5-b-Pawn alone with your
5-h-Rook open? Their future sure looks bright.
Chuckle
Well then, how about my 6-a-Bishop
takes your 6-d-Gold?
There's no way you'd approach my gold
when you can't even take the 7-d-Pawn!
There are many words here, so we're providing
metaphorical images as accompaniment.
If you let me take your 5-b-Pawn,
I've already won.
How about 4-g-Bishop takes the 7-d-Pawn?
Just use the 5-f-Pawn, right?
What? You don't even get that?
Why don't you start over from the 1st dan?
Checkmate within 45 Moves
Captured Piece:
Silver
Silence...
They've finally quieted down.
Stare
Checkmate
within 7 Moves
Trick to quiet down hyper students in a classroom
So this method still works, huh?
Once you've solved it, take your seat.
So what do you think about this, Kiriyama?
Sorry?
Would you go for the 6-a-Bishop?
Or the 7-d-Pawn?
The thing is, it's already...
Once the board gets to this position,
you're already in bad shape.
Don't undermine the premise.
We can't learn anything that way, Kiriyama.
But unless we imagine it in the context of
a real game, there's no point in studying it.
Something would have to be done
before the board got to this point.
Be specific. How do you figure this is hopeless?
You mean explain it?
Um... How can I put it?
It's disturbing... or like...
Disturbing?
Disturbing?!
Kiriyama, did you want to say something
abstract, and think we'd interpret it as genius?
Speak clearly! Or do you want me to
stimulate your speech center?
Hey, put my cactus down.
Sorry, Kiriyama.
This is a workshop,
so verbalize your feelings for us.
Until now, you studied alone,
so I'm sure you didn't bother with that.
But do your best, and go ahead.
Um... First...
The 3-g-Silver is still on the board.
That's one thing I find disturbing, or...
So, in what way?
Um...
I think going with black's 7-d-Pawn
will only result in injury.
Injury? No way, what are you saying?
Yeah. At this point, I agree
with the steamed bun's opinion.
Steamed bun?
What's that, you bastard?!
You wanna step outside?
That would make my day!
Damn it, it's noisy. Shush it, you guys.
Or I'll smack you.
I see.
Disturbing, huh?
Interesting.
Well, see you next time.
Yep. I'll check my schedule and give you a call.
Okay!
Oh, Kiriyama.
Yes?
Are you free tomorrow?
Yes. After school, I don't have any plans.
"Can you come back tomorrow?
This time, just you."
That's what Mr. Shimada asked me.
And so, the next day...
Hey there.
Sorry to make you come continuously.
Wobble
You haven't slept?
I have. Or more like, I passed out.
At the board.
What do you want to drink, Kiriyama?
I'll take care of it. What would you like?
Oh. Then hot coffee.
I only have instant, though.
Here you are.
I appreciate it.
One more loss and the next one
will be do-or-die.
Straight losses...
That's the one thing I don't want.
I shouldn't have been wondering
if I get to play in my hometown or not.
First, I need two wins.
The sixth match is in my hometown.
Um, your hometown...
It's Yamagata.
Yamagata...
What's it like?
It's just snow.
What about when there's no snow?
Mountains, rivers, rice paddies...
Yeah, nothing.
But if there are rice paddies, that's not nothing.
But they're reducing the acreage.
Even now, those rice paddies...
Well, even if I say this,
it's hard to understand, huh?
Really, it's a place that
doesn't want anything there.
That goes for people... and rice paddies...
Schools... and homes...
That's why...
That's exactly why...
I couldn't hear what he said,
but...
I have a feeling he said, "That's exactly why."
So, shall we get started?
Go ahead an build the fortress normally.
You remember the board
from yesterday, right?
Like that.
Here we go.
8-h-King.
9-e-Pawn.
3-h-Rook.
Wh-What is this?
7-c-Knight.
1-f-Pawn.
4-b-Bishop.
3-g-Silver.
5-c-Silver.
3-e-Pawn.
It's rushing towards me.
Mr. Shimada's thoughts.
Like water that's been let loose from a dam.
So suddenly, and so much force!
3-e-Bishop.
Same, Bishop.
4-c-Pawn.
Crap! I was sleeping.
I-I could've died.
That's right.
I came home.
Ow!
My shoulder and my eyes? What is this?
I'm totally exhausted.
If I think about it, it was the first time
I was subjected
to a Rank A player's thoughts
for several hours.
It was like a muddy stream.
But I wouldn't let myself
be swept away or retreat,
so I held on desperately.
I am...
No, we're both professionals.
It's not a relationship where
just one person is allowed to benefit.
At that time,
Mr. Shimada thought I had something that
he could "steal," which is why he invited me.
And though possibly minor,
I thought I had something to offer,
and that's why I asked to join
the workshop.
Because on that day,
a thought pierced my mind.
"There's something I want to ask him."
Until I get that answer, all I can do is hang on.
All right.
The next day.
Mr. Shimada left to Tokushima.
The curtain was about to lift...
on the third match
of the Lion King Tournament.
Torrent
Passing Time
Report Card
You just barely made it, huh?
Mr. Hayashida.
End-of-Year Party
I guess everyone's going to Mouseland
in two days for an End-of-Year party.
Did you know about it?
Although I wasn't invited, of course.
I don't know why you keep informing me
of these things throughout the year.
I really think this falls
into the realm of bullying.
- Seriously?
- Come on now.
Nothing has changed.
I squeaked by with attendance.
I didn't join a club.
My rank is stagnant, too.
I haven't accomplished anything.
But I was able to move up a grade because of...
Because of you, Mr. Hayashida.
Thank you.
Come on, now.
Haven't accomplished anything?
Don't say that.
You've been coming to school while working.
You make your own meals.
You do the laundry, take out the trash.
You fight...
Make money, pay rent...
When I was 17, I thought,
"I can be a big shot when I grow up."
I had that groundless dream
while going to the arcade, reading manga,
hanging out with friends, watching TV...
I never worried about rent
or bothered to save up money.
I never cleaned or prepared meals
or did the laundry.
Takashi!
I need
to vacuum!
So don't tell me
you haven't accomplished anything.
You did your best!
I saw it!
I want him to stop.
He's always like this.
Insensitive, outspoken...
I just wish he would stop.
When he suddenly says things like this...
...I can't handle it.
Hey. It's still cold outside, right?
How about we go for some oden?
My treat, to celebrate you advancing.
That's okay. You don't...
Then you wanna go? To Mouseland?
Just us two guys!
You wanna go? Right now?
No. Oden...
Really, oden is good.
And so,
my short spring vacation began.
The Lion King Tournament,
match three, day two.
Lion King Tournament
Live Feed
Mr. Shimada is in a tight spot.
At this rate, all he can do is persevere.
On top of that, Mr. Shimada
has expended more time.
One more loss and the next one
will be do-or-die.
Straight losses...
That's the one thing I don't want.
Mr. Shimada... Please... Please...
Coming!
Who could that be?
Hina, and Momo, too.
Um, w-we came to pick up our empty boxes.
Tiny
Glance
Um, hold on a second.
I'll get you something to drink.
What should I serve guests?
I'm sure tea would be fine for adults,
but what do I serve a middle school student
and a kindergartener?
You have hot tea with inari sushi!
Don't you have any chocolate?
Serve me something sweet!
In a way, relatively easy to serve as a guest
You don't have any soda?
Um... Thank you for
the multi-tiered box of food.
It was delicious.
Did you eat all of it, Kiriyama?
I-I did.
Nom
Even though she ate most of it...
I managed to have two pieces.
Um, the one with wasabi was really good.
I see. That's good to hear.
Sis and I made that together.
It turned out really well for Girls' Day,
so we made some for you, too.
Grandpa likes wasabi,
so we put that in for him.
So...
When we last saw you,
who was that person with you?
Stare
Um... from that...
Um... How can I put it?
Uh... I was wondering if you were all right.
U-Um, because it looked like
you were arguing with her.
I mean, it seemed like you were
on the receiving end...
S-So I wondered if you were okay, and...
I-Is she a witch?
If I really were a witch,
I wouldn't have such pathetic hardships.
No. No, she's not.
She's no witch.
She's my...
older sister.
Older sister?
Yeah. We're family, so sometimes we fight.
But it's all right. Because we're siblings.
It's the same at your house, right, Momo?
That's true! Akari and Hina
are always fighting!
She really cries a lot!
Hey! Momo!
But still, really close!
Yeah. That's my point.
We're home! Mystery solved!
Sis, that woman is Rei's sister!
What a relief!
I was worried over nothing.
It was just an argument between siblings.
Who would've figured?
Is that so.
Huh...
Oh no
Wait, Hina, that's probably worse.
Heap
- Warm.
- This is the best.
Cozy
Let's watch Squirrely Teacher!
Yeah, let's watch Squirrely Teacher!
I'm hungry!
Teach us, Squirrely Teacher!
Squirrely Teacher! Squirrely Teacher!
Mreow
I'm hungry!
Squirrely Teacher, please teach us something!
Never mind that squirrel!
In fact, I'm so hungry,
I could eat that squirrel!
You shouldn't eat squirrels.
Teacher knows everything
While eating some nuts...
They lived under the same roof
for almost ten years...
But when we saw them together...
...they didn't seem at all like brother and sister.
I see... Rei...
So that's why...
...you left that home, isn't it?
The third match of the Lion King Tournament.
After 113 moves,
Kai Shimada 8th-Dan...
...conceded the game.
And at 5:00, I heard a familiar tune
being broadcast throughout town.
For the first time, I noticed
that song is called "Hometown."
Passing Time
Next Episode Preview
Episode 19
What's Master Souya like?
He really pisses me off.
The way his skin is so shiny,
or how fluffy he is...
Um, Mr. Shimada...
I'm going home for today.
1-2...
Don't miss the next
"March Comes in Like a Lion"!
I wonder what Squirrely Teacher
likes to eat?
Bubble gum!