Not Enough Money
Will I get to
make an appearance
this time around?
*nervous*
Poor guy
Grr
They cut down on the extra
mini-segments because there isn't enough money?!
Put together a two-hour
Saturday 8 o'clock special!
Write a 500 page script!
Don't spend the whole time
talking about Chihaya!
Pissed
What?!  I thought you were finally
going to show my Road to Class A!
Stop toying with me!
Considering my skill, it's obvious that
I'll make Class A before Mashima does!
I didn't get any screen
time the first season,
so I'll be the main character
this time around, yes?
What?
I'm not?
My story about giving up on love
to pursue my dream of designing—
Wait!  Who is this Johnny
Depp look-alike?!
Lock on
He's so hot!
Good morning.
Impossible...
I was dumped...
I need to find a new boyfriend!
The hottest guy in this school!
This is the last new member, um...
I'm Tsukuba from class 1-10.
Um, nobody was in the classroom...
Are we in here today?
Thank you for coming, Hanano-san!
Thank you!
...are wet with dew
So the flower has wilted during the long
spring rains, just as my beauty has faded
I know this one!
You were happy about taking
your first card, right?
You'll start moving faster and
faster to take cards, Sumire-chan.
O-Okay, how about your right hand?
Just trim your right hand.
Wait!
Stop this!
I already said that I joined this
club to be with Mashima-senpai,
not to play karuta!
Oh...
Oh gosh...
I've had enough!
Wait!
Sumire-chan!
Ayase!
Forget it.
She's made it clear that she
doesn't want to play karuta.
Just ignore her.
Ever since I collapsed and had to forfeit
last year during the national championship,
I've spent every day wondering
what would have happened
if we had one more member.
We finally have new members...
Two of them stayed.
I can't ignore them!
Yesterday, when you said
that Hundred Poets was
a bunch of love poems,
I had to admit you were right.
We share the same feelings
that they did in the past.
However, Hundred Poets
is an anthology of poetry.
Their poems are still known
a thousand years later,
because they expressed their
feelings and techniques
in adherence to the 31 syllables rule.
The feelings expressed are
dependent on the rules!
Do you really think that
the president knows your
true feelings after hearing
that little outburst?
Hanano-san.
Can you teach me how to put on mascara?
Since I only have three eyelashes...
There's no such thing as a human
with only three eyelashes!
Let me see!
This is my
eighth year
in college now
Adding
Eyelashes
I'll have some wagashi to celebrate
Three...
Sorry, the mascara doesn't change the
fact that I only have three eyelashes.
Why do I feel defeated...
I can no longer call myself
the Mascara Shogun!
Kana-chan, for the next school
club committee meeting...
Yes?
I had to resort to fake ones!
Everybody will be used to
it by the last episode
Chihaya Furu
Boarding for @@ Line
Love Hunter
That hurt!
Hey!  Looking like Johnny Depp
doesn't mean you shouldn't
watch where you're going!
Sent him flying
Don't exaggerate. I just bumped into you.
Pull yourself together.
It may be broken...
Well, I guess I'll have
to take you home then.
Good-bye, Desktomu-kun
Where do you live?
Wanna stop by the hospital?
You're awfully skinny, you know.
Wanna grab something to eat?
Episode 16
Wait
for
the
Emperor's
return
Last year's champions will
now return the trophy.
This was the first trophy
we worked together to win.
We have to win again
and make it to Nationals.
Our next dream is to be
number one in Japan!
Group A Round 1
Mizusawa High School
Nishida Yusei
Oe Kana
Ayase Chihaya
Komachi Tsutomu
Mashima Taichi
Yeah, we want to get off
to a running start.
Let's use the order
Komano came up with.
Sounds good.
I think it's fine.
Oh, then I'll go turn this in.
Huh?  Oh, thanks.
Tsukuba-kun?
Komano Tsutomu [Removed]
Tsukuba Akihiro [Replacement]
What do you think you're doing?!
How could you change the order?!
If you've got a problem, say something!
B-But!
I came within three cards of
beating Komano-senpai once!
I've almost caught up
in terms of skill!
I'm...
Cool down.
If you can't, go home.
Let's switch up the order.
For our first match against Shuryukan,
let's switch me out
for Hanano Sumire.
Huh?
For our second match against West High,
we'll switch out Kana-chan
for Tsukuba Akihiro.
The remaining three players
will have to play every game.
Mashima, Porky, Ayase...
It's on you.
Let's go, Mizusawa High School.
The night breaks to day...
May I live to see...
In the sleepy...
Uh...
Why are you giving me a chance?
Shh.  You're too loud.
I said a lot of rude things.
I've been in your shoes.
I was also given a chance.
One win for Mizusawa!
Two wins for Mizusawa!
Not President Mashima...
Okay!  Three wins for Mizusawa!
Not Porky...
We wouldn't be this strong,
if the first-years weren't here.
Hey, Retro!
What are you thinking?!
Your projected order was
completely different!
Amakasu-kun, calm down!
What are you trying to pull?!
Predictions are gonna
be wrong sometimes!
Was your prediction wrong?!  Well?!
Why should we use minimal energy?
What?!
Aren't we supposed to be Hokuo Academy?
Our ace against their ace.
Our number two against
their number two.
Isn't that how we should win?!
Hokuo Academy is the
strongest school in Tokyo!
That's what I want to show everyone!
Ms. Miyauchi?
Sorry to show up right when
you're about to start.
I had the idea to make these yesterday,
and I just put on the finishing touches.
It should be easier for
you to move around now.
Tasuki...
I can move now.
I don't feel as hot now.
Waves creep closer...
When the misty bridge...
She's lost two of her
best cards in a row.
That boy has good sense.
Feel sorrow wash...
Retro!
Why do you always use strange motions?!
Impassionate gods...
Yes!
All four of them got it!
W-Wait!
"Impassioned vows" is still in play,
so I was able to cover in time!
I touched the card first.
I moved around your hand
to tap it from the side.
One win for Hokuo!
What?
Porky was crushed?!
Lost by 13 cards
I know that my heart...
Uh, I'm moving "The hazed early" left.
Is he doing this because
I'm left-handed?
I'm moving "The fall paddy" left.
Oh, sorry.  I think I'll move it back.
No, that's not what
they're trying to do!
Wait until Kana-chan has received hers!
Don't send your card yet!
I'm sending "The hazed early."
They got us.
Hokuo...
...successfully split their cards.
Huh?
The hazed early
dawn light
The fall paddy
The hazed early
dawn light
The fall paddy
Does this mean...
...it's really hard for
us to score three wins?
No way!  What do we do?  What do we do?
What am I doing...
If "The hazed early" is read,
Chihaya will take the opponent's card!
If "The fall paddy" is read,
I'll take the opponent's card!
We're not giving up!
Mizusawa will take three wins!
We'll be the champions!
The fall wind parts the wispy clouds
A fault...
One win for Mizusawa!
Amakasu...
Be careful, Amakasu!
There are people...
to reveal moonlight, clear and bright.
capable of clearing their
minds in this situation.
The hazed early dawn light
comes not from the moon
Shouldn't we wake up Ayase?
Yes, the closing ceremony's
about to begin.
E-Everyone!  I'm sorry!
It's all because I screwed up!
Because I lost first!
Chihaya...
Th-That was fun!
That was the most fun we've had!
Karuta
Club
Secrets
Treasure
We've run into a serious problem in the
second season that affects all of us.
The fact that my sister
Aw, you're sweating so much
and Retro-kun are the only people
we know who are dating someone!
We can't be positive that
they're the only ones.
Girlfriend?  I've got plenty of those.
A whole bunch
They give me candy
Naturally
I-I have a bunch...
We can't trust their claims!
I have...
We already know what
you're gonna say, Queen!
Besides, we spend too much
time playing karuta!
Mashima probably has girls
confessing to him all the time!
Why don't you go out with them?!
I'll start calling you Piggy instead of Porky
How can he treat something
so important so lightly?!
Look at how heavy he is!
Yeah, but,
relationships aren't all sunshine and rainbows.
Insurmountable Wall
Yes, I know what you mean
You can tell they're experienced!
Wait, I'm grouped with Retro?
I want to go out with
someone who's good at karuta.
I want to go out with someone who
knows how to put on a kimono.
Just
kidding
<3
Well, I guess we'll be the best
couple for the time being
Cough
I hope the second season
has more romance
Tsukuba!  Let's practice!
Yes, sir!
Oe Traditional Clothing offers lessons
for putting on kimono, right?
Desktomu-kun, let's go together!
Huh?
1 Nishida Yusei
2 Oe Kana
3 Ayase Chihaya
4 Mashima Taichi
5 Tsukuba Akihiro
What?!  Tsukuba's really a starter!
That's amazing!
Starter...
The group stage match-ups
were drawn yesterday,
so Komano and I already came up
with the order for the first round.
Why me?  Isn't Komano-senpai a starter?
For the National Tournament
A month has passed since
the Tokyo regional.
You've worked very hard.
In terms of skill, you're even with me.
Don't forget that our goal is
to become number one in Japan!
While the two rounds in the
group stage are taking place,
I'll be scouting the other top schools
to prepare for the
championship bracket!
The five of you have to get us there!
Does that mean you're not
playing in the group stage?!
Are you really okay with that?!
Yeah.
Though I prayed...
Porky!
What are you doing?!
We've been looking for you!
The match is about to begin!  Hurry!
There's no time for us to talk strategy now.
Why were you in the cafeteria?
We bought three lunches.
Oh, we'll be going with the same
lineup we used in the group stage.
Playoff teams, please head inside.
Really?
So you don't want to play?
Porky!
If you're matched up against
Kawabe, try to stay calm!
I don't need your help.
He's just guessing!
Hurry up.
No, I'm not...
Don't need your help...
May it be that I...
This is bad...
I can't keep up with his
sporadic bursts of speed.
My arm won't move.
This Kawabe guy is really good...
Kawabe?
He's just guessing!
We won!  Mizusawa won!
You're playing in the
next match, right?
next match, right?!
You're going to join us, right?!
Desktomu-kun!
Long last we meet, only for
me to leave hurriedly,
She knew to pay extra attention
to "Long last we meet"...
She couldn't get it.
This is the West representative.
No...
She's much faster than she was that day.
She has the potential to become Queen.
Silent waves creep closer...
The storm will soon carry...
For you, I would have given up my life
Megumu?
I have to beat her.
But I have to win to
make everyone happy.
I have to beat you now.
Feel sorrow wash...
I don't remember her having
such a fast motion.
Megumu-chan...
Megumu-chan is me.
Stop taking cards with your speed.
She's who I'd be if someone
hadn't taught me better.
Megumu, I'll secure our first win,
so you can take it easy.
Okay...
Time to attack!
Mizusawa!
Yeah!
Okay, one card!
One card!
One card at a time!
Y-Yes!
I'm treating you like a boy!
You're weaker than Megumu!
Okay, I won!
One win for First Akashi Girls'!
Rain takes longer...
No way!
Megumu even lost her "Rain" card?!
One win for Pizusawa!
I lost "Silent" and "Rain."
Her speed is real.
This girl...
Ayase Chihaya...
Impassioned gods...
Got it!
Two wins for Mizusawa!
First Akashi Girls' has 2 wins...
Mizusawa has 2 wins...
Desktomu-kun!
His opponent has "The sight of Mount,"
while Komano has "May my lonely"
in a luck of the draw.
There are four more dead cards...
Though my hatred has waned...
So the flower petals...
I wish I could show the
people how my sleeves
It's not over yet?!
Excuse me.
It's scary.
This is the last game...
to decide the match!
Said world grants no escape
Komano, have you noticed?
There aren't any more dead cards!
The next card will decide
the game!
It's scary...
But...
I hide in the mountains, only to
hear the haunting cry of a deer
I'll always have...
The sight of Mount Arima...
Desktomu-kun...
Desktomu-kun!
Mizusawa High School defeats
First Akashi Girls' 3-2.
Retro-kun?
Wataya-kun...
Aren't you going to cheer them on?
Mashima and Chihaya are playing
to become the best in Japan.
Goodbye then.
Shinobu-chan.
Won't you watch some of the team match?
Your presence will encourage
some of the players.
I'm actually a greedy person.
Huh?  We know.
Compared to becoming Queen, becoming
the strongest woman in Japan,
it's much harder for us to
become best in Japan together!
Let's do this!
Mi!
Zu!
Sa!
Wa!
Fight!
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
It's completely different.
This is the sound of
a certified reader.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
This is our grand finale!
Coach Sakurazawa's
Be Grateful Speech
They might as well make a live action movie
Then I would be...
It seems you all don't understand, so I'll tell you.
Over the two days, a total of 1000 students
participate in the High School Championship,
but there are about 100 people
who put the entire thing on.
Staff of the National Karuta Association, as well
as members of the local karuta societies
and Kansai's college karuta societies
work hard on the reading, judging,
setting up the tatami mats,
and preparing the cards, just for you.
What you mustn't forget is that these people
are mostly Class A or High Class A players.
The top people are Grade 10,
or even former Masters or Queens.
Meaning?
Put simply, if this were the
High School baseball championship...
The unsung heroes
are all stars
Third Base Ump.
Ichi**
Home Plate Ump.
Sada**** Oh
Second Base Ump.
Shige* Nagashima
First Base Ump.
Yu Darvi**
See you next week!
Next time I'll have
screen time