Isabelle...
I'm getting used to my new life.
How about you?
Are you sleeping well?
That's dangerous, Ruth.
S-Sorry. I was so happy,
I couldn't stop myself.
Welcome home, Ruth.
I'm home, Chise.
Silver.
How's Elias?
Still?
Elias...
It seems like breakfast is ready.
Sorry.
Can you tell Silver that I don't
need to eat today, either?
I wonder what's wrong with him.
It's been two weeks since we got back from the
church, and he still hasn't come out of his room.
Why don't you open the door and ask?
Let's go, Ruth.
Maybe the transformation from
the fight took a toll on him.
Transformation?
It takes a lot of energy to
change your appearance, maybe?
Why do you say that like a question?
I can't quite remember.
Maybe it hasn't quite hit
me that I'm a fairy.
Are you settled in now?
You've been exploring the
property this whole time.
It's something I need to do.
Instinctively.
As a dog?
I don't want to admit it, but yeah.
What's this?
W-Wait, Silky.
What is it, Chise?
I-I don't know what just happened,
but we got kicked out.
"For a change of pace.
Be back before it gets dark."
It looks like she gave us some spending money.
Looks like it.
I wonder if it's safe to
go out right now, though.
You have me.
Hey, long time no see, Chise!
Angelica-san.
How've you been?
Hey, Robin.
Um...
Elias is a bit...
No, I'm not asking about him.
I want to know how you're doing.
Do you have some time?
Talk about a shopping spree.
I can't buy any gifts for Silky, but I'm hoping
there's something she can use at home.
That sounds good.
Now, can I take a look?
It looks like it's functioning properly.
How do you feel?
Nothing unusual.
She looks sleepy all the time.
Ruth!
You seem especially tired
after you use magic.
Learn to depend on people,
or you'll screw something up...
When you're on your own someday.
You must be Chise's familiar.
Thank you.
You seem like a good person.
Don't try to do everything by yourself.
Otherwise, what's the point
of having helpful neighbors?
You're hot-blooded,
but you have a weak heart.
You have to take care of your body.
I'll do my best.
Speaking of which, what are
you doing about school?
You could be going to school, at your age.
I don't know.
I have to take care of
the flowers and herbs.
Studying magic is a lot of work.
Each season has its own special chores
to do and lessons for me to learn.
I'm just content being allowed to
stay with Elias and the others.
Chise, are you sure you
aren't being overly dependent?
You're young.
You have a long time ahead of you.
Don't spend your time relying
on handouts from others.
You were bought by Ainsworth.
I know you had a hard time elsewhere,
but you don't have to be fixed to him.
I-I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
I'm sorry.
No, I've said too much.
That's not true.
I know you're right.
I'm sorry.
Sorry about today.
No, thank you for caring about me.
Don't be too much of a good girl.
See you, Robin, newbie.
I'm a coward.
I'm depending on someone who
doesn't think anything of me.
I tell myself that I wouldn't mind being
abandoned, yet I don't want to be.
I'm selfish.
I used to hate coming home
when the lights were on.
Chise.
Yes, Ruth?
I share a little bit of many things with you.
Yeah.
Senses, emotions, and even memories.
If that event was a curse put upon
you, I want it to be lifted soon.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I'm home.
Thanks for the money.
I bought some gifts—I mean,
some snacks and such for us.
How's Elias?
Elias,
are you all right?
Elias, where are you?
Eli—
Chise!
Chise, sorry.
I can't control my body very well.
It might be scary, but let me stay this way.
Will you explain things to me in the morning?
Yeah.
Don't worry.
An inhuman body.
Limbs,
face,
neck.
The reason I'm not scared must be
because I'm cursed.
I shouldn't have given birth to you.
Elias...
Elias?
Morning, Silky.
Have you seen Elias?
Okay.
Ruth, it's time for breakfast.
Thanks, Silky.
Chise-kun.
Good to see you here.
Are you feeling better now?
Yes, thank you.
Stay away.
You seem fake.
Ruth, why did you shrink?
I can move with you easier in this form.
I see.
You must be her familiar.
You have a good big brother now.
Stare...
Um, have you seen Elias?
Ainsworth?
Sorry, I don't—
Thank you.
Wait, so soon?
I think he's rubbing off on you!
Where is he?
You must really love him.
Wh-Why?
You're afraid of him being gone.
More than that, you're worried.
But...
Why do you try to deny it?
It's important to love
something other than yourself.
It's important both to protect that
something, as well as for your own sake.
I love you, and I'll always love Isabelle.
Is that wrong?
I wish it were that easy.
You're so obstinate.
Well, hello.
Hello.
I haven't seen you before.
We just moved here recently.
Is that so?
It's remote, but it's nice here, isn't it?
Feel free to come see my
garden, if you're interested.
The queens will be happy, too.
Hey, you're a Sleigh Beggy.
That's unusual!
Speak of me, and I'll eat you.
A Leannán Sídhe.
She's a vampire that grants a man
talent in exchange for his blood.
Meanwhile, you're just a doggy.
Aren't your kind interested in younger men?
Suck that man's blood,
and he'll die in an instant.
So, you're Thorn's bride.
Apprentice.
Hey!
Would you two like to come in for tea?
Go get some rest, Chise.
You look pale from your lack of sleep.
I'll let you know if I find him.
Ruth.
Mess with her, and I'll
rip you apart, vampire.
I live alone here, so I've been longing for someone to have some tea with me.
I'm Joel Garland.
What about you?
Chise Hatori.
That's an amazing book collection.
I like books.
I write my own, occasionally.
It's quite enjoyable.
I have a short story, actually.
Could I ask you to read it?
Um, uh, but...
Do you not have time?
I'm not good at reading.
It might take a long time.
That's all right.
It was a love story.
A simple story about two people
who meet in a rose garden.
But there was something nostalgic about it.
Wasn't it a nice story?
Yes, but it didn't seem like you
were giving him the talent.
Why are you haunting him?
You're not taking his blood, either.
I felt like our eyes met that
day, in the rose garden.
It's not like he's my type!
He's old, and a skinny slob to boot!
He doesn't have anything he's devoting
his life to or anything, either,
so I can't take his blood.
And I can't give him what I otherwise could.
I don't know what to do.
Maybe, since you're a human,
you understand how I feel.
Sorry. I can't believe I dozed off.
I've been really sleepy lately.
Was that story about the roses here?
You got me.
I once saw someone very beautiful
here, a long time ago.
It might have been a daydream,
but it must have been...
Joel-san?
Oh, it's nothing.
I feel like our eyes met again just now.
Was it because of you?
Are you in lo—
That's not the answer I'm looking for.
We love by consuming and giving.
So I don't love him.
Come give him a visit again.
It'll make him happy.
Uh, okay.
It's not a word that I deserve to say
when all I can think about is myself.
Chise.
Ruth.
I found him.
He's in the forests north of the house.
Over there.
Chise.
It's dangerous to come
into the forest at dusk.
I left you a note saying
I'd be home by night.
You aren't going to tell
me anything, are you?
Why this is happening, what
kind of creature you are...
You always avoid me when I ask.
You're always quick to understand.
You accepted what I said
without questioning me.
That doesn't mean...
No matter how selfish I am,
it's not like I'm so disinterested in you
that I can bear not knowing about you.
I've never seen you make such a face.
Was I making a weird face?
Yes, I've never seen you like that.
Were you looking for me the whole time?
I left you a note and everything.
Huh?
What?
You're making a scary face.
Are you asking me to just take that note and
leave you, with the way things were going?
I may accept everything you say,
but if you vanish on me like that...
Why were you resting here?
My body's out of balance.
I was here adjusting.
Half of what he says is a lie.
I think.
I didn't mind him trying to
gloss things over before.
Why am I so scared now?
As for any other questions you may have
about me, could you give me a little time?
I want time to gather my thoughts.
I'll be waiting, then.
Are you angry?
I'm not angry.
Not angry.
What are you thinking about, then?
I told you, I'm not...
Kaboosh!
Elias!
A fairy?
Echos' familiar.
"From Lindenbaum to Thorn."
I have a message from Lindel-sama.
"I have business with the child
you foster. Come quickly..."
"To the land of dragons."
The girl visits the land of
dragons for a second time.
There, she learns of a side to the mage
that she'd never known before.
It came as certain as the night.