Maison de Ayakashi...
Also known as Ayakashi Kan.
An apartment complex
where humans, partially descended
from supernatural creatures, gather.
We're proper humans.
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about,
but I'm telling you, just keep quiet!
Don't...
touch me.
Oh, really?
This form is so much more relaxing.
I came here to be alone.
And yet...
Miss Ririchiyo,
are you really going to leave?
And discard me?
I'll be right back.
To me, a single moment apart from you
feels like an eternity.
You...
Miss Ririchiyo!
At least let me use the toilet alone!
I shall await you here forever!
This is a golden retriever.
Just being by his master's side
gives him the happiest expression.
However...
Miss Ririchiyo,
any moment without you is
empty and devoid of meaning.
Please be sure to give them lots of love.
That's just like him.
A Lonely Dog
Hey, Ririchiyo.
'Sup?
Didn't I tell you not to address me like
one of your buddies?
Good morning.
That's your whole breakfast?
Not very much, is it?
It's none of your business.
And you're having curry
udon for breakfast?
Not that I care.
Just don't splatter any soup on me.
Don't worry. I'm a pretty careful eater.
Whoops.
What did I just tell you?
Sorry.
So, how's it going?
How's what going?
Your Secret Service guy.
He's supposed to go shopping with me later.
Since I just moved, I still need a lot of stuff.
Oh, really?
You seem to be getting along
better than I expected.
I thought you'd fire him immediately.
Well, I don't know how long it will last.
You finally made a friend...
Mama's so happy, my little Ririchiyo!
I-It isn't like that!
Well, if anything goes wrong,
there's always your specialty,
"What you can't say out loud, write down."
You're surprisingly honest on paper...
That letter hit me right in the heart.
Forget about that!
I already told you.
I was just practicing my handwriting.
Yeah, yeah...
Also,
this lifts curry stains.
You're always so responsible.
Good morning,
Miss Ririchiyo.
I'm looking forward to
another day with you.
Your clothes suit you, as always.
You have a very distinct face,
which works perfectly with any outfit—
You may stop flattering me now.
Good morning.
How is...
your right hand?
It is fine.
As you know, our bodies
are more durable than an
average human body.
Miss Ririchiyo,
will you be breakfasting in the lounge?
I already ate.
That means you ordered it yourself,
carried it to the table,
and even poured your own water.
Does that mean you have no need of me?
How much do you want to do?
Everything...
From the moment you wake up.
You know...
your irritation level is
increasing exponentially!
What do you mean?
All I desire
is to take care of you.
And you said you would allow it.
I should have kept my mouth shut...
Oh, good. You're still here.
What do you want, Sorinozuka?
Did you need something?
I'm going shopping, too.
You're driving, right?
Can I get a lift?
The American cocker spaniel...
It's a docile dog that loves being babied
and following its master around.
They are also intelligent,
and are quite capable
of getting their masters to do
exactly what they want.
That's just like him.
May I bring you another drink?
No, I'm fine.
It's rather unexpected to see
your lazy self go shopping.
I was sort of sent on an errand.
Huh?
Is this really part of our job?
Look, look! It's amazing!
Here you go.
You can have whatever you want, Karuta.
Anything I want?
God, but I love girls with an appetite!
Ah, Karuta fantasizing about
some yet unseen food...
Mmm!
Where's Chiyo?
She's fine, don't worry!
Just open wide for me.
Say, "Ah!"
That's expensive.
He said he knows me from the past.
I told you when we first met
that I have known you for a long time.
He says I saved him.
But I don't remember.
It's not a mystery.
Our community isn't that large,
and there is a lot of activity.
I suppose
it really isn't some mystery...
Still...
The only reason I am here
is my loyalty to you.
It is irrelevant whether you are
the daughter of a great house or not.
He told me that it was for me...
for me alone, with no
connection to my family name.
How long I've waited to hear those words.
I'd like to repay them.
I may not be able to change right away,
but surely I can at least
do something in return.
Is everything all right?
A-Are you all settled in your new life?
Is there anything you require?
I'm fine, thank you.
And I thank you for your concern.
You interpreted that as concern, huh?
I merely want
you in perfect condition
if you are to work for me.
Thank you so much!
Ever since you agreed to
let me stay by your side,
my body and soul, and even my life,
are in perfect condition.
Because you gave your permission.
Are you trying to coerce me?
All that's left is the cell phone.
Yeah, you're right.
You don't have one?
I see.
I guess you didn't have any friends to call.
Miss Ririchiyo...
I don't need your pity!
I'll be living on my own now,
so having one will come in handy.
Well, yeah.
So have you decided on one?
What a silly question.
Everything I buy
undergoes multiple rounds
of careful analysis.
Digi Mono Station
I've done my research.
Wow.
Exactly what I'd expect, Miss Ririchiyo.
Now I have everything I need.
What did you want to buy, Sorinozuka?
Huh?
Oh...
Cake?
You wanted to buy cake?
Why not?
Cake and me are tight, man.
Don't you mean you and cup noodles?
You're such good friends.
Huh? Are you blind?
Well, we've known each other a while.
I'm kind of like a big brother.
We're just neighbors.
You know how she always makes enemies?
Then her trusty big bro comes in
and cleans up the mess.
Neighbors... That's all.
Feel free to call me "big brother."
I shall be sure to.
No, you won't!
Well, let's get going.
Why don't we hang out more?
Specifically, until six o'clock.
Why specifically until then?
Isn't there anything else
we need to buy?
Like...
How about you, Miketsukami?
I am here entirely in my capacity as
Miss Ririchiyo's Secret Service agent,
so please don't concern
yourself over me.
Come on, dude. Isn't that boring?
Not at all.
Just accompanying Miss Ririchiyo
on her shopping excursion...
It's like a dream to me.
What did you do to him?
I have no idea.
Like he did for me...
Isn't there something more
that I could discover...
to do for him?
We're back.
Why are we going to the lounge?
Just come on—
Huh?
Hey, hey...
You flattened me.
I'm not in the mood for jokes!
This is not the time.
Karuta hasn't come home yet!
Karuta hasn't come home yet?
I can't reach her cell phone.
It's already twilight.
It couldn't be...
When I imagine my little Karuta
being subjected to tentacle torture,
I can't just sit here!
Your glasses have fogged up.
The sun is setting.
This is a dangerous time.
Dangerous for those of us carrying
ancestral blood of supernatural creatures.
Miss Ririchiyo, you should wait here.
We don't have time for this.
Let's get a move on.
So, let's split up to look for her.
Give me your cell phone numbers.
I didn't think my first use of
this phone would be for this.
Ready?
Receiving
Finished.
Would you like to save?
1 - Yes
2 - No
Renshou Sorinozuka
Soushi Miketsukami
I... I think it's saved now...
It is.
Of course it is!
Then I'll search by air.
Wait!
What if someone sees you?
Don't worry...
I'll just pretend to be some paper
floating in the wind!
You idiot...
What if you get lost, too—
Miss Ririchiyo!
Where am I?
A wall...
Miss Ririchiyo!
Miss Ririchiyo... Miss Ririchiyo!
Are you all right, Miss Ririchiyo?
What is this?
I'm afraid she's behind this wall.
What?
Big Brother, could you go in
and have a look?
Sure, but what about you?
I...
I shall try to do something from here.
Hey! Ririchiyo!
Sorinozuka?
Whew, that was high...
You okay?
Why wouldn't I be?
It's just a stupid nurikabe.
All this spirit can do is block your way
when it manifests at night.
A nurikabe is a creature that creates
an invisible wall at night,
preventing you from moving past.
In recent years, it is often depicted
as a wall with arms and legs,
but originally, it was a three-eyed
spirit dog, with droopy ears.
So that's all this is?
That's right.
And you say it will be gone by morning?
It should be.
Then let's go to sleep.
Your adaptability is too extreme!
Hey, it was a joke, kind of...
But I can't go back without you.
We haven't found Karuta yet, either.
Is he okay?
Oh, yeah!
I should tell him you're safe.
He was worried about you.
Good morning, Miss Ririchiyo.
To me, a single moment apart
from you is an eternity.
You're such good friends.
It's like a dream to me.
As you know,
our bodies are more durable than
an average human body.
All I need to do
is break down this stupid thing!
This probably won't destroy you,
but prepare yourself!
I'm sorry, but I'm cutting you down.
There's a lonely dog...
that's waiting for me!
Oh, wow... It's fading.
You...
Miss Ririchiyo!
H-Hey...
You're safe!
Miss Ririchiyo...
Don't be so melodramatic.
Hey, it's me.
Where was he carrying that?
Trust the big brother to
have a secret spot.
Huh?
Karuta's back?
Oh... I see.
Hmm... Okay.
Well, you know...
This happens all the time.
Welcome back, you guys!
Welcome to Ayakashi Kan.
Yeah!
Welcome!
Wh-Wh-What is all this?
It's a welcome party.
I'm sorry for being out so late.
I couldn't find the house.
I thought this would be
appropriate for a celebration.
Yup, for a Christmas party.
A welcome party...
That looks delicious!
I truly am grateful.
But if I say something horrible again
and ruin the mood...
Miss Ririchiyo?
I think I'll pas—
Don't be like that!
This is a welcome party for Soushi, too.
But I am merely a Secret Service agent.
I don't think I...
Oh, come on.
I suppose, letting the food go to waste
would be an insult.
Oh...
Then, I shall join you.
Do you want some chicken?
Let's carve it.
Karuta, let me feed you... Say, "Ah!"
Ah!
You're going to drip gravy everywhere.
It's fine. I'm...
Whoops.
Renshou Sorinozuka
Soushi Miketsukami
I still don't really know
what I can do.
Sending
I sent it!
Wait...
Did it really go through?
But if we spend more time together,
maybe I can discover something.
I certainly have
my flaws, but I
look forward to
working together.
D-D-D-Did I do it right?
Does "Welcome" sound weird?
I'd like to think...
Unlike a letter, I can still reread it.
This is so embarrassing!
...that perhaps I can repay him this way.
Looks like you watched to
the bitter end again.
Good job, I guess.
"I'd like to thank you for watching,"
is what she's saying.
Well, you can tune in next time, if you
don't have anything better to do.
"I really hope you'll watch
our next episode:
Inu X Boku Secret Service:
The Real Contract.
Please enjoy it,"
is what she's saying.
S-Stop interpreting for me!
You really are a shy and
adorable person!
The Real Contract
Please permit me to accompany you again next time.