Miss Nureha!
Londark, anything to report?
Nothing so far.
The princess does what she pleases, anyway.
Does Mizufa intend to search for her?
I'll tell you what Mizufa had to say...
We're in the middle of Operation Red Night.
And if Miss Nureha left of her own free will,
it's none of our business.
Is that sarcasm, Londark?
The princess is the leader of Plant Hwyaden!
Miss Nureha...
If you were going home,
you should have taken me, Loreil.
West?
Again...
The Odyssey Knights, huh?
Around here, they aren't such an unusual sight.
Really?
The People of the Land welcome them.
They risk their lives fighting to
protect the villages and towns.
They do seem a bit tense,
but they're so cool and disciplined.
You think so?
They do seem like they'd be
handy to have around...
I don't like that thing.
It just doesn't feel right.
Me, either.
I couldn't say why.
When the Concert Ends
When the Concert Ends.
Let's eat!
How is it?
I haven't gotten any better at it...
That's not true. It's great.
It's perfect!
You're getting better and better at cooking.
And under this star-filled sky...
It's a fantastic dinner.
You're all so close.
Because we're friends.
Yeah, we're friends.
If you don't mind my asking,
why are you headed to the Redstone Mountains?
We're going to hunt a wyvern.
We need it for the materials for a magic bag.
I see.
We're almost to the town of Safil, aren't we?
That's right.
Have you ever been there, Dariella?
It's on my way home, so I've
been there a few times.
Once we get there, I'd like to hold a concert!
A concert?
What's that?
Come to think of it, Roe 2 hasn't seen one, either.
Isuzu is a bard.
But I'm still not much more than an amateur.
Wherever we go, she plays all
kinds of different songs.
Oh! Music?
Back at Blume Hall in Akihabara,
I was called a rock 'n' roller!
A rock 'n' roller?
Um, in other words, they think she's cool.
What?
That's leaving too much out.
You play music, though. That's interesting.
It's kind of wonderful.
Okay, when we get to Safil, we'll do one!
Yeah!
The Town of Safil
Japan Server
South Fuji Area
City/ Monsters Present
PVP Permitted
Skill Use Permitted
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
I can hear a song of love.
Let me be closer to you.
I'll change color and shape to protect you.
I can hear a song of love.
If I can keep looking at you,
even these blurred days will feel precious to me.
Always... Always...
Thank you, everyone.
Want another song?
Okay, here we go!
That was fun...
And I'm full.
Miss Isuzu, are you sure
you didn't eat too much?
I couldn't help it.
Thanks.
People of the Land kept buying me food.
Still, it was a good concert today.
Another good concert, you mean.
Another good one, yes.
Miss Isuzu, you really do
love instruments, don't you?
I love them.
But you still keep saying you're not
much more than an amateur?
Yeah...
It's not like I'm trying to be humble or anything.
I may have said this before,
but my dad was a pro musician.
I understand.
Then the reason you're so good is due to
your father's blood and your training.
Oh, come on, that's a bit of a stretch.
My dad was a really free spirit.
He was a rock 'n' roller.
He was so cool.
He had long hair that flowed in the
wind, and this leather jacket.
His legs were so thin.
And he loved to brag to me, his daughter...
Stories about the things he did
when he was young, I guess.
He worked at a part-time job
to buy this lousy old car,
and he put all his instruments
in it and went touring.
He said he went from Tokyo all around the country.
Like us?
Yeah, that's right!
He sounds like a wonderful father.
Right?
He was a little weird, but he was my hero.
He even made his major debut!
Major debut?
A major record company streamed his music.
Uh, in other words... He got really famous.
So famous you could hear his band's
songs all around the town.
That's amazing!
But you know, in my world, there are
a lot of amazing people like that.
Every year, over a hundred people
make their major debuts.
But most of them don't last long...
Only a handful keep selling
long after their debut.
And my dad wasn't one of them.
Did he quit?
No, he loved music, so he couldn't quit.
So he became a studio musician.
That's, well... How should I describe it?
I know. He became a super-pro instrument player.
He helps out many different
people with their music.
Then you'll make your major debut, won't you?
No.
A major debut is something professionals do.
You play, and it makes everyone happy.
Doesn't that make you a pro?
No, it doesn't!
I'm sorry... I'm not like that.
I like the lute, of course.
I love it.
And I love singing, too.
But... I don't have any talent.
My dad would always say that
becoming a pro was really hard.
You're expected to have natural talent.
Even if you do, you have to
work as hard as you can,
and only then can you see the starting line.
Oh.
So I'm happy just doing it because I like it.
And it makes everyone happy, too.
I also love your songs, Miss Isuzu.
You're so nice, Rudy.
I'm nothing special at all...
That isn't true.
We all look forward to hearing your songs.
To hearing a forty-two we don't know.
Huh? Forty-two?
Sometimes, it seems like we're not
really understanding each other.
Oh...
So that's how it sounds to you.
Yeah, that's happened to me.
You, too?
A while back, I asked for fish paste at
a store, and they gave me flour paste.
What?
It's probably because of that...
That?
The auto-translator.
Oh, the one that lets you
talk with foreign players.
Yes.
It seems like the languages of adventurers
and People of the Land are actually a bit different.
Normally, thanks to the auto-translator,
we can talk to each other...
Which means...
Sometimes, there are things the system
can't handle, and it causes errors.
I get it!
Then that's why we don't
always understand each other.
Let me see...
If I say, "seven colors," what do you think of?
A rainbow?
Yes. If I say, "seven colors," in People of
the Land's language, it means a rainbow.
Then what's "forty-two"?
Music.
Why?
To us, the People of the Land,
"music" only encompasses forty-two songs.
God only gave our ancestors
those forty-two songs.
And we can't make new ones.
A leftover from when it was a game?
That's the only music we have.
Since we were born, that's how it's always been.
We thought that was normal, and went our
whole lives without thinking about it.
I never considered that.
So, Isuzu, we really love the songs
you sing and the music you play.
Do you remember the inns
and pubs before we left?
You just played a simple song,
and everyone was so happy, they cried.
They were really happy.
Bright, upbeat songs that they'd never heard.
Songs that made them want to dance.
Or songs that made them want to
be with someone they cared for.
We'd never heard anything like that.
And you brought them to us.
That made you a hero.
Rudy...
Do you think Isuzu will become a pro?
I think she wants to, honestly.
It must be nice to have something
you're better at than anyone else.
You're right.
I'm jealous of how she can sing and
play an instrument like that.
I'm not really good at anything I try.
Have you ever thought about your future, Serara?
You mean if we get back to our world?
Yeah, if we do.
No, even if we don't.
Like, what you want to be.
I don't know...
It isn't really clear.
I see.
You seem like you've really thought about it.
I don't know.
I know who I'd want to be like...
I want to be like Shiroe.
But what does that mean?
It isn't his job, I know that much.
And no one could replace him, anyway...
I just don't know!
Minori?
Did you notice that more and more young
People of the Land are coming to Akihabara?
Nope.
They're all coming because they
have dreams for their future.
Blacksmiths, tailors, chefs, musicians...
A lot of others, too.
Just a few months in Akihabara
will teach you skills
you couldn't learn in a lifetime anywhere else.
You can be who you want to be.
Like you?
Yeah, that's right.
I became an adventurer.
They also have something they want to be.
We get together to talk about that stuff.
That's why I occasionally run off.
It's sometimes hard for People of
the Land to live in Akihabara.
But it's lucky, too.
Every day, something happens there.
What you couldn't do yesterday
may be possible today.
Tomorrow will be different from today...
And your songs are one of the wonderful
things to be found there.
The People of the Land are all thinking
about their futures, aren't they?
I'm not even...
I feel embarrassed for irresponsibly
singing about love and life...
No, Miss Isuzu, that isn't—
I'm sorry, Rudy.
You can go back to your room.
All right.
I'm so pathetic.
Come to think of it, there was
a river next to Choushi, too.
Why is that, again? Umm...
Settling near a river gives a town plenty of water,
which is better for living and for fields, right?
Depositional plains, was that their name?
School classes come in handy...
Good morning, Tohya.
Good morning.
Why don't you come over here?
S-Sure.
Dariella... Are you on a morning walk?
Yes.
I'm a light sleeper.
You live in Minami, right?
I travel all the time.
My job is to go all around,
and write down what I see and hear.
But I suppose my home would be near Ikoma.
Ikoma?
Past Kyoto, is how I think you would describe it.
I see.
But I live alone in a shack.
It isn't a place where you get visitors.
So when I want to enjoy the town air,
I go on journeys like this.
Isn't that dangerous?
I'm used to it.
And the roads have gotten a lot safer
since Plant Hwyaden started patrolling.
Plant Hwyaden, huh?
Plant Hwyaden has made Minami into
a beautiful, prosperous town.
Have you no interest in it?
I wouldn't say that.
Then, if you get the chance, come to my house.
If you do, I'll show you around.
We'll go out together.
You've been avoiding looking at me.
No, I'm not.
You don't dislike me, do you?
That part of you, I do dislike!
You're always smiling.
Yes.
What of it?
You wouldn't look weird without that smile.
You'd look better that way.
That isn't true.
Why do you say that?
Whoa!
How rude!
Well, where'd you even come from?
The window.
At least come in the door.
And?
The reconnaissance went off without a hitch.
There wasn't any problem this time.
Well, we were mostly after basic information.
Can I report to you now?
Yes, please.
Regarding the city of Maihama
and the Cowen family,
you're well acquainted with Princess
Lenessia's grandfather, Sergiatte, right?
Yes.
By the way, Duke Sergiatte's recent favorite
foods are seaweed salad and dorayaki.
Before bed, he has a glass of warm milk.
W-Wait a second.
How do you know all that?
Did you sneak into the castle or something?
Lenessia told me.
Huh?
I got this information using my feminine skills.
Feminine skills...
Do you doubt my feminine skills?
No, not really...
My feminine skills are amazing!
Are they?
I even went to a girls' night out.
Well?
"Well"? I think it's good to have friends...
Indeed, it is.
Then, continuing my report...
The well-regarded Duke Sergiatte is the Cowen
family head and is sixty years old.
His wife has already passed away.
When he was young, he led the
knights against monsters...
What's wrong, my lord?
You look unhappy, as usual.
Oh, well. You see...
Reports from the chief have stopped coming in.
From the old master?
That's rare.
He isn't responding to telepathy, either.
Is that possible?
No, not normally.
It makes me a little worried
about Minori and the gang.
He isn't picking up on telepathy.
Yeah.
I wanted to talk to him about something...
This is strange.
When did this start?
Maybe...
And I don't know if it's a side effect of that,
but I'm told it disturbs the voices
of adventurers' hearts.
Did she mean telepathy?
That mobile temple might somehow
be affecting things.
Then let's ask the knights.
They look a little scary,
but they're protecting the People of the Land.
Yeah.
If only Shiroe were here.
That's no good.
We decided to try to avoid relying on him
and the others as much as we could.
You're right.
You dislike me, don't you, Tohya?
No, I don't.
Then why would you say something like that?
That's...
By the way, what's Roe 2 going to do?
Yeah, I wonder, too.
She said she was going to Ikoma.
Maybe she'll go with Dariella?
Isuzu won't leave her room, either.
Maybe something happened with Rudy.
If Roe 2 will be splitting up with us,
we can't rely on her summons.
We need to find a place to
repair our summon flutes.
Serara?
What's that?
It looks like black clouds...
No, that isn't a cloud.
Those are wyverns!
They're heading straight for this town!
This is bad...
Hide somewhere safe, Dariella!
What are you going to do?
What the heck is going on?
Individual levels confirmed.
Wyvern
Rank/Normal
42, 46, 43, 50!
What do we do, Minori?
Regardless of their levels,
we can't handle that many!
Minori! Serara!
Tohya!
We have to get out of town for now.
We can't let this place become a battlefield!
But...
Hurry!
All right.
Let's go, Serara.
Yeah!
The Odyssey Knights stand against the
wyvern horde attacking the town.
They fight not to protect,
but to risk their lives in a horrific battle.
Tohya and the others are frozen stiff.
But Isuzu and Rudy run...
To challenge a god to a fight.
The Red Night
Next time: The Red Night.
I have friends to run with me.