High School Championship Tokyo Regional
Final Tournament Bracket
Mizusawa High School
Homei High School
Hokuo Academy
Shoha High School
The top two teams get to
go to Nationals, right?
We don't need to try that hard then.
How can you say that,
President Amakasu?!
Have you forgotten how we
were humiliated last year?!
We must defeat Mizusawa
and reclaim our trophy!
What?  That's too much effort.
Whatever.
We still have our Retrot cards.
Tell us the enemy order so we can win
with a minimal amount of effort.
We'll go after those three.
Mizusawa has one Class B
and two Class C players.
If we know their order,
we can guarantee three wins.
Retro's never been wrong before.
Well, we're counting on you.
Retrot
Chihaya Furu
Verse 5
Be as
dear now,
those were
the good
old days
Hey, why do they put all
the responsibility on you?
Are you getting enough rest?
Well?
What order should we go with?
Not sure.
It'll help if we can out think Hokuo.
But it's great that we still go
to Nationals, even if we lose.
This means we can relax...
What are you talking about?
Our goal is to become
number one in Japan!
To become number one in
Japan, we can never lose!
Hokuo will give us their best shot.
We'll take it back next year!
We get to play a 100% serious match!
Well, it's a good idea to aim high.
I'm a little worried about the
ultimate weapon Retro-kun mentioned.
Here, drink this.
Honestly, you can't do
anything without me.
S-Sis?!
I got a boyfriend recently
who's totally hooked on me!
Retro-kun is her boyfriend?!
Is this the ultimate
weapon he mentioned?!
Excuse me.
I went over to scout the other team
during their semi-final match,
and I heard their president
talking, since he wasn't playing.
It'll be easy to win against Mizusawa.
I just have to beat Mashima.
We only need three wins.
Any one of our regular starters
can beat glasses boy and boobie girl.
Huh?  He ignored us?
No way!
They wouldn't be so conservative
in the final match!
No, Chihaya.
This is how the strong schools play.
It makes sense to focus
on securing wins.
If they can guess our order,
they'll use that against us.
That's fine.
We just need one or two of
us to pull off an upset!
I just have to beat Mashima.
I'm mad now!
Any one of our regular starters
can beat glasses boy and boobie girl.
I'll make him regret that!
Boobie girl?!
Our captain wants us to
become number one in Japan!
No trickery!
Nishida Yusei
Oe Kana
Ayase Chihaya
Komano Tsutomu
Mashima Taichi
Here's the order we'll use!
Oh, I'll turn in the order.
Yeah, thanks.
Wait, hey!
Not again!  Why you...
But Oe-senpai looks a little tired.
That doesn't make it okay
to change anything!
You lost your match earlier!
But I was getting better as I played.
I think I can win my next match!
Your methods are wrong.
But!  But!
I'll be more useful than someone who's tired!
Enough!
Starting today, the boys in
this club aren't allowed
to start sentences with "but"!
What?!
Just the boys?!
We're sticking with
a second-year order!
You're a spectator, Tsukuba!
Good thing I'm a girl.
The president snapped...
Ta-Taichi...
Why are you telling
them not to use "but"?
I've been following that
rule since third grade.
Huh?
Men should never begin a
sentence with the word "but"!
I didn't always agree with my mother,
but she taught me to pay attention
to when I'm making excuses.
I'm a little scared of your mom...
but that's incredible.
Your mom helped you become strong.
This year, Hokuo is lead by the
third-year Class A Amakasu.
The first-year Shiroyama
is also in Class A.
A first-year in Class A?
The other players are in Class B.
Schools with real coaches
have way more depth.
Our coach is a science and PE teacher.
Okay, everyone!
We've reached the final!
Stay focused!
To ensure that all the
practice we put in after
last year's loss will pay off,
I have an ultimate weapon...
We lost last year because we
correctly guessed their order,
but failed to use that advantage.
That won't be an issue this year.
This will be easy.
Retro's Projected Order
Oe (C) - Shiroyama
Ayase (A) - Kameda
Mashima (B) - Amakas
Nishida (A) - Takuma
Komano (C) - Kinashi <- Me
Even if we lose to Ayase and Nishida,
we're guaranteed to win
the other three matches.
After we win the final with
a minimal amount of energy,
the coach will buy us yakiniku!
Yeah!
Fight!
I will now read the order
for the final match.
Hokuo Academy, Shiroyama-kun.
Mizusawa High School, Nishida-kun.
Huh?
Hokuo Academy, Kameda-kun.
Mizusawa High School, Oe-san.
Hokuo Academy, Amakasu-kun.
Mizusawa High School, Ayase-san.
Hokuo Academy, Takuma-kun.
Mizusawa High School, Komano-kun.
Hokuo Academy, Kinashi-kun.
Mizusawa High School, Mashima-kun.
What's going on?
They're playing us straight?
Hey, Retro!
What are you thinking?!
Your projected order was
completely different!
Amakasu-kun, calm down!
What are you trying to pull?!
He can't predict the order
correctly every time!
Was your prediction wrong?!  Well?!
Why should we conserve our energy?
What?!
Aren't we supposed to be Hokuo Academy?
Our ace against their ace.
Our number two against
their number two.
Isn't that how we should win?!
Hokuo Academy is the
strongest school in Tokyo!
That's what I want to show everyone!
H-He's so cool!
You're going to cost us this
match because of your pride!
Being good doesn't mean you
have to win straight up!
Hokuo Academy is the
strongest school in Tokyo?
Isn't that common sense?
You're late, Sudo-senpai!
I'm not late.
I made it just in time.
Though I would have left,
if you didn't reach the finals.
E-Err, Sudo-senpai?  Why are you here?
I didn't know you were
coming to cheer for us.
I'm not here to cheer for you.
Mochida-san asked me to be
the reader for the final.
Reader?
Who is that?
The former Hokuo Academy ace, Sudo-san.
He was the runner-up in the individual
bracket of the National Championship.
Huh?
Is someone like him allowed
to be the reader?
Get to your places.
Hokuo players never dawdle!
How come Retro knew and
I didn't, when I'm in charge,
Mr Mochida?
Amakasu-kun, you're a good player,
but you always want to relax.
You've given up on becoming
the best in Class A
with all these monsters around.
Sadist
Monster
Bear
This is tough...  Very tough...
But...
If we lose, he'll kill us.
Their facial expressions have changed.
He's putting pressure on Hokuo, not us.
Their ultimate weapon...
Ms. Miyauchi?
Sorry about showing up
at the last second.
I had an idea to make these yesterday,
and I just put on the
finishing touches.
It should be easier for
you to move around now.
Tasuki...
I can move now.
I don't feel as hot now.
You made it just in time.
Ms. Miyauchi...
You might be a science
and PE teacher...
You might not know much about karuta...
Please begin placing your cards.
Good luck.
You look pretty sharp...
at least on the outside.
However, I'm going to win today.
I will win.
Retro...
He's entered tournaments
in Hiroshima and Kyoto,
and he's still Class B
because he couldn't win.
Hiroshima
Tournament
It's him again!
Ogura Hundred Poets Competitive Karuta
Kyoto Tournament
Not again!
I'm getting sick of his face,
but it was comforting at the same time.
He hasn't given up on himself yet.
Your mom helped you become strong.
Chihaya...
A lot of people have helped
to make me who I am.
Aren't you the same way?
This sucks.
It's so exhausting to play
someone who's intense.
Why can't they learn to take it easy?
This would be a lot easier
if we still had Sudo-senpai,
but he's gone now.
He's gone...
If you don't pull it together, I'll stab you
...but he's still putting
pressure on us.
Both teams have secured their
places in the finals.
They could end up wearing
each other out.
So why...
is it so tense?
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
His voice is much stronger
than I expected.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
The air conditioner above
us is still broken,
but it's not as hot now.
Thank you, Ms. Miyauchi.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
They can keep the air conditioning off.
The only sound I need is...
Shallow waves creep closer...
They're too fast!
They're both way too fast!
Who got that one?
The little Hokuo guy?
Chihaya-chan was looking at the
Swift card on the opponent side.
Both start with the same "S" sound.
She was being cautious since
she doesn't know this reader.
I should have gotten that one.
I just need another 3 millimeters.
If my finger had been
right on the corner...
There.
Connect.
in my dreams, I creep closer to you
When the misty bridge...
She's lost two of her
best cards in a row.
That boy has good sense.
Got it
Rather, I guess, he has good reflexes.
Get back to your seat
A flexible upper body with
a snappy and firm spring...
I need to be sharper.
Here.
This is the point.
The point I want to reach.
I need to be more accurate!
Are you trying to insult me?
Reviewing your mistakes between cards?
Is this a practice match?
Ah, he makes a good point.
That's my student
You should focus on the next card
instead of the one you just lost.
I've been telling Chihaya-chan
that for a very long time.
Here.
It's okay, Chihaya-chan.  Carry on.
You sgould never dwell
on the past in a match.
Connect...
Connect!
The sound of birds crossing...
Who is this guy?  He's weird.
He moves a little slow,
which is throwing me off.
And...
That
hairpin is bugging me!
No matter where I stand...
After I determined...
You're pretty good.
Those boobies should
be weighing you down.
is that I have no way
to tell you in person
1, 2, 3, 4.
Said bed was cold as I lay awake
for the night would drag on
when I thought of my beloved
Sudo-san's voice
dissipates into the air.
As my love first came...
I can trust him!
Four in a row?
Excuse me.
I take that back.
Sudo-kun is pretty good.
His rhythm is accurate and
his enunciation is clear.
Did you have him read when
he was still on the team?
I can't imagine that he was interested
in reading during practice.
Well, that was the case before
he reached middle school.
Mr. Mochida.
I'm going to attend
a class for readers.
I believe that Master
Suo has spent more time
studying readers than he has
studying cards or opponents.
Sudo-kun's strength...
I'll be the one who crushes the Master
is drawn from his pride.
It's ironic, but the people
who have the most pride
are the ones willing to
put in the hard work.
Looking up every step of the way.
I thought she was faster,
but I guess I was wrong.
I'm already 7 cards up.
This should be a fairly easy win.
What is she doing?
She's being really sensitive
about her motion...
Focused on her accuracy...
Is she looking at Wakamiya Shinobu?
That's impossible!
I lost by 24 cards last year,
and you lost by 20 cards, too!
She's strong enough to
give you nightmares!
She's out of our reach.
Connect...  Connect...
Connect...  One more millimeter...
You can keep your eyes
focused on a distant goal,
while you lose the match you're in.
My own sleeves are like...
Good!
He was fast on that one.
He moved towards "My own home" before
returning to "My own sleeves".
Hokuo's players are pulling ahead.
It was only six months ago that we were
experiencing Sudo-san's pressure,
glares, and voice every day.
We have a home advantage when
Sudo-san is the reader!
Feel sorrow wash...
Retro!
Why do you always use strange motions?!
That was cool!
Your fingers are injured and taped up,
but you insist on worming them in!
Win!
The sky may hold the same moon
I'm in trouble.  Boobie girl is good.
It's our fifth match, but I'm
still able to move around.
Mom made sure that my
sash was tied tight,
and I have the tasuki
from Ms. Miyauchi.
I tire less easily in a kimono.
Oh, crap.
I'll be in big trouble if
I lose to boobie girl.
You probably wouldn't know,
but a kimono is designed perfectly
for moving around with boobies!
The more I learn about
competitive karuta,
the more magical it seems.
Gender doesn't matter.
Size doesn't matter.
Intelligence and strength don't matter.
Age doesn't matter.
Would this old palace courtyard
and the eaves strewn with weeds
Every poem read sends you
back a thousand years.
How many sports are
capable of such a feat?
Thank you very much!
Huh?
One win for Hokuo!
Yes!
Way to go, Shiroyama!
What?
Porky was crushed?!
Lost by 13 cards
This is bad.
The first victory in a
team match is critical.
The losing side feels
a lot more pressure.
So even when you're losing,
it's important to drag out the match...
Yet he lost this early!
It's been so long since
I played five matches in a row
and my head's starting to spin.
Those circles kept bothering me.
I got distracted every time I saw Sis.
You're so awesome, Retro-kun!
But...
Not allowed to start
sentences with "But"...
I thought we could count on Nishida...
What about everyone else?
How are Oe-san and Komano doing?
They're in close matches.
What about Chihaya?
Huh?
Chihaya's losing by 5 cards?
Chi—
I'm in a close match myself.
I don't have time to ask
her how's she doing.
If I speak, it'll be to signal
Mizusawa's first win!
You're trying to copy
Wakamiya Shinobu's style,
but you're closer to Suo
Hisashi's style right now.
Porky, I've always wanted to become
something I wasn't close to.
She can accurately and precisely
touch an exact point
with her fingertips...
She plays silent karuta...
However, I can't beat Amakusa-kun
with my accuracy right now.
It's not easy to be as
good as Shinobu-chan.
You have twenty!
Twenty one-syllable cards!
In the sleepy spring sunlight,
Chihaya-chan, are you...
...trying to use both
of their strengths?