It seems the Ancient Dragon is
approaching much faster than anticipated.
But the Queen's fleet
should be here soon.
Unfortunately, it's taking longer
to get additional cannons.
I saw the dragon!
Fifteen leagues, south-southeast!
It looks like the fleet
won't make it in time.
Zero's Familiar
Hiraga
The Gandalfr rune...
My contract with Louise is still active.
I forced Louise to make
such a sad face.
Someone who can't even make
the girl he loves smile
isn't a man!
H-He's here!
Calm down.
Here we go.
It's a counter from the
aboriginal school of magic.
They use tools to fortify
the power of the spirits.
Who are these Elemental
Siblings, anyway?
You see, never a boring day in
the land of the barbarians.
Since the area is so big,
it might not last too long.
For now it's enough.
I just hope this lasts
until the fleet arrives...
Everyone, look!
It's a flight of dragons!
I've got to get back to Halkeginia!
But how?
Think!
There's got to be a way!
E-Excuse me...
Are you going to buy that?
I see... Today is...
That means...
Sorry I can't buy it!
D-Don't worry.
It shouldn't break from that.
Th-They're here!
The fleet is here!
To all ships of the Halkeginia Alliance!
Ready the cannons!
Load the shells!
Yes, ma'am!
I'd like to thank you for your
cooperation, Miss Agnes.
It's a strange day,
for me to fight alongside you.
Not for our personal past,
but for the entire world's future.
Let's give it everything
we've got, Mr. Colbert!
Thank you.
If this attack succeeds, the magic
barrier should be dispelled.
And if Louise then casts her
Explosion, it will surely work.
All ships, fire!
It's working.
Round two, fire!
It stopped moving.
We did it!
It's a success!
No...
This is...
Lord Bidalsha?!
The elves?!
By combining the power of the
spirits with this fire stone,
we can create a fire barrier.
I had no idea it could be used that way.
Perhaps Joseph's rampage was
actually brought on by a greater power...
It's the Nephthys fleet!
Lord Bidalsha came,
just like he promised!
I never knew there were this many elves
who support friendship with the barbarians!
This is going to be okay, right?
How should I know?
Ask my brother Damien!
This is bad!
F-Flan!
Guiche!
It looks like this is no longer of use.
We have to go to the others.
Fireball!
Let's move!
Tiffa!
The dragon is after you and me.
We've got to get away from here.
Y-Yes!
Illococoo, can you help us?
Of course!
Thank you!
Louise, I'm on my way!
Midois Algiz Delcana Manlagun!
Thanks, Tiffa!
Of course.
My lady, shall we fire?
No.
If you attack now, you might
hit Louise and Tiffania.
The magic barrier was torn
open by the previous attacks.
If that's the case, then...
Aoren Suhn Fil Yarnsaksa...
Osu Suhn Uryn Rurin Lagon...
Windy Icicle!
Deoru Yuru Sugia...
Fly, my sword!
Ossia Jer Undil...
Valkyrie!
Hagal Beocs Fil...
Explosion!
It's still alive...
Louise!
My strength is...
A Total Eclipse Over Japan
They said that flying into
an eclipse might bring
me back to this world.
If that's true, then the
opposite must be true as well.
Tiffa!
No...
Saito, help me!
Saito!
Did Saito actually...
Saito came back?
Yahoo!
It's Halkeginia!
This is a surprise.
I never thought that'd actually work.
Yeah, I'm surprised, too.
Wait... Derf?!
Yup. Have you been well, pal?
Have I been well? Seriously?!
What's going on?
To tell you the truth, I'm not
quite sure I understand it myself.
It seems like I was sleeping in
your rune after the sword broke.
You were sleeping?
Well, it doesn't matter.
You're alive, that's all that counts.
Yup. I feel great.
Oh yeah?
Then let's get wild.
You got it.
Damn, the magic barrier is still...
Then...
Saito, why?!
Great timing, Louise!
Come over here, please.
Saito, wait!
You stupid idiot!
Ow, ow, ow!
Why did you come back here?
It took me so long to
finally make up my mind!
That hurts!
I'm sorry, Louise!
But...
I want to protect this world, too.
So let's take him down, together!
Y-Yeah.
I'm going to attack him again and
get rid of his magic barrier.
Then you cast your Explosion.
But I'm all out of power.
I'm here.
No!
If you use your Lífþrasir
power, your life is...
This is not the time for that!
No means no!
I don't want you to die!
If you die then...
I have no reason to live!
Louise, I promise you,
I'm not going to die.
You think I'd leave behind
the person I love?
I mean, I am your...
I am Zero's familiar!
Saito...
First kiss kara hajimaru  futari no koi no hisutori
Our love's history starts with the first kiss
Kono unmei ni mahou kaketa  kimi ga totsuzen arawareta
I cast a spell on this fate  then you suddenly appeared
Tsuki ga futatsu kienai sora
The sky where the two moons never disappear
I can feel it.
I can feel Saito's life force.
Arienai koto da yo ne
This is unbelievable
I'm going to do it!
Hajimete da yo konna kimochi
I have never felt like this
All cannons...
Yake ni koko ga kokochiyoku natte yuku
I'm starting to feel so at home here
Fire!
Moshi kimi ga tsumazuite ochikonde mo
Even if you stumble and get depressed
Aoren Suhn Fil Yarnsaksa...
Boku ga gyutto! Kimi wo zutto! Dakishimete ageru!
I will tightly! Hold you! Forever!
Osu Suhn Uryn Rurin Lagon...
Sweet kiss
Deoru Yuru Sugia...
Mada samenai ano hi deaeta Story
I'm still not awake  from the story of our meeting that day
Kan Ossia Jer Ihs...
Hora kimi no mahou kakete  kimi ga totsuzen arawareta
Now, cast your spell  then you suddenly appeared
Louise! Let's do this!
Undil...
Hagal Beocs Fil...
Explosion!
Yeah! They did it!
Louise... Saito...
Saito...
I'm going, too!
They're over there!
Saito... Saito!
Hey, Saito... Saito!
Wake up!
You said... You said you wouldn't die!
No...
No!
No, Saito, I won't allow this!
Please come back, Saito...
I'll do anything, anything you want!
So please, Saito!
I have to remember that.
Saito, Saito, Saito, Saito!
It looks like you used up
your Lífþrasir powers,
but your life as Gandalfr did not end.
I see. Well, whatever.
All that matters is that I'm
right here with Louise now.
So, Louise, you said you'd
do anything, remember?
Well, what I meant was...
There's something I've
wanted for a long time,
so maybe I'll have you do it right now.
What do you mean, right now?
What are you talking about?
In a place like this?!
It doesn't matter where we are.
Yes it does!
I mean...
It doesn't matter where we are,
I can't live without you.
So, Louise...
Will you marry me?
You really want to marry me?
It has to be you!
I want you, too.
I want to be with you forever.
Let's be together forever, Louise.
Louise, you're beautiful.
Don't stare so much.
I swear that I'll make you happy.
Of course you will!
I'll punish you if you don't.