So it's not in bloom yet.
I told you that it was too early.
But I really wanted to see it in bloom...
Since today's my last look at it.
Rin.
What is it?
Are you going to follow your dad's dream?
I'm not sure yet.
Hey, there's stuff written on the bricks.
For graduation, we made this garden
and wrote our favorite phrases on the bricks.
Here's mine.
I swim.
What does it say?
For the team.
"For the team."
Oh, this must be Haru-chan's.
Haru-chan!
Hurry up!
I'm coming!
What's he doing?
Oh, is that tree...
Ah...
It looks just like that tree.
Distant Free!
It's so big.
And it's packed.
Yo! There you are.
Good morning!
Morning.
Seems Rin isn't here yet.
I'm sure he'll show up soon.
Yeah.
Did something happen with
my brother yesterday?
No.
We just agreed to both do our best today.
We got seats for everyone.
Thank you!
Let's get going then.
If we win today, we make it to nationals.
Can we win?
Hey!
Don't wuss out now!
Stop worrying about the outcome!
Just be free.
Swim to your hearts' content!
Swim so you have no regrets!
Yes!
Matsuoka-senpai...
Uh...
Cheer up!
You'll get another shot at
the relay at nationals.
Our school will definitely advance!
So you should focus on
your 100 m free today
and forget about the relay—
Shut up!
Senpai...
I'm sure that
everyone here has been
practicing hard for this day.
This tournament is your opportunity to
Hey, which one is your brother?
Um, he's on Samezuka's...
show that your hard work has paid off.
Men's 100 m freestyle, heat three.
Rin-chan's up next!
Yeah.
Big brother, you can do it!
Set.
Go!
He had a late start?!
Rin can make it up on the turn!
Go! Go!
And turn!
Last spurt, last spurt, last spurt!
Rin...
What's wrong?
Last spurt, last spurt, last spurt!
What happened to Rin?
Big brother...
Haru!
I'm going with him!
Me too!
Senpai! Matsuoka-senpai!
Please wait!
It's okay!
You just happened to have a bad day.
Your talent is the real deal.
If you were in better
condition, you could have...
Shut up!
That was...
This way!
Senpai! Please calm down!
If you do that, you won't be allowed to
participate in the next tournament!
It doesn't matter!
I don't give a damn about what happens!
I'm obviously no better than this!
That's why I was taken off the relay!
Forget it! I quit!
I'm done swimming!
Matsuoka-senpai!
Gou, look at this!
This is...
Rin-chan was removed from the relay?
We thought we'd be able to race
Rin if we made it to the final.
Haru...
I'm done swimming!
I'll quit swimming.
Haru!
I won't get to swim with Rin again?
Haru...
Haru-chan...
What now?
The relay prelims are about to start.
Let's focus on our own race right now!
But look at Haru-chan.
Haru...
I have something to tell everyone.
Rei-chan?
Last night, Rin-san called me outside to talk.
He told me that when he said he wanted
to quit swimming in middle school,
it wasn't because he
lost to Haruka-senpai.
He hit a wall while training abroad
and his confidence was shaken.
That's why he wanted to quit swimming.
But after returning to Japan,
running into Haruka-senpai,
and racing him again,
he could put it behind him.
After watching us swim at prefecturals,
he remembered what it was like,
and wanted to swim in a relay again.
That's why he said
he'd swim with Samezuka to
give us the best relay ever.
I didn't realize Rin-chan felt that way.
But that's not what he really wants.
He didn't care about the race.
He just wanted to swim
with all of you again.
To swim with the best
teammates he could have...
How do you know that?
Because...
I feel the same way he does.
I want to swim in a relay
with all of you.
With the best teammates
I could ask for...
I'm sure you feel the
same way, Haruka-senpai!
The race isn't important!
There's someone you
want to swim with, right?!
I want to swim with Rin!
If you don't do something,
Rin-san will stop swimming.
You're the only ones who can help him!
But what are we supposed to do?
You still don't understand?!
Logically speaking, there's
only one possible solution!
Rei, are you really okay with that?
Of course!
No luck! Can't find them anywhere!
The medley relay swimmers are
supposed to report soon.
They'll be disqualified.
No way!
He's not here!
Let's split up and look!
Got it!
Yes!
Rin!
Rin-chan!
Rin-san!
Rin!
Rin! Where are you?!
We're running out of time!
Rin!
Maybe...
Haru...
Why are you here?
Come to laugh at my pathetic loss?
Rin...
You saw what happened in the free.
And I was taken out of the relay.
The world is laughing at me.
So join in!
No need to pity me.
I told you to laugh!
That's all I'm good for, anyway.
I'm not even good enough to
race you guys in a relay!
Calm down, Rin!
Shut up!
What would you know?!
I know!
How fun it is to swim with friends...
How good it feels to
swim in a relay together...
You were the one who taught me that, Rin!
You're the reason I...
Shut up!
I understand now!
I found the answer!
Why it is I swim!
Who I'm swimming for!
I told you to shut up!
This tree looks like
the cherry blossom tree that
was in the school yard.
Isn't that why you were here?
Why?
Why can't I be free?
I want to swim with you guys.
I want to swim in a relay with you guys.
But it's too late now.
No, it's not too late.
Let's go, Rin.
Oh, there they are.
Rin-chan!
You guys...
Honestly...
Watching you irritates me so much.
If you want to swim, go ahead.
Rin, come.
It's my turn to show you
a sight you've never seen before.
Men's medley relay, heat one.
Damn, it's already starting.
They came all this way to be disqualified?
They're here!
It looks like they made it in time.
What a relief.
Men's medley relay, heat two.
Makoto!
Makoto-senpai!
Set.
Go!
Go, go, go, go, go, Makoto!
Swim, swim, swim, swim, swim, Makoto!
This is...
Nagisa!
Wait for me! I'm coming!
They're in third place,
ahead of top schools!
Amazing!
That's a personal best!
Rei's up next.
What?!
Matsuoka-senpai?!
What's he doing?!
Rin-chan!
I told them to be free,
but they went too far.
His entry angle was five degrees
off, but I suppose it will do.
Why are you here?!
I'll explain everything later.
We need to cheer them on now.
Gou-san.
Uh-huh!
Go, go, go, go, go, Rin!
He's fast...
Matsuoka-senpai!
Haru!
Haru-chan!
Haruka-senpai!
Haru!
Haru-chan!
Haru-senpai!
Go!
Hurry!
Iwatobi
Haru!
Haru-chan! Haru-chan!
Stop crying, Nagisa.
Haru!
Haru-chan!
Hey!
Haru!
You showed me the best
sight I could've asked for!
Haru...
Yeah.
Makoto! Nagisa!
Rin!
Rin-rin!
It's been too long!
Big brother...
Rin's really fast.
I was shocked at first,
but this is touching.
I know!
You guys are truly beautiful.
Okay, and so...
After that emotional performance,
you were disqualified.
Naturally.
It wasn't easy to endure the
staff members scolding us.
They've never had someone swim in
a relay for a different school's team.
We're very sorry.
Well, it's okay.
Young people get to do crazy things.
Why did you pull that stunt?
Because...
It was only right.
Yep, we may be on different teams...
...but we're still...
...teammates.
What does that mean?
I'm very sorry!
I will take responsibility for my actions.
Please kick me off the swim team.
Matsuoka-senpai...
Nitori,
sorry for yelling at you.
You don't have to worry about that!
And anyway, we can't kick you off...
I won't accept that!
I have a better way for you
to own up to your actions.
Swim the way you just did for our team.
Captain...
Okay, boys. Let's head home.
Yes!
Hey, Nakagawa. Take the lead.
I'll be at the back.
Yes!
Nitori.
Er...
Ai.
Practice with me again starting tomorrow.
Yes, Rin-senpai!
It's over.
Will we make it back here next year?
We have to make it back.
It'll be my turn to unveil my
dazzling butterfly technique.
Right.
Don't worry.
We'll be back.
The water is alive.
Once you dive in, it will immediately
bare its fangs and attack.
But there's nothing to fear.
Don't resist the water.
Thrust your fingers into the surface
and carve an opening.
Then you slide your body
through that opening.
Moving your arms, your head, your chest...
Young Shock
Special Issue
Close-up on
Nishikujo Marin!
Bold Fold-out
Photo, P21
Matsuoka Rin
Hello, everyone.
My name is Matsuoka Rin.
I previously went to Samezuka Academy.
I have a girly name, but I'm a boy.
Looking forward to being...
Hmm, it doesn't feel quite right.
Zero points. Put more effort into it.
You used to be more...
Fresh?
Yeah, that's it!
Shut up!
You guys told me to do this!
Hey! Why are you fooling around?
Our joint training's about to start.
Big brother, stop playing around!
Fine!
Man...
Let's get going then.
It's time to avenge my previous
showing at our joint training.
I will show you my beautiful
butterfly stroke.
Strong words, Rei!
I'll show you how good Samezuka is!
Wanna have a race?
You won't beat us.
We've got our eyes set on the world.
Haru, what are you doing? Hurry up.
So you're following your dad's dream?
No, I'm not following my dad's dream.
I'm following my own dream.
What about you, Haru?
Me?
I'm...