Damn!
If you accept, please follow
General X's directions.
Help me... please.
Help...
Utsutsu?
Anyone?
Is anyone out there?!
Thank you...
That's enough!
Doing that will kill you!
I want to save them!
You know that, right?
But I want to save them!
I want to save them... save them.
Save them! Save them!
Use my life, as well.
I'm... dreamy.
Amazing, isn't it?
Can they see Gatchaman?
Are you a... Gatchaman?
Yep!
Amnesia...
Remind!
Hi!
I'm Ichinose Hajime.
Why'd you do that?
Idiot!
Why?
Is anyone there?
Are you all right!?
Why, why, why, why, why?
Why'd you do that?!
Gatchaman!
Gatchaman played
major role in rescue?
Yesterday, at approximately 1:00 PM,
a ceiling panel collapsed in Kanishiro
Tunnel on the Joufuku Expressway,
Really?
trapping dozens of cars inside
in what became a major accident.
However, those present on-site used
Did you know
a Gatchaman played
a big part in yesterday's
tunnel collapse?
information provided
by the social network service
What?! Really?
GALAX to conduct a speedy
rescue operation.
Gatchaman's cute.
I saw the Gatchaman.
It was a girl.
Miraculously, there were no casualties.
It wasn't some cosplay?
Aren't Gatchaman an urban legend?
During the rescue efforts,
a strangely-dressed girl was caught
Wow! Gatchaman.
Why don't we let Gatchaman
on a security camera inside the tunnel.
handle politics and stuff?
Why don't we let Gatchaman...
Mayor of Tachikawa Shimizu Shouhei
Huh? This is...
It is causing wild speculation that
Hajime?!
she may be a Gatchaman,
a figure who was thought
to exist only in fiction.
We now have confirmation
that Gatchaman exist.
What will you do?
Of course, I'll take
advantage of them...
to update the world.
Why does she break
the Gatchaman rules so easily?
What's more, why aren't I
chewing her out for it?
What have you done, Newbie?!
Not only did you transform
without permission,
you exposed your true face!
Unacceptable!
Inconceivable!
Unprecedented!
Messed up!
A big problem!
It's a big problem?
O-O-O-Of course!
In any military organization,
divulging information is a capital offense!
Aiding the enemy!
A Class S war criminal!
JJ-sama!
Please judge her!
However, for my sake,
please spare her life.
Please! Please, I beg of you!
Oh, no response.
Impossible!
JJ-sama!
How can there be no summons,
given this crisis?
Will you not even offer
any words to us?
Without this one's punishment,
the team will lose discipline!
JJ-sama!
Then why don't you decide, Pai-Pai?
You're the leader.
Um... Well...
I can hardly take it upon
myself to deliver judgment
on such an important issue.
Indeed, it would not do
to make a rash or hasty decision.
That's right.
Hey, Jou!
Where are you going?!
Now that it's come to this,
we should keep a low profile
for the time being until
the heat dies down, right?
I'll go wait it out at the apartment.
The apartment?
Oh, yes!
Let's go on hiatus for a while!
Don't take any action
for the foreseeable future!
There haven't been
any MESS sightings, anyway!
That must be what the lack
of response from JJ-sama means, too!
That's right!
All right. Dismissed!
You rarely come back
to this apartment.
So your coming here means
there's equipment you need.
You were lying when you said
you won't do anything.
I can now focus on finding
that joking Gatcha bastard.
Want to come along?
Well, I...
I see.
You're worried about that girl, too.
No, that's not the reason!
Well, good luck.
I said that's not it!
Utsutsu-chan, you were
out of it the whole time.
Are you okay?
Yesterday, someone I helped said...
"Thank you."
Wow!
That's great!
But...
I feel dreamy...
I see. I see.
Squeeze!
Cut, cut, cut...
Snip, snip, snip... snip!
There!
Here!
A present to Utsutsu-chan
for a good deed!
What?
Perfect!
Right, right?
Wow!
Ultra cute!
Oh, it's from the Papyrus store owner.
Senpai, why are you coming along?
To keep an eye on you.
Who knows what you'll do
next if I leave you alone?
Oh, sounds tough.
Wow!
There's a fireworks festival today!
Utsutsu-chan, let's go see!
Hey.
Yeah?
Why'd you show your face
to an outsider yesterday
at the accident site?
Oh, well, isn't it obvious?
I told you, right?
That you must never reveal
your Gatchaman identity?
Well, it was because I wanted
to talk face-to-face.
Just for that?!
What are you talking about?
It's super important!
You didn't need to do it right
then and there, though, did you?
But I did need to.
So, it wasn't a whim?
You were aware
of what you were doing?
Yeah.
A whim?
I'm not that irresponsible.
I see...
I've been waiting forever
for this new release!
The handling feels great!
The edge is awesome, too!
Scissors? At a time like this?
Hajime-chan, you should run.
Huh? Why?
Oh, there she is!
Are you Ichinose Hajime-san?
Yeah, that's me.
You're the Gatchaman
who appeared at the
scene of the accident yesterday
when the Kanishiro Tunnel
collapsed onto the Joufuku
Expressway, right?
Yeah, th—
Achoo!
It's a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding...
Oh, are you Ichinose-san's boyfriend?
What?!
What's it like to have
a Gatchaman girlfriend?
Are you people
also Gatchaman, too?
Please transform for us!
X.
Yes?
Summon the GALAXters for a game.
We seek everyday knights who wield
a weapon stronger than the sword
to rescue a princess
in a certain predicament
from scoundrels who've
forgotten the meaning of chivalry
and help guide her to LOAD!
Those who give aid shall be
astonished by the princess!
The only reward is honor!
Come to the Round Table!
Join    Close
Don't get a big head
from all the attention.
Forget Gatchaman!
You're pissing me off!
Run!
I'll hold them back!
Oh, you're cool, Senpai.
Just go!
Okay!
Utsutsu-chan, let's go!
Yeah!
Huh?
I think we can run away as soon
as we use the Amnesia Effect.
Oh, right!
But this is kind of fun,
like playing hide-and-seek.
Oh, it's from GALAX!
Invitation
Greetings.
My name is LOAD GALAX.
There are still many reporters
wandering around in your vicinity.
Being found will be
an inconvenience.
If you would accept my invitation,
I could let you escape
without being caught.
If you accept, please follow
General X's directions.
Smells fishy...
What?
I accept.
Acknowledged.
Ichinose Hajime-sama,
in 15 seconds,
please exit to the corridor
and head right toward the stairs.
Fun!
4, 3, 2, 1!
Let's go!
Hey, there she is!
We got caught.
Please keep walking.
Really!?
Can you tell us a bit more?
Come on, Hajime-san!
I'm dreamy...
So do you finally feel like
giving a proper interview...
Wh—
Ah, so you are the princess.
This is, indeed, surprising.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for protecting
us all this time,
dear Gatchaman princess.
I am honored to meet you.
I am a knight who has received
instruction from LOAD.
A princess?
Ah, this way, please.
Please wait for four seconds.
Okay!
2, 1...!
Oh, you're the princess?
We've been had!
I'm not a princess.
I'm Hajime!
Please get on.
I entrust the rest
to you, young knight.
You can count on me!
So fun!
Look!
They're going up!
Oh, those pearls are wonderful.
Hanadama pearls, no?
You're right!
Yes, indeed.
There she is!
Okay!
Please head toward the North Exit.
Roger!
Oops!
Please head straight
toward the North Exit.
Impossible...
So fun!
What?
Amazing!
Where'd they go?
Invitation
An invitation?
See you!
LOAD GALAX is waiting
for you in this building.
Oh!
They're the bat guys
who came to Papyrus!
This way, please.
Reserved All Day
Oh, you're the one I saw yesterday!
How was your journey here?
Yeah, it was super fun!
It's like everyone was playing a game.
The people who helped us all looked
like they were having fun!
That's the world to come, the world
I'm trying to create through GALAX.
What?
You're the one behind GALAX?
Yeah.
Thank you for accepting
my invitation, Gatchaman.
Or, rather, Ichinose
Hajime-kun and your friend.
I am LOAD GALAX.
So it's here...
Amnesia Effect.
Go, Bird!
Don't glare at me like that.
I am not your enemy.
Well, just telling you
is kind of boring.
Oh, I know.
As a token of my friendship,
I'll start by erasing all of the info
about Ichinose Hajime-kun
that's now circulating online.
I don't really need that.
Why?
Because I don't really care.
You really are different.
Interesting.
You seem interesting,
too, LOAD-kun!
Thank you...
The last guest
seems to have arrived.
So they can see us!
I invited you all here because
I wanted to talk with you.
Talk?
With GALAX, I'm trying
to create a world like
what you just experienced.
An ideal world where people
are matched to the situation
by their skills and act based
on internal, positive motives—
that's the world I want
to update this one to.
Wow!
GALAX is pretty amazing, for sure!
Lately, everyone's been solving many
incidents and accidents together.
It was a huge help yesterday, too!
GALAX is great.
Will you stop
being Gatchaman, then?
Gatchaman aren't necessary
in the world to come.
What?!
Oh, Senpai.
"Gatchaman aren't necessary"!?
That's right.
They're more of a hindrance.
Those who were given power
protecting the weak—
what part of that
is a "hindrance"?
When there are those
with special powers,
people come to rely on them.
That will not help
raise their awareness.
You can see this, just by
observing this distorted world.
The world has become
too large and complicated
for the minority
with power to support.
I don't know how many
of you there are,
but how many people can you
claim to be capable of supporting?
But that doesn't mean—
The world we're aiming
for through GALAX
can support even those who
fall through your cracks.
What the world needs from now
on aren't stand-out heroes,
but the entire human race
turned into heroes.
Do you understand now?
The world will be updated very soon.
If you really want to save the world,
stop being Gatchaman and
act as GALAXters...
Oh, this?
Isn't it cute?
It's my current favorite!
That is all I wanted to say.
Will you stop being Gatchaman?
I understand what you're saying.
But, I don't think
Gatchaman are unnecessary—
I won't stop.
Why?
Were all the sparkly things
at the accident site yesterday
your friends, LOAD-kun?
What are you talking about?
LOAD-kun, you're prettier
without makeup.
You're so pretty.
It's such a shame.
I think you can
become even prettier!
I'm sure of it!
Go on ahead.
When we were talking to LOAD,
I hadn't deactivated
the Amnesia Effect.
But they could still see me.
In addition, they reacted
when they saw your NOTE.
They seemed to be playing dumb
about yesterday's accident, too.
It's far more than suspicious.
There's definitely
something more to that guy!
Of course there is.
The heavy makeup was
a bit of a disappointment.
But... there might be
a reason for that, too.
I still don't get you, you know.
Really?
I'm the type who has to be sure.
No makeup, huh...
What an amazing girl.