A tall, tall wall looms in front of me.
What's the view on the other side?
What does it look like?
The view from the top...
it's a view I could never see on my own.
But if I'm not doing it alone...
Let's play.
Haikyu!!
Episode 1: The End & The Beginning
All right.
Yukigaoka Electric
Congrats
Karasuno
High
School
Score.
The "little giant"
lives up to his name.
That's five points in a row.
Here we are at the National
High School Volleyball Championship,
spring season, where Karasuno
High School's little giant
has been springing up and down
among players 190 centimeters tall.
Karasuno, is that the school
in our neighboring town?
Pretty impressive.
Sho-chan, hurry. They'll take the court.
Karasuno...
Approximately 3 years and 3 months later
Sho-chan wait up.
It's huge.
The smell of Air Salonpas!
Sho-chan, you're too nervous.
They'll think you're a country hick.
B-But I've never been in
a real tournament before.
Three years later and I'm finally here.
It's sure been a struggle to get here.
Izumi, Koji,
thanks for being here for moral support.
Stop it.
Our tournament's already finished, so...
First-year students, you too, thanks!
It's a miracle the
three of you are here.
Oh, yes.
We're total amateurs, but...
Don't cry, Shoyo.
I'm not crying.
You're super tearful.
U-Um, Hinata-senpai,
we should get started.
Come on, Captain. Get on the ball.
That's right.
You dragged us here.
We don't even know the rules.
I know that.
We made it all the way to the
tournament, we have to win.
National Junior High Team Sports     Miyagi Prefecture Volleyball Tournament <Men>
Combinations
Championship
What?
You think we can win with
our last-minute team pick?
Of course.
What's our opponent
Kitagawa Daiichi like?
I don't know.
But we're going to do it.
Whoops, sorry! Come on.
They're huge.
What the...
Victory
Kitagawa Daiichi Junior High School
Kita-Ichi!
It's Kitagawa Daiichi.
They're huge.
They're so intimidating.
They're candidates to win.
The "king" is among them.
Who's that?
Don't you know?
It's Kageyama Tobio.
They call him the "King of the Court".
He's an amazing setter.
We're playing against those guys?
What's this "king" stuff?
Don't worry about it!
Who cares how lanky they are?!
I'll shoot past them.
That's right, Sho-chan's
jump is amazing.
We're counting on you!
But first, the bathroom...
I never even heard of
Yukigaoka Junior High.
They're small in number it seems.
They don't even have a libero.
They're the height of
elementary school kids.
They're no match for us.
Hey, dudes.
Don't underestimate us.
Soon as my stomach settles,
I'll teach you guys a lesson,
so be ready.
Is this guy serious?
Yes, sir. We'll be ready!
Elementary school.
He's got the captain label on him.
Making fun of me...
Hey, second-year.
It's time for the official warm-up.
Hurry it up.
I'm sorry, right away.
Bad news, it's Kageyama-senpai.
Hurry up, two more energy drinks!
We don't need to drink that much.
Just look at our opponent.
That's for sure.
What did you say?
You guys.
You're not even on the bench.
You think you're good enough
to look down on your opponent?
Don't ride the coattails of
your school's reputation.
S-Sorry!
Scary...
I was going to tell them
a thing or two myself, too.
You're not even physically ready.
Don't talk big.
That's why they look down on you.
What did you say?
What are you doing here, anyway?
Making memories?
I came here to win. Nothing else.
You make it sound so easy.
Sure, I'm not tall.
But...
I can jump.
You can't assume we'll lose,
as long as we don't give up—
"Don't give up."
That's not as easy as it sounds.
The six of us...
the six of us can finally
play volleyball on the court.
The first game, second game...
We'll win and keep winning.
We're going to give it our all!
The first game, second game,
the playoffs, the nationals...
I'm going to win them all.
Sho-chan.
Izumi.
Why are you making that scary guy mad?
Weren't you going to the bathroom?
Let's get back, hurry.
How's your stomach ache?
It's all gone.
Huh?
Crap. He's good for real.
He's a setter.
That's him, the so-called "King
of the Court," Kageyama Tobio.
By the way, what's a "setter"?
That's the offensive position
that tosses the ball.
Setter
We studied it, remember?
We did?
Your timing is slow.
"Come in faster for the
quick," I told you.
My bad.
Kageyama, don't focus on speed alone.
What matters is not your own skills,
it's how you let the
spiker hit the ball.
I know that.
This is it.
It's finally about to start.
Let's play.
Our opponents sure are short.
Koji.
Your back number. Show your back number.
Huh?
Koji.
Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Nice serve.
Kitagawa Daiichi   Yukigaoka
Oh man, they probably
won't score a point.
Fine by me.
It'll be over quicker.
That's a fact.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
Let's do better next round.
Uh... yeah.
We finally got here.
We won't let it end so easy.
What?
I'm the only club member?
Yeah.
The club members got less
and less every year.
Plus, boys' volleyball
isn't a club activity.
It's just a fan club.
Oh...
What do you want to do?
Change to another club?
Or do you want to join the girls' team?
Well, no...
I'll be a one-man team then.
Is that right?
I'm going to be the little giant.
You're going to be the what?
Nice serve.
Here...
Gather round!
Let's go for a run.
Okay.
My chance.
Izumin!
You're taking a break right?
Toss for me.
"Toss"?
I want to spike the ball.
I can't. I don't know how.
You just toss it up.
That's all you have to do.
I can't. Senpai's watching.
Gather up.
Right!
Hey, Hinata.
I heard you're on the
girls' volleyball team.
Are you serious?
N-No, I'm not.
Who are you after?
There's a foxy third-year senpai.
There is a foxy senpai, but...
I knew it.
You got it wrong.
I'm the boys' volleyball team.
Victory
Kitagawa Daiichi Junior High School
You can't even enter a tournament.
What drives you to practice?
I'll enter a tournament. Eventually.
I'll get a team together,
though I'm striking out for now.
But I will, you'll see.
How about you, Koji?
How many times must I turn you down?
Hey, Izumin!
Can you spare just a little time?
I have after-school class today, sorry.
Kitagawa Daiichi   Yukigaoka
I'm sorry.
Lucky. Lucky.
Watch out!
Shoyo, are you all right?
Ouch...
My bad.
Toss for me then.
I got it this time...
Koji.
Izumin.
Hey, haven't you had enough?
My arms hurt.
I can't shoot the ball accurately.
I've had it.
Please. Just one more.
First-year students agreed to join me.
You keep saying "one more."
This is the last one, okay?
Got it.
Here goes.
Oh, sorry.
Go, Sho-chan!
Sure, I'm little,
but my legs can jump...
over any wall.
All right!
Sho-chan, don't worry about it.
We'll toss it for you again.
S-Sorry.
That was a good toss, too...
I'll get it in next time.
Haikyu!!
++Yukigaoka   Kitagawa Daiichi
Wow, that number 5 is a powerhouse.
Yukigaoka is sneaking a few
points in, in the second set.
Thanks to their opponent's misses.
It's up.
Sho-chan.
This is bad...
I can't see the other side at all.
The opponents are totally
seeing through their plays.
Shame. That guy's got
amazing jumping power.
Shoyo, let's do this.
Sho-chan, don't worry.
Close call.
Faster!
Nice.
Reckless tosses today, as usual.
I know. The opponents can't
even block; what's the point?
What's he so serious about?
When will you guys get serious then?
Stop it. We're in a game.
++Yukigaoka   Kitagawa Daiichi
Scary.
Kita-Ichi's setter is good,
but it's like he's playing
out there all by himself.
All right.
Service ace again.
Not yet.
He won't get that.
It hasn't dropped yet.
Not yet.
Sho-chan!
Wow. Looks painful.
He's trying hard.
++Yukigaoka   Kitagawa Daiichi
One more point and it's
curtains for Yukigaoka.
Yeah.
Damn it...
Excuse me, um... I...
Sorry. I'll get the next one.
Um!
We don't want to get injured.
We're out of their
league to begin with...
One more, same way.
Why must you do this?
Um... what?
Huh?
I don't know what you mean.
But...
we haven't lost yet.
That's right. It's simple.
No matter how challenging the volley,
there's only one reason
we chase the ball.
Koji.
The ball hasn't hit the court yet.
Sho-chan.
There's only one reason
we continue fighting.
Because we haven't lost yet.
One touch!
You touched it!
Cover it!
I can't do this...
Score.
--Yukigaoka   Kitagawa Daiichi
Don't give up on the ball!
M-My bad.
We haven't won yet.
You can't let down your guard.
I know, but look at the points.
Not unless a miracle happens...
That last point was no miracle.
He scored a genuine point.
That guy. He scored a genuine point.
Well, sure, but...
As long as we don't give up...
It's in the net!
It's dropping, forward, forward!
All right, Sho-chan,
we're counting on you.
Toss miss?
There was no double hit.
But there was no one there...
We should've been on the left.
We had it marked.
So why...
why is he here?
Sho-chan!
You there, are you all right?
O-Out?
++Yukigaoka   Kitagawa Daiichi
Sho-chan, are you hurt?
This guy overwhelms me.
We scored only because
their setter missed.
He knew there was no back set,
yet he still hit the ball?
He was able to handle that toss?
Sho-chan. We have to line up.
High level of physical
agility and reflexes.
Hey, Kageyama.
What are you doing? Get in line!
Finely tuned bodily control
and his obsession with victory.
He's got it all.
What were you doing
for the last three years?
What did he say?
Stay out of it.
What do you know about what
he did the last three years?
What's the point of
telling him about that?
Yeah, but...
My first and last official match of junior high...
Boys, hurry up and get in line.
Sho-chan, let's line up.
++Yukigaoka   Kitagawa Daiichi
Our sets: zero.
Total game time: only 31 minutes.
"King of the Court," huh...
He's going to be a difficult opponent
when he starts high school.
My money's on that little guy.
Karasuno High
Volleyball Club
What did you expect?
They're candidates for the nationals.
Man, I'm hungry.
You're always hungry.
It doesn't matter if
they're strong or weak,
the bottom line is whether
we win or lose,
and if we lose, we're
off the court for good.
Sho-chan.
Shoyo?
You...
If you're the king that
rules the court,
I'll have to defeat you,
and I'll be the last one standing!
The last ones standing are the victors.
Only the strongest.
If you want to be the last
one standing, become strong.
What I'm lacking...
Thank you for today.
D-Dumbass.
You don't have to thank us.
Huh? Why are you crying Koji?
I'm not crying.
Men's Volleyball Prefectural Tournament
Kitagawa Daiichi
Bitterly Defeated
See ya, Shoyo.
Take care, Sho-chan.
30-minute bike ride over the mountain.
Starting today, Miyagi Prefectural
Karasuno High School.
Wanna join the soccer club?
Wanna get managed by the baseball club?
Here, the club applicants list.
Thank you.
So few... we used to have a lot more.
It'll grow, Daichi.
Kiyoko-san, looking
pretty today as usual.
She turns me on when she ignores me.
I'm here. I'm here at Karasuno.
I'm going to train a lot.
And then, against that "king"...
I'll get my revenge!
Wh-Why are you here?!
Ow.
Next Episode Preview
What is the "King of
the Court" doing here?
Or was that somebody else?
Just a doppelgänger?
Was there a guy who looks just like him,
who happened to be in the
gym, hitting a serve?
Of course not!
Episode 2: Karasuno High School Volleyball Club
Next episode of Haikyu!!
"Karasuno High School Volleyball Club"