Tatara Nishi High School
Tamaki Mari-san and Kobuchizawa
Shirase-san will be embarking
on a trip to Antarctica next month.
Please come forward.
Um...
It's still a little hard to
believe this is happening,
but I'll do my best where I'm going!
I'm going.
You shouldn't have waited so long.
But...
I get it, I get it.
It made me happy.
You're very smart, Megumi-chan.
I felt like I had become a big sister.
Mari-chan.
We can play together tomorrow, too.
1 Like
1 Comment
#100kgAllTogether  #GirlsTea #TheMadness
This is the new Antarctic Icebreaker ship,
modified from the Shirase II,
the Shichishinya Penguin Manju!
Its basic performance hasn't changed,
but there have been some
internal modifications,
and as you can see, it's had
a big external makeover!
"Let's go inside!"
...is what I'd like to tell you!
But the truth is, we won't get to
board it until we reach Australia.
So, let's make the jump
to Australia right now!
One, two...
Jump!
Okay! That's a wrap!
What a total pro!
You're amazing!
You don't have to make fun of me.
We're not! We're not!
We genuinely respect you.
By comparison, our next report's
not until we reach Australia,
but look at her freaking out already.
I-I'm here in Autsralia. Wait! I mean...
I have to jump first...
then land.
Wait, no!
Land, then jump?
Land?
Land means...
Shirase-san, calm down.
What am I gonna do?!
I can't land in Australia!
They can work it out in editing.
For now, just do your vocal warm-ups.
Have you been doing your warm-ups?
She sells seashells on the sea floor.
Not quite right, but close enough.
Why would a person sell seashells?
Please don't try to dissect it.
What happened to her?
She spoke just fine at morning assembly...
Because there's no one she
sees as an enemy here.
When someone she's hostile
to is around, it's like
the "screw you!" switch gets flipped "on."
Ah, I see.
You! You're talking about me, aren't you?
We're really getting on this thing, huh?
Yeah.
Have you finished packing?
Not yet. There's a lot to
think about, isn't there?
Is there?
Including our body weight,
we're allowed 100 kilograms all together.
It should be more than enough.
Yeah, but we're staying
for three months, right?
Yeah! That's over 90 changes of clothes!
Do laundry occasionally.
Oh, right!
Although it's a journey, once we arrive,
we'll just be living life like normal.
And there'll be lots of work to do,
so they say it'll pass quickly...
But when you start thinking and
packing things into the boxes,
it does end up being quite a lot...
Is it that much?
Hey, have you not even gotten started?
But it just needs to be less than
100 kilograms, including body weight, right?
For me, that's 50, 52, 53...
I can take upwards of
58 kilograms of luggage!
That's easy, no problem!
Underestimating your weight
is a serious crime.
Fifty-eight kilograms?
That means you weigh 42 kilograms?
Please leave my arm flab alone...
This might be harder than I thought...
Mari-chan, how many times do I have to
tell you to carry up your own laundry?
Mari-chan...
What's all this?
I don't think you'll need cooking supplies.
You think? It's diamond-coated!
Nothing sticks to that!
And this?
An inner tube!
An English-Japanese dictionary!
Junior Ace
English-Japanese Dictionary
Japanese-English Dictionary
A Japanese-English dictionary.
Conversational English
for Travel.
Conversational English for Travel.
A peeler.
Conversational Chinese for Travel.
Conversational Chinese
for Travel.
The Reliable World Travel Guide.
The Reliable
World Travel Guide
I bought them all just for this trip!
You'll be with tons of people
who can speak foreign languages!
I know, but still...
That should do it, I think.
So little!
You should consult with Shirase-san, too.
There might be some specific
things you'll need.
But do you really think this'll be enough?
I'll be gone for over three months.
Sis... are you sure you can handle this?
It's just...
Comprehensive
Summer Training Documents
It's not like that pamphlets
tell us what to bring...
Because it's an adult thing.
You need to be responsible.
Responsible, huh?
Adulting is hard, huh?
Pen-Pen
This thing!
Oh, what's up?
It's...
Ta-da!
What's that?
Look! It's your game!
The one I thought I'd lost!
Wow, I'd totally forgotten about that.
You don't actually have to test it, you know.
But I haven't seen it in so long!
After three years, it might not even work.
Wow, this takes me back!
You sure loved this thing, huh?
Yeah!
After all, it's the only
game I ever beat you at.
Is it?
You couldn't beat me at all,
so you said you'd lend it to
me as long as I wanted it.
And then...
You lost it?
Eventually, yeah...
But I did beat it before then!
Yay!
I lose~
I win!
So, how'd things go in Tokyo?
Pretty well, for the most part.
Did Antarctica manage to
get through her report?
Antarctica? Oh, Shirase-chan?
Shirase-chan doesn't have
to report for a while yet.
She's pretty weird, huh?
Seriously!
She swings between super-confident
and super-timid.
I was talking to Hinata-chan about that...
Is that the girl from your job?
Yeah.
But Yuzuki-chan did the
report perfectly, so...
Is that the girl from Hokkaido?
Yeah.
Well, don't push yourself too hard.
If you fail, you'll just
regret it all the more.
Sure!
Good point...
Oh.
Sorry.
I'm back!
Challenge for Antarctic...
A Place Further Than
the Universe
Kobuchizawa Takako
Yuri-chan
Aina
Delete
Challenge for Antarctic
Okay!
Tatara Nishi High School
Good luck in Antarctica!
See you later!
Bring me an iceberg, okay?
I'm not sure it'll fit...
I'll send you pictures of warm things.
Thanks.
Does your snot freeze in Antarctica?
I wanna have some shaved ice.
Is it true there's a UFO
buried in the ice there?
Feels like I'm changing
schools or something, huh?
Goodbye, pudding shakes!
I won't be seeing you for a while...
What kind of reception did you expect?
I just didn't think they'd
make such a big deal over it!
When Shirase-chan said she
was going to Antarctica,
everyone just made fun of her.
Because they didn't think
she'd make it, I guess.
Besides, some people still make fun of her.
Oh, that's right!
I won't be able to come here
for three months, either.
Feeling lonely?
No...
I just wasn't sure how I'd feel...
You know, maybe it's best
not to show off so much.
A lot of people think you're
getting full of yourself.
I'm not showing off anything.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Well, that's true...
It's just, they're saying
some awful things about you.
Really?
Out of jealousy, I guess.
That you shoplifted from convenience
stores to raise money.
That you were messing around with
boys in Kabukicho and stuff.
Wait, what?
Girls'
Strawberry Tea
I'm telling you, people think
you're full of yourself.
But I'm not!
You know...
What?
Are you sure you should just
leave with this unresolved?
Once you're back,
it's only going to get worse...
Kimari.
Would this be Megu-chan, by chance?
Yeah!
That's right, you guys haven't met yet...
I'm Miyake Hinata, Kimari's co-worker!
What's up?
Hello.
I'd better go.
Wait!
What?
That stuff you said before...
Who's saying that?!
I don't know, I just heard it...
I'll search out the culprit!
Shirase-chan...
Remember, we're heading out tomorrow.
I can't just sit back while someone
spreads those ridiculous rumors!
Starting a fight now won't help anybody.
You've ignored all the
nasty rumors so far, right?
Just let it go.
This isn't the same thing!
These are bald-faced lies!
To claim we've been messing
around with boys in Shinjuku...
We did go to Shinjuku, though.
But we weren't messing around!
Can you prove that, though?
Still, it's just wrong!
Megu-chan, what do you think?
Me?
Sometimes, people are just mean.
Don't fight mean with mean.
Hold your head high.
Is that a quote?
You bet!
Besides, you're not alone right now.
What do you mean?
I mean you have people to vent with!
Cheers!
Rest Station
Udon   Soba
That hits the spot!
I see!
This must be what it feels to grab
a drink on the way back from work.
I suppose it might.
Okay, let's have one more!
It's payday, so the old man'll cover it.
Still, it's extremely exasperating.
You sure hate to let things go, don't you?
Well, the people spreading the
rumors are the ones in the wrong.
Why should I yield to them?
I get it, I get it.
Calm down.
I just want to scream at the top of my lungs!
Scream, then!
Next to a temple? Not a great idea...
Then let's go to karaoke!
If we do it within the hour,
we're probably good.
I've never been to karaoke.
No way!
Then let's do it!
No, no way!
How can you all do something so embarrassing?
It's okay to get it all out.
It's our going-away party!
Right?
I suppose...
You're invited, too, Megu-chan!
But...
You're invited.
Karaoke Parlor
Tanuki-Neko
Let's raise the roof!
Kobuchizawa Shirase!
No.
Oh, come on!
Then... Takahashi Megu-chan!
My friend, Megu-chan!
Let's raise the roof!
Kobuchizawa Shirase!
The Madness of Shirase
I'm so glad I wasn't there.
I'm so refreshed!
Are you?
Yeah, tonight's been the best!
I never thought I'd get to do this
stuff the night before I left.
I mean, I haven't gotten
to hang out with you much
since I decided to go to Antarctica.
Though I guess that was a relief to you...
I wouldn't say that...
Well, maybe it was.
Right?
But it wasn't like that for me at all.
I've been thinking this whole time...
About how I want to go far away,
about how I hate being where I am,
about how I hate myself.
I never knew why I felt that way.
It was probably because of you, Megu-chan.
I'm always uncertain,
needing you to fuss over me.
Always clinging to you,
asking what I should do...
Are you?
Yeah, and I always hated that.
I think I wanted to change it.
So I wouldn't just be clinging to you;
I wouldn't be worthless.
I'd be someone you could
play video games with.
So I'm gonna do my best out there.
Okay, see you later.
I'm home!
Wow, what's all this? Amazing!
You're late!
A special treat.
That's it!
But wait, there's more!
Yes! Egg Paradise!
Come and eat?
Oh...
Okay!
See you later.
See you later. See you later.
I'm in
I'm out
See you later.
You're heading out?
Yeah.
Make sure you get breakfast in Tokyo, okay?
Sis!
Rin...
Why didn't you wake me up?
Well, it was so early...
I'm worried!
Don't worry. I'll keep myself safe.
See you later!
Megu-chan?
Sorry to bother you right before you set out.
What's up?
I came to break up.
I'm saying, we're not friends anymore.
What? What do you mean?
You still haven't realized it?
Where do you think the rumor about you and
Antarctica going to Shinjuku came from?
Did you tell anyone about it?
No...
The first time you met Antarctica,
how did those older girls
know she had a million yen?
How did your mother know you were going
to Antarctica before you told her?
How?
Because I told them, of course!
I thought you'd finally catch
on and get mad at me...
eventually...
Why?
But you and Antarctica and the others
are such morons you didn't catch on!
Why?!
I don't know!
I don't know why I got so
mad when you first told me
you were going to Antarctica!
You always consulted with me
before you did anything...
No way... Wait a minute...
I know I've put you through a lot.
I apologize.
I'm sorry.
Yesterday, when you were
talking, I finally realized.
You weren't the one hanging on, I was.
Having you rely on me, consult with
me... me getting exasperated with you,
pretending to mother you,
acting so smart around you...
Because if I didn't have that,
I didn't have anything.
Civilian Icebreaker Ship Leaves
Port for First Time in Three Years
And because I wasn't anything,
I didn't want you to have anything.
You're not the one who was worthless.
I am!
I'm the one who needs to go
somewhere that isn't here!
So long.
Megu-chan!
Come with me.
Where?
To Antarctica!
Don't be stupid.
I'm finally taking my first step
into a world without you.
New Message
To: Mom
We're taking our first step.
To a world without any of the
things we usually rely on.
To a world where we don't know
what lies around the corner.
Where we don't even know which way home is.
To a world where we don't
know where we'll be tomorrow.
Where we can't even imagine where
we'll be headed the next day.
Yet we're taking that step.
Breakup rejected.
Water collects into stagnant pools.
I've always loved watching
it spill out all at once.
Breaking free, liberated, rushing out.
The energy stored up during
its stagnation bursts forth.
Everything springs into action!