The other team chose to
receive the ball first.
We'll be serving first.
All right.
It's finally the qualifiers.
Everyone looks more nervous than usual.
Fly
Especially the third-years...
Those are so awesome!
Your new glasses look so cool, Tsukishima!
You've been saying that
nearly every day, Hinata.
Having you say they're cool shakes my
self-confidence, so I wish you'd stop.
What'd you say?!
Ta-da! Here you go.
They're sports glasses.
I made sure to find cool-looking ones.
With those on, blocking with
your face isn't scary at all!
Uh, yes it is.
I don't care if it's Ushiwaka
or Benkei... Go stop 'em.
What's up with the first-years
putting on braver faces than us?
The third-years can't just
sit here cowering, either.
All right!
Matches are super fun, aren't they?
Fly
Karasuno High School
Boys' Volleyball Team
Simplicity and Fortitude
Johzenji Parents' Association
Let's play!
Haikyu!!
Episode 15: "Place to Play"
Johzenji! Johzenji! Johzenji!
We're finally at the qualifiers.
Our first opponent was a semifinalist
at the Inter-High prelims.
We've got our work cut out for us.
You better go all out on
that first one, Azumane!
Karasuno, fight!
Yeah!
Asahi-san, nice serve!
Make sure you guys get that ball!
Whoa, that was intense.
Smiling and Having Fun
Winning and Having Fun
Nice cover!
Get the last, Terushima!
Chance ball!
Yahoo!
Nice hit!
A hit like that from the end line?
Not to mention, while he was turning around?
That would usually be returned
with an underhand hit.
Karasuno                Johzenji
Nice serve!
Got it!
Left!
Simplicity and Fortitude
Johzenji Parents' Association
Heave ho! Heave ho!
It feels like...
...we're playing against some super-talented
baseball team in gym class.
Yeah... Their plays aren't
exactly cookie-cutter,
so we can't seem to read
what they're gonna do.
So, the question is whether they're
doing that on purpose or not.
Unpredictability is normal for Johzenji,
and that's their weapon.
One more!
Come on, now!
Sorry!
Don't mind! Don't mind!
Pick up the ball, and hit it back!
Jeez... They get out of hand so quickly.
You're the only third-year left.
Those guys must be a handful.
Tsukishima, nice serve!
A quick!
This shouldn't be a surprise, but
I guess they can attack normally, too.
Karasuno
Lucky! It got over the net.
Damn it!
Nice reaction!
But I don't know if they'll
be able to connect.
Nice, Hinata!
Whoa, he jumped!
L-Look out!
H-He's Spider-Man!
In the back!
He managed to return it!
We also have some guys on our team
who are skilled and unpredictable.
Yeah!
Well, that was definitely surprising,
but Karasuno hasn't even done
their ridiculous attack yet.
Go! Killer serve!
Regardless of how the receive looks,
as long as it goes up, they
can do whatever they need to.
That's what they all think, and
that's what they're able to do.
Damn it!
One more! Hit it direct, Numajiri!
All right!
Karasuno hasn't gotten
one actual attack in yet.
Daichi-san, nice receive!
There it is!
#10's super quick!
Hey, Kageyama! We can't just sit here losing.
So that was the quick I heard about. So cool!
Ow!
Their moves are hard to read,
but it's not like the ball's gonna disappear.
Let's just calm down and keep going.
Yeah!
Well done.
Karasuno                       Johzenji
#10! #10!
All right!
Johzenji's so unrefined about everything.
Their blockers just keep jumping,
and they fall for feints a lot.
And yet I wonder what makes them
so persistent and hard to play against.
I have a friend on the
Johzenji basketball team.
Really?
Apparently their volleyball
team mostly practices
with two-on-two games.
Two-on-two games?
That's rough!
They're used to that,
so they don't really feel like
anyone will get the ball for them,
and all of them are constantly
trying to attack.
Cover!
Leave it to me!
You idiots! Be willing to
give up the ball a little!
And that's probably why that happens...
They're all annoying.
People from other schools think
you guys are annoying, too.
Huh?!
Tanaka-san!
Whoa!
Nice, Jiri!
Right now, Johzenji has two attackers
up front, not counting their setter.
Other than that, there's
a chance of a back attack.
Let me hit, too!
He's the setter, isn't he?
Who's going to set?
The guy on the back line is going to set?
What?!
Simplicity and Fortitude
Johzenji Parents' Association
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
Karasuno                        Johzenji
Despite everything, I must say
their volleyball is fun to watch.
I can't argue with that.
But in regards to freewheeling attacks,
we're not so bad ourselves.
Let's have some fun and play.
They go all out and play around.
In a match...
Huh?
In order to fully enjoy a match,
you need strength.
Apparently, the former
Coach Ukai said that a lot.
I didn't really know what he
meant about enjoying it, but...
All right!
Watching Johzenji, I think it
might be something like this.
The strength... to enjoy.
Nice receive!
It might because they're
playing against Karasuno,
but they're playing around more than usual.
Yes. They really do play a good
game when they get into it.
Sorry! Sorry!
And that happens as soon as I compliment them.
Karasuno                        Johzenji
That little guy sure can jump!
Nice touch!
Chance ball!
Not to mention...
All right!
He's got such a stern face,
but that setter sure does some crazy attacks.
Karasuno                        Johzenji
Nice receive!
Asahi!
Nice, Tsucchi!
Who's going to hit it?
A dump?! I'm not gonna let it happen!
Fly
Karasuno High School
Boys' Volleyball Team
Kageyama-kun, nice block!
All right!
That... wasn't a block...
That was his face.
Haikyu!!
Karasuno        Johzenji
Time!
Kageyama, don't die!
He's not dying...
Hey, we're switching you out
until your nose stops bleeding.
My nose isn't bleeding!
It is. Why would you lie about that?
Are your eyes okay?
They're fine.
Did he got caught up in the
excitement of the other team?
Well, it's a good chance
for you to cool your head.
You can't go back out there
until your nose stops bleeding,
so go have it checked.
Just in case!
Come on. Let's go.
Hey, Kageyama!
I'll handle things while you're gone.
Yup. Leave everything to your senpais.
Tsukishima, nice serve!
Huh? Karasuno...
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
I wonder why they're switching out their #10.
He seems to be doing fine.
I think they're going to use this
opportunity to try other things.
Not to mention,
I think the other players
are better at basic plays.
What? Isn't that the truth?
At the Inter-High prelims,
Aone and Karasuno's #10 ended up
becoming friends, oddly enough.
That might be true for now.
Huh?
Aone just spoke?
And their #10
is aware of that.
Hinata.
These past few months,
Narita's spent quite some time
paired with Sugawara as setter.
Just watch your senpais play from here.
Right.
Let's do this in one shot!
You got this, Narita!
Calm down a little.
I understand you want to play, but...
I wanna play and I wanna practice.
I have a lot to do.
All right!
Nice kill!
That's it! That's it!
Right.
Karasuno                       Johzenji
Terushima, nice serve!
All right!
Whoo! Service ace! Whoo!
That guy acts like he just scored three points!
It seriously pisses me off.
You're one to talk, Tanaka.
What?!
Don't let their excitement overwhelm you.
We're gonna finish up this set!
Don't mind! Don't mind!
Get one through!
Kageyama's back.
Kageyama-kun's okay.
Yeah, seems like it.
Good job.
You okay?
But it doesn't seem like they're
going to switch out yet.
Yes.
Nishinoya!
Got it!
Nice receive!
Didn't you say you'd handle things?
Shut up!
I'll eventually be able to do that...
Eventually.
Nice kill!
Nice!
We're not gonna lose...
Karasuno                       Johzenji
Chance ball!
Got it!
Synchronized attack: Sugawara version!
All right!
Now they're at...
Karasuno                       Johzenji
Set point.
That thing where they all move at once...
That's so cool!
Hey, so, like...
Don't tell me they're...
Narita, one more! Nice serve!
Johzenji's also doing a synchronized play?
All right!
Karasuno            Johzenji
We did that a lot, too...
Not bad, Narita.
We still do, from time to time.
Johzenji's synchronized attack just now
was most likely monkey see, monkey do.
They just did it on a whim.
What? But that'd put them
at a disadvantage...
Not to mention, it was a set point.
It probably also has to do with the fact
I totally thought I could do it!
that we're in our first set,
but their recklessness is scary.
I've been wondering about this, but...
Johzenji High School's banner...
Simplicity and Fortitude
Johzenji Parents' Association
How do I put this?
It doesn't really fit the team... Does it?
I'd say they're more "wild and free."
Actually a long time ago,
or rather, up until recently,
simplicity and fortitude described
Johzenji's team accurately.
You guys seriously need to
think about when to do things.
I totally thought I could do it.
Now they got a set from us!
Just like you guys, they're a pretty
troublesome team if you get them riled up.
That #10 sure jumps well.
Well, I mean, their motto is...
Fly
"Fly!"
And yet, we get that.
Simplicity and Fortitude
Johzenji Parents' Association
Our banner is so lame.
Let's hurry and get a new one.
"Simplicity and Fortitude" is cool, too!
I guess that depends on taste,
but it doesn't fit the team.
At least our generation.
Or rather, it won't fit the
future generations, either.
I know, right?
Miyagi Prefecture
Johzenji High School
I'm Anabara, and I'm gonna be
your coach starting this year.
I'm going to rebuild this
team from the ground up.
First, you'll get better at
playing two-on-two.
That team apparently has five second-years.
Seriously? And they got into
the semifinals? That's awesome.
Yahoo!
Terushima!
Huh?
Eventually, there will come
a time that's not fun.
What are you going to do then?
Even then,
I'll do my best to have fun.
We're gonna fool around even more!
Yeah!
Johzenji                       Karasuno
Man...
That weird duo's coming back?
Hinata, Kageyama, stay calm.
Shut up, jeez.
Looks like you're back, Mini Spider-Man.
It's boring without your attacks!
Boring?
Like your captain.
He may be good, but he's boring.
Right... Though I don't really understand.
Anyway, we're gonna have tons
of fun and win this next one.
I can't beat you one-on-one, though,
Mr. Close-Cropped Hair...
Hey, don't give me a weird nickname!
Got it. I'll be more careful.
But if these guys are with me, I'm not gonna lose!
Thanks.
Please.
Leave it to me!
Fly
Higashi, nice serve!
Nishinoya!
Got it!
Ah!
I warned you guys!
Wow! Those are some amazing reflexes!
Actually, I think he was expecting that.
Huh?
Daichi-san, nice job covering their asses!
Don't say it like that!
Here!
He's going for another insane hit!
All right!
We got it this time!
I-I'm sorry! Nice cover!
Thanks!
No matter how much you
were told to calm down,
I figured you guys might do something
like that right when you got back,
because you would get too excited.
I can't do any fancy plays,
but I can give you guys a solid foundation.
Well, go all out.
Thanks!
Well, in the terms of wild and free,
it's not guaranteed that
Johzenji would beat us.
But...
That's not all that we have.
Fly
Johzenji         Karasuno
All right!
The point difference is getting bigger.
Let's get hyped up!
Yeah!
Damn it!
It's up. Get the last!
Get back!
Tanaka, nice!
All right!
Counter!
Yeah!
Damn it.
We can't handle that #10.
Hinata, nice kill!
Thanks!
I-I'm sorry!
Johzenji                        Karasuno
Don't worry about it.
We're gonna end this.
Out!
Don't mind! Don't mind!
Daichi-san, nice serve!
Got it!
Sorry!
Why you...
Is he going to do a dump attack?
Yeah, you go!
Crap...
All right!
The other team called a time out!
It's good to be on the offensive,
but Johzenji is definitely panicking.
Let's get more hyped up!
Yeah! Hyped! Super hyped!
It'll all work out.
So what are we gonna do
about that #10's quick?
What are we gonna do?
Wh-What will we do?
Don't think too much about it.
We just have to go at them harder! Yeah!
What are you going to do now, Misaki?
I don't have anyone to take over for me,
so I'm thinking about staying
until the spring tournament.
That puts me at ease a little.
When they're doing well, everything is fine,
but once they break, I think
they're still pretty weak,
so you'll have to spank them for me.
I don't think they'll listen to me.
That's not true.
Yeah! Let's go all out! Way out!
All right!
Way out! Way out!
What do you mean, "way out"?
Huh?
You guys try way too hard to solve things
by getting riled up and excited.
Eventually, there will come
a time that's not fun.
What are you going to do then?
Even then,
I'll do my best to have fun.
Having fun even if you're
inferior or not doing well?
If anyone's actually like that,
they're either creeps or weirdos.
M-Misaki? What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Sensei.
But if I don't say this when they
have an idea of their weakness,
I don't think they'll get it,
so please let me finish.
Huh? Uh, okay...
Okudake-kun told me to give
these guys a spanking...
Spank?
Hana-san...
...said "spank!"
Well, yeah, the situation
right now isn't fun.
It's annoying, but those guys are
playing around much more freely.
Okudake-kun used to always
say in order to play,
you need a place to play.
Endure through the time that's not fun,
and play all the way to the end.
I thought I heard that
pretty lady say "spank"...
What's wrong?
Kiyoko-san...
I'm not sure why I'm asking,
but would you scold us, too?
In the most condescending way possible.
No.
Then—
I will not spank you, either.
We got Kiyoko-san to say "spank!"
Johzenji                   Karasuno
Now that we're in the middle
of our second set...
It looks like we're finally
starting the second round.
Johzenji's style of volleyball
is constantly changing.
We do that, too!
Rolling... Headbutt!
You're so cool, Noya-san!
Er, that's not volleyball...
Episode 16: "Next"
Next time on Haikyu!!: "Next."