We’ve fought under gravity
several times now, remember?
“You judge a man by his looks”!
Randy, you’re the one
who always says that!
Sorry to interrupt your meal!
You’ve been ordered to sortie!
The Wulgaru army has broken
past our absolute defense zone!
“Defensive Battle at
Cosmopolitan Academy (First Part)”
Delish! Ashagi, ish dis
your weal calling in life?
Why are you eating?
The operation has already started!
I’m bored stiff after
all of this waiting.
Hey, Izuru! How was
your date with Teoria?
“How,” huh? Everyone saw
how it went down, right?
We only got to talk for a
bit before I was summoned.
But-but a date is still a date!
You suddenly grew closer or something
along those lines, right?
Well, I’ll admit I do
think we’ve grown closer.
Ange is running late!
What could be keeping her?
Black 6 is already in position
to sortie and will be
working independently of you.
We just received an emergency
call from Captain Amane.
Our vessel will change its current
course and return to Earth.
However, Black 6 will continue
to head toward the frontlines.
We’ve identified an enemy
detachment headed for Earth.
We believe they are targeting
Gurantseere Cosmopolitan Academy.
Our school...?
The allied armies of Bela-Russia,
the Great Chinese Alliance and the MJP
are currently fighting
the Wulgaru fleet that
has broken past the
absolute defense zone.
However, we noticed a detachment
that is acting independently
of the main fleet.
Here is an image of the enemy
squad headed toward Earth.
It’s a small group...
Doesn’t the fighter in front
look like the one Ange
just recently thrashed?
Why are they going after the academy?
According to Commander Simon,
they probably intend to steal
some DNA samples from the school.
There are signs that the enemy stole a
vast amount of Earth’s
data the other day.
This attack is probably related
to the information they obtained.
At the moment, our vessel
is the closest one to Earth.
Earth will also launch
their reserve fleet.
We are to go and offer our support.
Klein, what are you doing there?
You have not received orders to sortie.
I’m not going to let
you hog all of the glory.
I’m going to take
these lamata for myself!
Restrain yourself, Klein!
The purpose of this operation
is to verify the information
Lumes has obtained.
It is a reconnaissance mission
to determine whether or not
the Earthlings possess prime DNA
samples on their home world.
Furthermore, your wounds
have not yet healed.
These injuries can’t hold me back!
If the genes are there, I’ll
simply swipe them all!
I’m gonna restore
the honor I’ve lost!
Klein!
These are my lamata!
Lumes, remain where you
are for the time being.
No. We shall charge
through, just as planned.
With two squads, this will make a
coordinated effort all the easier.
Going by the looks of it,
Klein may very well fire
at friend and foe alike.
Remain on standby for now
and see how things progress.
My fleet shall work to maintain
our current standing.
Very well, Sir.
My plans have gone horribly awry...
No... Perhaps he predicted that
there was a chance this may happen.
Here is the information on Earth
that I obtained the other day.
According to this, the Earthlings
have a facility where they
combine advanced genes on their
home planet to produce highly
advanced individuals.
What an absurd species.
Ultimately, they have created nothing
but a poor imitation of our civilization.
Yet even so, fascinating individuals
can appear on occasion.
If not for that, this
would be far too tiresome.
Here is the information on
Pleguzesia Teoria and Daneel.
As suspected, they are on Earth.
My prediction was right.
Perhaps my younger sister’s
genes were calling out to me...
It would seem that Pleguzesia
is near this facility.
I do not know if those
of Earth apprehended her
or if she went to Earth
on her own accord.
Have you reported to my brother yet?
I have not told anyone.
I felt that it would be appropriate
to report to you first.
Keep it that way.
Henceforth, you are to be
my eyes and ears as you
continue to gather information.
Is it safe to assume that you
do not want me to submit
an official report?
I do not want to distress
my older brother.
And if this information came to light,
ambitious fools would try their
upmost best to topple our clan.
What is my younger
sister doing on Earth?
Until that is made clear,
do not tell anyone.
Understood.
I will speak with my brother
and see to it that you
are sent to Earth.
But I must take other
measures, just in case.
To think that he had foreseen
that I may not land on Earth...
Pleguzes Jiart...
Just how far can his eyes
see into the future?
I imagine the Wulgaru fleet we’re
currently facing on the frontlines
is a diversion meant
to draw our attention.
I think their real target is Earth.
Isn’t this the first time they’ve
landed a direct attack on Earth?
I hope everyone evacuates in time...
We just received some new
information from Commander Simon.
The commander of the enemy’s
infiltration squad is Klein.
Supposedly he is one of the
Wulgaru’s Military Commanders.
A Military Commander?
What’s that? Sounds kinda tough!
Once you’ve entered combat air
space, launch out of your cockpits.
After that, our main ship will
engage in artillery combat.
Everyone, prepare to sortie.
Here are the routes we expect
the enemy to take to Earth.
It’s hard to say whether we
can catch up with them or not.
In the end, they may breach
the earth’s atmosphere.
The GDF’s reserve fleet has
reached the first line of defense.
They will engage in combat.
Do you think those measly
ships are enough to stop me?
Speed up! We’re gonna
send these wimps reeling!
Topeka of the GDF squadron Providence
has been severely damaged!
Galveston and Little Rock
have been destroyed.
The enemy fleet hasn’t
suffered any losses!
They will enter range within 20 seconds.
All ships, prepare to launch an assault.
You are free to use
all of your artillery.
Commence fire once enemy
fighters are within range.
Your targets are the enemy
squad on track for Earth!
The enemy fighters seem to have
rather advance evasion systems.
I’m not sure if we’ll hit them...
We don’t have to hit them.
We just have to slow them down a bit.
I never expected our main ship
to engage in actual combat...
That goes to show how
dire the situation is.
Depending on how things
go, we may find ourselves
strapped to a gun.
That isn’t funny!
I always get a Rank
C at target practice.
All ships, blast off!
Reinforcements?
But I don’t have time
to play with them!
You’re in the way!
The enemy squad has
suffered minor damages!
The enemies are moving at high speeds,
allowing them to dodge our attacks.
Even when we do hit them,
it doesn’t do anything.
As suspected, it looks like
they are equipped with
high-performance defense systems.
Yeah... They’ll get away if we
use normal shells and artillery.
But that might work...
Do you have an idea?
I modified the weapon we used at Ceres.
It’s a powerful
long-range optical weapon
that pierces through objects
at the speed of light.
But I’m afraid the enemy will
notice before we can fire a shot
if we don’t snipe from
a substantial distance.
Crap! At this rate, they’re
gonna break through.
But their speed has definitely dropped.
If they maintain this pace,
we should make it in time.
We have to stop the Wulgaru!
We can’t let them lay a single
finger on our old school.
Your assignment is to evaluate
yourself and then surpass yourself.
You’ve reached the
designated airspace!
Team Rabbits, prepare to sortie.
But we are going to change
Gold 4’s armament.
We’re changing it?
Team Rabbits, blast off!
Go to Hell!
You still haven’t seen nothin’ yet!
I dare you to come at me all
at once, you pathetic wimps!
Even in mass, you’re nothing
before the great Black 6!
That’s one feisty pilot, huh?
Supposedly this is Ange
Kuroki’s fighting style.
Compared to him, Patrick is...
Tamaki isn’t coming, is she...?
Get yer act together, Patrick!
What happened to all that vigor
you had just a minute ago?
It looks like I’m the type that
uses love as energy in my fights...
Go meet your maker!
Oh, Tamaki...
Dang, they’re the polar opposites.
Black 6, huh?
I hope this is the only time we have to
fight alongside someone like him.
They dived into inner space!
Let’s go after them!
Wait! We’re outfitted for
fighting in outer space.
If we get caught in Earth’s gravity,
we’ll become shooting stars
and get burned to a crisp!
Red 5 and Blue 1,
use Rose 3 as a shield
and descend to Earth.
Will that actually work?
Rose 3 is capable of entering the
earth’s atmosphere in its basic form.
If you cling to the back of
Rose 3 while its shield is up,
Blue 1 and Red 5 should be
able to handle the entry.
Purple 2, stay there on standby.
Help direct the units and
coordinate their formations.
Roger. I will begin calculating their
speed of descent and angle of incidence.
We’re off and away!
I’m sending you my
orbital calculations.
Rose 3 is faster than their fighters,
so you’ll just barely beat them there.
But if you stray from this
course even a little,
you’ll wind up at a totally
different location. Be careful!
Got it! I’m heading on out!
We’re falling!
My unit’s surface temperature
is rapidly increasing!
We’re still in the green!
Tamaki, up the speed!
Rose 3, you can do it!
We made it!
Whoa!
Did your unit get damaged?
It’s just heavier
than I was expecting.
Relax!
As long as you keep your
cool, you can handle this!
Got it! Keep my cool... Keep my cool...
I can’t believe we’re running
away when the enemy is right there!
It can’t be helped...
What’s going on up there?
It’s the Fail Five!
The Fail Five?
Yeah! Blue 1, Rose 3 and Red
5 are up there fighting!
You mean Izuru, Asagi and Tamaki?
Hang in there! Fight!
One fighter down!
I can see our school from here!
It’s going to take a while
before Gold 4 is ready.
Please buy some time!
There are a bunch of enemy fighters!
Tell us what to do, Kei.
Klein is their primary fighter.
Someone mark him while the other two
deal with the remaining fighters.
Izuru, you should defeat Klein.
Tamaki and I will handle the others.
Huh? But...
Red 5 is superior in combat.
Leave the others to us.
You do your job as the ace!
All right. I’m leaving
the rest to you.
Izuru was Team Rabbit’s ace pilot?!
I hate to admit it, but he’s a
better pilot than either of us.
So we should focus on doing what we can.
Dang! And here I thought
I was our ace pilot!
Great!
All three of them have high Harmonic
Levels, especially Blue 1.
This may be his highest level yet.
The primitive creature
I fought last time?
Excellent!
Let’s have a return match!
My weapons don’t work on him...
What should I do?
Thanks for waitin’!
Gold 4 is now on the scene!
Izuru and the others have already
made contact with the enemy.
Please prepare to fire immediately.
Don’t be in such a rush!
Optical weapons take a delicate touch.
They pierce through the
enemy at the speed of light,
so as long as your aim is good, there
is zero chance of them dodging!
In exchange, they require
pin-point accuracy.
And there is a crazy huge distance
between me and my target!
I’ve gotta account for the earth’s
rotation, vibrations in the atmosphere
and even gravitational interference!
Hey, at least I don’t have to
worry about the Coriolis Effect
like I do when sniping on Earth.
To top it off, I’ve
gotta fire at max power.
So once I let her rip, it’ll take
a while before I can fire again.
Even on Earth, I’m
probably the only person
capable of pulling this mission off!
We’ll help adjust the laser’s sight.
But since the enemy is moving,
everything ultimately rests
on the skill of the gunner.
Be careful.
I know, I know! You can count on me!
I want something if I pull this off.
Like one of the GDF’s
G-11, Steyr-ACE or IWS-2000!
All right. I’ll take
it into consideration.
Fer real?!
You may pull the trigger
when you’re ready,
but don’t take too long.
I know you can do it.
You’re really pilin’ on the
pressure by actin’ all nice...
Gold 4 is ready to snipe.
Do something to restrict
the enemy’s movements.
In that case--!
Now you’ve done it,
primitive creature!
How dare you make me lick
your planet’s dirt!
Hurry, while the enemy is still dazed!
Don’t push me!
If I’m not careful, Izuru
might get caught in the blast!
“Defensive Battle at
Cosmopolitan Academy (Second Part)”