Akatsuki...
Where am I?
Where am I going?
Come one, come all!
If you don't buy one today, your Christmas cake...
How about that? It turned into a plain old cake!
It's hip with today's youth!
If you buy one now, it comes with a reindeer mask!
You there! Yes, you, beautiful!
Damned adventurers...
A Lost Child at Dawn
A Lost Child at Dawn.
There's no need to worry.
When Akatsuki wakes up,
Henrietta will contact us.
Yes...
Aren't you cold?
You've been standing by the window for a while.
You're right...
Compared to where I used to live, it's cold here.
You weren't born in Akihabara?
No.
I was born in a town called Kiyose.
In this world, it would be around Nobidome District.
You're not a noble, Rieze?
No, I'm not.
I was born in a small, normal home.
I don't know anything, do I?
About you...
No, about Akatsuki or Henrietta, either.
Or Marielle.
And...
No.
It's not that I didn't know.
It's that I never tried to know.
Not even about Crusty...
It's especially cold today.
In school, I was a good student.
The teachers loved me,
and I was adept at my studies.
When I showed how clever I was,
everyone praised me.
I became skilled at it.
In that sense,
I'm glad I joined D.D.D. when I came here.
I met a lot of people,
and I was forced to realize that the only
world I had ever tried to see was so small.
If I hadn't, I may have gone on like that forever,
with something very important missing.
I was really on a bad path.
Yes.
What's most important is always there, somewhere.
And because it's important,
I think you need to treasure it.
That's why I think I need...
well, to be a princess.
But I'm never good enough.
So...
So I want to treat you properly, Rieze!
Otherwise, I won't have the right
to be treated kindly by you,
or to delude myself into thinking I'm protecting you.
Treat me properly?
Very well.
Then here's my first bit of advice.
To treat someone "properly" is too difficult.
Let's be friends, Lenessia.
I'm an adventurer, but if you don't mind that...
No... This couldn't be...
Where am I heading?
Being pushed, rushed, driven along...
Where am I trying to go?
I may not have a destination.
I'm just trying to run.
I didn't think it would be so quiet here.
Yeah.
Something disappeared...
Did you also feel it, my lord?
Akatsuki...
I see.
Amazing, isn't it?
It isn't snow, is it?
No.
Everyone's thoughts...
The memory fragments they offered up,
so they could rise up once more.
You were defeated, Akatsuki?
That's right.
I died.
I had almost figured something out...
I see.
So was I.
I died.
You, too, my lord?
Yeah.
It's been a heck of a Christmas Eve, my lord.
I failed.
I was naïve.
I couldn't trust them enough.
I don't understand.
It isn't that I'm upset because I couldn't win.
You didn't do the best you could.
You didn't do what you needed to do.
It's strange.
I didn't think I'd see you here.
Yeah, my lord.
It is strange.
Is it only a coincidence?
No, I'm sure it's because I wanted to see my lord.
I wanted him to pat me on the head.
Maybe I can find that which I almost found,
if I search for it myself.
I'm going to try again.
I will, too, I guess.
Everyone taught me.
My lord...
I passed through some quiet place...
It's gone.
But...
I feel like I found something,
like I understand something.
So there's something I should do...
Something I must do.
Akatsuki!
Are you okay?
You don't have any scars, do you?
S-Stop...
You're so cute!
I thought it was about time for you to wake up.
Um...
I know this isn't an appropriate request,
but I'd like you all to help me.
Would you share your Teachings with me?
I want to capture that murderer.
Nazuna, didn't Soujirou use the Teachings?
Yeah.
But it wasn't enough.
Yep.
Why do you seek them, despite that?
Because...
I want to end the murders!
And not just your Teachings, but... well...
If there's a way to stop him,
please tell me anything you know!
You think you can beat him?
I don't know,
but I have to do something to end it.
With my lord gone, someone has to do it.
What do you mean?
Shiroe isn't here?
We were asked to keep it a secret,
but that's right.
At the moment, Shiro is away from Akihabara.
Now I get it.
No wonder you're so desperate.
Well?
I haven't heard your answer.
Do you think you can beat him?
Do you think you can end this?
Can you do it alone?
I can't.
I can't do it alone.
That's why I want your help.
Please help me!
You half-passed, I would say.
There are eight Teachings
that D.D.D. is aware of.
I've already gained my lord's permission.
He's told me to share them with you.
Really...
To come all this way, just to start
over as a middle schooler...
Doesn't seem there are any more
goblins over here, either.
Yeah.
My lord...
Are you bored?
You got me.
I am, yes.
Deal with it.
I've dealt with it all this time, and I'm still bored.
What's wrong?
Lately, my weapon's been acting strangely.
Why not send it to be repaired?
Yeah...
But it's not any less powerful,
so I've just overlooked it.
Its name is "Disaster," right?
Yeah. Its flavor text is pretty dark, as well.
It seems to be fine.
Sorry to bother you.
Onigiri Shop Enmusubi
What a relief!
Research announcements are always tense,
no matter how often you do them.
But it looks like everyone was surprised.
For one of Roderic Research's recent
announcements, it had a lot of impact.
That now everyone can cook,
even if their sub-class isn't chef.
It's limited to simple stuff like salad...
But why is a change like this happening?
Guild master?
Oh, you can keep eating.
Our investigation's interim reports are in,
so I'll just briefly interrupt.
Personality
Woman             Man
Voice
Sex Differences
There are three things I need to announce.
First, regarding sex differences between
now and when this was a game.
Sex differences?
Some people play a different sex
than they are in real life, right?
He's talking about that.
RDR has reported in the past
that personality is influenced by a person's body.
But it appears the voice is affected, as well.
An adventurer with a female
body will find their voice
gradually becoming feminine,
even if the player is actually a man.
Next is optical observation.
There's still a lot we don't know,
but it seems the distance between
Akihabara and Mt. Fuji is increasing.
Actually, the distance between any two points
is increasing by a small amount.
Excuse me.
Go ahead.
Is that occurring everywhere?
Does that mean Yamato is getting bigger?
We believe so.
Lastly, regarding flavor text...
As you know, flavor text is merely
Healing Potion (Basic)
Effect/ Healing Potion (Basic)
Restores a small amount of HP
an explanation that describes where
an item originated or what it is.
Explanation/ Healing Potion (Basic)
A magical medicine created by adventurers.
Its capabilities, flavor, and scent change
depending on the skill of the creator.
As the name suggests, it's just for flavor.
It has no in-game effects.
Yeah,
it's just to add atmosphere...
Yes.
It should have no meaning at all.
But we've confirmed
that some items' flavor texts are
having real-world effects.
No way.
Could so many coincidences really occur at once?
Shouldn't we assume that this world
is undergoing some large-scale change?
The Apocalypse is not over yet.
I've already heard the broader details.
The murderer is a Person of the Land.
You told them.
If this gets out,
relations between adventurers and
People of the Land will worsen in Akihabara.
Akatsuki tried to resolve the situation
because she was concerned about that.
Right?
I can understand that.
Though I can't imagine you'll be
able to hide it completely.
Not with all these victims...
Is the West Wind Brigade going public with this?
No.
Souji said he's pulling out.
Though that's up to you two.
That's...
Stop wasting time confirming things,
and get on with the lecture.
Is this what you mean?
You two were vain enough to think
you could deal with this yourselves.
You knew you should have spoken to us, didn't you?
Aren't you being a little arrogant?
Aren't you insulting the people around you?
How long do you intend to remain alone?
Don't you think it's childish to tell yourself
that all you need is Shiroe?
True, it's always been that way.
I was content with how
comfortable I felt in his shadow.
I never tried to get close to anyone else.
Because I was totally reliant on him...
When he left, I suddenly couldn't do anything.
Not even what he asked me to do.
Did you think you've been
coming here to protect her?
You weren't the only one
who had the job of visiting Watermaple House.
I was, as well, and so was Rieze.
I'm not the only one my lord relied on.
Of course.
But...
It's true that I wanted to help her
because she was trying so hard.
So...
I want your help.
I need your help.
Yes, of course.
Rieze and I will help you.
But who should you be saying that to?
Who...
Akatsuki...
Akatsuki is my friend!
Lenessia is doing her best,
so I want to help her!
I want you all...
all of us... to help her.
Because we're friends.
Very well.
Let's stop that murderer.
I'll come up with a plan.
I'm a friend, too, after all.
My lord, the sun has set.
Let's hurry.
A broken spearhead...
What's the matter?
It looks like this is a training area.
For goblins.
Goblins?
Surely not. I've never heard of them training.
I'm sorry... It's acting strangely again.
Sansa!
My lord!
My lord?
The Graupel Sword Byakumaru?
That's the katana the samurai had?
I knew it on sight.
I saw it many times at Amenoma.
Marie, is something wrong?
W-Well, just...
It's about time, and I haven't gotten a call.
Shiroe and Naotsugu aren't playing around.
They won't always have time.
Yeah, I know, but...
Today, something just doesn't feel right.
Did you notice anything else about the murderer?
One second.
Yes?
Yes.
What?
That can't be...
The murderer's mind is taken from him
as he becomes a true monster.
Is he remembering a legendary hero?
Rieze and Henrietta begin preparations for a raid.
Akatsuki attempts to master the Teachings.
At some point, they find themselves
with many friends.
Twenty-six, in all.
Next time: The Maidens of Watermaple.
The Maidens of Watermaple
Rise up once more.