My new boyfriend often says...
You're pretty quiet, Kamine.
To be honest, I thought girls
would be a lot more work.
You aren't possessive,
and you don't get selfish.
I guess there are girls like you.
Wanting More
But the truth is,
I want to be possessive,
and I want to be selfish.
Do you lice Kamine?
Lice...?
I get a bit jealous
when I see him talk to other girls.
I want to be connected with him
from "good morning" to "good night."
And this distance...
I want to cling onto him
and cuddle right now.
But if I told him that,
he might think I'm a pain.
D-Don't you ever feel possessive
about me, Goda-kun?
Not so far.
I hear those kinds
of relationships don't last.
Y-You're right.
But don't you think it's okay in moderation?
I guess a little is fine.
For example?
For example, holding our hands when we walk.
Not when we're sitting?
Now?
We don't have to, if you don't want to.
Sure, that's fine.
You don't need to be that cautious.
Really?
Th-Then can I come closer to you?
Y-Yeah, if that's what you want.
Is it okay if I'm this close?
Fine.
Th-Then what about this?
I don't mind,
but I might smell from club—
No.
I like this smell.
What's gotten into you today?
S-Sorry!
Do you not like clingy people?
No, I don't mind.
But you said that's a pain.
This isn't that bad.
Isn't this normal if we're dating?
But, well...
Huh?
I actually thought
you didn't like being clingy.
Wh-Why?
You're always so quiet.
I thought you didn't think about it.
Do you want to cuddle more, then?
Well, a little.
O-Oh.
I wouldn't have held back if you'd told me.
All right, can I make a request, too, then?
What?
I've always wanted to do that once.
Forgive me.
I choked on my first kiss!
That was my first kiss.
I wasn't prepared at all.
Sorry.
I coughed on my first kiss...
Want to try again?
Rumor had it that a guy in my class
kissed his girlfriend.
Can you believe it?
They've only been together for three months.
Man, they didn't look like
they'd take it so fast.
So what about us, Chiaki?
Shoot
About that...
I wanted to talk to you about that.
They've had so many opportunities already.
Why do you think they can't score, Coach?
The forward, Chiaki, keeps chickening out.
That's harsh.
But Coach, his teammates
have to pass him the ball.
It's not just Chiaki's fault—
Should I pass to you now, then?
Kamine and Goda scored
a shot in the park, I hear.
R-Right.
Everyone seems to think
we've at least kissed already.
Well, does it matter
how long we've been dating,
or if other people have already kissed?
What matters most is
improving our own game.
Then you want to?
Why now?
Well, you want to, don't you?
Not if you feel like you're being forced.
I don't feel forced.
You just keep nagging me.
Forget it. I'm not feeling it.
K-Kana-chan, are you angry?
Sorry.
Kana-chan.
Shit, this is where she refuses
to talk to you for a while.
Game's over.
Huh?
Did we get stoppage time?
We did!
She's totally waiting for me!
All right, now's my chance.
Shoot!
Th-This is a difficult angle!
I can't get near the goal,
though the audience has their eyes fixed.
I'm going to have to just go for it.
Hey!
He misses!
But I kissed a girl on the face
for the first time.
Awesome!
Coach, I'd like to go again.
I feel like I can do it now.
Once more.
Give me a chance.
O-Okay.
O-Or not.
Yeah.
The End
Library
Yeah, that's correct.
I think I'm getting pretty good at English.
Maybe it's thanks to you.
Let me squeeze your boobs, then.
Akagi, dude, we're in the Library.
Boobs
Yup.
Aren't we here to study for exams
because we mess around too much at home?
Yeah.
So what was that?
Let me squeeze your boobs, Ryoko-chan.
You say some of the dumbest shit
for someone that's as smart as you.
Dumb shit?
Why would I let you touch my boobs
when there are so many people around?
I'm sure you'll let me squeeze them
if I ask persistently enough.
Right?
Don't you think so?
O-Of course not!
Are you sure?
You tend to buckle.
I'm not that easy.
I know.
But am I the only one holding back?
What about you?
I'm not really...
Don't you feel like messing around more?
I don't—
Wh-What?
Can't you see?
I'm telling you to come here.
I told you, I'm not really...
You don't have to hold back.
I guess no one's watching.
Just a little...
But in return, let me squeeze
your boobs a little.
Wh-What the hell?!
Are you telling me to hold back
while you run free?
Fine, then.
I'm not really holding—
Here.
Goddammit!
See, you were holding back.
It's your fault for tempting me.
So I can squeeze your boobs, then?
I can?
D-Do whatever you want!
All right, let's get back to studying.
Huh? Why?
It's fine.
I never intended to feel you up.
Even though you were ready to let me.
Then why'd you say all that?
I wanted you to know how much
I'm holding back all the time.
Wh-What?
You say that like I'm
the only one being needy!
I'm not.
I feel better, now that you understand.
Were you expecting something?
The End
My love was like a sparkler.
The fragile spark of passion has burnt out.
But the image of its vibrant light
still shines in my mind.
This is where I first met him.
I'm such a fool.
He's already rejected me.
K-Katori-senpai!
Bruised-Up Angel
A-Are you okay?!
Huh?
Who are you?
It's me, Kazuko!
Hosokawa Kazuko!
We met here before!
I'm sorry, I don't remember
every girl's face.
Could you smile for me?
I might remember if I see your smile.
Gorgeous!
Ah, the little kitten from before.
How did you get hurt?
I got in a bit of a fight.
I'll call an ambulance!
You mustn't, little kitten.
They'll find me.
He's being chased!
It's my fault.
I made a taken girl fall for me again.
That's awful!
They shouldn't blame you!
No, it's my fault.
Say, little kitten,
how can I become less popular?
I can't.
I can't tell him it's impossible.
I have to go.
They'll find me.
But you're so beat up!
They're probably waiting for me at home.
I'll have to be a stray cat for a while.
Th-Then, why don't you come to my place?
Stay near me, and you'll die.
I'm not afraid!
You don't get it, little kitten.
The people chasing me aren't my true enemy.
Why am I so popular?
Who made me this way?
There's only one man
who could make me that way.
Do you mean....
God?
Magic!
As long as the god of dating implores me
to be popular, I will hurt someone again.
I don't want to hurt anyone anymore.
No!
You're the one who's hurt!
I'm sorry, little kitten.
That's just my afterimage.
I'm impressed you can keep up with me.
Don't underestimate me!
That's enough.
You're not ready for these moves.
Still, I want to be with you!
Oh dear, little kitten,
Or perhaps you're a fine leopardess now.
One finger.
Watch me stop you with one finger.
Who do you think I am?
Do you honestly think
you can stop me with one finger?
Fall for me even more,
and you'll suffer more than just burns.
Am I...
Am I not good enough for you?
If you're prepared for that, then burn.
Just kidding.
I'd make a bad senpai
if I let my juniors play with fire.
No... I...
I'm going to go beat the crap
out of the god of romance
so that I don't get any more popular.
Until then, be careful around fires of love.
Katori-senpai!
Tonight!
Next episode: Square One.
Square One