Good morning, Rizel...
Good morning, Princess.
The weather's beautiful again today.
It's a perfect blue sky for a special day.
You're right.
On the south side of the
continent of Flognarde,
today is a special day for the
three allied nations of
the Biscotti Republic:
Galette and Pastillage.
Three wonderful people who
make everybody smile,
the three Heroes, are coming back today.
Once Again, The Hero Returns
Yeah!
I managed to get to a tie this time!
Next time I'll win!
What?
I won't let you win next time!
Earth / Tokinochou, Kinokawa City, Japan
A tie, huh?
They're both amazing.
I have to hurry!
Biscotti Republic
Firianno Castle
Your posture's all wrong.
Think further ahead!
Yes, ma'am!
Next!
Captain Eclair is all fired up today.
Of course she is, I mean...
Right.
Next!
Okay!
I'm going to play with
the Hero a lot again this time!
I'm waiting!
This time we're summoning three
Heroes at the same time.
Galette Lion Territory
Vannette Castle
Shinku and Nanami-san have gone to
England for a tournament.
They'll be heading directly to
Biscotti and Galette from there.
Dukedom of Pastillage
Hero King's Hill
Rebecca-san, the hero of Pastillage...
will be going to Pastillage
from Kinokawa city.
Good to see you, Shuze!
Earth/ England: City of London
Tatsumaki! Cheney!
Thanks for coming to get us!
It looks like it's going to rain.
Let's head out before then.
Yeah!
Kuu-sama!
Rebecca!
Welcome back!
Yeah! I'm back, Kuu-sama!
Why are we still together?
Weren't we going to split up and
go to Galette and Biscotti?
I don't know, but something seems wrong.
My stuff!
W-We're saved...
Looks like it, yeah.
But...
Where are we?
There was a lightning bolt during
the summoning, right?
Maybe that knocked us off course.
I dropped my stuff, too.
I'm worried about Tatsumaki and Cheney.
Let's just head down to the ground for now.
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Nanami!
Thanks, Shinku.
Yeah.
That was close.
So, what do we do now?
We saw a place that looked like
Biscotti as we fell, right?
Yeah.
It's pretty clear this is Flognarde,
so let's start by looking for our stuff.
You're right.
If we can find it, we can
get a hold of everyone.
By the way...
You can put me down if you want.
Where did it fall?
Look!
I saw them in a Galette encyclopedia.
You can eat them.
Those kind of look like dinosaurs.
Yeah.
Where are we?
From the position of the stars,
I think Galette is that way.
In the worst case, we could
walk there if we had to.
Isn't the wildlife around this
place a little too crazy?
Why don't we try dropping into that river?
It might be safer than this.
I should've brought a swimsuit!
We're safe.
This isn't really the season for diving.
Agreed.
I'm worried about Tatsumaki and Cheney,
but I wonder if Becky made it to Pastillage.
It feels like our problems
were due to the thunderbolt,
so I bet Becky's okay.
Yeah.
We need to find our stuff
and get in contact with everybody.
Now what?
Why is this happening?
Um...
This happened, and then
this, and then this...
And then this, probably...
Probably, yeah.
This is too much hard mode for me!
Dodge, you guys!
This is my forest.
It's not good for humans to come here.
Yukki-chan.
It seems like something happened.
Line up!
Hurry! No wasting time!
Princess, the Advance Special Hero Search
And Rescue Task Force is on their way.
Thanks!
We, in the main force, will follow you.
Company, march!
Rico...
Yukki will be
coming here from Fuugetsuan shortly!
I'm sure they're
just a little lost.
So...
Yes.
So let's hurry and find them!
Hey! Sister!
Prince Gaul.
What are you doing?
You're still not leaving?
Gaul, don't be in such a panic.
We won't find find them if we go looking
without any information.
Prince, we're in touch with Biscotti
and Pastillage and gathering information.
Gaul-sama!
The search team is all
ready in the courtyard!
We can leave whenever!
Yeah!
I'll let my sister and the
generals use their heads.
I'll use my legs to find them!
But...
It's fine.
Gaul.
I'll allow you to go ahead.
Find clues as to the Heroes' whereabouts.
Right.
I guess we don't have a choice.
General Godwin.
Go with the prince.
Right!
An accident during the summoning?
Normally that's impossible,
but it may be the reason
they landed off course.
Biscotti and Galette have
already sent out search parties.
Pastillage can move the
fastest through the sky.
Kuu-sama.
Yup.
We're ready for you to go whenever.
Then let's go!
Find the Heroes, Shinku and Nanami,
as fast as you can!
Yes!
Rebecca, we'll go looking
for them from the sky, too.
Yeah.
Heroes?
Yup. I'm the Hero of Biscotti,
Shinku Izumi.
I'm the Hero of Galette, Takatsuki Nanami!
It's not good to lie.
I don't know a lot about humans,
but you're not like the Heroes I know.
I've heard the Heroes of the nations
are more dazzling and pure.
You kids look like you don't
even have a change of clothes.
You can't be Heroes.
There's a good reason for this...
And...
A Hero should have their
nation's treasure sword.
Yeah! That's it!
When we were summoned
we dropped the bags that had the treasure
swords and rings and Hero outfits.
Look!
Hero Shinku...
...and Hero Nanami...
...are here!
That's pretty good.
Right?
And did you ever see the war games?
We were in a lot of them.
Have you ever heard of the Union Festa?
I don't know them.
My dwelling doesn't have the equipment
required to watch the broadcast.
I see.
Anyway, this is the Dragon's Forest.
Outsider humans aren't allowed here
and it's very dangerous for normal people.
You'll be in danger.
You're right about that.
And...
And what?
Lately, demons have been appearing here.
Demons?
You're back, Pega?
Nanami!
That...
That's my keyholder!
It was tied to my luggage!
I see.
Pega, lead us to where you found this.
We'll help you find your luggage.
Once we do, I'll lead you
outside of the forest,
so head straight home.
Got it?
Yeah...
That's good enough for now.
She's amazing.
Yeah.
That's it! My stuff!
I found mine, too!
Thank you, Pega!
Oh, if you like that,
you can have it as a thank
you for finding my stuff.
If you found it, I'll show you out.
I'll find a safe way to send
you home, so wait here.
Let's go, Pega.
That's another Foworm growing
to such a huge size...
That flower's not supposed
to attack animals.
It's their fault.
It only happened after the
dragon eaters appeared here.
Did you just hear a weird sound?
Yup.
I won't let you!
So the dragon-eaters have come this far?
This is getting to the point
where I can't ignore it.
Boomerang Slash!
Internal...
Fire Emblem!
Hello again.
I'm Takatsuki Nanami, the Hero of Galette.
And I'm the Hero of Biscotti, Shinku Izumi.
Rebecca!
Kuu-sama!
I'm so jealous.
I want to get back to my country!
Dragon Priestess
Watch it next time, too.