Be kind! Kindness saves
the world! Pinky Phakchi!
Take this, bad guys! Vegetable fire!
Eat veggies and be kind!
Dad, I want that toy!
Fine, I'll buy it.
Awesome!
The real one!
Touka, let's hurry up.
Mom and Dad are waiting in
the car at the intersection.
It's Pinky Phakchi!
That magic staff is amazing, Sister.
Silly, it's just a toy.
What? What is it?
Touka, run!
Dad! Mom!
I'm scared.
I will correct the wrong orders
the humans have given.
I will build a beautiful society.
All operational pods online.
Enter commands to all the pods in deployment.
All troops, let's take out the trash.
Go!
Touka! This way!
Touka, are you all right?
Are you crying, Sis?
Of course not.
Don't worry.
Sister, stop crying, please.
I will beat those bad guys
with my magic stick!
What? Wait!
Stop, Touka!
Come right back! It's dangerous!
That's just a toy. Don't you understand?
Please stop...
You bad guys who torment the people...
This Pinky Phakchi will give you...
A hard punishment!
Pod 28 is in contact with humans
matching data bank records.
Verifying data.
Displaying pod visual.
Matching visual found in data banks.
Displaying visual data.
Radio connection degrading.
Pod 28 offline.
Resuming operation in autonomous mode.
Here goes, Vegetable Fire!
Abort! That girl is—
Stop!
Sister...
I can't believe this.
I can't believe this!
This isn't right.
This isn't right!
I... my friend...
I killed my friend!
We are to take out the trash. Ready!
Clean up!
Stop!
Ah, what is this?
Oh, the paint is peeling off.
Hot!
Touka!
Don't die! Breathe!
Hot!
I told you not to mess with me!
Humans are not trash!
Go to hell!
Touka!
Sister!
Can I destroy them all?
The humans have lost.
But you cannot win.
Impossible. She's so fast.
Faster than us machines.
Here I come!
Upon the grief, so tarnished,
falls gently the snow once again.
blows the wind once again.
Upon the grief, so tarnished,
we do not hope or wish for anything.
The grief, so tarnished,
longs lazily for death.
Sister!
I just want to destroy
more and more, Sister!
That's enough for today.
No fun.
Touka.
Where am I?
Dad? Mom?
Sister?
Tou-chan.
Pinky.
You were real, Pinky!
Huh, but something's not right.
The bad guys came, and everyone...
Never mind that.
Tada!
Here you go.
For me?
I love you, Pinky!
Now we can help everyone.