So this is the city of Tokyo...
What a beautiful place.
My Talent Is Being a Scarecrow
I was sure the place I'm staying
was right around here,
but I don't see a building
that looks like it...
Hey, look.
That girl has chicks on her head.
How cute!
Tokyo has so many buildings and
train tracks, it's like a maze...
What's the matter, miss?
Are you lost?
There are a lot of
dead-end streets in this area.
Wh-Wh-Wh-What should I do?
That's a big bag. Did you just move to Tokyo?
I-I...
Are you a student? Is the place
you're heading to near here?
Wh-Which question should I answer first?
Oh, by the way, that restaurant
has great Russian cuisine.
Come to think of it, when
my daughter came here yesterday,
No, maybe I should introduce myself first...
she got lost and had a pretty rough time.
I'd better not say anything that
would offend someone from Tokyo...
A scarecrow?
Once again, I wasn't able to speak well.
I've always been bad at talking,
so I've practiced a lot, but...
Hello, tanukis, bunnies, birds!
Which story should I read today?
Do you like Cinderella?
Animals sure do love you, Hina-chan.
That keeps the birds out of my fields,
so I appreciate it.
I don't even need a scarecrow anymore.
U-Um...
Oh, my! You froze up!
You look just like a scarecrow.
For some reason, I was always
being put to work as a scarecrow.
I finally got into the
high school of my dreams.
I want to at least try to
not freeze up in front of people,
-Japanese
There's a quiz tomorrow
We covered most of it yesterday
-PE is basketball,
so prepare gym shoes
-We're going to be doing oil painting in art,
so wear clothes and an apron that can get dirty
Preparations are necessary,
so get to the art room early
and be able to talk easily with others.
And while I was worrying about that,
I made it here...
Used Bookstore
Hitotose
This is where I'm staying?
I'm pretty sure
it's the right address, but...
That employee is so pretty.
Is she reading?
Or... eating?
Can I help you?
U-Um...
Um, I...
I was told that I could stay here...
Oh!
You're Hinako-chan, right?
The landlady's told me all about you!
The second floor is used for apartments.
That's where I live, too.
Um... I...
My name's Kuina.
I'll go get the landlady!
-Thank you for letting me borrow the textbook yesterday!
-The book I borrowed is inside the desk.
-Sorry I couldn't return it to you in person.
-You're a lifesaver!
-If you ever need anything let me know.
-Thank you so much!
Lets hang out again!
Some of these books look so old.
This shop has such a nice atmosphere.
In the Forest, Under Cherries in Full Bloom
Sakaguchi Ango
Sorry, it looks like
the landlady's out right now...
Why won't you look me in the eye?
I've never seen someone
eating a book before...
That was... um...
I love reading,
and books are basically my friends.
I adore them so much, I want to eat them up.
D-Don't eat your friends!
A-Anyway, I'll show you to your room.
This room is yours.
What a beautiful room!
It's like I'm in a hotel!
A chest with its own atmosphere,
a cute bed...
and even a maid!
Wait... a maid?
Oh?
Wh-Why is there a maid in my room?
Nice to meet you. I'm Mayuki.
Huh?
I live and work here.
You can call me Mayu.
You live here?
She's a resident here.
All residents work here. That's the rule.
Schoolwork comes first, though,
so it's only on weekends.
I see!
So that's why Mayu-chan is a maid?
No.
I'm an employee in the coffee shop.
This is just what I always wear.
Huh? They're your own clothes?!
I-I heard that someone new
was moving in today,
so I was just cleaning up this room!
Mayu-chan wants to be a princess. Right?
You like frills.
N-No, I don't!
Don't treat me like a child!
I'm just rehearsing for when I'm
invited to dances in the future,
so I won't step on the hem of my dress!
She's like a child...
Hina-chan, you're starting at
Fujimiya High in spring, right?
I'm so glad I'll have a kouhai there now!
Huh? A kouhai?
Did you think I was a first-year like you?
I may not look it, but I'm a second-year!
I'm sorry!
People always think I look younger than I am.
I can't tell her I thought
she was in elementary school...
But don't worry, it doesn't bother me.
By the way, I'm a first-year, too.
So we'll be together.
Yeah! I'm looking forward to it!
The toilet is in the middle of the hallway.
We only have a given amount of time
to use the bath, so be careful of that.
Kuu-chan, that's immodest!
Bad!
Well, I didn't finish my breakfast...
Oh, all right.
It's noon, anyway. Why don't we have lunch?
In a bookstore?
Nope.
See? This is the coffee shop where I work.
You're right!
Coffee shop
Used Bookstore
You Are Here
There's a coffee shop
in the back of the bookstore!
Here, Hina-chan.
Take this.
Huh?
I have to eat a book, too?
This is a menu.
Oh, so it is.
Why did you enroll at our
high school, Hina-chan?
Huh?
What do I do?
Where should I start explaining?
Well... when I was a scarecrow
out in the country...
Huh? A scarecrow?
You mean those dolls that stand in fields?
What did you do?
She froze up...
She really does look like a scarecrow.
Today's practice menu
-Stretches <-- Do them properly!
-3 kilo marathon <-- Try your best not to walk
-Vocal exercises
-Review the script
-Review strong and weak points
and check on props
-Check on costume
I wondered what exactly she did.
So she literally freezes up
and does nothing...
As you can see, I get nervous easily...
It's unusual to see someone become
a scarecrow because of nerves.
But during my school's field trip last year,
I saw a theater club play here.
I was so moved by the
actors' bold performances.
I wanted to be like that, too.
So I decided I wanted to be in theater, too.
And that's why you enrolled
at our high school?
Um, are you two in theater or anything?
You're both really cute,
and I bet Kuu-chan could write good stories.
And Mayu-chan could play
a princess, maybe...
I'd probably eat the script
right after writing it...
Really?
I could never wear a dress!
I'd be too embarrassed!
But that outfit doesn't embarrass her?
So you're going to join
the theater club, then?
Yeah.
Our school is pretty prestigious.
I want to be able to talk a lot
in front of people,
Huh?
and I want to make lots of friends, too.
Good luck!
I'm rooting for you!
Thanks!
I heard the theater club was
shut down last year, though.
Oh, yeah, come to think of it...
You're kidding!
I didn't hear about that!
I know it's my fault for not checking
before I enrolled there, but...
But, but... there was no Internet
out in the country!
And I just bought that cell phone yesterday!
I'm going to join the theater club!
I'm not interested in any other clubs,
and I'm not good at any sports or arts...
Good at... The only thing I'm good at is...
...being a scarecrow, I guess.
Scarecrows wouldn't be
of any use in Tokyo, would they?
I almost forgot.
If I'm going to live here, I have to work.
Which means...
W-Welcome.
No way, no way! I could never do that!
Hina-chan?
What's wrong?
Why were you yelling?
S-Sorry! It was nothing!
Tears
Family Photo
Hina-chan, are you...
...homesick?
I'm sorry I didn't notice!
Uh...
Of course. You just moved to Tokyo.
H-Huh?
Want to go out for a change of pace?
There's a big park nearby.
Really? A park?
There's lots of greenery there,
too. I'm sure you'll like it.
There's a place near there
that has great chicken skewers,
and a stand that has great dumplings, too.
And also ice cream...
No description of the actual park, huh?
Kuu-chan, are you hungry again?
Once we're on this road,
it's straight ahead.
Oh, the café there has amazing cakes!
Hey, come on. We just ate lunch.
And once we turn this corner...
Taiyaki
Hey! Kuu-chan, not there!
Honestly, you're so easily tempted by food.
Sorry... I smelled delicious taiyaki,
so I couldn't help myself.
Don't blame me if you get lost.
You're like an older sister, Mayu-chan.
An older sister...
Taiyaki...
H-Honestly, Kuu-chan,
you're hopeless without me.
W-Wait here, okay?
Your big sister will go buy taiyaki for you.
Yay!
When did she become our big sister?
Mister, I'd like three taiyaki, please.
Sure thing.
And since you're such a cutie,
I'll give you a discount.
Thank you!
Here you go.
Taiyaki
She's so cute...
He gave me a discount!
She was our big sister a minute ago,
and now she's an elementary schooler.
So sweet!
Yum!
It's crispy on the outside,
with lots of soft red bean paste
on the inside.
Actually, I think this is the first time
I've bought food and eaten it on the spot.
Hina-chan, are you heading home?
Want some watermelon?
Hup... hup...
Here's a fresh-picked tomato and cucumber.
I'll throw in a daikon, too.
Um...
I got most of my food for free...
Aren't these great?
See? Here it is.
It's so big!
And the cherry trees are in bloom—
U-Um...
I met a kitty cat in town today
It kept meowing
and kept calling to me, so I followed it,
and ended up at a gathering spot for kitties!
There were a lot of cute kitties,
and they all came up to me
and were friendly.
I was so happy.
Hina-chan, have you calmed down?
Yeah. Sorry I worried you.
Not many people come
over this way, so you can relax.
Too bad...
The dumplings from the stand
by the entrance were so good, too.
Darn it, Kuu-chan!
Get your mind off food already!
She can eat more?
Can we go look at the ducks?
Ducks?
It's true!
There are ducks in the pond!
How cute!
Stare...
She couldn't be...
I won't eat the duck.
U-Uh... Kuu-chan, do you like ducks?
Yeah! Especially the way
they slide through the water...
It looks so cool, like a stealth fighter!
Uh... S-Ste...?
What do you think? Isn't it a nice place?
All the greenery reminds me
of the forests out in the country.
I was feeling a bit down,
but I feel better now.
That's great.
I guess you're not homesick anymore.
Homesick?
Who did it?!
Who killed my friend with this blade?!
Identify yourself at once!
Who are those people?
There are lot of small theater
troupes around here,
The killer couldn't have been
someone here. Can't you see that?
so the aspiring actors and troupe members
come here to practice often.
You're wrong! The door to this
place was closed the whole time!
Wow...
Aren't they cool?
And the windows lock from the outside.
They look like they're running
straight toward their dream.
Nobody could've gotten in or out.
I really do want to go into theater...
Wait!
That girl practicing over there is Aki-chan!
Hey!
I wondered why you weren't at home,
but I didn't expect to see you here!
What were you doing?
If you were going out,
you should have said so.
Vocal practice.
Hina-chan, this is a classmate of mine,
and the landlady of our building.
Huh?
Hello. Nice to meet you.
I'm Chiaki, the landlady of Hitotose Manor.
She's tall and has a nice figure...
She's so beautiful.
N-Nice to meet you!
I-I'll be in your care starting today.
I-I'm Hinako.
Looks like an arranged marriage meeting.
You know, Aki-chan
used to be a child actress.
She still loves theater to this day.
She used to be in the theater club
at Fujimiya High School, too.
She's normally quiet,
but on the stage, she's a different person!
Her role as a former biker gang member
and young proprietress at a traditional
inn who's now an idol singer
was especially powerful.
What kind of play was that?
I can't decide...
I-I...
I entered Fujimiya High School because
I wanted to be in its theater club.
But when I heard the club was
shut down, I was so shocked.
More accurately, it's on hiatus.
Hiatus?
The club's advisor is on a theater trip.
It's on break in the meantime.
What?!
It's on hiatus because of that?
What are the other members doing?
Just like me,
they're all doing
the things they want to do.
O-Oh, no...
But if you want to perform
theater that much,
why don't you start a theater troupe?
Huh?
Small theater troupes
don't need many members.
So you'd be the leader, Hina-chan?
More accurately, she'd be the principal.
A theater troupe...
What, what?
What are you guys talking about?
Could I really make one?
You have members. You'd be fine.
You have four.
Huh?
Four?
Wait, are we being dragged into something?
Hitotose
I feel alive again...
So many things happened today.
I met lots of people,
went to lots of places,
and experienced lots of firsts.
I was sad when I heard
the theater club had been shut down...
But...
Starting a theater troupe, huh?
Could I really do something like that?
Still, all the people at
Hitotose Manor are so nice.
I hope everything will work out.
Hina-chan?
You're been in here
for a long time. Are you o—
Hina-chan, hang in there!
Oh, what do I do?!
Something wrong?
Get Aki-chan!
Ah! Hina-chan!
I'm here.
Whoa! She looks like a boiled octopus!
What do you mean, "I'm here"?!
I'm not sure how to answer that.
Hina-chan!
What's wrong?
What do we do?!
It Begins Here
Can I really start a theater troupe?
I can't be a scarecrow forever.
I have to remember how I felt on the day
I decided that's how I wanted to be!
Next time: "It Begins Here."