June
SHOGI HALL
They're huge!
Whose shoes are these?
They're freaking enormous!
- Kumakura 9th-Dan, right?
- Most likely.
He's here for the qualifier
for the Kiryuu Championship.
Hey, what size is it?
Want to check?
Yeah, yeah!
RUMBLE RUMBLE RUMBLE
Whoa, 29.5 cm! Incredible, almost 30 cm!
That's how he kicked that hole in the inn's wall!
These are beyond human!
You can't fit these into a cubbyhole!
But I was shocked, you know?
For that cool, stone-faced Mr. Kumakura to kick
the wall of an inn after losing a title match...
I never realize he had so much hidden passion
beneath that calm exterior.
That makes him so much more cooler!
I'm going to start kicking, too!
Kengo, you the man!
I bet if I put these on,
I can become stronger!
I'll get closer to Class A!
I'm starting to believe that!
You might be right!
You could get closer!
What do you think?
What do you think, Smith?
You think I can be Class A?
His feet are huge!
You're unbalanced.
But that's fine!
Sorry to interrupt
when you're having a good time.
But can I have my shoes back?
S-Sorry!
I-I'm sorry!
Such a giant. So cool.
Look at that trunk.
That's not a professional shogi player's body.
Is it true he's a 5th dan in judo?
I heard he was invited to join
a mixed martial arts organization!
Crap! It's already been 25 minutes?
Our precious 50 minute lunch break
will be over soon!
Hurry! Oh, no!
We've only got time
for the soba shop on the corner!
Nikaidou Family Special
30-Item Bland, Healthy Matsubana Bento
So we've both cleared our first match, huh?
The Newcomer Tournament
is for players 26 years old and younger.
PLUMP
MOIST
LUXURIOUS
CHEW CHEW
Players 5th dan and below can compete.
There are 42 players in the tournament.
CHEW CHEW
However...
NOM NOM
You're always eating healthy but high-class.
You should either eat or talk.
KIRIYAMA
NIKAIDOU
Listen. If we win three more times,
we'll reach the finals.
You and I won't face off
at any rank-deciding competitions this year.
FINALS
WIPE
The Legend Begins!!
You need to hang in there, no matter what,
so we can battle each other in an official game!
"I need to hang in there"?
It sounds like you're pretty confident
about getting to the finals.
Where does that confidence come from?
Listen! Whatever you do, make it to the finals!
That's where our legend begins!
PROJECT X
TOP RUNNER
Meijin Nikaidou's Challenge
~ The Rivals are Best Friends ~
After I become a Meijin,
I'll get featured on a program like Project X,
and they'll show
black-and-white freeze frames of that match!
That's what...
Nikaidou thought...
at the time.
HEARTRENDING
QUIVER
It'll have narration like that!
Hey, you're getting way too deep
into that future outlook of yours.
And, are you crying?
The Newcomer Tournament, huh?
That brings back...
a lot of memories.
GASP
But kid, you should only indulge in such
idle chatter after you beat this old man today.
Got that?
SMILE
A pie in the sky is tasty, but it won't fill you up.
Right! I'm looking forward to our game today.
I'm sorry we interrupted your lunch!
What's your problem, Kiriyama?
He got mad at us because of you!
From the gentle Arimoto 9th-Dan!
GWARRR
No matter how you look at it,
it's all your fault.
Talking loudly about winning a title, becoming
a Meijin, and going on NHK's Top Runner...
Kiriyama, you're always going with that
"Oh, I'm not greedy" air,
acting as if you're watching
with the cool detachment of a spectator,
but I know what's up!
About this Newcomer King, you're like,
"Well, if I play properly,
I can win it without much hassle."
Am I right?
Excuse me?
Wh-Where is that coming from?
What?
"I don't need to make a fuss about the
Newcomer King because of course I'll win it."
"In fact,
regarding the age restriction,
I'm totally confident,
but if I had to worry about anything,
I think I'm getting closer to 6th dan,
so if I don't win soon,
I may miss my chance.
Well, I'll cross that bridge when I come to it.
There are plenty of other title championships,
so I could always work hard for those."
That's more or less what you're thinking
deep in your heart, isn't it?
What? Of course I don't think that.
Where do you come up
with these ridiculous ideas?
Sheesh.
I would never...
I would...
Huh?
Wait.
BLUSH
Kiriyama didn't realize it?
That brat pisses me off.
Geez. That's adorable, though, dammit!
That's what I can't stand about a middle school
child prodigy going professional.
Ticks me off. That idiot!
Look at him blushing, the ninny.
God help me, that's cute.
Relax, Kiriyama!
No matter how puffed up you get with success,
and pretend to be a fake herbivore shogi player,
I won't abandon you over something like that!
The reason is...
I'm the only one who understands you.
(RIVALS)
BEST FRIENDS
Because we're best friends!
This is so embarrassing! I'm the worst!
Hey, wait! We're not done talking!
Oh, man.
He's so shaken.
A fragile teenager.
Just leave him be, Nikaidou.
It's funnier this way.
Kiriyama.
Good grief, Kiriyama. You don't have to worry,
since this was always a den for demons.
You'll only find the strong-willed here,
as arrogant as a fiery soul.
Word of mouth is steadily driving up sales
of our "Puffy-Puffy Daruma."
They're really starting to take root
as a March Town specialty.
And it's all thanks to you girls.
You've made Grandpa really happy.
BOOM
Let's get a specialty
in March Town
And so, would you help me
think of an idea for a new sweet?
This one will be a "summer confection," huh?
Something that looks refreshing,
and would go well with cold, green tea...
Purr-purr...
Have any dried bonito or dried sardines?
I'd be satisfied with just a little.
Can you please pet me a little?
But when it comes to summer, our go-to
is the waterfront series that uses agar, right?
That's right. It's important
to stick to the basics.
It would be perfect if we could
add just a little novelty to that.
SCRIBBLE
Momo, any ideas?
Like, what would be fun
to see floating in the pond?
What do you like?
Let's see...
A duck?
Ducks, huh?
Nice! That'd be cute!
That's my granddaughter!
Oh, but if customers bought it as a souvenir,
the duck could fall off
while they are walking with it.
Good point. As a gift, that shouldn't happen.
What if we sunk it?
Inside the block of agar?
All of a sudden, it's become something else.
Something... kind of sinister?
Momo, any other ideas?
Like something that splashes into the water.
SCRIBBLE
Does that bring anything to mind?
Splashes...
into the water?
A sandal?
I dropped my sandal!
Don't cry.
I'll buy you new ones.
(VISUAL IMAGE)
It dropped in there, huh? It's okay, it's okay.
A sandal, she says?
We've got a child prodigy here!
Could this girl be a blessing
from the god of sweets?
My granddaughter is the best!
That sensibility is fresh and then some!
It'll be a hit!
Grandpa...
CRESCENT MOON
Will Crescent Moon be okay?
Honestly, what are we
going to do with you, Grandpa?
Right, Hina?
Hina!
Sorry for the wait. The bath's open.
What's wrong?
You seem down.
Oh, no. I'm fine.
Well...
I'll go take a bath.
Then don't forget the fire.
You're the last one, so be sure to put it out.
Right, got it.
Good night.
Come to think of it,
she left some food on her plate tonight.
Hina...
I wonder if something happened at school?
June
Ladybug Bush (Part 1)
EGG SALAD SANDWICH
FUJIMORI BAKERY
Thank you!
It's true.
It's really good.
Bought some
for lunch, too
The egg salad sandwich from
the Fujimori Bakery on 2nd Street is delicious!
LOVE
They're open from early in the morning,
so if you have a match, you could buy your
breakfast there and eat it on the way.
LOVE
I love you, Sis!
Fujimori Bakery?
Rei, the doughnuts there are great!
Try them. You have to try them!
If you go there in the evening,
you'll get them freshly-fried.
Maybe I should've gotten doughnuts, too.
Like Hina recommended.
Then I could've had them
as a snack during the match.
In today's open tournament,
the amount of time the players have is short.
It starts at 10,
so I can go in 15 minutes before that.
I still have time, so I'll eat out here.
I've played against today's opponent
a number of times before.
He's good at playing quick games.
Maybe he'll go with the Fujii System...
COFFEE
In that case, it'll be a fast battle.
That bush...
That's right. I remember.
There was one in the yard
of my elementary school.
A ladybug bush.
Out of all the bushes there,
for some reason, ladybugs only laid
their eggs on that bush.
I haven't seen one in a long time.
It makes me feel nostalgic.
Nostalgic?
No, that's not right.
This is... This feeling is...
Uh-oh! He's looking at us!
- I'm scared!
- Four-eyed robot!
You're the one who threw it!
After I lost my parents and little sister
to a car accident,
I became part of
a shogi-playing family in Tokyo.
My school in Nagano
was small and I was alone.
But after coming to Tokyo,
I learned the true meaning
of being alone in my huge new school.
Still, I'd never had a single friend before,
KIRIYAMA THE SHOGI ROBOT
so that was normal for me.
"It's normal."
That's what I tried to think.
SHOGI HALL
I went as far as to make myself unnoticeable
so the direct attacks on me
from my classmates wouldn't escalate.
I was used to that kind of thing,
so I acted indifferent about it every day.
During recess,
I would pretend to be absorbed in a book.
And for lunch break,
I would stand out if I stayed in the room.
So I'd hide in the bushes
in a corner of the schoolyard.
Pass me the ball!
Rook to 2-3, promoted.
CHECKMATE IN FIVE MOVES
TIME TRIAL
Same, King.
Bishop to 1-3, promoted.
King to 3-4.
My adoptive mother was kind.
Good morning.
Morning.
She always smiled with a worried expression.
I did everything I could think of
to please Mother, but...
Wash the rice?
Why don't you have Rei do it?
He's better at it than I am, isn't he?
Clean the bathtub?
You should make Rei do it.
You're always saying
that he's such a good boy, Mom.
The more I helped around the house...
...the more troubled Mother looked.
- Let's have a good game.
Listen, could you quit trying to be
so obvious about scoring points?
She's our mom.
I hate him. He's so creepy.
He's like a robot.
At night, I would get stressed, wondering if
the rest of my life would be like this.
I couldn't even breathe.
And so I tried to become
completely absorbed in shogi,
so I wouldn't have to
think about anything else.
For the longest time,
my days were like bobbing on a sea at night,
with my legs failing to reach the bottom.
All I had that I can cling to...
was this little board.
I would solve every last one
of the composed shogi problems
and read until I broke out into a fever.
Then I moved on
to the untouched shogi game records
in Father's study,
50 years' worth of official matches.
From there, beautifully preserved shogi
game records from the Edo era were stored.
I would study them day and night.
I'd spend all of my days off at the Shogi Hall,
or playing shogi from morning to night
at a shogi dojo Father introduced me to.
I would play, and play, and play,
and play, and keep playing...
I lost.
I would play, and play, and play,
and play, and play,
and play, and play, and play, and play and play.
Akari Kawamoto
Dinner
Come over for
dinner tonight.
We're having
hamburger steak.
Akari
And so, that's how I'm here right now.
Welcome. Oh, doughnuts!
You bought them for us?
FUJIMORI BAKERY
They're still a little warm. Freshly-fried, huh?
GLEAM
I wanna eat doughnuts!
It would be nice to eat them
while they're still warm.
But then we wouldn't have room for dinner.
Hina isn't home yet.
She's late.
What? Can I partake?
Is it okay? Can I have some?
Such long arms!
There she is now.
Welcome home!
I wonder what's wrong. Hina?
That's you, right?
Hina?
Rei...
S-Sis...
Hina!
Ladybug Bush (Part 1)
Next Episode Preview
Episode 26
Rei brought over many books
about beautiful Japanese-style sweets.
I see.
What I thought was the two-spotted ladybug,
was actually called the Asian ladybeetle.
The word for "ladybug"
actually has a kanji?
I didn't know.
ILLUSTRATOR:
KENSHI YONEZU
Go ahead, Momo!
Please watch
"March comes in like a lion" again!
Momo is the world's,
no, the galaxy's best granddaughter!