All units, stay put.
We grab him when he flips off the engine.
Once in a while, O'Neill's tips
actually come in handy.
I'm tired of waiting, Kei.
Let's finish this up and go home.
We're not here on a shopping trip.
This isn't that easy.
Shopping is a lot harder than this.
Doreany shops have far too many things for sale.
You've been here four months.
Get used to it already, country girl.
Country girl?
My Narma is a major city, you know.
Just shut up--
The target's spotted us!
He's getting away!
All units, head in!
Grab the target!
Can we use our guns?
No!
Do not use your weapons!
Block off the runway with your cars!
Leave it to me!
What?
Hey!
Shield of law, protection of the war god!
Stop!
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
Hey, what the hell were you thinking?
Just watch.
Behold the strength of vaifaht steel.
Moron.
Fifteen years ago, a hyperspace gate
appeared in the middle of the Pacific.
Beyond the gate lay a strange world
filled with fairies and monsters.
Kariaena Island. The city of San-Teresa.
This city is Earth's "front door."
Over two million citizens
from this other world live here.
A mixture of different races and
diverse cultures, haves and have-nots...
The world's newest "city of dreams."
But in the shadows of all this chaos
lurked countless crimes.
Drugs. Prostitution. Weapons smuggling.
The San-Teresa Metropolitan Police maintained
a special unit to deal with these crimes.
Two hours in the mud and we didn't find the guy.
If only a certain idiot hadn't brought
the plane down into a swamp...
Hey, are you referring to me?
Is this the smuggled goods?
It's all junk.
What's up?
I smell latena.
Hey, don't touch that without permission.
Who are you?
Officer Hellmandes with the CBP,
Customs and Border Protection.
I don't need your permission.
We're the ones running this case--
You, the ones who let your target get away?
We'll take over here.
We haven't even made a list
of what we've found yet.
So you're refusing a request from the CBP?
Of course not!
It'll just take a little time.
Give us some time.
Do it as fast as possible.
Who's that rude man?
An elite investigator on his way
to the top, I guess.
This is part of the job.
Take a look at it when we get home.
You should be able to get it done tonight.
No fair, Kei!
I'm supposed to take a bath first today!
It's past midnight so it's a new day!
I'm first!
Rakebye! That's not how it works!
Don't you doreany always
talk about "ladies first"?
Are you listening, Kei?
Night!
Dummy.
Oh, when you're out of the bath,
sort through that stuff we found.
I'm going to bed.
You're the only one who
can smell that stuff, right?
And who was it who was snoring
next to me as I drove home?
S-Snoring? I don't...
We need to put that stuff into the
evidence lockers by 11:00 AM tomorrow.
Got it? Goodnight!
Kei is a rude boor!
Everything he does and says makes me so mad!
Don't you think so too?
Right?
He doesn't know how to treat a lady.
You're a lady too, so I believe
you understand my frustration, but...
I thought I smelled strong latena.
Hey, Kuroi! That's bad manners!
Kuroi, you're being a bad girl. Get off--
Hey! Wait! Kuroi!
Oww!
What's this?
Kei...
Kuroi, it's too early in the morning...
What the heck?
Are you still asleep? Your bed is downstairs!
Kei!
Tilarna? Hello?
Knock it off--
Wh-What is going on?
K-Kuroi!
You too? What is going on?
We're late!
Hey, Tilarna! We need to get going!
What are you doing?
Are you not feeling well?
I won't know if you don't tell me.
I know. I know. You need food. Hang on.
Okay, stay home today.
I'll tell the chief you've got some
kind of special alien disease.
Get some sleep, okay?
Oh, right! The garbage!
She left all this out? Jeez.
Kuroi, take care of Tilarna. Be a good girl.
This is terrible...
That bow had a mildey of Moz Nel Valva on it...
She got on top of Kei
wearing practically nothing!
She's like an animal!
Calm down. That's right. Calm down.
First, that crossbow.
It fell off the sofa and into
the garbage can next to it...
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Quenishuba...
Quenishuba!
Oh, no... Oh, no!
Is she... don't tell me...
Stop it, Kuroi!
At least... at least take off your underwear!
No! No! No...
No!
A simple raid ended up with a plane crash?
What the hell happened?
Just like I said.
The local cops screwed up, and...
Shut up!
The Golanbiza county police were
on the phone screaming at me!
At midnight!
My wife was pissed!
Right after I spent the last few days
eating oysters and taking zinc supplements, too!
Chief, was it just the county police?
What?
The complaints you were getting.
Nothing from the CBP?
The CBP?
I talked to their guy Hellmandes this morning,
but he didn't really say anything.
What?
Hey! You got into some kind of fight
with the CBP, didn't you?
Tell me the truth, Matoba! If you did--
Really, there was nothing! We'll talk later.
Hey, Matoba! Wait!
She's still asleep?
I can't take anymore...
I need to do something.
First, that crossbow.
The trash gets picked up in the afternoon.
It should still be in the dumpster.
But I can't get out of this locked
room in the form of a cat!
I need help!
Tilarna? She almost never texts me.
Dear Cecil. I have a serious problem.
Please come to my home as soon
as you can. It's an emergency!
What happened?
"Don't tell Kei"?
Okay, thanks, guys.
Who the hell is Tilarna talking to?
Hello? Tilarna?
I saw your text. What's going on?
Hello, kitty! No, I want to talk to Tilarna!
You don't understand what I'm saying, do you?
Anyway, I'm heading over.
Be a good girl, okay?
Hello?
What the hell is going on?!
With what?
When I was there yesterday,
there were 28 Semanian items found!
And now I've only got 27!
One is missing!
Oh, I see.
That's strange.
Well, it happens, right?
Things were a mess yesterday.
Get me the missing one now,
before I get you arrested for embezzlement!
Come on. It's just a minor screw-up!
Calm the hell down.
Well...
Just get it to me now! Got it?
What the hell is his problem?
Tilarna? Are you there?
Is she not home? Tilarna?
Jeez...
I'm coming inside!
Tilarna?
Hey! What's going on?
You did this, didn't you?
Are you telling me you didn't do it?
What?
I know this is impossible, but...
are you Tilarna?
No way...
You really are...
A mildey did this?
You need the crossbow back?
The tool that caused this?
It's in the dumpster outside?
Why would you put something so important there?
The trash truck?
They'll take the trash away!
Without that bow,
you may not be able to turn back?
Oh, no!
Ce... Ce!
If you're Tilarna, then...
Ce!
Hey!
Hello?
It's me, Matoba.
Is O'Neill in?
I heard he was still living here.
The boss? Just a second.
Man, my head hurts.
Hey, I'm coming in.
Hey there, mister.
Kenny, what the hell is with that outfit?
What? I always sleep like this.
I can't sleep without my pajamas.
And this mess?
There was a party last night.
And the man on the floor?
Um, no idea.
Who is this guy?
Where the hell is O'Neill?
I can't find him...
Last I remembered, he drank
soda water mixed with vodka,
ketchup, and habanero sauce,
and was doing pelvic thrusts on the table...
Where did you get a goat?
I'm not sure. He wasn't here yesterday.
What a mess.
O'Neill isn't here.
Maybe the goat ate him?
That's ridiculous.
I need him to check something for me.
Hey, get off me!
Did I just hear...
Forgive me, Lord, for I am
within your blessings...
Where are you, O'Neill?
It hurts to breathe... It hurts so much...
I will drown within the flesh of your blessings
and come to you in your kingdom...
There you are.
Hey, get off the man, lady.
I'm afraid that's impossible.
When the Virgin Mary gets like this,
she won't wake up for at least 12 hours.
The Virgin Mary? She's a prostitute, right?
Yes. But that's what they call her.
Take this.
Mister, that was mean.
Well, I didn't think she'd react like that.
Shouldn't we call an ambulance?
You're Tilarna, right?
It's not a dream, right?
The garbage truck! What happened to it?
Oh, no!
I need to chase after it!
Are you coming too?
Okay!
First, let's find the garbage truck.
It hasn't been that long,
so it should still be close.
What? Did you find it?
"Lower the blinds. I won't be able
to keep living if someone sees me."
Jeez, we're in a hurry!
Let's hurry!
"Next time"
Next time on COP CRAFT.