This world has one type of currency: gold.
The standard cost for the items in
a single meal is around five gold.
A night at a cheap inn is ten gold.
Thirty-five gold a day will suffice
to supply life's basic needs.
You can earn that much by defeating six goblins.
And adventurers
can put money and items in
the guild building's bank,
to keep them from being stolen by others.
Of course, any one person's
account has limited space.
I need money.
For now,
five million gold.
That's insane!
Our treasury only has sixty thousand.
Even if we included all our members' belongings...
What would you use all that money for?
Imperial Garden Forest
Japan Server
League of Freedom Cities, Eastal/ Shinjuku
Field/ Monsters Present
Entry Restrictions/ None
Events/ None Currently
Imperial Forest Boar, Lv. 18
Rank/ Normal
It's pretty tough to catch them alive...
If you kill them, they just become ingredient items.
It's impossible...
That huge boar becomes a mere
two kilograms of meat!
But with a good cook, if you catch them
alive, you can use the entire thing.
Okay, let's do this!
Our quota for today is sixty!
Okay!
If it's for Marie,
I'll catch as many as you need!
That isn't quite right.
Something easier to move in would be nice.
Let's see what clothes we have in the bank.
Okay!
Taste this!
Let me see...
It needs a little salt.
And add coriander as a secret ingredient.
Okay, thank you!
Nyanta is so wonderful...
Crescent Moon
Crescent Moon.
I haven't left the room for three days...
I can't take this anymore...
We need these registers for our plan.
Look through and approve them.
Wait, it's impossible... That's impossible!
It is, indeed.
You know paperwork isn't really my thing.
Approving budgets is your job, guild master.
Shut up, shut up...
Stupid Umeko!
Don't use my real name!
Umeko! Umeko! Umeko!
I've brought more, Marie.
Shiro, you're a demon...
Shiroe, I've compiled a list of
everything you requested.
That was fast!
And the numbers are accurate.
Our treasurer is amazing.
The devil himself would run
if he saw her coming with a stack of budgets.
No, there are limits to my abilities.
What amazes me is the
mercilessness of Shiroe's plans.
He should just call himself Mr. Super Villain.
Compared to Marie's spaciness,
my villainy is nothing.
That's true!
I give up...
Anyway, there's so much work,
having Akatsuki for a full day is
the only way I can keep going.
She's on a separate mission right now,
but she could probably spare a bit of time.
Oh, my!
Is catching a cold even possible in this world?
Here's the money for this week.
This is a great way to earn money.
Thank you.
Tell Isaac hello for me.
Hey, I heard you started dealing
in leather-working, too.
We're open twenty-four hours a day,
and can repair things quickly.
Well, now... This is quite the haul.
Now it's up to you, chief!
Naotsugu! Thank you!
Rub, rub, rub, rub!
Hey...
Don't cling to me!
Marie, behave yourself.
Shouryuu and Hien, thank you both, also!
He was all fired up.
No, you're just good at slacking off!
Who's slacking off?
You loyal little puppy!
Shut up, you flippant fox!
But there still isn't enough.
I'm on it!
I don't know why, but he's really into this...
I can always count on you, Shouryuu!
No more!
This is all the paperwork.
Then, I'll return to my own job.
Now I'm scared of glasses.
The glasses all frighten me!
Ta-da!
Oh, it's wonderful!
Cute and distinctive.
It's amazing how nice handmade stuff looks.
Now we're almost done.
It's finally time...
What do you think, Henrietta?
In the old world, weren't you an accountant,
with a master's in business administration?
I think it can work.
Basically, we just need to get
the money, any way we can.
We don't have to worry about where
it came from or whose it was.
At the moment, this world has no rules.
There's no point in restricting
ourselves by making new ones.
This world has no rules...
In other words, we can make up our own...
We need a new rule to make money.
A way to make people bring us money,
and be happy doing so...
We can do it.
Five million gold.
We can get the money.
Now it's time for the plan's first stage.
Marie, I brought you a snack.
Chief Nyanta made this sandwich himse—
I can't go on!
Stupid Umeko, I hate you!
Hey, come on...
I can't take this room anymore.
I want a bath.
I want to go outside!
Okay... Okay, Marie...
Easy there.
This is great!
Hey...
Hmm?
Thanks for going along with Shiro's plan.
Eh?
I think it made him happy that you agreed.
Thank you.
You're a good boy, Naotsugu...
Good boy, good boy.
I'm glad you're with Shiro.
Keep being his friend.
Y-Yeah...
So, tomorrow's the day.
Yeah, tomorrow.
Hey...
Before we head into the field,
let's grab something to eat.
Does it matter what?
Everything tastes the same, anyway.
Don't say that.
Anyway, this place sure is deserted...
Of course it is.
Well, if it all tastes the same,
the cheapest food is as good as any...
I smell something good.
No way.
Hello, residents of Akihabara!
For those of you who miss real food,
we have good news.
Now you can bring genuine
flavor back to your table!
The Crescent Moon refreshment stand opens today!
Please give it a try!
Thank you! Thank you for your purchase!
Serara, we haven't sold any yet.
"Crescent Burger, fifteen gold.
One crispy chicken strip, eighteen gold...
Black rose tea, five gold."
That's pretty pricey!
What noisy, strange people.
Mister, care to take a
leap of faith and try one?
You'll be amazed at how good it is.
Ah, th-then... I'll take a Crescent Burger.
Or she will.
Me?!
Thank you.
One Crescent Burger coming right up.
Thank you!
This smell...
No, even if it smells good...
It either tastes like nothing or like salt.
Give it a try!
What is this?
Huh?
It tastes like a hamburger!
What?!
Hey, I want one, too!
Me, too!
It tastes like grilled meat and sauce...
It's so good!
We can't just stand here!
Let's go tell Sou!
I'll take three Crescent Burgers!
Don't cut in line!
Five crispy chicken strips!
I'll take one of everything on the menu!
End of Line
Um... Um, this is the end of the line.
Thank you for staying in line!
We only have one box of burgers left!
Eh? Really?
Don't worry, Marie.
I'm bringing more.
This is where things will get tough.
We'll go at full speed!
This is...
Delicious?
Who made this?
How?
Have you tried the Crescent Burger?
I heard it's food that actually tastes like food.
Not just ingredient items? Seriously?
This flavor, at this price.
I wonder if we can get in on this...
Trouble, boss!
Look at this!
You're too slow on the draw, Kayu...
This is good, though.
Investigate the shop.
Who's running it, what they use for
ingredients, and how they get them.
Everything you can find!
Right!
This will change the world.
Okay, that's enough for now.
Let's go, kids.
Right!
I will gather more.
You two, go on back.
Don't push yourself... There's a long way to go.
No.
I don't want to lose.
Huh? To whom?
Then, let's go.
Is he okay?
He'll be fine...
Just watch me,
Marie.
I...
A-An area boss?
You're joking.
Good work, everyone.
Well? Well?
How much did we make?
We earned 43,776 gold in sales,
representing 1,159 customers who
spent an average of 38 gold each.
We sold out the crescent burgers we prepared,
Cheers!
as well as everything else,
except the black rose tea.
Wow!
This is great!
At this rate, we'll get that five
million in no time at all!
We'll never make it in time...
Not even close, Marie.
We won't?
Basic math shows it would take
one hundred, twenty days...
Or four months.
But today, we turned away a lot of customers...
If we wanted, we could sell a lot more.
Our total market size probably
measures in the tens of thousands.
In Akihabara alone, there are
over fifteen thousand players.
The problem is,
no matter how high the demand,
we can only serve around a
thousand customers a day.
Our guild just isn't big enough.
That's it.
Money isn't the point of this plan, anyway.
That's right.
I was just blinded by the huge
fortune in front of me.
I'll go deposit our earnings in the bank.
Thanks.
Hey, Shiro.
If money wasn't the Crescent Burger's goal,
does that mean you'll use your other plan?
I'm sure it'll work.
But I don't know if I can do it.
Just leave it to Henrietta.
Right?
Yes.
Leave it to me.
In exchange...
Where are you going?
My lord has given me a secret mission!
Don't try to stop me!
Shiroe was kind enough to lend you to me.
My lord, you sold me out again!
Now, hurry...
Put this on!
I refuse!
I am not a doll for you to dress up!
You can't enter that room.
What?
This zone belongs to the Crescent Moon Alliance.
Zone Setting:                                                                                Guild Hall 236
Entry Restrictions Active                                              Guild Master: Marielle
Guild: Crescent Moon Alliance
ID Recognition                                                                       Zone Information:
Akatsuki   Guild/ Log Horizon                                          No Combat Allowed
Access: Not Allowed                                                          No Skill Use Allowed
And that warehouse only permits guild members.
I guess I'll have to...
Skills
Zone Information
This zone does not
permit skill use.
I can't use it?
It's useless...
I set it so that skills can't be used here.
And I can also set combat
permissions individually.
Have you forgotten?
Curse you...
So cute!
My, my...
It looks wonderful on you.
Ah! My exhaustion is flying away!
Hey, have you seen Shouryuu?
Now that you mention it, he's late.
He was so excited, he hasn't
returned from hunting...
R-Really?
Maybe something happened...
What's going on?
There's a boar stuck in the hall.
Shouryuu...
Marie, am I helping a little?
Shouryuu!
Eh?
He hasn't rested or slept for a long time.
He's been killing himself.
Thank goodness...
Thank you, everyone.
I'm blessed with such wonderful companions.
He looks so happy in his sleep.
Guess it was worth almost killing himself.
After all that work, I'm sorry to say this...
But giant boar tastes too strong,
so I can't use it.
Shh!
You'll wake him up!
The Crescent Moon Alliance
members are all so nice.
Yes...
I'm sure it's due to Marie's kindness
and sunflower-like smile.
Actually, I've made a guild of my own.
I'll introduce you to them soon.
Our preparations are progressing.
Hold out just a little longer.
It'll be okay,
Minori... Tohya.
Zone Setting:                                                                                Guild Hall 185
Entry Restrictions Active                              Guild Master: Twilight Explorer
Guild: Hamelin
ID Recognition                                                                       Zone Information:
Shrayda   Guild/ Hamelin                                                        Combat Allowed
Access: Allowed                                                                       Skill Use Allowed
Shiroe said that?
Yeah.
I see.
Is this okay?
Is this really okay?
Chief, did you know this?
When this was a game,
these buildings were just background.
But now they appear to be zones for purchase.
So it seems.
And that isn't all...
Every city and building in the world is for sale.
But they're astronomically expensive.
Then should we buy Tokyo Station
as the Log Horizon base?
No.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Shiro and Master Nyanta, it's been a long time.
Hey, Soujirou.
Souji, I hear you've started your own guild?
Yes, it's called the Caravan of the West Wind.
Soujirou Theta
Race/ Human
Samurai, Lv. 90
Caravan of the West Wind
It's a small guild, but as powerful
as the biggest ones.
Not at all...
We were just getting things set up
when the Apocalypse happened.
Since the Tea Party disbanded,
I hadn't been logging in as often.
Are Nazuna and Miss Saki still with you?
Nazuna is still with me.
She's as relaxed as ever.
Saki, too, but she wasn't logged
in during the Apocalypse.
Hey, so, um...
Are you still as popular with
girls as you used to be?
No, well...
It's nice to be young.
A-Anyway...
Why did you contact me?
Oh, you see...
I thought you didn't like me.
Hmm? Why?
Because, well...
When I founded my guild,
I invited you, but you didn't join.
It wasn't like that.
It wasn't that I didn't like you.
Back then, I just didn't want
anything to do with guilds.
But after the Apocalypse, I realized
that I had to make a place for myself...
That I have to be one of those
that protects others.
I made a guild.
There aren't many in it yet,
and it's just getting started...
But I'll only have a place for myself
after I've made one for others.
I finally realized that.
So what did you want from me?
What do you think of Akihabara, as it is now?
I think it's a prison...
A prison?
Not only Akihabara.
Depending on your point of view,
this whole world is currently a prison.
I have a way to improve it.
And I need your help.
All right!
Huh? Are you sure?
Don't you want to hear the plan?
But you're busy, aren't you?
I can't take up your time.
And I'm a moron whose place
is in the front row.
Even if the Tea Party's best
strategist told me the plan,
I wouldn't understand half.
Soujirou...
You're a good kid, Souji.
No...
I have more burgers!
I'll take three Crescent Burgers!
Five super Crescent Burgers!
While you wait, I'll take your orders!
You're so cute...
Please add me to your Friends List.
Hey, stay in line, and follow the rules!
Oh, so this Shiro guy wanted
you to help with the store?
Of course not.
It's far more than just this.
There's no end
to his plans.
Now, then... Time for the plan's second stage.
Michitaka, of the Marine Agency.
Karashin, of Shopping Street 8.
Roderic, of the Roderic Merchant Guild.
Masters of the largest crafting
guilds gather in one place.
Their trading partners are the Crescent
Moon's sunflower and lily,
Marielle and Henrietta.
And the shadow that manipulates
them from behind...
Next time: Villain in Glasses.
Villain in Glasses
This is our reality.