Hey, little boy! That thing
I asked you to do yesterday—
Right, right!
Those limited edition figurines from
Akiba and the yokan from Masuya, right?
I already got them for you.
Well, well! Aren't you Mr. Competent?
Dammit, who would've thought
Ms. Hana was such a callous mom!
Just you wait... I'll
get back at you for this!
Chitoge! Over here, over here!
Thanks for waiting, you two!
It's another chilly day, huh?
Where should we shop today?
Hey, you're not wearing
your usual ribbon today?
Is this a make-over?
Uh, yeah, I guess you could call it that.
Oh? Well, I think that one
looks good on you, too!
Hey, by the way, what's going on
with that Christmas party?
You know, Shu's idea...
Looks like it's a go for tomorrow!
We're inviting people from our
class, and we'll all be there, too.
Today we're getting
gifts for the grab bag.
Would you mind if I came, too?
"Mother"
Here.
The reservation for your company dinner
and all the schedule adjustments are done!
Please give me my next task!
Oh, my, you took care of
that quicker than I thought.
What on earth has gotten into you?
Your work has been
stellar the last few days.
Well, not that you haven't
been a godsend.
It looks like I'll have to add
a generous tip to your paycheck!
I'm getting paid?
Of course you are.
Those who work must be compensated.
It's a rule of society.
Also...
I've already made that
hotel reservation for you.
You've passed.
I'm sure it will be fine,
entrusting her to you.
As a mother, I don't know
if it's appropriate to say this,
but go on and have as much fun
as high school kids should!
I don't want a paycheck.
Or the hotel room, needless to say.
But...
I do have one favor to ask of you.
If I work extra hard,
and that gives you some extra time
tomorrow on Christmas Eve,
do you think you can
go see Chitoge?
What are you talking about...?
I know you can do it!
If I keep up this pace and work to death,
I can open up some time for you!
Isn't that right?
Well, I suppose...
Can you go or can't you? Which is it?
Well, of course it's a possibility, but...
That's all I need to hear.
I'm getting back to work.
Oh, hey - wait!
It could be that I'm only
butting in needlessly.
Same as the other day - it's like
I will end up hurting her.
But...
I can't leave things like this...
that would be too cruel to poor Chitoge!
I don't know if it'll fix things
between them if they meet up,
but I want to do whatever
I can for her, at least!
All the work I was supposed to do
this month... It's all right here.
And judging by your
recent tendencies,
everything you might need
as gifts for your clients...
I've gone out and purchased them all.
My, you do amaze me.
I've done everything that
I possibly could. Ms. Hana...
I'm asking you now! Please go see her!
Oh, I won't be going. Not me.
Why not?!
If it's a matter of time,
you've got that!
Well, then, at least just a second!
Just give her this!
What is that?
It's a present.
I went out and bought it.
There's a scarf inside.
Please give it to her!
Not another one. Didn't I
tell you there was no need?
But that's not really
up to you, is it, Ms. Hana?
I'm telling you, you're overstepping!
You're sticking your nose into other
families' business way too much.
Ms. Hana, don't you want to see her?
Well, it's not really as if I don't...
I see... Is that it, then?
So you never had the slightest interest
in Chitoge from the start, huh?
If you've opened up my schedule,
then that's convenient for me.
All I have to do is book
another appointment.
Why, you...
Enough is enough!
I did get her something,
but it seems I won't get a chance
to give it to her this year, either.
Uh, Ms. Hana... is that...
It's a present. For Christmas.
They've just been piling up
for the last ten years.
Every single year, I get her one,
and then end up not being
able to give it to her, see.
Ms. Hana, did you just eat...
Oh, this?
This is just a chocolate cigarette.
Didn't you used to
eat these as a child?
As for real cigarettes,
once I became pregnant
with Chitoge, I quit cold turkey.
Wh-What the...?
Uh... But I thought you didn't
have any interest in Chitoge?
Why would you think that?
Well, because...
You forgot all about
Chitoge's ribbon,
and you always
forget how old she is.
Of course I'd never forget!
That's the ribbon
I gave her, you know!
Wh-Whaaaaat did you say?!
Well, come on,
that girl's still wearing that cheap
ribbon I gave her ten years ago!
When I'm sure she can find something
that would become her more.
As for her age, of course I remember!
It's just that... when I'm
with her, I get so nervous...
that I start out by asking her age.
No, no, no!
That will only backfire on you!
Isn't she an amazing girl?
I told you this before, didn't I?
If you have the ability,
it's your duty to exercise it.
That girl is gifted with
marvelous abilities.
If she put her mind to it, she could
far surpass both Adelt and myself.
Not only that, but she's
a beauty, just like me.
So like me...
I've raised her quite strictly.
But I'm sure I was far too strict.
Before I knew it,
she stopped calling me "Mom."
I'm sure she must
really hate me now.
Is that why you came up with the idea of
sending us to a hotel on Christmas Eve?
That's because I thought
that would make her happier.
Am I wrong?
This woman...
Dammit, so that was it, huh?
I finally see it now!
Ms. Hana?
You moron!
Ouch!
Why, you... How dare you do such a thing to me...
You've got it wrong on the most basic level!
She doesn't hate you at all!
She's needed you all this time!
Even now!
She was totally looking forward to
spending Christmas Eve with you!
Even now, except
when she's with you,
she still calls you "Mom," you know!
Please, go see her!
You can still make it!
But...
I'm supposed to head
to the U.S. after this today.
What should I do?
Then... how much
time do you have?
Three hours before
my flight takes off.
Crap, that's cutting it close!
Ms. Hana, once you've finished
getting ready for your trip,
please wait at that five-star suite!
And I'll bring Chitoge to you!
But...
Damn,
here I was, thinking Ms. Hana
was a wizard at her job...
but other than that, she's
nothing but an airhead!
I guess the apple doesn't
fall too far from the tree!
Look, look outside! It's snowing!
Oh, yeah? It's a white Christmas!
I bet something wonderful's
in store for us this year.
Young Mistress, aren't you
cold standing there?
Please come over here.
By the way, when will
Master Raku be arriving?
Oh, right, I'm sure he'll be here soon.
Hey, Mom! I want
a ribbon just like this!
All right, you can have one.
Take good care of it, okay?
I wonder when things
got like this between us?
I used to be able to
talk to her, just like that...
Is it always going to be like this?
Mom and me...
Never...
Chitoge!
What, what, what?
Chitoge, are you there?
Raku?
Oooooooh! Master Raku!
What are you doing here?
Aren't you supposed to be with my mom?
No time to explain!
Just come with me, all right?
Hey...
Hold up a second! This is so sudden!
At least tell me where!
All right, then...
To a five-star hotel suite!
Ms. Hana Kirisaki
This is a boarding time change notification.
As the snow is predicted to become heavier,
the charter flight you have reserved will be leaving earlier than scheduled.
Please be sure to be on time.
It's no good, Ichijo!
The heavy snow up north is
causing a major traffic jam.
This car isn't going anywhere!
Are you serious?
Not at a time like this...
Hey, hold up a second!
Tell me what's going on!
My bad!
I promise to bring it
back right away!
Hey!
That hotel you mentioned...
it's the one Mom was
talking about, right?
No way am I going!
Why would I go with you?!
Ms. Hana is waiting for you there!
I'm taking you to see her, so just
shut your mouth and sit there!
Mom's there? Why?
Well, Ms. Hana... Sure, she said a lot of
things that could be taken the wrong way,
and I wouldn't blame you
if you didn't believe me, but...
The truth is, she really,
really cares about you!
No way...
No way could that be...
No way could I ever believe that!
Believe it!
For once in your life,
why don't you just...
Trust in me!
She's gone?
Yes. She said her flight was
leaving early because of the snow.
The airport, then! Come on, hurry!
Okay!
The snow is intensifying.
Please hurry.
If you were to miss this meeting,
it will mean a loss of several
billion yen for our company.
We're not gonna make...
It's not too late!
Please ditch that appointment, Ms. Hana!
Little boy...
Thank you, little boy.
But that's enough, all right?
It made me happy to hear
how Chitoge feels about me,
but... I've got to go.
Please give her my regards, will you?
There you go, blaming it
on your work...
The truth is, you're
just scared, aren't you?!
A woman your age, what
are you doing running away?!
Which is more important,
your work, or her?
I want you to think
long and hard about that!
Mom...
Please...
Mom!
Mom?
Chitoge...
I-I...
I...
Do you...
Do you still love your mom?
I do... love you...
Even though you're scary...
And I never get to see you,
and even when you're with me,
all you do is yell at me...
And even though you never
even look at me...
And I have no idea
what you're thinking...
And did I mention that
I'm terrified of you?
But I still love you!
Chitoge!
Mom!
What the heck...
Just as I thought,
they're two of a kind.
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry, Chitoge!
Mom! Mom!
Ms. Hana?
It's too cold for you to have
a long heart-to-heart here.
I'm going to head back to the office,
and deal with the aftermath
as best I can,
so you go on to the hotel
and spend a relaxing Christmas
Eve with her, all right?
You need to dial down
the heroics, little boy.
Come on, you can make
an exception. For today...
...as a "Merry Christmas," okay?
Come to think of it,
I still haven't given you your
Christmas present, have I?
Here you go.
A new ribbon - I picked it out for you!
It does make me very happy to know
that you treasure that ribbon.
But you are a girl, after all...
Thank you, Mom.
But...
I still want to go on
treasuring this one.
Since this one brings back
so many memories.
I see.
I'm sure that will make that
boy very happy as well.
Raku? Why?
What, have you forgotten?
That boy is the reason you started
wearing that ribbon, you know.
Ten years ago, you and that boy spent
a summer playing together, see,
and there was a girl
wearing a ribbon like that
in one of the picture books
you adored at the time.
And that boy said to you, "I bet
this ribbon would look good on you."
And you rushed over
to pester me for one.
Don't you remember?
He said that?
Why don't you go to him? Chitoge...
It was all thanks to that boy that
I got to have this long talk with you.
He's your boyfriend, isn't he?
You should go to him.
Okay.
If you sleep here,
you'll catch a cold.
Stupid bean sprout...
There, now...
Thank you, Raku.
Thank you, little boy.
I really owe you one.
I never thought you'd help me out
this much, both in business and in private.
Still, to think that
I'd be reunited like this with that little boy
who played with Chitoge ten years ago...
It really is a strange
twist of fate, isn't it?
Ms. Hana, you were there,
too, ten years ago?
Well, just for a few days.
But I remember you very well.
Um... Ms. Hana...
Does this locket look
at all familiar to you?
There's something about that
time that I want to remember.
But I just can't seem to recall it.
I don't think I can
help you with that. Sorry.
I see.
Little boy,
come here for a second.
Okay.
Listen... I hear you and Chitoge are just
pretending to be dating, aren't you?
Ms. Hana... you knew all along?
Of course I did.
Well, not from the start, but still...
Then you should've told us.
Now I feel stupid for
going all-out to fake it!
I'm starting to feel embarrassed.
Faking it, eh?
If I work extra hard, do you
think you can go see Chitoge?
I'm asking you now! Please go see her!
Is this really nothing
but a sham, I wonder?
Are your feelings for that girl
really nothing more than a sham?
All right, then - please
look after my daughter.
After Chitoge and I saw Ms. Hana off,
I got a call from Shu.
Apparently, they were
under the impression
that Chitoge and I had spent
the night in a hotel suite,
and wanting to know what we'd
been up to, they interrogated us.
Though we did manage to
straighten them out,
it ended up being
a hell of a Christmas.
Hey, now I remember.
That locket...
It's the one that came out
in Chitoge's picture book.
Oh, well, till the next time I see him.
I wonder how many years will
go by before we meet again?
What? You're heading over now?
The Christmas party ended hours ago!
Oh, Ruri, telling me the trains weren't
running... don't give me that!
You were really asleep till now, right?
We really had our
hands full, you know.
Yes...
I really am glad that
it was a misunderstanding.
What? Oh, that's okay,
no need for apologies!
You use that present
yourself, all right?
No, I don't want it!