One more! Give me another!
Shut up. I know that.
Here goes.
Yeah.
Gosh, that feels good.
I feel the heft of the ball,
snug in my palm.
I love that.
All right.
We'll use our quick offense against Neko!
Neko?
A match against Nekoma?
It'll be a practice match
on the last day of Golden Week.
Yikes.
What do you mean, "yikes"?
Hey, don't run away.
But you're scary when you get mad.
I'm not mad right now.
Well, Nekoma sounds
like ancient history to us.
Our generation doesn't have the same
Karasuno-Nekoma rivalry.
Although... "Cat vs Raven:
Battle at the Garbage Dump."
We've heard the stories about Neko.
It'll be our fist match with them in years.
It does pique your interest, doesn't it?
But I've lost face with Suga and Nishinoya.
You're too much.
You're still a goofball
in a big body, as usual.
What a contrast to Nishinoya.
Can't you sugarcoat your words a little?
Don't worry about Suga and Nishinoya.
They're fine.
Unlike you, they have big hearts.
I always thought of you as a kind person...
Was I wrong?
I'm kind to everyone, except you.
Because you're a goofball.
You ditched us for a whole month,
you complain about your anxiety...
but those things don't matter to me.
If you still like volleyball,
that's reason enough to come back.
Oh, yeah.
We've got a guy who
hopes to become the ace.
Ouch.
Haikyu!!
Foothill Store
By the shores of the
coursing Hirose River,
Episode 9:  A Toss to the Ace
memories do not return.
Amidst the dancing lights of Hayase...
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm sorry. I was checking to see
if you had any customers.
You're here about the coaching
thing again, aren't you?
Yes.
I still like to play.
I even have a local team.
But I don't want to coach. It's stuffy.
I see...
And I don't want to go
to that gymnasium, either.
D-Do you have bad memories or something?
The very opposite.
The place is filled with
fond memories of my youth.
Then, why?
That gym and club room may still be the same,
but I can never go back.
It was a limited time with
its own distinctive feel.
The atmosphere belongs
to that place and time alone.
So it's nostalgia.
How nice.
Shut up.
That's why I don't want to go back.
Even if Nekoma High School were coming?
We're having a practice match
at the end of Golden Week.
The first match in five years.
B-But wh-why now?
Their director, Nekomata, who was
close friends with Director Ukai,
just came out of retirement.
When I heard that, I requested
a practice match.
When you were there, Ukai-kun,
wasn't that when the Nekoma rivalry
was at its peak?
Yeah.
And I hear their coach now was
Nekoma's setter seven or eight years ago.
This year is our last chance, Ukai.
Promise to definitely,
definitely see us at the nationals.
Yeah.
I promise.
That was when you were playing, too.
Maybe you know him?
Hey...
You trying to seduce me?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Are you kidding?
You think I'll fall for such an obvious ploy?
What time does practice start?
I'm sor— Huh?
Um...
So Nekoma is coming.
I can't let them see my successors
in a pitiful state.
I'm gearing up.
Go there and wait.
Y-Yes.
Mom! Mind the store for me.
All right.
Hello, Tatsu-san?
Maturing to Greatness
Say, Noya-san.
Huh?
What kind of training did you
do while you were suspended?
Hm, mainly block-follow.
Training for saving balls
after they're blocked.
I still can't do it well,
but if I get good at block-follow,
you guys can spike with greater confidence.
This guy...
He has a new bruise every time I see him.
Noya-san, are you for real?
You're such an awesome guy.
What're you crying about?
Good job, everyone.
Huddle up.
Let me introduce you.
This is Ukai-kun, who will
be our coach starting today.
C-Coach?
Is this true?
Only 'til the match against Nekoma.
Oh...
But this is the guy from Foothill Store.
He's really a coach?
He's a senpai to all of you.
He's the grandson of Director Ukai.
What?
But that's not the name on your store.
The store's named after
my mother's side of the family.
We got no time to waste.
Let's get started.
I want to see what you guys are made of.
The game will start at 6:30 PM.
The opponents have already been invited.
Huh? Opponents?
The Karasuno neighborhood association team.
If you still like volleyball,
that's reason enough to come back.
Here goes.
Okay!
Damn, they're not coming.
I guess it's impossible
to get everyone on a weekday.
Here.
Thank you very much.
Hey.
Wow.
Brings back memories.
Um...
The team Neighborhood Association...
...is here!
Hey, guys, thanks for coming on short notice.
I was expecting geezers from
a neighborhood association.
Me, too.
All right!
Let's get started.
Yeah.
It's a match!
Hey, you. What's the matter?
Oh, I'm sorry. He's sort of...
What? He has a problem? Is he injured?
No, it's not that kind of thing...
What, you're not injured?
Whatever the case,
I need you on the neighborhood team.
Their libero has to work.
He couldn't make it.
Well, maybe...
We need two more.
How many extras have you got?
Hey, it's Asahi-san!
Asahi-san!
This guy again...
I... I... um...
Asahi-san?
You're late! Who do you think you are?
What's your position?
Wing spiker...
We're short of players.
Hurry up and take your position!
Chop chop!
All we need is another setter.
I wish I could do it,
but I have to watch the game.
I need to borrow a setter from you guys.
Sugawara-san.
You're not doing this for me, are you?
If you're stepping down
so I can step up, I'll refuse.
Ever since Kageyama joined
the team as official setter,
I've been relieved.
The setter is the pillar
of our team's offense.
He must be the toughest of everyone.
But I never felt confident
about throwing tosses.
I've been scared
the spikers would repeatedly
be blocked because of my tosses.
So I hid behind Kageyama's
overwhelming abilities,
and enjoyed the relief.
When I think of spikes getting blocked...
It still scares me.
But...
Let me toss to you again, Asahi.
That's why I'll be on their team.
Kageyama.
I won't let you outplay me.
I won't, either.
Nishinoya, I'm counting
on your nice receives.
That goes without saying.
All right. Let's get ready.
Asahi-san's here. Right?
Yeah. For now, anyway.
Karasuno     Neighborhood Assoc.
Let's play.
They definitely have an
intimidating presence.
Let's do it, high schoolers.
It's a battle against the ace...
Karasuno     Neighborhood Assoc.
Nice receive.
Hey, good one. Nice toss.
Thank you very much.
Sugawara-san's fast attack!
Of course. Suga is an
experienced setter, after all.
He looks happy...
Suga-san, nice toss!
Yeah.
But the neighborhood folks are
skillfully accommodating me.
They're veterans, for sure.
All right.
My tosses still need a lot of work.
But, I have to use lots of fast attacks,
and confidently keep building offense.
Otherwise, the whole match will be
on the ace's shoulders again.
Suga-san, you've become awesome.
Huh? Really?
That's high praise coming
from you, Nishinoya.
Why's that?
Oh, well...
Suga, you've grown dependable
in the short time I've been away.
And Nishinoya is dependable, as usual.
No, seriously, you've become awesome.
I, on the other hand,
came moseying back, and am standing
on the court without a purpose.
I feel pathetic.
But...
Nice serve.
One more.
But...
I like being here.
What was that?
All right!
Yes.
That was an amazing jump.
Amazing. That toss was perfection itself.
Nice, Hinata, Kageyama.
But now I have this guy tossing to me,
so I can get past any blocker.
All the blockers vanish from sight...
and the view of the other side
of the net opens up.
The other side of the net...
Don't mind.
One more.
68th Prefecture Sporting Competition
Volleyball Tournament
Karasuno Gymnasium
Indoor Sports Arena
Idate Ind                Karasuno
It's a feint. In front!
Nice, Noya-san.
Asahi.
Iron Wall of Idate
Idate Industrial High School Volleyball Club supporters association
Damn.
He missed, but still, that libero is amazing.
I'm sorry. I'll get the next one.
Yeah. His skills are amazingly high-level.
But the offense is weak...
Blocked again...
I've lost count of how many
they've blocked.
I kept calling for a toss.
"Bring it to me."
"I will score."
But I've reached the very end.
I'm scared to call for a toss.
Asahi-san?
Asahi?
Suga, to the right.
Da-Daichi!
Idate Ind                Karasuno
Damn it!
I couldn't follow on any of the blocks.
Dashing
Full Force
Why? Why aren't you berating me?
We lost because of me.
No matter how much you followed,
if I can't spike and score, it's all for nothing!
Asahi.
What do you mean "it's all for nothing"?
Then why didn't you call
for a toss at the end?
You were in a position to spike.
Stop it, Nishinoya.
I was only bringing the ball to Asahi.
He must've been tired.
Toss to me all you want.
I'll never score.
You don't know that 'til you spike.
Maybe the next one will score!
I kept the ball in the air.
It's not your place to give up.
Noya!
I'm a libero. I'm essential to defense.
I'm the cornerstone of the team!
But...
I'm not the one who can score points.
I can't attack.
I don't care if your spikes don't score.
I would never berate you in the least.
But I won't stand for you
giving up so selfishly.
A-Asahi-san.
Asahi.
Wait, Asahi.
Why didn't you show up at club yesterday?
Soon after New Year,
it'll be the Inter-High.
It's no fun hitting spikes that don't score.
What am I saying?
I don't think that at all.
You, too. You save the ball,
but if no one scores,
it's all in vain.
Stop it.
Nishinoya isn't a guy that thinks like that.
Suga felt responsible every
time my ball got blocked—
Who cares about the other guys?
Hey, who's shouting?
Don't make noise in the hall.
Asahi-san.
Hey.
Shut up!
How dare you!
He did that in front of the dean.
Don't you want to spike and score again?
Nice, Hinata.
Thanks!
Hinata, you serve next.
That's what I want.
No matter how many times I fail,
I still want to spike.
Then, I'm fine.
Now that you said that, I'm fine.
My job is to keep the ball in play.
That's all.
Hinata, nice serve!
Net in!
Whoops.
Sorry! Cover for me.
Long-hair guy, you do last.
The sky is the domain of spikers.
I can't do battle up there...
Let's block 'em.
Don't give orders.
Asahi-san, I'm blocking you for real.
If I keep the ball in play...
as long it stays connected...
I want to spike again.
I know the ace will score for us.
He saved it.
Nice follow.
Mainly block-follow.
Training in saving balls that get blocked.
Noya-san...
Even if the ball bounces off the wall...
I'll keep it in play.
So call for a toss again,
ace!
Cover.
All right.
What should I do?
Who do I toss it to?
The left is open.
That might be the best, but...
If I toss to Asahi and
he gets blocked again...
Sugawara-san.
Give it to him
'til he scores.
You're a total sadist, King.
What?
When the going gets rough,
when the receive is tenuous,
the last ball is entrusted to the ace.
I know. I know it,
but Asahi isn't waiting for a toss,
and I'm putting him on the
spot against three blockers.
The spike...
I can spike because the toss goes up.
Let me toss to you again, Asahi.
The toss goes up because
of the connecting receive.
I kept the ball in the air.
It's not your place to give up.
I'm not the only one who spikes.
Everybody plays his own respective part.
And yet, I...
You don't win alone.
That's just how it is.
That's why everyone calls
you an ace, Asahi-san.
If you still like volleyball...
Call for a toss again,
ace!
All right.
Shimada-san－
Suga!
One more!
Ah,
the ace awaits.
He's calling for a toss.
A high toss, slightly away from the net.
The toss, Asahi's speciality,
which I've tossed to him many times.
Even if it's just a plain toss,
give it all you got... carefully...
You're rooting for the
other team, aren't you?
Well, sorry to say it,
but I'm blocking them.
Of course. What's the point of holding back?
The dependable guardian behind me...
The easy-to-spike tosses he sends me...
I lack for nothing.
I had forgotten such simple,
obvious things...
I'm...
...not fighting this battle alone.
To strike past all obstacles...
That's the ace.
Next Episode Preview
Tanaka-senpai, stop crying
and block properly.
Jackass, I'm not crying! This is...
Sweat? Oh, sure, that's what that is.
My nose is running!
Episode 10: Yearning
Next time on Haikyu!!
"Yearning"