Would you all be interested
in a treasure hunt?
What?
I found this while cleaning out the History
Club's storeroom the other day.
A map?
It looks pretty old.
After deciphering it, I now believe
that the map leads to buried treasure!
Iga
Shi
Nana
Ni
Huh?!
Wait, wait. Why would something
like that be at school?
It was hidden inside an old pot that
a former club member got
at a temple a long time ago.
Temple? A pot?!
Our club room has all kinds
of things, doesn't it?
Like Haniwa terracotta figures,
or cursed Daruma dolls.
Or replica swords and helmets.
Right?
This all sounds way too shady.
Huh? Then you don't want to come?
I'm afraid not.
Shouldn't you just go with club members?
I see.
I guess it'll be just
you and me, then, Senpai.
I suppose so.
Iga
Shi
Nana
Ni
Hold up! What do you
mean just the two of you?
Huh? Well, you know, because
I'm in the History Club.
A-And what about the other members?
They said it looked suspicious
and didn't want to go.
No Kidding!
Shi
Nana
Ni
Iga
No Kidding!
Actually, I'll go!
Me, too!
Yay! Let's go! Let's go!
Isn't this great, Senpai?
Yeah!
No way are we leaving you two alone!
Kiss Him, Not Me
Brother Invasion!
Jeez!
That guy acts like a saint.
You can't let your guard down!
Seriously!
As if nothing would happen if you go
alone with the girl you're into, right?!
Hmm...
He seems more gentlemanly than you, Nana.
Huh?! You're one to talk!
Yeah, it definitely applies to you both.
Actually...
There's something I've been
curious about for awhile.
Does Mutsumi-senpai actually
like Serinuma-senpai?
Shi
Nana
Iga
Huh?
Isn't it obvious?
Why else would he try to
spend time alone with her?
But, when we all hang out together,
I don't get that feeling from him at all.
Are you stupid? Isn't that what
he's been aiming for from the start?
Huh?
You're right. He's been competing
with us from the beginning and—
Th-Then... me, too?
Luck is a skill, too.
I like all of you.
I know. How about we all go?
Huh?
See?! Like I said!
Wait. That means...
Why exactly is he doing all this?
Wearing a Tracksuit Because
it's a Club Activity
It's Mount Fuji!
So this is the cave?
Is this really it?
Yup. That's what's on the map.
To think there's treasure buried near
Mount Fuji! It's like a fantasy!
You really are excited, Serinuma-san.
Well, yeah!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams!
Together we will find
We'll go ahead and head down.
everything that we're looking for!
You girls wait outside a bit.
Sure!
It's so cold.
It's hard to get a good foothold here.
It's pretty big inside.
Everyone, be careful.
Mutsumi-san!
Ow...
A-Are you okay?
You need to be careful.
Yeah. Sorry.
It's dark and easy to lose your footing here.
It would've been dangerous
with just you and Serinuma.
You're right. I'm glad
you all decided to come.
Thanks.
Uh, Mutsumi-san.
Yes?
How do you feel about Serinuma-san?
He said it!
Me, Nana, and Shinomiya
all like her and that's why we're here.
You feel the same way, right?
Yeah, I like her.
I see. Of course you do.
See? I told you.
I guess Nishina's intuition
isn't all that great, after all.
Igarashi-kun, I like you, too.
You too, Nanashima-kun and
Shinomiya-kun! I love you all!
Love For Humanity
N-No!
Th-That's not what I mean!
I'm asking if you like her romantically!
I'm asking whether or not you
see her as your special person!
Wait, that's the part that floors you?!
Sorry. I don't really get that kind of thing.
What?!
Like, when your heart
pounds when you're near her!
Or you don't want to give
her up to anyone else!
Exactly!
Um...
Hey!
You were gone so long, we got worried.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Seems like there's no problem,
so let's keep moving.
Sure.
It's pretty big in here.
So cold...
It's actually pretty scary, huh?
Don't fall now, Shinomiya.
I'm asking whether or not you
see her as your special person!
Senpai, is something the matter?
No, it's nothing. Let's go.
Sure.
Special...
Serinuma-san is a dear
underclassman, and a sweet girl.
When we're together, it's a whirlwind
of fun and excitement.
That's how I feel. But...
Does that make her special?
Senpai? Is there something on my face?
No.
What is it?
Water dripped on me or something.
From above us?
They're all flying!
This is bad! There are too many!
Run!
Crap! I dropped the flashlight!
Is everyone here?
Serinuma, are you okay?
Serinuma, were you scared?
Squeeze
It's okay, I'm here with you!
Thanks for the show.
Shi
Nana
What are you doing there?!
You're the one who took
my hand and held me!
Get away from me!
Hey! Where's Serinuma-san?
It's gross!
Mutsumi-senpai's missing, too!
We got separated?
This is bad. We gotta get back fast!
Ni
Shi
Nana
Iga
Wh-Which path did we come from?
Ouch. I took a nasty fall.
G-Guys?
Guys? Are you there?!
Hey!
Silence...
Wait. What do I do?
I need a light.
Senpai?
I'm so happy you're here!
Yeah.
Where's everyone else? I wonder
if they ran deeper inside.
All right, let's catch up to them!
I'm sure they're waiting for us up ahead.
Senpai?
S-Sorry, I...
I was locked inside a storehouse in
the countryside a long time ago.
It traumatized me, and now I can't
move an inch anywhere pitch black.
Not even the moonlight reached inside...
I could hear cries outside, but couldn't
tell if they were insects or animals.
The sounds of the rustling trees
and the wind howling sounded
almost like a human scream.
I'm amazed you even
entered this cave at all!
Sorry for causing so much trouble.
I can move if there's even
just a little light, though.
Senpai...
D-Do you feel a little
less anxious like this?
Everyone has something
they have trouble with.
If there's something I can do
to help, I'll gladly do it.
Huh?
Now,
let's get going.
What's going on? My fingers feel hot.
Huh? Do you think that might
be Igarashi-kun and the gang?
Hey!
Serinuma-san!
I knew it!
What a relief.
Sorry.
Senpai?
I-I did it without thinking...
My strength...
S-Senpai?
S-Sorry!
W-Were you that scared?
Oh, no.
Hey! You two!
Serinuma-san, are you okay?
I'm fine! Sorry.
Glad to see you're safe.
What was that? I...
Mutsumi-san, we found what you
were looking for over there.
Th-The treasure?
Uh, yeah. But...
What's with this thing so desperately
trying to assert its position...
A treasure, I guess...
No.
I told you, someone definitely set us up!
Dammit!
They even prepared a map.
It's all way too elaborate.
Who would put in all this effort?
Oh, it's open.
Jackpot! The second generation
president of the History Club is you!
Congratulations.
Heisei Year 25 (2013)
Founding President
Shi
Ni
Mu
Nana
Ka
Iga
But I'm already the president.
Already President.
What the hell is this?!
This was written three years ago.
So, it was supposed to be opened that year?
Seems that way.
In other words, it was a prank
pulled by the stupid club founder!
What the hell's wrong with him?!
Heisei Year 25 (2013)
Founding President
Mutsumi Kazuma
Mutsumi?
My older brother.
Wha—
What?!
That was the worst.
We walked quite a bit
Let's head on home.
And thus ended the journey
to find the great treasure...
Or, so we all thought.
I'll be your student teacher
here. I hope we get along.
My name is Mutsumi Kazuma.
A pleasure to meet you.
That founding president?!
Afterward, there came a great storm.
Kiss Him, Not Me
Got a 7x4.
Nice!
Kiss Him, Not Me
Apparently, he teaches
second year Japanese History.
No, more like...
It was quite the shock, right?
I-I'm sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
It just felt right.
Mutsumi-senpai, you didn't hear anything
about him being a student teacher?
No. My brother lives on his own,
and we haven't really kept in touch.
What? Do you guys not get along?
I-It's not that—
Bam!
At all!
Nana
Ka
Iga
Ni
Shi
Where the hell did you come from?!
That scared me.
Nii-san!
Pet Pet
You look well, Asuma.
You too, Nii-san.
I never thought I'd see you here.
I got you, didn't I?
Yup.
I kept quiet about it since
I wanted to surprise you!
Looks like it worked!
That's so you.
These brothers have so much body contact!
So satisfying!
And who are all you? Asuma's friends?
Uh, yes.
I see!
They helped me look for that hidden
treasure the day before yesterday.
Huh? Hidden treasure? What's that?
Huh?
Snap
Snap!
The one you set up, Sensei.
Huh? I dunno what you're talking about.
C-Come on, Nii-san.
The one you made a map
for and hid in the clubroom.
From three years ago!
What?
Oh! You mean that fake map I set
up for the current second-years
that I thought would be fun for
picking out the next leader
that was completely ignored?!
That's the one!
Nana
Shi
Ni
Iga
That's the one!
Seriously?! So three years passed
before someone fell for it?!
And it was you guys?
Awesome!
Th-This bastard!
Nii-san! Everyone went because
I asked them to come with me.
Oh. Is that right?
That's right!
I see. Thanks for going out of
your way for my little brother.
Nana
Iga
Shi
Ni
Ka
Huh? He kind of seems like
a good older brother.
So, which of you is Asuma dating?
Jolt
I-It's not like that.
What? It isn't?
What a waste.
With a group of such pretty boys and
girls, I'd want to date all of you!
Wait, "all" of us?
The majority of us are guys!
What are you talking about?
Gender's not a big deal at all.
I could sleep with every one of you.
Love for humanity.
H-He really is a weirdo!
"I'm not into men, but I fell
for you, and you're a man."
Am I right?
Shameless!
That's the common route! I totally get it!
Yup. That's the gist of it.
Right!
You really get me, huh?
You little!
Nii-san!
Lunch break is almost over.
Are you okay on time?
Oh, you're right. I'd better get back.
Later!
Nii-san's free-spirited as ever.
Too free.
Get a hold of yourself, Nana.
But, he sure seems kind.
He really does seem like your
older brother, Mutsumi-senpai.
Is that right?
Yes!
That was unusual.
Asuma lost his cool.
And so...
The student teacher will
be observing our class.
I know he's handsome, but
please try not to look at him.
Especially you girls.
Come on!
Okay!
Guess that's expected.
And so, Mutsumi-sensei fit into
our school without a hitch.
His lessons were interesting
and easy to understand.
The girls were first to like him.
And before long, even the boys
came to grow fond of him.
In just a matter of days,
he became hugely popular!
What a great haul of new
releases I got today.
Putting things on hold
really is the way to go.
Huh? Serinuma-san?
Sensei, what are you doing here?
I was thinking of catching a movie.
Are you here to shop?
Oh, yes. At Anime Ito.
anime Ito
Huh? Oh, I see.
So, she's an otaku.
Are you by yourself?
Oh, yes. I'm all done now, so
I was thinking of heading home.
Is that right? How about we
grab a light lunch, then?
I bet you didn't eat yet.
Huh? But...
I've got time until my movie starts.
It'll be my treat.
Come on, keep me company.
I ended up going with him.
This place is so fancy that I can't relax.
So, you're a member of the history club?
Oh, yes.
I see. How's he doing?
Is he doing a good job?
Asuma. He's always been a bit meek.
He's not terribly assertive, either,
so I was a bit worried about
whether or not he'd do well.
Um, I think he's doing just fine.
Yeah? He's always so zoned out.
He's super gullible, so I used to
pull pranks on him all the time.
He was so cute when he cried.
Pranks?
Oh! L-Like, maybe locking him in a storehouse?
Yeah! I totally did that!
At our grandpa's place in the countryside!
I forgot him there the whole night!
H-How heartless.
Huh?
That traumatized him.
When we went to the cave, he was
so panicked that he grabbed on to me.
Huh? Oh, sounds like my brother
put you through a lot of trouble.
What? No, that's not what this is about.
It's true that Senpai
isn't the assertive type,
but he's helped me out
in lots of different ways.
And it's like, he's really strong
where it matters, and truly kind.
Looks like he's grown up to be quite a guy
to get so much praise from
his cute underclassman!
Asuma!
Nii-san?!
When did you get here?
Just now! I was looking for something,
and decided I'd drop by for dinner, too.
Looking for something?
Today, I was hanging around Shinjuku.
And I met that girl, Serinuma-san?
She was on her own, too, so
I had her join me for lunch.
But, really!
She sure is cute.
You're so lucky!
I wish I'd had an underclassman that cute!
I wanted to be adored like that!
Come on, time for dinner!
Been a while since I ate Mom's cooking!
Hello!
I'm here first?
What happened here? How weird.
We just cleaned up, too.
Books should be put back!
Uh, what's this cardboard box for?
Oh, there you are. Hello!
Sensei!
That's dangerous! Need a hand?
No, no, I'm fine.
Do you need something?
Nope. I just had something
I wanted to give you.
It's this.
Mirage Saga
Local Collaboration
Isn't it from that anime
you said you liked yesterday?
Th-That's...
The legendary Mirage Saga
Local Collaboration prize!
I've never seen it before!
I-I remembered I had it lying around
my house after winning it in an arcade.
Mirage Saga Local Collaboration
You sure are drooling!
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Y-You're giving it to me?!
But, I can't take something this amazing!
This is sold at a really high premium!
Look out!
That was close.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I-I'm sorry. Thank...
you...
We're so close!
I-I-I'm sorry!
You really are cute.
Nii-san!
A-Asuma?
S-Senpai!
What are you thinking?
Do you think it's acceptable for a student
teacher to make a move on a student?
Then, once my term is up,
I'm free to pursue her, right?
You don't have a reason
to stop me then, do you?
I do.
The truth is...
Serinuma-san is my girlfriend.
Sorry for being late!
It's not like you to be late, Shinomiya-kun.
An older lady called
out to me on the train.
She said I looked like her
grandson and I couldn't get away.
Speaking of, you get candy a lot, don't you?
Well, I much prefer having to talk to
ladies like that than girls my own age.
Huh? Do you not know how?
Not at all. When it comes to age,
I much prefer someone older.
I get it. You definitely
have that look about you.
Everyone's got a type they're not good with!
Next time:
Forward! Guard the Castle!
Look forward to it!
Not me!
I can get a feel for anyone when we meet,
and make everything work out.
That's how—