Ten years ago, somewhere in Tokyo.
Now, let's begin.
What should I do?
Just sing, like you always do.
I love your songs, Setsuna.
Container shields deployed.
Now, let me hear you sing.
Wow...
The moment she started singing,
the brain wave electromagnetic resonance
spectrum intensity increased by twelve digits!
High-density libido is materializing.
Activating Orgone charger.
This is the next generation of energy!
Magnificent.
Good morning, Lappa.
Good morning, Setsuna.
Good morning, Mao-san.
The hibiscus is blooming beautifully.
It's so brilliantly colored.
I'm happy.
Through the Window of Setsuna
Huh? Where's the Vice Commander?
Said she had something to do.
Daichi...
You're the captain, so you
can't rely on Rita-san forever.
You're right.
Last time, it was my fault the enemy escaped.
I'm really sorry.
You saved us last time.
I heard the Nebula Engine's testing wasn't done yet.
You surprised me.
It was like what happened with the Earth Engine.
But if this'll make you feel better,
I'll take it, Captain.
Two more to go...
Let's do this!
One of them is Siren-sama?
"Sama"?
But I don't know their avatar name.
What does Pitz say?
The image isn't as clear as last time...
But he says he can sense Orgone energy moving.
What's Rita-san doing?
Maybe she went to get some good food...
What?!
That is possible...
No, I don't think so...
You were the one on the phone?
Yes.
Thank you.
From your voice, I guessed you were pretty,
but you're prettier than I imagined.
It's still early, but do you
want something to drink?
A bourbon on the rocks, then.
So what do you want to know?
You used to be a detective with the police.
But you quit ten years ago.
Can you tell me why?
Women like you scare me.
If they think they have a reason,
they'll tell any lie straight-faced.
Between being a detective and a bartender,
I've gotten pretty good at guessing
what someone does for a living.
A journalist, huh?
Well, it doesn't matter.
Basically, you're interested in
the Kanda incident, right?
That's right.
Yes, I was on the task force for it.
But the official story is that the case was solved.
What do you want to know?
Everything you know.
Everything you remember.
I don't know anything beyond
what was in the media.
Then, your thoughts regarding the incident.
That's a very abstract way of putting it.
At the time, Macbeth Enterprises was developing
a man-machine interface for new mobile weapons.
To aid in their research,
they had six children, believed to have been
created by illegal genetic manipulation.
An anonymous whistleblower
reported them to the police,
and Macbeth was investigated.
The six children were found
and taken by the police.
Children born in Japan,
but who didn't appear in any government records...
Macbeth was using those children
to develop weapons.
Of course, this was a major human rights violation,
and the responsible parties were arrested.
At the time, there were cases
occurring in the Tokyo suburbs
where people would fall into
a comatose state at night,
and not wake up for several days.
It was said that a Macbeth
experiment caused that, too.
After that, there was a purging
at Macbeth's executive level,
and supposedly, the majority of
their operations were reformed.
Naturally,
members of the Kube family, the original
founders, were the next executives.
Kube took advantage of the
incident to return to power.
In the end, the incident was
blamed on Takashi Kanda,
the former CEO who had
taken over Macbeth previously.
And then...
Kanda committed suicide.
Why did you quit the force?
What happened to those six children?
I see...
So that's what you wanted to know.
Hey, Akari... Is it okay for us to have fun?
The motto of the Midsummer's Knights
is to do what you have to, when you have to.
The rest of the time, we're free.
Did Daichi decide that?
No, I did.
You came all the way here.
Aren't you going to swim?
Only children come to the pool to swim.
Then what did you come here to do?
Relax and enjoy all the guys looking at you.
Wow.
I'm jealous of the squirrel.
Maybe it was a bad idea to bring Hana.
Hey, Akari...
She's been swimming this whole time.
I wonder what really happened to them.
Were there any photos?
No, I heard all our materials on
them were destroyed.
I was on the task force,
and even I don't know where they went afterward.
All we were told was that
to protect their rights, measures were taken to
keep their personal information confidential.
So I looked into it myself,
and they found out, and fired me.
Why did you decide to do that?
Something wasn't right.
Wasn't right?
Were those children really being kept safe?
I didn't have any proof,
but it didn't seem that way to me.
What's happening?
What's going on?
What happened to them after that?
Unfortunately, I don't know.
You'll have to ask the guys who fired me.
Thank you.
And thanks for the drink.
Do you know where they went?
As you said, the government
had no records on them,
but they had names inside the company.
And they had numbers, too.
Each of them had a serial number
between three and eight.
Which means there was also a one and two.
Or maybe there were even more.
Are they still involved in some kind
of illegal weapons development?
Sometimes, I think they are.
Takashi Kanda committed suicide,
and I inherited this company and you.
This is Kube, right?
Kanda-san, yes?
I've been set up.
But not by you.
Be careful.
I think that our meeting was
a very fortunate event for both parties.
You "think," eh?
Puck, could you kill someone?
Or do you ever think you want to kill someone?
There is a high probability
that the weapons I devise will be used
to take lives on the battlefield.
In that sense, it is true that
I am a party to murder.
But I have never thought about
killing a specific individual,
nor would I do such a thing.
Takashi Kanda has committed suicide.
My sole reason for existing is to do my job.
Puck does not lie.
I'm out.
And we're running out of capsules, too.
This is bad.
If Siren-sama awakens, we'll be fine.
We can make new capsules.
Is the seat next to you free?
Sure.
Thanks.
Want some?
Oh, my.
What a kind offer to a girl
you've just met. Thank you.
You were swimming a lot, weren't you?
My quota is 1,200 meters a day.
Are you on the swim team or something?
No, I'm not.
But I've been told to exercise,
so I can stay healthy.
Well, that's a good thing, yeah...
Yes.
I'm glad they gave me such kind advice.
I could never do that.
Two squirrels?
Did you make a friend, Pitz?
Lappa is my friend.
Hey...
Does that squirrel talk?
Squirrels don't talk.
You're right.
How can I be the heroine, when I'm
the only one without a squirrel?
This whole thing is squirrely!
The project's finally nearing its final stages.
This install device
seems to be a system to give
the subject a specific dream.
Why does it come in pairs?
Sorry, Ban-kun.
I'll take care of the rest myself.
You can go home for today.
My contract with my sponsor means
that I can't show anyone the tests, even you.
Sorry, did that upset you?
No, I'm your assistant, so of course
I'll do whatever you say.
But...
Can you do it all on your own?
You're right.
Wouldn't it be convenient if there
were another one of me?
I'm back.
Welcome back, Setsuna.
I'm so glad.
It's still blooming beautifully.
Isn't that nice?
But it seems to me you like sitting by
the window more than you like the plant.
Is that true?
You're amazing, Mao-san!
You know everything!
A long time ago, I wasn't allowed
to go outside when I wanted.
I can do that now, so I'm really happy!
Now that I can visit it whenever I want,
the world I see outside the window
looks totally different than it used to.
It makes me happy to see it!
Okay, Setsuna.
Time for your medical checkup.
I'm not sick, so why do you give
me so many examinations?
Because you're that important to me.
So sit in that machine today.
A medical equipment manufacturer?
Akari did some research,
and found that this research group was
connected with Macbeth Enterprises.
Then there's probably something here.
Well, well...
Good to see both of you.
You, too.
Amarok and Malkin...
We can assume they're the enemy leaders, right?
I think so.
But since they have avatar bodies,
they must have thought of themselves
as being from Earth
until they awakened as Planetary Gears.
When did they awaken?
If you kiss, you can read someone's
mind for a second, can't you?
I think we have special powers
because we're designer children.
Is that why they lock us up?
And why we can only see the
outside from the window?
Amara... Moco.
Good news.
You get to leave this place.
You're going to a country called Japan.
Japan?
What is this device?
This is your machine.
It's a Neural Maneuver System
created specifically for you.
Try it.
You think one of their friends is here?
Probably. They likely haven't awakened, though.
You said that touching a powerful Orgone energy
or kissing an awakened avatar brings
back their memories, right?
Yeah.
And even if an avatar hasn't awakened,
if they kiss you, they can read your mind
or telepathically communicate.
My beautiful Setsuna...
You're so beautiful.
I wonder if the designer children
weren't created as pilots for new weapons,
but as vessels to install a human consciousness.
In other words, if you could keep installing
your mind into a young body,
you could become immortal.
No!
What?
What did you see?
You were raising me to be your own vessel!
You're a terrible person!
Wait, Setsuna!
Wait!
Captain, behind you!
Daichi Manatsu!
You drove Albion mad, so we'll kill you first!
This light...
Teppei?
The Livlaster?
Albion was the other Neoteny that
Lieban was talking about?
Albion is a Neoteny?
Seriously?
They did a good job of cleaning it up,
but someone just shed blood here.
What?
But it isn't Siren-sama's blood.
It's me.
Where's the install device?
It's been safely removed.
Then take it to the place I directed you to.
Understood, Robin-sama.
Where's Siren-sama?
She wasn't on the second floor.
This keeps getting more complicated.
Let's go, Amara.
Yeah.
Every night, illegal fighting matches
are held at an underground ring in this town.
Of course, bets are placed on the fights.
And the next Machine Goodfellow
is going to appear in this town.
Is the enemy one of the boys
that are forced to fight?
Next time, on episode 12 of Captain Earth:
Boys' Battlefield.
Boys' Battlefield
Earth Engine, scramble!