Stella!
She's alive.
She isn't as pale as she was before.
You must be dizzy.
Come here.
It's not dead.
Long time no see.
Joseph.
When did we last meet? At the graveyard?
I could never forget you after
what you'd done to me.
He doesn't remember.
You always cause me so much trouble.
Well, it's fine.
You accepted my deal, after all.
You're the same as me.
Your curse is as powerful as mine.
I'm cursed to live on forever.
You're cursed to die.
So give me your left arm.
It's my arm that you want?
Yeah.
That part looks the most usable right now.
I'll give you a part of me in exchange.
That way, you'll have
a body that can never die.
I can't trust you.
Are you saying you have another option?
You're doing it.
Do I just need to give you my arm?
First, let's make sure my
body doesn't reject it.
There.
Now it's your turn.
What? Are you scared?
You might be freed from your curse.
It's okay.
You won't change into
another form or anything.
Even if I did...
I wouldn't care.
Why are you so...
What?
Nothing. I was just thinking
about how I still hate you.
I'll help you.
There.
Transplant complete.
Don't worry, you won't
die just from bleeding.
It doesn't seem like my body's rejecting it.
Your eyeball makes the world
look bright and shiny.
I envy you.
We're the only people in this
world who see what we do.
I'll have your arm once
the curse settles in.
Don't worry. It'll all be
done while you're asleep.
I'm going to borrow the power
that's left in your eye.
What are you...
I told you. I hate you.
So...
What is this place?
I don't know...
No...
It's nostalgic.
I know this place.
Sorry, Chise.
Mom?
Welcome home, Mom!
Thanks for watching the house.
It wasn't too scary, was it?
Yeah, Fumiki was with me,
so everything's okay.
Okay.
Fumiki's lucky he takes after his dad.
This is before my dad and
little brother vanished.
Fumiki's a good boy.
Hey, I can change his diaper now!
You're right.
Thank you.
You're a good girl, too, Chise.
Mommy, Mommy, I want to help make dinner.
Really?
What should I have you do?
I'll do anything.
That's right.
She used to have a really happy smile.
Welcome home, Dad!
Just a sec.
You're gonna get wet.
Welcome home, Yuuki.
You're home late.
Hurry!
Yeah.
I'm home, Chise.
Welcome home!
Hey! I can't walk!
Hey.
I guess I took after my dad.
Is work tough?
I have more night shifts now.
I'm sorry. I wish I could work, too.
You already take care of things
around the house, Chika.
Besides, Chise's like you.
She's got a frail body.
I feel better with you around her.
Thanks, Yuuki.
Frail body...
Mom was the same as me?
This is my memory.
He's keeping me in a dream
so that I don't wake up.
Car—
No.
You aren't him.
I'm a fragment of him
that's been chopped off.
He's attached and assumed
all kinds of things.
Which is the real him, what
he even was to begin with...
none of it is clear anymore.
Why is he making me see
all this stuff from my past?
Probably to upset you.
That there is hurting you,
but it's also protecting you.
It's the reason you're able
to talk to something like me.
You're...
You don't want to touch me.
Not until you're ready.
Ready?
It's okay, I'll calm him down.
Thanks.
Dad, are you going somewhere?
Chise, do you want to...
No, I'll be right back.
Wait here.
Well, good night.
Come back soon.
Dad never...
No!
...came back home.
That's all you remember.
That door won't open.
Yuuki?
That's right.
Ever since this day...
Come on, again?
I'm sorry.
Something's odd lately.
Ever since Hatori-san showed up, right?
Want some help?
Welcome h—
What's wrong?
I was the one who said you can't be scared.
I'm sorry.
It'll be okay.
Help!
Help, Mom!
Get out!
Now!
Hey, it's midnight! Shut up!
I have to protect her.
I have to be strong.
That guy who was protecting
them isn't around lately.
Poor thing. He must have gotten sick of her.
An abandoned woman.
An abandoned daughter.
Pitiful and appetizing.
Yes.
I see.
I understand.
Popular job listings!
It'll be okay.
I have to protect her.
I'll be okay on my own.
It'll be okay.
It would be so much easier
for me without her.
That's crazy! That's crazy!
But, if she weren't here...
I shouldn't...
have given birth to you.
I shouldn't have given birth to you.
M... om...
What have I done?
Mom?
I'm sorry, Chise.
Please forgive me.
To upset me?
This is really upsetting.
Mom...
I shouldn't have given birth to you.
It's your fault.
It's because your body is so weak.
Why?
You should have died.
Die, die, die, die,
die, die, die... Die!
Why didn't you finish me off, then?
You aren't my real mom.
You're the mom that exists inside of me.
The mom that I created
after she strangled me.
I'm glad I talked to Nevin.
Angelica-san, Simon-san, Alice and Renfred,
Lindel-san, the people of the fairy world...
Ruth, Silky, Stella,
Elias...
I'm glad I got to meet all kinds of people.
Without them, I would have
died before I'd met you.
Forgive me.
Forgive me, Chise.
You endured for my sake, didn't you?
You endured and endured, but in the end...
You're free.
I won't forgive you.
I loved you, Mom.
I have lots of happy memories with you.
And yet, ever since that day,
I couldn't remember any of them.
But thanks to you,
I met someone that I cared
for even more than myself.
I thought he was strong, but he
turned out to be pretty troubled.
Yeah.
So...
Thanks for letting go of me that day.
I won't forgive you.
I won't forget you yet,
but I'm going to leave you and move on.
Are you ready?
What are you?
I'm what keeps one living on.
The curse and blessing that
was given for his sake.
Joseph.
Cartaphilus?
They planted me in you, and
you're trying to accept me.
So as long as you wish to
live, I'll be your blessing.
Even if that means tearing at what consumes
and protects you for all eternity.
What do... What do you desire?
Me?
What's the price?
What you say sounds good only for me.
There's one wish that I've heard many times.
Can you grant that for me?
It looks like it's starting to set in.
How vile.
Just like me.
Y-You're awake—
I'm going to do things the way you do.
I don't know if I can grant you your wish.
But I can hear you out,
and try to do something.
"Help me."
For centuries, for millennia,
they've been shouting, "Help me."
I don't know why you desire this.
Why, when you think as you
do, you still do this.
Why you've done this.
So I'm going to find out.
The girl tries to make
sense of Joseph's truth.
Meanwhile, the mage, having lost the girl,
loses his human form, and is forced to wander.
You saw?
You saw me?
My past?