Go out with you?
I don't really know.
Yeah.
Give me some time to answer.
I've hardly talked to Azumi-kun since then.
Hi-yah!
What the heck?
Bullet train!
Yay!
You're pretty excited.
Did you bring underwear, Kota?
Shut up.
Roman, I'm upgrading from boxers
to make my boxer briefs debut today.
Better look forward to it.
What? Finally?
Wait, really?
I've always worn boxer briefs.
My debut...
We're doing a luggage check.
Sensei, that's a girl's...
Okay, next.
All right, I'll check it, then.
No cell phones, remember?
I'll hold on to this.
She caught me!
Too bad. Hidaka was so easy.
Potato Chips
Lightly Salted
All right, next.
They got quite a few of us.
Where were you hiding your phone?
I hid mine in my underwear.
Her phone's in her panties?!
Dude, don't.
Panties!
Seriously? That's hot.
Ta-da.
Wow.
You really can't tell.
I opened it once, then closed it with tape.
Here.
Good, now I'll be ready if she sends an answer.
Point the camera to the right, Akanecchi.
Like this?
No... Up.
God of
Relationship
Success
Stone
It's supposed to be a god
of relationship success.
Romance Fortunes
Jinushi Shrine Kyoto
Hey, is "semi-good" good or bad?
"Your luck ends where your money ends."
What?!
Nagahara!
Romance Fortune
Kyoto Jinushi Shrine
#104: Bad Luck
#108: Excellent Luck
Hey, you got "excellent luck."
Yeah.
Romance:
Ambiguity brings calamity.
Akane!
Akane.
Let's pick out gifts for the club members.
Good idea.
One, two...
For eight?
Yeah, that's right.
How about handkerchiefs?
That's kinda boring.
Keychains?
Snacks for the boys.
Curly-kun.
Pick one.
Me?
What kind do boys like?
Um...
I think the bigger one.
That's it!
We're choosing gifts for our club.
Oh, really?
Yeah. You know how guys eat a lot.
What do you like?
Me?
Yeah. For reference.
Anything.
Really?
Guys like sweets, too.
Be done in ten minutes, please.
I wonder if they have open-air baths.
The bath's tiny.
I'll just take a shower.
Oh my God, whose panties are these?
Is there a name on them?
Crap, I think I've gained weight.
Let's see.
Don't look!
Mizuno-san
Why the shrine?
Neighborhood association stuff
Pray for me lots! I want
to beat my own record
I've got you covered
Thanks
Combo!
Damn it, no way...
Combo, combo!
Four combo!
Seriously, stop, please! Sorry, wait!
Here comes a bunch of them.
Crap, too many! What the heck?!
I'm winning.
I'm totally going to win.
Shoot.
Oh, crap, here they come...
Damn it!
Is she gone?
She's gone.
Are we clear?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
That's hilarious!
It's not funny.
So, who's next?
Akanecchi.
Me?
You have someone, don't you?
If you're curious about
someone, that counts, too.
There is someone I'm curious about.
Who? Who? Who? Who? Who? Who?
Hira?
Did he ask you out?
Hira's cool.
You should go out with him.
Just like that?
No, I...
That was close.
The teacher was right there.
That scared me.
Why are you guys here?
Why not?
What's the problem?
We're going to be the ones to get yelled at.
Why so cold?
We don't want you here.
Come on, we're already here.
Azumi-kun: What're you up to?
Stop, idiot! Idiot!
Here we go!
Combo!
Four combo!
Eight combo!
What're you up to?
Talking about relationship stuff
Sixteen combo! Here we go! Here we go!
What? No way!
Okay, here it comes!
Combo! Combo!
Huh? No way!
What are you doing during free time?
I haven't decided yet
If you want, tomorrow...
Hey...
Let me see!
No!
Come on!
Tickle, tickle...
Stop it!
Hey!
Lengthwise four-quarter hold.
Okay.
Ogasawara Buster!
Stop it!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Stop!
Passcode?
Come on, stop it!
I bet it's his birthdate.
Right.
Come on!
A girl?
Stop it!
Hey, I'm in.
If you want, tomorrow at 12:00 in front
of Doimaru Department Store
Hey, what are you up to?
If you want, tomorrow at 12:00 in front
of Doimaru Department Store
U-Um...
I'll be taking that.
You have free time today until this evening.
Once again, stay safe and be careful.
Enjoy your school trip.
If you want, tomorrow at 12:00 in front
of Doimaru Department Store
Don't get too carried away.
Be mindful and considerate
of the people around you.
Hey, where's Setsuko?
Off with Nagahara.
Where should we go first?
What about Kaneko?
Who cares?
You're coming with us, right, Akanecchi?
Um...
If you want, tomorrow at 12:00 in front
of Doimaru Department Store
Huh? Say what?
Suspicious.
Uh... Yeah.
No secrets, remember?
I, uh... My parents are asking about souvenirs.
Oh, that's all?
Want to come with us, then?
Oh, yeah.
Where should we go?
I heard the bus might be faster.
Yo, Kota.
Let's go!
Want to?
Let's do that.
Okay.
Let's go to that place we were
talking about yesterday.
Okay.
Blotting Paper
10 booklets
per pack
Aren't these famous?
I heard they pick up a ton of oil.
Yasaka Shrine
Hey...
I have something to do.
Huh? What?
Shopping.
We'll come with you.
Where?
Tell us.
We're friends, aren't we?
I'm gonna get a drink.
A date?
Why's she hiding it from us?
Yeah, we're her friends.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What?
Have to go?
No?
That's enough.
We're torturing her.
Let's split up.
Let's go, Miu.
Huh?
Come on.
Hey, wait...
See you later!
I'm at Doimaru Department Store
Where are you?
Didn't you say you were going
to practice here, Chinatsu?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
No, I know I said I would, but...
Where are you?
He's not answering me.
It's pouring.
It's so cold.
We're all wet.
Here, I'll wipe you off.
Hey, that tickles.
We aren't dating.
I never even gave him an answer.
He might not come.
H-Hey...
Curly-kun?
What?
You scared me for a second.
I thought you were going to hit on us.
You're soaked.
What happened?
Wait...
Can I go?
Sorry, I'll be in touch later.
So what's up?
I, uh...
Can you lend me your phone?
Sure.
Here.
Shoot, I don't know her number.
I can't ask her to tell me
Mizuno-san's phone number.
I couldn't possibly...
Actually, never mind.
Let me guess...
Akane?
Wh-Wh-Why?
I mean, come on, Curly-kun...
Oh, forget it.
So are we calling Akane?
Yes, please.
Hello, Akane?
Here.
H-Hey...
Who's this?
Azumi.
Why?
Some stuff happened...
I don't get it.
I was waiting for you.
Where are you?
You're so late.
Sorry.
You told me to meet you here,
so I came, but you weren't here.
It's raining, and you aren't
answering your phone.
S-Sorry.
The teacher took my phone.
Why Chinatsu's phone?
You guys are close, huh?
She just happened to...
I...
What?
Nothing.
I don't know.
I don't know, but we can't even talk at all...
Yeah.
I want...
to talk with you more, Azumi-kun.
Is that...
your answer?
Yeah.
Passing Shower
Ryouko-sensei and Roman 3
~In Kyoto~
She's so cute!
Huh...
Aren't you interested in maikos, Sensei?
Not especially, I guess.
I'm Roman the maiko.
Holy crap, she's gorgeous!
I thought you weren't interested...
How?!
Setsuko and Nagahara 2
~Kyoto Travel Sentiments~
Where should we go first?
I'll show you around.
Wow, he's actually really dependable!
Shou-chan must be especially pumped
because it's the school trip.
That's so cute.
A school trip is special, isn't it?
A Rest Area,
Somewhere in Kyoto
But we're in Kyoto.
Setsuko and Nagahara 3
~Memories of Kyoto~
A Rest Area,
Somewhere in Kyoto
Shoot, I don't have any money.
Crap!
Breaks    Weekdays (Monday to Friday)
Second Impact             Basic
1 hour | 1980 yen | 2180 yen
2 hours | 2680 yen | 3170 yen
4 hours | 2980 yen | 3670 yen
Let's go back, then.
Sorry, Setsuko, can you take care of it?
What?!
Let's go home with some good memories.
Businesses Affecting Public Morals Regulation Act
(Prohibitions)
Article 22 states entertainment businesses must not engage in the following:
1.   Pull customers into said business
2.   Stand in the way of or follow other people on the streets or
in other public places in order to pull customers into said business
3.   Allow those under the age of eighteen to serve customers at said business
4.   Allow those under the age of eighteen to perform duties that
entail interactions with customers between the hours of 10 PM and 6 AM
5.   Allow those under the age of eighteen to enter said business as customers
(In the case of businesses to which Article 2, Paragraph 1, Item 5 pertains,
allow those under the age of eighteen to enter said business as customers)
6.   Serve alcohol or tobacco products to those under the age of twenty
This kid's no good.