Boobies, White Panties and Me
Don't move...
I'm blushing...
All done!
Here!
That was quick!
Did you make me look cool?
WHO IS THAT?!
H-Huh? Did I make the areola's too big?
That's NOT the problem here!
I tried real hard to use my imagination!
This is WAY too imaginative,
in a lot of places!
You're supposed to draw me
the way I actually look!
And I worked so hard, too...
Sheesh...
Sensei.
You're underestimating Futaba's
breast obsession.
That voice...Hitoha-chan?
Where? She's not here...
Stop popping up from in between my legs!
And draw me, not the hamster.
Forget that. You can't underestimate
Futaba's breasts.
I'm not underestimating anything!
Her obsession is abnormal.
Normally she just goofs around all the time,
but breasts are the one thing that
she gets deadly serious about.
Paintings
She's a breast artisan,
Clay sculptures
tirelessly seeking to create the perfect
representation of her ideal.
Calligraphy
Sketches
Sometimes she gets so hard on herself
she'll roam around aimlessly.
Her refined breast creations are
masterpieces, beautiful...
And sexy!
SEXY
H-Hitoha-chan?
Look!
Look at her dedication.
So she's still drawing me with breasts?
Of course.
My hand slipped.
It's still not done-
Would someone draw me normally?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Done!
Great.
What do you think?
A solid F-cup!
Don't hold it there!
Fantastic!
Mr. Principal?
What beautiful, natural curves.
Soft, gentle shading...the complexion
of the areolas...
These are the ideal breasts I've sought
these 55 long years, second daughter!
Mr. Principal!
Fantastic, wouldn't you say, Yabe-kun?
Maybe you should put it somewhere else...
I think it's perfect...it has a reality to
it beyond what any photo can show.
Yes, I think we can say
these ARE real breasts.
I...I've never seen the real thing.
Oh! M-My apologies...
I-I can't help but agree though,
I bet this is what it feels
like to see a real woman!
Wow, you're good.
That's awesome, Middle!
They're looking, everyone in the
school is staring at my picture!
I changed my mind, this is embarrassing!
Stop looking at my boobies!
Aww come on, it's not hurting anyone.
Yeah, we wanna see more!
We want more!
You're such a baby.
You don't understand the joy of
being the center of attention.
But it's embarrassing...
It'll start feeling good before you know it.
Really?
I like your breasts too, Futaba-chan.
Me too...
Yabecchi, Hitoha...
Okay!
Everyone look at my boobs!
Stare at them, lick them
with your imagination!
Boo-bies boo-bies boo-bies!
Hi Kuriyama-sensei.
This whole grade is sick!
Huh?
And the winner is class 6-3's Marui
Futaba for "Portrait of an F-Cup!"
They're all looking...
A few days later
What's up?
There are thumbtacks on the nipples!
Who would pull such a mean prank?!
Futaba-chan-
Futaba-chan...
Not bad!
Yes it is!
Boobies!
Why did you wreck my desk?!
There was a bee on it...
You shouldn't swat bees
with your bare hands.
Hey look, Futaba! An H-cup!
Marvelous!
Boobies boobies boo-BIES!
You idiot!
It's boobies!
I'm used to it, though.
H-cups!
You even broke my pencil case!
Whatever, I needed a new one.
I...I'm sorry!
I-It's okay.
Just be careful next time.
I'm sorry...
Check it Futaba, sideboob!
What's wrong with her?
Futaba actually ignored boobs.
Well, it's good that you feel bad,
but do it somewhere else!
Hitoha's right, this is kinda nice...
What a weird information network...
I rented it to her for 100 yen a day.
You can't rent out my leg space!
It's not like you to get so down.
I'm retiring my fists!
Micchan might not forgive me, but...
Weird...
Those fists have broken countless things
and she's never been upset about it.
Whoopsie-doodle!
I wonder why...
Futaba-chan still won't come out.
Who cares?
I do...
You've been using that since
we started school, huh?
Oh? You actually take good care of
your things, don't you?
What do you mean, "actually?!"
She's been in there for two hours...
What're you doing?!
Don't trouble yourself with me!
But that's your dogi, you're
never without it!
It's for Micchan!
This is about her pencil case, right?
She said she was going to get a new one.
She loves that pencil case.
I didn't get that feeling, but...
School's out for the day.
You missed gym and didn't eat a thing,
how long do you plan on staying there?
Here's some pudding from the cafe.
For me?
Yes, from Micchan.
Sh-Shut up!
Micchan!
I-It's not because I was worried about you!
Th-These...
What's that?
Pencil cases...made from my dogi
Are you brain-dead?
Three?
Daddy bought one of those pencil cases
for each of us when we started school.
Look!
Look, we all have one!
How adorable!
Who's this little angel?!
Wh-Why do you remember
that, it was ages ago!
These might not be able
to replace them, but...
I thought Micchan would be happy if
we all had the same kind again...
What is this crap?
You thought this garbage would PLEASE me?
Well, if you INSIST, I guess I'll use it.
Micchan!
All's well that ends well, I guess...
I don't want one.
I'm home!
Welcome back, Micchan!
Why are those filthy boys in MY room?
You all SHARE this room.
We're still preparing our presentation
for science class.
Hitoha didn't care?
Hitoha's at the pet shop getting a bunch
of on-sale hamster food for Nipples!
Fine, just finish up and get out!
Man, girls' rooms just give off bad vibes.
Then go away NOW!
I don't mean to be rude, but we can't get
anything done if you keep bugging us.
Wha-
Well excuse me if I can't understand an
honor student's thought processes!
So, Futaba can do the diagrams
of the flow of current-
Wh-What're you drawing?!
Are they too big?
That's not the issue! You're supposed
to draw a circuit diagram!
You moron, Futaba! Look what you've done!
Go buy a new piece of
posterboard right now!
O-Okay!
Wow Chiba, you're not usually
so serious about homework.
Fools!
Hey!
This's our chance, Satou!
We must find the precious!
What's a "precious?"
The hidden treasure that
waits in a girl's bedroom,
treasure beyond a man's wildest dreams.
I don't get it.
S-Stop!
Cut it out, you can't just
raid someone's room!
Let's see if you still say
that after seeing THIS.
P-Panties...
Yeah...they're beautiful.
Okay, who wears which panties?
What is this, a game show?
Plus I can't tell.
Look, that's enough, we came here
to work, not gawk at panties.
You're such a stick in the mud, dude.
What are you, a cop?
Someone's coming!
Futaba's back already?
Crap...close, close!
What?
Bear!
What're you doing, you idiot?!
Excuse me!
Where's Futaba?
To get more posterboard...
You two aren't messing with
our room, are you?
O-O-O-Of course not!
We're not doing anything, please
leave us alone so we can work!
Yeah...and do it without turning around.
If I catch you doing anything
you're dead meat!
Bear!
Catch!
Put them...
back!
You dirty rat!
You took them out,
you do it!
He's good!
Pretty good, Mr. Ace Striker!
You're not bad yourself!
Futaba, you butthead!
Why did you leave them alone in our room?!
Why not?
Who knows what they're doing!
Listen, it sounds like they're
having fun in there!
My expert panty-profiling skills
say these are Futaba's!
What a baby, huh?
Too high, you idiot!
Header, Satou!
Here goes!
BEAR!
I-It's not what you think, Futaba!
I didn't put your little girl panties
on my head on purpose!
SHUT UP!
Oh God!
Mitsudomoe!
Morning, Satou-kun!
Good morning!
I caught you, you perv!
Am not!
That was just an accident!
Please hear me out, I'm not a-
Don't touch me, PERVERT!
H-Hey!
Wait, Eldest!
Wait...
You believe me, don't you, Futaba?
I've always been an upstanding
moral person.
Yup!
Futaba...
Here's a present for you, Shin-chan!
Don't tell Micchan, okay?
You don't believe me at all!
Shin-chan!
He looked like he was having so much fun
with Micchan's panties on his head,
I thought he'd like these.
You don't get it, Futaba.
Chibacchi?
You'll just embarrass him if you
give them to him directly.
He's really shy.
Oh, I understand!
How do I clear this up?
I need my book...
Bear!
What the crap?!
Futaba must've done this-
What're those?
Panties?
No, no they're not mine!
Sit down everyone, time to start.
So don't forget that little tip, okay?
Futaba!
She's gone!
Where are you?
Futaba!
Futaba?
Did she go outside?
How many did she put in here?!
Shin-chan...
Ta-da!
Don't use them for magic tricks!
All for you!
I don't want them, get away!
Chiba! This is all YOUR fault!
Go explain things to Futaba and Eldest!
So suddenly your desk is overflowing with
panties instead of love letters...
Must be nice.
What's your problem?
Leave the high road behind and join
me on the path of a lothario!
Never!
Shin-chan said he doesn't want them.
You're still missing the point, Futaba.
It's not the panties that are valuable,
it's what's INSIDE them.
Oh, I understand!
Stupid Chiba...
Shin-chan!
What now? I told you I don't want your p-
Ta-da!
What a crazy fashion statement!
Chiba said I'm supposed to WEAR them.
That moron...
You can have these too!
I don't want them!
I stole them all from Micchan just for you...
Don't cry!
And take those off, aren't you embarrassed?
You want them?
Oh for the love of-
Yes, I want them, give them to me!
Satou?
The more I think about it, Satou's not
really the type to do something
stupid like wear my panties on his head.
Maybe Chiba put him up to it.
I guess I can at least hear him out.
Satou Shinya
12 years old
Honor student
and
PERVERT
I think I've had enough of
modeling for class 3...
That's too bad, I wanted to
use you for my next model.
Okay, sure.
Episode 5
Love Love Pig!
I'm over here.