I'll do it.
I'll change history.
I'm going to protect them.
I promise. I promise. I promise!
When is this?!
Huh?
I'm asking you what month and day it is!
I-It's December 21st...
Yes!
Punch Line
So anyway, I've really been through hell.
Seriously, one wrong move
and I could have died.
Welcome back!
Did it go okay?
The police investigation was rough, huh?
I just got back, too.
Come on, we can talk about that later.
Before that, here. Want one?
It's hot.
What's his problem?
Panty Panic Returns
Yeah, it's my room.
Yeah, it's my body.
I'm back, baby!
Must be that thing they call PTSD.
Wait! This isn't the time for celebrating!
Only ten days until New Year's Eve.
What do I do?
For starters, I'll try outlining
everything that's about to happen.
Cheermancy / Muhi discovered
23rd: Cheermancy; Muhi discovered.
Turtle Man = Tomoda attacks
24th: Turtle Man, a.k.a Tomoda, attacks;
Miyazawa Kenji arrives
Miya Ken arrives.
I slept through this day, didn't I?
I think they had a Christmas party or something.
Meika discovered to be a robot
26th: Meika discovered to be a robot.
Gliese visits / Miyazawa Kenji attacks
27th: Gliese visits; Miya Ken attacks.
Ito in danger!
29th: Ito in danger.
Turtle Man = Tomoda Battle
30th: Battle with Turtle Man.
Meikaemon Party
Asteroid Hits
31st: Meikaemon Party; asteroid hits.
The two important dates
are the 24th and the 27th.
Tomoda attacks on the 24th,
Turtle Man = Tomoda attacks
and Gliese comes to Korai House on the 27th.
Gliese visits / Miyazawa Kenji attacks
Those two must know something.
Sitting around thinking won't help!
I've gotta move!
I'm going to find them!
Ow...
Chiranosuke!
What the hell was that for?!
Wait, I can still see you.
You're still at the same spirit power level.
It's the same as if you'd
trained to become a psychic.
And? What was that for?
Chiranosuke's Code, number one:
You must not change history
without my permission.
Number two:
You must not tell anyone else the truth.
Why not?!
Because then the plan will fail.
Just like the previous Miya Ken.
The previous Miya Ken?
You saw him on the rooftop.
That's you from the future.
Still, I can't have you
becoming that Miya Ken.
What are you talking about?
I'll make it easy to understand.
First, this is the world you're in.
And this train travels down
the rail, toward the future.
If it goes straight, it will arrive here,
at the worst-case scenario,
the New Year's Eve when the asteroid hits.
That Miya Ken ended up here.
But I need you to go
toward the New Year's Eve
where the asteroid doesn't strike.
Beyond that is a supremely
happy and peaceful future.
To guide the world to that future is
the ultimate purpose of the
Human Preservation Project.
The Human Preservation Project?
To stop the asteroid from falling,
thereby protecting the human
species from extinction.
In any case, you absolutely, unfailingly,
must succeed in this project.
That is your destiny.
My destiny?
That's the reason.
That's why when your spirit
sees panties, humanity ends.
Huh?
A spirit without its body is
like an egg without its shell.
It's delicate and easily damaged,
and sensitive to all kinds of stimuli.
And what happens when such a spirit
becomes excited twice in a row?
You become infused with a massive
torrent of excited energy, and your body
dies.
You undergo a technobreak.
Seriously?
That's the relationship between
panties and human extinction.
By being exposed repeatedly to panties,
the person executing the operation is lost...
And ultimately, the asteroid hits Earth...
How do I make sure I don't fail?
Y-You wanna know?
There, I put all of them up.
Yes. Well done.
Um, is that really all I have to do?
If I just do the same thing as last time,
won't history stay the same?
Don't worry.
Just have faith in me.
Good, good.
Now Niconico Live Encoder
should start automatically.
Next...
I know.
Akina's Secret Box
Don't look
inside!
Danger
Is this it?
The Indian Sacred Book
Nandala Gandala
My crazy sister...
Why'd she give it this title?
What's wrong?
You didn't forget the word that
was written in it, did you?
I remember.
"U-turn," right?
Then...
No.
I don't want to write it.
Why not?
I feel like I'd be admitting defeat.
I used this when I failed.
But this me won't fail.
So I don't need to write it.
Good evening-ning!
Good evening-ning...
Wait, Yuta-kun, what happened?!
Your room's plastered with talismans!
Oh, this is, um... interior design.
Oh, really?
So what brings you here, Narugino?
Oh, well, there are some kanji in
this script that I couldn't read.
Encounter
"Encounter," I think.
To meet unexpectedly,
or make contact by accident.
Wow, you know a lot, Yuta-kun!
But why come to me?
Jeez, you're so dense.
Mikatan came to check up on you.
Really?
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
She knows about what happened on
the bus and at the river. Everything.
That's why she's—
Just shut up!
But I haven't said anything...
Anyway, thanks.
Oh, I mean, thanks for teaching me that.
And...
Sorry, see you later!
She's...
'Sup!
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
I thought maybe you were tired.
Here.
Genki Maker
Z
Daihatsu Pharmaceuticals
What's this?
My special drink.
For nutritional fortification and
replenishment when you're exhausted!
Genki Maker!
It seems poisonous, no matter how I look at it.
Fight poison with poison!
So it is poison.
By the way, isn't that Narugino's
script you're holding?
Yeah, she forgot it here just now.
I'll bring it back to her later.
See ya.
Isn't this...
So that's it.
In that case, um... what happens next, again?
I think my spirit...
What happens when such a spirit
becomes excited twice in a row?
Oh, no! I have to do something!
Sorry, Ito.
I'm coming in.
Man, this room's always so messy.
Well, I guess I'll take a shower for once.
Oh, yeah, I have to grab some more shampoo.
No! If Ito comes out now...
Huh?
Why...
I'll kill you!
Wai—
S-Sorry, Ito! I didn't mean to!
You animal!
Where did that book go?
Oh, no!
You pervert!
Freak!
Creep!
Stop... Stop it!
Harakiri Harassment
Harahara Production Group
Damn!
Maybe it's on the top shelf.
No you don't!
Salt, huh? Sorry, I'm out right now.
I guess I'll borrow some from Mikatan, then.
Oh, if you're going to see Narugino...
Could you return this to her for me?
Sure, but what's this?
A script.
For She's Mei.
No... This isn't, uh...
Stop!
You! Give me back my body!
Punch Perms and
Chirashi Sushi
Hey, what's up with you?
Sorry, Rabura!
Shit!
Looks like I changed history a little...
But I guess that's okay.
What the heck happened here?
Harakiri Harassment
Harahara Production Group
Wait... No!
This isn't the book!
Oh, did they get mixed up?
It must have happened when I crashed into him...
I get it.
She's Mei Musical Project
Debut Piece
Punch Perms and Chirashi Sushi
The apples of Tsugaru Mountain...
This sucks.
I've walked all this way, and made no progress.
I couldn't get into the
Qmay Group headquarters with all
the police and reporters there.
And I couldn't find Tomoda, either.
That leaves...
Rabura?
Rabura!
Wait up!
Were you out for yuuhan (dinner)?
What? It's only 4:30.
Korai
House
No, I mean a yuurei hanto (ghost hunt).
How did you know?!
A-Anyway, listen, there's
something I want to ask you.
Can you tell me how to get
in contact with Gliese?
W-Wait a second!
How do you know about Gliese-sama?
Just tell me, please.
No way.
Tomoda!
You bastard!
What's your problem?!
Just shut up and get back here!
You're not getting away!
Hey, what was that for?!
I told you, you're not allowed to
change history without my permission.
What is going on here?
The cooperation of the tenants
is vital to the success of the
Human Preservation Project.
Try to remember all those things that
happened in the previous history.
There was Cheermancy,
and the thing with Muhi.
Mikatan and Meika's identities were exposed.
Everyone got into fights.
Each of those events brought
you all closer together.
That's important to this operation.
So in order to create those bonds,
we need to recreate history up to a point.
And if we don't protect it?
So far, six billion, three hundred
seventy-three million,
one hundred fifty-three thousand,
seven hundred forty yous
have broken that code, and went on to fail.
If you want to be the six billion,
three hundred seventy-three million,
one hundred fifty-three thousand,
seven hundred forty-first,
then do what you want.
But I'll tell you this:
there is no "next" for you.
What do you mean?
If you fail this operation, it's all over.
Not for me, though.
I have the next possibility.
The next possibility?
I'm talking about the next you.
Hey,
this might be a dumb question, but...
Why did I end up out-of-body?
What?! You can't even figure that out?
It's because your spirit came from
the future and possessed your body.
So then, my original spirit
got kicked out of my body.
Indeed.
What about when I possessed Rabura, then?
No, Rabura's spirit remained
attached to her body then.
Why?
Why is it just me?
You were Yubafied when you'd
passed out at the river side.
While you're Yubafied,
your subliminal mind can
eject the conscious mind,
creating a state in which your
spirit can easily detach.
Try to remember what happened
during the summer nine years ago.
I'm sorry about everything that's happened.
I'm guilty of being an accomplice in the project.
I'm doing this to atone.
I want to end things right!
You're finally awake.
Where am I?
You're at my grandpa's and my house.
Grandpa found you this morning
and brought you here.
You were passed out by the river, apparently.
I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm Akina.
Iridatsu Akina.
Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you.
No way.
Why is Chiyoko...
See?
Right before you three fell into
the dam, you were Yubafied.
Just then, you were struck by lightning,
and the three of you swapped spirits.
Guriko's spirit entered your body.
Chiyoko's spirit entered Guriko's body.
And I went into Chiyoko's body.
Huh? Where'd he go?
Here.
You weren't here during the day.
I held on to a delivery for you.
Oh, thanks.
From my sister?
I have a bad feeling about this.
She's Mei
Dude, seriously?
It's...
Lose Not to Rain