Dungeons are places such
as abandoned structures,
fortresses, shrines, or caves.
Closed-off areas where battles
with monsters occur.
Many dungeons are home
to low-level monsters,
while more powerful monsters, like dragons,
will sometimes guard treasures there.
And since you have to work in a limited area,
fighting them is more difficult than in the field.
Thus, defeating them requires complex teamwork.
I know this song...
It's the opening theme from
when Elder Tale was a game.
Once girls reach a certain age,
they make their social debut at a ball.
The ten-day conference that starts tomorrow
is also a chance for us to get acquainted.
The Forest of Lagranda
The Forest of Lagranda.
Go and join the dance.
Just look...
Everyone is quite interested in you.
How about it?
What about you, miss?
I am my lord's ninja...
I mustn't be seen in such a public setting.
Then what about you?
No, no...
I'm better suited for other things.
That's right... The obvious choice is...
...Shiroe, right?
As the Round Table's representative,
I'd like to speak with Lord Sergiatte a bit more.
Crusty...
He's doing this deliberately.
I suppose I'll go embarrass myself...
Shiroe...
A gentleman must never show
his lack of confidence.
Right now, you're a member of
the Round Table's delegation.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Okay...
Then, since you're being a good boy,
I'll give you a magic present!
H-Henrietta...
Shiroe, smile.
Thrust out your chest.
Put your hand on my hip.
Just so you know, I can't dance at all.
You know what my class is, don't you?
Class?
That's right.
I am a bard.
Now, then...
Let's dance.
So you are a bard, Miss Isuzu?
Isuzu
Race/ Human
Bard, Lv. 24
Crescent Moon Alliance
What an elegant sound...
It perfectly suits this clear night air!
You're exaggerating...
Um, what's a bard?
One of the weapon-based offensive classes.
But unlike the assassin or swashbuckler,
they play a support role.
Support? Like an enchanter?
Um...
They specialize in lowering enemy stats
or enhancing their allies' abilities.
Or so I've heard.
That's a very bland explanation.
The difference between bards and
enchanters is that they use music.
One trait that distinguishes them is the
long duration of many of their abilities.
Think you've got it, Shiroe?
Mostly...
Basically, it's like any other rhythm game.
Right step.
Right forward.
Half turn!
That's it.
Got it, teacher.
Oh, my.
Music, huh?
I'd forgotten about it.
Hey, wait—
Ow...
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Huh? Where are you from?
Play with us!
It's boring hanging around the grown-ups, right?
We're playing hide-and-seek.
Hurry! Hurry!
She disappeared!
Wow!
She's a genius at hide-and-seek!
I'm exhausted.
Yes?
Shiroe?
Can you talk right now?
Oh, Minori...
What's up?
Tomorrow, we're going to a dungeon.
Worried?
It's true that at your current level,
it may be a bit rough...
I'm worried I'll slow everyone down.
Naotsugu and the other
trainers won't be there...
Listen to me, Minori...
You aren't alone.
And there's more to a battle than your level.
Do you remember the basics of
party combat that I taught you?
Oh, yes... Just a second...
Formation, operator, field monitor...
And patrol teams, right?
If you remember that, you'll be all right.
You can do it.
Yeah!
I know I should understand...
Unfortunately, it's something she
has to figure out for herself.
Good luck.
This is good!
This is so good!
The nobility eats pretty well.
So, the cooking method has spread
among the People of the Land...
Doesn't that mean we're affecting this world?
Yes.
And for us to avoid being
a destructive influence,
we need to know more about this world.
Exactly.
I think I understand what you've been saying.
By the way, Shiroe,
did you sleep well last night?
You had quite a workout!
Yes, thank you.
One day, I'll get even with you.
I didn't know you were the type
to hold a grudge, my lord.
How petty.
What about you, Akatsuki?
You seem a little grouchy today.
Not at all.
You are.
Am not.
Are, too!
My lord!
Pear Jam
Maihama
The jam.
Pass me the jam.
Oh, right... Right, right.
By the way, Michitaka...
Did we bring any cooks with us?
Hmm? A few...
We should call in the support squad.
Indeed.
What do you mean?
From the size of this terrace,
I believe they're expecting guests.
Guests?
Nobles?
The conference lasts for ten days.
But it isn't held every day.
The majority is backroom deals
and private meetings.
Like a tea party, you might say.
The politics here are more complicated
than I'd expected...
Within Eastal's League of Freedom Cities,
there are twenty-four noble families.
Add in the Round Table, and it's twenty-five.
Lord Sergiatte's city, Maihama, has a
population of thirty thousand or so.
That puts Akihabara's strength, with its
twenty thousand, into perspective.
I have a good idea as to what the nobles seek.
Their first goal
was to learn the scope of Akihabara
and the Round Table's ambitions.
But last night, at the ball, it's likely that
we dispelled some of those concerns.
So, next, they'll try to win us to their side...
Yes.
Since the Apocalypse,
we haven't received any quests from
the People of the Land, after all.
The May incident caused all this.
Supposedly, the adventurers
call it the Apocalypse.
Until now, Akihabara adventurers
were merely a disorganized mob.
That made them easy to deal with individually.
That's true.
Exterminating monsters, guarding caravans...
As long as we paid them,
they were willing to do anything.
But since then, they've stopped coming
to our territory almost entirely.
And now, they've founded that Round Table,
trying to rule their city just like we do!
I've heard their technology
advances by the moment.
We must get them on our side, and fast!
If we screw this up, we could
find ourselves left behind!
They need our power.
But they'll never act like our inferiors.
Most likely, they'll grant a noble title
to Crusty or the Round Table.
Always trying to put us in their debt...
The problem is how to deal with them
when they come to us individually,
rather than through the Round Table.
It's a difficult problem.
Most likely, some nobles will try to speak
to individuals or to guilds in the future.
But both the combat and craft
guilds are likely to want
to take them up on their offers.
As will individuals.
It's impossible for the Round
Table to monitor everyone,
nor is it our purpose.
But we'll have to establish rules of some sort.
And that's one reason it's so important
for us to know what they're thinking.
And so, Akatsuki...
Your turn.
Go and recon.
Understood.
That is the Forest of Lagranda.
It's fairly large inside, but basically,
at the first branch, the right side
leads to the beginner course.
The left is for intermediate players.
Lagranda Forest
Walkthrough
Don't push yourselves too hard.
It's important to know your own limits.
That's right, don't get yourselves killed.
You'll all be camping in the clearing here,
entering the dungeon each day.
After you return, I'm in charge of your support.
All right, time to split into groups.
After that, each group will
hold a strategy meeting,
then enter the dungeon.
Okay!
Right, let's start by introducing ourselves.
Tohya
Race/ Human
Samurai, Lv. 29
Log Horizon
I'm Tohya.
I'm a samurai.
I'm level 29.
Leave the front rank to me!
Serara
Race/ Human
Druid, Lv. 25
Crescent Moon Alliance
I'm Serara.
I'm a druid.
I'm level 25.
While I'm not good at attacking,
leave the healing to me!
Isuzu
Race/ Human
Bard, Lv. 24
Crescent Moon Alliance
I'm Isuzu!
I'm a bard.
I'll be taking part in attacks, too.
I'm level 24.
Nice to meet you all!
Minori
Race/ Human
Shrine Priest, Lv. 21
Log Horizon
I'm Minori.
My class is shrine priest.
My specialty is defensive magic.
I hope to work in combination with
Serara to keep all of you healthy.
I'm level...
21.
21?
Don't slow me down!
Who are you?
My name is Rundel Haus Code.
You can call me Rudy!
What's your class?
Can't you tell by looking?
I'm a sorcerer.
You sure talk a lot.
What's your level?
Rundel Haus Code
Race/ Human
Sorcerer, Lv. 23
23... Why?
That's hardly different from Minori's!
Do not fear.
My elegant and devastating techniques
will annihilate the enemy.
You can simply stand behind
me and provide support.
Your class doesn't fight in front!
Don't worry over the details.
Um, why don't we hold our strategy meeting?
What are we supposed to talk about?
Yeah, I have no idea...
Um, let's start with our basic formation...
It isn't hard, guys.
Just get yourselves fired up!
Um...
Yeah! That must be it!
We're about to go fighting!
Well...
It's a dungeon, a dungeon!
We should be fired up!
That's right...
Although we must also be elegant and noble.
But a man must be fired up and hot blooded!
You really do get it!
I can't get a word in...
Okay, let's go.
Tohya, do you remember
what you promised me?
Master...
The job of a front-line tank is
to absorb all the enemy hits,
and to trust his companions.
Tohya,
as a man, you must promise to do that!
Of course I remember.
Okay, then!
What's wrong with Minori?
O-Oh, it's nothing...
Listen, if you ever have a problem, step forward!
With your heart, not your legs.
My heart?
Right!
What? What?
An enemy attack?!
Calm down! We need some light first!
Understood. I'll handle this.
I hope the enemy won't
see it and come for us...
That's exactly what I hope they'll do.
What?
Most of the enemies here are undead.
I get it!
The undead can locate us, even in the dark.
So the darkness acts to their advantage.
Fox Light!
Mine is brighter!
See?
That isn't the issue!
In battle, you're supposed
to have multiple lights.
Oh... Then it isn't that my light is weak.
Of course it isn't, since I'm awesome!
B-Bones...
It looks like one of the groups that went
before us fought skeletons here.
The path splits!
Wasn't the right for beginners,
and the left for intermediates?
Seems the ones before us went left.
For today, we'll go this way. C'mon.
Sure.
But don't assume I'll always be turning right.
Um, Rundel Haus...
You can cast your magic from the back row.
What are you talking about, Miss Minori?
The battle begins the moment
the enemy's in sight.
I need to minimize the lag between seeing
the enemy and using my magic.
If he gets into trouble, I'll help out.
I can't heal as well as Serara,
though we're both healers,
but my magic can cancel a certain
amount of enemy damage.
The samurai's strength is its powerful attacks,
but they have a long cool down...
Knowing when to attack is hard.
Stop.
Skeleton                   Skeleton                   Skeleton
Rank/ Normal         Rank/ Normal         Rank/ Normal
There are three.
Okay, I'll go first.
Tohya!
Don't just charge straight ahead!
I know!
Iizuna Slash!
The samurai also has ranged attacks!
Now, come and get me!
I see.
He was drawing the enemy's attention.
Whirlwind Slash!
How's that?
Tohya
Race/ Human
Samurai, Lv. 29
Log Horizon
Purification Barrier!
Oh, no...
I need to use my magic first, or it won't work!
Heartbeat Healing!
Tohya, ten seconds until you're
back to full health.
Not bad, Mister Tohya.
Now it's my turn!
Orb of Lava!
Wow.
It's a ranged attack, but it's so powerful!
This is the power of the sorcerer,
the magical attack class?
I did it! It worked!
Isuzu, what did you do?
I set up a support song in advance.
Round Carol...
If a party member attacks with magic,
it automatically follows up with another attack.
That's amazing, Miss Isuzu!
My artfully destructive spells have
reached the level of legend!
Grazie!
Nice play.
Rundel Haus...
Behind you!
What's wrong, Miss Minori?
Have you fallen in love with my beautiful magic?
They're targeting you...
Wh-What's happening?!
Skeleton Archer
Rank/ Normal
There's another one?
Stop!
We haven't checked over there yet!
Five skeletons.
Tohya, fall back!
No, my health's recovered.
I'll tank!
They'll attack from multiple directions.
At times like these, I must stay calm.
First, I should cast magic
to protect the front row.
No... It takes too long to cast!
Then I'll just burn them to ash again!
Wait!
Wh-What's happening?
Rundel Haus's aggro exceeded Tohya's!
What?!
It's no good!
My healing magic won't make it in time!
Only one thing left!
Run!
This is pathetic...
This is truly pathetic!
Your army must be very fortunate
to have a commander like you.
Your strength rivals the Eastern Knights!
You flatter me.
How about it?
I brought some good alcohol from home.
The sun's setting...
Why not join me for a drink?
I'm sorry, Lord Kiliva...
But I have another engagement.
Another engagement?
Oh, Princess Lenessia...
I understand.
I can't interfere with that, after all.
A pleasure to meet you.
I am the adventurer Crusty.
The winter rose of Eastal.
Long, silvery hair,
a delicate curve to her neck,
a mysterious light in her blue-gray eyes.
Her name is Lenessia El Arte Cowen.
Her dream is to lie in bed
all day, in her pajamas.
Shield and Freedom
Next time: Shield and Freedom.
Always look thirty seconds ahead.