Aw, damn it.
If we had won yesterday,
we'd be in a match right now.
Now if only Karasuno can beat Shiratorizawa,
we'll look a little cool.
No, we wouldn't.
If their #10 wasn't there,
we would have won.
No, you mean the setter.
That guy is insane.
I think it was the captain.
The one that was the most
interesting was their #10 though.
The captain, huh?
Well, you've got a point.
Sort of like the foundation
that no one really notices?
Haikyu!!
Sawamura-san!
Daichi!
Daichi-san!
Episode 17: "The Battle Without Will Power"
What's going on?
What's wrong?
He's on the ground.
What's going on?
They collided.
Right after they returned that last ball,
#5, the bald guy, and the captain
crashed into each other.
It looked like he hit his head pretty hard.
Seriously?
Ow...
Where did you get hit?
M-My face?
Sawamura-kun, where are you right now?
Sendai City, in the gym.
Who are we playing right now?
W-Wakunan.
I'm fine!
But it appears that you hit your head,
so please go to the infirmary.
Right.
Go have them confirm that you really are okay.
That's the quickest way for
you to return to the match.
Yes, sir.
Blood...
Eh?
Did you cut your lip?
He doesn't seem to be dizzy.
A tooth?!
There's a possibility their captain
won't be playing any more this match.
Though that's the coach's decision.
It'd be scary if he had a concussion, though.
Sensei, can I leave the rest to you?
D-Daichi-san...
I'm sorry—
Sorry, Tanaka.
I saw you go in for the cover,
but my body moved on its
own and went in there.
But look.
Because you got that ball over,
we're now in the 20s.
Karasuno                                                 Wakunan
Baldy from Karasuno usually displays
a high level of mental toughness,
but he's used to being forced into a corner.
I wonder what he'll be like now,
since he broke their leader.
If they lose this match,
it'll probably be the captain's last.
Sorry, Asahi. I'll be right back.
Hold things down until then.
I'm counting on you.
Of course. Leave it to me.
He's walking on his own,
so I think he'll be okay.
But the problem is this match.
I wonder who's going to take
charge in their head's place?
The second setter, maybe?
Unless there's someone who
often practices in pairs,
a setter who's skilled enough in both offense
and defense to take on a wing spiker...
It'll be hard for someone to fill in.
A wing spiker to take his place, huh?
I'm not sure if Karasuno has one.
You're the only one we have.
We're counting on you.
Chikara! You've got this!
He played in the practice match.
What was he like again?
I don't really remember him.
Well, he seemed like a guy
who can handle things well.
Karasuno doesn't have a lot of players,
so they may just not have anyone else.
This is the same as a practice match...
Same as a practice match...
Same...
Well, go out there, and
give it all you've got.
This isn't the same!
Playing behind him and taking
his place are completely different.
Oh, so it is you, Ennoshita-san.
Is it okay if we start with a fast attack?
Ah... Sure.
Chikara! Their #1 tends
to hit toward the outside,
so keep that in your head.
R-Right...
Ennoshita-san, you've got this!
Ennoshita, you have every
right to be worried.
Let's do this!
But if anyone has to replace Daichi,
You can do it!
everyone on our team
thinks it should be you.
Ennoshita, sorry.
We're counting on you.
Fly
What do you mean, "sorry"?
About running into Daichi-san?
Of course one of you got hurt
after something like that.
In the end, maybe it may cause
Daichi-san to leave the match,
but what's on our minds right now...
Asahi-san, if you would.
...is how glad we are that
you weren't hurt, too.
Right, right. Come on, come on.
Our offense is already weakened
just by having Daichi-san out.
If you get depressed,
it'll just make things worse.
Wow, this is surprising.
At first glance, Ennoshita seems
like he'd be pretty timid.
No way!
Judging by how he is whenever
he's over at our place,
Chikara's definitely the
don of the second-years.
He's the best wing spiker for managing
the out-of-control second-years
who are the core of our offense.
And lately, his influence has spread to
our first-year troublemakers, too.
True...
Ennoshita, nice serve!
Nice receive!
Center!
All right!
All right...
We're gonna take this back quickly.
Damn it... I'm sorry.
All right!
I'll guard a little wider.
Thanks, Nishinoya.
Don't worry!
There's no way I can beat Daichi-san
in technique right now...
We'll get the next one!
But... now that I'm standing here,
Takeru, one more! Nice serve!
there's no point in running away
by making excuses like that.
Not to mention...
I already know that I'd just make things
troublesome later if I run away.
Bring it!
Not bad, Karasuno's substitute captain!
Haikyu!!
Nothing's gonna change with the third-years
taking charge until the spring tournament,
but you second-years need to
at least start thinking about
who's going to be the next captain.
That's what Ukai-san was saying.
The next, huh...
I think Chikara should do it.
Why?!
Just 'cause.
Wait, you just ate that
popsicle in two bites.
According to the rules, liberos
can't be captains, right?
Yup!
I think Tanaka's qualified, too,
but looking at the first-year lineup...
The simpleton idiots.
The smartass.
Yeah... you can't help but think that we
need someone with a sound mind in charge.
I agree with having Ennoshita as captain,
but I'm not fully satisfied.
You two need to put yourselves in, too!
Nope, nope, nope, nope...
Yeah, not happening.
Damn it!
But I ran away...
There's no way I could lead the team.
Summer vacation one year ago...
Not yet! Not until you can do this!
Come on! Don't get exhausted after that!
The day after, we lost two first-years...
At this rate, we're never gonna finish!
And a few days later...
I had gone to practice ever
since junior high, but...
I skipped one for the first time.
I pretended to be sick.
I felt guilty,
but I didn't have to deal
with that painful practice,
or being yelled at.
The air conditioner is amazing.
The next day,
and the day after that...
I don't have to run in the heat.
I don't have to get yelled at.
I wonder if I'm actually some huge masochist.
I-I'm sorry I skipped!
Please let me practice!
Ennoshita, thank goodness you're back.
Well don't come in your uniform, then!
Captain...
I-I'm sorry! I'll go change right now!
Dealing with other people is hard,
but you can't just be nice, either.
Right.
Hey! If you're going, get changed first.
All right, let's get started.
Right!
Get running!
R-Right...
Karasuno... Fight!
Yeah!
Fight!
There were five first-years that
boycotted practice at the time.
Two of them quit the volleyball team,
and seem much livelier now.
Which is better?
That probably depends on the person...
It was harder for me when I wasn't
playing volleyball, so I came back.
But the thought of running away...
...will stay with me
That might be why.
You're back right now and
that's all that matters.
Hey, I won!
I'm gonna get another one.
Not everybody who joins a sports club
is going to be the reckless type.
I don't know much about those who
are a different type than me,
but I think you do.
Well, this is all in the future, so...
Yeah.
All right!
In any case, there's no way
that a coward can do it.
Bring it!
It's up!
Ennoshita, nice!
Connect it! Connect!
Give it to me!
Azumane-san!
All right!
Nice kill!
Chikara! Great job getting it up!
R-Right...
Even if I'm a coward,
even if I'm no match for Daichi-san,
I'm gonna fight!
That's why I came back!
Karasuno                   Wakunan
Asahi-san, nice serve!
Sorry!
All right!
It's okay. Let's get the next one!
Nice serve!
Nice, Asahi!
One more!
Like hell we're giving it to you again!
I'm gonna get this!
Nice, Hanayan!
Wakunan's pretty calm.
Nice!
Don't mind, don't mind! Let's do this!
Yamaguchi...
Yes!
Nice receive!
Shimizu-senpai's calling you.
All right!
Karasuno                    Wakunan
Tanaka, nice kill!
Huh?
When Tsukishima's up to serve,
we'll have Yamaguchi come
in as a pinch server.
In this situation, we just want to avoid
them coming back and taking this set.
We're gonna make a run for it.
All right.
You're too tense.
This isn't like last time when
the other side had the lead.
Right now, everyone's just thinking
we're lucky if we get the point.
Thanks, Tsukki!
Was that him trying to
make someone feel better?
Tsukishima's such a smartass.
Yamaguchi, do you feel like throwing up?
Huh? Not just yet.
Then you'll be fine.
Because I feel like I will.
A-Are you all right?
I can barely stand.
Well done, Ennoshita...
What?!
He knows how to get people to calm down
when they're nervous.
I feel sick...
It'll be okay. It'll be okay.
Just like Tsukki said, we're in the lead.
And I practiced...
Crap! The serve toss was a bit low!
Nice serve!
It's over the net!
Karasuno                        Wakunan
Just one more point!
Yamaguchi, nice serve!
One more!
R-Right...
You've got this, Yamaguchi!
I was lucky that made it over.
But if I miss the next one, the plus
and minus will zero each other out.
Then, I have to...
It's got to be better...
to make sure to get it over.
Huh? I guess he's not doing
a jump serve this time?
Got it!
Nice!
He gave up on a jump floating serve?
Is this some kind of plan?
I think I remember that guy
missing a serve when he was the pinch
server during the Seijoh match, too.
Not to mention, that last
serve was dangerous, too.
I think he's just scared.
Crap! An attack is coming.
Move, legs!
It's falling! Front, front, front!
It's up!
Cover! Cover!
Nice, Chikara!
Azumane-san!
Right!
All right!
Karasuno                                   Wakunan
Asahi-san, that last back attack was awesome!
Thanks.
Hey, Ukai-san's back.
Doesn't he seem really pissed off?
Yamaguchi!
U-Um...
H-He knows.
I think he knows more than anyone else.
What? Was there a problem?
Even if you don't jump,
you can make serves that don't
spin and are hard to receive.
But if you jump and hit it from a higher point,
the ball will travel faster
and with more force.
Huh...
I don't think it's bad to
be cautious right now.
Wakunan                       Karasuno
In the end, Karasuno scored the point.
But...
For Tadashi to be able to fight as hard
as everyone else around him right now,
the serve is all he's got.
If he runs away from that,
there's nothing left.
What else do we need besides pride?
Hey, Tsukishima.
I acted all tough with Tsukki,
Don't you have something
to say to Yamaguchi?
but I'm just a coward.
Why don't you go say something?
I'm so lame...
Ukai-san, how's Daichi-san?
He's fine. There's no worry of a concussion.
But his mouth is bleeding pretty badly,
and he's in a lot of pain.
I'm having him rest for
a while, just in case.
I know.
We're gonna win, and ready
the next stage for Sawamura.
There's nothing else to
think about right now!
Right!
All right, let's go!
Karasuno, fight!
Yeah!
Furiously Vigorous
Nice kill, Ushijima!
Ushijima!
Shiratorizawa                                       Hakusuikan
Shiratorizawa's just got
five more points to go.
Let's go.
Yup.
Also, the match between Karasuno and Wakunan
seems like it's going to go on for a while.
I wonder how Karasuno's
doing without their captain.
Just because a super receive is flashy,
doesn't mean it's good.
If a ball that had always gone up for them
suddenly doesn't go up anymore,
Wakunan                                        Karasuno
that will slowly but surely get to them.
I think...
They're feeling that right about now.
Nothing less from Ennoshita-san.
You'd probably make a good captain.
I wonder who'd be fitting for vice captain...
Tanaka-san and Noya-san definitely aren't it.
Why?
Because they're both kids.
Did that really just come out of your mouth?
Episode 18: "The Losers"
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"The Losers."