Today, I am giving the Honnouji Academy
Student Council system a fresh start!
All students have the right
to attack all other students!
Secret meetings, scheming,
backstabbing, anything goes!
Seven days from now,
reach the schoolyard alive!
FIRST HONNOUJI ACADEMY
NATURALS ELECTION
And then, use your strength to
lay claim to your social
standing once again!
This shall be Honnouji Academy's
first naturals election!
FIRST HONNOUJI ACADEMY
NATURALS ELECTION
"Naturals election"?
In this election, you will not
be choosing some candidate!
You will be choosing yourself!
Your standing! Your strength!
Your way of life!
At 8:30am, seven days from now,
a sudden death runoff
election will be held
with the survivors who
arrive in this schoolyard!
SUDDEN DEATH RUNOFF ELECTION
Fight one another!
Emerge victorious!
And I will grant you your
Goku Uniforms anew!
And now, fellow comrades
of Honnouji Academy!
FIGHT!
EPISODE 8
I WILL WIPE MY OWN TEARS
Iori, begin.
Yes, Milady.
Beginning High Velocity
Life Fiber Jammer Emission.
They're circulating finely chopped
Life Fibers at a speed of 100 m/s.
HIGH VELOCITY LIFE FIBER JAMMER
Any and all attacks are
neutralized by that barrier.
It would probably be difficult
to breach even with Senketsu's power.
Damn, I was thinking this was
my chance to challenge her directly.
She whips everybody into a frenzy,
and then sits behind an impenetrable shield?
It's probably the other way around.
She's ruled absolutely here,
and by sequestering herself,
she's causing a state of anarchy
within the academy. See?
I swear, I'm so sick of her...
This is crazy.
Is she trying to tear down
the order she herself created?
As always, she's taking
things to extremes.
That's Satsuki Kiryuin in a nutshell.
If something is to be done, she doesn't hold back.
Still, this will give us a chance
to kick back and relax for a while.
Ah, I follow you.
Personal time.
In that case, gentlemen,
I will see you in seven days.
That sound just now...
Was that a car key?
I hear he got
his license recently.
It sounds like he intends to see
to Lady Satsuki's
chauffeur needs himself.
His loyalty is impressive.
Okay, I guess we'll meet up
in seven days, too.
I don't think any of
us is a moron who won't
make it to the Sudden Death Runoff Election.
The loincloth is mine!
MANKANSHOKU BACK-ALLEY CLINIC
Gosh, things sure are
crazy in town, huh?
What's with you guys
looking all philosophical?
Well, due to that recent
incident, we learned that
obsessing over short-term wants isn't any good.
Yes indeed, there is luck
in the last helping.
If I wait until everyone's
exhausted from fighting,
I'll be able to lift one or two wallets easy!
Mataro, you never learn!
In that case, sir, I'm gonna
borrow your scooter.
I swindled it from
the owner of a scooter shop
especially for you.
Use it all you like.
Where are you going, Ryuko?
Nowhere special.
Oh, just tooling around, huh?
I'll go with you!
Okay, let's go!
Hey!
I'm not letting go!
Oh, what the hell.
Senketsu, grin and bear it
for a while.
C-Can't breathe...
Aren't you gonna
fight in the election?
Nah, I'm a No-Star.
I don't have anything to lose.
Rather, I'm happy 'cause
it's like a one week vacation!
You have a point.
We'll be outside cheering you on
in the Sudden Death Runoff,
so fight hard, okay?
Will do!
ISSHIN & RYUKO MATOI
Is this—
My family's house.
A wreck like this?
Wow, so you were poor, too!
I wasn't living in
these burnt-out ruins.
It was a regular mansion,
but it burned down.
Oh, it was?
Wait, does that mean
you're a rich girl?!
No, of course not.
My mom died
right after I was born,
and my dad was a scientist who
only had time for his research.
We never got along, so I started living
in the dorms in grade school.
OX ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
I started to turn bad
and fight all the time.
By my first year of high school, I was
a full-blown juvenile delinquent.
And then, six months ago,
I got a message from Dad saying
that he wanted to talk,
so I went home for the
first time in ages.
But...
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Don't make a scene, Ryuko.
If you want to live a peaceful life,
just get up and walk away.
But if you're going to
fight in my place...
...take this Scissor!
What do you mean, fight?
If you take that Scissor, you're sure
to find the person who killed me.
But a cruel fate
lies in store for you...
Hold it!
Let them go, Ryuko!
There's still much that
I have to tell you!
Dad...
DAD!
When we lived apart, there were
times when I hated him.
But when he died, I realized
for the first time
that I didn't know anything about my father.
So I wanted to at least find out
who killed him, and why.
And what he was trying to tell me.
And what this Scissor is.
I want to find those answers.
And to know why my dad
created you, Senketsu.
There's nothing here...
I thought that there might be some
kind of clue where I found you,
but I guess it was
a waste of time.
Mikisugi's doing, no doubt.
Maybe.
I'm sorry, Dad brought home
a messed up scooter.
I can't believe the
gas gauge was busted.
Say, Ryuko.
You have us now.
You're not alone.
It's not just Senketsu.
Me, my family, we all love you, Ryuko.
Sure, I know that.
Then let's hitchhike!
- Say what?
- Hey! Heyhey!
Heyheyheyhey! Hey!
Heyheyhey! Hey! Heyhe—
Jackass! Watch where
you're driving!
What's the matter?
Did you break down?
I reeled in Gamagoori!
Gamagoori! You followed me
all the way out here?
Calm down.
I have no intention
of fighting you here.
Come again?
My fight with you will be on
Sudden Death Runoff day.
What do you want, then?
Get in.
I am Ira Gamagoori, Honnouji Academy
Disciplinary Committee Chair.
If we come across a Honnouji Academy
student in trouble off of campus,
it is the duty of committee
members to assist them.
That holds true even for you.
Get in.
But we can't—
This seat is so soft!
It must must be brand-new!
It's all sparkly!
And your license is
all sparkly and new, too!
Ryuko, let's go for a drive!
Get in, get in, let's go!
On a drive, on a drive!
On a drive to Hell!
Goin' totally upside-down
to the bottom of the pit! Hey!
We've left the track
and are gonna crash!
Matoi, make her stop
that god-awful singing.
Hit someone from behind
and you get a pileup!
Do you honestly think
anyone can make her stop?
We'll all go to hell together!
True, Mankanshoku has
never had a red light.
On a drive, on a drive,
on a drive to Hell!
That's right!
My life's traffic lights
are always yellow!
"In life, proceed with caution," eh?
There is truth in that.
What nerve! This is a no-passing zone!
Doesn't he know the rules of the road?!
Mako, get down!
Who the hell are they?!
The Automotive Club and
Airsoft Club merged to form
the Automotive Airsoft Club.
I'm the one that
they're gunning for.
It's because Maiko Ogure
proved that no one
but you can wear your Kamui.
So what they're after is your
Three-Star Goku Uniform, huh?
Ryuko, look at that!
What's the matter, Gamagoori?
AUTOMOTIVE AIRSOFT CLUB PRESIDENT
RYOSUKE TODOROKI
Do you think you can escape
Automotive Airsoft Club
President Ryosuke Todoroki in that clunker,
Mr. Disciplinary Committee Chair?!
Looks like we picked the
wrong car to get into.
Whoa!
Interesting!
But can you keep up
with my driving skills?
H-How can this be?!
Don't give me that!
When you spin the steering wheel like
a maniac, you're obviously
gonna spin out!!
Is your brain as rookie
as your license?
Ow... You okay, Mako?
Oh, you guys think
you're hot stuff, huh?
Matoi, stay out of this.
What?
It was my mistake,
so I'll fix it.
We have you cornered, Gamagoori!
Cry or shout all you want,
you'll get no mercy from us!
It'll take more than the likes
of you to make me cry!
And even if I did shed a tear,
I would wipe it away myself!
I would ask no one else to!
You're still gonna talk big, huh?
Let him have it!
Three-Star Goku Uniform:
Shackle Regalia!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
SHACKLE REGALIA
H-He transformed!
Don't let that faze you!
Get him!
Man, that thing is hard...
It's not just hard.
That's it! More!
Punish me more!
I've been a bad boy!
Punish me! Every time you punish me,
my heart is whipped!
Yes! The more it's whipped,
the stronger I become!
Just like I was that day...
THREE YEARS AGO
RINNE-DO JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL
Go on! Hurry up and jump!
You got milk on my uniform.
That was an accident...
That's why we're saying we'll
forgive you if you jump off.
You there! What are you doing?!
IRA GAMAGOORI
THIRD YEAR JUNIOR HIGH
Well, well, if it isn't the
Student Council President.
But you're going to stand there
and do nothing.
Gamagoori, it's okay!
If I don't do as he says,
my dad will be fired!
Yeah, his dad works at
my old man's company.
And my daddy is this
town's chief of police.
He covers up little things
like this for me.
Hojo! Imagawa! Do you two
call yourselves human beings?!
That's right, we're humans.
We're humans, so we understand
the fear of status and authority.
And sacrificing himself for
the good of his family is
the mark of a true human being, right?
Go on, jump!
Wait!
How about that, Gamagoori?
You can pull that righteous
act all you want,
but here at Rinne-do Junior
High, no one can oppose us.
Damn it!
The Kiryuin Deluxe Trampoline
bounces well, doesn't it?
Come here!
Let go!
If I live, my dad will get fired!
You needn't worry about that.
I have bought out
that despicable company.
What the hell?
What are you, a new student?
What's this crap you're spouting?
Yeah! If you keep talking rubbish,
I'll have my daddy arrest you!
Your father has just been
relieved of his duties.
If you don't believe me,
look at this.
- KIRYUIN PRODUCTS ABSORBS HOJO PRODUCTS IN MERGER
- CHIEF OF POLICE IMAGAWA ACCUSED OF BRIBERY
W-What the hell?!
Who do you think you are?!
Everyone! Make her suffer!
First Year Class A,
Satsuki Kiryuin!
SATSUKI KIRYUIN
FIRST YEAR MIDDLE SCHOOL
As of this moment, I rule over every
student in this junior high school.
Crooks like you, who can't see
beyond their own self interest,
will no longer be
tolerated by me.
But you are using your
parent's influence, too!
How are you any different
from these two?
These petty thugs are merely leeching
off of their parent's power.
I am different!
The power of my parent, of others,
I will exploit everything to my ends!
But I am the one
who uses it!
I absorb all their power
and make it my own!
It is a difference of resolve.
Resolve?
Gamagoori.
Those who lack resolve are incapable
of even wiping away their own tears.
That was how I first met
Lady Satsuki!
And for two years, I waited.
I awaited her graduation, enrolled
in Honnouji Academy at her side,
and acquired this Goku Uniform.
Hang on, how old are you?!
I turn 20 this year.
That explains your old man face!
How much longer are you
gonna keep yapping?!
Yes! That's more like it!
The more I'm punished, the more
my hardness towers mighty and strong!
He's a pervert with
an old man face...
Not pervert, convert.
The instant I reach my climax,
the power that has been building
up inside of me will burst out...
...all at once!
Three-Star Goku Uniform:
Scourge Regalia!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
SCOURGE REGALIA
Oh, wow...
A secondary transformation, eh?
BACK-ALLEY GAS STATION
SELF-SERVE
Be careful.
They say "a picnic is not
done until you reach home safely."
Jeez, it's not a picnic...
I'll be waiting for you at the
Sudden Death Runoff Election.
I'll arrange a fitting spot
for our battle.
Come again?
HONNOUJI ACADEMY
8:30AM
It is time, Lady Satsuki.
Fellow comrades of
Honnouji Academy!
You have done well to struggle through
seven days of mortal combat
to gather here to take part in the
Sudden Death Runoff Election!
However, your battle
has only just begun!
Every battle over the last seven
days has been recorded!
With that in mind, I will
begin by designating new
Three-Star students based on the results of the battle here!
What the—?
There are five towers
in the schoolyard!
Those standing atop
them will be considered
front-runner candidates, and
the election will be conducted!
There she goes, being devious again!
Fine by me!
Well, well. I see you aren't called
the Elite Four for nothing.
Did you expect anything else?
Lady Satsuki!
We, the Elite Four, hereby
propose a new rule
for the Sudden Death Runoff Election!
We each wish to be allowed to face
Ryuko Matoi in single combat.
If we're going to fight her anyway,
this grand stage is the place for it.
I believe it to be a fitting way to cap off
the climax of the Naturals Election.
This should prove
just as amusing, huh?
NATURALS ELECTION
POLLING PLACE
KING OF THE HILL
FINAL BATTLE
This is a king of the hill
final battle!
Matoi! Battle the Elite Four
and emerge victorious!
Do so, and I shall tell you the
details of your father's death.
Say what?!
Matoi! This is where
I will face you in battle!
I am Lady Satsuki's
impenetrable shield!
And this is where I am
going to crush you!
I accept!
Life Fiber Synchronize,
Kamui Senketsu!
KAMUI SENKETSU
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
A king of the hill-style final battle!
Her first opponent is Ira Gamagoori!
IRA GAMAGOORI
From Shackle Regalia
to Scourge Regalia,
feast your eyes on his fearsome,
two-stage transformation!
TRANSFORMATION
HARDASS
This straightlaced hardass stands
mighty and erect on the battlefield!
STANDS
Next time on Kill la Kill,
"A Once in a Lifetime Chance"!
EPISODE 9
A ONCE IN A LIFETIME CHANCE