The fifth match,
the exam with Team Uraraka
and Aoyama against Thirteen,
is in its final stages...
"Yuga Aoyama - Quirk: Naval Laser"
"Ochaco Uraraka - Quirk: Zero Gravity"
We were so close!
"Pro Hero - Thirteen - Quirk: Black Hole"
Oh no, I won't let you get away!
This isn't good. We'll get caught!
Think!
Think about how to get out of this!
What would Deku do in a time like this...
Hey.
Hold on! Right now, I'm--
You were thinking about what
Izuku Midoriya would do, weren't you?
Do you...
...like him?
You should not fight on your opponent's field
"Pro Hero - Gunhead"
but on your own field, see?
What?
Whee!
...and catch!
What I learned with Gunhead just
happened to come in handy right now!
"Stripping the Varnish"
Team Aoyama and Uraraka have passed!
Nice judgment, Uraraka!
"Izuku Midoriya - Quirk: One For All"
"Tsuyu Asui - Quirk: Frog"
I can't believe she thought to use
her opponent's power to get in close!
Ribbit...
To me, it looked like Ochaco
just happened to let go, though...
Really?
Yes. I wonder what she was talking
about with Aoyama right before she let go?
Who knows? We can't hear
what they're saying over here.
"Recovery Girl's Temporary Nurse's Office"
Uraraka passed, huh? I don't expect any less.
"Tenya Iida - Quirk: Engine"
"Momo Yaoyorozu - Quirk: Creation"
Congrats to you and Yaoyorozu, too!
Ribbit!
Thanks, Midoriya.
I wonder which team will
take the practical exam next?
The sixth match is Team Ashido and Kaminari.
They will be up against Principal Nezu.
The principal, huh?
I wonder how he'll fight...
We must watch carefully.
--Yeah.
--Ribbit.
Team Ashido and Kaminari, practical exam.
Ready, go!
Kaminari, what do you wanna do?
Basically, run.
Even if we're found, the principal's small,
so I should be able to take
care of him with my electricity.
"Denki Kaminari - Quirk: Electrification"
"Mina Ashido - Quirk: Acid"
Ashido, you shouldn't use your Quirk!
It'll be bad if you melt the principal.
Yeah, right?
What's that sound?
It's not the principal... is it?
Run!
Kaminari, what's going on?!
I dunno, but I'm sure the
principal's behind it!
That's right.
The principal's riding in the crane?!
But how is he attacking them...?
He's so far away from them.
It's probably with his forecasts.
Forecasts?
Yes. What's more, he probably reached
those through sophisticated calculations.
What chain reaction will be caused
depending on what I break where...
Those calculations are
as easy as making a cup of tea.
And you two aren't noticing...
...that the paths to the escape gate
are getting sealed off one by one.
Intellectual-type villains will sit back
and watch from the sidelines.
"Nezu - Quirk: High Specs"
Principal Nezu. Quirk: High Specs.
He's an animal with a Quirk that
makes him smarter than humans!
He's a unique being that you
won't find anywhere else in the world!
"Pro Hero - Recovery Girl - Quirk: Heal"
Humans did a bunch of
experiments on Nezu in the past,
so in times like this, he can't
help but let out his true self.
Kaminari, you can't do
anything with your electricity?
I don't know where he is,
so I can't waste my shots.
Do you want a dead weight on your hands?
Anyway, all we can do is run!
Which way's the escape gate?
Probably... this way!
No way...!
Is he trying to bury us alive?
There's still a way out!
Come on, use your heads!
Think carefully! Rack your brains!
Kaminari, this way!
Okay!
We'd end up taking a detour,
but if we go out through the
other side to the escape gate...
He's one step ahead
of everything they can think of.
And they can't attack if they
don't know where the principal is.
His plan is so completely perfect...
In the end, they couldn't make it to
the escape gate before time ran out,
and--
Team Ashido and Kaminari
retires due to running out of time.
--Damn it!
--Man!
And I left one escape
route for you, too. Too bad.
Kaminari... Ashido...
They really couldn't do a thing.
They must be very frustrated.
What? Mina's team lost?
Yes. The principal's
strategy was too perfect.
Really? That's too bad!
Uraraka, congratulations on passing!
Thanks! You too, Iida!
Ochaco, when you were
fighting against Thirteen,
what were you talking to Aoyama about?
Hm? We were talking about...
Do you... like him?
...n-nothing! That's not how it is!
--What's the matter, Uraraka?
--Th-That's not it! It's not!
--Your face is red. Are you sick?
--It's not! It's not!
Something happened, huh, Ochaco?
Team Koda and Jiro, practical exam.
Ready, go!
Let's avoid combat with Present Mic
if possible and head toward the escape gate.
"Koji Koda - Quirk: Anivoice"
"Kyoka Jiro - Quirk: Earphone Jack"
Sound good?
All right, let's go!
The practical exam matches up
students with the teachers
they'd have the hardest time
with on purpose, right?
Yes.
It's easy to understand
Jiro and Koda's match up.
Ribbit.
They're up against Mr. Present Mic.
The two of them have sound-related Quirks.
What will they do against
a Quirk that drowns out sound?
"Do your best!!"
Come on, let's hurry up and finish this.
I don't like working with
ardor in an arbor like this.
"Arbor"                  "Ardor"
Yeahhhhh!
So loud...!
Koda! You can control animals
with your Quirk, right?
Can't you get the birds
to attack him or something?
"Even if I wanted to order them to do that,
Present Mic's Voice
will make the animals run away!"
Even if I plug my ears,
I feel like my eardrums would burst.
He's not just better...
He's like a new and enhanced version!
I can't even get close to him!
Even if we got close to him,
whether to handcuff
him or escape through the gate,
he's probably in front of the gate,
so we wouldn't be able to avoid fighting him.
Hurry up and...
...come out!
My ears...!
You coming yet?
I can't take this anymore! I can't...
"Present Mic - Quirk: Voice"
Present Mic. Quirk: Voice.
He's got crazy volume,
crazy high pitches, and crazy low tones.
"'Put Your Hands Up' Radio"
"Every Friday night from 1 a.m. to 5 a.m.
on HERO FM! It's a nonstop blast!" "Please listen~"
With his first cry, his parents and the delivery
doctor had blood coming out of their ears.
By the way, the device on
his neck is a directional speaker.
Hurry up!
If this keeps up, our eardrums'll be shot.
What should we do?
An ant?
Koda! Can you control bugs?
There was a bug! A little ant.
He's not good with bugs, huh?
There you are!
This isn't good... For now...
Cancel out!
What a cheap sound.
Do you have a plan?
--What should we--
--You coming yet?
W-We need some way to break out of this!
At this rate, we won't even be able
to get close to him.
What a joke!
Koda...
Just tell me if it's possible
for you to control bugs or not.
"It's possible..."
Then...
Sorry, I know it's scary, but...
Hey...!
...he's too strong!
I can't think of anything else!
If you can do it, we might be able to win!
You can do it. You want
to be a hero, don't you?
If so, then let's pass this!
Jiro's ears are...
Because I've just been
running away, Jiro's...
You got into U.A.?
As your mom, I'm so happy!
Koji, you're amazing!
That's right, I got into
my dream school, U.A.!
U.A., where we're always moving forward!
That's right, my heart
should always be Plus Ultra!
"tremble tremble tremble"
Go on, little ones. Now is the time to
take out the man responsible for the noise.
--You can totally talk!
--Listen...
What, are they planning
on hiding until time's up?
They're coming from underground,
where it's hard for sound to travel...!
This is why I hate forests!
That's hard even for a pro...
Koda, that's harsh...
How pathetic, to be taken down by some bugs!
Team Koda and Jiro have passed!
"Affiliation: U.A. High School Hero Class 1-A"
"Birthday: 5/30" "Height: 168 cm"
"Blood Type: O" "Likes: Himself"
"Yuga Aoyama"
"Quirk: Naval Laser"
"He can shoot a strong laser beam from his bellybutton."
"Affiliation: U.A. High School Hero Class 1-A"
"Birthday: 2/1" "Height: 186 cm"
"Blood Type: A" "Likes: Nature"
"Koji Koda"
"Quirk: Anivoice"
"He can put his will into his voice
and make animals do as he says."
"Eighth Match"
"Team Hagakure and Shoji vs Snipe"
Shoji, at this rate, we can't move at all!
"Toru Hagakure - Quirk: Invisibility"
"Mezo Shoji - Quirk: Dupli-Arms"
Calm down, it's just a diversion.
Even so, escaping will be a Herculean task.
The only consolation is that our opponent's
movements are slowed by the weights.
Now, let's see who's better at hide-and-seek.
A smoke bomb?
Is he trying to obstruct our view?
But he'll have to deal with it, too.
"Pro Hero - Snipe - Quirk: Homing"
However, I can feel your presence.
Are you all right, Hagakure?
Hagakure?
So that's what she's doing.
You're being too rash!
Aren't you giving up a little too easily?
Got him!
When did you--
Bounce?
Mr. Snipe!
It was a misunderstanding! It was beyond
my control! I didn't do it on purpose...!
Team Hagukure and Shoji have passed!
As expected, Hagakure is a cut above
when it comes to covert activities!
Shoji also did a good job helping by
drawing Mr. Snipe's attention away from her.
--Ribbit.
--Yeah!
Team Mineta and Sero, practical exam.
Ready, go!
Deku, you're up next, right?
You're not going to the exam area?
Oh, yeah, it is, but I'll watch
everyone fight until the last minute.
It's useful to see how
everyone's using their Quirks,
but I also feel like I'm getting
strength from watching them.
Everyone's really amazing.
Even if they couldn't pass,
they fought until the end...
They're all excellent
U.A. students who never give up!
Yeah!
Well...
There's one...
...who's totally given up.
Mineta?!
Damn it! How can I take this stupid test?!
"Minoru Mineta - Quirk: Pop Off"
This is crap! It's completely unfair!
How can I take such an unfair test?!
But he was looking forward
to the training camp so much!
Why is he so ready to run away?
If it's gotten that far,
it might be hard for him...
For this practical exam,
All Might, Mic, Cementoss,
and Midnight are all especially hard.
Depending on the person,
it isn't hard to imagine someone being
checkmated or feeling like they are.
"Midnight - Quirk: Somnambulist"
Midnight. Quirk: Somnambulist.
She can make people fall asleep
with the fragrance coming from her body.
It works better on boys than girls!
It's working, it's working.
"Hanta Sero - Quirk: Tape"
Grape Juice, the gate's
in the opposite direction.
Sero, damn it! I won't forgive you!
Why is he crying blood?
Maybe because he's jealous of Sero?
Sero, you bastard!
Look out!
Don't get too close, Mineta!
Chest!
And--
Knees!
If Sero hadn't saved me, then I'd
be in that position right about now!
Mineta...
It might be hard for a kid
like that to survive in this place.
What do you mean?
U.A. is constantly preparing walls
and making the students overcome them.
In order to keep overcoming
those walls without losing steam,
the students need a
concrete goal to focus on.
It's not so easy a path that one
can climb it with vague feelings
of wanting to be a hero.
Even if they do become heroes,
people whose end goal is
to become a hero have no future.
In the end, is there a goal in
that child's heart that he can focus on?
I want to touch a woman's body...
I want to be popular with the ladies...
He's very direct.
What the heck? Why is my exam
the only one like this...?
Just one sniff and you'll fall
asleep and be forced to retire...
Jeez!
Mineta, did you really come
to U.A. wanting to be a hero?
Shut up, what's wrong with that?
What? No way, is it really true?
Yeah, I'm serious! Wanna
go together next time?
Yeah, sure!
I wanted to be popular with girls.
That's why I wanted to be a hero.
I thought that I'd be
popular once I became a hero.
I thought that I'd be popular...!
I thought I'd stay enshrined in
front of the gate until time ran out,
but I suppose that's too inconsiderate.
If someone runs away from me screaming,
my sadistic side starts
to throb so much I can't help it.
This is it! The eyes of a
predator who's cornered its prey!
You really are toeing the
line there, Midnight!
That's right, whether it's
through your nose or your mouth...
If you take just one breath,
it'll be over for you.
What do you think you can do in that state?
That's right! You'd run, right?
That's not it.
After coming to this school and
having a brush with death, I realized...
It's not that they're cool
because they're heroes...
They're heroes because they're cool!
Right, Midoriya?
Just how long do you plan on keeping
that up while holding your breath?
That's not it...
It's not that I'm a fan
of pervy heroes like you!
I ran away from the gate, and whined,
and fanned your sadistic side
and drew you all the way here...
I did all that in order to be cool!
Are you saying you had me
in the palm of your hand?
That's fine. I won't let you!
"Your fragrance won't work like this!"
Sero's Tape!
Can you fight in that state of suffocation?
There's no need to fight.
Because my special move...
...already worked!
Grape Rush!
You're pretty amazing.
He got her stuck far away from the gate
so her Somnambulist
wouldn't be able to reach!
Oh, he's pretty clever.
He had me completely fooled.
Thinking it through, wanting to be popular
with girls is also a goal one can focus on.
Jeez.
"Do your best!!"
If you hadn't tried to save me,
then I wouldn't have had to work this hard.
"Good job!!"
Just this once, we'll save
the boobs for another day!
Team Mineta and Sero have passed!
All right, they passed!
Mineta's plan worked!
Ribbit.
Deku, it's your...
Mineta, congrats!
I'll also try to become a great hero so
that I won't lose to the others in our clas...
"Katsuki Bakugo - Quirk: Explosion"
Team Midoriya and Bakugo,
practical exam.
Ready, go!
"Pro Hero - All Might - Quirk: One For All"
"Preview"
Here's the preview!
The last match of the practical exam
is Kacchan and me versus All Might!
In order for us to win against All Might...
...we've got to beat him up, of course!
Kacchan!
I told you, your power isn't needed to pass!
There's no way we can win
if we fight him head on!
I'll win... Because that's
what it means to be a hero!
Next time, "Katsuki Bakugo: Origin"!
I only look at victory! That's all!
Go beyond!
"Next time: Katsuki Bakugo: Origin"
Plus Ultra!