Final Episode
Spring Wind
Kousei...
Kousei!
Arima!
Mr. Arima!
Kousei...
Everybody's watching...
The people who made my life fuller.
The people who called me back to the stage...
Everybody's watching...
I... I can't let them down.
This is the sound that my mother gave me.
The sound that Watari made me notice.
The sound that Tsubaki found for me.
The sound that was born out of my battles
with Aiza and Igawa-san.
The sound that Aiza-san and I created together.
The sound that Hiroko-san made me remember.
I'm so scared... I can't hear...
Somebody...
But you have me.
Yes.
It's just like you said. If I listen closely...
I'm overflowing with so many sounds.
I'm not alone.
From the moment that we meet someone else,
none of us can ever be alone.
We're all connected.
Don't leave me all alone!
Dummy. You have me.
Inside me...
...You exist.
No way am I gonna leave you all alone.
Reach her... Reach her...
I'm piling on everything I have...
Reach her!
Just kick your illness to the curb!
And then, one more time, we'll...
You and I...
Thank you.
Wait...
Please don't go...
Pester me for canelés again!
Call me to kill time again!
I don't care if I'm just Friend A...
Don't go... Don't go...
Please don't go!
Please don't leave me behind!
Goodbye...
If you don't mind, please take this.
Thank you.
For making Kaori's life such a full one.
Kousei Arima
Kaori Miyazono
Sumitani Junior High
Yo!
Dear Kousei Arima.
It feels weird to be writing a letter
to someone who was just with me a moment ago.
You're an awful person.
Laggard, slowpoke, dummy.
The first time I ever saw you
was when I was five...
It was during the recital
for the piano school I was going to back then.
The boy who appeared so awkwardly
drove the audience to laughter
when he bumped his behind on the stool...
He sat before the piano that was too big for him,
and the moment he played that first note...
He became the object of my admiration.
Playing notes as colorful as a 24-color palette,
the melody began to dance.
I did it!
Oops!
I was totally surprised
when the kid next to me burst out crying.
And yet, you're going to quit playing the piano.
After influencing my life the way you did...
Opening Soon!
How awful is that?
Daddy! Mommy!
Hey, welcome home, Kaori!
Are you hungry?
Buy me a violin!
What?
I'm gonna quit piano and play the violin!
What's this all of a sudden?
I want Kousei to play the piano for me!
Awful! Slowpoke! Dummy!
When I found out that we were going
to the same junior high, I was elated.
How could I find a way to talk to you?
Maybe I'll go buy sandwiches everyday?
But in the end, all I could do was watch you.
After all, you guys were all too tight.
There was no space for me to slip into.
Totsuhara University Hospital
I had surgery as a child,
and then got treated regularly as an outpatient.
After I collapsed in seventh grade,
I was in and out of the hospital, repeatedly.
I started spending more time in than out.
I was hardly ever in school by then.
I knew that I wasn't very well.
One night...
When I saw my mother and father
crying in the hospital waiting room,
I realized that I didn't have much time.
That was the moment.
That I...
Broke into a run.
I started doing whatever I wanted,
so I wouldn't bring my regrets with me to heaven.
Those contact lenses
that scared the heck out of me.
Eating a whole cake, which I'd never done before
because I worried about my weight.
Even the music scores
that bossed me around so haughtily...
I played them my way.
And then...
I just told a single lie.
Kaori Miyazono likes Ryota Watari...
...that was the lie I told.
What?!
That lie...
Would bring before me...
Kousei Arima...
It brought you to me.
From: Keiko-chan
What are you doing later?
There's something I want to tell you.
Please tell Watari-kun that I'm sorry.
You two-timer!
Go to hell, you miserable cheater!
What's the big deal!?
All I did was go out with some girl!
You should've gone with me
the day before yesterday!
Well, but still.
I guess it won't take long
for Watari-kun to forget all about me.
As a friend, he's a fun guy,
but I'd rather have someone more intense.
Also...
Please tell Tsubaki-chan that I'm sorry.
I'm just someone who's passing through,
who'll be gone.
I didn't want to leave an awkward mess behind,
so I couldn't ask Tsubaki-chan.
Or rather, even if I asked her straight-up,
"Please introduce me to Arima-kun,"
I don't think Tsubaki-chan
would've been okay with that.
After all, Tsubaki-chan was so crazy about you.
We'd all known that for a long time.
The only ones who didn't know were you...
...and Tsubaki-chan.
Hey, Kashiwagi?
Huh?
Um... Go check on Kousei, will you?
Ask him if he's eating right.
No way.
What? You're so heartless! So callous!
You're the heartless one. It's super-unnatural.
Don't rely on me. Go yourself!
But Kousei... Now that Kao-chan...
Now that the person he was in love with is gone,
I just know that he's feeling down.
I just don't know what I should do for him...
Dummy Tsubaki.
You're such a dummy, it wouldn't do any good
to rack the brains that you don't even have!
Muscle-for-brains!
Don't you think that's a little too harsh?
I don't think it has to be anything special.
It's all right to just be yourself, I bet.
At times like these, you don't listen to your head...
...you listen to your heart.
Where'd you get that perspective on romance?
BL.
Nao Kashiwagi
15 years old
Hasn't had a boyfriend yet
Book Collection: 108
The "you" that my underhanded lie
brought to me
wasn't who I'd imagined.
You were more negative and passive
than I thought,
not to mention stubborn, relentless,
and a camera voyeur.
Your voice was lower than I thought,
and you were more manly than I thought.
And you were... just as gentle as I thought.
The river was so cold and felt so good
when we jumped off Courage Bridge, wasn't it?
The round moon peeking into the music room
looked like a delicious manju bun.
When we raced that train,
I really thought that we could win.
It was fun singing Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star
together under the shining stars, wasn't it?
There's just something about school at night, right?
Don't you think snow
looks just like cherry blossom petals?
To be so consumed by everything off-stage
when I'm a musician...
...that just doesn't make sense, does it?
Look how you've gotten more sensual.
You've grown up, haven't you?
He's so cool!
N-N-N-Not like I want to be able to play
just like Mr. Arima, all right?
What a cliché!
Isn't it funny how the most
unforgettable scenes can be so trivial?
That's not true.
What about you?
Was I able to live inside someone's heart?
Yes, you were.
Was I able to live inside your heart?
You barged right in without taking off your shoes.
Do you think you'll remember me at least a little?
If I ever forgot you...
...you know you'd come back to haunt me.
You'd better not hit "reset!"
As if I ever would.
Don't forget me, okay?
Okay.
That's a promise, okay?
I'm glad it's you, after all.
Will I reach you?
I hope I can reach you.
Kousei Arima...
I love you.
Sorry I didn't finish all the canelés.
Sorry I hit you so much.
Sorry I was such a brat.
Sorry a million times over...
Thank you.
You're so selfish.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
P.S. I'm enclosing something
that I've always treasured.
If you don't want it,
feel free to tear it up and throw it away.
Yo.
...Yo.
Uh... Um... Uh...
What do you think you're doing!?
Don't go thinking you can ever be alone, Kousei!
I'm gonna stay with you forever and ever,
like your guardian angel!
Get used to it!
Spring will be here soon.
Spring, the season I met you, is coming.
A spring without you...
...is coming.
Your Lie in April
Thank You For Watching!