I'll ask once more.
Why did you call me by the
name of the Jealous Witch?
Because you told me to.
I don't know who told you that,
but they have terrible taste!
The Jealous Witch is the epitome of taboo,
and you call me by her name,
which most dare not even say!
That's right!
That's going too far, boy!
If you have nothing to say, I'm leaving.
I have things to do.
Felt!
Were you stalling me?
Are you working with her?!
N-No!
Hey... W-Wait a minute!
You have it all wrong! I'm...
Damn it!
Could someone just treat me a little nicer?
Why was I even...
summoned to this world?
What are you babbling about?
If you don't wanna get hurt, cough up
whatever you've got!
Would you stop it already?!
No one is this damn persistent!
You think you can mouth off to us?
You're in my way! I have somewhere I have to go!
Man, now you've done it.
You stabbed him?
You've gotta be kidding me...
It hurts... It hurts...
N-No! He walked right into my blade!
What are you doing?
Well, no sense in wasting it.
Take anything on him that's worth selling!
Huh?
Whoa, wait! The guards will be here any second!
But Old Man Rom ate those.
How?
C-Could... this be...
Run! We're in trouble!
Well, boy? You want this appa?
Hey, mister...
Huh?
How many times have you seen me now?
What do you mean? I've never seen you before.
Well? Are you buying it or not?
Sorry, but I'm broke beyond compare!
Get the hell outta here!
Wallet, cell phone, corn potage snack, cup noodles.
My tracksuit and sneakers are intact, too.
And naturally...
Thank god. A wound to the back
is a warrior's greatest shame.
Well, with so much circumstantial
evidence, there's no denying it.
It's kinda hard to believe, but this has to be...
A time leap.
And each time, I return to my initial state.
I'll call it
"Return by Death."
I actually get a time-leap ability,
and it only activates when I die.
The precondition being pitiful is so typical.
If I've gone back in time, Satella hasn't
helped me in this fourth life.
Meaning the debt I owed her for saving me is gone.
In that case, I should forget everything, sell this,
save some funds, and use my knowledge
of the modern world to live in luxury!
My dream is taking shape before my eyes!
Right, mister?
Wh-Why are you asking me?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Aw, that's cold...
I don't wanna get caught up
in other people's problems.
Don't talk to me.
Well, I guess "Let sleeping dogs
lie," applies in any world.
But still, there are always softies
who help others, even when
they really can't afford to...
She'd just had something precious stolen.
She didn't have time for me.
Yet she saved some useless stranger,
and even healed him.
Then she let that useless stranger
be pleased with himself...
Even if Satella doesn't know me,
Felt still stole her insignia. And Elsa will...
No matter how many times I repeat
this, that won't change.
They say history repeats itself, right?
Yeah.
If I have knowledge that people
I used to know will be killed,
I can't just ignore it!
Hey, mister...
What do you want, broke kid?
There's something I want to ask you...
Have there been any pickpocketing
incidents around here?
Asking questions, without buying anything?
You really do have guts.
Incidents like that aren't uncommon at all.
Though, that last one was unusual...
They threw some magic around
in the street a few times.
Things that looked like icicles flew
around and lodged in the wall.
But they disappeared fast.
I'm too late?
I thought if I could keep the insignia
from being stolen, then maybe...
Maybe what?
Oh, just talking to myself, but...
Thanks, mister... For telling me,
even though I didn't buy anything.
It's no big deal.
A broke kid, like you, just helped my
daughter after she got lost earlier.
I guess fate is a compelling force, too...
What are you smiling about?
Nothing.
I'll buy an appa next time!
Sure. Buy one, and you'll be a customer.
Get to work, broke kid!
Right!
This means there's only one way.
Before Elsa comes to the loot house,
I have to buy the insignia from
Felt, and return it to Satella!
Wait...
Satella was just an alias, wasn't it?
Then I've gotta get her to tell
me her real name this time—
What are you babbling about?
If you don't wanna get hurt, cough up
whatever you've got!
I'm getting sick of seeing your faces,
Larry, Moe, and Curly.
After doing this four times,
I've learned my lesson!
Guards!
What the hell, you bastard?!
My memory from before was right.
This world does have some kind of police force!
Someone! P-Please, I need a man!
Damn it, shut up!
No, don't touch me... Stop.
I can't hear you. You're not being sincere enough.
Police... Huh?
Don't scare me like that.
I might have freaked out, just a little.
Just a little bit.
Just a tiny, little bit.
Trying to run won't help you.
That's enough.
Red hair.
And a knight's sword, with scratches
made by dragon claws.
It can't be.
Reinhard?
The master swordsman, Reinhard?
Seems I needn't introduce myself.
Although, that nickname is a bit much.
I don't know how much my modest
strength could aid him.
But if you wish to resort to extreme measures,
as a knight, I would have to fight back.
S-Screw this! It's not worth it!
I'm glad we're both safe. Are you unhurt?
A-Allow me to thank you, from the bottom
of my heart, for saving my life!
I, Natsuki Subaru,
deeply admire your selflessness!
No need for such formality.
Once it was three against two,
they lost their advantage.
If I'd been alone, it would have been different.
H-His nice-guy index is off the charts.
Uh... Reinhard-san, right?
You may just call me "Reinhard," Subaru.
He closed our distance like it was nothing...
Well, thanks again, Reinhard.
You're the only one who heard me
shouting and came to help...
Talk about lonely.
For most, it's too risky to face off
against people like them.
As far as it goes, you were
right to call for the guards.
Are you a guard?
You don't look like one...
I'm off duty today, so I'm not in uniform.
And I realize that I don't appear
particularly intimidating.
Come to think of it, didn't they
call you a master swordsman?
My family is fairly unique.
Every day, I feel I'll be crushed
by their expectations.
Anyway, Subaru...
You have quite the unusual
hair, apparel, and name.
What nation are you from?
At the moment, Lugunica is a bit
more restive than in peacetime.
If you have a problem, I'd be glad to help you.
Would you come to the loot house?
The loot house?
N-Never mind... Forget it.
I can't trouble you with that...
I'll handle the rest on my own, somehow.
But... I'd appreciate it if you
could deliver a message.
I'd be glad to, of course.
To whom? And what?
Well, I don't know her name, but...
Have you seen a girl with white
robes and silver hair nearby?
White robes and silver hair?
She's also extremely gorgeous!
No, I haven't.
Then, if you do see her,
tell her not to go near the loot
house, no matter what.
I'll find what she's looking for
and bring it to her myself.
Very well. If I see her,
I shall relay your message.
Thanks.
I'll repay you one day!
All right.
Take care.
Felt's den?
Yeah, just go two streets down that way.
Thanks, I appreciate it, bro.
Don't mention it, bro. Live strong.
The question is whether Felt will return there...
I'd rather catch her before she
goes to the loot house,
and trade her the cell phone for the insignia—
Whoa!
Oh, dear!
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I don't look it, but toughness
is one thing I... have...
What's wrong?
You don't have to be so scared.
I won't do anything to you.
I... I'm not scared...
What gave you that idea?
Your scent.
When people are scared, I can smell their fear.
Right now, you're frightened.
You're also angry, aren't you?
At me.
It's fine.
I'm a little curious, but this isn't
the time to start a commotion.
That's not a very nice thing to say...
If you're too scary,
that beauty will go to waste—
Oh, very good.
Conceal your hostility,
and you'll be even better.
Well, I'll be going now.
Something tells me we'll meet again.
Someone actually lives here?
Elsa hasn't already been here
and trashed it, has she?
I-It's fine, I'm sure...
I don't smell blood.
But it does smell like garbage.
What do you think you're doing,
peeking into someone's house?
Sorry, but there's nothing worth stealing in there.
Beat it!
No, wait! That's not what I was doing...
Shut up! Don't argue!
Whoa, stop...
Calm down! This is no time to fight!
Before it gets dark—
Before it gets dark, you'd better be gone.
I told you, you've got it all wrong...
You don't give up, do you?
I told you to get out of here!
Just listen to me!
P-Please! Just hear me out, Felt!
I came to see you on important business!
How do you know my name?
You want me to steal something for you?
You should have said that first!
You're the one who attacked me right away.
You know, this is a greedy business you're running!
Do you pride yourself on sticky fingers?
It's all a matter of how to stay alive.
If it weren't this, I'd have no
choice but to sell my body.
So, what's your business with me?
Spit it out.
There's one thing I want.
Here and now, I want to buy the insignia you stole!
You aren't associated with my client.
Are you a business rival?
Call her a rival, or call her the
one who killed my parents...
Or even the one who killed me!
You make no sense.
Well, I'm only interested in selling
to whoever pays most.
If you've got an offer that might
be profitable, I'll listen.
Very shrewd...
I have something worth more
than twenty holy coins.
I want to buy your insignia with it.
It's what everyone wants these days, a metia.
That is the power of a metia!
It's a one-of-a-kind item that can capture
and stop a moment in time.
So, how about it?
You don't seem to be lying.
But that's supposed to be me?
I'm way prettier.
If you look this good without makeup,
you're doing fine...
Don't complain.
Well, it is unusual. I'll give you that.
But twenty holy coins? Not likely.
I'm not so stupid as to believe, without question,
everything a prospective buyer says.
Well, of course not.
At the far edge of the slums is a loot house.
The fair thing is to have the codger who
lives there, Old Man Rom, appraise it.
So it still comes to that...
Okay, got it. Let's go.
Right now... Let's move.
On the double!
We'll have him take a look,
and get right out of there!
Hey, hey!
What's your problem?
Why are you in such a hurry?
You're soaked with sweat.
Live strong.
Everyone in the slums says that.
Is it some kind of slogan?
Don't lump me in with those guys!
They're all talk. They aren't strong at all.
They're just a bunch of
stingy losers at life.
That's a bit harsh...
I'm not like the people here.
I have no intention of living out
my life in these back alleys!
And you think twenty holy coins will
make your dream come true?
It's true that it'd be a
huge leap toward my goal.
Even if I were alone, it isn't as
if I couldn't get by with effort.
If you were alone?
Never mind...
What are you smirking about?
You really piss me off!
Don't worry about it.
H-Hey, what're you doing? Stop!
Hey!
Just gotta make it work, huh?
I said, "Stop!"
And only I can do that.
Don't get all sentimental and babble nonsense!
I'll bite you!
It isn't only for her.
I'll change the fate that's waiting for me.
And to do that, I'll...
I told you to cut it out!
So this is a metia...
Even I've never seen one before.
It's fairly delicate, so handle it with care.
Think along the lines of, "If you
break it, you have to die,"
like no do-overs.
Yeah, I'm definitely impressed.
If I were to sell this, I'd take no less than fifteen... no, twenty holy coins.
It's worth at least that.
All right! Negotiations complete!
Now, if we're done talking, let's go for
drinks to celebrate a completed sale!
Hold it!
Why are you in such a hurry?
Life doesn't last forever.
Make every second count. Don't waste any—
Yeah, yeah!
I don't care about all that.
Why do you even want the insignia, anyway?
This insignia is worth a lot more than it looks.
That's why everyone wants it.
In other words, this would sell
for more than a metia—
Hang on, Felt! That's a dangerous way to think!
He appraised it at over twenty holy coins.
Just sell it for that! Don't ask for more!
El— The woman who asked you for it
can't go higher than twenty, either.
She won't pay more than that!
How do you know that?
You just admitted that you're with them.
I don't have time... Please, Felt!
Begging won't help.
I acknowledge you as a negotiating party.
But not hearing what my client
says wouldn't be fair.
The reason I want that insignia
is so I can return it to its owner.
Huh?
I want to return it to its owner!
That's why I want the insignia!
That's all! So please!
Felt, it doesn't look to me like the boy's lying.
Don't get taken in by him.
He's obviously joking around.
Return it to the owner? Ridiculous!
If you're gonna lie, make it believable!
I won't be fooled!
Felt...
Who's that?
It might be for me.
It's a little early, though.
Don't open it!
W-We'll be killed!
Kill you? I wouldn't do something so terrifying.
Reunion with the Witch