N-Now, now, let's calm down, Ryuko.
Bite me! What the hell is going on?
Were you in cahoots with
that Mohawk Man, too?
I-I have no idea what you mean.
Keep playing dumb after
seeing this, I dare you!
See? Here's you and Mohawk Man
in the corner of this picture!
T-That's not—
After I got attacked by Mohawk Man,
I asked Mataro to track him down!
That kid has connections
all over this town.
And he found pictures of a guy
who looked like him drinking.
It also explains why he
brought me to your place.
I was at death's door, dammit,
so tell me what your deal is!
But because of him, the bond between you
and Senketsu has grown stronger.
His name is Tsumugu Kinagase.
I admit, he's a member
of my organization.
As a result of your battle with him,
you and Senketsu have
become true partners!
Now that Satsuki Kiryuin
has her hands on a Kamui,
it was necessary to put
you through a trial
by fire so that you could defeat her.
All that crap was you trying real hard
to use the evidence to justify
what you did, wasn't it?!
I knew it!
That bastard tried to kill Senketsu!
Who are you people?!
I thought you were fighting
against the Kiryuins!
Didn't you say that you'd
need Senketsu to do that?
What are those "Life
Fiber" things, anyway?
What was my dad researching?!
Don't get so angry.
Once I'm convinced that
you're someone I can trust,
I'll tell you everything.
I'm tired of hearing
that excuse from you!
Nudist Beach.
Huh?
We're Nudist Beach.
Are you nuts?
It's the name of our
organization. Nudist Beach!
Forget it.
It was stupid of me to try to get
a straight answer out of you.
Ryuko?
Fine, I get it! I'll keep fighting
and keep growing stronger.
That's what you want, right?
But that really is our name.
Oh well, it worked out in the end.
EPISODE 6
DON'T TOY ME ON A WHIM
SEWING CLUB RESEARCH LAB
UNDERGROUND PARKING LOT
Okay. Load the Life
Fibers into the vault.
SEWING CLUB PRESIDENT SHIRO IORI
I wonder what Lady Satsuki is going
to do with so many Life Fibers?
Mass production of Goku Uniforms.
What else could they be for?
LIFE FIBER
But every time we've proposed
increasing the number
of Two-Star Goku Uniforms
to bolster our ranks,
she was the one who shot it down.
Because prioritizing
the quantity of club
presidents has a very real risk
of lowering the overall quality.
Lady Satsuki was worried about that.
But even so, she decided that we
needed to increase the
number of club presidents.
I guess this means that Ryuko Matoi's
arrival set things into
motion in a big way.
Yeah, even the Anti-Uniform
Guerilla showed up the other day.
And the clincher is the
fact that Lady Satsuki has
donned a Kamui herself.
There are two people who can wear a
uniform that's 100% Life
Fibers and make it work...
Personally, I can't believe it.
Wow! There's something
that not even Information
Chair Inumuta can believe?
It's one unbelievable
thing after another here.
That's what makes this
academy so fascinating.
Ah, I see.
Personally, I came here because I
heard that I'd be able to cut loose.
That Matoi is worthy
of my full attention.
Hold on, Sanageyama.
Have you forgotten Lady Satsuki's
order that the Elite
Four were to do nothing but watch?
Oh? Did she really say that?
It is rather draining, isn't it?
Do try not to overexert
yourself, Milady.
Don't worry. This is the path I chose.
Your tea warms me through
and through, Soroi.
Thank you, Milady.
Do you think you've snuck
up behind me, Sanageyama?
Not at all.
If I had the slightest
intent of attacking,
you could easily kill me
with just that teacup.
What do you want, then?
Let me fight Matoi.
Why?
Need you even ask?
I believe you know perfectly well what
happens when I see someone powerful.
Just like three years ago, then?
THREE YEARS AGO NORTHERN
KANTO, SUSUKIGAHARA
One against 500, eh?
This will make it clear whether or not
Satsuki Kiryuin is worthy to lead us.
I suggest you start practicing
your bowing, then.
I'm Uzu Sanageyama, Northern Kanto
Gang Leader Alliance Representative!
NORTHERN KANTO GANG LEADER ALLIANCE REPRESENTATIVE
UZU SANAGEYAMA (THIRD YEAR MIDDLE SCHOOL)
You've got guts, Kiryuin,
picking a fight with me!
I have no intention of fighting.
SATSUKI KIRYUIN (THIRD
YEAR MIDDLE SCHOOL)
I'm telling you to surrender.
Who do you think you're messing with?!
You used the "Chi" technique,
huh? Impressive.
But that won't work on me!
I've seen through your moves!
You're mine!
You think you've snuck up behind me?
Come.
I'll provide you with the ultimate
stage where you can
unleash your strength...
...the stage called Honnouji Academy.
My bamboo sword is itching to
test out the skills of this girl
who's infiltrated the stage
you've provided for me.
You know the price of failure, I assume?
Not to worry.
I have these eyes. I
can't possibly lose.
Nicely blocked.
I would manage to win in a fight
against your middle-school self now.
That was the way you
moved three years ago.
I assume you were holding back.
As you wish. See what you can do.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
If I win, treat me to tea or something.
That was rude of me, Soroi.
No Milady, though I do find it a
shame. This was your favorite cup.
Make a fresh pot for me.
Very good, Milady.
Hello, you have reached the
Honnouji Academy Student
Council President's Office.
Y-Yes, ma'am. One moment, ma'am.
It is Mistress Ragyo.
This is Satsuki.
What's this I hear about you
putting on your wedding dress?
CHALLENGE TO A DUEL
Attention, Ryuko Matoi of Second Year, Class K.
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school. —Sanageyama
SPORTS GYM #1
That wild monkey beat us to the punch.
If I'd gotten permission to make a move
on her, I would've taken her out first.
Where is Lady Satsuki?
She has stepped out.
She said this battle
was not worth watching.
What's that mean?
So you've come, Matoi.
I was called out by name
by one of the Elite Four.
I couldn't run away from that, could I?
I like your spirit!
Let's get right to it!
Three-Star Goku Uniform: Blade Regalia!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM: BLADE REGALIA
It's not just the Kamui
that can transform!
Hey, I'm impressed, Elite!
Then I'll do the same!
Life Fiber Synchronize, Kamui Senketsu!
KAMUI SENKETSU
Why, you!
I can see all your moves!
Senketsu! I'm going full-speed!
Understood.
What the— Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
No matter how quickly you move,
you can't escape my blade!
Behold! Secret Weapon: Higi Tengantsu!
SECRET WEAPON: HIGI TENGANTSU
As long as I have these eyes,
I can anticipate any
move my opponent makes!
Say what?!
For every motion a human makes,
there is a preparatory motion.
ORBICULARIS OCULI
Of the eyes. Of the muscles.
DORSAL INTEROSSEOUS / ADDUCTOR POLLICIS
Sanageyama instantly reads all
of those preparatory motions
PECTORALIS MAJOR
GLUTEUS MAXIMUS
and preempts any move
his opponent makes.
That is what the Tengantsu does.
And his Goku Uniform succeeds
magnificently in amplifying that ability.
Gosh, Mr. Wild Monkey has learned
some new tricks, hasn't he?
Is that what Lady
Satsuki meant when she
said this fight was not
worth watching? But—
I didn't hear it that way at all.
Keep it together, Ryuko!
I'd love to, but it's all I can
do to deflect all these strikes!
I'm impressed!
But let's see... how you handle... this!
Shinsoku-Senbonzuki!
I've read all your
blocking moves now, too!
Even your Scissor Blade
that can slice a Goku
Uniform to pieces is worthless
if it can't hit its target!
Come on, is it over already?
That's a little disappointing,
don't you think?
That's more like it!
Senketsu. I need you to do me a favor.
I understand. Bet it all on a
single roll of the dice, eh?
Ryuko!
You're mine!
T-They won't come off!
M-My eyes!
Now!
Finishing Move: Sen-I-Soshitsu!
SEN-I-SOSHITSU (FIBER LOST)
Oh, dear. He went and lost.
It would appear that this
is what Lady Satsuki meant.
You did it, Ryuko!
You beat one of the Elite Four already!
You're amazing! And so
fast! And so awesome! Yeah!
This isn't over yet!
I can still fight! Come on, Matoi!
Don't be pathetic, Sanageyama!
You have disgraced the Elite Four!
One who relies overly
on a single skill will
be brought low by that
very same skill, huh?
MANKANSHOKU BACK-ALLEY CLINIC
Ah, that hits the spot.
That feels good?
Yes, irons are wonderful.
It feels like all the wrinkles
in my body melt away,
and my Life Fibers line up one by one.
I'm glad my plan for you
to blind Sanageyama worked.
Being cut up was rather
painful, I'll have you know.
Sorry about that.
Don't worry about it.
If we hadn't won, I wouldn't be
enjoying this pleasant ironing.
True.
And make sure to get
behind my lapels, too.
Be thorough about it.
Man, you're one demanding article
of clothing, you know that?
Ryuko's mumbling to her uniform again.
I think it's fine.
Who's there?!
Iori, I have a favor to ask you.
How was your mother's mood?
I explained to her why
I took out Junketsu.
You needn't worry, Soroi.
I've no time for losers, Sanageyama.
I was overconfident in my eyesight.
Give me another chance!
I'll defeat Matoi for certain next time!
Pathetic.
I don't need subordinates
who lack resolve.
Resolve I have!
Here is the proof!
CHALLENGE
HONNOUJIGAHARA
Giving someone who was
beaten a second chance...
You're a soft touch, Satsuki Kiryuin!
Tell me again after the fight
just how soft I am, Ryuko Matoi.
Watch closely what happens when
you force a man to change.
Three-Star Goku Uniform:
Blade Regalia MKII!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM:
BLADE REGALIA MKII
Be careful, Ryuko.
I'm getting a totally different
vibe than last time.
Let's work fast, then.
Life Fiber Synchronize, Kamui Senketsu!
KAMUI SENKETSU
Sorry about this, Senketsu.
I've covered up every
last eye you've got!
Now you can't use your Tengantsu!
Look, Ryuko!
His eyes are shut!
Iori, I want you to sew my eyes shut.
But if I did that, you'd
lose your Tengantsu!
That's all right.
It was my overconfidence
that made me lose.
Unless my eyes are sewn shut,
I won't be able to beat Matoi!
This is the resolve of
a man who has realized
the error of his ways and
sacrificed everything!
Know that as you face him, Matoi!
Here I come.
What's this intimidating aura?
Men (Head)!
Dou (Body)!
Kote (Wrist)!
Oh, crap! These aren't the
moves of someone with no eyes!
You're terrified, aren't you, Matoi?
Say what?!
Your breathing. The smell of your sweat.
I can see the inner workings
of your mind as clear as day.
I can see it far, far more clearly
than I could with my eyes!
Everything about this world!
Shingantsu. The eyes of the mind.
Sealing his eyes shut boosted his
affinity with the Goku Uniform.
Men! Dou! Kote!
The Goku Uniform is now
Sanageyama's eyes!
His nose! His ears!
Men! Dou! Kote!
He has acquired the Shingantsu,
which surpasses even the Tengantsu.
SHINGANTSU
No one can evade his attacks!
Men! Dou! Kote!
Without your weapon, you have no means
of turning the tables this time.
So you'd think, right?
What the—?
I thought I told you that I
could see the entire world.
Did you think your pathetic
little trick would work?
Men!
Dou! Kote!
Men! Dou! Kote! Men! Dou! Kote!
Men! Dou! Kote! MEN!
It's all over.
It's—
What?!
What? What happened?
The Goku Uniform overheated!
This was no disgrace, Sanageyama.
It was the result of your power
outstripping that of the Goku Uniform's.
Yes, ma'am.
Matoi, you got lucky this time.
That was a close call.
Yeah, I guess the Honnouji
Elite Four aren't all show.
That dude was seriously tough.
But I can't run away from this.
I have to learn the secret
behind Dad's death!
I swapped out the Life Fibers in
your Goku Uniform and restitched it.
It should be able to keep up
with even your movements now.
You think that you've snuck
up behind me, Sanageyama?
Front and behind mean nothing to me now.
Thanks to my eyes being sewn shut,
I can now sense the
world in its entirety.
I only came to thank you for
giving me a fresh start.
Wait.
We had an agreement. Let's have tea.
Thank you, but I'll pass.
My other senses have
become so heightened
that my tongue is sensitive to heat now.
The Mankanshoku family had a dream.
Four people in a one-room house,
along with a dog and a freeloader.
FAMILY
DOG
A FREELOADER
POOR LIFESTYLE
This poor family suddenly find
themselves living in the lap of luxury!
LUXURIOUS LIFESTYLE
TOP
Walk on air as you aim for the top!
WALK ON AIR
Next time on Kill La Kill,
"A Loser I Can't Hate."
EPISODE 7
A LOSER I CAN'T HATE