The Earth has a skin,
and that skin is plagued
by many different things.
One of those plagues is humanity itself.
We are that which cures the
Earth of its plagues.
We are the Council of the Seven Virtues.
Born from the plague, but not of the plague.
Number Zero.
Hatate Souta.
A heretic that can perceive the flags,
and control fate with his own hands.
We must assess this heretic.
Is he a true messenger of the Sacraments,
or will he bring harm to this world?
This will be dangerous.
Man is a rope—a rope over an abyss.
A dangerous across, a dangerous on-the-way,
a dangerous looking-back,
a dangerous shuddering and stopping.
And I think he
represents the rope we see before us.
My name is Daimyouzamurai Mei.
Nice to meet you all.
If Her Flag Breaks
Flag 6
Phew. Don't Scare Me Like That. I Guess You're Just a Little Sister.
Just ask me if you need anything.
If you have any boy trouble,
I'll be glad to help.
I'm not interested in the opposite sex.
Yuri?!
You want to get some crêpes on the way back?
I'll buy.
I gain weight every time I eat too much.
My boobs, anyway.
The world's so unfair!
A person with the same power as me...
Who is this girl?
You just sighed looking at someone.
Who was it, Sou-kun?
My name was on the list.
I'm going to the forest with you!
I get to go on the ocean trip with Souta-kun!
Huh?
Wait a second.
What's going on...
Ocean Field Trip
Forest Field Trip
Hatate Souta
Why is my name on both lists?
Would you like me to clear that up for you?
Yes or no?
Yes, I guess.
Sorry about that, Hatate-kun.
We normally would have
you go on the ocean trip
since your swimming grades are bad,
but Eiyuuzaki-kun threatened me...
I mean, asked me to do something.
So I put you on the ocean trip
during the first half of the trip,
and the forest trip for the second half.
That doesn't really sound like...
You get to see the ocean and the mountains,
and you get to have fun with
everyone from Quest Dorm easily.
Sweet, huh?
Oh, yeah, how about going on a date with me,
while you're at it--
That sounds like a good time, then.
Yes, everyone in Quest Dorm gets
to spend half their time with you.
Sou-kun, Sou-kun,
if you ever get lonely, just come to my room.
H-Huh?
I get the feeling there was just a
"this is going to be trouble" flag.
Non non!
Yay...
The beach, huh?
The beach!
Great. Now we're here.
Let's go!
After hiking you've got
make-up lessons, Akane-chan.
We're going to get you into
shape on those mountains.
Beach!
Souta-kun!
You kind of feel bad for Akane-chan.
Don't worry about it.
We'll be lodging in the same place.
So this is the ocean?!
This is your first time seeing the ocean?
Yeah, my country is surrounded by land.
Anyway, you should come in, too!
Sure.
It feels good on my feet!
You won't rust if you get in
the water, will you, Ruri?
I have special waterproof coating,
so I should be fine.
Souta, don't just stand there. Join us.
R-Right...
I'm surprised you can't swim though, Megu.
You were great at track.
I didn't do any swimming at all...
Why?
Y-You know boy swimsuits
only have bottoms...
But I don't mind now because...
Wh-Why'd you poke me in the eyes?!
I guess I shouldn't have... Sorry.
They have boy swimsuits with a top now!
Tee-hee.
Uh, right.
Why can't you swim, Souta-kun?
I-I...
So this is where you guys have been...
Big!
Wh-What's wrong?
Who knew you had such big boobs...
Girls with bigger boobs look
good in kimonos, don't they?
She was wearing a uniform, though.
Well, whatever.
Go for a swim.
Barf, barf, barf.
That's gross!
Are you okay, Souta-kun?
Do you not feel well?
I can't handle getting
too close to the ocean.
It all comes back to me...
The Premium Ambriel, correct?
Yeah.
What's that about?
You don't know, Granny?
Souta-kun...
He saw all of the destruction and despair.
I didn't know you had such a tough time...
You must have had it rough, Souta-kun.
I'll help you learn to swim, Souta.
Like a grandma taking care of her grandson.
Yeah.
Ruri, watch after little
Nanami and little Megumu.
I'll take care of little Souta, here.
Come to me.
R-Right.
Just think of it as a giant puddle.
Come on.
Barf, barf.
Are you okay?
Sorry for making a mess...
It's fine.
Want to take a break?
Yeah... I think I'll do that, Granny.
Here you go.
Huh?
Oh, thanks.
This doesn't taste like anything!
What's in here?!
I got some milk and put enough water into it
until it looked like your
average sports drink.
Would you like a popsicle for
100 yen to go along with that?
You were trying to sell me things?!
Oh, I didn't really...
I gave that to you because
I thought you needed it.
You don't have to buy anything.
I'll take one.
You're a nice guy.
She'll move the story to the next stage...
It's a story flag.
Is something wrong?
Oh, sorry.
Here's the 100 yen.
Thanks.
You're here on a field trip?
Y-Yeah.
My name's Hatate Souta.
I'm Daishikyougawa Kurumiko.
Daishikyougawa (Bishop)?!
Are you sure you're not getting heat stroke?
No, I'm fine.
Is this your job?
Are you always around here?
I...
You in middle school?
S-Something like that.
I-I'll see you later.
Please buy something again.
Kikuno-senpai and Rin-chan-senpai,
keep whispering this chant every
time they get close to me.
Don't make people get the wrong idea.
We just told you the formulas
you needed to know.
I'm terrible with numbers.
I was wondering why you got assigned to the
forest trip when your grades were so good...
Sou-kun, were you able to swim again?
I...
That's terrible!
You've been through so much...
How long do you have to keep
going through all of this?
Akane...
You're such a good girl,
crying for little Souta over here.
I'd love for you two to have a kid and
show me a cute grandson.
No! No!
I'm sure Nanami-chan and Megu-chan
would make a cuter child!
Why me?!
Not sure I can help there...
Actually, how old are you really, anyway?
It's rude to worry about a woman's age.
Yeah, but I'm kind of curious to know
if you've always looked so young.
Well, if you want to know...
Take a look.
Who's that?
You shrink when you get older.
No... No... No... No...
A few decades and you'll look like me.
Seriously?!
Okay, everyone!
We're about to reach the halfway point for
both the forest trip and the ocean trip.
I can finally get away from the ocean.
So tomorrow, as a change of pace,
we'll have the guy and girls
from the forest trip go to the ocean,
and vice-versa.
Huh?
The beach!
The beach is nice.
Yeah, it really feels like summer.
I've been had.
Souta-kun! It's the beach! The beach!
Yeah, I guess it is.
Let's go. It's the beach!
Wai—
Barf! Barf! Barf!
I'm fine.
You guys have fun.
But...
I can't go and have fun
all by myself without you!
Yahoo!
That was fast.
You just left him there!
That's fine.
I'd feel worse if you guys just sat here
worrying about me instead of having fun.
Sou-kun...
I'll go and have fun.
Let's go, Rin-chan.
If Souta insists...
You're not going to go
swimming today, either, huh?
Nope.
The water's too much.
You must be working pretty hard every day.
If I don't work hard,
my parents in heaven won't be able to relax.
Kurumiko...
I-I have new products today.
I can put these on your tab.
My mom and dad always said that...
I shouldn't depend on other
people and remember that
I need to get by on my own.
That's why I'm all right.
You're strong, Kurumiko.
That's not true.
Souta-kun!
It's a sea cucumber!
It's so slimy!
You're always with a
different girl, aren't you?
Yeah, I guess so.
I finally got it out.
Hm? Who's this?
She's my friend.
Daishikyougawa Kurumiko.
I sell popsicles.
Oh, if you're Souta-kun's
friend, then you're my friend!
Let me buy all of your stock.
Thank you for getting everything.
Here you go.
What a flashy person.
Well, she was born into a rich family.
Rich... family.
Do you like selling popsicles?
No,
I'm just trying to make enough
to live and go to school.
I guess you're working to
put yourself through school.
Thank you.
I-I...
Akane,
it'll be fine.
Yeah.
Sorry...
When I thought about how
there could be someone there
that could just buy all of
my stuff just like that,
I didn't think I belonged.
I don't think you need to be embarrassed.
Struggling to be alive, to look
at becoming something more,
that's something that only humans can do.
It's precious.
No one has a right to laugh
at someone like that.
You're a nice person.
I'm sure that girl means a lot to you.
Akane's such a good person.
Her name's Akane...
I should apologize to
her next time I see her.
I should apologize to you and thank you, too.
The story flag has progressed
to the next stage.
I'll do something special.
What's this?
Whenever I'm having a hard time,
I come here and remember
what my parents told me.
"You shouldn't depend on other
people and remember that
you need to get by on your own," huh?
That's what I thought, too, but...
It isn't that bad to depend
on others, you know?
There's something I couldn't tell you...
When I first gave you that drink,
I knew who you were, that's why I did it.
You knew who I was?
Why would you...
Could you...
My parents were crew on
the Premium Ambriel.
So you hated me because of that and...
No!
You should hate me instead.
It was the duty of the staff to
make sure everyone was safe, and...
The TV and newspapers made
it all sound like your fault.
That was wrong.
So when you said you weren't
going to depend on anyone,
you wanted to carry that burden,
that cross in the stead of your parents?
Everything's been so hard every day.
I wanted to give up on everything.
And that's when I saw you.
I'm not the only one in pain.
It's embarrassing I thought that.
I'm sure you won't forgive me for
trying to seek help from you...
I forgive you.
There was no reason
for you to carry that cross.
You're really nice.
No way.
Onii-san?
The tide
came in?
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't brought you here...
It's fine.
Don't blame yourself so much.
If I had a brother like you,
I'm sure I would
have been a lot happier.
Same here.
If I had a nice sister like you,
I'm sure everything would be different now.
Um...
Is it all right if I ask you something?
Is this...
If we're able to get out of here safely,
would you promise we'll become
brother and sister in spirit?
Death flags...
I need to get rid of those...
I'll tell her no...
Wait... No, I don't know
why, but that's not it.
I don't need to tell her no.
Kurumiko,
let's become real brothers and sisters,
not something "in spirit."
Onii-san?
Is this the power of the story flag?
Yes.
I'll do my best to be your sister.
I don't have to worry about anything
having a nice brother like you.
I'm happy with just you as my brother.
Why are they coming up like that?!
Fine...
Come with me to Hatagaya Academy!
Huh?
There's a middle school dorm there!
I'm sure we can do something
about the tuition!
Also...
everyone there helped me.
I want to help you this time.
I guess you might not want to go, but...
No, that's not true.
Huh?
Wh-What's that?
Mimori-san told me that it would be
good to surprise people like this,
so I gave it a try.
Don't do stuff like that!
Someone came to save us?
Or should we be saving her instead?
I think she's
beyond our help.
This is Ruri.
I've found Souta-san.
I'm so glad...
I was so worried when I
found out he was missing...
Would you like me to rescue you?
Yes or no?
Yes.
Is it really okay for me to go with you?
Yeah, I have to introduce
you to everyone, though.
Yeah.
Roar! Gawo!
Do you two know each other?
You noticed?
It's kind of like friends of friends
just kind of sat down with you,
and it's kind of awkward.
W-Well, I guess you'll have to
watch the next episode to see.
I guess we just had the "you did
a good job on the preview" flag.
Flag 7
I Learned Something Amazing. I'll Hide Myself Before I can be Erased
Roar! Gawo!
If Her Flag Breaks
Watch it with your big sis next time!
Illustration: Niwa