If I were to borrow Tendo's words...
"I'm starting to get into it."
There's something wrong with his hand.
There'll be no victory
without risks, either.
Fly
Karasuno is only Karasuno when
we're persistently attacking!
Synchronized attack: all!
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
All right!
Episode 08: An Annoying Guy
Damn it!
See? That's why you've got to have
someone follow up with a block.
Having everyone attack is way too reckless!
That block was rather effective.
Did that just decide this match?
Next time...
We'll do that again next time.
Shiratorizawa!
Hinata.
Always keep the block timing in your head.
Since you lack height, that'll be
much more important for you.
Shiratorizawa!
Yeah.
If you feel like it's going
to be even a little late,
switch over to a soft block.
Shiratorizawa!
The plate, right?
Push through!
Go!
All right!
Sorry.
Don't mind!
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
It finally stopped.
How many points in a row did they get
with Ushiwaka serving there? Five?
Six.
More than a third what they need to win.
But Hinata's coming back out now.
Pull something off again!
Yeah!
Narita-san! One more, nice serve!
Fly
Nice serve!
Here I go!
Sorry!
Tendo!
Asahi-san!
It's not Kageyama. Don't jump too early!
It's first tempo with anyone.
One blocker!
All right!
Go, go, Karasuno!
Push it, push it, Karasuno!
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
We're just two points behind!
Hinata, is your eye okay?
Yup!
You sure got hit in a strange place.
My hands couldn't go up in time, so I
thought about receiving it with my face,
but I didn't want it to hit my nose, so...
What?! So you moved your face
because you could actually see it?
Well, if I got a nosebleed, I'd
have to go back onto the bench.
When I heard about Karasuno's first-year duo,
and when he stole my ball at the school,
I was anticipating...
That he was like the other small
yet talented players I have met.
But I was wrong.
I couldn't feel the same talented
techniques or intelligence in him.
But...
I see.
Something about him annoys me.
Shiratorizawa
I haven't doubted once that we would win.
But right now,
I am completely sure
that I want to crush you.
Kazuhito, nice serve!
All right, keep it up. Don't give up!
Oh, hey, look!
Kageyama's warming up!
He's going back in!
Ohira-san!
All right!
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
The taste of blood in my mouth...
I wonder if Shoyo's in pain after all.
But having someone to follow
up and block is reassuring.
Earlier, he followed up
like that because there was
no getting around Asahi hitting it, but...
Usually, their style is anyone
who can attack, will attack.
They don't think their attack being stopped.
They trust that it won't.
So as soon as their attack is stopped,
they're pretty much out.
Though we did get yelled at about
following up with a block quite a bit.
If I were the coach, I'd do the same thing.
Actually, even as a player,
I can't help but hope
that someone follows up.
Because it's scary.
Good! Nice, Wakatoshi!
Goshiki!
Narrowing the paths for angle shots...
And Daichi's in the path for a straight.
Bring it! I'm going to take
my chance with that straight!
Sorry! It's long!
Suga!
If we go for what's somewhat safe here,
it'll mean we never changed!
They're going to do it again!
Aren't they scared?
Synchronized attack: all!
Judging by his form, it won't be a back toss.
I haven't seen him do any
combos with their #10.
So it'll probably got to the guy
with the facial hair in the back...
No.
We'll do that again next time.
I know...
When I'm in this kind of thought
process, I've already lost.
Is there a toss going up for me?
All right!
I'm not going to think about that.
I'm going to hit it.
Soy, soy, soy!
By attacking with that in mind, our
opponents' blocks become confused.
Soy!
It's obvious when you see their faces.
I can't believe Sugawara was able
to fearlessly charge like that again,
right after he was shut down!
I'm sure he's scared,
but I guess it's more important to
have an even stronger will to attack.
Satori!
Stick your hands up, damn it!
I don't care if your
prediction ends up wrong!
I put you in there knowing damn
well that might be a possibility!
Right!
Here he comes!
Are you finally back, Tiredyama-kun?
Watch out for the back of your head.
Kageyama, one more, nice serve!
He just got back and he was
able to serve like that?
It's coming back!
Chance ball! Be careful with...
Got it—
Got it!
The first touch turned right into a set?
Damn!
There it is! The straight-down hit!
I-I didn't really see it,
but everything's so fast!
One point behind!
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
Now I really don't know who's going to win!
That bastard!
Great job, Hinata! Awesome!
I thought that our usual quick would
have been enough of a surprise attack,
Thanks!
but this time he came at me on purpose.
That's fricking dangerous!
Go, go!
Hey! You guys aren't being loud enough!
Be Courageous Warriors
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
Now they're in double digits...
Concentrate on the one!
His serves are intense.
Try to stop him at one!
Hey, why isn't Semi-san our main setter?
He's way better than
Shirabu-san, to be honest.
It all depends on what you
consider to be better.
I think Shirabu-san's pretty
reliable, so I like him.
I know what makes me inferior to Shirabu.
The need to show just how strong I am.
Even though I know Shiratorizawa's
setter doesn't need that right now,
it can't be stopped.
But serves... With serves, I'm free!
No-touch ace!
All right!
Be Courageous Warriors
Nice kill, Semi!
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
Semi!
I have to find the right
words to say to them...
Shiratorizawa!
Don't shut up!
This is exactly when we should be cheering!
Shiratorizawa!
We're going to finish this.
Yeah.
Do another one, Eita-kun.
Shiratorizawa!
Fire it up, fire it up, Karasuno! Get it, get it, Karasuno!
The City of Trees, Sendai, lies below
And when you look up, the
magnificent Sendai Castle
Fire it up, fire it up, Karasuno! Get it, get it, Karasuno!
...Karasuno! Get it, get it, Karasuno!
Our school, our glorious
Shiratorizawa Academy
Fire it up...
Our glorious Shiratorizawa Academy
Eita-kun! One more, nice serve!
Chance ball!
Wakatoshi!
But he's that far from the net...
All right!
He stopped it!
Shoyo...
N-Nice block...
Was that a block?
I told him to do a soft block,
but that was more of an insanely
close receive than a quick block.
I'd be too scared of that hitting
my face to ever do that!
Now Karasuno's at double digits, too!
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
Now Karasuno's at double digits, too!
Right. All right! Yeah...
Don't get so worked up over a lucky shot!
That's a block that got
in the way of a receive.
U-Ushijima-san, you just got
stopped by a nameless first-year.
Guess you've still got a ways to go.
I guess so.
Ushijima-san is a great
ace that's always marked.
Of course, he's going
to be stopped sometimes.
But to think that tiny first-year did it...
Hinata, you're serving next.
Right!
He actually had the instinct
to jump back at that moment...
Yeah!
Narita-san, come in whenever
you'd like. I'll follow you.
R-Right.
Get out there!
We're counting on you!
Go, Yamaguchi!
Don't hold back.
There's not a single thing
for you to be scared about.
I'll be aiming straight down diagonally
to the other side, right at Ushiwaka,
but there's no point if the serve is soft.
Hayato!
Damn it!
Chance ball!
Got it!
Here we go!
Synchronized attack!
Come on! Come right over here!
All right—
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
All right!
He touched the net! Lucky!
I don't think that's all.
If we keep hitting them hard,
they're going to start pushing back.
Damn it...
We're counting on you.
Wakatoshi!
Slowly. Slowly.
Ready, and...
Despite all these barriers, it's still
not enough to stop him?
Got it!
It didn't match...
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
All right! We caught up!
That was a little high. I'll correct it.
No, uh... sure.
You're using a quick when
you just matched up
for the first time today?!
Yamaguchi, one more!
It's long!
Out!
All right!
Sorry. I judged that too late.
No, um... Damn!
Yamaguchi!
Nice serve, Yamaguchi!
Thanks!
Time—
What's the matter, Goshiki?
Why would you have any reason to
panic with all of your talent?
Shiratorizawa!
Right.
We're going to stop it this time.
He doesn't dress up his words, nor
do they have any other meaning.
Right!
No encouragement, just the truth.
Shiratorizawa!
No more words are needed from
the great ace to the other ace.
They turned it around!
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
They just scored three points in a row!
Holy crap! They might
just make it all the way!
Win...
Win, Karasuno!
All right!
That's perfect, Ohira-san.
Whoa... That angle was brutal.
Nice kill, Goshiki!
They got that precisely through
that incomplete block.
Goshiki!
I'm sure he wanted to make up
for his last serve receive.
Great job, Yamaguchi! Leave the rest to me!
But you're going to be switching
immediately with Nishinoya-san.
Tsutomu, keep calm!
Be Courageous Warriors
I know!
Here we go.
Bring it!
Damn it!
Isn't that #8 supposed to
be the impulsive type?!
Tsutomu is our only first-year
that's in the starting lineup.
Don't underestimate him.
Noya-san!
All right!
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
Nice kill, Ushijima!
They've got Karasuno cornered.
Ushijima! Ushijima!
Not to mention Glasses isn't here, either.
I wonder how they're gonna
survive this match point.
One more point! One more point!
Nice receive!
Synchronized attack!
All right!
You actually made the guy who just
received the ball hit it again?
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
A deuce...
They should be running out
of stamina any time now,
and they're all still able to run like that...
Messing with us with numbers...
I have no choice but to admit
that it's an effective attack.
Coach!
I won't lose to anyone in receiving,
and I can jump really well,
so I'm confident in my attacks, too!
Right. Now you just have
to get a bit taller...
I'm so small, I can't even fight?
I'm going to lose to someone
just because they're tall?
One more!
One more, please!
No one here is just big.
I understand that.
I envy them, and they annoy me,
yet I admire them greatly.
Do I want a way to fight,
even though I'm small?
No, I...
If they don't break, Karasuno's
going to continue to be in danger.
Their stamina and concentration's
could run out at any moment.
No matter what it takes, just get the ball up
from Shiratorizawa's powerful cannon
any way you can.
Daichi-san, nice serve!
It's short!
There has to be a limit to
aiming for the damn net!
Goshiki!
Right!
It's connecting! It's connecting!
Kageyama, get the last!
This is our chance! Hit it once more!
They made our setter get it!
Ushijima-san!
Don't panic! If we get the
timing wrong, it's all over.
Ready, and...
Do I want a way to fight,
even though I'm small?
No, I...
I want a simple strength that
can make anything surrender.
They're not giving up!
Damn it. But it's taking everything
they have just to return the ball.
A rally where both sides are low stamina
and fighting for control of the game...
Don't let your energy run out,
and don't stop hitting the ball.
It hasn't fallen yet.
Stop it!
This point!
We have to get it, no matter what!
Shut up! We're stronger!
All right!
Nice kill, Ushijima!
Ushijima! Ushijima!
One more point! One more point!
Shiratorizawa              Karasuno
Oh, no... Everyone's mood just plummeted.
But we don't have any more timeouts...
Don't you dare look down!
Volleyball...
is a sport where you're always looking up!
Hitoka-chan!
A-Are you okay?
I don't usually climb stairs
two at a time, so...
All right! Now that Yacchan's back, it's
finally time for the counterattack!
Episode 09: The Volleyball Idiots
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"The Volleyball Idiots."