Hello, everyone! Thank you for tuning
in to Kill la Kill every week!
My name is Kamui Senketsu.
I am a living sailor uniform who
loves ironing— or rather, being ironed.
The compilation episode that I'm sure you
were all wondering about begins right now!
COMPILATION
Ryuko Matoi, who is searching for her father's
murderer, someone with a Scissor Blade,
FATHER'S MURDERER
RYUKO MATOI
arrives at Honnouji Academy and encounters its
student council president, Satsuki Kiryuin.
HONNOUJI ACADEMY
SATSUKI KIRYUIN
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT
Using Goku Uniforms, which contain Life Fibers
that unleash the human body's special abilities.
LIFE FIBER
ATHLETICISM-AUGMENTING
TWO-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
Satsuki was plotting the conquest
of the country's academies.
But when Ryuko met me,
Kamui Senketsu,
KAMUI SENTEKSU
she gained the power to fight
Satsuki and her forces!
Boxing, Tennis, Disciplinary, Trap Development, Gardening,
Rakugo, 100 Poets, Knife Throwing, Nanjing Lily, etc.!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
BLADE REGALIA
A Naturals Election was held, involving
battles amongst the various clubs!
FIGHT CLUB-SPEC TWO-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT MAKO MANKANSHOKU
NEXT TIME! HONNOUJI ACADEMY
NATURALS ELECTION
And at the end, a battle against
the Elite Four began!
NATURALS ELECTION
POLLING PLACE
Although the battles were hard, Ryuko defeats Ira Gamagoori,
Houka Inumuta, Nonon Jakuzure, and Uzu Sanageyama,
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
SHACKLE REGALIA
PROBE REGALIA
EVASION IMPOSSIBLE
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
SYMPHONY REGALIA GRAVE
but then a young girl named
Nui Harime suddenly appears!
NUI HARIME
She was the woman with the Scissor Blade
who killed Ryuko's father, Isshin Matoi!
Satsuki Kiryuin's mother, Ragyo Kiryuin, leader of the
Kiryuin Conglomerate makes her first appearance.
REVOCS CEO
RAGYO KIRYUIN
To complete her conquest of the nation's academies,
Satsuki puts her Kansai School Raid Trip into action.
TRI-CITY SCHOOLS RAID TRIP
Its target was not only the academies,
but also Nudist Beach,
a rebel organization that
opposes the Kiryuin clan.
To restore me, who had been chopped into
pieces, Ryuko also heads to Kansai!
HONNOUJI ACADEMY ELITE FOUR REGALIA MKII
A battle to the death between Ryuko and Satsuki
unfolds in the commerce city of Osaka!
And today, the mystery of the Life
Fibers will be revealed at last!
Those of you whose hearts sank at the words
"compilation episode," rest easy!
Kill la Kill is known for
its lightning pace!
Even our compilations are
wrapped up in the teaser!
The episode proper
begins right now!
But in war, the situation
is always fluid!
One such as yourself who is ignorant
of everything can never win!
That's why I keep saying to tell me
what's going on, damn it!
You bastards with your vague hints
think you're such hot stuff!
You perpetually frowning,
caterpillar-eyebrowed bitch!
EPISODE 16
THE GIRL CAN'T HELP IT
Mistress!
- Shiro!
- Right away!
That was a tranquilizing coagulant.
Please undress while it's restrained.
Thank you.
Your level of exhaustion
is greater than before.
It is unsafe to remain in Life Fiber
Override mode for extended periods.
I'm well aware of the risk.
But given that Matoi
is wearing a Kamui,
the only way to fight her
is by wearing Junketsu.
As you say, Milady.
Is that wise, Uncle?
Shiro, if you are my nephew,
understand this one thing quickly.
Once Lady Satsuki has made up
her mind, nothing can dissuade her.
All we can do is support her
in that decision.
Soroi. Iori. I am
asking much of you.
However, continue to indulge me
for a while longer.
Oh, so you've been pushing yourself
pretty hard, Lady Satsuki.
Who said that?!
That voice...
Is that you, Harime?
Indeed it is!
When did the High Order Tailor
come aboard?!
I go wherever I want.
No one can stop that.
What do you want?
Oh, don't be all,
"What do you want?"
It's Mistress Ragyo.
She says she wants a firsthand report
of the School Raid Trip's results.
I wasn't doing anything
because a certain someone
had banned me from Honnouji Academy,
so I came all the way here
to welcome you in person!
You just came to watch Senketsu
and Junketsu fight.
I can't put one
past you, Lady Satsuki!
You're the only one who
truly understands me!
Amusing, coming from someone
who defies understanding.
Okay, let's head on back
to the mansion, shall we?
Iori. Send word to the Elite Four.
"My return will be delayed.
All students are to remain on alert until
you arrive at Honnouji Academy.
Until you are home,
the Raid Trip is still underway."
At once!
It would appear that you have
time for another cup of tea.
Yes, thank you.
They've gone and done it now...
But we still have our lives.
If we're alive, we can fight.
Exactly.
Ryuko, you fought Satsuki Kiryuin
to a draw. That was impressive.
Come with me.
Hey! Mikisugi!
Where are you going?!
It's just like Satsuki Kiryuin said.
The situation has shifted.
Now that it's come to this,
it's pointless to keep things hidden.
It's now time
to show you everything.
You! You're...
Mr. Mikisugi, is that you?!
Oh, right, you haven't seen me
like this before, have you?
Mr. Mikisugi,
you're an exhibitionist!
- We are Nudist—
- Just like you, Ryuko!
Don't lump us together!
Mako, this time you're
going home for real.
Mankanshoku.
If you follow, it will mean throwing yourself
headlong into a whirlpool of battle.
Do you possess that resolve?
I don't!
Figured as much.
Go on home.
I'm not prepared to go around
buck-naked just yet!
You meant that?!
But what I do have is the desire to be
Ryuko's friend through thick and thin!
So I'm coming with you!
Mako...
All right, then!
Come with us!
Kay!
Huh? Mako?
Wait! Why are you diving
into the river?
Ryuko, this is the entryway to
the truth you must know.
Let's go skinny dipping!
Huh?
Hey, wait for me!
Please remove Junketsu.
I will see to it.
You have a message
from the president.
Please wait at the grand bath.
KIRYUIN MANOR
GRAND BATH
You wear it well, but you do seem
to be overexerting yourself.
Mother...
This medicated bath water boosts
Life Fiber harmonization.
Soak yourself in it.
Yes, ma'am.
Such lovely skin.
Give your heart over to me.
I will conduct
a ritual purification.
Humans are such frail things,
are they not?
When they become naked like this,
they become so unbearably uncomfortable.
They are immediately
overcome with the desire to
cover themselves in the miraculous
thing that is clothing.
That is instinct.
A species that defies
its instincts...
will eventually...
meet with extinction.
Come out of the bath.
There is somewhere
you must go.
You mean—
I do.
You save served me well, Satsuki.
As a member of the Kiryuin clan,
and as my successor,
it is time for you to learn
the origin of power.
There was a cavern
like this under Osaka?
It's busted up
pretty bad, though, huh?
Jakuzure did a number on it.
But this isn't all there is
to our base.
Mr. Mikisugi!
Mr. Kinagase!
This section made it through
unscathed, huh?
It was the right call for us
to evacuate as you ordered.
Being a worrywart
sometimes pays off.
This Nudist Beach deal of yours
sure must cost a lot of money.
Your father saw to that.
My dad?
He was an amazing
scientist, you see.
Thanks to all
the patents he held,
he cobbled together money
from companies all over the world
He used those funds
to create this organization.
You mean—
Yes! It was Dr. Isshin Matoi
who founded Nudist Beach!
- Oh my, grandpa, you're magnificent!
- My goodness!
I don't think
that's what he meant.
How did you know what was
going on inside my head?!
You must be
telepathic now, Ryuko.
I'm not too thrilled
at the prospect of that.
That's amazing, Ryuko!
You're a friend who's both
inside and outside my head!
Hm...
Answer me this, Ryuko.
How many creatures do you think there
are on this Earth that wear clothing?
Duh, just humans.
Correct.
Of all the countless species on Earth,
only Homo sapiens wears clothing.
Why is that?!
"Only humans wear clothing"
isn't entirely correct.
This "clothing-wearing creature"
became what is now humanity!
Life Fibers caused Homo sapiens,
which was just another
anthropoid species, to evolve
to its current state.
Yes, in this case, the clothes
made the mankind!
KIRYUIN MANOR
PROHIBITED ROOM - FIBER CASTLE
This is the origin of power?
Yes, this is the beginning of it all.
The Primordial Life Fiber.
PRIMORDIAL LIFE FIBER
When this glowing ball of thread that had
drifted through space arrived on Earth,
humanity was doomed to become
a being that would serve clothing.
For Life Fibers to become clothing
and cover this world.
They are COVERS, and no one in
this world can oppose them.
We of the Kiryuin family are the
spokesmen for the COVERS' will.
You understand, I take it?
I do, Mother.
Clothes made humanity?
What are you talking about?
Life Fibers are a lifeform that
came here from outer space!
They arrived on ancient Earth and
accelerated the evolution of humanity.
Then Senketsu is an alien?!
He's a sailor uniform,
but he's an alien!
So that's what I am...
Don't buy into it! What the hell
is that crazy garbage?!
Would you mind listening quietly?
I'm explaining everything
in due course.
Life Fibers are a lifeform that
came here from outer space.
They infest a world's
lifeforms as parasites
and breed by devouring using the electrical
current of the creature's nervous system.
However, if they infest the
host directly, within its body,
the nervous system is unable to
withstand the strain and burns out.
It is for this reason that they decided
to cover their host's body.
Although the current received
via the skin is minute,
the infested animal does
not die with this method.
They chose Homo sapiens,
the terrestrial creature
with the most developed cerebrum at the time,
to be their hosts and
accelerated their evolution.
Humanity evolved.
They developed humanity's brain far
beyond that of any other
terrestrial lifeform.
Their numbers multiplied,
and they came to stand at
the top of the ecosystem.
But that pinnacle will only be temporary,
and we were led there by Life Fibers.
In other words, we humans
are the Life Fibers' food.
I don't believe it!
You mean that I will do the same to Ryuko?!
Calm down, Senketsu.
We haven't heard everything yet.
If that's true, why doesn't
all clothing have Life Fibers in them?
We humans wear clothes and
go about our lives every day.
It's only the people at Honnouji Academy
that're wearing messed-up clothes, right?
What you say is indeed true.
The only conclusion is that the Life Fibers
that accelerated human evolution
went into a long period of dormancy,
leaving behind only the tradition of wearing clothing.
They only emerged from their
silence about 20 years ago.
Ragyo Kiryuin made contact
with the Original Life Fiber,
and they awoke
once again.
That's what we were told by Dr. Matoi.
They were waiting
for harvest time.
They were waiting for their
human livestock to grow!
I.. was waiting for Ryuko
to reach maturity?
That is why I needed
Ryuko's blood?
Look, just calm down!
You're not like that, Senketsu!
Has Senketsu's world been
turned upside-down?
Then tell him for me.
You and Senketsu are our hope.
Hope?
Yes.
Kamui Senketsu was artificially created
by Dr. Matoi to fight Life Fibers.
And the only one who can wear that Kamui
to its full potential is you, Ryuko!
Only me...?
But why?
You have an unusually high
Life Fiber tolerance.
Dr. Matoi was probably
aware of that.
So he made Senketsu for you.
To thwart the Kiryuins' ambitions.
The Doctor had originally
studied Life Fibers under
Ragyo Kiryuin's orders.
But when he learned the
threat they posed,
he escaped from under her thumb and
secretly founded a rebel organization.
And that organization...
is Nudist Beach.
I see... Dr. Matoi
created me to—
Yes, I remember now...
I was born in that
underground lab.
But I was put to sleep
immediately afterwards.
Until Ryuko arrived
six months later, I slept.
I apologize for keeping you
in the dark all this time.
But the Kiryuins are powerful.
Until you were able to summon up
all of Senketsu's power at will,
I couldn't tell you
the whole story.
And if I got overwhelmed by the
power of the Life Fibers,
you'd put me down
on the spot without mercy.
Yeah, that's right.
And I still intend to do just that.
Tsumugu...
You're right, I wouldn't have
been able to believe any
of this stuff otherwise.
This is the truth.
The clothing made by REVOCS,
the company headed by Ragyo Kiryuin,
is worn in almost every country
around the world.
Life Fibers are woven
into all of them.
They are still dormant right now,
but when that clothing awakens,
REI HOUOUMARU
NUI HARIME
SATSUKI KIRYUIN
RAGYO KIRYUIN
TOP SECRET
I can't begin to imagine
what will happen.
But one thing is for certain: it will be
a profound threat to the human race.
All the country's academies
have been conquered,
and Nudist Beach has been neutralized?
Yes, Mother.
Then the Honnouji Academy experimental city
can be moved to the next stage, as well.
The Ragyo Stadium
is already complete.
Preparations for the festival are complete.
Very well. The plan is now
at the final stage.
Put the Cultural & Sports
Grand Festival into effect.
Yes, Mother.
What are your plans?
I haven't been home
in some time.
I will spend the night here.
I see. Kuroido.
Look after things while I'm away.
I'm looking forward to seeing what
this Honnouji Academy you've created is like.
We will give you
a warm welcome, Mother.
Oh, now I get it!
You want me and Senketsu
to work hand in hand
and fight for the sake of the peace
of all mankind, is that it?
To hell with that!
Ryuko!
So Senketsu is just a weapon, huh?
A combat uniform created to fight?
Screw that!
He's got a will of his own!
Created to kill others
of his own kind?
That's seriously screwed up!
Don't you think?!
W-What are you doing?!
Your name's Nudist Beach, right?
What's wrong with
me getting naked?
Ryuko...
I can't put you on to fight.
And there's no reason for
you to fight, either.
Let me tell you two useful
pieces of information.
One: A Kamui that doesn't fight
has no value.
Two: In which case, I will terminate it
right here and now!
You'll have to kill me first.
Fine. If that's what you want,
I'll be happy to oblige.
Everybody's getting real scary...
This is some nasty stuff
going on here...
Let's have some snacks
and calm down, okay?
Let's see here...
Let's borrow a souvenir, and...
Ew! This snack
is nasty stuff, too!
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Ryuko learns of
her father's wishes!
Remain steadfast, Ryuko!
You scratch my lapels, I scratch yours!
YOU & ME
CULTURAL & SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL
The Cultural & Sports Grand Festival!
The Kiryuins' declaration of victory!
DECLARATION OF VICTORY
We are the only ones
who can stop it!
ONLY US
Next time on Kill la Kill,
"Tell Me Why"!
EPISODE 17
TELL ME WHY