Please!
Really... What am I
going to do with you?
Idiot husband!
Better brace yourself!
Or I'm gonna step out on you!
Hiro-chan, did you have another
fight with your husband?
This is no fight. This is war!
If he apologizes, we're done for good.
Idiot husband!
Better brace yourself!
Or I'm gonna step out on you!
Kousei...
You...
How can you play the piano?
Why wouldn't I be
able to play the piano?
Saki!
Let's turn Kousei into a pianist!
Kousei's...
Kousei's
...a genius!
I'm heading out now.
By yourself?
Yes.
Are you serious?
What are you going
to play? Without a violi-
I'm not changing the song.
It's not music or anything at all!
See, I'm pissed.
So I'm going to prove it.
Just how great a musician Kaori Miyazono is.
And besides...
This is a supreme directive from the shrew.
These galas are all about standing out.
Wait, this is a violin concert, right?
Is that accompanist
going to play on his own?
This is all your fault.
Because you put me
back on the stage.
Always... you always move me.
Look at me!
I'm going to prove it.
That I'm incredible.
That Kaori Miyazono, who's named
me to be her accompanist...
...is even more incredible!
Once again, unprecedented! Arima again?
This isn't the accompaniment. This is...
Kreisler... Love's Sorrow...
Rachmaninoff's Piano Arrangement.
The song that Saki loved...
So you've been facing it
alone all this time. But...
Is this the Love's Sorrow
that you've always known?
Just watch...
Just watch... Just watch...
I'm incredible... Kaori Miyazono is...
...even more incredible!
Gala Concert
Unbelievable!
So powerful!
What a disappointment.
He's only venting his anger.
He's confusing crudeness with ferocity.
This grates on my ears.
Huh?
Was I pounding the keys that hard?
My whole body is taut...
This won't do at all.
This piece isn't... This isn't
how you play it, right?
The song that I always listened to was...
This song was my lullaby...
I don't understand...
Even though I can't hear the notes as usual,
I can hear the sound inside me.
I think it means that you're not bound by sounds.
Wasn't there ever a moment
when you sensed the notes suffused
with your desires and emotions?
Losing the ability to hear the notes...
I'm sure that that's... a gift.
Kousei...
Play it more gently.
Like you're caressing a baby's head.
Play it like you're embracing him.
Mom... This song... If it were her,
would she have played it like this?
His playing style just changed...
He's doing it again.
The sound is changing.
Kousei...
It's Saki.
Saki is there...
Saki!
Even for you, that's going too far!
Hitting him hard enough to
draw blood - that's way too harsh!
You call yourself a mother?
Kousei was doing his best
just to make you happy!
I know that! Of course I know that!
Saki!
I do know that... But...
I'm... running out of time.
Saki...
Help me... Please help me...
Somebody help me... The notes...
The piano... My hearing is...
I can't hear the notes!
Somebody... Please help me...
Mom...
Kousei...
I'm the one who drove
you into this corner.
It's all because I told her
to turn you into a pianist.
I'm so sorry...
If music only brings
Kousei pain and suffering...
I'm so sorry...
Then I have no business
being by his side.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
Kousei Arima
Sumitani Junior Highschool
But...
Kousei has returned.
What made you turn to the piano?
I want to see that sight again
with my own eyes one more time.
That's what made me think...
That I'd like become
a really weird pianist!
After losing Saki, Kousei...
...met someone who
means the world to him.
If Kousei believes in
that, then as a pianist,
how can I not believe
in the power of music?
Saki. Be sure to watch this.
That son of ours
is about to bid you a last farewell.
Oh...
I can't help thinking
about her, after all.
This song has my mother's scent.
Who are you going to play it for?
Will it reach her?
I hope it reaches her.
After I'm gone...
What's going to become of Kousei?
Will be able to earn a living?
Can he make music his livelihood?
All I can do right now is make him
play accurately, faithful to the score.
As long as he has the skills, he just
might be able to support himself someday.
What a terrible mother...
There's nothing I can leave that boy...
Will he brush his teeth every morning?
He falls asleep anywhere,
so what if he catches a cold?
He isn't good at sports,
so what if he gets seriously injured?
I wish I could've stayed with him longer...
Will my treasure... ever find happiness?
I knew all along. The ghost of my
mother was a shadow of my own creation.
An excuse for me to run away.
My own weakness.
Mom isn't there anymore.
Mom... is inside me.
Yes, that's right. The piano...
...is meant to be played like
you're embracing it, right?
Hey, hey... Mom?
There's both Love's Joy
and Love's Sorrow, so why...
...do you always play Love's Sorrow?
I play it so...
...you'll get used to sorrow.
We're all connected.
Just like the notes
are intermittently connected...
It's shared by us all.
Through music...
With the people you know,
with the people you don't know,
with all the people in the world.
You come, too!
Just like with her, I'm
connected to Mom, too.
I'm moving forward
because I believe that.
So... So...
Goodbye...
My knees are shaking...
Guess I'm exhausted?
Kousei!
Hey, look at you, hot stuff!
If my husband hears that his daughter
threw herself into a man's arms,
he'll be devastated.
So did you get to see Saki?
My mom...
She's always been by my side.
Yes.
The way I touch the keys, the way I move my
fingers, my habit of squeezing the pedals,
my tastes, the order that I eat...
Mom's in every little
gesture of mine.
We're... Mom and I are... Connected...
Hiroko-san... Do you
think it reached my mom?
The way I played my very best...
Do you think it reached Mom?
You dummy. You two
are connected, aren't you?
Of course it reached her!
Because of music, I was given
the chance to meet others.
I was moved by those encounters.
There are people that I got to meet.
I got to discover emotion.
These are all...
...memories that my mother, who taught
me how to play the piano, left me.
Mom, I'm happy.
Thank you. Thank you.
Goodbye...
That was so exquisite...
I'm ready to just go home now!
Oh, the next performance, huh?
I don't want to hear anything right now.
I never thought I'd be
so scared to go onstage.
Miike-kun...
Now this is a tough act to follow...
I want to run away...
Mom...
Would I have played my
heart out like he did?
Would I have played with
as much sincerity as he did?
I want to see if I can sacrifice
body and soul like that.
I want to see if I
can give it all I can.
Just watch me.
Right now, all I want to do
is hear my mom's voice.
Is his playing softer
than usual? I see...
So your heart's been pierced, too?
And you're both going to raise the bar, eh?
That was awesome.
Isn't violin music lovely?
Ms. Ochiai?
I'm glad that I'm a musician.
To obliterate a powerful enemy...
Now that's the ultimate pleasure...
A bona fide extreme sadist?
Kousei...
...and Onee-sama!
Hey!
Kousei...
Huh?
Huh? This is so weird...
I can't find the words to say...
Freaky...
Was it okay for you to just leave?
Well, why not? I was just a throw-in
for the throw-in. And besides...
I've got to find that throw-in who
blew me off, and rip her a new one.
He's mad.
All right, ready to head home?
I'm exhausted from all this.
I want some juice!
Hey, your mom could go for some, too.
Tsubaki?
You've got nothing to say to me
after all my hard work?
Huh? Um... You look all grown up.
What's up with that? I was
hoping you'd praise me.
Huh?
What the heck? So weird...
If I don't hold them in,
I might shed tears. Tears?
Tears of relief because I was
able to talk to Kousei normally?
Or because I was able
to talk to him normally...
...tears of disappointment?
31st - Gala Concert
If you were there at the concert,
you could've said something to me.
You're as spiteful as ever, aren't you?
Ms. Ochiai...
To think that Arima-kun was being
mentored by you... That was unexpected.
After all, ever since Saki Arima passed
away, you never went near that house.
That boy has changed, too.
He's become quite an intriguing musician.
Yes. Instilling something into his music,
leaving something in those who hear it.
That kid has taken his first
steps forward as an artist. But...
The loss of Saki Arima
was tragic for Kousei, and for me,
but was it really necessary for
Kousei Arima, the musician?
There's an ever-present sorrow
hanging over Arima-kun's music.
If the death of his beloved mother
triggered something in him...
Totsuhara University Hospital
Then it's a demon's path
that he must walk.
Kaori Miyazono
His growth is spurred by sorrow...
If Kousei is to walk that path,
Love's Sorrow
he might have to lose someone to move forward.
Episode 14
Footprints
Watch Again Next Week!