Gather round!
Our first game today is with Nekoma.
How did we do yesterday?
This will be our third
set overall with Nekoma.
Yesterday, we played two sets with them.
The scores were 17-25 and
19-25, both our losses.
Simply put, we haven't won a single set.
But if we calm down and go out
there in full force,
they should be opponents
we can fight on equal footing.
Hinata and Kageyama, this is your
first Nekoma set in a while, isn't it?
Go show 'em what you've got.
Right!
Okay, we're good to go.
Nice serve, Fukunaga!
I'll be the first one to stop
your quick tomorrow, Hinata.
Come on! Bring it!
Haikyu!!
Episode 5: "Greed"
Tenchu
I drank way too much with
the teachers last night.
What time is it?
Nice receive!
All right!
Damn it... That's amazing.
Don't mind, Lev!
That was close.
Okay!
So Karasuno's #10 really is closing
his eyes when he hits the quick.
One more, Tanaka! Nice serve!
Yeah.
Cover! Cover!
Which means the truth behind
that godly quick attack
is the setter's superior technique.
Nice receive, Daichi-san!
He flew from A to C.
All right!
He actually did it!
H-He stopped it...
He stopped that quick attack so easily.
Well, Nekoma's always been
pretty good at reacting to that quick attack.
On top of that, that newbie
middle blocker's height
and quick reaction time are amazing.
Nice serve, Kenma!
Hey, I'm gonna add in more normal quicks.
The floaty ones.
Hey, are you listening?
Yeah...
Lev.
They're probably going to start
using a lot of normal quicks,
so please switch over to read blocks.
What's a read block again?
It's when you see where the toss is
going to go, then jump up and block.
Ah, okay.
Nice serve!
Ryu!
Got it!
It's when you see where
the toss is going to go...
One touch!
I thought he was totally
being lured by Hinata.
Even though it was a bit late,
his block is still high.
Chance ball!
These guys...
All right!
Damn it!
Karasuno         Nekoma
Now, calm down.
They already had a careful eye on our quicks.
For the time being, when
we're up against Nekoma,
let's mainly have Azumane and
Tanaka attacking from the left.
Right.
Got it!
All right!
We've only just begun!
Is that all right? Or is that being weak?
Let's calm down and get that point.
Is there any evolution that comes from
going on the defensive, Keishin?
Here.
Thanks.
Here you go, Azumane-san.
Crap... What is this?
Nekoma, Lev...
They're strong. They're so strong!
I have to get stronger,
Shiratorizawa
Academy
or there's no way we'll win!
Cover! Cover!
Left!
Two blockers!
Right!
It's up! Nice, Kageyama!
Nice cover!
All right, let's get the last ball!
Sorry! It was a bit short!
Asahi!
Last ball!
Yeah!
Huh?
U-U-U-Uh... Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh—
I'm sorry!
I was just staring at the ball... I'm sorry!
Are you okay? I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
I-I'm perfectly fine...
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
Hey, be careful.
No matter what, Shoyo's gonna
be the one that goes flying.
Pay attention to your
surroundings, you idiot!
Why do you think everyone's
calling the ball, you dumbass?!
Right... I'm sorry.
Moron! Hinata, you moron!
Now, now. Calm down, Kageyama.
I'm sure Hinata acted completely
subconsciously just then,
but it looked like he was trying
to steal the toss from the ace.
Is the baby crow about to evolve?
And will that be a blessing
or a curse for their team?
Though in the end, those who do not
want to change will not evolve.
If that is what you wish for,
even if you are the star of the court,
the hero,
or the ace that brings forth the victory,
you need to greedily proclaim
that you are indeed
the best.
Hey, Kageyama.
What?
The quick that goes like whoosh...
I'll...
stop closing my eyes.
Haikyu!!
I'll...
stop closing my eyes.
I can't stay like this.
I can't keep hitting quicks
that are set just for me.
You can't, and that's why
we learned normal quicks.
I don't know what's going
on with you right now,
but if you have something
to say, I'll listen to it later.
But if you're gonna do that right now,
I'm not going to set to a
guy who I know will miss.
Nice serve!
Asahi-san!
Sorry, cover!
I couldn't understand the
conversation from earlier, but...
Got it!
Left!
I wasn't imagining the tension
between Hinata and Kageyama-kun, right?
Yeah...
One touch! Chance ball!
But it's not just Hinata and Kageyama.
Ever since Hinata and Azumane
bumped into each other,
they're all on edge.
All right!
Karasuno             Nekoma
Let's go!
I can't stay like this.
Hinata just blurted out what
we all had realized.
What happened there was looming fear.
All right! Here I go!
At this rate, I'm going
to be eaten up by Hinata,
I'll show you how it's done!
whose greed keeps growing.
It appears that there's been a
change in your players' wills.
It's true that an impasse like this
is a perfect time to grow,
Gather round!
but how am I supposed to explain that?
You guys are the weakest team
out of all the teams here.
We can't argue with that...
If we were to have an official
match with any of these teams,
they would be a troublesome opponent.
Are we going to view them as mere opponents,
or teachers that we can
absorb techniques from?
The fact that you are weak just
means that you have room to grow.
There's nothing more exciting than that.
Thank you!
What you said out there
made you almost seem
like a really reliable teacher.
Thanks!
Uh, well... I am a teacher, so...
It wouldn't hurt to at least try.
I mean, he was able to do a normal quick
on the fly in the last Nekoma match.
At the time, there was a possibility
the normal quick would work,
and I thought that was
the only chance we had.
Before I knew it, we lost
the last set with Seijoh.
When I realized it,
the ball that was hit was behind me,
and on the floor.
Sorry.
They totally read me in the end.
I'm the one who lost,
so I don't want you to apologize, Kageyama.
I want to fight in mid-air
until the very last moment.
I sort of realized in the Seijoh match
that it's the setter that brings out
100% of the spiker's strength.
That quick is your ultimate weapon.
Any slight slippage in that quick
becomes a fatal mistake.
Your will is not needed for that quick.
Kageyama isn't denying his
worth out of emotion.
He's just stating the truth.
Sorry, Hinata.
This time, I've got to agree with Kageyama
after hearing him say that.
That quick is amazing in itself.
I think it might be best that
you use that as an axis,
and polish up other attacks.
Yeah... I agree with Sugawara.
Ukai-san.
You say that you want to fight on your own,
but that weirdo quick is a battle
that lasts a split second.
I honestly think it's pretty hard
trying to figure out what to do
in that split second mid-air.
But when I'm doing well,
I can see it in slow motion,
just like Tanaka-san said.
Some times, I can see
the opponent's block
in slow motion in the air.
It's just like light passing by.
Well, there are times that
blocks are more visible.
In the practice match against Seijoh...
The last point...
The Great King...
I could see Oikawa-san's face.
I could see his eyes.
Face? Eyes?
Oh... You mean you felt
like you saw them, right?
Even when I first did that
quick during our 3-on-3...
I could see the other side.
I could see the scenery from the very top.
But you mean you just felt like you saw...
Oh, there you are. We're starting.
Oh, I'll be right there.
Fukurodani                 Karasuno
Narita.
Yes?
Switch out with Hinata next.
Huh? Uh, yes, sir!
Despite what you think
you want to accomplish,
you need to chill out today.
I don't think it's gonna work
to try things out today,
and I'm not gonna have you end up
in a contact play like that again
and get hurt.
All right!
One!
Don't mind! Don't mind!
Next one! Next one!
One more on the dot!
All right!
Don't mind!
Nice kill, Lev!
All right!
Cover! Cover!
Nice serve!
One more! Nice serve!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
We'll see you the week after next,
at the summer vacation training camp.
Yes, sir! It'll be a
pleasure working with you!
This is where it's going to get real.
It's the last long-term training camp
before the spring tournament prelims.
Yes.
Just know that you're gonna be joining me
for drinks every night for a week.
Yes, sir!
Thank you very much.
I'm mentioning this a bit late,
No worries.
but looks like all your
third-years stuck around, too.
I'll start packing the gear into the back,
so keep bringing me more.
Yeah. You guys ended up going
Right!
against last year's winners
on the second day, right?
During the Inter-High prelims?
I heard that from Hinata.
Yeah. We stopped at the quarterfinals.
Tokyo's quarterfinals are amazing.
There's no point if we don't win.
You're right.
See ya later, Hinata.
I'll stop you next time, too.
I'm not gonna lose!
I may be 163 centimeters, but I'll
beat your 194-centimeter butt!
This training camp was really great.
I think we found a lot of areas for improvement.
Well, we're gonna have to take
them one at a time.
Indeed. Let's go home and
carefully think about them.
Go home, huh...
Ukai-kun?
Speaking of going home,
a rather annoying relative is coming home...
All right, everyone. Good work.
Thank you!
So, as I mentioned, tomorrow there
will be inspections in the gym,
so there'll be no club activities.
You've all gone a long time without a break,
so please enjoy it.
Kageyama.
Give me a toss.
Huh?
You two aren't going home yet?
Yachi-san, if you don't mind,
could you throw us some balls?
Huh? Can I do that?
You just have to throw the ball
above Kageyama's head.
S-Sure! I'll give it a try.
Let's do this!
Here you go.
He keeps getting distracted by the ball
and can't jump his highest.
One more time!
Instead of practicing an attack we're
not sure you'll ever be able to do,
you should be working on
the attacks we've been using,
as well as serving and blocking!
But if this quick doesn't work,
there's no point in me
being on the court.
And I told you, your will
isn't needed for that quick!
I'll give you tosses that
won't be stopped by blocks!
But then I'll never get better!
The prelims for the spring
tournament start next month!
They're right around the corner.
What do you think will be
an effective weapon for us?
A complete quick or an absolutely
useless quick?! Huh?!
N-No fighting, guys.
Calm down, Kageyama-kun.
Damn it!
What I'm saying is correct,
You, too, Hinata...
so why...
Why does he keep hanging on?!
I want to be strong enough
to compete by myself!
Your selfishness is going to
destroy the team's balance!
L-Let's all...
Let's all be friends, o-okay?!
I'll toss to anyone who's
essential to winning.
But I don't think you're
essential to winning right now.
And I don't feel any different now.
Kageyama!
Damn it! Let go!
I won't let go until you give me a toss!
Give me one!
Someone... Senpai!
Don't be ridiculous!
That quick was stopped!
Today, and during the Seijoh match!
Are you trying to say that
my toss was at fault?
No! That's not it!
It was perfect! It was spot-on!
And yet, it was stopped!
If I don't get better, it's not going
to work on stronger opponents, either!
Hey!
Stop it, you two!
I-I'm just going to the bus stop
over there, so I'm fine here.
Thanks.
I'm sorry, Yachi-san.
N-No worries!
It's fine... I'm totally fine.
But you're...
In my first and final
tournament in junior high,
we were destroyed by Kageyama.
I vowed revenge when I got into high school,
Kids' Volleyball
and of course I ran right into him.
He was even worse than I could have
imagined and we went through a lot,
but once we started playing our matches,
I felt like we understood each other.
It wasn't that he was the first friend
I'd made. He was a partner.
Well, see you later.
Yeah...
What?
They got into a fight?
There's been tension between them
ever since the training camp.
I wonder if they're gonna be okay, considering
the spring tournament's coming up.
But this isn't the first time
they've ever fought, is it?
Come to think of it,
they were fighting even before they
turned in their membership applications.
What? Seriously?
The first day, they blew off
the Vice Principal's toupee,
and they even got shut out
of the gym by Daichi.
It was ridiculous.
Well, that also means they've
gotten over those things, too...
Right? So I think
we should just believe in them and wait.
Sakanoshita Shop
Thank ya.
Considering he was never able to see it,
it's pretty much impossible for
him to power it up even more.
I could see the other side.
I could see the scenery from the very top.
Those eyes...
The moment you're at the
highest point of a jump
is a mere moment.
Even if you're able to see the block,
it shouldn't be anything more than a blur.
But every once in a while,
I've heard that there are moments
where spikers can clearly see the
blockers' fingers, and even beyond that.
Can Hinata actually see that?
A quick attack that comes
from a spectacular set up...
If Hinata could hit that
at will while in mid-air...
No, no, no... There's no way!
It's just an empty theory.
But maybe...
If he could actually do it,
that duo would become even greater champions
of mid-air battle than the Little Giant.
Welcome—
Oh, it's you, Hinata.
Coach, exactly how am
I supposed to practice?
Hinata and Kageyama are fighting, huh?
You can totally feel their youth.
Yeah, I can't say I really feel
any youth from you, Asahi.
Huh? Then what do I feel like?
On the outside, your youth is over, Asahi.
Episode 06: "Tempo"
That's so mean!
Next time on Haikyu!!
"Tempo."