Good grief. Why did you completely
burn our ingredients?
Well, my apologies.
Have more faith in the gas stove.
I thought the heat wasn't strong enough.
Use a flame, not a blaze.
Your brain was the thing
that wasn't strong enough.
That reminds me, this is my first time
going shopping with Tohru, isn't it?
I wonder what she's like when she's shopping.
Oborozuka Shopping District
Huh?
This is the shopping district.
You don't use the
department store over there?
That place is like a castle
and makes me uncomfortable.
Castle?
The white color reminds
me of the crusader's bases.
And the shopping district?
Shop at your local shopping district!
Use your point card for savings!
It's like the guild's bazaars.
It's a little better.
So your standards are basically
based on your past experiences, huh?
Toda Fresh Seafood
Well, let's start by buying the fish.
Yup.
Oh hey, Tohru-chan.
Good afternoon, Mr. Toda.
Huh?
It's not often I see you with anyone.
She a friend?
She's my Master.
Huh?
H-Hello.
Tohru-chan's funny, isn't she?
We've got some good mackerel
in today. How about it?
In that case, I'll take two of those
and two dried jack mackerel.
Coming up.
He gave us an extra fillet of mackerel...
Wasn't that nice of him?
Why are you friends with the fishmonger?
Huh? We're not friends.
What about it?
When I was courteous to him he started
being nice in return, that's all.
Tohru, I think you have a tendency
to not understand human emotions.
Of course things are different
with you, Miss Kobayashi!
We share mutual love!
You definitely don't understand.
Tatsuda Butchery
Hey, Tohru-chan.
What'll it be today?
I'll throw some extra in.
Huh? You mean it?
Here, too?
Or rather...
My, long time no see.
Hello.
Oh, it's the cosplay lady!
Hey!
Getting along well?
This dragon's better at socializing than me?
Here and there.
How about it, Tohru-chan?
She make talk condescendingly, calling humans
Care to have your romantic fortune read?
an inferior species and lesser creatures,
Huh? Thank you, but I'm good on that front.
but she's interacting
with them normally enough.
I guess she doesn't hate us.
Farewell, then.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, it's fine.
Now that I think about it, I hardly
know anything about Tohru.
I'd like to know more... I guess.
I think it's probably best
not to ask about that.
Homemade Western Confections
Salmandra
It's clearly a touchy topic for her.
Well, shall we buy some dessert?
Huh? Really?
What would you like?
I'd love an eclair!
Did you know? Eclair means
flash of lightning!
Wow.
Speaking of lightning, there's the Norse
god Thor... is your name related to that?
Absolutely not.
According to my parents, it comes
from an author here in this world.
Huh? Your parents—
Purse snatcher! Someone stop him!
Miss Kobayashi, may I stop him?
Huh?
Uh, can you do it without
exposing yourself as a dragon?
Yes!
Understood!
Good, now that I'm this far away...
Huh?
Doesn't this mean trouble?
Tohru!
Huh?
Amazing, Tohru-chan!
I can't believe you're so strong!
That was cool, lady!
You've got quite the legs on you!
It worked out.
Impressive!
I can sleep soundly tonight!
Just now, I was scared.
I was sweating, too.
Sorry. I should have told
you to hold back more.
It's okay.
Um, your hand...
You want to hold hands a little longer?
Yes.
I won't wash this hand for a while.
How does tail taste?
Sweet and creamy!
Singing your own praises, huh?
Is my package here?
Hello?
Huh?
I invited her into my house...
But she's Tohru's friend, right?
She has horns and a tail, so...
But Tohru's out shopping right now.
Today we're having meat and potato stew!
What to do about this...
What's your name?
Break up with Lady Tohru.
Hmm? Lady?
What did you just say?
I know that you've seduced her.
With your body.
Huh?
Cuckold.
Slut in glasses!
Hey, aren't you making
a mistake? I'm not a slu—
Whoa now.
Break up with her! Give her back!
Miss Kobayashi, I'm home!
Why you!
Are you cheating on me?!
Don't make things more
complicated! Not worse!
Lady Tohru.
Ah...
This girl is called Kanna Kamui.
Kanna Kamui
She's an acquaintance of mine.
Figured.
Lady Tohru went missing,
so I came searching for her.
Went missing?
Tohru, you need to let your friends know.
Sorry.
Still, I'm surprised you found this place.
I saw Lady Tohru breathe
fire on that cloudy day.
And I sensed your magic power.
Ah...
You were careless there, huh, Tohru?
Lady Tohru, why are you in such an outfit?
Come home with me.
I need you, Lady Tohru.
I'm not going home.
Why not?
Because...
I'm in love with Miss Kobayashi!
Hey, take this seri—
I knew it!
Huh?!
I saw you on your date at the bazaar!
You were holding hands in public!
You perverts!
On our date?
Don't blush about it!
In that case, I'll kill you if I must...
Die!
Why you!
Why... you!
Kanna...
You've become incredibly
powerless, haven't you?
You're the odd one, Lady Tohru!
The mana purity here is too low!
Kanna-chan, do you mean...
you can't get home?
Th-That's not true.
It's not? But you don't have
anywhere to stay, right?
Come on, look me in the eye and answer.
I think your dead-fish eyes
are scary, Miss Kobayashi.
Kanna, please tell us honestly
about what you're planning.
If you're after Miss Kobayashi,
then I'm sorry, but give it up.
Tohru, be quiet for a moment.
Actually...
You were exiled for a prank?
Kanna does love pulling pranks.
Uh, so to sum things up...
It's like this?
Mommy, open up!
I'll be good!
Like that, yes.
She's probably not allowed to return
until she reflects on her actions.
It would be futile for me
to try sending her back.
So right now she's all on her own...
Yes.
Kanna-chan.
If you have no place to stay,
want to live here?
Huh? You told me no the first
time I asked, though. Huh?
Once you have one, two's nothing.
I don't trust humans!
You're plotting something!
You're trying to use me!
So you can't trust anyone
in an unknown world?
That's natural.
I wouldn't trust anyone either.
Trusting someone is something that happens
after you become friends or become lovers.
Kanna-chan, I won't ask you to be my friend.
Let's live together.
That's all.
Okay.
I'm so glad I fell in love
with Miss Kobayashi.
There!
Am I domesticating her with food?
Episode 2
Second Dragon, Kanna! (We're Totally Spoiling Here)
I want to play!
What about your game?
I'm bored with it.
Kanna is a child, after all.
She wants to exercise her
body to the fullest.
When I was a kid I spent my days
playing video games, though...
Well then, would you like to
play with me outside today?
Yeah!
Would you like to come, too, Miss Kobayashi?
No, please come!
I hate exercising.
Is this Japan?
Who knows?
I just landed in a big
field that looked nice.
Well, whatever.
I'm going to sleep off the
fatigue from my deathma.
Deathma: Short for death march.
To work without rest under an
overloaded schedule.
No Reception
Wake me up when you're finished playing.
And return us to Japan.
Oh well.
Okay, shall we play by ourselves?
Yeah.
Wait, wait, wait!
Huh? I thought you were going to sleep?
How can I sleep?!
What are you battling to the
death over all of a sudden?!
Oh, no. We were just
roughhousing a little bit is all.
You're over-exaggerating, Kobayashi.
Shoot, I'm at the disadvantage here.
Oh, I bet you wanted to join in,
too, right, Miss Kobayashi?
Jeez, you're not very honest.
I'd die!
It's fun to move around in a human body.
I thought your strength
was gone, Kanna-chan?
The source of my power is electricity.
So it returned after I recharged.
Are you made of lithium?
If we're playing around,
keep it to human standards.
Huh? We were at human standards, though?
Huh?
In our world there are plenty of
humans capable of doing that.
There's very few, in fact
none, who can here.
No, I saw some on TV the other day.
That's fiction, it wasn't reality.
Oh, sorry, for crushing your dreams.
Whatever.
I'll be sleeping over here.
Keep your playing around to my level.
Yes.
So there you have it, Kanna.
First, let's try to recall how
Miss Kobayashi usually acts.
Yeah!
The power of dragons...
I've seen it a few times now,
but it's still terrifying.
If they felt like it, our world would be...
My lower back! My lower back!
I'm tired! I'm dying!
Ah, never.
They'd never destroy our world.
And that exhausted behavior
is totally me, yeah.
Ah, that was fun.
Was it?
I guess you really didn't want
to play, Miss Kobayashi.
Hmm...
Guess we can play shiritori.
Apple (ringo).
Gorilla (gorira).
Trumpet (rappa).
Parachute (parashuuto).
Tornado (toruneedo).
Do, do... hmm...
Oh, dragon (doragon)!
Okay, you lose.
Ah.
You only left my tail-meat behind again!
I told you I can't.
Though if you turned it into ground
meat, I probably wouldn't notice.
But then you wouldn't know
it's my meat, would you?!
You want to emphasize that?
Hmm?
The Crane Repays a Debt
Miss Kobayashi, please don't peek into
the kitchen until I call for you.
The Crane Repays a Debt
Now, then.
That was fast!
I don't need grilled tail.
Wha?!
Kobayashi, where are you going?
Hmm? To work.
I'll go, too!
Kanna, you have things to do
with me today, don't you?
Things to do?
Kanna hasn't been in this
world very long, so...
I thought I'd teach her a few things.
Huh? You will?
No! I want to go with Kobayashi!
She's suddenly attached to me.
If you keep being selfish, I'll break you.
I'm off!
Have a safe trip!
Now then, Kanna, we're going to have you
learn the commonsense of this society.
Commonsense of this society?
First, you should learn
what you must not do.
Oh!
First, you must honor traffic lights!
Otherwise, you'll be hit by a car.
That's what those iron boxes are called?
Lady Tohru, you're smart!
How do they move?
Probably with magic.
Apparently you need a device
called a "license" for them.
Does Kobayashi possess a license?
I'd love to try riding in a car!
She seems to possess a license,
but she doesn't have a car.
Apparently it imposes strains
called "vehicle inspections" or "loans."
I guess power comes at
a price in every world.
Oh, but it would be really easy
if she had you carry her!
Why doesn't Kobayashi do that?
Right?
Wow, you've got another relative with you?
Is she a maid, too?
No, a Gothic lolita.
A Gothic lolita with a tribal theme.
Hmm, interesting tastes.
Tohru said she was going to teach her
some things, but I'm so worried.
First we should run tests using this module.
Mhmm.
Tohru-chan seems to have
her act together, though.
Then merge it with this one,
and run an integration test.
Together?
Well, I suppose perhaps she does have a lot
of compassion for her friends.
For real? That can't be. That's wicked!
For real?
What's he saying?
Magic words.
Yeah.
That can't be.
You can get through most conversations
using them, so try to remember them.
That's wicked.
And that?
In Trouble.
I don't know.
A tool children play with?
How do they play?
It looks like it uses the
principle of levers, but...
That's a training device for catapults!
Oh!
This is how children learn the means
of combating monsters in the sky!
Oh!
And that?
A crepe stand.
It's sweet, like yatagarasu eggs.
And that?
An ice cream stand.
It's cold. But good!
This world is peaceful.
Isn't it?
Are there dragons in this world?
Seems like there aren't.
I don't know if they went extinct
or if they moved elsewhere...
Is it wrong to revert to my original form?
Yes, it's fine, it's fine, it's all right.
Well, I wouldn't let your
form be seen, at least.
I'll be waiting here.
Can you use perception blocking, Kanna?
I can't.
I see.
Well, there's hardly ever
any need for it anyways.
Lady Tohru?
Yes?
Why did you come to this world?
I heard you had died...
So I was happy to find you survived.
I came to this world to escape.
Truth be told, I was on the verge of death,
but Miss Kobayashi saved me.
Kobayashi did?
I decided to repay her by
being her maid.
While letting people think I was dead.
I've only told a handful of
dragons about my survival.
Like Miss Lucoa and Mr. Fafnir.
You're like a retiree.
That might be close.
But, Kanna,
I'm very happy right now.
Yeah.
Come on, Kanna, isn't there
more you'd like to know about?
I'd like to see Kobayashi's work.
She'll be mad at you.
That's fine. I want to see.
Let's go say hello, then.
I blocked perception of us.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Huh? Oh, nothing.
Whatever.
It's not practice for catapults?
It's not. It's equipment kids play on.
This is fun!
I see.
This is fun, isn't it?!
Glad to hear it.
Next Episode
Kanna, supposedly there are
myriads of gods living here.
Lady Tohru, what does "myriads" mean?
Apparently gods reside in
all manner of things here.
What? That's scary.
Episode 3
Start of a New Life! (That Doesn't Go Well, Of Course)
You can't let your guard down.
Yeah.