Listen up, everyone.
I'm putting Chihaya in the
number three position.
Huh?
In the regional final,
Hokuo went with even
match-ups across the board.
Do we really want to
dodge our opponents?
Chihaya, you just have to win.
Bring home the win!
Victory for Mizusawa!
Yeah!
But...
1. Yuube (Third-year) Class A
2. Hayasaka (Second-year) Class B
3. Ousaka (Third-year) Class A
4. Nanase (Third-year) Class B
5. Tanimura (Third-year) Class B
Akashi Girls might
change up their order.
I didn't mention this...
But...
They probably went with the
same order every match
as preparation for the strong
teams they'll face from here on.
They'll switch it up once they
face a strong team.
So the question is whether Akashi
thinks we're good enough.
I will begin reading the order for
Mizusawa High School versus
First Akashi Girls' High School.
Mizusawa High School, Nishida-kun.
First Akashi Girls', Yuube-san.
Good, all according to plan!
Mizusawa High School, Oe-san.
First Akashi Girls', Hayasaka-san.
All according to plan!
Mizusawa High School, Ayase-san.
First Akashi Girls', Ousaka-san.
All according to plan!
Mizusawa High School, Mashima-kun.
First Akashi Girls', Nanase-san.
Mizusawa High School, Komano-kun.
First Akashi Girls', Tanimura-san.
It's so exactly according to our plan,
it's kind of sad...
Are they looking ahead to the finals?
They don't respect us?
Or perhaps...
they have absolute faith
that their ace will win?
Chihaya Furu
The
only
sign
of
summer
Verse 12
Hold on, Megumu.
We're not playing Fujisaki.
Over here.
What?
Oh, sorry about that.
Swoon!
Oh, this is still the semifinal.
Megumu, how could you screw that up
after they read the order?
What?  But...
They should just let us play the final now.
Swoon!  Swoon!  Swoon!
She really is ordinary and
sharp-tongued, yet popular!
Megumu-tan is our bitter and sweet idol...
We first met her early last summer,
during the brilliant First
Akashi Girls' cultural festival.
Wait, we're going to cut
to your flashback now?!
We belong to the photography club
at the neighboring boys' school...
What's this?  Taking pictures
without permission?
Get lost!
Teacher, there are perverts here!
Our intentions were pure,
yet they called us perverts
for taking a few pictures.
That was when...
That's mean.
Would you like to take pictures of
the demonstration our club's doing?
I'm from the competitive karuta club.
Megumu-tan was so kind
and lovely that day.
Hey, hey.
How did the pictures turn out?
Let me see.
Oh...
Wow, very nice.
Delete all pictures?
Deleting...
No data
Feel free to come take more pictures.
I'll delete them when you're done.
Swoon!
Ever since, we've been taking
pictures for Megumu-tan to delete.
What?!
What is it, Mori?
That picture!
It's from Megumu-tan's
tournament last year!
You were able to salvage it?!
Bastard!
You've betrayed Megumu-tan!
We can't allow the chronicle of
Megumu-tan, the next Queen,
to be completely erased.
Anyway, haven't you noticed?
Megumu-tan has changed...
Is that Ousaka Megumu?
Which one?
If she was the West representative,
she must be strong.
She lost to a veteran in
the challenger final,
but she may be the one who
faces Wakamiya Shinobu
in the Queen match this year.
Is she really that strong?
That's amazing.
The one in glasses?
Which one is she?!
There.  The one putting on a headband.
She must be fast, then.
I doubt she'll lose to
anyone in her age group.
Sounds like she's strong.
Oh, but her opponent's really pretty.
When I watched Ousaka-san last fall,
she was more focused on adapting
to her opponent than being fast.
I need to be careful and accurate.
Everybody helped to give me this chance.
Oh, that's right.
No matter how hard I worked,
I couldn't have made it here alone.
This
Omi Jingu tatami is for five.
They should just let
us play the final now.
You shouldn't say such a thing.
We will begin now.
Thank you for the game.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Creepy
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
The sound of birds crossing
from Awaji Island
Megumu-tan is faster now.
She's way faster now than when she was in
last year's Queen match.
I got it.
Okay, one card at a time, guys.
Yes!
Akashi Girls' has this match in the bag.
Mizusawa placed second
in the Tokyo regional,
and Group B didn't have
any strong opponents.
Akashi Girls has them beat in
both history and current lineup.
The match to watch is definitely
Creepy
Hokuo against Fujisaki.
The real final.
Wataya-kun, what was
your objective today?
Huh?
I came here to cheer for
my friends from Tokyo.
Then you're no longer
allowed to do that.
So he's cheering for Hokuo...
Creepy
Last year, Mizusawa prevented us
from making it to Nationals.
Amakasu and Takuma are the only
ones with experience at Nationals.
This year, we were able to bring
some first and second-years.
Fujisaki is fielding five third-years.
If we beat them here, they
won't be a threat next year.
You can do this, everyone!
However, I'm...
Fujisaki High School
Karuta Advisor
Sakurazawa Midori (39)
...really scared of Coach
Sakurazawa from Fujisaki!
The players from Akashi Girls'
are playing well, Coach Minami.
Ousaka-san is a strong weapon.
Naturally, Coach Sakurazawa!
First Akashi Girls'
Karuta Advisor
Minami Daigoro
Everybody's in a groove!
I'm looking forward to an exciting final,
whether it's against Hokuo or Fujisaki!
Please keep it down.
Understood?
Yes.
When I watched Ousaka-san last
fall, she didn't seem that fast,
but she attacked that
card at full speed.
Being too aggressive with
"The sound of birds" is risky.
Was she camping that card?
when I should have
gone to sleep instead
She passed me the only
"A" card on the field.
She'll be targeting it.
Here.
Oh...
Older alumni
Wait, why am I holding this?
awakens the guards of
Suma Gate at night
While the autumn leaves of
Mount Ogura would never...
Tough luck.
She shielded the "While autumn" on her right,
but "While the autumn" was read instead.
Couldn't have done
anything about that one.
No need to worry.
It's still early.
I need my first card.
One card at a time...
I'm sending this card.
people would always ask if
I was pining for someone
The only "Since" card on the field...
Heh, she plays a tougher game
than her appearance lets on.
"A night" and "Since I"
are cards that Ayase likes to
attack on the opponent's side.
Now that they're on her side, she'll
feel like she has to protect them.
Okay.
One card at a time...
She'll feel like she's on the defensive.
The opposing team is made
up of slender girls,
yet they look so strong.
They're moving in tandem.
Oh!  Could it be?
Are the headbands the key?!
Next time, I should make headbands!
Your brother can easily win if he tries.
Hey, Tsukuba!
How can you fall asleep?!
Wake up!
But I played three matches in a row!
No ifs or buts!
You wouldn't understand how tough it is!
We're talking three to four
serious matches in one day.
I'm a man and I'm about ready
to fall asleep on my feet.
Oe-senpai...
This being her fourth match today,
Oe-senpai is the one most likely
to be running low on stamina.
Especially since she lost her second
Lost by 2 cards
and third games by 2 cards each...
Lost by a lot
It really hurts when you fight hard,
only to lose at the very end.
If you're gonna lose
anyway, you might as well
let yourself be blown out
so you can get some rest.
Blown out of
all his games
Oe-senpai isn't the only
one I'm worried about.
Komano-senpai's first game
today comes in the semifinal.
Ayase-senpai is up against
the opponent's ace
and just lost two cards in a row.
It's usually up to the
ace to set the tone...
Outbox
To: Mom
Re: Nationals
Your brother the ace has
led the team to the
semifinals!
The championship is
within sight!
"Your brother the ace has led
the team to the semifinals!"
That's our Bro            So cool
"The championship is within sight!"
Inbox
From: Mom
Re: Re: Nationals
That's our Bro!
Good luck!
Take a picture
when you win!
I can always say that
I jammed my finger.
Do I attack?
Defend?
Don't doubt myself.
Chihaya-chan, when in
trouble, go lower right!
Always go to the lower right!
Make sure you check their names.
In Ousaka Megumu's case,
she's probably good at "While it pains,"
"While it may," "While it brings," and "Long,"
the cards with the starting sounds of her name.
Me (Long)
Her best card is at her lower right.
I beseech them to wait for the
Emperor's return before falling
Long last we meet, only for
me to leave hurriedly,
She knew to pay extra attention
to "Long last we meet"...
She couldn't get it.
No need to look.
Megumu-senpai would never lose "Long."
My opponent's card in the lower right was
read right when I set my eye on it.
This is the West representative.
No...
She's much faster than she was that day.
She has the potential to become Queen.
Hey,
that's mine.
You got mine, too.
Why are you holding
three of the same card?
Huh?
Swoon!
Okay, one more card.
Yes!
There's a saying that
boys grow up very fast,
but the same applies to girls.
You should all get
serious about karuta!
The Kyoto tournament is in May!
Any application fees will
be paid by the club!
You're such a pain, Daigoro!
Use your energy on the volleyball team.
The karuta club had plenty of history,
but it wasn't particularly strong.
Ousaka practiced all the
time at her karuta society,
but she never tried very
hard during club practice.
Everything changed after the Queen
challenger final in October.
The West representative
is Ousaka Megumu from
the Akashi Karuta Society!
She'd always had the talent,
but this time she was also lucky.
That was great, Megumu!
Next up is the challenger final?!
If you win that, you get to play the Queen?!
Her classmates and friends...
Good luck, Megumu
...believed...
...she could become Queen.
It's too bad for Ousaka-san.
She made it this far
on beginner's luck,
but that's not enough
to face the Queen.
Yamamoto Yumi-san had more
dedication and motivation.
Megumu, are you upset?
No, not really...
I definitely wasn't as good as she was.
We'll help you.
Huh?
We'll help, so let's practice until you're
invested enough to get upset.
Let's make you Queen.
Everyone is working together to
make Ousaka Megumu the Queen.
I tear up when I think
of how hard they've
been working ever since.
And I'm a grown man!
She got used to all the attention
Ignoring...
she draws as the last West Representative.
This proves that circumstances
can change a person!
The ace usually plays
in the third position.
We'll put Megumu in the
third position every match.
Our goal is to get Megumu
more experience, not win!
...like the moon hidden
behind the clouds
Said night was young when
the false rooster's crow,
I hadn't marked that one.
This is no good.
She's taken four cards in a row.
I need my first card.
My first card...
banish any lingering memories of the past
but the gates of Afusaka remained shut
When winds blow oak leaves in the twilight,
There!
I finally got a card.
This is just the beginning!
I can catch up!
Attack...
Attack!
"When winds blow," Chihaya-chan.
The rain...
When winds blow oak
leaves in the twilight,
the only sign of summer is the
ritual purification in the waters
Stopped...
This poem by Junii Ietaka
describes a comfortable
last day of summer.
This day will define our entire summer.
Oe-senpai is leading by 4 cards!
She's probably tired!  Exhausted, even!
That card is more than
"When wind blows"...
More than three syllables...
Chihaya-chan, when this poem
was written 800 years ago,
they must have felt very refreshed.
the only sign of summer is the
ritual purification in the waters
They could
probably hear the wind blow.
Silent waves creep closer to the
Suminoe shore, and when night falls,
Got it!
What?!
Megumu?!
Kana-chan,
I remember.
Speaking of dreams,
there's "Silent waves"!
in my dreams, I creep closer to you
Megumu-chan...
Let's...
have a good match!