O-Okay.
Counting on you.
They're at the station now.
Oh my God! She's really coming!
I-I need to calm-
Madam Manager!
You are to be in charge of
our next customer, Nako.
Huh?!
You're going to give Nako
such a difficult task?!
I get the feeling she'll like you.
But...!
Wouldn't it be better to have Ohana,
someone related to
her, be her attendant?
No, that's out of the question.
Then how about you taking
the position yourself?!
Same goes for me.
I might attempt to slap
her if I see her.
Geez, why did Ohana have
to go and bring an enemy?
She's an important customer
Ohana is bringing.
R-Right.
Despite the circumstances,
she's still a customer.
The Kissuiso will operate as usual.
Though I don't know how I'm
going to react to everything.
Madam Manager...
They're here!
Whew!
Thanks for the ride, Tohru!
No problem.
Wow, nothing's changed.
Actually, it's gotten a
lot older and trashier.
Oh.
You haven't changed either, Mom!
Actually, you've gotten
a lot older and...
I'll stop there.
Thank you.
Oh, god! The young master!
Oh-
Man!
Come on.
You've put on some weight!
A-Allow me to escort you
to your room, ma'am.
Okay.
Please wait, ma'am!
Wow, Beanman?!
That aura...
So that's her...
Welcome back.
Thank you.
Huh? Where's Ohana?
Episode 13
Shijima's Girl
(Broken Heart MIX)
So the yukata design
hasn't changed either.
There are places nowadays where they
let customers pick from a few designs.
I think it's important to
have things like that too.
I-I see...
Oh, please have some tea.
I think you can improve this, too.
Like, for example, these snacks.
Huh?
This area is known for its Yuzu.
Serving a yuzu-flavored
snack would create
a topic of discussion between
the waitress and the customer.
U-Umm...
I tend to speak to myself a lot,
because of what I do for work.
Sorry about that.
N-Not at all...
Huh?
Wow...
Y-Yes?
You have such pretty eyes!
Geez, will you calm down?
I can't! I just can't!
You don't know how scary
she is, Ms. Tomoe.
She made me do all of her
summer vacation homework,
and took my New Year's money!
I see.
So that explains why you like Takako,
someone with a similar personality.
N-No!
Nako!
How was she?!
She's a wonderful person.
She gave me so much advice
on how to make this inn better.
Advice?
Yes.
About yukatas and the tea snacks...
Wait-
Don't.
So what?
I'm not writing them down because
it's what my sister said.
It's as an opinion of a cust-
What was that for?!
You're so hardworking, Ohana.
You just returned and are already back to work.
Just returned?
Huh?
Nothing...
I returned...
So suddenly, to my regular self.
The me that was holding
placards in Tokyo,
and the me who was having
dinner with Ko...
They're not my regular self.
The me who works here has
become my regular self.
Hello, waitress!
There's a place I want to visit!
Will you accompany me?
W-Why me?
It's scary to climb a
hill with heels on.
What are you going to
do if something happens
to a customer after ignoring her plea?
There really is nothing
here, is there?!
But there's this thing called a
Bonbori Festival around here.
That's the one thing I
liked about this place.
They say your wish comes
true, and I believed them.
Did you know about that?
Since forever.
Why don't you ask the gods to restore
your relationship with Ko?
W-W-W-W-
Oh, did I guess correctly?
So you did get dumped by him.
Got dumped?!
Don't worry.
There are so many other boys out there.
You're a little short and thick,
but since you're my daughter-
Don't...
Don't suddenly start
acting like a mother!
I'm going back now.
Wait, Ohana.
What?
I came to this inn because
you speak so highly of it.
You get it, right?
It's no time to be depressed because
you got dumped by some guy.
You'd better show me what's
so great about this inn.
I guess her situation with him
is worse than I'd thought.
"It's no time to be depressed because
you got dumped by some guy."
Dumped by...
Dumped...
Did I really?
So this is what it means to be dumped?
What's going on?
We've been had.
Huh?
Tohru, I need you to make the dashi.
Okay.
It smells so good!
Being this time of the year,
are you cooking smelt-whiting?
Or is it tempura?
You might laugh, saying that
it's "plain boring," but...
Oh?
Predicting is the same thing as hoping.
It's not nice to kill
my hopes like that.
Huh?
And that's why you should
be trying to surprise
me in a different way,
like preparing several kinds of salt.
It would have been a lot easier if
she had just called it "boring."
I've been had as well.
The bath isn't ready yet-
Geez, this inn is as strict as ever.
It's better to randomize
cleaning times,
based on watching the customers' activities.
The good thing about a hot
spring inn is being able
to enter the hot spring
whenever you like.
Right?
She got me.
The nape of her neck was so sexy...
What are you talking about?!
She's a troubling customer, but...
But I still think she's wonderful.
Yeah, what she said about
the cooking wasn't wrong either.
Yeah!
She's definitely better than that
Takako that the young
master always brings!
Takako says she'll be on her way!
Die.
Man, we're saved!
As long as she's here,
we'll be able to handle my sister-
You're going to rely on an outsider
even during a situation like this?!
This isn't only the Kissuiso's problem!
This is our problem! The Shijima's!
Though she's my daughter,
she's still a customer.
And that's why I didn't
take charge of her room.
If my personal feelings get in the way,
I wouldn't be able to do my job.
What would you do if the
daughter of the Mikasa family were here?
Umm...
I'd always prepare two bath towels.
What about for the mother?
She likes very hot tea,
so I'd raise the temperature
of the water in the pot.
Precisely.
For people visiting for the first time,
you need to find out
about their preferences,
and make sure to use it for reference
the next time they come.
But, though that customer is
visiting for the first time,
she actually isn't.
You and I know a lot
about that customer.
Madam Manager...
They're a lot similar.
That customer and the
Madam Manager, that is.
You think so?
I see what you mean.
They're different kinds of people,
but they have their similarities.
I can tell that they're
mother and daughter.
You're praising that
customer too much there.
It's rude, even for the
Madam Manager to take part
in the kitchen's activities.
However, do you mind letting me
use it just this once, Mr. Ren?
Madam Manager?
Nakochi.
Ohana.
Do you mind letting me prepare the futon
for the customer in the Wisteria Room?
What?
Sure, but...
Huh?
Yeah?
You're back to your regular old self.
I'm glad.
My regular old self...
Excuse me.
I've been waiting for you!
Wow, this is good!
Thank you.
A lot of effort has been put into it.
What's this?
It's a special dish for you.
Stewed fish cake is pretty
plain for a dish at an inn.
Huh?
Oh... well...
Serving my favorite food like that...
I'm using the bath, Beanman.
Mind getting out?
You don't need to leave.
A customer will be here soon.
He'll be cleaning despite
whether you decide to
use the bath or not.
B-But-
If you don't want to be seen,
wash yourself in the kitchen.
Fine, be that way!
Those sheets aren't dry?!
I can't believe you can't sleep
if you're not hugging rolled-up sheets.
Then I need you to be its
replacement tonight!
Please ask your boyfriend instead.
Is that something a daughter
should be saying?
You're more of a "woman"
than a "mother" to me.
That sounds cool.
Anything else?
Oh!
I think it'll be better to
wake her up three times.
I agree.
She's not a morning person.
Additionally...
She tosses about in bed!
Yup.
In this area, it's cool at
night even during the summer.
Serving hot rice porridge in the
morning might be a good idea.
Yeah.
And maybe we should serve some
vegetable juice with that.
Hey...
I think this is the most
I've spoken with the
Madam Manager by myself.
And it's about Mom, too.
The Madam Manager is my grandmother,
and obviously, Mom's mother.
I'll get it.
Hello?
Mom-
The customer in the Wisteria Room?
Could you bring me some sake?
Warm, not hot.
Oh, and three cans of beer, please.
Soft drinks, too.
Oh, and a geisha.
G-Geisha?!
Well, at this hour, we can't...
Then in that case, an old lady
and a young girl will do.
Umm...
Thanks.
Excuse us.
You're here!
Come in and have a seat!
I'm sorry, but we still
have work to do...
Don't be so uptight!
Have a glass.
That was fast!
Bravo!
She got drunk over soda.
She's really good at getting
the wrong idea, after all.
I-I knew.
Okay, what did you know?
I knew that Ko was important to me.
But...
Then why didn't you tell him so?
When I realized I like him,
I got rejected!
What are you talking about?
A woman from the Shijima family
giving up after being
rejected once or twice?
Huh?!
Don't tell me you fought
hard for Dad, Mom?
Of course I did.
He was strait-laced,
so I was rejected four times in a row.
The fifth time's the charm!
Wow!
No!
I'm not giving up.
I don't want to keep him at
my beck and call anymore!
Ko already has a life of his own.
In that case, do you want
to come back to Tokyo?
You can enter his life again.
No!
No! No! No!
I already have my life, too!
A life at the Kissuiso! So...
So you'd rather put work over love.
She really is a woman
of the Shijima family.
Though you're an exception.
Wow, I got told.
Mom's also festing it up!
I understand now.
Both Mom and Grandma are festing it up.
Fes-
That's why...
I also need to...
Hey, having their kid
recognize their effort
signals the end of a parent.
She's not listening to you.
Wow, you can hold your drink!
Another shot, then.
What are you doing?
Do I look like I'm working overtime?
No, not really...
Nothing's changed.
You mean Miss Satsuki?
Her, Mom, and myself.
I'm always out of the loop.
I can't. I ride a motorcycle.
What a boring guy.
Huh? Done already?
I don't remember you being this weak.
Come on, Mom.
You'll get sick.
I saw...
I saw a dream.
You succeeded the inn, and
Ohana was there, too.
And then you always make
me do stuff like this.
Don't say that.
You okay?
Yeah.
You're pretty light, aren't you, Mom.
Don't make her worry too much, okay?
I don't need you to tell me that.
Anyway, good night.
I didn't hear anything.
Please continue to be that
mother I always hated.
Thanks for everything!
Oh, right.
I promised.
If you really start hating
your job, you can come back.
All of a sudden acting
like a mother again!
Come on, you need to let
me act cool at the end.
Take care, Beanman!
You too.
Thank you very much!
Hey, what's it say?!
Come on, read it!
Hurry! Hurry!
Okay.
Calling it "retro" would be too simple.
However, without change, things
would be too sedimented.
It's very difficult to get
through to your customer that
your inn isn't going to change.
The Kissuiso is always evolving,
in order to continue its
service that is unchanging.
In order to protect its
"retro" tradition.
I can really tell that
the staff have spirit.
It was a very warm inn that
I enjoyed staying at.
Hey...
It was praise.
Indeed.
Yeah!
Sis...
Beanman!
There, there.
I realized something
after Mom came here.
Though I miss Ko,
I never feel the urge
to go back to Tokyo.
It's not that I'm not returning
to Tokyo because things
aren't the same between Ko and I.
It's because this place is my home.
I chose this place to be my home.
I love the Kissuiso.
I love everyone who works here.
I love Grandma, the Madam Manager,
and I also love my mother.
Ko, too...
See ya.
Ko!
I'm sorry for everything I've done!
Thanks for everything!
Thanks!
See ya!
Okay!
Let's go!
I even brought my swimsuit
I wear during competitions.
You're going to ask her out, right?
You want to become a waitress, Ohana?
I don't really understand you, Yuina.
Episode 14
This is My Way of Life