Kageyama Shigeo, also known as Mob.
A second-year in middle school.
The second year of middle school kicks off
the most sensitive period in one's life.
People call it adolescence.
Some hone their bodies playing sports,
some work hard on their studies,
some devote themselves to their hobbies,
some polish their talents,
some rebel,
and some fall for the opposite sex
and get a taste of bittersweet love.
All those youthful desires come together to
form the amalgamation that is adolescence.
And Mob was spending that
precious time working as
an assistant at a psychic business
for 300 yen an hour.
The reason is porn sites!
What?!
Porn sites...?
Yes! The curse that is on your shoulder is
a terrible one-click curse!
Doubts About Youth
~The Telepathy Club Appears~
Spirits and Such
Consultation Office
A-A one-click curse from porn sites?
They use illegal 18+ sites
to curse your shoulder
and make you pay fees.
Curses nowadays are becoming digital, too.
Who the hell would believe that hogwash?
Just don't move for a second.
I'll lift the curse now.
No, it's fine!
Your right shoulder is stiff—
The curse is strong.
Hey! I'm not paying for this. Sto—
H-Huh? It actually feels good?
Sorcery Crush!
Sorcery
Crush
It's finished!
Reigen's special move
where he relieves the stress
from physical fatigue
Abeshi
and gets ride of stiff
shoulders and back pain.
I believe that I was able to
lift the curse,
but do your shoulders still feel heavy?
I'm sorry that I doubted you.
I feel much better!
May I come again?
Of course!
Reception
Manual
If there are 3 evil spirits,
the exorcism fee on 1 of
them will be on the house!!
This Month Only
So the 40-minute massage course
fee comes to 3,800 yen.
You idiot! Don't call it the massage fee!
Call it the curse-dispelling fee!
Your change is 200 yen.
Here. You'll eat some won't you, Mob?
Oh, sure. I'll have some.
Master Reigen, you're getting
much better at massages.
Well, yeah. I've been trying
various methods to improve,
like reading books on Seitai and stuff.
Limited-Time Offer
If there are 3 evil spirits,
the exorcism fee on 1 of
them will be on the house!!
This Month Only
Of course, it's only effective
because of spiritual power.
Hot!
Such a waste!
Master, I've been thinking...
Well, this is rare.
You never try to start a conversation.
Well, I can use a little ESP and
I'm different from other people,
so I came to discuss that with you
and ended up becoming your student.
At the time, I didn't have anyone
else to talk to, so I'm grateful,
because you teach me various
things and pay me.
However, is this really okay?
That's what I've been thinking lately.
Does he think his pay is too little?
Or did he finally find me out?
Fake
Liar
Con Artist
Self-Proclaimed Psychic
What do you mean?
How do I put this...
Rather than things ending with me
working part-time after school,
I have a feeling that there may or may not be
some other things that I
can only experience now...
Huh?
Oh, so that's it.
Such is puberty, Mob-kun.
Is there something that
you want to do right now?
Be in a band?
Dance?
To Wakkanai
Hitchhike?
No, I don't have anything particular in mind.
Listen, Mob.
There's no need to rush into things.
In my expert opinion, I'd say the
going-home club is the absolute best.
You're just goofing off during
the period you can goof off the most,
and that makes you a winner in my book.
Keep on lazing around and
make money from me. Got it?
Wait a sec, Takenaka!
I get treated like a weirdo
just for being in this club!
Telepathy Club
Just wait!
I can't do it anymore!
This isn't good.
A club must have five
or more members, right?
What should we do, President?
What else can we do?
We have to find new members
like our lives depend on it!
Telepathy Club President:
Kurata Tome
Maybe Takenaka-san came back.
That's gotta be it! Takenaka!
Student
Council
I just received a submission of resignation
from this club, so be forewarned...
The...
The student council!
Student Council Vice President:
Tokugawa
This club will now be abolished.
Abolished?
Already?!
Sadly, I'm going to have to ask you
to gather all of your things.
I actually just had a brand-new club
request a club room.
Q-Quit jumping the gun!
I'm not going to let you
abolish the Telepathy Club!
The Telepathy Club bond is strong.
The student council's got nothing on us!
You think you're all high-and-mighty
because of how you part your hair?!
Shut up. Do you really want me to get angry?
If you're that desperate
to keep this club going,
bring me a new club member by
the end of the school day on Friday.
Telepathy Club
B-By Friday?
That only gives us two days.
That's impossible.
Quit whining!
If we ask everyone we see to join,
we'll be able to snag at least one!
No, that's impossible.
Recruiting season ended a long time ago.
No! I'm going to do this!
We have overcome so many obstacles
up until now, haven't we?!
President...
We haven't done a single thing...
The Next Day After School
Telepathy Club? Sorry, what the hell
are you talking about?
It's creepy, so no.
I've got a job.
Abolished? What's wrong with that?
You should be studying.
We've got entrance exams this year.
Are there hot guys?
Do you have any hot guys?
I want to be able to date.
Girls Bathroom
I'd be worried about the stares,
and it seems dangerous.
It's creepy, so no.
Sorry. It's creepy, so no.
Creepy.
Nope.
It's creepy, so no.
It really was impossible to find
new members this time of the year.
Not to mention we just keep
getting called creepy.
Now even I want to quit.
No!
The president's lost it!
Please calm down!
The going-home club...
President!
I've brought him! He's not
in any clubs or committees,
and he doesn't seem to have a
girlfriend or any friends.
Salt Middle School's final
go-homer and all-round bum,
Kageyama Shigeo-kun of class 2-1.
Well, he's basically right.
Well done, Inukawa! Let me introduce you
to the other members, Kageyama-kun.
This is Kijibayashi, and Saruta.
Nice to meet you.
Hey.
And I'm the president,
Kurata Tome, from class 3-5.
Call me Tome-chan.
The president is desperate!
Tome-chan... That's my grandmother's name.
I-I'm sure that's because of fate, too!
There you have it!
Join the Telepathy Club!
I can't today.
What?!
Wait a second, Mob! You actually have plans?
Yeah. After this, I have
to go to my exorcism job.
E-Exorcism? What's that supposed to mean?
Ah, President! Actually, this guy
was sort of famous in grade school.
He could bend spoons and make erasers move...
In other words...
He's an esper!
Stop being weird and just join our club.
I'm sure the exorcism can
wait a little while.
Spirits and Such
Consultation Office
Hey, what's up, Mob?
Ah, Master.
Is it all right if I'm a little late today?
I'm being recruited into a club.
That should be over instantly.
No, I actually have to wait until
the student council meeting is over,
and then go submit my club admission form.
Uh, wait. So if I tell you I need you to
come immediately, you're not going to join?
Yes, well... Shouldn't I keep
the promise I made first?
So it's not like you actually want to join?
Not really, no.
Then hurry on over.
Show them how fast someone in the
going-home club can leave school.
He says he needs me right away,
so I'll be going now.
P-Put me on for a sec!
I really need Kageyama-kun to
join this club, no matter what!
A girl, eh? She must be trying to use Mob.
Mob's not the type to play any sports.
Forcing him into things isn't good.
We're not a sports club!
We're the Telepathy Club!
Huh? What the hell is that?
It's a club where we train in
order to feel telepathic powers.
Yeah, that sounds shady as hell.
What do you mean "telepathy"?
Like you're one to talk!
I heard that Kageyama-kun has ESP,
but aren't you using that
to get more customers?
Because you're a phony!
Shut your mouth, amateur!
Don't you dare try to steal away my
student's precious time with your nonsense!
What?!
Are you saying that you don't care
if our club gets abolished?
We're going to be kicked out of the room!
Master, Senpai is about to cry, so I'm
thinking about joining after all...
Don't be fooled!
Those are crocodile tears!
Bonds, memories, and friendship...
Like any of those things will disappear
because a club is abolished.
No! They just don't want to lose
their room, their budget
and their pointless after-school time,
judging from what their club sounds like.
See through it, Mob!
That shady club is going down
because it's meant to go down.
If you understand, hurry up and come to work!
I understand...
And so, I'll be leaving after all.
Wait! Hear me out, too!
It seems that the president
seriously believes in telepathy,
but honestly, yeah, I just want to goof off.
But right now, we're in middle school.
This is the only time we're going
to be able to goof off!
Play cards with us in this lazy
little paradise we've created!
You're not going to find a more
carefree club than this.
We have until tomorrow, so think it over.
You're our last hope, Kageyama-kun!
You properly declined, didn't you?
No. I thought I'd think about it overnight.
You shouldn't procrastinate, Mob.
You need to properly decline things
that you don't want to do.
Right now, the thing I least want to do
is be dressed like this.
Oh, there it is.
Saint Highso Girls' Academy.
It's a private all-girls high school.
We're meeting the clients up on the roof.
Okay.
Highso Private Girls' Academy
Stop! What are you doing?
Pardon?
You! I'm talking to you! Don't play dumb!
I'm a student here.
Reporting from the front gate.
A suspicious individual showed up!
Requesting backup!
Hey, that's a bit mean, isn't it?
You perverted weirdo!
I knew this wouldn't work.
But thank goodness that they saw
through our disguises so early.
I didn't want to infiltrate the school
dressed up like this.
That was close. Now hurry up
and get away from the pervert.
Huh?
We'll deal with the suspicious individual.
G
GO
Huh?
Progress toward Mob's Explosion: 30%
Progress toward Mob's Explosion: 31%
Progress toward Mob's Explosion: 32%
Progress toward Mob's Explosion: 33%
Progress toward Mob's Explosion: 34%
Progress toward Mob's Explosion: 35%
Mob Psycho 100
Won't I get in a lot of trouble
if I'm busted?
He said we were meeting on the roof, but...
Um, hello.
I've come from the consultation office.
Are you the clients?
Huh? Who the hell are you?
An unfamiliar face.
You a transfer student?
Huh?
Consultation office?
You trying to get through to us thugs?
So annoying!
Like we're going to let some
twerp like you lecture us!
No, I'm just—
Why don't you mind your own business?!
If you don't, you're going to regret it!
Sorry about that...
Man, talk about a downer. Let's go.
Hmph!
Hello?
You promptly got picked on
by thugs. How funny.
Chihiro
Clients:
Mari
We're your clients.
Isn't that Reigen guy coming?
He was caught at the front gate.
Also, you both came here
dressed as girls? Seriously?
He couldn't get us permission to come in,
so we didn't have a choice...
I see.
Sorry to make you go through all that.
The school just refuses
to take us seriously.
What did you tell them?
Students' belongings have been disappearing
under mysterious circumstances,
and we've been hearing weird noises...
What do you call it,
a poltergeist phenomenon?
We heard things have been spotted
floating through the air, too.
Right. Apparently a bra started floating
around on its own in the locker room.
Bra...?
We're dead sure it has to be
something supernatural.
So we just called the cheapest
exorcist in the area
and somehow ended up with you.
Huh?
You're a guy, but you were trembling so much
dealing with some high school girls.
You must be quite the reliable gentleman.
Th-Thank you...
That was sarcasm, duh!
She wasn't complimenting you!
Are you sure we can trust you?
I have my doubts.
You seem unreliable.
What?
What's wrong?
I-It's fine...
I just have to perform an exorcism.
If you feel anything spiritual, let us know.
Right.
Well? Do you sense anything?
Just slightly...
I wonder if he's being serious...
It's here. Nearby.
Huh? Really?!
Someone!
What's wrong?
Something was here...
Something was looking in
from the top of the door...
The windows are locked.
And no one's gone through the exit.
I'm going to follow the spirit.
Nothing so far?
We can trust you, right?
Yes.
You still can't find it?
The spirit's angry.
Huh?
If we keep pursuing it,
it might try to do something.
Eek! What are we going to do?
The basketball team is practicing inside.
I'm going to end this.
I've trapped the spirit.
Pass! Pass! Hey!
I've found you.
Huh?
It's huge!
What is that?! A ghost?!
Psychic brat...
How dare you trap me?
Are you going to try to ruin my paradise?
Evil Spirit: Scent-Ghoul
This is what you get!
Crap. I underestimated the psychic.
If I don't take a hostage, he'll erase me!
You smell nice.
I choose you!
Look out!
Huh?
It's over.
Wow.
Want to go home together today?
How did you do that?
What class is she in?
So cool!
Tell me!
Listen to them cheer. Good for you.
Thanks. Apparently you were
pretty reliable after all.
Damn it...
To think that I was defeated
by a loser like you...
And I thought I'd finally
be able to be happy.
You seem to be similar to me.
Similar?
The way you get nervous around girls...
You're playing the loser role in
youth just like me, aren't you?
Things...
Things finally started to get
fun for me after I died.
I was content.
But I guess it's all over now.
Hey... Are you living
every day to the fullest?
What's wrong?
You seem out of it.
Is something troubling you?
Huh? No, I'm fine.
All right, then...
Mob!
You came!
We believed in you, Kageyama-kun!
Now, hurry up and sign
this club admission form.
You're already here?
That was awfully quick...
Vice President!
Well, I had to show this room...
to them.
This room will become the club room
for the newly formed Body Improvement Club.
What?! Hey, hold on a sec!
The Telepathy Club won't be abolished!
Kageyama-kun here is just about to join!
What?
Are you insane?
Huh?
What grade are you in?
I'm a second-year.
Do you have any experience in other clubs?
No.
Do you have a close friend
in the Telepathy Club?
I have an acquaintance.
Do you go to cram school?
No.
Do you study?
Not really.
Do you have any hobbies?
Um...
Don't you have anything
that you want to do?
Huh?
If you let them goad you into joining
despite having no interest in the club at all,
what exactly will you gain from it?
Well, I just want to live
every day to the fullest.
And will spending your time after school
with cola, snacks and video games
help you do that?
If you want to join of your own free will,
I will not stop you.
However, you should carefully
reconsider this.
What is it that you really want to do?
What I want to do...
Do I have anything I want to do?
Does everyone else have something?
Something enjoyable?
Something I'm envious of?
What are they enjoying?
Clubs, hobbies, and studying?
Hanging out with girls might be fun...
I did have a dream!
I wanted to confess my feelings to
my first love, Tsubomi-chan,
and walk home together, holding hands.
Look, Tsubomi-chan.
When you make frogs float,
they start swimming.
Wow, how cute.
I can make the bar all squishy.
You're amazing, Mob-kun.
Look! I'm only showing you, Tsubomi-chan!
I'm bored of that.
The red team is fast!
You're so fast, Akira-kun!
That's right. If I can change anything
by joining a club...
I'll join!
Thank you for having me,
Body Improvement Club!
Huh? You want to join us?
Huh?
Good to have you!
Thank you!
Progress toward
Mob's Explosion
Progress toward Mob's Explosion: 40%
Club Admission Form
I will join the Body Improvement Club.
Class 2-1         Kageyama Shigeo
Contact Information
Reason for Joining