That was your last
supplementary class. Great work.
Thank you very much.
Yes! Now I can—
Not yours, hers.
This is your note.
And, go.
You sound great together.
Episode 7
Spinning in Circles and Losing Sight
Choir and Sometimes
Badminton Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: White Festival Discussion
Let's begin by having
our now official member,
Sakai Wakana, introduce herself.
You should've warned me!
Sakai-san, please stand.
Go on.
Do I have to?
Hurry up.
You can do it!
Jeez... What should I say?
Fight!
Um...
I've decided to actually take
part in the choir club's activities.
My name is Sakai Wakana.
I know I haven't been participating,
and my attitude could've been better,
so I would like to
apologize—
Let's cut off the formal
intros right there.
Stop it, Wakana!
Okay, let's talk about the White Festival.
Question!
Yes, Wien-kun.
What is the White Festival?
We have to start there?
It's a white rhinoceros.
It's the culture fair.
Huh?
It's a white rhinoceros.
You mean, with the horn?
That's right.
Didn't you know there's a
white rhino under the gym?
There is?!
Did you know?
Of course.
They let it out once a year for a festival
and parade, where it sings and dances!
Makes sense.
It'd be pretty mean to keep it locked up.
Today, we'll discuss what our
club will do for the fair,
so give me all your ideas.
Okay.
Girls are scary.
Hello.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Horsemanship Class
Badminton Class
Cat Café
Hero Show
Competitive Eating
No, no, and no!
These don't have anything
to do with singing!
We could do singing lessons on horseback?
Singing badminton?
An exciting super hero show?
Singing cat café?
Singing eating contest?
No!
We'll sing on stage, in the gym.
It'll be packed with visitors!
This is our first and final
chance to shine!
Will the rhino be there?
Get over the rhino.
We can't just do a normal choir piece?
But then we'll be upstaged
by the other choir.
The bigger group will be more impressive.
I don't want the vice principal to win...
What about an opera?
I like!
With five people?
Plus, we can barely manage traditional songs.
Opera is way out of our league.
Yeah, I guess so.
It's not a competition. What matters
is that we sing our own song.
Wow.
Cool!
What the hell?
I'm right, aren't I?
Yeah, that is the bottom line.
Yeah.
All right!
Let's show the vice principal and her choir!
Move.
Sure.
Your friends?
Yeah. Ueno-san's in the other choir club.
Isn't this one too easy?
And Hirohata-san's the president.
Yes, but let's take it.
I see you've found some friends
to goof off with. Congrats.
Huh?
You know, most people in our choir
are seriously thinking about their futures.
I hope you don't mess things up for us.
Ciao, strepitoso.
Ciao!
Strepitoso?
It means noisy.
"Strepitoso" is a musical term
meaning noisy or boisterous.
Works for me!
I really don't want them to upstage us.
I'm off to the student council room.
God speed to you, my people.
I've got mounted
archery practice,
so I need to take off.
My cram school classes start today.
Cram school?
I'm prepping for entrance exams.
I thought you had an
athletic scholarship.
I do, but I can't count on that.
If I fail my entrance exams,
I can't play badminton.
See ya around.
Bye.
I guess everyone's thinking
about the future.
What will you do?
I don't know yet.
I guess we have that in common.
There's something I'm determined
to create right now,
so I'm focusing on that first.
I need to hit the library.
Later.
Uh, yeah.
Excuse me.
Oh, Makoto.
What have we here, a dirty book?
I'd like to reserve the main
stage for the culture fair.
Mr. Assistant Secretary sure
has a lot of time on his hands.
Here.
Fill out your application,
then get lost.
Yes, sir!
"Our performance will consist
of singing and dancing."
Guess that's good enough for now.
Do you honestly think that'll pass?
Huh?
Why wouldn't it?
There's a selection process
because of all the
individual and group
applications that come in every year.
That doesn't apply to
official clubs though, right?
It does now.
Before, only established groups with
good track records applied.
What are you trying to say?
That the vice principal is in
charge of running the main stage.
Seriously?
Yes!
Sabure, we've got practice on Sunday.
After I graduate, we'll probably
have to say goodbye...
Let's make the most of our time.
I'm home.
You opened it?!
I can't believe you!
I've told you a thousand times.
Keep riding as a hobby.
Have you considered the
consequences if you fail?
Some obstacles can't be
overcome by hard work alone.
Especially as a woman.
Horseracing is a gamble.
You don't have to succeed the
temple business if you don't want to,
but at least get a position with the goverment,
or any other real job,
and ride in your free time.
I have nothing to say to you anymore.
How will you make a living?
I've been saving my pay!
It's not that much yet, but...
What about the rest?
Listen to me.
Your food, clothes, and tuition
are all paid for by honest work.
Supporting a family through your job
is what working is all about.
Horseback riding does
not constitute work.
It's play!
Get off my back!
I didn't ask your opinion!
Here, you can have it back!
You might as well sell it
and get your money back!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Having fun in here?
You know, there are better
ways to talk about this.
This world of winning and losing
isn't as nice as you think.
I hate you.
I hope you go bald!
Hey!
She hopes you go bald.
Quiet.
Musical Vocabulary Dictionary
Old Music
Career Planning Sheet
My dear friend Yang,
My friends in the choir club are
all working hard to reach their goals.
I'm happy for them, of course,
but my heart is uneasy.
I wonder if I'll also find my calling.
Where have I come from,
and where am I going?
This is bad.
I can't sound so depressed.
I have something amazing to tell you!
They keep a white rhino
in the basement of the gym here!
They let it out once a year,
and hold a festival to celebrate!
Wakana, are you still sleeping?
It's pretty rare for you to sleep in.
Why didn't you wake me earlier?
You mean, "thank you for making
me breakfast," right?
Thank you.
Can you feed Dora, too?
"Please feed her, Father Dearest."
Please feed her, Father Dearest.
By the way, Sugi-san from the
sake shop gave me tickets again.
You might check out a musical
with your old dad now and then...
I want to go with my friends!
Can you ask him if he
can get you another one?
What?
Please, Father Dearest.
Sure. And here, I made you lunch.
Oh, thank you.
See you later.
Have a good day.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What?
Is that all you're eating?
Huh?
Yeah.
Did you eat earlier?
I'm just not that hungry.
Why are you covering that up?
Oh wow, it's a heart!
Is not! I overslept this morning,
and my dad made this for me,
for some weird reason.
He's doing this to bug me!
Lotta daddy love in that lunch.
There is not!
Totally love, right?
Love, huh?
Oh hey, I have tickets for a musical in town.
You guys want to go?
It could help give us
ideas for the White Festival.
Really? I'm in!
Yeah...
Maybe opera's out, but we could
definitely do a musical.
We could sing in cat costumes!
Yes, that could work!
Keep spinning like that
and you'll fall again.
Worry not, it'll all work out!
Right, Sawa?
What?
Huh?
What's wrong?
You haven't touched your rice ball.
I don't have much of an appetite today.
Sorry. You eat it.
I'm heading out.
What's with her?
Think she's on a diet?
What're you doing for
the culture fair?
Maybe a concert or something.
Great idea. I could play bass for you.
Cool, let's do it!
I sense spring.
What?
Y-Yes!
Come on in.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Oh, it's just you.
There's an issue with the choir club.
They want to use the main
stage during the cult—
I leave that all in your hands.
But, sir...
All in your hands.
Certainly, sir.
Good day, Mr. Chairman.
I've been waiting for you.
Thank you so much for coming.
How may I be of assistance today?
How are you feeling?
Completely fine, now.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
You didn't.
My only concern is how this might
adversely affect my business plan.
So it's a sure thing?
Yes, though the roadmap has
been slightly accelerated.
That's what I'm here to discuss.
If you want a comfortable retirement,
you'll have to work for it.
Naturally.
What's wrong?
My stomach hurts.
Do you need some medicine?
It's not that bad, thanks.
Raise your velum, open your throat,
and let your tone be bright.
Listen to each other.
Sawa?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Should I get the nurse?
Here, sit down.
Are you anemic?
Of course not.
I'm fine.
You're really pale.
Have you been dieting?
Aren't you going a bit overboard?
You're on a diet?
But you're, like, so far from being fat.
Girls worry about this stuff too—
Shut up, Tanaka.
Idiot.
Insensitive.
Jackass.
Jackass!
Stupid.
What the hell?
I'm worried about her, too!
Sorry, but I don't feel so good today.
I'm going home.
She's been acting so weird lately.
Yeah.
She hasn't been herself.
We should go after her.
Definitely.
Was that my fault?
No clue.
Please, just give me a chance!
I've always...
Being passionate isn't enough?
But I have thought it through! I'm serious!
Can we at least meet in person?
Please!
She fell in love.
She fell in love?
Yup. No doubt about it.
Are you sure?
Her head's been off in the clouds lately,
and now she's suddenly started a diet.
You probably don't understand
because you lack experience,
but this is a clear case of lovesickness.
That phone call makes me think
the guy must be older.
Could he be married with children?
Konatsu!
My romance radar is never wrong!
Good morning.
Sorry I'm late.
Morning!
Feeling better today?
Of course.
Shall we go?
That was awesome.
Boy, do I love singing!
You guys feel like going
to a café or something?
Sure!
I found this pretty cool place,
but I felt weird going in alone.
I'm going home.
I've got mounted archery practice.
Practice doesn't start until evening...
I know.
But I'm taking Sabure with me today.
I need to get home early
and get everything ready.
Sorry.
This is serious.
Want to head to that café
and come up with a plan?
Can we take a little detour first?
Composition for Dummies
Composition?
My mom left me a piece she wrote,
but it's not done.
So you're going to finish it?
Yeah.
I promised her.
That's great!
I'm feeling inspired!
But first, let's scope
out the newest manga.
Special!
Arts College Corner
Okita-san.
Okita-san, please start.
Right!
Ambulance!
Somebody call an ambulance!
Right away.
Excuse me, someone's been hurt!
So you're not going to
ride professionally?
You can hug me, too!
That's not okay!
Episode 8
Worrying and Racing Ahead
I might as well just quit.
I'm on my way, so wait right there.