Passing Time
Let's see, 135 over 80.
Not bad, Someji.
All right.
That's what I'm talking about.
Your blood pressure has gone down quite a bit.
But I'm going to give you more medicine.
Keep taking it.
Sure thing. Lay it on me!
About three months' worth.
SAKUMA, MD
Internal Medicine
Pediatrics
Idiot, I can't give you that much.
Three weeks' worth.
Come back again next month for more.
Feh. All right, fine. Guess I'll see you then.
But you really have changed, Someji.
A long time ago, you were like,
"I'm not counting on any doctor!"
You used to say, "I'll live how I want to,
and die whenever!"
Well, my wife and daughter
left me with three little ones.
For them, I'm all they have.
Come hell or high water, I have to stay alive
until all three of them are married off.
No way can I let them stand in front of
that gold leaf folding screen alone.
Someji...
But still...
With Momo, it'd help me out
if she got married as soon as possible.
HMMM
The youngest, huh? How old is she again?
SQUEEE
MUD BALLS
PRESCHOOLER
She's still in preschool.
If she got married just after 20, I'd be...
in my mid-90s?!
I'm sorry, Someji.
I can't look after you for that long.
Five more days until the entrance exam.
I'm so nervous!
GROAN
ARGH
AOWWW
MEOWWW
The anxiety is spreading
Got hooked in,
and crying as well
You've done everything you could.
Even your weakest area, proof problems,
you got up to an average score of 80 or higher.
So you'll be fine.
Now we should just
review everything thoroughly.
And if there's anything you're still unsure of,
we'll practice it again with a worksheet.
Oh, that's right.
Takahashi said
he's going to a private school in Kouchi, Shikoku,
thanks to a recommendation, huh?
Huh?
Hina, you didn't...
In Shikoku?
When I saw her surprised face,
which looked like that of a young child,
It felt like I had...
broken a small egg.
I'd heard he was going to the high school
affiliated with Meitei University.
That's what he said before.
So...
Shikoku?
That's so far away.
I thought she already knew about it.
I wish I'd never said anything.
What the hell am I doing?
With the exam just days away...
And she worked so hard for this, too.
I made her feel so terrible.
But she only feels this way because...
it's Takahashi, after all.
Oh, Hina, are you out grocery shopping?
That's wonderful.
Hello, Mrs. Yamada.
TSUKUDANI
It hasn't changed since I was a kid.
My town.
YAMADA STORE
The scenery of the neighborhood...
Drink Milk to Be Healthy
Takahashi Milk
And at the edge of the shopping district...
Hokkaido
Milk Pudding
I smell curry.
I see. Takahashi's family
is having curry for dinner tonight.
I bet he'll be happy about that.
After all, Takahashi loves curry.
Kawamoto, your curry is awesome!
Shikoku, huh?
That's far from here.
And Chiho in Iwate is far from here.
Mom, Grandma...
and Dad, too.
It's always like that.
I take it for granted that tomorrow
will come like it always does...
and that I'll always be able to see everyone.
But then I get a surprise.
Just like this, time after time...
Kiriyama, are you sure you don't mind?
It's fine. I'll stay here until you get back, Akari.
Besides, you helped me so much last year.
I'm sorry. There's suddenly a party
at my aunt's pub.
Momo's going to stay over at Grandpa's place!
I'll come back as soon as I can.
Okay.
What should I do?
The entrance exam is the day after tomorrow
and I'm like this.
You'll be fine. You studied plenty.
Now you just need to rest up
and recuperate as much as possible.
What'll I do if the fever doesn't go down?
What if...
I forget everything I've learned?
You won't forget.
It'll be okay.
In a little while, you can have some porridge,
and then let's take some medicine.
Until then, get some sleep.
Okay.
Well, it's easier to sleep if it's dark,
so I'll close the door.
Okay.
Call me if you need anything.
I'll be right next door.
Okay.
And by the morning of the exam,
her fever had dropped considerably,
to just over 37 degrees.
Hina! Kiriyama has come to pick you up!
What, Rei?
You didn't have to go to the trouble.
I'll be okay!
Well, it's my day off anyway.
From school?
Well, you and the other exam-takers
will be there, so we don't have class today.
Oh, that's right.
Hina, good luck!
See you later!
Be careful of the snow. Don't fail—
EEK
I-I mean, don't trip.
Right! See you later!
During the time I had the fever,
I kept thinking about all the people I had lost...
and the tears wouldn't stop.
I'll hold your bag.
That's okay. I've got it.
The sidewalk's iced up,
so it could be dangerous. Here.
Thanks.
Kiriyama, you're kind of like a mother.
What?
I feel like someone told me that before.
But...
But that's right.
Rei suddenly appeared before me.
Mom, Grandma, please watch over Hina.
CRESCENT MOON
Good luck, Hina.
Hina! Are you all right?!
You fell—
No, um, I mean...
I'm fine! I-I just tripped!
That's right.
Not everyone has gone far away.
Not everyone has disappeared.
I mustn't ever forget that.
Passing Time
Spring Comes
QUIVER
Wow!
SIZZLE
PIPING HOT
Heap of Juicy
Deep-Fried Chicken
Eggplant and Meat Gratin
with Plenty of Cheese
Tuna and Soft Boiled Egg
Macaroni Salad
Garlic Toast
Mini Onigiri
and Sweet Pickled Daikon Radish
Hina, congratulations on passing!
CELEBRATE
I-It's like a mountain of fried meat!
MOUNTAIN
It's juicy!
HUFF
Grabbing it
with her
hands
And the eggplant gratin!
I'm so happy!
Look at all this cheese!
A huge pile of macaroni salad!
With lots of tuna and soft boiled eggs!
HUFF
What do you think?
I made all your favorites, Hina.
HOHOHO
It's really delicious!
All right, everyone, fill up!
For tonight, fried foods are the beverages.
Since we're celebrating, I got carried away
and deep-fried two kilograms of chicken.
T-Two kilos?! As beverages?
Akari, wait...
Hina, congratulations!
Thank you, Momo!
I'm moving up too,
to senior year of preschool!
Really, now...
My little Hina is becoming
a high school student.
Time sure flies.
I'm getting old.
No, Akari, knock it off! No mom-speak.
You're still only 23!
But it's really all thanks to Rei.
Because you helped me with math,
I was able to solve a lot of mysteries!
Like proof problems!
True, your average math score has gone up
30 points since Rei started tutoring you.
Even though you really didn't like math!
Whoa, that's impressive, kid!
I guess professional shogi players
are smart cookies.
Thank you so much. Can I call you Rei too?
Eat some more.
Keep eating!
Uh, th-thank you.
HEAP
The Night Before the Exam
(Flash Back)
EHH!?
RATTLE
Y-You left the two of them alone in the house?
Kiriyama is that boy who's always over, right?
How old is he now?
A second-year?
You left a third-year middle schooler and a
second-year high schooler home alone this late?
Wh-What will you do if something happens?
If they make a mistake, it'll be too late!
You need to go home right now!
Wh-What'll we do
if something happens to Hina?
Calm down, it's all right, Aunt.
There's nothing to worry about.
It's all right?!
How can you be so blasé?
Well...
We're talking about Kiriyama.
The Next Day From There
(Flashback 2)
CRESCENT MOON
Hey, Dad, are you okay with this?
No matter how well-behaved he is
or that he's helping her study,
I can't believe you're letting a young animal
have the run of an all-female house.
What's this, all of a sudden?
What'll we do if something happens to Hina?
It's fine.
After all, we're talking about the kid!
Nothing, nothing's going to happen.
Not only Akari, but Dad too!
They fully trust a second-year high school boy?
Does he really such a safety piece?
I worry about the future.
I mean, I have doubts about boys these days.
Go on, eat. This and this too!
Really, thank you so much!
SYMPATHY
Thank you.
Pet me, pet me, pet me right now!
Rei, I'm looking forward to April.
Me too.
Noguchi and the other members
of the Shogi Science Club are graduating,
so I'm happy that you're coming
to my school.
And for some reason,
Mr. Hayashida is thrilled about it too.
Really?
That's the teacher I met
with the flume noodles, right?
That makes me so happy!
Yes! Here it comes! Yes!
Mr. Hayashida?
I really don't know how to thank you, Rei.
Even though you had
a lot of your own work to do,
you came here several times a week.
Don't worry. I was studying here, too.
Besides, I was incredibly careful.
If I got bad results,
she would've thought it was her fault,
so I played each and every match
as carefully as possible.
It was a different way of facing things
than I've done up to now.
Kid, you have about two more
rank-deciding competitions for this period?
Yes. Right now I have eight wins.
E-Eight wins in a row?
So you’ll go up a class? To B-2?!
Yes. Unless something really bad happens.
You say it so matter-of-factly.
Hina, he's fine!
In that world, the kid is as terrifying as an ogre!
Oh man, this guy is scary!
Ogre? Rei?
Go up a class?
That's a great thing, right?
Um, uh, thank goodness!
Hina, more juice, please.
Juice? What kind?
- Cola!
- You're too young for cola.
I hate to see her cry
or be troubled about something.
Then orange!
Okay, hold on. Hup!
I can't stand the idea of her being in trouble
with me not knowing about it.
So when I heard she wanted to come to a place
that was within my reach,
I wanted to make sure she was accepted.
Until then, I thought that whether
what I did was right or wrong
was something that other people
would decide, as if in a trial.
But that one day...
when she said, "I didn't do anything wrong,"
and while filled with anxiety,
she still kept a firm grip
on the helm of her heart.
I found...
a light within myself that I didn't have before.
That's right.
Without a doubt,
SHOGI HALL
on that day,
she has made...
a part of me.
Rei.
Father.
I won today, so I barely managed
to avoid a demotion.
Looks like I'll be in B-2 next period.
Maybe we can pick up
where we left off last time.
Rei.
That's right, Father.
Spring Comes
Next Episode Preview
Episode 44
Both of you, congratulations
on your graduation.
Wait a second.
When are you leaving?
Shall we go?
Hina! Here!
I'm going to do my best here, too.
My little sister is too cute!
I messed up.
I'm never leaving the house again.
ILLUSTRATION:
CHUUYA KOYAMA
SHOGI HALL
It's almost spring, so I'll be
a high school student, huh?
I'm looking forward to being
in the same school as Rei.