Dear Mom...
The weather in Tokyo is cool,
but hotter than the Tohoku region.
Today is the third day of the
week-long training camp.
We're almost at the turning point.
Go!
It's hot!
No saying "hot!"
It appears that everyone
is nearly exhausted.
It has also been three weeks since
Hinata and Kageyama-kun's argument.
Here.
Thanks.
Thank you!
Even though they're practicing
together, they still aren't talking.
All right!
Service ace!
It's gradual, but it looks like
they're making fewer mistakes.
Fukurodani            Karasuno
And they narrow the point gap
with every set they play.
I am surprised every day by their progress.
I was worried about Tsukishima-kun,
who seemed down,
but apparently that's just
how he usually looks.
Asahi-san, one more! Nice serve!
Nice serve!
Although he must be exhausted,
he seems to be playing well.
However...
Damn it! It was short again!
All right!
Don't worry about it!
I'm sorry!
Hinata and Kageyama-kun's new quick
is not working out very well.
At this rate—
Sorry!
I hope I'm able to see it work at least
once during this training camp.
Thanks.
Haikyu!!
Episode 09: VS "Umbrella"
It's their first long series of away games
and the temperature just keeps rising...
The going's going to get rough
for them right about now.
Center!
Hinata, get the last!
Sorry! It was close to the net!
Damn it!
All right!
Everyone's gotten better.
It was only for a moment, but
even Tsukishima was different.
I'm the only one who hasn't changed.
I don't think I've ever seen
Hinata so agitated before.
Yeah...
Nekoma               Karasuno
Chance ball!
Got it!
It's a chance for a quick...
This time, for sure...
I'll get it!
Nice cover! Nice cover!
Well done, Hinata.
Hey!
You held back, didn't you?!
Held... back?
Me? With volleyball?
Say that again.
Hey, come on.
Excuse me. Can we get a time out?
That wasn't the falling toss.
Huh? It wasn't?
No idea.
You probably need animal instincts to tell.
It wasn't?
I mean... Looking back,
it technically may not have been...
I think what just happened is
that the toss right now wasn't like
the falling tosses he's been getting,
but was more of a parabola.
Which means Kageyama was trying
Kageyama, calm down.
to get Hinata to hit the ball,
no matter what.
Hinata hasn't hit a spike
comfortably for a while now.
That's pretty stressful for a spiker.
Kageyama might have
subconsciously been worried
that Hinata's might not
play as well because of that.
But, Hinata...
Calm down, already!
I'm impressed that you could tell,
but is that something to get angry about?!
Don't you dare fight here!
If anything, he made sure you didn't miss!
Did I subconsciously back down just now?
Don't stop it, Kageyama!
I said, "gather round!"
Are you giving the shrimp
the exact tosses he wants?
Have you even tried to?
What are you doing, Kageyama?
Starting tonight, I'm
not practicing with you.
And I won't be using the new quick
with you during matches.
What?!
I-Is their relationship worsening?!
You're the one that told me
not to stop, aren't you?
There's no point in us
practicing together right now.
Uh, um...
Okay!
Kenma, give me some tosses!
What?
Huh?
Kageyama started training by himself again.
I can't lose!
There's only one thing
I need to do right now!
That's to be able to fight
the blocks in mid-air by myself!
Gymnasium #3
Oh? Tsukki, did you bring a friend today?
Pardon?
What happened to your partner?
Kageyama's practicing on his own again.
I was trying to get Kenma to throw me tosses,
but he ran away after the fifth one.
It's amazing that you got Kenma to
even give you five during practice.
So...
Please let me practice with you!
Lev!
Oh, Hinata.
Lev, I thought you were
practicing receives with Yaku.
He said I was doing well
today, so he let me go.
Really? Sure you didn't run away?
Hey, have you seen Lev?
Maybe he's in the bathroom.
No, of course not!
He said you said it was okay
and went running off.
I didn't say that!
Well, whatever.
Then...
We have the right number of people,
so let's play some three-on-three.
Eh?
Yay!
A match!
Owls            Cats
Um...
Isn't this just a bit unbalanced?
Whoa!
I'm playing with a setter and an ace
from one of the Tokyo powerhouse schools!
And... versus Tsukishima!
It's fine!
Let's do things we can't do during the day!
Woo-hoo!
And then I looked over
and there was a giant rhinoceros
beetle, and I totally freaked out.
Oh, I saw a stag beetle, too.
Lev!
I told you to jump after looking at the toss!
Read blocking!
Oh, right!
Don't try jumping too far
to the sides when blocking!
Wow, he got it...
When you have enough time,
full stop, then jump up!
Right!
Chance ball!
Full stop,
then jump up.
Damn it!
Bring it again!
Um...
If you don't wrap up soon,
the cafeteria will will close,
and you won't get any dinner.
We cannot go into battle on an empty stomach.
Food!
Shrimpy.
We'll continue tomorrow, all right?
Yeah!
Haikyu!!
It's morning!
Let me sleep a little longer...
Cafeteria
Thanks for the food!
How is it that you eat that much,
and none of those nutrients
go toward making you taller?
Mff mmmm mrrrf.
Yeah... I have no idea what you're saying.
Ubugawa               Karasuno
Gora, one more! Nice serve!
It's off! Kageyama, follow through!
Hinata!
Tanaka, free!
All right!
Sorry! I overcompensated!
Ubugawa               Karasuno
Thank you very much!
Time for our penalty!
Right!
Tanaka, you get double.
That's not fair!
Whoa...
You know...
Go!
They've changed a bit.
I'm starving.
Same.
I'm so hungry that I'm
starting to feel nauseous.
Same here.
But seriously...
I wonder how long they're gonna go on.
Next, please!
Damn it!
Kageyama, don't think of
the bottle as a target.
Actually visualize it.
As much as you can, visualize a spiker.
Visualize the spiker...
Oh, by the way, when you're
going one-on-one with a spiker,
don't try to block by centering
yourself to their body.
Center yourself with their
dominant arm instead.
Oh!
Um...
We are technically opponents as
soon as we're in a match, right?
Why are you giving us advice?
I've always been a nice person.
You don't have to look at me like that...
I want to make the Battle at
the Garbage Dump a reality.
All right, let's drink!
It's what our coach wants
more than anything.
Yes!
Hm? Where did Keishin go?
But who knows
how much longer our coach is
going to continue coaching?
He's apparently helping out
with the students' practices.
So because of that,
What? Get him over here, Sensei.
we need you guys to keep winning, too.
Yes, sir.
Well, it's practice for me, as well,
so don't sweat the small things.
Come on. Let's get back to practice!
Owls                   Cats
Akaashi, cover!
Sorry! It's a bit short.
Surround him! Spread out the block!
Damn it! You're still ridiculously
huge for a first-year.
He hit the block on purpose?
One more time!
You better make that toss
a good one, Akaashi!
Yeah! Hey, hey, hey!
Was that... on purpose?!
When you lightly hit the block.
Yup! It's a rebound!
A rebound? That's so cool!
Is it? It is, isn't it?!
You sure are good at flattering
the airhead, Shrimpy.
When you aren't completely ready,
and you feel like your spike's
going to get blocked for sure,
you purposely hit the block with the ball
and try one more time when it bounces back.
Well, of course, there are plenty of times
that fails and they just slam the ball down.
That happens quite often
with you, Bokuto-san.
You're supposed to say,
"That's not true," there, Akaashi!
Spiking doesn't just involve
slamming the ball into the ground.
If you're calm, you'll see how to attack.
Oh, that's not true, Bokuto-san.
You're late, Akaashi!
Owls                   Cats
All right!
Akaashi, nice!
Get the last part, Shrimpy!
Right!
Ah! Hey!
You guys are playing dirty!
This isn't even a wall...
It's more like an umbrella...
There isn't anywhere to aim.
If you're calm,
you'll see how to attack.
He hit up?!
Ow...
Did you... actually aim for that?
That was an amazing wipe!
Oh. Well, I did aim for Lev's fingertips.
What?!
It was sheer luck that it hit.
I can't hit that accurately—
You were covered by three blockers,
each around 190cm tall!
Not to mention that terrible toss!
Well done! I'm moved!
The valiant little warrior who
fights in the face of a two-meter wall!
Talk about over-exaggerating...
Somehow 190 cm turned into two meters.
I shall give you a new special attack.
A special attack?!
Here's the next one!
Slot five.
One more.
I'm sure you must be pretty
tired, Hitoka-chan.
Are you okay?
Yes! I'm sorry!
Today's the last day, so let's do our best.
Right!
Morning, Hinata!
Ah, Yachi-san. Morning!
Man, I'm starving!
Oh, yeah...
You sure are full of energy this morning.
You were up practicing late,
too, weren't you, Hinata?
Yeah, but I just woke up.
How are things shaping up?
I'm practicing something super awesome
right now, so look forward to it!
"Super awesome"...
What the heck, Tsukishima?!
Nothing.
Hey! Someone wake Yamaguchi up!
About the thing I was telling you earlier...
Yes, it's all been taken care of.
It should arrive around noon.
I see...
Seriously?!
Nekoma                  Fukurodani
Hmm...
We can't seem to win against Fukurodani much.
Nice serve!
Senpai! I tabulated all of the stats
so they're easier to read.
Got it!
Thanks!
Right!
Shibayama's pretty great.
Left!
Fukurodani: 50 Wins  14 Losses
Nekoma: 42 Wins  22 Losses
Ubugawa: 36 Wins  28 Losses
Shinzen: 29 Wins  35 Losses
Karasuno: 3 Wins  61 Losses
As we thought, looks like
Fukurodani's at the top right now.
Ubugawa                    Karasuno
Looks like Ubugawa and Karasuno finished.
One round of diving receives!
Right!
They have a strange dignity around them
when they take their penalties.
Including the last away games,
they've done more penalties
than any other team.
I definitely couldn't do it.
Now, diving receives!
Whoa! Karasuno's Shrimpy's gotten
really good at diving receives!
"Shrimpy"? Yaku-san, you're
not much taller than Hinata.
Lev, stand over there!
There was no saving him from that.
Lev!
I told him not to mention Yaku-san's height...
That fool.
Damn it. We basically kept
losing all the way to the end.
You guys need to keep doing
your best and survive.
Daichi-san?
I just happened to hear this,
and I was going to keep it quiet...
Wh-What is it?!
When all of these practice
matches are over...
Apparently, the coaches are going
to treat us to a barbecue.
Bar...
...be...
...cue?!
Akaashi, who do we play next?
Karasuno.
Karasuno, huh?
What?
Well, they're sort of the
hardest to play against.
Who knows what they're gonna do?
Well, it does look like
they're getting pretty tired.
Meaty meat, meat, meaty meat!
Put 'em together, you get meat and meat!
Meaty meat, meat!
Hooray for meat! Energy times a hundred!
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
What the... They're terrifying.
Meat is god! Meat is god!
Sensei...
Did you not tell them about the barbecue?
It just says "meal" on the schedule.
Well, I guess it all worked out in the end.
Hinata, do your best in the match.
Thanks!
I'll be looking forward to
that super awesome thing.
Just watch, you jerk!
But...
I really want to see that new quick soon.
Me, too.
Huh?
Kageyama!
I want to hurry up and hit that falling toss!
He just told you yesterday you
guys won't be doing that quick...
Don't rush.
As long as I'm missing the tosses,
it won't be any practice for you.
What?!
Your will is not needed for that quick.
I'll give you tosses that
won't be stopped by blocks!
He was saying all of that,
but Kageyama-kun was actually
trying to respect Hinata..
I was thinking this yesterday, too,
but you're really creepy
when you worry about others.
I get it, but hurry up
and give me tosses!
I want to hit them!
That's why I'm practicing
so hard, you dumbass!
And Hinata believes that Kageyama-kun
will master that toss.
Ah...
So that's why he got so mad back then!
He completely believes that
Kageyama-kun can do it,
but Kageyama-kun doubted
himself for a second.
How long are you going to make me wait?
Hinata and Tsukishima-kun
call Kageyama-kun the King...
But today,
it looks like the crown is on Hinata's head.
I demand the ultimate toss!
Fukurodani                        Karasuno
Anyway, try to work the new things
you've all practicing into this match.
Right!
Also, I say this every time,
but put pressure on
Fukurodani's #4 when he hits.
Right.
Yeah!
In the end, this training camp
was filled with penalties,
but you guys should definitely feel different now
than you did in the first away games.
Let's get an awesome win here
and go eat some delicious meat!
Yeah!
Man, meat is the best.
And nothing goes better
with meat than white rice.
I like eating them together, too!
Throw in a salad, and it's perfect.
All right! Let's win this match
and eat some delicious food!
Yeah!
Next time on Haikyu!!: "Cog."
Episode 10: "Cog"