Kanna...
...likes you.
Tanigawa likes me?
Yeah.
Did Tanigawa ask you to tell me that?
Nope.
I decided to tell you.
Tanigawa-san likes Kaito-kun...
What is Kaito-kun going to do?
But Tanigawa-san didn't
tell him herself...
I'll just have to act
like nothing happened.
Why did Ishigaki-kun tell Kaito-kun?
Ah, I'm exhausted.
Oh, I didn't see you there.
You're building that stuff again?
And you're fighting
with Satoshi-san again?
Nope.
I was supposed to go on a trip
with some friends from high school,
but everyone ended up being busy.
I see.
After I took the time to come back here...
You're not very cheery.
Did you have a fight with
Kanna-chan or something?
Why even mention Kanna?
What are you doing?!
I'll give you these.
Go have fun with everyone.
Okinawa.
What?! Okinawa?
The day after tomorrow?
For free?
Of course I'll go!
If I'm going with everyone,
I think my mom and dad will let me go!
I'll contact Remon-senpai.
You let Mio and Kai know.
Huh?
W-Well, okay.
This is your chance.
S-Stop that!
I told you I'm not going to
think about that right now!
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Yes, Kirishima residence.
Huh?
T-Tanigawa?
Wh-Why are you calling so late?
Tanigawa-san's calling?
A trip?!
To Okinawa?!
Tanigawa
Oh, I see.
So that's what you meant.
Got it.
I'll do that. Later.
Were you just talking to Tanigawa-san?
Y-Yeah, I was invited on a trip.
Are you going?
I was thinking I would.
He's just going to go with her?!
Senpai, do you have
any plans or anything?
Huh?
We'll all be going and shooting
the movie while we're there.
Oh, I see.
We'll be going to Okinawa.
Really?
Okinawa?
Th-This is Okinawa?!
Okinawa Edition!
The Sea and Beach Await You!
A place like this is being liburai'ed?
Liburai'ed?
I don't really get it,
but I guess you like it?
A lot!
So you'll go?
I'm totally going!
So when are we going?
I can't really put it into words,
Tomorrow? Right now? I'm so happy!
but I was really relieved
when all of that happened.
We could all just enjoy the trip together,
without having to think about
anything too difficult.
This Summer's Top 5 Picks!
That's what I was thinking.
So we're here.
In Okinawa.
Yeah, we're here.
I'm feelin' it.
Yeah, me too.
Feeling what?
Nothing really.
Wh-What?
You look like you're trying hard.
Th-That's not it!
The store clerk told me it's
popular right now, so that's why.
Is that what happened?
Mio!
Sorry! I was joking!
It was a joke!
It's fine. It looks good on you.
Really?
Yeah.
Huh?
Thank you.
No, it's fine.
Mio, what swimsuit did you pick out?
N-Nothing really that special.
But my skin is sensitive, so
I have to wear a sweatshirt...
When you've got such a great body, too.
D-Don't stare!
Where are the Senpais?
Sorry about that.
Sorry.
It took some time to get changed.
Hey there.
Glad you came, huh?
Yeah.
Ishigaki-kun, how's my swimsuit?
I'm sure there's an age range out
there that would appreciate it.
Am I ready to take on the world?
Senpai, the world is a large
place, and extremely deep.
I wonder if I look too old.
S-Sorry.
My sister only had that
swimsuit available...
There have been several great individuals
within that genre to make that challenge.
No, I'm glad you lent it to me.
This is getting old, so that's enough.
I really prepared for this...
Keep fighting.
That seems kind of needlessly huge.
We're not done yet.
Not done yet?
Kaito-kun, how about we bury you, too?
Huh?
I'll pass.
Really? It'd be fun!
Isn't Kirishima-kun acting kind of weird?
Maybe.
So what did you mean by "not done yet"?
The tide will come in soon,
and then it'll look like it's
floating, just like the real one.
Let me out right now!
Kai, help me!
Anyway, now that we've
enjoyed the Okinawan ocean,
we should start filming.
What?
On our first day here?
I rustled up some ideas.
In order to escape from her pursuers,
the heroine temporarily
hides herself in Okinawa.
Did you really rustle that up?
I thought about it so much,
I stayed up all night.
You sure don't look it.
Everyone's kind of watching us...
That's because you're so beautiful.
No, uh...
Are you sure we don't have to
get permission to film here?
Tanigawa-san, the ocean
belongs to no one.
Don't blame me for what happens.
Excuse me, what are you guys doing?
Oh, we're just putting together
our own independent film.
Cool!
Kaori, don't bug them.
I was just asking.
Huh? Are you... Umi-chan?
Why do you know my nickname
from when I was a kid?
I knew it was you!
It's me! Me!
Kaori!
Kaori Kinoshita!
Kinoshita...
Huh?! Kinoshita?!
Really?!
What's going on?
Wow!
It's been a long time!
How many years has it been?
I knew it was you!
You haven't changed at all!
That frizzy hair and those
large glasses of yours.
Kinoshita...
You've changed quite a bit.
Really?
Well, I've become a lot more feminine
since I entered high school!
But I never thought I'd see you here.
Y-Yeah.
Kirishima-kun, who is this?
Oh, she's my elementary school...
His fiancée!
Fian...
...cée?
That's quite the interesting
relationship there.
No!
When I was a kid, it was common for guys
and girls to pretend they were couples.
She sat next to me, so everyone in
our class made us out to be that way.
What? That's not nice.
I really believed it.
Huh?!
I gave you that letter during
graduation, didn't I?
You did?
It's incredible that you've run
into your first love again!
I know, right?
And in Okinawa, too!
Totally a work of fate.
I, uh...
Huh?
I...
Way to go, Kai-sensei.
S-So, what's your name?!
Tetsuro Ishigaki...
Ishigaki-san...
Do you like, have a
girlfriend or anything?
No, I don't...
Oh, really?
My name is Arisawa Chiharu.
Could you scoot back a little?
Why?
Everyone's got great
looks on their faces.
Episode 6
Senpai has a rival.
Wow...
This is a pretty nice room.
The food was really good, too.
That was the first time I've had barbecue.
Oh, really?
I'm really glad we could...
...come to Okinawa.
Right, Kaito-kun?
Y-Yeah.
You even had a meeting of destiny with
your classmate from elementary school.
She's quite energetic and
cute, don't you think?
I mean, being able to run
into your first love,
who you promised to get married to.
Pretty wonderful, right?
She wasn't really my first love, you know?
She and I...
Senpai.
They sounded really close.
Almost like all that time
never passed at all.
Nothing really happened
with Kinoshita at all.
Actually, why are you guys
questioning me so much?
That's because Nanami-san
told Takatsuki-senpai...
...to watch after you.
We can't have you running
off with some girl...
...you met on your vacation here!
I won't do that!
I'm not sure about that.
Please just listen to what I have to say!
So you were doing something
you have to make excuses for.
No! I'm trying to tell you what's going on.
So something did happen!
Sucks for Kai.
No! Calm down!
What about you, Tetsuro-kun?
About me?
That Arisawa-san girl was pretty cute.
She had a pretty nice body, too.
You traded cell phone
email addresses, too.
I don't turn down requests
from cute girls.
Really?
Wh—
Why?!
I'll introduce you.
She'll be appearing in our movie.
Her name is Kaori Kinoshita-san.
Nice to meet you all.
Remon.
What's going on?
I wanted a guest star for the
Okinawa portion of the film.
She agreed to help out
quickly, which was nice.
Somehow this feels very contrived...
She fit what I was thinking perfectly.
That's exactly what I mean!
What are you doing, Umi-chan?
Besides, do you even know
what "contrived" really means?
You being punished for something?
No, I, uh...
What are you talking about?
So which of them is your girlfriend?
Actually, you're just trying
to change the subject!
It's not like that.
Oh, really?
Then there shouldn't be an issue
with me being in the movie.
Umi-chan, you're the director, right?
What are you filming?
We're in Okinawa, so maybe
everyone'll be in swimsuits?
Hm, yeah...
No! I wasn't saying anything!
Tetsuro-san, you were born on the 24th?!
Your guardian tree is the apple tree,
your guardian animal is the swan,
and your guardian spirit is Étaín!
You have a calm and cool demeanor,
and seem older than you actually are,
but in reality you're actually
quite a delicate person.
That makes your ideal girl...
...someone really energetic
who'll pull you around.
That sounds just like me and—
Those girls were something.
Yeah.
But Kinoshita wasn't like that before.
And now she'll be in the movie...
Tomorrow's shoot will be fun.
You're making fun of me!
Good night!
Hey!
God...
No, it's nothing.
I was sort of thrown for a loop.
Stupid Kaito-kun.
He's not straightforward at all.
Being straightforward...
That means...
I...
Wh-What am I thinking?!
Thinking about this
won't get me anywhere.
I mean...
I...
I?
Remon!
When did you—
I thought I smelt something good.
Could I have some, too?
S-Sure.
Wait just a second.
Do you take sugar?
Without's fine.
But add a lot of milk.
Hey, Ichika.
Hm?
Well, you saw how those
girls were acting,
but why don't you try being a
little more forthright yourself?
Huh?
When in Rome, do as the Romans do.
Wh-What are you...
Oh?
I'm talking about handling
things the Okinawan way.
This isn't going to work either.
You still can't choose?
These just aren't doing
it for me, I guess.
You're pretty cute, Kanna.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?! He—
Good night!
You're going to sleep like that?
Y-You know if I don't go to bed
like this, I can't fall sleep.
G-Give him back!
Sure!
That is, if you let me capture
you without a fight.
Wh-Who are you?
You let people on this undeveloped
planet know your true identity!
Therefore I shall arrest you
according to Federation law.
Are you a Galaxy Police agent?!
And what if I am?
Cut.
Man, acting is pretty hard.
Come on, don't get so close.
You don't have to get so embarrassed!
It's hot.
So if it wasn't hot, you
wouldn't mind me clinging?
That's not what I meant!
You're getting all red again.
I guess you can't help it.
Right.
R-Remon, about how much
longer are we going to film?
Let's see...
I'd like to do five more scenes.
I see...
Mio?
Film making is pretty
interesting, Tetsuro-san!
Y-You think so?
I'm totally interested in it now.
Remon-senpai!
I left a prop in the cottage.
you think I could go grab it?
Hurry up.
Roger that.
Tetsuro-san!
That's weird.
I thought he'd be totally
in love with her by now.
That's because he's actually delicate.
Delicate?
Tetsuro is?
You're just too close to
him to realize, Kanna.
You think so?
Huh?
Where's Kaito-kun and Kinoshita-san?
Ah!
The smaller one isn't here, either.
Huh?
Th-They couldn't have...
Couldn't have?
Couldn't have!
They couldn't have!
So...
Why did you take me all the
way out here, Kinoshita?
You already know, right?
I wanted to be alone with you.
That okay?
Is something wrong?
I'm not really sure, but you're acting
a lot more hyper than usual.
It's because I'm so happy to see you.
There you go again.
Huh?
When you were a kid,
and something bad happened
or you felt uncomfortable,
you put your finger on your lip.
Something's wrong, isn't it?
That's why you're forcing
yourself to be with me.
You can talk to me about it, if you wan—
And what if I'm serious?
Huh?
What if I'm serious?
What?
Let's see...
Where did I leave that?
I didn't leave anything here,
but where did I leave it?
I guess I'll just waste some time here.
Oh, Kai?
What's up? You here for the same rea—
Did you find what you were looking for?
Arisawa-san, why are you...?
I think you already know!
What if I really still like
you after all this time?
But it's been so long...
Time has nothing to do with it.
Last night, you said there
wasn't anyone you like, right?
I...
I said I wasn't dating anyone.
Huh?
I do like someone.
I really like them, so...
Huh?
Wai—
What's gotten into you, Arisawa-san?
I'm quite selfish, you see.
I see...
I can't hold myself back.
And I'm aggressive, too.
W-Wait.
Y-You're surprisingly... strong...
You shouldn't embarrass a girl.
Wa—
No!
Where did they go?
Caught in the moment,
I just came along, but...
What am I going to do after I find him?
Kaito-kun...
Mi...o?!
Umi-chan...
Kino...shita.
Sen...pai?
No one's...
...coming back.
Episode 7
Senpai's feelings.
Tell me, Remon!
Tell me how Kaito-kun feels!
I'm sure he's thinking about doing it.
Wow! As big as a horse!