Major! Major!
I'm... okay.
Major!
Save yourself. Leave me here.
You have to run.
I cannot do that!
I will take you with me!
Leave me here.
I will not leave you behind!
I will stay here and fight!
I will only go if I take you with me.
Violet!
I will not let you die!
Stop.
Just stop!
You have to live.
Violet.
Be free.
From the bottom of my heart.
I love you.
Love?
What is love?
What is...
love?
I don't understand!
Major!
I thought I'd find you here.
It was a brutal battle.
After your team sent up the signal flare,
the rest of our forces attacked,
and sensing their defeat,
the Gardarik Army bombarded
their own headquarters before retreating.
You were found
at the bottom of those stairs.
Most likely, he pushed you out of the way
to protect you from the blast.
Everyone told me the major was fine
when I was in the hospital.
We couldn't tell you.
You were more concerned about him
than you were about yourself.
Let's go.
Violet.
Where...
would I go?
I can only go where the major is.
We're going back to the office.
You're our Auto Memory Doll.
Then I'll stay here, too,
until you decide to come back with me.
After all, he did ask me
to look after you.
Right before the battle began,
he came to me and told me...
Take care of Violet
if something happens to me.
Take her to the Evergarden House
in Leiden once the war ends.
Gilbert?
I'm counting on you.
He never saw you as a war tool.
He thought of you as a normal girl
and was concerned about your future.
Hey. I'm sorry I pulled you away.
You okay?
You're okay, right?
I wasn't sure what would happen when you
were first discharged from the hospital,
but you've learned
how to be an Auto Memory Doll.
You've come so far.
You should be able to live your life
without his orders.
Will I never receive any orders
from you again, major?
You've done nothing wrong.
We can talk about this later.
The road has been blocked.
-Lieutenant colonel!
-I'm not...
-Never mind. At ease.
-Yes, sir!
Did something happen?
The city of Caisseclaire was attacked
by an anti-peace faction from Gardarik.
I've heard that anti-peace sentiments
have been growing.
What's the status?
They've been defeated, but we must
stay alert for any remaining insurgents.
Let's take a different route then.
Copy that.
Violet's back, right?
Seems so, but...
She'll come back to work, too, won't she?
Can you go check on her?
-Why don't you go?
-She needs someone like you right now.
What's that supposed to mean?
I've got better things to do.
Benedict.
Could you look around District 12 for me?
I'll try heading over to District 14.
Did something happen?
One of our new deliverymen
threw away the letters
he couldn't get around to delivering.
What?
We're going to go look for them.
Don't worry.
We have a good idea where they might be.
Violet, you're in here, aren't you?
I just want to see how you're doing.
I am terribly sorry...
for any worry I've caused.
How are you feeling?
Are you eating?
I'll leave your food out here.
Think you'll come out tomorrow?
We can't wait to see you,
and there's a lot of requests for you.
I...
It's just as President Hodgins said.
I am burning.
For the things I've done.
You'll understand one day.
And then you'll realize for the first time
that you have many burns.
Why did you say that to her?
She didn't have a choice,
considering her background.
It doesn't matter what her background was,
or what the details or reasons may be.
You can't erase the past.
-Then just forget and start over...
-It can't be forgotten either.
She's not the only one who's on fire.
You and me both.
We have invisible scars
left behind by the flames.
Then...
Then what should she do?
She'll have to decide on her own.
After she looks at her burning body
and accepts it.
But...
She's lost the major,
and everything else she had.
It'll be okay.
She hasn't lost him.
Or anything else.
Cattleya hasn't come back either.
I'll go check on her tomorrow.
It might be better
to give her some space for now.
But...
I want to know what "I love you" means.
I became a Doll because I wanted to know
what the major meant by "I love you."
Is giving her space
all we really need to do?
What?
What if she never comes back
to being a Doll?
I'd like to hire a scribe.
Major.
What's the matter?
Violet?
Major.
Major!
You're alive!
That outfit.
I am currently working
as an Auto Memory Doll.
You are?
Yes. I scribe letters.
Letters, you say?
With the very hands
that took the lives of so many?
Major?
You write letters to connect people?
Major.
Major!
What...
should I do?
Please.
Please give me an order.
I've got a letter for you,
Violet Evergarden.
It's addressed to you.
Erica and Iris asked me to deliver it.
Well, I've done my part.
You are still delivering at this hour?
Yes. We found the letters
that had been discarded.
Where's Benedict?
He sprained his ankle.
It's because of those shoes he wears.
What is wrong with you?
Ow, ow, ow!
Well, I'm heading down Craft Street.
Could I get you to cover one street back?
After all, each one of them
contains someone's precious feelings.
Every letter deserves to be delivered.
Hey, a letter!
Mom! It's from Dad!
Have you finished your deliveries?
Thanks for the help.
That's great!
They all made it home.
"How are you doing, Violet?
I thought about coming to see you,
but after talking with Iris,
we decided to write you a letter instead.
It might be strange for a Doll
to write to another Doll,
but we wanted you to know
that we are worried about you.
And that we are also...
waiting for you."
You might not feel like coming back
to work right now,
so, take all the time you need.
But if something happens,
please don't hesitate to call us.
Both Iris and I have faith
that you will return.
Also, someone named Spencer
came asking to scribe a letter for him.
He wanted to send a thank you and
an apology letter to his younger sister.
He specifically asked for you...
and insisted on
having you write the letter.
Is this to your satisfaction?
Yes.
It's a little embarrassing sending
a letter to your own little sister,
but I found a new job thanks to her.
She helped me want to start over again.
Sorry for all this.
Making you come all the way here.
I heard that you were taking
some time off work.
My coworkers informed me
of your request...
through a letter.
It was the very first letter
I'd ever received.
It helped me realize just how special
it is to receive a letter.
I think Luculia will be very pleased.
Thank you.
A person matching their name.
A name that is suitable.
Violet?
It is just as you said.
I had many burns all over my body.
Is it okay?
Do I...
Do I have a right
to be an Auto Memory Doll?
Do I...
Do I have a right to live?
You can't erase the past.
But...
But all your Auto Memory Doll
accomplishments...
shall never be forgotten either,
Violet Evergarden.