Why?
How?
What the hell is this?
Since I become a spirit, all I can do is watch...
I can't do anything...
This is bullshit.
This is bullshit!
You humans sure are selfish, huh?
You didn't care when seven
billion people died.
Yet one person dies,
and you're crying and screaming.
That doesn't mean a damn thing!
It doesn't, huh?
You're quite cold.
You're the cold one!
Damn it...
Damn it!
You just said you couldn't do anything,
but maybe you just didn't do anything.
What's your point?
What's the point in telling me that now?
Now?
Wait... I just have to go back in time!
True, with your current spirit power level,
you could land anywhere you want
to in the space-time valley.
But there's something you need.
Something I need?
A strong desire to save someone.
Without that, you'll bounce off
the curved surface of space-time.
I do—
Once you bounce off, that's it.
You'll never be able to come
back to this world again.
Are you prepared for that?
Of course I am!
Okay. Make a strong wish, then.
Towards your own soul.
Ito, I'll protect you.
I'll save you!
I promise.
Ito...
Ito!
#05
Ito Dies
Punch Line
Am I back?
From: frontier-headman@xxx.xx.jp
To: Hikiotani Ito
December 29 7:24 P.M.
There's been a second victim.
Raishi Moena.
If you don't want to lose any
more classmates, come to
Ishinogari Shrine at ten tonight.
It's all my fault.
It's my fault that Meiko and Moena...
You know them?
In any case, now you know what happened.
Ito went to the shrine according
to the email's demands, and...
The person who sent the email killed her.
But why?
Whatever the reason, you can't
let Ito go to the shrine.
That's all you need to worry about right now.
Thirty minutes left until it's time...
Mikatan, do you have a minute?
There's something I want to ask you.
Of course! Rabura!
I'm going home now.
You can stay longer.
The air's getting stale here.
Bleah!
All right.
Why don't you two make up already?
So, what did you want to ask?
Oh, yeah, um... Have you seen the
protective charm that was in my room?
There!
What was that?!
It couldn't be... a poltergeist?!
What the heck?!
Now!
Again?!
Narugino, listen to me!
Ito's life is in danger!
That Burabura chick seriously pisses me off.
Meika.
Ito?
Can you keep him for a while?
Huh?
Raishi Moena (17)
Chouka Rina (17)
Namado Suisei (17)
Shujo Manoto (17)
Koto Monami (17)
You're saying all the people whose
names are in this video were killed?
Yes.
All right.
Let's hurry to Ito-chan's place!
My boobs... My boobs...
Where are you going?
Does it matter?
Move.
I won't.
I saw the video.
I know about the emails, too.
Wait!
Stay away!
Calm down, Ito-chan!
I have to go, no matter what,
because it's all my fault.
It's my fault those two people were...
Ito-chan!
Let go.
Let go of me!
No.
I never will!
If you go to the shrine, you'll...
Leave me alone!
It's not your problem!
Yes, it is!
Because, Ito-chan, you're... You're...
my precious friend!
Mikatan...
Umbeijini nyopurasara...
I'm going to put a spell on you.
What's that song?
It's a magic song to cheer you up.
Ishigata-san taught it to me.
Ishigata-san?
Yeah.
See...
He was a researcher at this
place called Yuba Labs.
I was—I mean, we were born
and raised at that lab.
Yuba Labs?
They used to do research
on genetics and stuff.
There were two other kids at the lab.
A boy and a girl.
We were together from birth.
They both helped me out so much.
No, let me go!
Shut up!
Settle down!
Come!
No! Let me go!
Chiyoko!
Pine! Guri-chan!
Let go of Chiyoko!
Sorry, I can't do that.
You kids have the ability to Yubafy,
yet you never use it.
Why?
The only way I can find out is to take a look.
I have to cut open your heads
and look inside your brains.
Like hell you will!
Pine!
Are you okay?!
Damn! I damaged my precious test subject!
Oh, well.
I'll be cutting you up eventually anyway.
I won't let you have Chiyoko.
Never.
Never...
Never!
That's it!
That's the power!
Did you like that boy?
Huh?! Wh-Where did that come from?
Bingo.
That's not it!
What about you, Ito-chan?
Huh?
Do you have any crushes, or anything?
It's not really a crush,
but there is someone I like as a person.
Who?
A teacher at school.
He's my homeroom teacher,
but he's like a friend.
One time, he gave me a ride home.
He was worried it'd be dangerous,
since it was getting late.
Some kids in my class saw us.
The next day, when I went to school,
no one would talk to me anymore.
Why?
There was a girl who liked that teacher.
She was like the leader of the school.
She targeted me.
That's when it started.
Every day was hell.
Die
Math
I don't know how many times
I bought new pairs of indoor shoes.
My textbooks and notebooks
were rendered unreadable.
I had to keep throwing them out.
On days when we had P.E., I stayed
in my track suit until after school,
because my skirt would get stolen.
My underwear went missing one
time when we had swimming.
That much I could bear, though.
Ew, there's gum in your hair, Ito.
You put it there, didn't you, Moena?
Of course not.
Oh, well. Let's cut it out for her.
No!
Good going, Meiko.
Nice cut!
Maybe I cut too much?
That's why I stopped going to school.
Even then, my teacher was nice to me.
Have you ever talked to him about it?
No.
I didn't want to give him trouble.
That's the reason for the video.
The video?
You said you saw it, right?
I'm the one who made it.
The names on it are the names
of the kids who bullied me.
I just wanted to scare them
a little, so I put it online.
But your name was in the video, too.
It wasn't on there when I made it.
So...
Someone edited it afterwards...
It was probably...
whoever it was that killed Meiko and Moena.
Why didn't you say somethi—
How could I have admitted
that I was being bullied at school?
Why not?
Isn't it obvious? Because I'd look stupid!
I'd look pathetic.
I'm not a loner. I'm not shy.
I could make new friends easily if I wanted to.
That's what I wanted them to think.
I wanted to show them that.
Even if I knew no one really thought that of me.
The truth is, ever since I saw that video,
I've been really scared.
But whenever I saw everyone smiling,
it started to feel like none of it was real.
Ito-chan, it's okay.
It's okay.
I'm on the side of justice.
I'm on your side.
No matter what happens,
I promise...
I promise I'll protect you.
Looks like history's changed.
Yeah.
Aren't you happy?
There's too much to think about.
I don't know anything about who did it.
And...
What's this?
Looks like you two are getting along well.
Th-That's not it!
He just keeps clinging to me!
Hey! Shoo, shoo! Get off me!
You've been with him since
last night, haven't you?
Why did you take care of him for me?
Well, y'know, he saved me one time.
Yeah?
So, what are you doing here?
There was some noise in the satellite link,
so I came to check it out.
And you?
Oh, um... It doesn't matter now.
Actually, I came to take Muhi, but...
Take him, damn it!
One more day until New Year's Eve.
Mikatan, what are you doing?
Oh, nothing.
Those are...
Meika?
What was that?
Meika!
What happened?
Muhi?
Where's Muhi?
Sorry... That man...
What man?
Turtle Man.
The one who was here before.
Him?
Muhi!
Wait, Ito!
There's still more!
More?
He said...
Tell Ito that this is punishment
for not having come last night.
It was Turtle Man that
called Ito out last night.
Ito-chan!
Turtle Man is the one who
killed Ito's classmates.
If Ito runs into him...
Ito!
Not here.
Not here!
Isn't Turtle Man here?
He might have run far off by now.
How can you be so nonchalant?!
What if right now—
Why don't you try luring him out, then?
Email!
I see.
You're going to send a reply
to Ito's email from yesterday.
Sender: Hikiotani Ito
Subject: No Title
"Please come to the Korai House rooftop.
There's no one here right now."
Okay, send!
Awesome Spirit
No!
It's gone!
The jar of cinnamon?
Why?
There was another one!
Were you thinking of using Rabura's body
to fight against Turtle Man or something?
I have another plan!
I do!
All right, almost done with repairs.
What could I use to beat Turtle Man?
That's it! A stun gun!
Then how about these?
I've seen these before.
They're...
Wow, you're a genius, Meika!
I still have more amazing stuff.
Like this.
Face Maker!
It's basically a disguise mask.
Awesome!
Right?
You can look like anyone,
if you have 3D data of their head.
It's totally Rabura.
Let's change my voice, too.
Using this tiny voice changer, Voice Maker...
Hi, I'm Ito-chan, and I love BL.
Chiranosuke, I have a plan!
Cancel New Message Send
To: Daihatsu Meika, Chichibu Rabura
Sender: Hikiotani Ito
Subject: No Title
"To: Meika, Rabura."
"Turtle Man is headed to
the Korai House rooftop!
Please! Do what you can
together to defeat him!"
When you say you have a plan, you really mean...
I wonder if it'll work.
Don't worry, those two can pull it off.
Muhi, where are you?
Muhi!
Ito-chan!
Here he comes, just like the email said.
I guess we'll have to do it.
Let's call a cease fire for now.
Cease fire?
We were in the middle of a fight, remember?
Oh, right.
Anyway, for now...
I know.
Come on, let's begin the operation.
Now, bring it on, Turtle Man.
If I recall, she changes her appearance
to draw the enemy's attention,
Rabura holds his arms from behind,
and they finish him with the stun gun.
Was that it?
Yeah.
It sounds like it'll work!
He's here!
What is that?
Hey, you.
You're not Ito, are you?
Wh-What are you talking about?
I'm Ito-chan, and I love BL.
Moe moe...
Totally moe...
Cut the crap.
Oh, no!
I knew it.
This isn't a game.
Stop!
Shoot me, if you're going to shoot.
Rabura!
You idiot!
Just run—
Do you think this is a toy?
What?
I... I was just
about to cut you off like a badass.
I didn't think you'd shoot first!
Th-This can't be happening.
I told you,
this isn't a game.
I said some awful things to Meika.
I can't have her dying on me now.
Fine, you can go first—
No you don't!
No!
Losing neither to rain,
nor to the wind,
nor to snow, nor to the heat of summer,
with a strong body...
Are you all right?! Hang in there!
Without desire, never losing temper,
and always smiling quietly.