Kiss Him, Not Me
The Beach! Bathing Suits!
Time to Get Serious!
It's gorgeous!
It's summer vacation.
We were all invited to
Shima-chan's holiday home.
It's a bit far from the beach,
but that's what makes it so quiet.
Amazing! It's so pretty!
It's really okay for me to have a room
with such a great view all to myself?
Yup. We've got plenty of rooms left over.
Thank you, Shima-chan!
How about we get ready
and head for the beach?
Yeah, I can't wait!
So...
How come we're all in the same room?!
Now, now.
It was nice of her to give
us a room. Don't complain.
This is summer vacation,
not some holy pilgrimage.
It's a purer trip,
and I get to spend my nights under
the same roof as the girl I like.
This is my big chance to
get even closer to her
after closing the gap during
our "Puri Puri Moon" event!
Or so it should be! But I can't steal
that chance with you guys around!
Well, I think that's exactly why
we're all in the same room.
Damn it!
Don't say that, silly.
Why not?
Scrawny
Gloom
This isn't working.
I'm pasty and scrawny,
and honestly, I'm not even the outdoors type.
I'm not a fan of the ocean.
I'd rather stay home in the summer!
Maybe I shouldn't have come.
Shinomiya-kun?
Are you okay? You've been in there
a while. Do you have a stomachache?
I-I'm okay, no need to worry.
Really? Well, that's good to hear.
Hey, you taking a dump?
Don't hog the toilet!
I am not!
You drop a huge load?
As I said, that wasn't it!
Okay, okay. Let's get going.
What is this, kindergarten?
It's the beach!
Mu
Shi
Nana
Iga
S-So cute.
Beach! Summer! Thank you!
Guys!
Wanna try bodyboarding?
You can rent boards there.
Bodyboarding?
Yeah, I like surfing.
Same here, it's been a while.
It's over there.
Should we bet on who's best?
I-I've never done it before.
Same here.
Looks like we're both
beginners. Let's work together!
Badump
I've never done it, either.
I take it all back.
I'm happy I came!
Th-Then, since we're both beginners—
Serinuma-senpai!
Whoa! She's so cool!
That's so like Shima-chan!
Y-Yeah, you're right.
Damn her and her unfair advantages!
W-Well, I'm sure we'll get
the hang of it in no time.
You th-think so?
We've just got to keep
the right posture, and...
Shinomiya-kun!
Th-That was so uncool!
Are you oka—
Serinuma-senpai!
Did you swallow any water?
I'm fine. Thanks.
Shinomiya-kun, there's
seaweed on your head.
You, too.
We match!
What's this? Everything's going really well!
Maybe it was a good thing
that I couldn't do it.
Serinuma-senpai, let's practice tog—
Look at them!
They're so hot!
Amazing! You guys look like pros!
You're pretty good.
D-Damn!
This is no time for seaweed!
Nanashima-senpai, lend me your board.
H-Hey!
I can do this, too.
Don't tell me he's gonna try and surf?
Hey! You can't do it without practice!
I'm going to show her how cool I can be.
Now!
Clara stood up!
Amazing, Shinomiya-kun!
You're riding the wave!
I did it!
Look at me, Serinuma-senpai!
I did it! I really did it!
Ni
Nana
Wha—
Iga
Mu
Y-You ass!
Get off her!
Shinomiya?!
What's wrong? Was there an incident?
Beach House
Yakisoba with Sauce
Draft Beer
Soft Drinks
I am terribly sorry about what happened.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Cut the crap.
You're practically a groper.
It wasn't on purpose,
so just forget about it.
It's okay. Please don't grovel anymore.
Cheer up and have some lunch.
Mutsumi-san, you're too nice!
If Serinuma-san's forgiven him,
then nothing needs to be said.
Eat up, Shinomiya-kun.
And then we can all play
beach volleyball together.
Okay?
S-Senpai.
Sob Sob
She's an angel!
Hmm, 55.
What? That's way too high.
I'd give her a 40.
Hey, Miss 40, another beer!
What's with them? Talk about no class.
Senpai, how about we go and borrow a ball?
We can walk off the food.
But Shinomiya-kun's not done eating yet.
Oh, don't worry about him.
We'll stay behind.
Okay.
We'll go on ahead, then.
Whoa! Look at those 100s!
100s!
They're both smoking!
Check out the ass on that
girl with the hoodie.
Gimme a piece of that!
Hey!
Wh-What's your problem?!
Wanna fight?!
Now, now.
Who the hell are you?!
Um, guys?
I really couldn't care less what
you guys have to talk about,
but you better not make
a pass at those girls.
We'll kill you.
You're on!
Are we clear?
Yes.
Guys, over here!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
All right, let's split into teams.
Let's!
Thanks.
Well, I don't think they'll
pull anything funny now.
Actually, that's the first time I've
ever seen you angry, Mutsumi-san.
I hate that kind of thing.
Even Nishina?
Is that why she went on ahead
with Serinuma-senpai?
That means I'm the only
one who didn't get it.
Come on, everyone. Hurry it up!
Was I really trying...
to compete with these guys?
How, exactly?
What can I do against them?
I can't wait!
Barbecue! Barbecue! Barbecue!
Are you really happy with this?
I could have had the head cook
take care of all this prep work.
A barbecue's better when we
do all the work ourselves.
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing. I think I'm just a little tired.
No, I've got to get a hold of myself.
I'm going to become a reliable
guy in my own way.
A guy that can protect Serinuma-senpai.
Right. A guy that can protect her.
W-Watch out!
Hey, hey, hey!
Are you for real?
No way...
What are you doing? Jeez.
I... I...
Come on, man.
We'll have to start over?
I think so.
I just wanted...
I... I'm going home.
Mu
Nana
Iga
Ka
Ni
Huh?
Hey. Wait!
I shouldn't have come after all.
I'm not the outdoors type.
I'm not a fan of the ocean.
I'd rather stay home in the summer,
and I'd have been better off if I had.
Ouch...
If I had just done that,
I wouldn't have to feel this miserable.
Kiss Him, Not Me
Wh-What do we do?!
What did he say again?
He was going home, or something?
Then, why did he run that way?
Isn't that just a forest, though?
I kind of had a hunch...
He's actually...
Pretty dumb.
We've gotta go after him!
Huh? He'll come back on his own eventually.
But, it could be dangerous
if he stays out until it's dark.
There's no one at the top of this mountain.
Shinomiya hates the dark,
though! I feel sorry for him!
She feels sorry for him?
I'll go get him!
Hey, wait!
It'll be dangerous for her alone.
Jeez!
Feels sorry for him, indeed...
Shinomiya-kun!
Hey!
We have to hurry up and find him soon!
Come on, hurry and move already.
The boards are loose there.
Yeah.
Did he really cross this?!
There's only one path, so he must have.
Shinomiya-kun.
Let's hurry!
No! I can't move!
Nana, get up! You're in the way!
You can't just stand there.
You've gotta move!
No!
It's really shaking.
I made it.
Are you all okay?
Huh?
You guys!
W-We're fine.
The drop was shorter than we thought.
Thank God!
The bridge felt like a bigger deal...
Really, thank goodness!
But this might be too high to climb.
There's a path over there.
A detour?
Probably.
It should lead to where there
used to be an old hotel.
Ka
Us
Let's regroup there, then!
See you later!
Serinuma-san!
You can't go alone!
Gosh, she runs off without a thought.
We'd better hurry, too.
Right!
How far could he have gone?
I should have caught up by now...
Help me!
Shinomiya-kun! Are you there?!
Serinuma-senpai?!
Hey!
Actually, stay away!
What are you saying?
He's over there.
I'll be right there!
N-No!
Tentacles X Pretty Boy
Tentacles X Pretty Boy!
P-Please don't look at me.
Ka
I'll free you right away.
How did you end up like that?
A-At first it was like...
Shi
The vine got caught around my ankle.
Ouch!
Shi
And I fell.
And when I tried to get it off...
For some reason, my hands
also got tangled up.
Shi
And when I thrashed around to break free...
My entire body got tangled up.
So he's a klutz!
Y-You really saved me.
Thank you very much.
I-I'm just happy you're not hurt.
It's good! All good!
I ended up looking weird
in front of her again.
Everyone else is looking for you, too.
We decided to group up ahead here.
B-But...
Don't worry about it.
That started quick!
Let's run, Shinomiya-kun!
Right.
Grand Hotel
Is this...
Ka
Shi
I-It's scary!
But it'll be more dangerous
if we stay out here!
Let's take shelter from the rain for now.
Right.
I wonder if everyone else is okay.
Here. Wear this.
Huh? What about you? Aren't you cold?
I'm fine.
R-Really?
Thanks.
Don't thank me.
Isn't it my fault we ended up
here in the first place?
It's because I can't do anything
right, and just get in the way.
Shinomi—
Wh-What?!
I-Is anybody there?!
Something's there!
What do I do? What do I do?
And now there's chanting?!
Lord have mercy. Lord have mercy.
Lord have mercy.
It's coming from you?!
Leave it to me!
I already have experience from
sending my lord to the other side!
Oh! But that was an illusion
caused by mushrooms!
It's fine, though!
Because I pray for Shion every day!
You're making me even more scared, so stop!
Don't worry.
I know you're not good
at handling scary things.
But I'm fine, so no need to worry.
No, well...
She's shaking.
It's all right!
Idiot.
I'm an idiot.
I'm a huge idiot.
Forget about not being able to do
anything, or not being good enough.
It's all right.
This is no time to lose my nerve.
I'll protect you!
Wow, so cool!
Seriously!
This is too funny!
Hi, there. We wanted to thank
you for what happened earlier.
Did you guys have fun at the haunted house?
Those are the guys from the beach house.
What are they doing here?
Surprised?
We were surprised, too.
We came to see who was crashing
our hangout, and it's you guys!
Plus, those troublemakers
with you before aren't here.
Talk about lucky, right?
And did you just say,
"I'll protect you" to her?
When you were the brat that just
hid behind those other guys?
Seriously, what a joke.
Stop it—
Now, now.
Please stop.
Please forgive me.
What a loser!
Get outta my sight.
And you, come over here.
No!
As if...
I'd say that, dumbass!
Senpai, this way!
Get back here!
Hey.
Didn't I tell you
we'd kill you if you made a pass at her?
No!
So, that detour we took was crazy.
There were snakes, and I swear
there was a wild boar, too.
Plus, that thunderstorm was serious.
I thought we were done for.
And Nishina, next time tell us if there's
a connected public road on the other side.
I really didn't know about it, though.
Um...
I'm sorry that I caused so much trouble.
Thank you very much.
It's all good.
We're all used to your freak-outs already.
Right?
Let's head home.
I'm not strong like these guys are.
And maybe I'm not on
the same level as them yet,
But...
But, still...
I don't want to lose her to anyone.
That's why...
Nana
So dense.
Klutz.
Are you okay?
I-I'm sorry.
I'm stuck.
Klutz appeal!
I'll do my best!
I feel so bored and lifeless.
The world should just end.
What's the matter, Nanashima-kun?
I'm sure he just hasn't bothered
finishing his summer homework.
Igarashi, let me copy yours!
I know you're cheating with
the other soccer club guys.
Sure, but a trade's gotta be fair.
What are you going to do for me?
A-Aren't we friends?!
It'll be fine!
You can do it all in just two days!
What? There's no way.
I used to think it was impossible, too.
Next time:
Brother Invasion
Look forward to it!
But to go to all the Kachu Rabu
events in the summer, I—