Those Awaiting a Star
Part 2
Welcome to the library of the forest.
Huh?
Umm...
I'm the magician of the forest.
No, hmm...
Let's see, that's not right.
I'm just trying to make
you feel comfortable.
Those guys won't come inside.
You can see them?
Sure.
Why?
Can you tell me why you can see them?
Besides, none of the wicked
ones can get in here.
Or rather, I don't let them in.
Everyone's busy with their books.
No one's going to hurt you.
You do understand, I hope?
Have a seat. Make yourself at home.
Let's see if I have a good one.
It's been a very long time
since anyone's come here.
I'm so happy.
I hope I have a book you might like.
Or, should I say, a book that likes you?
Hey, what's wrong?
I'm sorry for barging in.
You don't need to worry about that.
Hey.
Give me a second, just a second!
Where is it...
It should be here somewhere.
This'll do.
What's your name?
My name is Riichi.
Miura Riichi.
Well?
Hatori Chise.
That's a beautiful name.
Here.
Your library card.
It's yours.
You're going to need it to come back.
Make sure you don't lose it.
Listen carefully.
You're going to run straight through there.
Now, run.
That was so much fun.
I'm beat.
Why don't you put your phone down
when someone's talking to you?
Hold on.
Come on.
I said wait.
You always say that.
You never listen to me.
Huh?
Do you know what I go through every day?
I know, I know.
No, you don't!
I'm tired, too, you know.
You mean the girl, right?
I'm the one taking care of her!
You're the one who took
her in just to be nice.
Well, so did you.
That's because you...
Don't touch that.
Don't bother.
Daiki, hurry up and get ready.
Why are you here?
Go away.
It's your fault that Mom's...
What's wrong, miss?
Are you hurt?
Oh, my.
Here.
Book Report
Hatori-san.
May I read some books?
Of course.
You have your library card, right?
Listen,
as long as you have this card,
you're a member here.
You can come whenever you want,
and you can borrow the books.
Only one at a time, however.
And you must never leave the front door open.
Mind those rules, and you can
come here every day, if you like.
Every day?
Yup.
Every day.
As often as you like, as long as you like.
Welcome, Hatori-san,
to the library of the forest.
Here you are.
Bees
No, we can't deal with her anymore.
That's right.
My wife left with the kids.
We've done enough for her, haven't we?
It's your turn to take her, now.
You're a real bookworm now, huh?
Yeah.
I can forget all my problems
while I'm reading.
Oh, I know.
Hatori-san, if you'd like,
why don't you stay—
Oh, no.
I still can't decide which one
to do my book report on.
Even after you've read so many?
Well, I liked all of them.
Yeah?
What's that book like?
That one...
That's...
It's always there.
That one, well...
What was that book like?
Which one should I do?
Hey,
I love reading the last page
of a book more than anything.
How could this be?
Miura-san?
You have to leave for today.
Now.
Hurry!
But...
Quickly.
My book report.
Yeah.
So...
Won't your mom be worried if
you don't come home soon?
No one worries about me.
That's not true.
Auntie left home.
It's all my fault, though...
I keep noticing the weird things,
and it makes Auntie angry.
Just this once.
Just today.
Let's find a book for your report.
I just really didn't want
to go home that day.
That's unusual.
That you'd be so insistent.
I was a child.
Are you all right?
Thanks, Ruth.
I'm all right.
As long as this isn't hard on you.
And then? And then?
And that became a special night.
There's a book I want you to have.
"The Lonely Little Star."
A picture book?
I have a feeling you really need this book.
Now, will you clean up these books for me?
It's so pretty.
"The lonely little star, the tiny child of a star,
twinkled in the empty sky all by itself."
I'll send her home before sunrise.
All right?
Goodbye.
You'll never come back again.
Miura-san?
Flowers
What the?
No.
How?
Miura-sa—
How did you get in?!
Why?!
I'm sorry.
You, the door!
No!
Not this book!
Hurry, come here!
Miura-san...
You...
Hurry!
Hurry, run!
Miura-san...
Hurry!
Good morning.
Morning.
I'll lend you this.
M-Mayumi-san...
Promise you'll give it back.
Mayumi-san...
Are you all right?
Can you move?
Don't worry.
They're gone now.
I'm sorry.
I didn't close the door.
Hatori Chise-san, I need you
to do something for me.
Deliver it for me.
I can't do it.
Miura-san.
Miura-san!
A promise left unfulfilled.
The girl runs onward, holding
with her a young man's regret.
Not knowing what she'll find...
Mayumi-san.
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3