Time is a burden.
That's what I believe.
Do you know "Ayakashi Kan"?
Did you hear?
You mean Maison de Ayakashi?
They say the security is unbelievable.
Yes, that celebrity complex.
I've got a bad habit.
The one where each apartment
gets one member of the Secret Service, right?
Apparently she's a new tenant.
What do you mean, "Secret Service"?
A bodyguard.
I hear she's the daughter of an old family.
A huge conglomerate called Shirakiin.
Looks like you're the center of attention.
I've been doing it since I was little,
and it's not something
I can control.
Should getting attention from
those bored housewives make me happy?
I don't want to be the
gossip fodder of their circle.
Why don't you just do your job?
R-Right...
I will put up a bold front
and verbally abuse people
for no reason.
This is my bad habit.
Oh, Ririchiyo.
Looks like you made it.
Oh, it's Sorinozuka.
Haven't seen you in a while.
Loathing yourself for your own
groundless hostility again?
What are you talking about?
Is that all you brought?
They're bringing the rest.
Oh, okay.
Don't act all worried about me.
We lived close to each other,
but that's all we've got in common.
But I know lots about you.
Like back in the sixth grade...
Ririchiyo, want to come eat lunch with us?
You're nothing but sheep.
Is what you said to them,
but you cried about it afterwards.
I wasn't crying!
That was an allergic reaction!
You wrote a really polite apology
letter after we got in a fight.
I didn't!
I was just practicing my handwriting!
This place has a nickname: Ayakashi Kan.
Its real name is Maison de Ayakashi.
An apartment complex for the super elite,
where only chosen people may live.
That's what the public is supposed to think.
I...
I came here to be
alone.
I'm actually in room three.
Just call me if you need any help.
Thank you for coming out.
Room four... this is it.
Am I supposed to thank you now?
No.
Please don't waste such words on me.
I've been waiting so long to meet you,
Miss Ririchiyo.
Are you... crying?!
From this day on,
it's my duty to oversee your daily safety.
My name is Soushi Miketsukami.
My daily safety.
So you're Secret Service.
I didn't sign any contracts for you.
Are you saying you don't need me?
That's exactly what I'm saying.
Then please.
I implore you to dispose of me.
To... dispose of you?
I exist only for you,
so if you say you do not need me,
then that renders my life meaningless.
You should value yourself more!
You are so incredibly kind!
What are you doing?!
You are even more wonderful
than I could ever have imagined!
Please, make me your servant— No,
your dog.
The Dog and Me
Miss Ririchiyo, about those fish bones...
I don't want them!
Ririchiyo, you hired someone
from the Secret Service?
No, I didn't.
Someone in my family must have
set this up for me.
And...
they had to find someone so hard to abuse.
But the whole reason I came here was...
I don't need anyone from the Secret Service.
I'll just terminate your contract right now.
Then...
Don't die!
But what else do I have to live for,
if my raison d'etre is to serve you?
Just go back to whatever you
were doing before yesterday.
That life is dead to me.
Hey, no biggie.
So you got a pretty bodyguard.
You are too random!
Just ignore me when my
presence inconveniences you.
I will be happy to be used
by you only when it suits you.
Will that really make you happy?
Of course.
I've known you for a long time.
I've been wanting to meet you for so long.
You know... me?
It's not a mystery.
It's not that big,
and there is a lot of activity...
in our community.
Thank you!
I let my guard down
since it's spring break.
It's already nine.
I didn't shop for food.
I guess I'll get something
to eat in the lounge.
A lot happened yesterday.
Anyway, the contract is void.
Do you understand?
So I probably won't see you again.
Stop looking at me like that!
I guess not even he will show up today.
Good morning, Miss Ririchiyo.
I see you're looking beautiful today, as well.
Your beauty truly suits your name well...
How long have you been here?!
I have not been told your waking hour,
so I have been waiting here
since six in the morning.
Since six?!
That's ridiculous!
Spring just started... it's still cold!
Perhaps.
But when I thought that you might
be opening your door any
moment and stepping out,
the cold became irrelevant to me.
What are you, the faithful dog?!
Stop this, please.
If you need to talk to me,
just wake me up.
You are too kind.
I just don't want the hassle of you
croaking in front of my door.
I will be careful.
To know that I have even the
smallest place in your heart,
makes freezing to death seem a fine—
What are you, the faithful dog?!
Will you be breakfasting in the lounge?
I thought I told you,
"I don't need your services."
Today's menu features
a bagel sandwich with salad,
and fruit yogurt.
I told you I don't need your fussing,
and then you do even more?
The dressing is...
Good morning.
Who are you?
Well, who are you?
My name is Karuta Roromiya.
I'm with the Secret Service.
My client is in room two.
I'm Ririchiyo Shirakiin, from room four.
It's nice to meet you?
Yeah, whatever, I suppose...
A symbol of our acquaintance.
Thank you...
That was another Secret
Service agent, I suppose.
We could take a little
stroll inside the complex.
I'd give you a tour.
I keep telling you,
I'm fine by myself!
Thank you for bringing my food.
Anyway, what I'm saying is...
Thank you, that's very polite.
Won't you allow me to be your guide?
You're good at sucking people into your pace.
You're crafty.
You are an honest and wonderful person.
This is the bath.
There are baths in each room as well,
but this might be nice for a change of scenery.
Directly above the bath, we have this.
It's the rooftop garden.
With its spacious skies and relaxing gardens,
I'm sure this place will be perfect
if you ever need somewhere to think.
The stream under this little stone bridge
is made from pebbles, which means...
Meh...!
Meh?
This is too much!
Your black hair, your white skin,
your almond-shaped eyes!
Despite your slenderness and small stature,
your black tights look so supple!
You... are too much!
Who are you?!
This is the Secret Service's Nobara Yukinokouji.
Oh, how could I do such a thing?
This is Miss Ririchiyo Shirakiin,
who moved in here yesterday.
Ririchiyo. That's a strange name.
Pretty special.
I'm Sorinozuka's Secret Service agent.
My name is Nobara Yukinokouji.
I hope we will become... good friends!
Of course, I mean in a sexual way!
Sexual?!
Isn't her openness refreshing?
Openness.
It's a word that has no meaning for me.
When I'm uncertain,
the past comes to hunt me.
Good morning.
Today, I knew your waking hour, so...
Your herbal tea.
Thank you.
They say that lavender
has a natural calming effect.
The light was on late in your
room these last two nights.
You said you knew me.
Doesn't that knowledge repulse you?
The Shirakiin family has been
a honorable and rich family for a long time.
It is the house where I am from.
Good morning, Miss Ririchiyo!
Don't think you're special!
All your house has is money!
You're so boring!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Thank you for your troubles.
It's no trouble at all.
After all, I am her teacher.
I will make sure to pass
on your name to our master.
Thank you!
I was lonely.
Both because of being bullied
for being a Shirakiin,
and for being protected by the same.
I don't have anything.
It's like the house I am part of
is a bigger part of me than myself.
Is that...
Is that how you've felt?
To think that all along,
you've been carrying this burden alone.
Don't cry!
Here.
Miss Ririchiyo...
You cry easily, don't you?
I think I got my bad habit
sometime around then.
You're so boring!
Those words were true.
I was weak.
All I did was fit into the
mold of the Shirakiin family.
I was lonely and felt pathetic,
so I put up a front.
However, I know I have to change.
I have to learn how to
build up my confidence so that
I can properly interact with people.
I have to be alone until then.
Right now, all I do is hurt people.
I don't think...
If you stay with me,
sooner or later you'll get hurt, too.
Why don't we try it, then?
And you know, you are even
cuter than I ever imagined.
You are a wonderful person who
honors justice and you're a bit shy—
Just stop!
I suppose he is a good person,
but I've got to keep my focus.
If I start to enjoy myself,
I'll only get myself hurt again.
The cycle will just begin anew.
A blackout...?
Don't move.
So this is the high security
celebrity complex, huh?
What a joke.
Now, you're going to quietly
take me to your room
and give me all your money.
Looks like you're just a human.
What did you say?!
You're quite unlucky to have come here.
Her eyes... are glowing!
This house isn't guarded against mere humans.
After all, your kind are not a threat to us.
Don't move!
I'm sorry for being late.
You dared to point a
gun at Miss Ririchiyo.
M-Monster...
You're a monster!
Monster? How rude.
We're proper humans.
But one of our ancestors had
mingled with monsters.
We're just channeling them.
We attract the attention
of pure-blooded monsters,
which is why we decided to build this place
where we can live together
and help each other.
I don't want a mere burglar
calling me "monster."
And you're filthy, too!
Couldn't it at least have
been three sisters in leotards?
Your fantasies are running wild.
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about,
but I'm telling you, just keep quiet!
Don't...
touch me.
Are you all right?
You're the one who's hurt!
I'm sorry, I wasn't thinking.
Please take my left hand then.
That's not the point!
Please don't worry about me.
I exist to protect you.
That's stupid!
It's always Miss Ririchiyo this,
Miss Ririchiyo that...
You even got yourself hurt.
Is that how much you want to be a dog?!
You want to put yourself on the line for that?!
What are you—
A kiss on the tip of the nail is a sign of loyalty.
The only reason I am here
is my loyalty to you.
It is irrelevant, whether you are
the daughter of a great house or not.
I told you when we first met,
that I have always known you.
As you are the one who saved me,
I owe you all my respect.
You and nobody else.
You don't know how desperately
I've wanted to meet you.
And now I've failed!
I will do absolutely everything in my power
to make it up to you.
So please, please,
will you let me stay by your side?
Do what you like.
You won't listen to what I say anyway.
Are you certain?
Even if I am like this?
Who cares what you are?
Just go where you want
and live the way you want.
Miss Ririchiyo.
Thank you.
I am not worthy,
but please bear with me.
Let go of my leg!
I was pretty freaked out yesterday.
I was so scared.
You were scared?
Miss Ririchiyo.
It looks like you got a good night's sleep.
I was simply tired.
Hey, Sorinozuka.
Isn't this your core?
Oh, really?
Thanks.
Don't make trouble for the rest of us.
Sorry, sorry.
This form is so much more relaxing.
I mean, there's so much you have to
do properly in your human form.
What part of you was proper again?
- Shaggy, unkempt hair
- Track suit every day
- Sandals
I guess Mr. Sorinozuka is a
"Flying cloth monster."
This is nice.
What, you live in the same
complex and you didn't know?
Yes, I only moved in here
the day before you did.
So it was just a coincidence
that they hired you for me?
Miss Ririchiyo,
it was not a coincidence.
I am in the same place as you are,
and you have granted me
permission to do so, haven't you?
That's not what I meant last night.
Wait, it wasn't a coincidence at all?!
You are such a wonderful person
with such a high sense of responsibility.
You would never go
back on your word, right?
Pure
Black
You...
I
I pled
I pledged
I pledged some
I pledged something
I pledged something?
Could you be... You're a stalker!
Not at all. I am your dog.
After this, I will remember it again and again.
It was the beginning of a long, long time.
Miss Ririchiyo,
there's nothing that makes me happier
than being able to serve you,
but I have to say,
you are truly beautiful.
It's almost as if the
word "beauty" came alive
and materialized and that is—
Stop flattering me.
We're supposed to be
announcing the next episode.
There is no worth in
talking about the preview
when your beauty is right here.
My humble mouth wants to praise
your beauty for all of eternity...
A Lonely Dog
Just stop already!