She should have gone this way.
Let's look over there.
It seems they've left.
What did you do?
Yeah,
and why do you
think I did something?
Serikyan!
Hey, don't say that so loud.
You know her, Nanami?
You don't know Serikyan?
She's an idol on the national stage...
Ginyuuin Serika!
Huh?
Ginyuuin...
If Her Flag Breaks
Flag 11
We Don't all Have to Dance. I can Dance by Myself
She's sold more than 10,000,000 CDs!
Her photos make magazines sell five times better!
She's constantly on tons
of different TV programs.
In just the last six months she's
climbed to the top of the rankings.
She's easily the most famous idol right now.
Her name: Serikyan!
Sorry, I've never heard of her.
Are you stupid?
You've never heard of Serikyan?!
Do you come from another world
where they don't have TVs?
Do you live with the elves? Are you an elf?!
I guess I need to work on my popularity.
No, it's fine, Serikyan.
This guy's an elf and doesn't know anything.
Wait...
Thanks for letting me borrow
your uniform, Nanami-chin.
The uniforms are really cute.
Serikyan in a school uniform is so great.
Yes, if you use that uniform
to disguise yourself,
it should be more difficult
for people to recognize you.
You know what you're doing, Nanami-chin!
I'll give you a hug.
I've never seen this side of Nanami.
I never would have thought
you'd be so into idols.
I don't like idols.
I like Serikyan!
So why is this "Serikyan" here anyway?
You don't know anything, do you?
On the last day of the School Fair,
there's a special Serikyan concert.
That's obviously why she's here.
Wait...
Today isn't the last day.
Well, I wanted to take a
look at the stage and such,
and you know, have some
fun at the fair, maybe.
Well, then, we'll just have to
show you around the fair, then!
Thank you, Nanami-chin!
But aren't you on a date with your boyfriend?
H-He's not my boyfriend.
You're far more important to me
than this dark elf over here.
Now, let's go.
Sure!
The bard from the fairy tale...
I imagine that's her...
No use in worrying about it.
I decided that I would have fun while I can.
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
R-Right.
President!
I can't believe you.
How many girls are you leading on?
I'm not really...
You were supposed to be on a date
at the school fair with Nanami-chin,
but now you're flirting
with other girls instead.
I feel bad for Nanami-chin!
It wasn't a date.
It was more like I forced him,
but I'm glad you're concerned for me!
Serikyan!
Nanami-chin!
Uh...
Hm?
You wanted to see the stage you'll be
performing on during the last day, right?
I think that's it.
You're a national idol,
so this might not be much,
but we're all looking forward
to your performance.
No, I like these local concerts.
The first concert I performed
was at a school fair.
A school fair at my middle school...
We didn't have a stage,
so we just decorated the gym.
Ginyuuin Serika Idol Debut
I had just debuted,
and couldn't sing because I was so nervous.
But my classmates
and my teachers cheered me on.
I was so happy I could've cried.
They supported me.
But...
For the next year and a half
no one even noticed me.
I was an idol in name only.
Talent.
I guess I don't have any.
Maybe I should stop calling myself an idol.
I'm supposed to make everyone happy,
but instead they made me feel happy,
and I couldn't even return the favor...
I wish I could do more...
I...
You can't give up here.
Huh?
You will come to inspire people,
and become a woman that
represents people's dreams.
Your heart is not yet dead.
If you fall, you can get back up,
provided you don't give up.
I can keep going?
Do you think I can fly again?
Do you think I can sing and give people hope?
You can.
You have a flag on
your head that says you'll succeed.
I'll do it!
Half a year later,
Serikyan became a super-idol,
and it was all thanks to his words.
He said I had a success flag.
What a prophet.
I call him the purple flag guy.
I never was able to thank him,
but I wonder if he's out there somewhere,
having heard my songs.
I guess I just told you
my secret origin story. Whoops.
Don't tell anyone,
'Kay? 'Kay?
R-Right.
Anyway, I'll be going.
You're leaving, Serikyan?
Serikyan leaves, you know?!
What are you saying...
I'm glad I ran into you Nanami-chin!
Come to my concert!
I guess you can come, too, Hatate.
Anyway, bye.
Hey, Hatate Souta-kun.
What is it, Nanami-san?
It could just be me,
but I think I have an idea
who this purple flag guy is.
It's probably just you.
Yeah, I guess it is.
Silly me.
Silly Nanami.
Is there anyone else who'd go off
about flags when no one wanted them to?!
I had a lot of stuff
going on back then, so...
When I saw her
I was planning on taking
my own life.
I guess
I wanted to do one good thing before I died.
Ultimately, I couldn't end it all, though.
I guess it was pretty tough for you.
So I wasn't really thinking
about her specifically, per se.
I was just trying to make myself feel better.
Yeah, but you still helped her.
You saved her, right?
Huh?
Serikyan recovered,
I got to know you...
Everyone was happy in the end.
You know, if you'd used your power like this from the start,
you wouldn't have had such a hard time.
Nanami...
Anyway, putting that aside...
Huh?
It pisses me off that Serikyan
owes you so much!
Wai—
Making your way into
Serikyan's heart like that!
You're acting crazy.
They're fighting.
First time I've seen something like this.
Everyone, it's time!
It's finally the last day of the fair.
It's time for the grand finale!
Yes, the time has come!
Akane's got new clothes and
totally is ready to go.
Way to go, Akane, but I've
mastered a new dance!
Sounds like you're excited, too!
The night dance party!
Serikyan's concert!
Huh?
Ta-da!
Sob. Sob.
H-How are we, Souta?
Don't just stand there. Say something.
Huh? Y-Yeah...
You all look great.
Yeah, we all tried hard for you.
Yes, we can't embarrass ourselves
when we dance with you.
Huh? With me?
Everyone wants to dance with you.
There's a legend regarding this dance party.
Legend?
It'd be nice if the couples that
dance get married in the future.
Nice? That's all?
Must be nice to be a guy.
As your little sister, I don't
mind how many step-sisters I get.
You can't say that.
My little brother should
only have one older sister!
That doesn't even make any sense.
It's nice being this old.
I get to feel like I'm dancing with my grandson.
H-Hatate-kun,
could you dance with me, too?
I can't dance.
I'll lead for you, I will.
Everyone wants to dance with you.
Everyone really wants to.
Will you dance with us?!
Dance partner flags...
Got it.
I'm not confident at all,
but let's dance.
Yay!
In that case it's a promise!
Yeah, promise.
I-I'm fine with seeing Serikyan's
concert alone, but...
But...
If you're the only one not dancing
it'll feel like you're left out,
right?
D-Don't say it before I do!
Serikyan!
Thank you all for coming to
Serikyan's school concert!
Are you having fun at the fair?
I actually secretly went around
the fair with some friends.
It was a lot of fun!
I totally love this school now!
Serikyan!
Today's concert will be broadcast
to fans all around the world!
So cheer appropriately.
Nanami-chan broke.
But I'm kind of having fun.
I want to shout with everyone.
Broadcast all around the world. huh?
Pretty amazing.
She really made it.
She turned into a girl who inspires people,
who represents their dreams.
I found Nanami-chin.
I see that Hatate came, too.
Huh?
Listen to my song!
I saw you yesterday,
but will I see you again today?
My biorhythm is focused on you.
We only could talk for a
bit, but I still got red.
I'm such a girl.
As the gelato melts,
as the candy melts...
What's that?
A flag of light?
Could this be...
Did my power get stronger when I met
Serika, the bard?
No, this light is...
They're connected.
The world is being drawn
to her flag and song.
It's being drawn to me?
So that's how it is..
I thought that my death flag drew
evil from all over the world,
and brought me nothing but despair.
But that was wrong.
I have people connected to me with
kindness that can overcome any evil.
I have people who give me hope
that will paint over the despair.
All I did was turn my back on the world,
so I didn't notice something so simple.
Nanami...
Akane...
Okiku-nee...
Everyone...
Hatate Souta.
You're...
Number Zero.
What are these numbers?
I guess other data than the
flags has become visible.
The sudden growth of that power of
yours strained the servers,
and the world froze.
What are you saying—
The parallel world I went to with Mei.
The term "virtual world" would be more apt.
Virtual?
This is one of the many worlds we,
the Council of the Seven Virtues,
created to help combat the Angel Boat.
An existence in the network.
A world composed of data.
The trouble began when
the system that exists in
cyberspace to watch over
the real world, the Angel
Boat, went out of control.
At this rate, it's only a matter
of time before humanity,
which depends so much on the network,
is controlled by computers.
In order to prevent that, we—
You seem rather calm.
I'd like to scream
and say you're lying,
but the truth flag above your head,
and everything I see here...
Yes, your power is needed for the world.
You can see the flags and control them.
Only that power of yours that
can alter the data of all events
can reach the Angel Boat in cyberspace.
It is the best and only weapon we have.
Yeah, I know,
or more like I know everything now.
I just gained all the
information on the network.
But there is one thing I don't understand.
Why me?
We, the Council of the Seven Virtues,
have been running simulations
in the worlds we created
with the data from all humanity.
We set the simulations to run
one hundred million times
faster than reality.
The Sacrament guided our way.
You know the rest.
The Hatate Souta of this world...
In other words, only you have met with
the Sacrament and been given power.
Is this a coincidence?
Or an inevitability by the name of fate?
That is up to you.
What is Sakura...
No, the Sacrament.
It doesn't really matter,
now that your power has grown,
and been perfected.
Sakura...
I understand everything now.
Even I can't break this death flag of mine.
It's a curse.
You gave me this power
so I'd understand that?
Now, what will you do with
that power, Hatate Souta?
What will happen to this world now?
Now that your power has been perfected,
it won't end with a simple freeze next time.
I imagine it'll completely collapse,
so long as you are here.
I see.
I... can't be here anymore, I guess.
Dance Party
It's time for the Hatagaya
School Fair to end!
Good work, everyone!
The only thing left is the dance party!
Everyone dance
your hearts out!
This is only one of the many virtual worlds.
But... it was the only world I had.
What is Souta off doing?
It's fine.
He promised he'd dance with everyone.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I'm sorry, Nee-san.
What was that feeling just now?
Is something wrong, Nanami-chan?
It's nothing.
Everything's going to be over soon.
I wonder what Souta's doing.
Uh...
Who's Souta-kun?
Huh?
Roar! Gawo!
I wonder what I'm saying.
I'm thinking about that place,
all of them, before I realize it.
I'm sure that's because
I was happy until today.
That's why I might not be able to go back.
But as long as everyone's smiling back there,
no matter what flags I have to break,
Flag 12
It's a Cruel World. I'm Going to Take a Look in the Shadows.
I'll protect them.
If Her Flag Breaks
You'd better watch next time!
Illustration: Aoki Ume