Stronghold of Lust
<Where is Pleguzes Jiart?>
<You may begin.>
<Your Majesty!>
To see the oracle's prophecy fulfilled,
we have conducted multiple
reconnaissance missions.
I believe it is now time
to launch a massive strike.
I'd love to hear how you
came to that conclusion!
I hope that this encompassing strike
is not a waste of time, Dolgana.
Naturally, there is no
point in making such
a maneuver if it fails to
usher staggering results.
It would seem that some of the primitives
are capable of flying like us.
You mean the ones who kicked your butt?
I-if I had more time, I could have
turned them into a sea of blood!
That is enough!
Dolgana, let us hear your plan.
Your Majesty!
For starters, I would like
Klein to fight in the vanguard.
Cool!
We will follow behind and
hunt down the lamata!
Very well.
What would you have me do?
Babysit Lumes?
Lutiel, I would like you and Lumes
to finish off the remaining lamata.
Dolgana, you will be in
charge of this Ta Hevara.
Your Majesty!
May the gods be with you!
How does everyone find working together
for the shikaara amusing?
I've heard that this journey's prophecy
is of a scale that comes
only once every 300 years.
The lamata have resisted beyond our-
The thrill of the hunt comes from everyone
relying upon their own skills!
At any rate, I'm going
to put this to an end.
The impatient brat!
May I have a glass?
You're still here, Lutiel?
This wine is most delicious.
Shouldn't you see to your preparations?
I'll leave after one more glass.
I'm quite excited!
What will I get to mount in my manor
after this Ta Hevara?
This prophecy is not meant
for your personal gain.
Bear that in mind.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Take care of it.
Your Highness!
Pleguzes!
The parisada just adjourned
a few minutes ago.
I am aware.
Then where were you?!
Jiart!
Brother...
You are hurt.
Tend to him.
I would have appreciated
your attendance, Pleguzes.
That is enough.
But Your Majesty-!
You cannot measure him by
your set of standards, not my brother.
Brother, would you care for a match?
I must prepare for Ta Hevara.
Purify yourself and prepare for battle.
I can smell my brother on you...
Pleguzes?
Accept your fate!
Prince Jiart!
Move!
My!
Is it to your liking?
I like how it is more humble than you.
My brother's woman was also humble.
And she was not to your liking?
It made her boring.
Even I may not amply satisfy you,
Prince Pleguzes.
You are the very image of a Manaava.
You obey your instincts
as you obtain anything you desire.
Instinct...
But those lamata!
Supposedly they consider
it a disgrace to obey
one's instinct and drown in desire.
But isn't there dignity in
the instinct of the living?
Take what you want.
Kill those you wish to kill.
And rape those you wish to rape,
yes, Pleguzes Jiart?
Do you think that race of lamata
can defy our instincts?
So? Why exactly are we implementing
this kind of operation?
As I already explained,
we were successfully able to
shrink the light wave weapon.
However, it takes time to fire.
Furthermore, it is unable
to fire a chain of shots.
As such, we must rely on tactics that-
Got it, got it.
S-sir, I wasn't done yet!
I can figure out the rest from there.
Now, more importantly!
Could anything use some sprucing up?
Sir?
How do I look?
Commander in Chief Zorig of the GDF
will explain the situation
leading to the present.
Our GDF army was originally formed
as a space security force.
The economic powers of the world
established their own armies.
And those armies were unified as one,
becoming the GDF.
Afterwards, the Wulgaru hit us
with a surprise attack.
As it was our first encounter
with foes from outer space,
it was difficult for us to respond
in a unified manner.
However, we've finally reached
the point where we are capable
of full-scale operations.
Upon multiple analyses primarily
conducted by the Operations Command,
we have completed what we believe to be
the best strategy for this upcoming battle.
We consider it imperative that
the media and the people of
the world offer their support.
As such, we would like to disclose
the content of our strategy in detail.
If you would, Vice
Chief of Staff Komine.
Sir!
Huh? Lt. Amane, what are you doing here?
Why can't I be here?
Isn't it almost time for you to explain
the strategy to the media?
Weren't you were the central figure
behind devising this plan?
Look.
Allow me to explain our strategy.
The GDF's recent assault on
the enemy base on Planetoid
RA221 ended in success.
However, we believe that the enemy
is preparing to retaliate.
As such, we have decided
to destroy Ragazza,
the enemy's frontline base,
which is located in close proximity
to our army base on Ceres.
First we will attack
the enemy with our
cutting-edge laser-based system.
To prevent the enemy from rushing us,
we will set up a minefield.
On top of that, the mobile troops will
fire in unison with disposable rail guns.
After that, we will enter normal battle.
Having predicted the enemy's path,
we have positioned vessels in front of Ceres
that will fire a volley of guided
sublight speed guns and
free electron cannons.
Afterwards, we will focus
on absolute defense
until the light wave weapon is fully charged.
Once the heavy tactical
laser has charged,
the vanguard mobile troops
and vessels will leave
the laser's line of fire.
Upon evacuation, we will destroy the
Wulgaru base along with their fleet!
That is all!
With this, the Battle of Ceres,
the GDF will do everything within
its power to win this war!
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Let me introduce her.
She will be in charge of
managing your schedules,
Miss Peko Yamada.
It's a pleasure!
Th-the pleasure's mine.
She is boarding the mother ship with us.
I'll be supervising your schedules
and everyday lives.
If you run into any difficulties
in your work or daily lives,
please feel free to
come see me for advice!
I'll even give you tips on love!
In that case, I could
use some personal advi-
Please look after them.
Sure, Captain!
Excuse me!
Yes?
Um, what should we do?
Are we supposed to participate
in that Battle of Ceres
they just announced?
Yes, but you'll be on
standby for a while first.
S-standby?
You're free to do as
you like on Star Rose.
Now I have a meeting to attend.
Shall we get going?
I've prepared new rooms
for everyone on Star Rose.
Here!
You can also use it for purchases
in the mess hall and at kiosks.
Please let me know if
you need anything else.
Well, take care!
Uh, thanks.
Everyone gets their own room, huh?
This is mine!
Awesome!
It's like a VIP room...
It's so different from the dorm!
Everyone, go to your own room!
I-I guess we should.
Let's go to our rooms.
So what are all of you doing in my room?
Well, uh, it felt right...
My room gives me the willies.
These rooms are too big
for just one person.
Wanna live together?
Wh-why don't we check out the mess hall?
They have curry!
Excuse me! Do you have
pickled fish guts?
I'm going back to my room.
I'm not terribly hungry, either.
Sorry.
Izurucchi!
Why doncha join us?
Would you like something?
I'll get it for you.
I'd recommend the
yakiniku meal for today.
Th-then I'll have that.
Just hang tight!
Thanks!
Your schooling.
Huh?
I heard you graduated.
Uh, right.
Congrats!
Yeah...
You don't seem too happy about it.
It happened so fast.
And now I don't have
a home to return to.
Thanks for waiting!
But aren't you going to come back
here from now on?
Just think of us as your family!
Family...?
We're something like family.
Be sure to return,
once you've taken off in flight,
Migratory Bird.
You don't have to respond to that.
Y-you see, I don't have any
memories of my family,
so I'm not sure what it's like.
But supposedly I had foster
parents for a while...
You'll find out what it's like.
It's been a long time
since I left the nest.
Now this vessel feels like home.
I think of Degawa as my father and
Dan as my older brother.
Okay...
What's wrong?
Well, heroes are supposed to be loners.
What?
Finish eating?
Y-yeah.
Is something the matter?
It doesn't feel like I ate.
The Battle of Ceres is
disconcerting, isn't it?
There's that, too.
But my pit crew also wanted to talk.
I couldn't relax.
Say what?!
You're doing better
with yours than I am mine!
Totally! You've got it good!
I wanna swap with Kei!
Isn't Kei's crew filled with hot babes?
Not again...
Compared to that, mine's filled with...
And mine...
Ah ♪
My crew seems like it
was originally a family.
They even have a kid.
If this is where we're
permanently stationed,
do you think they'll want to talk every day?
It must be rough having a family.
That just made me feel a bit better!
Why?
Not having a family might actually
make life pretty carefree, huh?
Indeed.
So why is everyone in my room?!
I'm going to copy this.
F-fine...
What are you doing?!
This ain't the place for
manga-drawing brats!
How did you sneak in here?
Uh, well, ummm...
Hey!
What's going on here?
We'll help you out!
Are you making fun of our pilot?
He is doing a splendid
job fighting the enemy!
He's the one out there protecting us!
Let's go!
Damn!
Th-thank you very much!
There's no need to thank us.
It's no big.
You're awesome!
Izuru, you can really draw!
Make me the hero in your next piece!
This is great!
Heroes with families
can be nice too, huh?
What?
This is Godinion.
Requesting permission for takeoff.
This is control.
Godinion is cleared for takeoff.
Cleared for takeoff. All ranges: Green.
Increasing backup engine output.
Before start check: Complete.
External power has been established.
Disconnect all equipment.
Start all engines!
Internal pressure increasing.
Turbines activated.
Main engine military!
Blast off!
You've checked their heavy armament,
exchanged malfunctioning parts
and swapped anything that has
given any errors, right?
They just need one last fine tuning.
The Battle of Ceres is our
first big battle, isn't it?
That's true for the AHSMB, too.
I hope the AHSMB units
don't decide to turn tail and run.
The JURIA-SYSTEM...
It's insane how much it improves
the machine's response time,
but it's extremely difficult to control.
It's an amazing yet annoying system.
If it responds too strongly
to the pilot, it falls apart!
I imagine we'll use their full armament
and pit crews for this battle.
This reminds me of the F1's crew...
Leave them to me!
We've been working on how to repair
the AHSMB while they're
in the midst of battle.
What?!
Everyone in the pit crews
will offer their full support!
Pleguzes Jiart, thank you
for your participation.
I swear that we will protect you.
I do not need your protection.
I have no intention of
participating in the shikaara.
I am here only here in
case Teoria shows herself.
Pleguzesia...
That which I want never
falls within my grasp!
It drives my lusts and
stimulates my instincts!
Isn't this pretty close to Ceres?
Yeah.
When are we gonna sortie?
Once we get the orders.
When'll that be?!
Pipe down!
Come to think of it, where's Suruga?
Awesome!
On top of the usual fare,
I've got massive anti-ship guided missiles,
high-mobility guided missiles
and a midrange impact cannon!
You may be strappin' tough guns,
but you're still squishy.
Let's do push-ups together
until it's time to sortie!
Sweating with guys
just isn't my thing...
What?!
Th-that aside, can I
glue this on somewhere?
All AHSMB pilots, board your units!
Prepare to sortie! Please!
Once you've boarded,
wait there until further notice.
Uh, okay!
Do your best to remain calm.
If you shrink from battle,
the AHSMBs will focus on defense.
Let's do our best, Asagicchi!
Huh? Why the heck did you call me that?
Izuru was trying to help
you loosen up, Asagi.
Izuru!
I'll do my best to become a hero.
The goal behind DNA is to survive
and create copies of itself.
The JURIA-SYSTEM awakens
various instincts.
Consequentially, it horribly
shakes the pilot's heart.
Operation commences in T-30 minutes.
Enemy vessels at Point Tango!
What?!
The enemy is attacking our
primary line of defense!
They out-maneuvered us!
Fire your railgun!
It's too late!
We've lost 70% of the
1st Mobile Strike Force.
Then fight back!
Please wait! We aren't ready to-
I can't! Commence the attack!
We're starting?!
Battle of Ceres