I'm such a loser!
Leader, my ass!
I left my subordinates
behind and turned tail...
I'm a loser...
All right, that's enough.
Don't blame yourself so much.
Everyone knows well enough
that you are no leader, Pai-Pai.
OD...
Just kidding.
Hey, OD...
Hmm?
Do you like this planet?
Where'd that come from?
I sometimes wonder
if I can protect this planet...
If I can sacrifice my life
when the time comes.
Well, let's get going.
Thanks for always being there...
Take it easy today.
Thank you.
Don't push yourself too much.
If you save someone's life,
your own life will—
That's fine.
What?
It makes me happy.
I don't have to be
so gloomy, so it's fine.
I see.
You've changed, Utsutsu.
You'll be fine, even if I'm gone.
Why are you saying that?
Just kidding. Just kidding.
Goodbye, Utsutsu
Just kidding...
C'mon.
Everyone's way too down.
I know!
Why don't we play a card game?
Where's Utsutsu?
She's totally fine.
She had another helping of porridge.
I see.
Man, I'm pathetic...
Like I said...
you're all way too down!
I know!
Let's play Sevens.
All right!
Good morning!
Whoa!
I've been waiting for you, Hajime-chan!
Take a look around!
I've been feeling like I'm at a wake,
or the night before Earth's destruction...
Come on, everyone!
Now's not the time to be so glum!
Katze-san is just around the corner!
I know.
But what should we do?
It's unbelievably powerful.
It destroyed OD-san's planet,
and it cost our leader his close friend.
But Katze-san isn't going to stop.
Katze-san's having fun!
No one having fun
would stop what they're doing
just because someone asked, right?
I get it.
When I knit and stuff,
I sometimes knit till dawn!
I can't stop at all!
So what?
So,
we can't stop, either!
S-So what?
So, everyone, are you ready?
We, the Gatchaman,
need to present ourselves!
What?
All right!
It's decided, then.
Decided, decided, decided!
What was...
What was decided?!
W-Wait, Newbie!
Revealing ourselves to the public?
We must first report to the council
for such an important matter!
Gatcha, Gatcha, Gatchaman!
You're right.
When people are having fun,
no one can stop them.
Gatcha, Gatcha, Gatcha,
Gatcha, Gatchaman!
Yesterday evening,
over fifty people across
the nation lost consciousness
and needed to be hospitalized.
Those affected were males and females
from an eight year old to
those in their sixties.
It is unclear whether there are
any connections between the victims,
but one common factor has emerged:
the victims were all accessing
the social network service,
GALAX, via mobile or computer.
Doesn't it sound like GALAX isn't safe?
The police have announced that they
will investigate the possibility
Yeah. Maybe I'll quit!
that GALAX is somehow involved.
Who's that? Could it be the assailant?
Next, we...
Don't stare. Let's get out of here.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, hello.
I'm wondering if I should strike again.
Get everyone with this.
You can't be serious!
There you go using it again, Rui-Rui!
Snap!
All right, your revolution's over.
Was it fun to play the hero?
Now, it's my turn.
Just you watch.
I'll make the world update.
Nice job.
Confirm biometrics.
Returning error.
Ninomiya Rui-sama is already logged in.
Got your friend!
X, please respond.
X!
I am Rui...
The one running GALAX is a coward named LOAD.
He gave us the paranormal powers called CROWDS,
but in the end, he's keeping it all to himself.
That coward, LOAD...
Keeping CROWDS all to himself...
but in the end, he's keeping it all to himself.
You can't change the world
without bloodshed...
There's no way we can update the world like that!
You can't change the world without bloodshed!
Stop freaking out over the dead sleep incidents,
and give us our powers back!
Give my power back!
It was such a great chance
to change everything, too...
Damn bastard!
Papa!
You're not going to work?
Oh, we suddenly got a day off.
But don't tell Mama, okay?
Okay, got it!
See you!
I'm finished.
My life is over.
Preschool?!
That's right!
The first step in my
Gatchaman PR Campaign Strategy
is a preschool visit!
No way, Newbie!
Why do we have to go to a preschool?!
Baracchi just happened to be going
there for a disaster drill today,
so I was able to schedule a spot!
"Baracchi"?
A fire chief who is one
of her collage buddies.
Oh, really?
Is he hot?
I definitely object!
I hate human kids!
You wouldn't find life forms
who are more barbaric
and violent than them in the entire galaxy!
I'm not going, either.
What good will come from
a weak "hero" like me
going out there in public, anyway?
It's stupid.
Why not just give it a try?
Oh?
Hajime-chan, it seems you have another ally!
Well, it's not like I understand
why it has to be a preschool,
but it's better than
giving up and doing nothing.
Have it your way.
Well, let's get right on it, then!
Staying underground forever
will make us moldy!
You have to get some sunshine sometimes!
I'm not going!
I will not go!
Okay, everyone! All together now!
Gatchaman!
Hello!
We are the Gatchaman!
Nice to meet you!
What? They're the Gatchaman?
They're normal people.
I can be one, too.
There's a really tall queen.
Hey, Newbie.
Did you call in the press?
This is a PR campaign, so of course, I did.
It seems to be a live broadcast, too!
Hey, you should've told us, Hajime-chan.
Are you doing okay?
I'm fine.
What about you?
I'm fine now.
Thanks for yesterday.
Umm, we're here to talk
to you about something today!
Excuse me, can you let us
film your transformation first?
Why did you suddenly show yourselves after
refusing press coverage for so long?
Why did you pick this preschool?
Hey, stop pushing!
We were here first.
Hey, bring the camera over now.
You should all be ashamed of yourselves.
Who's acting more childish here?
No kidding!
Baracchi is way too cool.
Well, we need you to transform first.
We're not here just for fun and games.
I mean, are you people
even the real deal?
Why would you reveal yourself
at a preschool in a suburb, of all places?
You wouldn't happen to be putting on
a hero show using look-alikes, would you?
Go, Bird!
And what about you, Senpai?
Huh? Me?
Go, Bird!
Are you getting this?!
Get this on tape!
Wow! Amazing!
How did you transform?
Sorry, we didn't catch
your transformation on film!
Can you do it again?
Hey, out of the way, kids!
Hey!
Let's all play nice, people!
Yeah!
Oh, I guess we've now met each other!
It looks like that one's the strongest.
Yeah.
That concludes our food
travelogue of Manpuku Avenue.
Next, a live coverage!
What should I do?
I've lost both X and CROWDS...
How would I...
Urgent News - Live Broadcast
The Gatchaman Appear!
The Gatchaman have appeared!
We're reporting live from the field!
What?!
So until now, the Gatchaman
have been secretly capturing
and neutralizing aliens?
You've got it.
Hey, don't touch my boobs.
So you said you had something
you wanted to talk about, earlier?
Oh, I'd forgotten about that!
I met this person called
Berg-Katze yesterday!
Berg-what? Please say it again.
It's Berg-Katze.
It's a super-mysterious alien.
You can't see what it looks like very clearly,
and it asks you riddles out of the blue.
Oh, do you know the answer to this one?
What's the sweetest, tastiest
thing every human being loves?
Er, uh, well...
Who knows, right?
Chocolate!
Ice cream!
Honey!
And what about this Berg-Katze?
I think it'll start something up again.
And when it does, it'll be a huge crisis.
So I want everyone to be careful!
That's all I wanted to say.
An alien is coming!
Wow...
Are the Gatchaman going to fight it?
Umm, how can we be careful, specifically?
I don't know yet!
LOAD-kun!
What?
If you're watching this,
come here as soon as you can!
I think we'll be needing you in the future!
So you've surprised me by going
out into the open, Hajime-chan.
Okay, I see.
I guess you're not stupid,
but in the end, you'll still be humiliated!
Hey, X.
Yes?
Do you think the Rui who's all depressed
over there will go to the preschool?
I do not understand your question.
"Rui-Rui," or Ninomiya Rui, is you.
Oh, right!
Sorry, sorry!
Are you going to the preschool?
Umm, that's not a bad idea,
but I have a different task to do.
It's true!
Gatchaman are here!
Gotta send a pic on my phone!
No, not without permission.
Oh, Baracchi!
They can totally send photos!
Oh, really?
Who gave permission, Newbie?!
Hey, kid! Put me down!
The Gatchaman have suddenly appeared
at a preschool in Tachikawa City.
They transformed in front of the camera,
proving their existence was real.
Ichinose Hajime-san, who's shown
herself to be a leader figure,
also made a warning that a terrifying
alien named Berg-Katze is coming
and that there will be a crisis.
They say Gatchaman are real.
It can't be true, right?
Maybe the press is in on it somehow?
What's this "Berg-Katze" about?
Is Earth finally coming to an end?
But, GALAX isn't that safe either, lately.
Maybe we're better off depending on heroes.
I was serious about trying to change this country.
I even took time off from work to help people.
And this is what I get?
I've got a family, you know.
Do you know how much mortgage we still have to pay off?
No one this old can find a job!
It's all GALAX's fault.
How are you gonna make it up to me for ruining my life?
Upon being informed about
the Gatchaman incident,
Prime Minister Sugayama made
the following statement:
"I have not received any information."
Gatchaman Appear at a Tachikawa Preschool
"Until it is verified, I am
not obligated to respond."
C'mon.
What?
He's totally passed out.
How long is this rotten
world gonna keep going?
I can't stand it anymore.
This country's got to go
down in flames first.
You and I are in agreement,
Umeda-san.
You are...
It has been a while.
I am LOAD.
Well, I should tell you my real name.
I am Ninomiya Rui.
What do you want now,
you spineless coward?
It's because you're dicking around
that the world never changes!
I've found that less than
twenty percent currently
possess levels of self-initiative
that have been sufficiently heightened.
Huh?
As things stand,
I must admit that
achieving the bloodless revolution
of my goals is difficult in the extreme.
That's what I've been saying from the start!
Umeda-san.
I need your help.
Are you being serious?
I am.
Now is the time to put
ourselves out there in public.
Umeda-san.
Please be the one to lead
the Neo Hundred.
I have made adjustments to CROWDS
in order to improve their safety.
It will be fine.
I will protect you if there is a need.
Umeda-san.
My dear comrade-in-arms,
let us remake this country together.
Just kidding!
The king of a faraway land
went to a large forest...
Let me have it, too!
Me, too!
I'm not an object!
Oh!
Pai-Pai looks like he's having fun!
How can I be having fun?
Do something about them!
They're just kids!
They're making way too much fun of me!
Are they?
When kids are out of control,
it might be because they want something.
Something? What's this something?
Love! It's love.
What?!
I've never heard of such
a convoluted life form!
Aren't you also making fun of me?
Huh, why?
Of course you would.
I abandoned you guys.
I'm not worthy to be your leader,
let alone to be a Gatchaman.
That's not true!
If you need to run,
you should run the best you can!
Then you can just take your time to think.
You guys are way too spoiled!
Good job, Sugane-chan.
Thank you.
I'm exhausted,
but this kind of thing isn't bad...
When people grow up,
they change in different ways,
but everyone used to run around
carefree like that before.
Well, I'm only half human,
so I only understand half of it all.
Compared to other animals,
humans have a longer childhood.
So I think that time leaves
a long lasting impression,
even after becoming adults.
We get really nostalgic.
True, humans are very sentimental.
Here, names and titles don't mean anything.
But that's how it used to be for everyone.
There were many different kinds
of people all jostling for space,
but things somehow worked out...
I'm kind of glad we came.
Sugane-chan,  you've changed.
What? Not really.
She totally fits right in, doesn't she?
I can't tell who's the kid
and who's the grown-up.
You're right.
Maybe Katze is like that, too.
Huh?
Maybe it's like a troublesome child.
Oh, just listen to me go on and on!
Forget what I said just now.
I'm going to run!
I'm going to run the best I can!
Hey, catch me if you can!
Wow, he's super fast!
The panda man's awesome!
See?!
Aren't I amazing?!
What are you doing?
Hey, can you write "grave" on this?
What? Grave?
Why?
Because Papa might die soon.
Is your Papa sick?
No.
It's because of GALAX.
Papa fell down when he was on GALAX.
He's been sleeping in the hospital ever since.