You've put on quite the
amusing farce, but enough.
For the false Spear Hero
and for the Devil of the Shield,
clinging so desperately
to life, like a cockroach,
the purification of Holy Judgment.
And...
For this country, righteous order!
Watch out, Naofumi!
That sword is...
What power!
The impact's making my arms go numb!
For a devil, you are pretty tough.
That'll be enough trial shots.
Now face the real thing.
Wh-What?
I-Is that...
The Rising of the Shield Hero
The Four Cardinal Heroes
H-Hey! That sword turned into a spear!
There's no mistaking it.
That's a replica of the Cardinal Weapons!
A... replica?
In the past,
an attempt was made to duplicate the
four weapons of the legendary heroes.
To make the ultimate weapon,
which could change forms and
use each weapon's skills.
I was taught that it was
lost many centuries ago.
That's not fair!
Say, Myne. Is it true?
H-How would I know?
It's so famous,
anyone dabbling in Melromarc's
and the Church's history would know of it.
Finding it should've been huge news.
But the Three Heroes Church kept it hidden.
Maybe its loss was a lie
made up by the Church, too.
Why'd you summon the heroes if
you had a weapon like that?
That weapon is mighty, but it
consumes a massive amount of mana.
Just that one swing earlier must've drained
dozens of magicians of their mana.
No wonder you're first in line
for the throne, Melty-sama.
You have educated yourself well.
Completely unlike your sister,
who was too busy conspiring to study.
The mana this legendary weapon requires
will be provided by all the believers here.
My brethren, this is a battle between
our lord and the Devil of the Shield.
It is a holy crusade in the name of God.
Offer your prayers to the legendary
weapon imbued with divine power.
And we shall purge this world of the fake
Spear Hero and the Devil of the Shield.
That'll be a pain to fight.
Melty! Can't you take those
believers out of the equation?
Put them to sleep or something!
I haven't learned any magics
that affect the mind.
And also...
Such a large mana pool will also
give them high resistance.
Putting them all to sleep
will be impossible.
There has to be something we can do.
I shan't stand for this!
You manipulate us for
your own selfish goals,
and want to get rid of us
as soon as you're done?
That's evil, through and through!
As a hero, I cannot overlook it!
Everything he says is hollow.
Spear guy's annoying.
Pope, I will defeat you
and avenge Itsuki and Ren!
Lightning Spear!
What? A barrier?
No fair!
We can't even scratch the pope unless
we break through that force field.
Melty's right.
We need to cut off the mana supply first.
If I can't do it alone...
Naofumi!
Huh?
Now is the time for us to work together.
Let's go!
You will pay for the sin of turning
against the next queen with your life.
As source of thy power, I order thee.
As source of thy power and the
next queen, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature
and burn my target down!
Sister...
Both spear guy and his party are annoying.
Zweit Fire!
A combo skill?
This is the end!
Burst...
Flare Lance!
Did we get him?
Nah.
How deplorable.
Instead of gracefully accepting God's mercy,
you pointlessly continue to resist.
But, of course, there will
be no mercy for a devil.
We'll see how pointless it is!
Meteor Thrust!
Even Meteor Thrust didn't work?
This magical barrier is impregnable.
It is no devil's shield, that is for sure.
Is that the believers' power, too?
They're using the massive pool of mana
to construct a powerful magical barrier.
It is my turn to attack now.
What do you say?
All this power, with a simple wave of my hand!
Using that weapon is cheating!
Fight us fair and square!
This power can even annihilate a devil.
I don't know if I can block a
full-power attack from that thing.
Not to mention, they have
an almost limitless pool of mana.
If he unleashes a volley of
attacks, we're finished.
What can we do?
The time has come to bestow
God's mercy on our foes!
Hundred Swords!
Meteor Shot!
Pope!
Those skills...
Looks like we made it in the nick of time.
Itsuki-sama!
Ren-sama!
You came back to life?
Don't just assume we're dead.
Hundred Swords!
Have half our magicians focus
on generating the barrier.
Are you sure?
It'll cause a long delay in the
mana supply to the weapon.
They'll need time, too.
Time to understand their sins
and realize they must pray
for the mercy of God.
As you say, Your Excellency.
That's annoying.
H-Hey, how are you guys here?
We did nearly get killed.
But their attempt failed.
That's all.
"That's all"?
Itsuki and I didn't trust the Three Heroes Church.
so we began investigating them in secret.
One of our party members found a secret
file in the Cathedral's archive.
It mentioned the existence of a
replica of the Cardinal Weapons,
so we decided to check out the
place where it was hidden.
They must have not taken kindly to that.
The Three Heroes Church
lured us to a fake shrine
and tried to assassinate us.
We barely escaped with our lives
thanks to a squad that called themselves
"Shadows" and said they served the Queen.
Those women were also keeping
tabs on Itsuki and Ren?
I think the Three Heroes Church
were the ones who stole my reward.
You were framed, Naofumi-san.
"Framed"?
You're the one who misunderstood
and came at me!
You were framed, huh?
You really have zero luck.
You were trying to kill me on a
false charge a moment ago, too!
Let's do this, Ren-san.
Yeah.
Meteor Shot!
Meteor Slash!
That consumed too much mana!
The pope's weapon!
Will he be all right?
The queen's punitive
force will be here soon.
The queen?
Mother's coming here?!
Yes. A Shadow tipped us off.
Surrender at once, and I'm sure
the queen will have mercy on you!
Drop your weapons and surrender!
Did he just say "punitive force"?
What's happening?
Fret not!
As I said earlier, this is a battle
between God and the Devil.
Of course it will be difficult.
However, our victory is guaranteed.
After all, we are the ones
blessed by God.
The queen's punitive force
is nothing to fear.
And it matters not how
many false heroes gather.
They are no match for us,
with our legendary weapon
and our faith in God!
Pope!
We'll follow God and you to the end!
What's wrong with them?
We're the legendary heroes.
Looks like they need to be taught a lesson.
If words won't get through to them,
we'll have to fight.
Yeah. As much as I hate it,
this is an emergency.
I'll even take your help.
Shall we, the four heroes...
...present a united front?
Melty, you provide magic support.
Got it.
Naofumi, what are you doing?
I'm not gonna play along with you idiots.
Hey, don't be selfish!
I don't wanna hear that from the guy who
tried to kill me when I refused to fight.
But don't you think
it's far too selfish to fight
alone in this situation?
Yeah, we can't win if we
don't fight together.
We can survive without your help.
No, you'll die for sure!
And you'll die framed for
a crime you didn't commit!
Are you okay with that?
You, of all people,
have no right to say that.
Spear guy's so annoying.
You're the ones who let the
Three Heroes Church throw their weight around!
Myne, who fell for the Church's schemes
and did whatever the hell she wanted,
is most at fault.
But Motoyasu, you're just as guilty
for letting her take you for a ride.
Wait a second! Me, deceive Motoyasu-sama?
Quit making baseless accusations!
But it seems the Spear Hero had no idea
what you were trying to do, Sister.
Y-Yeah! All I did was trust
in a member of my party!
I didn't do anything wro...
Accepting everything someone says blindly
without thinking for yourself
is completely different from trusting them.
If you'd used your brain even a little,
things wouldn't have come to this.
Naofumi's right.
There, there.
Motoyasu-san feels bad about it, too.
Give him a break for me.
You two are no different.
As I mentioned before,
after you killed that dragon,
its rotten flesh poisoned the air and
nearly wiped out an entire village.
That's...
Sure, in video games,
monsters you kill just disappear.
Their corpses don't remain and rot away.
But this is reality.
You should've faced up to that fact.
And Itsuki, your little
secret vigilante adventure
forced people to become refugees
and live in abject poverty.
But if I hadn't taught that lord a lesson,
the people would've suffered forever!
Hero powers won't solve everything.
You could've used your standing as a hero
to pressure the people in charge.
Wha...
You should've spared a moment to think
about how best to use your powers.
Decipher the laws of nature and
grant my target water's protection.
Aqua Shield.
Give Raphtalia and Filo shields, too.
Your thoughtless actions
are what let the Church think they could get away with this.
Wh-What were you doing, then?
Sorting out your messes.
Master was always mad,
saying he had to clean up after you.
Cleaning up after us?
Y-Yeah! It's your fault!
You're one to talk!
I wish you would understand your
current position a little.
Instead of fighting, you just wrapped
yourself around your girl's fingers.
Leave the girls out of this!
We're talking about all the trouble
you caused Naofumi right now!
If you wanna talk about trouble...
How about the time you thoughtlessly
passed out a sealed seed
and let an entire area be overrun by vines?
You caused the most trouble!
I-I only did that because the
villagers asked for help.
Sure, they had a legend saying
the seed was dangerous,
so the villagers are at fault for taking
it just because a hero gave it to them, too.
Right?
It just goes to show how immense the
people's trust in the heroes is.
You should've been more aware of that.
You three let your hero's
welcome go to your heads
and didn't spare a thought for anybody else.
As a result,
instead of teaming up to fight the Wave,
you just embarrassed yourselves.
Maybe you couldn't have taken that Glass woman,
but you could've easily defeated the
Soul Eater if you'd worked together.
As the Pope says,
it wouldn't be surprising if the
people got sick of heroes like you.
I don't really get it, but I do
know it's the spear guy's fault.
F... Filo-chan!
Don't say that! I was doing my best!
Huh? Master was working harder, though.
Dear me. I can hardly bear to watch.
You're fighting among
yourselves in this situation?
Our so-called heroes are an utter disgrace.
You really should be cleansed at once.
Fortunately, you gave us time
to generate enough mana.
Farewell, fake heroes!
And goodbye, Devil of the Shield!
I knew he'd use a magic attack!
Naofumi-sama,
here it comes.
Brionac!
You're the same.
In my eyes, you and that
pope are no different.
You use and abuse people
for your own benefit.
You brandish your powers for "justice,"
without caring about the consequences.
You see nothing wrong with that!
And more than anything...
You try to take the things
I hold dear from me.
You people are scum.
It is unacceptable for
heroes to be fighting.
I'll give it my best shot,
but don't get your hopes up.
Shield Hero, please...
But...
I'll work with you until we take
him out and get out of here alive.
Naofumi...
Don't get the wrong idea.
I haven't forgiven you.
But...
I did make Fitoria a promise.
The four heroes finally stand together now.
Yeah.
Don't hold me back, you guys.
Right back at you.
It's only until this battle is over.
Sure. I think that's for the best.
We need to do something about the
Pope and live to meet Mother.
I'll do my best!
Lend me your strength, girls.
Right!
Of course, Motoyasu-sama.
Let's do this.
Let's show them what we heroes are made of.
Raphtalia, Filo, Melty! Let's go!
Right!
Fighting together with
the Devil of the Shield?
A foolish act befitting the fake heroes.
You leave me no choice but to purge you.
Not a trace of you must remain.
We pray to our God, the source of all power.
Decipher the laws of nature,
bring about a miracle,
and protect the blessed ones!
High-Level Multi-Caster Defense Magic:
Cathedral!
Welcome to my Cathedral!
This is your final destination!
F-Final destination?
Battle of Good and Evil