Seijoh!
One-hand toss!
All right!
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
They're tied!
They caught up in the eleventh hour!
What was this called again?
A deuce!
The one to get a two-point lead...
...wins!
Haikyu!!
Episode 24: Removing The "Solitary King"
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
All right!
Oh, Seijoh!
Rule the Court
Aoba Johsai High School Volleyball Team
Seijoh!
Oh, Seijoh!
Don't panic! Make sure you call out!
Right!
You got this, right, Kunimi-chan?
Yes.
Hey! That was awesome, Hinata, Kageyama!
So Kunimi can also chase the ball now...
Go after it, to the very end!
Kitagawa Daichi
Kageyama!
I'm going to go for as many
broad attacks as possible,
until I make one!
Let's go!
Right!
Nice serve!
We've got the momentum!
Give it all you've got, Tanaka!
All right! Bring it!
Got it!
It's a little off!
Center!
Block! Block!
Fly
Chance ball!
One more!
Nice receive, Watari!
#10 is super-fast at returning.
Nice one touch!
One more time!
There's no point in leaving you open,
if I know you're gonna jump!
Hinata's jumps are running out of power!
The timing's going to be off!
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
All right!
Shoyo!
Hinata really saved us on that one!
That was awesome! Great job!
This time...
We're gonna finish this in one shot!
...Karasuno is the one checkmating.
Let's calm down. We'll get it back!
Right!
Tanaka, one more nice serve!
Hanamaki-san!
All right!
Aoba Johsai                     Karasuno
Even if they're tied, as long
as Seijoh doesn't pull ahead,
Karasuno will have the advantage.
Now...
And now, it's time for
Oikawa to serve again...
I won't let you guys attack as you wish.
We're going to win.
We're going to the next round.
Shiratorizawa                       Kitagawa Daichi
This time,
we're going to crush Shiratorizawa.
One more, and we'll regain the advantage!
Nishinoya!
Good call, Nishinoya!
Right.
He missed... Oikawa missed the serve.
Aoba Johsai                      Karasuno
Karasuno's at match point again.
If he missed a serve, when that's
his strong suit, maybe he's panicking a bit.
Yeah. Even Oikawa...
And that nullified it.
We each have one point now.
Iwaizumi-san, you're so cool!
I feel like I've lost to Iwa-chan.
When the hell did you ever beat me?!
Usually, the weight of a point from a break
or a side out would be heavier.
Overall, I'm always a winner.
Ow!
However, right now, the important thing is,
All right. Let's get one.
Right!
because of Iwaizumi's point and words,
the team was just saved from crumbling.
Are you sure Seijoh's
never been to nationals?
They're not breaking at all.
But that doesn't change
Seijoh's position at all.
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
Even if the physical fatigue
they're feeling is the same,
the mental fatigue that Seijoh
is feeling is much greater!
Get through this, Karasuno!
Rule the Court
Aoba Johsai High School Volleyball Team
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
Wow...
They went over 30 points!
This is rough on both of them.
But... I think Karasuno is
just barely keeping it together.
I think their attacks are
becoming simple, too.
Seijoh should be worse off,
mentally, but...
Oikawa-kun, nice serve!
Gah! That was one full rotation!
Nice serve!
He'll probably have
the missed serve on his mind,
One point!
so I wonder how Oikawa will do.
Oikawa, if you're staring at Ushiwaka's
face during the match, I'll punch you.
Someone who can't see the opponent
standing right in front him,
can't defeat the opponent that lies beyond!
You're right.
We'll turn this serve around!
Right!
Spring High School Volleyball
King
It's coming back! Chance ball!
Got it!
Despite the fact that he just messed up,
that was probably the best
serve he's done today.
Damn it! Sorry!
I'm glad you were even able
to put that serve up!
Calm down, calm down...
Got it!
Make sure you don't jump at a decoy!
Is it going to be a quick?
Or, considering the situation,
will it be an ace?
Left!
The opposite side?!
Again...
It's Kunimi?!
Kunimi!
Even if you know it's a decoy,
hit it over like you mean it.
But it was way obvious that they
were going to come up the left.
There's no point in getting
tired for no reason.
You're good, so why don't you play seriously?
So does always being reckless
equal being serious?
Chance ball!
Got it!
They still have energy to spare?
Kunimi-chan, you just skipped out
on being decoy didn't you?
I'm sor—
Skip out a bit better.
Mizoguchi-kun's gonna yell at you again.
Kunimi, you idiot!
Being efficient, conserving energy,
and always being calm are your
hidden weapons, Kunimi-chan.
But when everyone else is exhausted,
I'll make sure you work even harder.
You're only the setter if you can bring out
100% of all your teammates' ability.
No matter who the player is!
#13 again?!
A feint?!
Aoba Johsai                    Karasuno
Seijoh pulled ahead!
Seijoh's at matchpoint again!
Not to mention, Oikawa is serving again!
Just one more point! Just one more point!
We were on the same team for three years,
but today's the first time
I've ever seen him laugh normally during a match.
Hey, just listen...
Who the hell
are you?
How am I supposed to face someone like you?
Kageyama...
Kageyama-kun...
Kageyama-san!
Hey, are you freaking out? How lame!
Well, it's obivious that the Great King
is going to be better than the King.
It's in the names!
Not to mention, he seems
way smarter than you.
Sorry, Kageyama!
I'll make sure I get the ball
back to you next time.
Then, all you need to do is
the attack you think is best.
Kageyama! Stop hesitating!
Everyone on our team is...
...strong, as they should be.
Do you think the King is
scared of the Great King?
It's okay.
Kageyama's not the Lonely King anymore.
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
Go, go, go! Go, go, Seijoh!
Come on, bring it!
Push it, push it, push it!
Push it, push it, Seijoh!
Bring it!
We're gonna get that point!
Push it, push it, push it!
Push it, push it, Seijoh!
Yeah!
Man...
Talk about annoying.
Nice serve!
Tobio...
One point!
I might actually lose to you,
Come on, bring it!
considering how quickly you evolve.
But...
Front!
It went up!
But it's messed up!
They won't be able to use a quick!
In this tense situation,
he still managed to find the smallest gap
and pulled off a feint.
His calm focus on victory is terrifying.
Left!
Center!
Asahi, go!
Connect! Connect!
Iwa-chan!
It went u— Ah!
Do it, Kindaichi!
My speed and reflexes always lose to you.
But...
But in a battle of height...
I won't lose!
It went up!
All right!
Kindaichi, Kunimi!
Right!
Left!
Now! In this position, with this timing,
this angle...
Dead on!
Tobio...
I might actually lose to you,
considering how quickly you evolve.
But...
That won't be today!
All right!
Let's go.
Hinata, Kageyama, we need to line up.
Captain, I'm sor—
That wasn't a mistake.
It wasn't a mistake, so don't apologize.
Thank you very much!
Everyone, just listen.
The next time that Karasuno looks
like they're going to use a quick,
Tobio will use the god-like quick.
Keep that in your heads.
How did you know the last one
would be a god-like quick?
Because Tobio evolved thanks to
all of the players in Karasuno.
He's starting to learn how
to trust for the first time.
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
When the deuces continued,
his physical and mental
fatigue were at their peak.
In the eleventh hour,
when they were cornered,
it was then they were given a crucial chance.
At that moment, Tobio...
only had one choice.
Line up!
Thank you very much!
Great work!
That was a great match!
Round up!
When we lost...
I hated being told we had a great match.
It was like, "but we lost."
However, being on the side to say that now,
I guess I don't know what else to say.
Um, that last block...
We need to clear out immediately.
The next team's warm-up is starting.
We'll start our cool down
upstairs or outside.
Seijoh will be going to the
quarterfinals after a short break.
"Even if one person is good,
you can't win. Don't mind."
Isn't that what you were going to tell them?
But Karasuno had more than one
strong player, didn't they?
You're really annoying.
How rude!
The end of that second set...
When he was able to read my toss to you,
I could tell that Tobio was trying to go
from being a dictator to a decent king.
Even if Tobio had stayed a dictator,
he might have still tossed
to the shrimp in the end.
I only thought it was a possibility,
and there was no guarantee
he was going to do it.
He was reading my attacks, but this time,
he ended up having his
attack being read by me.
So Kageyama has finally
started trusting other people...
Really...
Nothing could be more troublesome.
The meeting's starting.
Sorry.
They totally read me in the end.
Don't apologize!
Don't... Don't make it sound like
tossing to me was a mistake!
The meeting's about to start.
Both of you were amazing today.
But we lost...
Indeed, we lost.
But it was a worthwhile match, wasn't it?
Does losing prove that you're weak?
Isn't losing difficult for all of you?
A challenge where, after ending
up on your hands and knees,
you must see if you can stand-up again?
If you stay on your hands and knees,
that proves that you are weak.
Senseki                              Aoba Johsai
All right, let's go get some food.
Of course, I'm paying.
Eh? Food? But...
Just shut up and eat.
Closed
Izakaya
Osuwari
Sorry, Ma'am, for coming in
right before you open up.
Don't worry. This used
to happen all the time.
Running, jumping, and anything else
that stresses your muscles
will cause the fibers to tear.
Right after a match, like now,
your muscle are at their limits,
so you've got to repair them by eating.
That's how you build muscle,
and become stronger.
So eat. Eat a proper meal.
Th-Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food.
Enjoy!
Eat.
Eat...
A little at a time.
But, be sure...
...to grow stronger.
Next Episode Preview
Ukai-kun, I'll cover this...
Don't worry about it!
Hey, Ma'am, can I get the check?
Here you go. I gave you quite a discount.
Thank you!
Gah! Those guys ate a lot!
Next time on Haikyu!!: "The Third Day."
Episode 25: "The Third Day"