Wood Shop
Wow, this is...
Right?
Doesn't it look awesome?
Ready, and...
We did it!
Episode Seven: The Ofunehiki Shakes
You guys did a great job.
It's all thanks to me and Miuna.
Really? You're actually saying that?
This really is amazing.
I'm touched.
Right?
We really worked hard.
It was a lot more fun
than I thought it'd be.
All right.
This calls for some popsicles.
Huh?
I'll treat you guys!
Do you want Gori Gori-kun
pops or Homebase Bars?
So cheap!
Er, Sensei, it's too cold
for popsicles today.
We even canceled swimming today.
Right...
But sadly, they don't sell
meat buns this time of year.
I want to do the Ofunehiki...
They said that in unison.
Hot damn!
Talk about close.
They've totally got the hots for each other.
Th-That's not true! It's not like that!
Now, now, trying to play it off.
I wonder how far they've gone.
Ow!
That hurt...
That hurt a lot more than
I thought it would...
Well, we are going to do it in a sense...
No, I don't mean that...
But what you taught us in
class that they used to do.
With the sea and the surface
working together...
Couldn't we do that?
Hey, that sounds like a great idea!
Since we went through all the trouble,
it'd be nice to see a real Ofunehiki.
But we wouldn't be able to do it
without help from Shioshishio...
so it'd be a little hard.
But if we're going to do it,
we want to do it right.
Right, guys?
Yeah, since we came this far.
Yeah.
I understand. I really do understand...
But because of the disagreements
Shioshishio village and the Oshiooshi
fishery cooperative have,
they're saying there
won't be one this year.
Let's do it!
We went through all this
trouble making it...
Let's do it! A real Ofunehiki!
Hey, Hikari...
Hii-kun!
I'll do something about Shishio.
Tsumugu, you be the leader and
do something about Oshiooshi.
Hikari...
You say that, but I think
it'd be pretty hard...
I know, but...
I don't like doing
things only halfway.
Even if it's hopeless, I want to at least try
everything we can do to finish with no regrets.
All right, I'm in!
Me, too!
Tsumugu, you're in, right?
I don't mind.
Me too!
Sounds good to me.
Great... This is great!
This will be great!
Yeah!
This is indeed youth!
All right. I'll help out as well.
Let's all do our best!
Yeah!
That was great, Hii-kun!
Everyone's so great!
I'll make sure that
the Ofunehiki happens.
Yeah!
The thing that you and
Tsumugu wished for...
Association to Make the Ofunehiki a Reality
Please!
Let's make the Ofunehiki
a reality again this year!
Please help us get enough signatures!
Please help us out!
All right, we're not going
to lose! Right, Miuna?
Let's make the Ofunehiki
a reality this year!
R-Right...
Please help us out!
Please help us o—
You're going to scare
people off doing that!
Please help us out!
We're trying to do the Ofunehiki!
Th-The Ofunehiki...
Here!
Thank you!
Good work, keep it up!
Please help us out!
We are Hama Junior High's
"Association to Make the Ofunehiki a Reality."
Please help us out!
I heard they weren't
going to do it this year.
As Hama Junior High's volunteers,
we plan on doing something
even bigger than last year!
Can you middle schoolers
manage it by yourselves?
Please sign!
We're serious about this.
Please help us out.
Guess I don't have a choice.
Thank you very much!
Hikari's sort of amazing.
Thank you!
Why is he so serious about this?
I think he probably wants to get rid of
his frustrations so he's going all out.
To think that Hikari has
such a competitive side...
Humans really are pretty deep.
Ma'am. Pardon me, Ma'am.
Do you have a moment?
W-Well, if it's just for a moment...
Talk about "deep"...
I need to try hard, too.
We're doing the Ofunehiki...
I don't think that really suits you.
Huh?
Is that really the point here?
I mean... everyone
can only do what they can.
If you try hard at something you
can't do, it only hurts in the end.
You're all really going at it.
Pretty impressive.
Dad!
Akari-san, thank you for
talking to the manager for us.
Don't worry about it.
Not to mention Sayama-kun, the
manager's son, is helping out, too.
And I'd like to see it, too...
A real Ofunehiki.
Then, could you display these in the store?
You got it! Leave it to me.
Give me some of those forms, too.
I'll get you some signatures.
Could I get some, too?
I'll hand them out to people I know.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I mean, having the people of the
surface and sea hand in hand...
It sort of hits pretty close to home.
I want to do the Ofunehiki.
I'm going to make it happen.
I look forward to it.
It's not happening.
Why not?!
We got this many signatures!
You can at least talk to
the fishing association!
It doesn't matter how
many signatures you get.
Let's Do An Ofunehiki This Year!!
"Association to Make the Ofunehiki A Reality"
The Ofunehiki is one of our historical traditions!
It was Oshiooshi that said they wouldn't
do it this year in the first place.
B-But...
Come on, Dad.
This is the first time Hikari's been so
serious about asking you for something.
What kind of parent does it make
you if you don't at least listen?
I saw them collecting signatures myself,
and they were working really hard.
The people on the surface won't listen.
There's no point in talking to them.
Dad!
I thought that the guys on the
surface were all pigs at first, too...
That there's no point
in talking to them.
And they thought of us as fish...
so we were even.
But I was wrong!
We're not fish, and they're not pigs!
We're all humans that can
communicate with each other!
We're really serious about this!
It can be just once!
Please get everyone
together and talk to them!
You're going to rely on me?
Then we don't need your help!
Just don't get in our way, then!
So everything went okay with
the fishery cooperative?
It really wasn't that hard.
Right?
Even if people couldn't really
talk about the Ofunehiki,
they seemed to be concerned about it.
And what about your end?
My stupid dad wouldn't listen,
but the Young Men
Coalition heard me out.
If I mention that the people of
the surface already agreed to it,
it'll work out somehow.
All right. It's finally show time, then!
We're gonna do the Ofunehiki!
Yeah!
All right, time for food!
Hopefully everything works out.
If we don't hurry up and eat,
there won't be any time to play.
But they're all so stubborn...
Just watch. I'm going
to make this happen.
Hikari's working really hard...
Yeah...
But Hii-kun's sort of... um...
Different, isn't he?
Different?
Oh, I mean Hii-kun is always
trying really hard...
But um... this seems to be a
different kind of trying hard...
Um...
I think...
He's trying to change.
Change?!
I don't want to change.
I want all of us to be together forever.
Ch-Change? That's not good!
We need to hurry and stop Hii-kun!
Stop him and rewind!
I don't think we can do that.
But...
Thanks, Manaka.
Chii-chan...
There are some things that
change even if we don't want them to...
But once someone decides they're going
to change and work really hard at it,
I don't think even the
Sea God could stop them.
Wow, they did a great job on this.
That's pretty impressive.
Not bad at all.
I think we could actually use this.
Look at all the details.
To think that they were able to get
Hikari's dad to come out, too...
I'm getting nervous.
Me too. I sort of want
to go take a piss.
Then go already, jeez!
They even prepared offerings...
When we were kids, we made all of these
little things too, didn't we, Sakishima?
Why'd you come?
You... really made all this?
Yeah.
The four of us and our friends from
the surface all worked together.
I see... So that's why.
Ojoshi-sama's kimono's
fold is backwards.
Huh?
What?!
Wh-What are we going to do, Chii-chan?!
We sewed it so the left
would be in front!
Ojoshi-sama's going to die!
Wha— Calm down!
We can fix that in no time.
Hikari...
Talk about a preemptive strike.
No worries!
We're just getting started.
It appears that everyone is ready now.
I'll be moderating the meeting today.
So, what do you all think?
The students worked really
hard to make this.
So as their teacher, I'd really
like to see their dream come true.
Well, we never objected to doing the
Ofunehiki in the first place.
Yeah.
And festivals shouldn't be disregarded.
And it's not like we're
going to neglect the god.
Yeah, of course.
Hey, Sakishima.
The kids went so far to do this.
A lot's happened, but
why don't we let it go?
Yeah.
Well, go ahead and start.
But it's already started...
Not that.
I'm saying that we'll listen
to your apology now.
What?
Apology?
We came all the way here.
Apologize to your heart's content.
Our hearts are as wide as the sea.
It'll probably be a little
rude, but we'll hear it out.
Why would we have to apologize?
You're the ones that said you wouldn't
do the festival in the first place.
Hold on a second.
Are you trying to say you don't
remember the last Ofunehiki?
You guys were complaining about
how there wasn't enough money
or enough people, and you asked
to scale things down, didn't you?
Not to mention this happened
time after time...
At that rate,
even if we hadn't said we
weren't going to do it,
Hey, this doesn't look
very good, does it?
you guys would have said it yourselves.
That's not true!
Please wait!
This isn't a gathering to say who
should apologize or who's at faul—
Stay out of it, kid!
Anyway, you're the ones
who called it off first.
It's only natural that you apologize.
Not to mention,
the reason we don't have
enough people or any money
is because ya'll keep
taking them from the top!
That's right!
Both our fish and our women!
What?
The reason your women run off is
because you guys aren't reliable, isn't it?
You're gonna blame us for that, too?
What'd you just say?!
Looks like it's gonna rain...
You're going to come, too?
Yeah.
Hikari worked really hard...
so I want to help if I can.
Also,
I really want to show
Miuna-chan an actual Ofunehiki.
Maybe it's because of our roots.
There's that, and if
Miuna-chan is ever lost...
I thought it could be like
a light in her heart.
Akari...
Thank you...
For thinking about Miuna.
All right, let's go in.
The hell are you saying, fish head?
Excuse u—
Shut up, you pigs!
All your squealing's annoying!
All right then.
Why don't we settle
things once and for all?
What'd you just say?!
Is this a bad time?
Whoa.
That sucks.
Itaru-san...
Talk about bad timing...
Hey! You're the guy Akari's seeing!
Um...
You thief!
Thie—
We've got plenty of things
we want to say to you!
Get over here!
Hey!
What's going on here? Hikari! Dad!
Would you guys stop already?!
You're adults, aren't you?
Why can't you talk things out?!
Stay out of the way!
Are you satisfied?
Looking for Part-Timers!
Break up with him.
As Hikari said, because we're not fish or pigs,
we can understand each other...
But it's because we can communicate,
that we realize there are
differences we can never get over.
People from the sea and people from
the surface will never see eye to eye.
I always... thought
something was different.
I finally realize what it was.
I'm talking about Itaru-san and myself.
And yet, you always change the
subject to the sea and the surface.
I asked Mom a long time ago...
why she married you.
She said... the reason was simple.
She married you just because she loved you.
When I heard that, I was happy.
Because of that, I just
happened to ask her,
what if you were from the surface.
And then Mom just smiled and said...
"Even then, I would have
been with your father."
I'm going to be Miuna-chan's mother.
Are you leaving?
Yeah...
I'm sorry, Hikari.
You don't need to apologize.
Because I'm leaving, too.
But—
Being left alone with Dad...
I know that there's no way
things will be normal.
All right.
I see, so she said she's going to leave.
Look.
The shaking's gotten more pronounced.
There isn't much more time.
What are you going to do, Tomoru?
Uroko-sama.
Are you leaving?
Yes.
Would you consider changing your mind?
I will not.
But you're still under my protection.
Thank you for everything
that you've done for me.
But I've decided.
I will live life on the surface.
Thank you.
I'm not coming back, either.
Apparently everyone in
the family is stubborn.
Good grief.
Akari!
Hikari!
Uroko-sama!
We must do everything we can.
Why not give up?
No good will come of you
going up to the surface.
There will!
There's someone up there
who's waiting for me!
Uroko-sama! Why are you
trying to stop us?!
Because of a promise.
A promise?
I have to protect you both...
as you are his descendants.
Damn it!
You leave me no choice.
What?
The water temperature suddenly...
This isn't good...
At this rate, we'll freeze...
Like hell I'm going to give up!
I don't want to be... forced
into the flow anymore.
Well, well, they're definitely
giving it their all.
Uroko-sama!
Show some mercy... Please.
Akari, now!
R-Right!
Are you certain?
I want a shell from the sea that I love.
I don't want you to go through
the same thing, Akari.
I don't care if I can't
go back to the sea.
What's wrong with those
two being together?
Episode Eight:
Beyond the Wavering Feelings