No! I don't want to die!
Shut up!
Let go! This is why I
didn't want to come here!
Kimari-san...
Shut up! If you want her to
live, fork over the cash!
Help me! I have a turtle
and a hamster who need me!
I'm sorry, I'm just a temp. You'll want
to talk to the banking manager...
This is no time to be playing around.
You're still laughing?!
She's right. It's not nice
to keep laughing at her...
Yuzuki-chan. That's the kind
of thing that hurts most...
Can you hear me?
There it is!
Kimari!
Rin! Mom!
What happened to your face?
We've gotta take a picture!
That's the first thing you have
to say after all this time?
Sis, are you gonna do your New Year's
Eve broadcast looking like that?
My stomach hurts!
We're working on it...
Next. Miyake-san?
Yes?
Some friends of yours heard about this
relay test and came to talk to you.
Friends?
Of mine?
Miyake-san, it's been so long!
We haven't heard from you for
so long, so we were worried.
What is it?
Did it go down?
Hinata?
Ouchies! My leg's cramped!
Shirase, sorry, you take over!
Hey! Hinata!
New Year's Card from Antarctica
Time Table
Program
Introduction
Introduce the Syowa Base Post Office
~Japan's most southern post box~ by: Shiraishi Yuzuki
Recap episode of the girls' Antarctica report by: Shiraishi Yuzuki
Messages from Japan to the crew
Messages from family members for Tamaki Mari
Messages from Hanyu Daisan High School Track Team for Miyake Hinata
Messages from the National Institute of Polar Research
for the Challenge for Antarctic Crew
Introduce life in Antarctica
A Place Further Than the Universe
Bash That Drum Can!
12 Likes
22 Comments
#Ghosting #Jantei #Satellite Peace #WatchForAnimals
It's here.
That's all the extra stuff we needed
brought by DROMLAN from Japan
on its way to the new station.
Which means we have everything we need now.
Of course, we won't be able
to create an observatory
that can see the stars this year right away.
But a few years from now, if we try for it...
We should go, shouldn't we?
I think that's what everyone wants, at least.
Still... that's the place where Takako died.
It's not safe at all.
What should we do?
New Year's
From Syowa Station
This is awful!
I bet Mom's spreading it all
over social media right now!
What's the big deal? It makes better
advertising for the broadcast.
Hinata?
Oh... do mine, too!
Oh? Your only New Year's
card is to your manager?
None for your friends from earlier?
Well... they're New Year's cards,
but they won't reach anyone until
the boat gets back to Japan anyway.
I'm gonna hit the can!
Ouch!
Stupid thing...
Is she annoyed?
Did it hurt that much?
She seems a bit stressed out.
Shirase-chan, you're going, too?
Piss off!
Piss off, damn it!
Stupid thing!
Piss off!
There you are!
The weather's cleared up,
so they said they'd bring us along for
the sea ice and geological testing!
I'll prepare the camera,
so think about your report!
Huh? Oh. Right.
Expedition! Expedition!
Don't forget, you said you'd do the report!
Don't claim later that
you don't want to do it!
Um... Hinata...
About before...
That was a test, so it won't cut the mustard.
No—
Hurry up! They're heading out soon!
Coming!
We did this together three years ago.
Takako-senpai just wanted to do everything.
She did?
Yeah, she went all over.
She was here, too, Shirase-chan!
Isn't that nice?
Yeah...
Take that!
What's that?
It's all ice up ahead, so we're
digging a hole with steam.
After that, I think we went to Rundvågshetta.
Sounds like a powerful name!
It's a place with exposed rock.
If you ask Nobue-san,
she might take you there.
Let's go!
Sea Ice here! Nobue-san at geology?
Do you read? Over!
Haven't heard from him since Christmas.
The garnet he gave me two years ago...
Dry rocks and dry love...
No email. No nothing from Yu-kun.
She's currently unable to talk. Over.
It's cold!
Seriously. The difference in
air temperature is extreme...
Please, stop it!
Look! It's amazing!
So cold!
Watch for animals
Antarctica really is amazing, huh?
It's neat to see it from this angle...
The sky is flowing by!
I wonder if we'll see an aurora?
At night, maybe.
But it won't become night
during the time we're here.
Hinata.
Is something bothering you?
Bothering me?
Well, my lips get so
chapped with the dry air,
but my lip balm is frozen,
so it's hard to put on.
I know how you feel!
It really is hard!
It's like your skin is peeling off.
Right?
So dry!
Be Careful Going Outside
All crew outdoors, please seek
shelter in the main building
or a building with emergency rations.
It's not getting better at all.
You should probably give up on it.
Where'd Shirase go, anyway?
Someone asked her earlier if
she knew how to play Mahjong...
For real? Can she?
It sounded fun, so I looked
over her shoulder, but...
Hey, how do you read the one that
looks like a person next to a five?
"Go."
Hey, you've got some white ones
mixed up in your reserves.
They're not reserves.
That bird is so cute!
"Get out!"
...she said.
That's rather cruel.
Right? I was only asking questions!
Shirase's always been testy!
Block List
Misato   Edit
Ayaka    Edit
Satsuki    Edit
Delete
Block and Delete
No kidding!
Ron.
Menhon, Double South,
Three Dora nets me 16,000 points.
Are you for real?
Hey, have you been playing with
Takako since you were little?
Yes, once in a while...
Let's quit. We can't win.
Jantei
Not against the daughter of Gin and Takako...
Is Miyake-san here?
She's probably in the bath.
What's up?
We got an email from her
friends addressed to the base.
Friends?
National Antarctic Research Center
Re: About the broadcast timetable
(To Miyake Hinata) Hanyu Daisan High School Track Team
National Antarctic Research Center
Re: About the broadcast timetable
Declare all accounts online
Declare all accounts offline
Get new mail
Link accounts
Empty the trash can
Empty the spam folder
New mailbox
New smart mailbox
National Antarctic Research Center
Re: About the broadcast timetable
(To Miyake Hinata) Hanyu Daisan High School Track Team
National Antarctic Research Center
Re: About the broadcast timetable
None to the base, either...
He said he'd write me every day...
Want to use it?
Please.
National Antarctic Research Center
(To Miyake Hinata) Hanyu Daisan High School Track Team
Re: About the broadcast timetable
National Antarctic Research Center
(To Miyake Hinata) Hanyu Daisan High School Track Team
Re: About the broadcast timetable
you quit the track team and
quit school so suddenly
We wish we'd said something to the older girls.
We're sorry for leaving you all alone.
Shirase?
Are you...
Hinata-chan?
National Antarctic Research Center
(To Miyake Hinata)
You saw it?
Just a little.
But that was addressed to Hinata-san...
How could you do something like that?
But... but I was worried, so...
You seemed so mad about something, and...
you wouldn't say anything...
You were mad?
What, you saw it?
You should have said something!
I was worried.
I thought you were hiding something!
Something you weren't telling us!
We're sorry for leaving you all alone.
Let me tell you in advance,
it's a totally gross story.
I don't want to talk about it,
and I hate that you asked me.
Just tell us.
In short, it's about why
I stopped going to club.
It's the competition,
so the fastest people should go.
Your year and stuff doesn't matter!
But for the third-years,
this will be their last competition...
Exactly! It would be more
rude to go easy on them!
Two hundred meter, Miyake Hinata.
Yes!
Didn't you say something to that idiot?
O-Of course... we told
her to be more sensitive...
In that instant, nothing mattered to me.
But it does matter!
They're the ones to blame.
Humans can be scary, huh?
After I quit, they kept spreading all
kinds of rumors to lay the blame on me.
Is that why you quit school?
Hinata.
Sorry I'm a loser!
Then the ones who sent the email are...
Yeah. My old teammates.
They want to talk during the broadcast.
They said they were proud their
friend went to Antarctica.
Though mainly, I was thinking
"Oh, were we friends?"
Well?
What? Different from what you imagined?
It's almost otherworldly, huh?
Oh, uh, yeah!
What an unusual color!
We'll set up a tent and
antenna down that way.
Okay!
Hey!
How long are you gonna
drag this out? Forget it.
I don't like being treated this way.
But...
Look, why do you think I came to Antarctica?
Because there's nothing here!
I wanted to go to an empty place
with no one to tie me down!
Look, isn't it amazing?
Glaciers! Strata! Water from melted snow!
Colors and shapes I've never seen before!
We're in a place isolated
from everything we know,
a completely different world
from where we've been before.
That's what I came here to enjoy!
But it doesn't mean anything
if you're all sad, right?
Got it. Then we'll forget it!
First, we've got camping to do!
It's not a game!
Shirase?
It does mean something.
It absolutely does mean something!
It's like a sci-fi movie, isn't it?
Want to drink the water? It's delicious.
We can drink it?
In a way, it's the cleanest
water on the planet.
Hardly anyone's ever touched it,
and it doesn't get warm
enough to breed bacteria.
I'm first!
No fair!
How is it?
Delicious!
I want to try, too!
You're right! It's delicious and cold!
It really hits the spot!
Want some, Shirase-chan?
Later.
We got through.
Talk.
Me?
U-Um... this is Kobuchizawa at Rundvågshetta.
Over.
This is Syowa. We read you loud and clear.
How is the scenery? Over.
Um... It's like we're surrounded by cake.
Cake?
Takako said the same thing.
The minute we got there,
"I want to eat chocolate cake!"
My mother said that?
It's the best natural water I've ever had!
Like this?
Perfect.
Kimari-san, you're good
at the strangest things.
That's not strange, is it?
Can they see this on the satellites?
Yes. We use these so they can check
our location on the satellites.
It will definitely show up.
It's not taking it now.
Yu-kun...
Yu-kun!
Um...
Don't let it bother you.
She does this constantly.
We even put a plate here.
Someone's watching, huh?
It's nothing personal, okay?
What bliss!
Especially since it's getting colder.
And now it's time for...
Ta-da!
Next time we get hot water
going, let's make tamagoyaki!
You really like tamagoyaki, huh?
She did eat a lot of it for
breakfast in Singapore!
Hinata.
I'm going to collect water. Come with me.
We don't have enough?
Sorry I used it all earlier...
Kimari-san.
Wow, it's freezing when the wind blows.
I could just die right now!
I've been thinking about what
I'd do in your position.
We're sorry for leaving you all alone.
If someone had treated me so awfully,
then called me up out of the blue,
as though nothing happened,
wanting to apologize for the
permanent damage they'd done...
Hey, look...
I couldn't be okay with it.
I couldn't smile.
You're not me, though.
I know, but...
Shirase.
Take off your gloves.
Hand them over.
Your hands are enough.
Shirase, you're so annoying,
the way you keep talking and talking.
Thanks.
I'm sorry. I guess I'm still scared.
Hinata...
I'm scared.
But we...
I said your hands were enough, remember?
Thanks for bringing me along.
Tamagoyaki's ready!
Okay! We're on our way!
C'mon!
12/31
Choose Your Own New Year's Soba
Tempura
Mochi
Plain
You suck! They're not supposed
to be flat noodles!
They're thin enough!
Start from scratch.
Really?!
Ready to roll in ten minutes.
Understood!
My sun tan never recovered...
It's proof that you're
enjoying Antarctica.
Hey.
Do you think I'll feel
better if I forgive them?
You want to forgive them?
If it would make me feel better, I might.
But when I imagine them looking all relieved
afterwords, it gets under my skin.
"Piss off"?
Yeah.
I'm a pretty petty person, aren't I?
It's 9:00 AM here.
A six-hour difference from Japan...
Before we start, may I say one thing?
Shirase-chan?
I beg your pardon, but could
you leave Miyake Hinata alone?
Shirase...
You might think Hinata has been holding a
grudge against you since she quit school,
that she's been suffering badly.
Maybe you think she spends every day crying,
thinking about what happened to her.
But...
But that's not true!
Hinata-chan is having a super,
amazing fun time with us!
She's having a really fulfilling trip
of the sort you can't get where you are!
Hey!
Hinata is already looking forward!
She's already walking!
She's taking her steps with us!
Shirase!
It's fine! It's friendship!
Unlike Hinata, I'm a real jerk,
so I'll say it outright.
You can't live your lives in
this halfway state forever!
You hurt someone and made them suffer!
Now you get to live with that!
That's what you get for hurting someone!
That's what you get for hurting my friend!
Shirase!
You think you can come crawling back now?
Piss off!
Let's get things ready.
Okay.
The year is nearing its end.
Will it be on TV?
Last year's video, yeah.
It's here!
Yu-kun! Yu-kun! Yu-kun!
Let's do it, too!
Casting away our worldly desires!
You mean...
...like this?
Let's bash the bad thoughts
away, Hinata-chan!
What if we break it?
So what if you do? It's just a drum can.
Good point!
Okay, let's do the first one together!
One, two...
A Place Further
Than the Universe