What is it, Pega?
Look at the sky?
Yeah... the Sky Sea is too quiet, huh?
Did something happen to
the Priestess of the Sky?
The Star Whale in the Sky Sea
Anyway, Adel-sama and her friend's
adventures were amazing, weren't they?
Yeah.
It was truly a heroic tale.
They saved the world and changed the world
when they were about our age.
Risking their own lives, too.
Yeah.
We need to be like them.
We need to bring good things not just
to our own country, but to the continent.
Yeah!
Leo-nee! Nanami!
Good morning!
Huh? Where are Shinku and Leaf?
Practicing swordsmanship, I'm told.
Prince Gaul went with them, too.
They can't interfere with us girls talking,
supposedly.
I see.
What was that?
I don't know.
The priestess!
And the fire dragon!
Wow!
Leaders of the three countries! Heroes!
I'm sorry to appear so suddenly.
Would you hear what I have to say?
The Sky Sea has been acting
strange since last night.
The Sky Sea?
You need a simple explanation.
And me and Rebecca are the
perfect ones to give it to you!
We just studied it!
Ta-dah!
There's a sea called the Sky Sea
above Flognarde's skies.
It's a sea, but that doesn't
mean there's water.
The space between the floating
islands and the clouds,
and the creatures and
spirits that live there...
They're born in the Sky Sea,
and sleep in the Sky Sea.
There's a mysterious and
wonderful ecology up there!
There are no countries or
territory in the Sky Sea,
but there's something there that
is in charge of the peace.
And that's the star whale!
A huge flying spirit,
bigger than a mountain!
We surface academics call it a spirit,
but there are also theories that it's
the servant of an ancient god,
or a type of dragon.
It's older than people, of course, but
it's also older than the True Dragons.
The Star Whale has lived in
Flognarde for a long, long time.
Several times a year, you can see it
swimming in the sky from the surface.
And so, just like there's a Dragon Priestess
that connects the people and the dragons,
there is a Sky Priestess who connects
the Star Whale and the surface,
it's said.
If something happens above the sky,
the Sky Priestess will tell us.
I see.
Well, the Sky Priestess is
just a story in picture books.
Nobody knows if she exists.
It's such a romantic story, though.
You can tell how the weather
and temperature will change by
looking at the movement of the
stars and the state of the sky.
That might be where the legend comes from.
That's right.
Um... the Sky Priestess is real.
I've met her.
What?
Pega is a messenger from the stars,
created by the Sky Priestess.
Wow!
I had no idea!
Pega tells me something might've
happened to the Sky Sea.
It might be to the environment where the
Star Whale lives, or to the Star Whale itself,
or maybe to the Sky Priestess...
I'd like to go see what it is.
The Star Whale is above these
three countries right now.
I'd like permission from you
to investigate your skies.
Of course.
No problem.
No problem, but...
Don't tell me you're going alone.
If you're going on a sky
adventure, we'll follow you!
We'll be great to have around in
an investigation or an adventure!
I thought you'd say that.
This is the Dragon Priestess's job,
but it would good to have
the Heroes along, too.
Yeah.
Then Couver, Milfi, shall we go, too?
Yes!
Of course!
Is what I'd like to say...
But I have a bunch of work I have to do.
That's true for all three of us.
You're right.
You guys can stay in your countries.
This is a Hero's job.
That's right.
It would be better to
have more people, right?
And you'll need a researcher!
Onmitsu will be useful, too.
Then the members will be the
priestess, the three Heroes,
Genoise, Rico, and Yukikaze.
Of course, Leaf and I will go,
too. It's okay, right?
Yeah.
You're going as a representative
of Galette, Gaul.
Got it.
Prince Leaf, use your bow
and ears to help everyone.
Right!
Um... which means...
Yes.
A problem with the Sky Sea is a problem
not just for our three countries,
but for the whole continent!
We'll be ready to go,
if there's an emergency.
And we'll have the priestess
lead a team to investigate it.
Got it, everyone?
Right!
Okay, Sky Sea investigation team!
Off we go!
Everybody, hang on tight!
Don't let go of the ropes!
Right!
Rico, what's in the box?
A box of secret machines I prepared
with the people of Pastillage.
It's filled with useful items
to help with the investigation!
That's great!
Really!
It feels like being on a plane!
Yeah!
The humidity's terrible.
Clouds are clumped up
water vapor, after all.
I guess the fire dragon
doesn't like the water.
We'll get out of the clouds quickly.
I'm going faster.
Everybody okay?
I think!
Our trip to the Sky Sea is a little rough!
I'm used to flying, so I'm still okay, but...
We're almost out of the clouds!
This is the Sky Sea.
I've never seen it before!
It's beautiful!
It's pretty, isn't it?
Yeah.
Pictures! Pictures! I need to take pictures!
I want to, too!
So where's the Star Whale?
I can see it. It's there.
It's huge!
It's even bigger up close.
Yes.
You're right, its color is strange.
Is it?
Normally, it shines more.
It's pretty, like the starry sky.
Is it sick?
I'm worried.
If we meet the priestess
we can talk to her, right?
Where is she?
Inside the Star Whale.
We're going inside it.
I remember how to get to
where the priestess is.
Is it okay?
Is it going to eat us by accident?
It's fine.
From the Star Whale's perspective,
even the fire dragon's the
size of a grain of dust.
And I've heard
it almost never eats anything anyway.
That's right.
Yeah, but I'm still scared.
It's okay.
With the fire dragon's wings,
it will just take a second.
It really is huge, though.
I wonder how many times bigger
it is than an Earth whale.
What? What?
What's this sound?
I don't know.
Um... it's opening its mouth.
What do we do? Get a little further back?
Yeah, that would be a good—
Is it sucking us in?
Seems like it!
Fire dragon, get us out of here!
Rico!
Yuki-chan!
Where are we... Everybody?
That was awful.
Looks like we got separated
from the people of Galette.
Where are we, anyway?
Inside the star whale.
This doesn't look like the
inside of a living thing.
Even if it's dark, I'm surprised
there's any light at all.
There are a lot of light spirits.
Normally, it's a lot brighter...
For now, let's find Gaul and the others.
Brave Connect, on!
Becky! Shinku!
Are you all okay?
Are you okay, Nanami?
Who's with you?
This is what we've got.
We protected Rico-yan's secret
box of machines with our lives!
Thank you!
Gaul's not with you?
We got separated.
I thought so...
Gaul-kun hung in there until the end.
I hope he's at least with the fire dragon.
Gaul has a hero crystal, right?
The crystals can call to one another...
I'm worried about the Star Whale, but first
we need to meet up with the prince.
Yeah!
Um...
That's right.
I was sucked in and fell into the water.
It's so cold!
I'm amazed I survived even
though I was out cold.
I guess I'm just that good... maybe?
Forest people?
No... they're a different color.
The spirits here?
Sorry to bother you guys.
I'll be leaving soon, so don't be so scared.
Um... who are you?
Can I use this?
That's great!
It's so warm!
Did you
save me when I was drowning?
I see.
I'm from Galette.
I won't forget what you did for me.
Thanks.
So can I ask you something?
I see.
I should dry my clothes off, yeah.
So we're inside the Sky Whale, right?
What's your name?
Aria.
Did you just speak directly inside my head?
Oh, sorry.
Um, well...  I just thought
it was a pretty voice,
and it startled me.
Do you live here, Aria?
You don't know?
Then who are these?
The Sky People. They're my friends.
Are there any other people here?
I see.
Did you lose your memories?
You might've gotten sucked in, too, maybe.
You see, we've come from the surface
to check on the Star Whale.
We think something might've
happened in the Sky Sea.
And so I came to see the Sky
Priestess with my friends,
but when the Star Whale sucked
us in I got separated from them.
Do you know anything about this, Aria?
About the Star Whale, or the Sky Priestess?
No, it's okay. Don't worry about it.
Once my clothes dry, I'll go find my friends.
Want to come with me?
It must be lonely being here alone.
As a representative of Galette,
I'll take good care of you.
But...
It's dangerous now.
Gaul's signal is weak.
Looks like we're a good ways
apart from each other.
What about your end, Nanami?
It looks like I'm closer.
The crystal is responding.
Gaul-sama!
Answer us!
The Priestess must know we're inside.
And the Star Whale should know, too.
Normally, they'd speak to us.
The Star Whale talks, too?
It doesn't necessarily talk...
you can hear it's will.
If the priestess is with you, she can
translate it into human language
to make it easier to understand.
I don't quite understand,
but if we find the priestess we should be
able to talk to it about things, right?
We need to find Gaul-kun,
and meet the Sky Priestess.
I hope he's safe...
Something was just moving!
Is that...
Demons!
I can't believe there are
demons inside the sky whale.
Mercurius!
I don't know what's going on, but...
If you're going to attack us...
We'll fight our way through!
Let's go, everyone!
Yeah!
Yeah.
These aren't demons.
They're not animals, either.
Then what are they?
I don't know...
But they're like bacteria
or microscopic organisms.
Let's fight our way through!
Vert and I will make a path!
Let's go!
Yeah!
This sound... Nanami,
Noir and the others are fighting.
Sorry, Aria.
We'll talk later.
Don't go.
It's extremely dangerous.
You're worried about me? Thanks.
But my friends are fighting.
I have to go help...
So this is what you meant by dangerous?
Those are monsters with no definite form.
Those are Sickness Demons.
They make the Star Whale
sick and bring disaster.
Bad creatures.
I see.
Which means I can kick the
crap out of them, right?
But...
They're very strong and
there are a lot of them!
I see.
Then we just have to defeat them and
go forward so we don't get sick.
Lion King Lightning Circle!
Okay, let's go, Aria.
I'll introduce you to my friends.
We defeated a lot,
but there's no end to them.
It's like when we fought the dragon eater.
It was just like this.
Are these things why
the Star Whale isn't feeling well?
Maybe.
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
It's Prince Gaul's voice!
He's coming this way!
Hey! Guys!
Gaul-sama!
Prince Gaul! You're safe!
Gaul!
Gaul-kun! Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Prince. I'm glad.
We know where we are.
I found a path I took when
I met the Priestess last time.
We're heading to her throne.
I want you to find the Fire Dragon.
Sure.
I see. It's lost, too.
It would be bad if it was attacked
by the Sickness Demons.
We need to find her.
Sickness Demons?
That's what those things that
look like demons are called.
Aria told me.
Aria?
You don't know her either, then, Sharu?
Sorry. I don't.
It looks like she's lost.
She can't remember why she's here.
I see.
That sounds like fighting!
Did something happen to the priestess?
Priestess! Sky Priestess Farine!
It's Sharu, the Dragon Priestess! Open up!
Priestess! I'm glad! You're safe!
Of course I'm safe.
Things are getting
a little difficult here, though.
The Priestess Farine is
one of the local gods.
She's huge.
Oh, my...
The Sky Priestess and the Star People
See you next time.