Miss Kobayashi! Kanna! Breakfast is ready!
This miso soup is good.
Thank you. I made it using only
ingredients from this world, too.
We're off!
Yes, watch out for cars!
Kanna, make you sure you don't
destroy them if you run into one.
Yup.
Yes! This morning I wasn't chastised
by Miss Kobayashi for any mistakes.
It was a perfect morning.
I must be improving my skills as maid.
Perhaps that means I'm getting
used to this world, too?
You've been happier lately,
haven't you, Kobayashi-san?
Huh? Have I?
You used to be a bit more stoic before.
It's like you've become a little more open.
See you later.
I guess it's been two months
since she showed up, huh?
What was I like back then?
The secret is to marinate it in honey.
Today's Point
Then it'll grow softer, and the
meat will absorb flavor more easily.
Maybe Miss Kobayashi will eat my tail
meat if I prepare it like that.
What modern girls want
their lover to do most!
2) Pet their head
3) Hold their hand in public
4) Carry like a princess
5) Hug them from behind
First place is...
2) Head petted
3) Holding hands in public
1) Push them against a wall
being pushed against a wall!
I'd love to experience
it myself at least once!
Hmm, so they pursue love with sounds.
Just like birds.
Me, too!
Pursue love...
Miss Kobayashi.
Tohru.
Now for tonight's news.
Early this morning, there was a
fire in Tatsumi-cho, Nishi-ku.
Jigokumeguri System Engineering (Inc.)
Takinokuchi Office
Kobayashi-san.
Sorry, but could you help me out here?
Sure.
Whoa, you've taken on an awful lot again.
I want to see Miss Kobayashi
working at least once.
One of my 48 maid skills:
perception blocking.
Now I can enter without anyone noticing.
*It's actually magic
There she is, there she is.
Well, thank you for your time.
Goodbye.
What's wrong, Kobayashi-san?
Takiya?!
Well, remember Yamashita-kun's project?
There was a mistake in the product,
and he's in trouble if it's not fixed today.
Yamashita-kun
Out Sick
Ah.
Sorry.
So for now, I'll work on that.
It means I won't be able to help you,
Takiya-kun, but is that okay?
It's fine, it's fine.
Makes sense anyway.
Especially given the circumstances.
But...
Let's go drinking again.
Sure.
Hey, can you help me here?
I'll be right there. Wait a moment.
This schedule's impossible.
Can't we adjust it somehow?
We'll have to reevaluate this.
Humans may gather together, help each other,
and accomplish many things,
Let's check it one more time.
but their civilization could be
easily destroyed by dragons.
So I think dragons are better.
Kobayashi!
How's that project coming?!
Oh, not done yet.
What are you doing?! You're useless!
What did I tell you?
I told you get it done right away, didn't I?
Who's this guy?
When I say right away, I mean right away!
Chief's pushing his work
onto Kobayashi-san again...
Are you incapable of prioritizing?!
You need to work to earn your paycheck!
The chief's project isn't even that vital.
Listen!
Quit slacking off and get
it finished quickly!
Understood.
Hmph! Christ!
Stop it!
Serves him right.
That should help Miss Kobayashi—
Huh?
I thought I was blocking perception?
N-No one's found out, right?
Miss Kobayashi sure works hard.
And so many people rely on her, too.
Miss Kobayashi's so cool!
Kobayashi!
How's that project going?!
I haven't received a report on it yet!
This guy again?!
Oh, sorry. I had a lot of things to do.
Follow my orders first!
Yamashita-kun's work
is higher on the priority list.
Don't talk back to me!
Anyway!
Show more motivation!
Sorry.
Christ!
You're useless!
What?
Wh-Who is it?!
Chief's having bad luck today, huh?
Thanks for your work.
Jigokumeguri System Engineering (Inc.)
Takinokuchi Office
I'll be leaving now.
Thanks for your work.
Now, I should leave before
Miss Kobayashi does...
Tohru.
You're there, right?
Whoa, you really were?!
How did you know?
Huh?
I just had a feeling you were.
Jeez.
I bet it was boring to sneak
a peek at my work, right?
Not at all!
I wanted to know more about you.
I see.
Shall we go home?
Yes!
You've been happier lately,
haven't you, Kobayashi-san?
I wonder what I used to be like?
I've already forgotten.
I heard the chief got
canned for abusing power.
Someone sent the director
a recording of proof.
Who did that?
Okay. Now everyone pair up and please
draw a picture of your friend.
Okay.
Kanna-san, would you draw me?
Friend.
Episode 5
Tohru's Real World Lessons! (She Thinks She Understands It Already)
Oborozuka Shopping District
Asparagus, watercress, new potatoes!
I bought a bunch of vegetables in season!
Since we got them cheaper than planned,
I guess I'll buy some snacks for Kanna.
Mr. Fafnir!
I'm home!
Welcome home.
I was surprised to find you standing there.
Oh, here you go.
What's going on?
I've decided to live in
this world for a while.
Really?!
To be honest, I can't
recommend it that strongly.
Can you live with humans?
If you can do it, then I can do it.
I guess that's true.
Then why don't you stay he—
Oh, I guess you can't.
Do you have any place to stay?
I'll live in some nearby mountain.
Now for today's news.
Last night there were reports of a
monster spotted in the mountains,
and police were dispatched.
The monster was said to
stand 20m at full height.
What?
Don't stand out?
Why do I have to sneak around
and hide from humans?
Maybe I should just destroy them all.
Oh, forget about that stuff.
You'll be living amongst people.
So you have to show some restraint.
Right, I know!
I'll help search for a place
for you to live, Mr. Fafnir.
Huh?
Hey, are you sure, Tohru?
I'll be all right!
Please leave it to me, Mr. Fafnir!
Hmph. I guess I'll see what you can do.
Just the other day I watched Miss Kobayashi
move out, so I understand the process.
Oh?
You create a "family registration"
and a "proof of citizenship,"
also a "bank account" and a "personal seal,"
then you show them to a "realtor."
That doesn't make sense.
So, I made them for you myself.
Hold on.
Yes?
Is this me?
Ooyama Takeshi
Mysterious Large Creature
20 Meters Tall
Yes.
Your dragon form looked like
an Ooyama Takeshi, so...
You resemble them too much.
Huh?
You're growing too close to humans now.
When you return to your world,
will you be able kill humans?
I don't intend to return to my world.
This is where I belong.
In a century or so, that human
you're attached to will die.
Then...
I'm fine.
The more I treasure these moments
and being here right now,
the sadder I'll be when
that time comes, I'm sure.
But I don't want to call
those feelings regret.
Oh! Green means go.
You think they're worth
speaking so highly of?
I do.
Because Miss Kobayashi is one of them.
Were you worried about me?
I was just curious about what
humans are like in this world.
Mitani Real Estate
Oh, if it isn't Kobayashi-san's maid.
Thank you for last time.
So, what's your budget?
Money, huh?
We're not a pawn shop.
Guess that didn't work.
Oh well, I'll steal a fittin—
No, you won't!
I can't believe there's no money exchange.
Shows the limits of this world.
About that...
Are you sure it isn't best for
you to live in your own world?
I'm sure it's hard to live here
without a human you get along with.
There is a human you'd be
all right with, Mr. Fafnir!
Who is it?
Tohru-dono!
Oh, if it isn't Fafnir-dono!
I'm surprised you knew where I lived.
I asked Miss Kobayashi.
So, Mr. Takiya.
What is it?
Actually, would you let Mr. Fafnir
here... stay with you for a while?
Oh, Fafnir-dono?
Y-Yes.
Sure thing.
Huh? You mean it?!
Well, it's a little cramped, but...
You really mean it?!
I know I'm one to talk, but this
dragon's fairly dangerous.
Hey, about last time...
You mean the game?
What others are there?
Well, come on in.
Tell me more about them.
Sure thing.
Was Mr. Fafnir really worried about me?
Yes. Now let's conduct the experiment
according to the chart in your textbooks.
Yes.
I forgot my text book. Show me yours?
I-I guess I have to.
Now try bending it.
ESP!
Bending spoons
You don't need to use any strength.
Just bend it with your will.
He didn't bend it with
strength just now, did he?
Incredible! How did it happen?!
Doesn't look like he used magic either.
If I recall, he did something like this...
Oh, not that.
Bend
Snap...
Hey!
Hiss!!
Ah, you've bent them all.
S-Sorry.
What were you trying to do?
Kobayashi! That! That!
Now this 100 yen coin will
pass through the cup!
Oh, that's what you were doing.
Is that rare? ESP?
ESP?!
So humans really do have hidden powers?!
I knew Miss Kobayashi wasn't
just an ordinary person!
God! Kobayashi God!
Indeed!
Listen!
These are magic tricks.
Anyone can do them once they learn how.
Anyone?
I've heard of this before.
Humans usually only use about
10% of their brain capacity.
In other words, if humans put their minds to it,
anyone would be able to use super powers.
To be able to when they try.
What crafty, lazy creatures.
I can't forgive humans!
Never!
You're thinking something weird again.
Lady Tohru, this book was
on Kobayashi's shelf.
You Can Do It, Too!
ESP
Well done, Kanna!
Oh, that's a book I bought long ago.
I see. So if you do this,
then power enters your hand.
That's all fiction though.
Training! This book provides good training!
I'm going training!
Tohru's easily influenced, huh?
Miss Kobayashi, come with me!
Well, I'm free, so sure.
Oh, I'll fix your spoons first.
You don't need ESP, Tohru.
Again? How cliche.
Training 1
Mental Fortification
Will I actually learn how
to do it by doing this?
It doesn't matter if you can do it, does it?
Empty the mind.
Right now, I have no desires.
Training 2
Meditation
Kobayashi, I'm hungry.
Weakling!
Wha?!
Me, too!
Here.
Training 3
Clairvoyance
Star!
Wrong.
Miss Kobayashi! Miss
Kobayashi! Miss Kobayashi!
Training 4
Thoughtography
M-Miss Kobayashi?!
That's your horn, right?
Training 5
Forms
Training 6
Sparring
Miss Kobayashi, please look! This is our...
Compilation: Bear Slayer!
Training Compilation
Bear Slayer
What do you want to become?
Why?!
Listen, Tohru.
You can do plenty of things humans can't,
so isn't that good enough?
No!
I don't want to lose to humans!
I can't be inferior to them in any way!
Absolutely not!
Absolutely.
I don't think it's like that, Tohru.
I think you actually want
to understand humans,
and that's why you're so desperate
to understand what you can't.
Tohru.
You search for the spoon's center of gravity,
then using the principle
of leverage here, there.
Huh?
Once you understand, it's simple, isn't it?
This is, at least. But there are
some things that aren't that way.
So, Tohru, you should focus on the
things only you can do.
Right.
I understand.
Tohru.
Well!
I'm going to show you a
power only I can use!
Please watch, Miss Kobayashi!
But don't break anything, okay?
Then there's not much I can do.
Are you the avatar of destruction?
I can produce electricity.
Magic Show
of the Century
Now, the beautiful lady has
entered the box. Please watch.
This is the super magic
of instant teleportation!
This!
Now, it's the moment of the century.
What?! Huh? Wha? A maid?
A maid has appeared from the box!
This isn't what we planned? Huh?
Hey, hey, give me a big helping!
Milk
Sweet and sour pork with pineapples?
I hate this.
C-Cute!
We're likely to have
leftovers, so here's extra.
Extra?!
Next Episode
Miss Kobayashi, I learned new magic!
Wow.
Please take a look at this coin on a string.
Okay.
You will fall deeper and deeper in
love with Tohru! In love with Tohru!
Episode 6
Home Visit! (And Homes Not Visited)
That's not magic.