But if that's the case, what would
become of the Galactic Alliance
if the Hideauze are beaten completely?
What are you going to do, Ledo?
Chamber, do a search on work I could do here.
Search complete. Nothing found.
Database deficiency. Gargantia
employment circumstances unknown.
If there's work that you can do,
there must be something for me...
It is irrelevant to compare
yourself to this machine.
Non-battle duties that would be
appropriate for you are close to nil.
Recommendation: Maintain
the current situation.
In other words, I should
just keep standing by, huh?
Ledo! Good morning!
Good morning.
Agreement: It is early in the morning.
Chamber! I saw you coming here.
What are you putting together?
A component one of the
hull interlocking devices.
They're really putting you to work, huh?
You're making another one!
Bebel told me. So that's
actually a flute, right?
Let me see!
It's not done yet? Sound's not coming out.
Even sound comes out... not useful.
Oh, come on! You've spent all
this time working on it...
Not useful. No meaning.
Here.
What is this?
Your pay. For moving the
cargo that last time.
Use it wisely!
Say, don't you have any money in space?
The Galactic Alliance does not allow
personal possessions during military service.
That would put a damper on my motivation.
Amy. I want to... do my own work.
Yeah, that's not a bad
idea! Let's go for it!
What kind of work... there is?
For example, I do deliveries.
It would be a pain if everyone had to
hand-deliver letters and small packages, right?
So instead, I get paid for carrying
them all around and delivering them.
That's how we support each other.
Support... I... support someone, too?
That's right! So first, you should think
about what you want someone to do.
Want someone to do... Can't think anything...
Well, maybe it'll take a little time...
After all, you're still unfamiliar
with the way we live.
Tell me... what I can do!
Sure!
Calm Day
Delivery!
Thanks.
Here you are. Please sign this.
Sure.
Um, would you happen to
need a hand with your work?
He said he wants to do some kind of work.
Huh. So you're that Spaceboy
everybody's talking about...
A worker here retired last month...
Then...
...but a new kid's already started.
It's fine! There's always enough
room for one more fisherman.
Nope. Look.
This is how it's been recently,
ever since we lost the rip current.
I'll let you know when we get busy again.
Okay.
As you can see, I'm swamped trying
to organize all of these invoices.
And it'd be impossible for somebody
with no experience to help.
How about treasure-hunting?
We have a place in mind, but it'll
take another three days to get there.
I see... I'm sorry I got your hopes up.
Okay...
Well, it's about time for
me to do my deliveries...
Then I think I will search myself.
Alright! Alright! Alright!
Alright! A little higher! Higher!
Idiot! I told you higher!
No! Left! That goes left!
Sorry! I can't!
I didn't think finding a job
would be this difficult...
Chamber, have you updated your database?
As before, there are no jobs
that match your aptitude.
Situation!
The fleet's propulsion
system is shutting down.
What does it mean?
Yo!
Pinion!
Don't stand there like a lump!
You need a change of pace!
Pinion! Fleet stopped. What happened?
It's a calm day is what's happening!
Come on, everyone's gathering. Follow me!
This is some huge meat,
right? It'll go a long way!
I'm impressed you got a
hold of that. I can't wait!
But is it okay for you to party?
It's been so long since we've had a calm day
and there's a lot of repair work that can be done...
My assistants are taking care of
business while I'm occupied with this.
Really?
We'll start with Flange's ship.
What are you doing?!
Is the power off?
Yeah, I checked.
Okay, the party's over here.
Hey, you're supposed to do that work, Pinion!
Jeez...
What is this?
The wind's stopped and there are no waves,
so we traditionally do ship
maintenance on these calm days.
We take the fleet off of the
Milky Way and turn off the power,
so everyone but repair technicians
get to take a breather from work.
Oh...
Bebel, are you doin' okay?
Yeah.
Quite a sight, right? Not
many know about this place.
It's beautiful!
Ledo, this is what the sea
is like when there's no wind.
Hi!
Saaya! Melty!
You're late!
Hurry up!
Over there looks good!
Wanna swim?
Yeah!
Come in with us, Ledo!
I-I...
It'll feel good!
Take off those lame clothes!
Oh, my...
Nice body...
It's cold!
It sure is hot, isn't it?
Dr. Oldham!
I'll join you if you don't mind.
No, please!
At last, here we go!
You don't know what I went through to
get this fine meat. It'll be delicious!
Huh?
Crap... The power's still off?!
Hey, can't you get your tin can
to do something about this?
You want to cook it?
Yeah, that's it.
Incineration complete.
What are you doing?!
Jeez...
Oh, no! We don't got that!
What's wrong?
Hey, Ledo!
There's something I want you to do.
Work?
Yeah, that's right!
I need you to fetch me something from that
old bag of an ironsmith. You're most suited...
I mean, it's work that only you can do!
Hey, you're making Ledo go there?!
He ruined a whole plateful
of meat, so yeah, of course!
I'm counting on you!
Now my back!
I hope Ledo's going to be okay...
I'm kind of ticklish there!
I thought so!
Yeesh...
If I eat meat and stuff here,
I'll probably gain weight again...
"Again", Melty? You've got
nothing to worry about!
Everybody's got their own norm, right?
I don't care about that. A lot
of boys prefer chubby girls.
You're naive...
Believe in a wrongheaded idea like
that and you'll end up getting hurt.
M-Maybe I need to exercise...
M-Maybe...
This is Ridget. Is Amy there?
Here I am!
You know the crane tower sprinkler, right?
Even though the power's back on, it's not working.
Again?!
Would you take the surf kite
up to turn the pump on?
I've got a grill out party
that's about to start...
I mean, got it!
Grill out?
I mean, thank you.
It's a race!
Okay! I'm not gonna lose!
This way we don't have to
worry about getting fat!
Query: Why are they so focused
on maintaining their weight
even as they actively seek
to eat in great quantities?
That's just the way girls think.
That does not compute.
You can say that again. But I
wonder how this'll turn out.
Tin Can, I just noticed that you're black...
Is this the right place?
Oh, young man, are you alone?
You've got a sweet face...
...and a juicy body!
What's going on?
The goal is the top of the crane tower!
Okay!
Ready?!
Start!
Hey! Don't fly recklessly!
Query: Why is this necessary?
Don't move!
Pinion!
What happened to fixing the winch on my boat?
I'm still gonna do it!
Isn't now your busiest time?
Don't sweat the details!
Stick around and get some meat yourself.
We're gonna be startin' in a little bit.
Hey, wait!
How about working at my place?!
Chamber!
The ensign is having an emergency.
I told you not to move!
He's just learning a thing
or two about society.
Understood.
Pinion!
What are you doing over here?
W-Who are you?!
Ridget! What's the outfit for?!
I was overseeing inspection and
repairs of the bottom of the ship.
I-I see. Hey, when's the power
gonna go back on in this area?
Work is taking longer than expected,
so it'll be off until this evening.
Let's take a break.
You haven't started yet?
N-No...
Oh.
Excuse me.
Sure...
Something wrong?
N-No. It's just, your
swimsuit is pretty daring...
Is it?
New workers don't have a quota or anything!
Wait!
What is this?! What did I do?!
Looks like I'm gonna win this!
It's not over yet!
I'm not gonna lose!
You'd have a good chance of
being my club's number one!
Your bum has such a lovely shape!
You're dreamy... and have
plenty of stamina, too!
Amy!
Are you okay?!
Why is it always Amy?!
Still, a race is a race!
Wait!
Hang on tight!
Uh-oh!
There!
I did it! I'm first!
Okay. That was close, huh?
Anyway, what were you doing there?
I do not... really know.
Oh, well, relax for now.
There it is!
Look!
Yay!
Well, I will go back to work.
What the...?!
The street you want is straight ahead!
Here...
That was some good exercise.
Right?
Now we can eat a lot
without worrying about it!
Query: Why is this necessary? I
repeat. Query: Why is this necessary?
I said, don't move!
It's almost time.
This...
Young one... What do you
intend to do with this?
Alright, fine. Take it.
If this will settle things...
Um...
Shhh!
What's in here, parts?
Do I have to go back through there?
Here...
Dammit, who blabbed about the party?!
Welcome back!
Good job, Spaceboy!
Seasoning with salt just ain't enough. You got back just in time!
Okay, who wants some?!
Me!
That old lady's sauce is the best!
Ledo, if you don't get
some now, it'll be gone!
Y-Yes!
Here!
Is it good?
And try it with the fruit
of your labors, too!
Here.
T-This is...
Wind...
Well, better get back to work...
Did you get enough to eat?
Yes. Maybe...
I see. Well, you did come in a bit late...
Sorry about that. Even though
the party was for you...
Huh? You didn't hear?
Pinion heard you couldn't find a job,
so he planned the party to cheer you up.
Oh... Really?
Thanks for working hard for everyone's sake.
I did it... for everyone?
Sure! Thanks to that, we were all
able to eat something delicious!
Come on, let's go! I'll try
to help you find work again!
I wonder what kind of work
he'd be suited for...
Probably some kind of physical labor?
No cows!
What's that mean?
Pinion!
So this is where you've been slacking off!
Wait, t-this is legitimate work here...
I'm sorry!
Query: Why is this necessary?
I repeat. Query: Why is this...