I happened to witness
something outrageous.
Isn't that what people call...
"a love triangle exposed"?
Min-
Minko...
H-Hey...
Shut up.
Don't talk to me.
Don't even breathe!
But then I'll die...
Morning, Ohana.
Minchi?
What's wrong with her?
Has something happened, Ohana?
Umm...
Well...
What?!
Tohru?!
But why Fukuya?!
I'm just so lost...
Would you mind...
...telling me about this in greater detail?
Minko.
Fetch me a grater from storage.
Yes, sir.
Tohru's late today, isn't he?
He's not coming in today.
What do you mean?!
I need that grater now.
Yes, sir.
Episode 5: A Tearful Chef Romance
He's been offered a better job elsewhere?!
That's what I've concluded
from the information I've gathered.
What information?
I always thought that
I was more suited to writing a detective novel
than erotica.
In order to write my novel with
this shabby hot spring district as the background,
I've been gathering information
about the people here and their secrets.
Wow, a detective novel...
Who cares about that?!
We need to
discuss Tohru's job offer!
"Who cares"?
Whatever.
Did you know that...
our manager and Fukuya's manager
have been rivals for a long time now?
Yeah, I've heard the rumors.
Well, while looking for a way to crush Kissuiso,
Fukuya spotted Tohru.
The loss of a talented chef would be
a huge blow to Kissuiso.
Then that must've been...
I saw it last night!
Are you sure, Mr. Ren?
You'll be okay without me?
I can keep things going here
even when you're not around.
Okay.
I think he might've been discussing
his job offer with Mr. Ren.
Fukuya is a four star inn.
People have a brighter future
working there than here,
since we don't get as much business as them.
That's saying too much, don't you think?
Mr. Ren pointed Tohru,
who has great talent,
towards a better path.
That's my conclusion.
But that's so sudden...
We didn't even have the chance
to throw a farewell party for him...
But Tohru sure is good.
He's already gotten friendly
with the successor to Fukuya-
That's not true!
Minchi!
He may appear abrupt and cold,
but in reality he treasures
the people working here
and his job more than anyone else!
There's no way that
Tohru would do something like that!
Am I going to be killed with a grater?
Fine! Let's ask him ourselves!
Actually, Tohru isn't...
He's not in today?
We were too late.
He's flown the coop...
leaving us behind.
Minchi...
The white croaker will soon be done.
How's the pepper leaf bud doing?
It'll be finished soon.
Why...
did Tohru leave for Fukuya?
You're serious about
being a chef too, right?
Yes.
Then you'll eventually find out the answer yourself.
But-
That's what happens
when you don't focus.
I'm sorry.
I'll finish cutting these-
Are you out of your mind?
Do you plan on
handling the customers'
food with your hand like that?
I'll do the rest!
Minko...
My, my. This is a pretty bad case.
Although, you can't exactly blame her.
Her savior's no longer here.
Her savior?
The one who allowed her to work here
was Tohru actually.
Apparently,
Minko wanted to be a chef
without even attending high school.
However, her parents were against it.
She refused to give up her dream,
so she started
looking for places that would train her.
I'm begging you.
Please let me work here!
But...
Your parents are against this, aren't they?
I...
Being a chef isn't as easy as you think it is.
Do you think you'll be able to keep it up?
Yes!
Then show me what you can do.
I'm finished.
It's rather thick, isn't it?
Too thick.
I'm appalled that you decided to
become a chef with this level of skill.
She still has a lot she needs to work on.
Madam Manager, Mr. Ren,
could you let her work here
until she can at least be of some use?
Although she's still a rookie,
I can tell that she has the right mindset.
What do you want to do, Mr. Ren?
You're in charge of
training her in the basics.
Yes, sir.
What are you looking so dumbfounded for?
Chefs need to wake up early,
kitchen hand.
Th-Thank you!
I see...
Check up on her, okay?
Nako and I will finish the rest.
Okay!
Tohru...
H-Hey, Minko?
Don't you have duties to attend to?
I'm here because
I'm worried about you.
There's no need to worry.
I wonder if I can work at Fukuya too...
I guess not with my skill...
I-I'm sure you can!
Tohru will recommend you for sure!
Just like he did
when you first came here!
H-How do you know about that?!
I'm sure Tohru'll be
glad to work with you too.
You balut!
There's no way I can go and work at Fukuya!
I got a job here thanks to Tohru!
There's so much I need to repay Tohru,
Madam Manager, Mr. Ren,
and the inn itself!
But you were just saying that
you wanted to go to Fukuya...
You misunderstood me.
You're amazing, Minko.
What?
Whether it's work, love, or personal matters,
you're giving it your all.
I want to cheer you on!
You need to chase after him!
But...
You can't work without him, can you?!
Get out...
Get out, balut!
M- Minko?!
I've been locked out...
Minko must really like him...
Falling in love with someone
must be incredible...
Ko must be feeling the same way...
Ko...
Don't expect too much.
After all,
it's just a regional festival-
Now, I didn't say it was pointless, Takako.
She screams about everything.
Now, where did I put it...
What?
Aren't you supposed to be working?
Well...
Oh!
Do you mind lending me a hand?
What?
Let me know when you find the bonbori.
Just look in any of the boxes.
Okay...
You know what they look like, right?
Maybe I didn't
understand a single thing at all...
Bingo! That's it.
Is this for the Bonbori Festival?
You've heard of it?
Wow, it's so pretty!
What's this at the bottom?
It's a wish card.
A wish card?
If you write your wish on it
and tie it to the bonbori,
a god will use it to illuminate
his path home back to Izumo,
and in return, he'll grant you your wish.
Wow...
But only hardworking people
will have their wishes granted.
People like you who don't work
won't have their wishes come true.
Hardworking people...
But will we really get more customers
if we make our bonboris look more modern?
Well, it's not like I'm
going to disobey Takako's orders...
So hardworking people will
get their wishes granted, right?
What?
Let me borrow this!
Balut! Balut! Balut!
That idiot doesn't understand anything!
Minko!
Let's go and drag Tohru back!
What are you-
He may be sharp-tongued,
but he's more determined than
anyone, and kinder than anyone, right?
He may appear abrupt and cold,
but in reality he treasures the people
working here and his job more than anyone else, right?
And he has this much hair,
and his eyes are slanted upwards, right?!
We can't lose someone like that!
So-
You don't understand anything.
Tohru was invited to Fukuya
because of his skill!
Do you understand what
an honor that is?!
No.
Idiot!
I wish him all the best.
That's why I don't want to get in his way.
You balut!
You like him, don't you?!
Fine, I'll go to Fukuya myself.
You idiot!
How will that solve anything?!
I want to do something for you
because you're such a hard worker.
I have the feeling that'll allow me
to work hard towards something as well.
But it'll be impossible
to drag him back.
Then, we'll ask...
for help from the heavens!
I'm going!
W-Wait!
Hey!
What's her problem anyway?
She's such a ba-
Excuse me!
Gr-and-ma...
How many times must I tell you to
call me "Manager," Yuina?
Sor-ry, Gr-and-ma...
So, what do you want?
There... seems... to be
something... going on by the... entr-ance...
I want to talk to the manager!
Calm down!
What on earth is going on?
Ohana?
There she is!
Aren't you from Shijima's place?
I'm her granddaughter!
I'm here today
because I have a favor to ask!
Please give Tohru back to us!
What?
You're all horrible at Fukuya!
You have a large inn,
lots of cars,
and a very pretty granddaughter!
There's no need for you to
steal one of our staff away from us!
What's this girl talking about?
Have you got an idea?
Kissuiso needs Tohru!
So-
Tohru's gone back already.
Where to?!
Kissuiso.
Kissuiso?
What?
As a helper?!
One of our chefs was out with a cold,
so the head chef
of Kissuiso lent Tohru to us.
Oh...
I said that with a fake
Hakata accent today!
Did you understand me?
So that's what it all was about...
Then you and Tohru aren't...
Me?
You were with him on his motorbike.
Oh, I wanted to ride it, so he let me.
That was it?
Oh yeah, what should I do about the helmet?
Tohru won't be coming over anymore.
Do you want it, Ohana?
I've decorated it a little,
but you can still use it to ride a motorbike.
If I ever need it, I'll let you know.
I'm exhausted...
Ohana!
Ohana, Tohru came back!
Working at Fukuya?!
Who the heck came up with that?!
Why doesn't he
use his time to write his
erotica instead
of spreading dumb rumors?
Mr. Ren...
What if... just what if...
I actually went to work for Fukuya.
What would you do?
I'll stop you!
Next time, I'll definitely stop you!
I didn't ask you!
I'm sorry!
Go check how many
vegetables we still have in stock, Minko.
Yes, sir!
And while you're at it,
organize the food supplies in the storeroom.
I'm so happy for Minko.
Oh yeah...
Move.
I can't get on my motorbike.
You're always in my way,
even though none of the
right parts of you are sticking out.
I'm not in your way anymore, am I?
Why don't you just go on home already?
Goodnight!
You went all the way there to bring me
back, yet you're acting like this now?
So, when are you going to hold a farewell party for me?
That was-
So, in the end, you're the only
one who tried to stop me, eh?
Well, it's better than no one, I guess!
What's your problem?!
I've got a sensitive nose!
I'm not a big deal
until Mr. Ren tries to stop me himself.
So, Tohru went home.
What happened to you?
I'm still not very fond of him!
It seems like Tohru had a good experience.
Now he'll have somewhere to go to when we shut down.
Madam Manager!
I'm joking.
Enishi, call them later and apologize.
Shigeko, that is.
Fukuya?
That was a long day...
You did run around a lot.
Aren't you glad
he wasn't taken away, Minko?
I knew that all along.
You'll be with him for a while yet.
You can call me Minchi.
Really?!
But in return,
you have to write down
what you want me to call you.
I'll use it.
Nako told me that you wanted a nickname.
If you write it on the wish card,
I'll call you that.
Minchi...
Thanks.
Well, let's see...
I never imagined that
I'd have to come up with one myself...
"Nakochi," "Minchi..."
"Ohachi"?
Maybe "Hanachi" is better?
But that's too similar to "hibachi chicken!"
Then, I guess...
Let's see...
You're out of time.
What?! But...
You're too slow.
I-I'll come up with one really quickly!
Give me one more chance!
No.
What?
Minchi, please! Minchi!
Shut up!
Come on!
How are you, Ko? It's Ohana.
I finally feel like
I've given my all to something.
I'm sure it's because
you wished me luck in your text.
Thanks, Ko.
Ohana
But I don't want to challenge myself...
What are you looking at?
"Cheer up."
Good morning, low-class hot spring inn.
Good morning, staff of the
low-class hot spring inn.
Episode 6