Tomoe, what do you say to coming home next week?
What? What on earth are you talking about?
You're going to attend a marriage meeting.
I've already sent them your picture.
No one's mentioned this to me at all!
You're the only one in your group of friends
from high school who's still single, right?
How did you know that?
You'd be surprised at how information
spreads amongst neighbors.
Man...
You were saying
how you'd fine some rich customer,
but I bet no one rich visits your inn, right?
H-How rude!
I mean, your place is so busy
that they have to hire students, correct?
Just how much information
did you get from our neighbors?!
Anyway, the meeting's next week.
I don't want to die before I see my grandchild's face.
Whatever!
Take care!
Wait, Mom?!
Hello!
Jesus...
Pestering me about marriage...
I mean, I do want to show them
a grandchild while they're still healthy, but...
I wonder if there's any point in continuing this job...
Episode 7
All Quiet on the Kissui Front
Oh, good morning, Tomoe.
Morning. Are you off to school now?
Yes, we finished our job pretty fast,
so we wouldn't have to rush to school today.
It must be great to be young...
Nonsense. You're young too, Tomoe!
I think you're the only person
who can say something
like that without sounding sarcastic.
Did something happen?
Nope, nothing. Run along now.
Bye!
Seriously, it must be great to be young.
They have a bright future ahead of them,
Morning, Minchi.
and they're filled with hopes and dreams.
Morning. Let's go.
They can wear mini-skirts.
They can fall in love, go out, have fun,
and still find time for more recreation.
Compared to them,
my life is just an
endless cycle of doing the same thing...
I don't feel alive anymore!
Could you stop acting like an idiot
and get ready to greet the customers.
Yes, Ma'am.
Oh, and about those customers...
Yes?
It's them again.
"Again"?
Don't tell me...
Things will get hectic around here.
Hey, why don't we go out the day after tomorrow?
We can't.
Didn't you see the reservation for that group of customers?
Darn, you're right!
Guess we won't be relaxing this week either...
But it's probably better than
having no customers at all.
Target located.
Roger that. Commence pursuit.
Roger.
What's this? New stalkers?
Are they Nakochi fans or something?
How would I know?!
Nakochi, wait!
According to the spy squadron,
our target works at that inn.
Perfect.
This is Bravo 1.
Let's begin and enjoy our game.
Bravo 2, roger.
Roger.
Okay, let's move!
"Survival Gamers"?
What are they?
People who play survival games.
No, for starters, I was wondering
what "survival games" are...
What's up?
Huh?
Take a wild guess, Nako!
Basically, they shoot each other with toy guns.
Wow, do they come often?
Those types of customers come by every now and then,
but they're generally calm.
But they're...
They're?
They're different.
They've come by for
the past two years already,
and they're insane.
They do things that are on the verge of being illegal.
I think Nakochi just had a taste of one of their activities.
Th-That was the first time in my life
I've ever run so fast.
That's not the first time
they've chased people
around to practice what they call "pursuing."
But they'll only chase you.
They won't do anything else.
I-I just don't trust them!
We've reached our destination.
We're ready to enter at any time.
Wait until backup arrives.
But we can't miss this opportunity.
While she's cleaning the men's bath-
Remain on standby, Bravo 2!
Commander...
This is an order.
Commander!
What are you doing?
E-Excuse me? Sirs?!
Is someone there?
A-A peeking squadron?!
They only went as far as peeping in the dressing room last year,
but their actions keep getting worse and worse...
Wait, Ohana,
were you taking a bath while cleaning?
I couldn't help it...
Then I guess you deserve to be peeped at...
I'm sorry!
Oh dear...
Hello.
Hi.
One of the "rich marriage candidates"
turned out to be a fraud too.
What?
It's too big a task for those girls.
But we can't just turn the customers away.
Force them to work harder.
Excuse me, Madam Manager?
Yes?
I know this isn't the best time to tell you,
but I'm actually thinking about returning home.
A paid vacation?
No, it's actually...
Oh?
If you're going home during your paid vacation,
could you be attending a marriage meeting?
So, even the great Tomoe is giving up and-
Never mind.
Wh-What happened?
I can't take this anymore, Tomoe!
They're even chasing me in the inn now!
Oh my, they like you that much?
That doesn't please me at all!
Can't we just kick them out?
For me, right now,
returning customers are a godsend.
They do call customers "gods" sometimes, you know.
Something tells me that God isn't a stalker...
H-Here they come again!
Wait, Nakochi!
Please stay away!
Sirs?!
Another stressful day at work...
Nako seems to be at her limit...
If I were to quit right now, she wouldn't survive...
Wow, another old film...
Commander! We've been surrounded by the enemy!
But you know,
I don't have to worry about what's going to happen
I'll hold them back! You go ahead!
after I quit.
I should be worrying about how I'm going to quit.
C-Commander!
All of you have a future!
I'm not letting you lose your lives
on this shitty battlefield!
Commander!
Yeah, it's wrong to let kids with a bright future
throw their lives away.
Okay, baby! Get some!
Commander!
Huh?
Okay, baby! Get some!
But if I were to abandon those girls and quit,
wouldn't I be throwing my life away without doing anything?
Yeah!
Since I'm going to quit anyway,
I'm going to harass those customers
until they complain about me,
and get myself fired!
If all goes to plan, I'll be able to kick those slimeballs out
and quit my job at the same time!
It's time to put in some effort for their future!
Good morning, soldiers!
Good morning, Tomoe.
What's with the glum faces this morning?
It's those survival gamers.
We told them that breakfast is served at 8
but they don't seem to be up yet,
so we can't prepare their meals.
I see.
Wake up! Up! Up!
Drop your cocks and grab your socks, ladies!
Yes! My waitress life is officially over now!
Yes, Ma'am!
What?
Your order, Ma'am?!
We'd like to prepare breakfast,
so could you please leave this room?
Yes, Ma'am!
Men, face left!
Move forward!
Wow! You had the customers listening to you so obediently!
You're amazing!
Wh-What?
Doesn't Tomoe remind you
of an older sister you can trust?
Did you know that you can call more
experienced waitresses "older sisters"?
Really?
But you don't call her that, do you?
She says she doesn't like it.
M-Minchi?
How weird.
That was supposed to be a critical hit.
It's an emergency, Tomoe!
Y-You can't, Minchi!
Let go!
What's going on?
I need to have a word with them!
They didn't lay a finger on the meals
Mr. Ren and Tohru made!
They keep eating these processed foods.
Apparently, they brought them themselves.
Oh, no...
Those customers enjoy "battlefield meals."
Battlefield...
...meals?
Like rations.
In other words, I think they prefer eating light
rather than gourmet meals.
A riceball?
But we have our rations...
This is a lot tastier and healthier
than those foods that are
packed with preservatives and synthetic dyes.
Oh...
Oh, and before I forget...
Hey, Tomoe?!
She made them!
I figured there was no point in bothering the cooks for this.
Did...
Did this girl really make them?
What?
Y-Yeah!
Right, Minko?!
Y-Yes...
But I'm not an actual chef yet, I'm...
Then I guess I'll take a bite...
It's delicious!
It tastes exactly like the riceballs
my mother used to make me!
I'm so glad to be alive!
What?
More, please!
More! More! More!
Please, more!
You're incredible, Tomoe!
Before you did that,
they wouldn't lay a finger on our food!
I've also never seen Minchi look so happy!
What on earth?
I-I'll just have to do whatever it takes now.
We failed last time.
We can't afford to fail again.
Commander!
Our army's future depends on this battle!
Not one soul will grieve your deaths!
Will you lend your lives to me?!
All right!
Identify our current situation!
No enemies to the right!
No enemies to the left!
Charge!
Oh, my God!
Jesus!
Okay, let's clean this place up!
But Tomoe, this hose is...
I'll take responsibility for everything!
Okay, baby! Get some!
We're under attack!
Now I'm really done for!
Dammit!
Retreat! Retreat!
Those who run away are survival gamers,
and those who don't
run are well-trained survival gamers!
She looks like she's having a lot of fun...
You're sparkling, Tomoe!
What did you say?
You're sparkling!
Oh, come on...
Oops...
I was?
I did have a lot of fun out there, but...
But I'm surely done for now.
Madam Manager.
I'm terribly sorry.
The responsibility for all the events lies with me.
What are you talking about?
So, it was you.
Madam Manager, your inn has a brilliant commander.
What?
Thank you for your praise.
She followed through with our operations,
enabling us to have a wonderful time.
That ambush was marvelous.
We were completely defeated.
What?!
We'll be coming again.
Next time,
we'll break through your defenses for sure.
Thank you.
We, along with the commander,
will do our best to make your stay more comfortable.
What?!
Salute the commander!
We hope to see you again.
I'm so impressed, Tomoe!
I didn't know we were supposed
to change our procedures depending on the customers!
What?
R-Right!
So that's what Madam Manager means
when she always says, "An inn is a place that provides
things out of the ordinary."
I don't know about that...
We really feel like we have a long way to go still!
I want to learn more from you,
s-sis.
That's not fair, Ohana!
C-Can I call you "sis" too?
They're so cute!
O-Of course!
Of course you can!
Okay, sis!
Sis!
No... I take that back.
It's so ticklish...
Did you see the pictures?
Aren't they all handsome?
The meeting's next week!
I sent the pictures back.
What? Why?!
At first,
I really did intend to quit work and
return home, but...
But?
But I want to keep working here.
My co-workers are so cute, too.
I realized that I'm really cut out for this job.
When weirdos come, I get really hyped up.
What on earth?
I really feel alive when I'm working my shift
and being overwhelmed.
What?
Alive and stressed out, though.
You really sound like you're enjoying yourself.
Yeah.
I promise I'll present you a grandchild
before you go to Heaven,
so just give me a bit more time.
Okay.
I won't say anything anymore.
Just stay healthy, okay?
I will. Sorry.
Come home every now and then, okay?
Okay.
Actually, that might be a bit tough.
I'm the head waitress, after all.
Really?
Really.
Good morning!
Right, let's get crackin'!
Yes, Ma'am!
I couldn't be of any use.
A-An ambulance!
Idiot!
Mom, Grandma is...
Episode 8
Run
Something I can do right now...