Forest Exhibition
29th Suimei High School Culture Festival
Chocolate Banana
Come visit us.
Welcome.
That looks delicious.
Thank you very much.
You're really getting the
hang of this, Sora—
Welcome.
You've got the eyes of a fish
that's been rotting in the sun!
Hang in there!
Nyapollon's not finished yet,
so I've been pulling all-nighters.
Thank you.
I have a quota to meet at
the chocolate banana café, too.
Welcome.
You... You should have a banana, too.
They're really nutritious.
Kanda-kun, are you okay?
N-Nanami!
What? Don't stare like that.
Oh, um... you look great. Yeah.
Really great! Doesn't she, Sorata?
Yeah, just great...
Welcome.
This guy's operating on autopilot.
I'll work hard enough for both of us.
You can go to Nyapollon's prep room.
What? But...
I don't have anything to
do on Nyapollon right now,
so at least let me help you out.
You could've at least told
me it looked good on me.
Nanami?
Bring us a ton of customers!
I'm going to make loads of these!
#11 Milky Way Cat, Nyapollon
Nyapollon Prep Room
I wish I could just shut
down all culture festivals...
where I don't get to run around with girls.
Jin-san, you were that excited about all this?
Haunted houses? Crêpes?
Wonderful little blind spots...
appear all over the school
during a culture festival.
Which means...
some really thrilling "play" becomes possible.
I've never experienced anything
more thrilling than this.
Four days until opening,
and I've got even more...
blocking to do
for the drama sequences.
Nyapollon Production Schedule
Four days until opening!
It's so thrilling, I wish
I could just pass out.
Opening!!
I feel the same way, but the demon...
who won't allow that
is about to show up.
No one's sleeping on
the job in here, are they?!
Here, you two!
Whoa...
Drink before you die!
It's a potion to restore
your hit points!
It says it'll guide
us beyond our limits.
Yeah, I guess it's still too
early to exceed our limits.
That's not the point.
Okay then, let's wake ourselves up...
with something eye-opening!
Mashiron's wearing a cat girl
suit for this year's art exhibit.
You make it sound like she's a
monster, but that's not right, is it?
It's the cat version of a
"bunny girl" suit, right?
Start building up your expectations.
Mashiron's so cute, it made my nose run.
It gave you a nosebleed, you mean...
A cat girl, huh?
I bet it looks good on her...
Welcome.
Huh?
This is the Forest Exhibition, Etc.
Forest Exhibition
What are you doing?
Welcome.
This is the Forest Exhibition, Etc.
What are you, a mascot?
I'm the poster girl.
That's not what that means.
A forest exhibit, huh?
Welcome.
Please enjoy yourselves.
A café?
According to Misaki, it combines
an exhibit, a café, caricatures,
the forest, omelet rice, and animal suits.
Hence, "Forest Exhibition, Etc."
The "etc." carries too much weight.
This was handcrafted by
a forest bear! Boom!
We'll draw your face on
it in ketchup for free!
Come on, kouhai-kun...
I'll do it.
You're fighting me for this job?!
Kouhai-kun, who will it be?
Me or Mashiron?!
You're standing too close, Senpai!
We're never too close
nor too far away!
You draw the caricature right
on the face? That's novel.
I messed up your face.
What are you, a rebel without a cause?
Sorry, Senpai, but I choose Shiina.
I lost the battle between women!
I don't care. I have Jin...
You're good at this.
You've got such a delicate touch.
R-Really?
Now, now, Misaki-senpai...
Finished.
That was quick.
This isn't a caricature,
it's a portrait...
There's such a thing as cannibalism.
You did this out of spite, didn't you?
If you're finished eating,
let's get back to work.
Mashiron, your shift's
over too, isn't it?
Then, let's all go back together.
You're coming dressed like that?!
But it's cute.
Turn around. Let me see your back!
What?
Is something wrong?
You're the one who's got something wrong!
Why are you wearing a cat's
skin over your birthday suit?
Don't worry. I'm wearing panties.
As good as panties are, they aren't
the solution to every problem...
I believe in panties.
Sakura Hall
Takoyaki, ikayaki, okonomiyaki...
I love Japanese culture festivals.
If you're so interested
in the culture festival,
you should have gone to
work in the prep room.
Why are you in my room, anyway?
Because you interest me even more
than the culture festival, Ryunosuke.
If you'd be willing to go with me—
How could I go to a culture
festival swarming with girls?
Why do you hate women so much?
Well, why?
Don't come any closer, freeloader!
Don't accentuate your
cleavage more than necessary!
This is my natural look.
Then, stop looking up at me like that!
First, you chide me for my fake smiles,
and now, you're rejecting
the expression of my eyes?
I'd heard that Japanese
gentlemen were bossy...
and I guess it was true.
Who are you calling "bossy"?!
You foreign insect!
I'll exterminate you right now!
If you can do it from there, go ahead.
I'll get you one day!
Now, where were we?
We're home!
Don't act so disappointed!
This long interval bothers me.
Should we add a line?
Yeah, you're right.
Please do.
You killed Nekosuke-san...
Misaki-senpai, about this character...
I'll never forgive you... Never...
Huh? Which one?
Ein!
Ein?
No, no.
This henchman. The little one.
We're going to add some lines.
Got it.
I'm hungry. My brain isn't working.
Chin up, chin up!
Shiina.
Hustle, hustle!
This Nekosuke character here...
The only thing I can do is cook dinner.
Safe. Doesn't look like it'll stain.
I've reached my limit.
I'll go wash my face...
This... is...
Don't...
What?
D-D-Don't look!
Keep that on!
Oh, crap!
Sorry!
I'm sorry! It wasn't on purpose!
I mean, you forgot to put up the sign...
saying you were using the bathroom!
Well, that's...
That's because I wasn't planning
on taking my clothes off...
Did...
Did you lose a kilogram when
you took off your clothes?
H-How did you know?
There's an urban legend
saying you weigh less...
if you stand on one leg.
That's a lie!
Yes.
The flight departs on the
last day of the festival.
Yes, everything's fine.
Mashiro understands.
I'll contact you again.
Did you hear that?
S-Sorry...
Hey, that phone call...
That was Mashiro's father in England.
Mashiro has people waiting for her.
Mashiro will return to
where she belongs.
Do you want to take
a look around the festival?
I want to dream.
You were drawing until dawn.
Hey, Shiina.
When it's just the two
of us, call me Mashiro.
Oh, sure...
Mashiro, is there...
Is there anything you're
not telling me?
Shiina-san!
U-Um, there's something I'd like
to ask you about the exhibit!
Go on. I'll be waiting in the prep room.
Okay.
Mashiro has people waiting for her.
Mashiro will return to
where she belongs.
Oh, Kanda-kun.
You're late.
Akasaka, why are you dressed like that?!
When I arrived at school, a salesgirl...
with a ponytail forced me to wear it.
Okay, but why a maid?
I promised him he could just
stand there if he did it.
This is a disaster.
I didn't think you'd come
to the culture festival.
I didn't have any choice.
Ever since that woman
took over my room,
I haven't been able to sleep!
He's getting a lot of customers.
We should be grateful to Rita-san.
Yeah.
Kanda-kun...
Kanda, come check
the climax with me.
It's the final battle
with Ein the Hunchback.
There are two synchronized
controls during the battle.
The first is...
Dodge!
Ein's Cat Punch!
By lifting and lowering their hands,
the audience avoids Ein's attacks.
The second is...
Once they're backed into a corner,
the audience has to clap their hands.
Shout!!
Meatball Beam!!
The meatball beam shout.
Once it senses a set volume,
Nyapollon will use her finishing move.
You'll be the one who revs
up the crowd, ponytail.
O-Okay. I'm kinda nervous.
What do you think, Kanda?
It feels like there's
something missing...
Missing?
Yeah. Just having them
shout the name...
of the attack feels like a
waste of the system.
Then, what should we do?
We can manage to just barely
change the program in time,
but we don't have time to
order additional animation.
What's your idea to use
the system effectively?
What? No—
I didn't have an idea in mind.
A director has to be prepared
when he suggests a change.
You're right. Sorry.
Why are you just standing there?
A director who loses his way just before...
the development deadline
only creates confusion.
Hey, Akasaka-kun,
you're going too far again...
We're running out of time,
but I guess there's no choice.
You should really go think
about your responsibilities.
Special Lecture by Graduate Fujisawa Kazuki
For Anyone Aiming to Become a Creator
Discussing the Future of Video Games
Fujisawa Kazuki.
Special Lecturer: Graduate Fujisawa Kazuki
People often ask me how
to become a creator.
But I believe the impulse or desire...
to create something comes from within...
and isn't something that can be taught.
To create a product that appeals...
to the emotions of more users,
you must first move yourself.
If you do not move your own heart,
you cannot move the hearts of others.
Creating a product that
moves your heart...
But...
Nyapollon isn't what's in my heart right now.
I'm thinking about Shiina.
Mashiro...
What?
What are you doing here?!
I came to pick you up.
Ryunosuke said you'd be here.
Oh...
Jin and Misaki are over there.
They're waiting for us?
They're having an intimate moment.
What?!
Suimei High's culture festival is so lively.
Isn't it about time you told me
why you came to see me?
Do I have to answer that?
After all, you didn't answer me before.
I'm nothing more than a
substitute for Misaki to you.
That's not—
You're afraid to hurt Misaki.
You want to keep her by your side,
pure and untouched, forever.
Isn't that why you're with me instead?
At least think up a cover story.
My feelings for you were genuine.
So were mine.
Look who's talking.
Do you even know what "intimate" means?
Oh, there she is.
Misaki-senpai?
What are you doing here? Jin-san...
Misaki-senpai?!
Fuuka-chan...
Fuuka-chan?
She's my older sister and...
Jin's ex-girlfriend.
But maybe I'll believe you.
What?
Why don't we give it another shot?
We've both grown
up a bit since then.
I'm sorry.
I have no intention of doing that.
What's wrong with you? I was joking!
If you answer me so seriously,
I'm the one who'll be embarrassed.
Oh, yeah.
Your jokes were never funny.
I hear you're going to college in Osaka.
Your mom told me.
Yeah, their literary department is
more substantial than Suimei's.
Senpai, um...
Senpai!
Misaki-senpai!
I'm sorry...
I knew, but I couldn't tell you...
Jin...
He said he didn't want to give
Fuuka-chan another chance.
What?
I always wondered...
I figured Jin just hadn't
gotten over Fuuka-chan.
But that means I have a
chance, too, doesn't it?
Yes.
All right!
I feel motivated!
Huh?
First, I'll make Nyapollon a success!
I'll make this Jin's favorite memory,
and that goes for everyone else, too!
M-Misaki-senpai?
Oh, by the way, kouhai-kun,
what did you know?
Was it about Fuuka-chan?
N-No! That Jin-san was going
to college in Osaka...
Oh yeah, he did say
something like that.
That's your only reaction?
You won't get to see him every day anymore.
Don't you care?
Kouhai-kun, don't underestimate modern society!
Osaka's only two and a half
hours away by bullet train.
It's even faster by plane.
Senpai, do you have any concept
of time, space or money?
That doesn't matter, as long as
you really want to see them!
It's all about that irrepressible impulse!
It's time to exceed our limits! Yahoo!
Is that what love is?
Uh, yeah...
380 kilometers with one grain!
Probably...
Nyapollon...
We have to make this...
memorable...
Mashiro...
Nyapollon Prep Room
Dragon, dragon!
The timing for the switch
over to this 3D part...
I know what you mean,
so don't get so close.
Thanks.
Making the best memory
with Nyapollon...
Is it really okay if all
we do is make memories?
Is it okay for me to let Shiina
go back to England?
In order to create a
product that appeals...
to the emotions of more users,
you must first move yourself.
As long as you really want to see them!
It's all about that irrepressible impulse!
The impulse to move oneself...
That's right.
Back then, Shiina...
I...
I want to stay at Nanohana Hall!
wrote her emotions into her manga...
Akasaka!
Misaki-senpai, do you have a minute?
What's up?
It's about the climax of Nyapollon...
I want to add an impulse!
Emergency Sakura Hall Meeting!
I want to add an impulse to Milky Way Cat Nyapollon!!
by Kouhai-kun!
The final battle between Nyapollon
and Ein the Hunchback.
The system measures the
volume of the audience's cheers...
and launches its special attack,
but I want to use an additional value.
What value?
The power of love!
C-Carry on, kouhai-kun.
I want to give Nyapollon
an energy gauge...
and empty it once before the final battle.
Then, we'll have the audience
shout out the feelings...
they most want to convey to someone.
They can shout whatever they want.
It's fine if people declare their love,
and it's fine if they just
make a simple complaint.
Their voices become energy,
and once the gauge is full,
Shout!!
Meatball Beam!!
it sets off the meatball beam.
How does that sound?
That's it!
Kouhai-kun's right!
Love will save the galaxy!
Yeah, it does sound fun.
I can change the program in two hours.
Really?
All right, it's decided!
Add impulse
Changes
Add animation and backgrounds
Modify program
Opening!!
Let's get this battle started!
What am I supposed to do here?!
It's time to exceed our limits!
It's... done.
Five hours until we open.
In these few remaining hours, we can...
sleep!
Dismissed!
Let's get ready for the show by sleeping!
Yeah!
Once the festival's over, Shiina will...
Message Received
Shiina Mashiro
Are you awake?
I'm awake.
Sending
Message Received
Shiina Mashiro
Sorata.
What?
I want to see you.
You...
I want you to stay with
me until I fall asleep.
I'm starting to get
nervous about Nyapollon!
#12 The Power of Love in the Culture Festival
They say to eat three people,
right? Om nom nom...
What am I doing?!
These lame jokes just aren't me!