Takase!
I can't help but follow Sugawara-kun
with my eyes these days.
What's wrong with me?
Tuning
Chii-chan?
What's wrong? You've been weird lately.
Something on your mind?
Sorry, it's nothing.
Oh.
Are you in love or something?
Huh? Really, Chii-chan?!
Wh-What? No, Yo-chan.
I don't know much about love and stuff.
But don't you want to
when you see everyone else?
Especially Goda-kun and Ayaka-chan.
I-I don't really...
Huh?
Hey, we were just talking
about you, Ayaka-chan.
Really? About what?
Ayaka-chan, how did you start
going out with Goda-kun?
Don't you want to know, too, Chii-chan?
N-Not really.
Did you need something, Ayaka-chan?
O-Oh, yeah, I was just looking for Sensei.
Can't we talk just a little?
No, we shouldn't pry.
Well, if it's just a little...
Come on, aren't you curious, Chii-chan?
I don't care.
Okay, so who confessed first?
This is embarrassing.
Well, I did.
Oh, Chii-chan.
You are interested, aren't you?
N-Not really.
Huh? Is there someone you like, Chii-chan?
She's been sighing nonstop lately.
I have not!
Oh, I was like that, too, though.
That's what happens when you like someone.
I know.
There isn't really anyone I like.
I would follow Goda-kun
with my eyes unconsciously,
or think about him without realizing it.
I was pretty out of it during club work, too.
Come on, Chii-chan,
is there seriously no one you like?
Sugawara-kun's just a classmate.
He's kind to everyone.
Is it Sugawara-kun?
What? Really?
It's not.
Besides, why would you guess Sugawara-kun?
Oh, no, it's just a rumor that I heard.
That he likes you.
I've heard that rumor, too.
Sugawara-kun likes me?
Sugawara-kun does?
Suga—
It's just a rumor, though.
But maybe if you confessed to him...
I-I'm not going to, no way.
By the way, how did you confess, Ayaka-chan?
Well...
Come on, let's practice.
My girlfriend dumped me.
I want to die.
Can't we get back together?
Like, what?
Kana, about the other day...
Let's go.
But, Chiaki's...
I don't care.
Let's go.
Water Under the Bridge
I want to die.
What? Why'd you break up?
Because he gave the weirdest first kiss ever.
I do agree he messed up,
but are you sure you really want to break up?
Yeah. He's not worth it.
I'm really sorry!
Are you still angry?
See you at school tomorrow...
Still no answer.
Not even marked as read.
I think I'll stop messaging her.
I've been ignoring him.
Should I forgive him now?
It's not like Chiaki was trying to be awful.
All right.
If she doesn't reply
after one more message, I'll give up.
If he apologizes one more time,
I'll forgive him.
I'm really sorry about what happened.
I won't try to pull weird kisses anymore.
Can you forgive me?
I miss you...
Maybe a long letter?
Would that be too creepy?
He's been messaging me every day.
Why not today?
Hurry up and apologize, idiot.
Can I call you?
Yeah, this is the best way to do it.
I want to apologize directly if I can.
Come on!
You can't be serious!
What did he want?!
She's not answering.
She doesn't leave her phone
even when she takes a bath.
She's totally ignoring me.
I-It's okay.
I'm sure he was apologizing again.
I just need to reply tomorrow.
I guess I'll give up.
But what if Chiaki gives up?
After how long I've ignored him,
he might just quit.
He might even hate me now.
I don't want him to hate me.
He pisses me off sometimes, but I love him.
I want to apologize to him.
Please.
Turn on...
Turn on.
Turn on!
Kana, are you ever coming out?
What are you doing undressed?
I dropped my phone in the bath.
It's fine. Just give it a good whack.
Stop, Mom!
What if it gets even worse?
No way!
I'm good with technology.
Thanks, Mom.
I can't give up.
Let me apologize!
He hasn't given up yet!
Answer the phone, Kana!
Chiaki!
Hello?!
She hung up!
What the hell?!
Fine, I'm blocking you, too, idiot!
What? It broke?
That's the problem with technology!
Class 2-1
Huh? Did I forget my pencil leads?
Exam
I thought I brought them.
If...
If I gave her my pencil leads,
would she think I had ulterior motives?
If I asked Takase instead of my girl friends,
for a pencil lead, would he think
I had ulterior motives?
Well, I mean, I do have an ulterior motive.
All right, take your seats.
Yuki-chan, can I have some pencil leads?
Sorry, my pencil leads are 0.4 millimeter.
Why don't you ask Takase-kun?
You sit next to him.
Um, well...
It's your chance to get close to him.
No, don't bring that up!
Final Exams
Second-year English Exam Answer Sheet
Crap, I'm already out of lead.
I should have asked Takase.
Class 2-1
Time's up.
Pass your answer sheets towards the front.
Thanks for the lead.
Sure. No problem.
I'll give you mine sometime.
It's fine.
Why aren't they going out?
Solving for x in ax=b
1. When a ≠ 0:
x = b/a
2. When a = 0:
When b = 0: x is any real number
(Because it's of the form 0x = 0)
When b ≠ 0: No solutions
(Because it's of the form 0x ≠ 0)
Um...
The solution of ax = b is...
x equals...
Wait, is this wrong?
You want to go to college?
You're already in third year.
Isn't it too late to start studying now?
Th-That's why I'm studying now!
We don't have money, though.
Going to college is one thing, but private?
I-I know!
That's why...
That's what I said to my mom,
but am I really going to make it
into public college, studying now?
Shit.
I skipped or slept through
all my exams until now.
Now that I'm serious,
everyone else looks better than me.
I think I really did start too late.
Concentrate!
Concentrate, dammit!
Was Kaji always so studious?
I'm surprised, too.
She's awoken to the fact
that exams are approaching.
You could learn from her, Kyouko-san—
It's her man.
I mean, isn't she dating
the student council president?
Didn't you know?
Masafumi, your girl looks tense.
Aren't you going to talk to her?
It's part of her practice.
She'll be alone at the exam.
You say that, but you're the one
who's trying not to freak out.
Hit me if I try to talk to her.
Snap.
I'm handing out exams.
Take your seats.
S-Stay calm.
Remember what you learned with Akagi!
Ryoko-chan, that question there...
Was I wrong?
Can I kiss you when you're done?
Die.
Fundamentals of Exam Problems
Mathematics III
No, just forget it.
Finished.
I-Is this right?
I think I answered it, but...
Did I seriously?
No, I've got this.
I reviewed it over and over.
I'm going to get this right
and go to college with Akagi.
Uh...
What do you do in these situations again?
Oh yeah, tell the teacher.
Wouldn't people think
I'm weird if I raise my hand?
"There's a delinquent taking the exams."
"She's trying to go to college."
Of course.
It doesn't matter how hard I try.
Sensei, could you please pick up this eraser?
Oh, sure.
Let's see...
Oh, not mine.
Kaji-san's.
Hey, Kaji.
I see you're working hard this time.
Break a leg.
Th-Thank you.
I'm rooting for you, too.
What's wrong, Kaji?
Are you feeling sick?
No.
It's nothing.
Was it something I said?
N-No!
Want to go to the nurse's office?
I'm fine, dammit!
I want to nap in the nurse's office, Sensei.
Hey, now, Sano.
Get back to the exam.
Next episode: Summer Is Coming.
Summer Is Coming