Atsushi-kun!
I thought you weren't like that!
What's the matter?
I know.
Drink, Kunikida!
Here I go.
Good job!
You're quite a cheap drunk, aren't you?
Naomi-san!
You better take responsibility.
Kyouka-chan!
Despicable!
What?
I am.
I-I have a lot of work tomorrow.
Drink!
Wait, I --
I can't chug like that.
You... You...
N-Naomi-san, Tanizaki-san
can't really take jokes!
Hear me out, Kyouka-chan!
Come!
Beast Beneath the Moonlight!
Rashoumon Demonic Armor!
Come on, now.
I don't want to have spent
all that money on nothing.
Three minutes left.
Kyouka-chan, if you'd prefer, I can
set you up with a life of killing.
But your anguish isn't yours alone.
What should one do, when what they
want to be isn't what they're best at?
Everyone fights, searching for the
correct way to live their lives.
What do they seek by fighting?
How ought they live?
No one can say.
All we have is the right to waver.
Like stray dogs that have hit rock bottom.
No!
Weretiger!
If he's right...
It is worthless.
The words of your past are fundamentally
unrelated to who you are now.
If I may shed away my burden now, I will...
Die, weretiger!
I'm spent.
If he stands back up...
I won, Zelda.
Wait for me.
I'll bring you happiness once more.
Right, the control terminal.
You fool.
I took it from him during the last attack.
Dammit!
We need to stop it!
I'd love to rip you to shreds right now but,
unfortunately, I've used up all my strength.
You'll have to make do with this.
You're going to pay for
this when we next meet.
Descending?
It can't be.
I haven't done anything.
Hand it over.
It isn't responding.
Something's going on.
No good.
It isn't responding here, either.
It's going to fall!
That voice...
We're out of time.
We need to do something, or everyone's dead.
It's no use.
Someone has infiltrated from the outside.
They've taken control.
No.
There's still a way.
That voice...
Kyouka-chan?!
I heard about the situation.
Even if the Moby Dick can't
be stopped from falling,
with enough force from above, it can be
destroyed before it reaches the city.
I'll use this drone.
I see.
That's amazing, Kyouka-chan.
We can save everyone.
Prepare the parachutes, please.
You need to escape now, too.
I can't.
I'm captive here.
My ankles are chained down.
I can't make it to the evacuation system.
No...
Then...
Forget about me.
No!
I won't allow it!
Change course!
I didn't have a single
ray of light until now.
But today, I understood. I have choices.
If I sacrifice myself to save everyone
else, I'll pass the entrance exam.
I can really become a
member of the Agency.
I would regret nothing.
Stop it!
Let go!
Akutagawa!
Kyouka-chan, listen to me!
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Kyouka-chan!
Why?
Why her?
Kyouka...
What a fool.
If she hadn't embraced the hope of living in
light, she wouldn't have had to die in vain.
This is how it ought to
have been, Atsushi-kun.
Dazai-san.
Boss?
Kyouka-chan overcame herself
and saved the city.
With the high-mindedness
expected of the Agency.
But there was no reason she had to die.
True, this is a merciless conclusion.
But there was a reason that
it had to be this way.
My ability, All Men Are Created Equal,
has an effect only on my subordinates...
That is, on members of the Agency.
The ability allows for control over the
output of the abilities of another.
The reason you're able to control your tiger
abilities now is because you joined the Agency.
And Kyouka-chan passed the entrance exam.
Right in the instant before the impact.
Do you understand what that means?
I used Demon Snow's katana to
cut the chain and escape.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
You're hurting me.
Sorry.
Sorry I kept it from you both.
If I hadn't, it wouldn't have
made for a proper entrance exam.
Do we end in the mountains?
At sea.
Roger.
Was this all planned from the beginning?
The enemy's been defeated,
and Kyouka-chan passed.
I'm glad it all worked out.
Dazai-san!
There's no one left to get in my way.
Please see my strength now.
I don't know.
You're at your limit now, aren't you?
You just defeated the
Guild's leader, after all.
That's irrelevant.
I am—
You've become strong.
Oh, whoops.
Nice view, isn't it?
You protected it.
It's your city.
Episode 24
If I May Shed Away
My Burden Now
My city, huh?
The massive gifted war caused so
much collateral damage in Yokohama.
And it's finally over.
But the government's work
is just getting started.
Cleaning up after this huge mess...
I won't be sleeping at home for days.
Given that, we would very much appreciate
having your help, Mr. Herman.
I just want to watch the sea for now.
With your information, we won't have to
arrest Guild members who weren't part of this.
Do you think that a mere grunt like
myself would have such information?
Yes.
You were the leader of the Guild
two generations ago, after all.
It pains me that you young'uns always
insist on bringing up the past.
Please help us overcome
our sleep deprivation.
I don't need to use this, do I?
I never imagined the Moby
Dick being underwater.
It was such a nice place.
The Moby Dick?
The Guild.
The boss is missing in action.
I hear there are even insurgencies within
the Guild, now that we don't have a leader.
Looks like it's time to lower
the curtain on our adventures here.
Yeah.
But life isn't over.
That's true.
I'm going to go back home and
finish working on my biography.
What about you guys?
I'm going to look for Lord Francis.
I'm sure he's alive.
You're going back to your
family, right, John?
I'm not.
I have to stop the insurgency in the Guild.
You?
That's a surprise.
I thought you hated the boss.
I do.
I hate anyone who controls
people with money.
But he depended on his wealth to save
his family, and this was the result.
I can't bring myself to just leave.
The contract...
is finally fulfilled.
You made it, huh, Lovecraft?
What's going to become of you now?
I sleep.
Who is that guy?
What does it matter?
He's one of my few friends.
Kyouka-chan.
Go ahead.
Ready, and...
Congratulations on joining
the Agency, Kyouka-chan!
Cheers!
Atsushi.
How are your injuries?
I'm all better now.
Your actions have saved the
city from destruction.
I thought I should say something,
as your senior here at the Agency.
First of all, solo operations are an
exception at group organizations such as ours.
Blah, blah, blah...
I won't tell you not to apply the experience
you gained from this in the future,
but don't dare neglect the
Agency's prime activities.
Likewise for Kyouka.
Be mindful of the fact that you are
a member of the Detective Agency,
and act in a way that none
would be ashamed of.
No kidding, Kunikida.
You're all such buzzkills.
Drink with me.
No, I'd rather not drink much.
Isn't there something you wanted to say?
You did well, the both of you.
All right, let's drink all night!
Please, no.
Are you telling me you can't drink with me?
Act in a way that none
would be ashamed of, huh?
Haruno-san, Naomi-san.
I'm sorry.
I did some awful things to
you thanks to Q's abilities.
It would never have happened if
I'd known how unstable I was.
Oh, that?
I'm really sorry.
Atsushi-kun, that wasn't that bad.
We can't keep holding
on to stuff like that here.
Really?
Yes.
Thank goodness.
There was something seriously wrong with
me, to have done what I did to you.
Atsushi-kun.
I've never heard about this until now.
Atsushi-kun, what is this about?
Please, stay calm.
Rampo-kun, I brought the new piece that
you inquired about over the phone.
I can't.
I'm damaged goods!
Kunikida!
N-Naomi-san?!
Yosano-sensei, I think you've
had too much to drink.
Oh, hey.
Thanks for coming.
A-Atsushi-kun!
Do I really belong here?
Rampo-san, the boss wants you.
I'm from an enemy organization.
I'll be right back.
K-Kyouka-chan?!
Stay right there.
Rampo-kun.
What?!
Kunikida!
That was an impressive operation.
W-Wait, Kyouka-chan...
Don't make excuses, it's unmanly!
The Agency would be nothing without you.
What did you tell her, Tanizaki-san?
All the naughty things you did.
They seem to be having fun, huh, Karl?
He likes being
left out?
It's a '64 Romane.
May I really?
Isn't it your treasure?
Is there a better day than today to open it?
To victory.
This is delicious.
Boss, how shall we punish Akutagawa?
Punish?
He was instrumental in our success.
Akutagawa-kun has always been this way.
He runs off by himself, he causes
destruction and, in the end, he contributes the most.
He has a strong nose.
So long as he continues to succeed,
there will be no punishment.
Say, Kouyou-kun, why did you not try to
escape when you were captured by the Agency?
It ought to have been easy for you.
I wonder why.
Perhaps because the tea was so delicious.
Sister, let's make a deal, as two grown-ups.
I have a plan for saving Kyouka-chan.
What?
If we succeed, it'll be the only way to
protect both her life and her dreams.
Dazai saw how it would all play out.
What a terrifying man.
Pfft.
Kouyou-kun, you are strong.
Now that your beloved Kyouka-kun is gone, it
would be difficult for me to chase you down,
should you decide to leave
the Port Mafia now.
Of course.
Sadly, I must help a clumsy leader
with reestablishing the organization.
I'm grateful, but I deal only
with those under twelve.
Silence.
I'll sew your lips shut.
Dazai!
You're so dead!
It's so cute!
Hey, where's Dazai-san?
What a weird painting.
I bet even I could do it.
Hirotsu-san, thanks for the help.
Did I do enough?
All I did was leak the Moby Dick
infiltration route to Higuchi-kun.
If she knows, she will tell Akutagawa-kun.
If Akutagawa-kun knows, he
will come in by himself.
It was as I expected.
Why did you go through all that trouble
to bring Akutagawa-kun
together with the tiger boy?
I wanted to be sure.
For the real disaster that's about to come.
He's already on the move.
So the destruction of the
Moby Dick was a failure.
Still, just about everything
is according to plan.
We succeeded in creating strife within the
Guild and recruiting talented gifteds.
I'm only helping for the time being
to fulfill my end of the deal
and have Margaret brought
back to consciousness.
That's fine by me, Pastor.
Fyodor D.
Ability:
Crime and
Punishment
Let us paint the land with the
blood of the guilty together.
For a better world.
We won't be able to avoid going to war
with that demon I've fought in the past.
Akutagawa-kun is formidable enough by himself,
but his abilities are most
valuable in a supporting role.
In complementing a forward
attacker such as Atsushi-kun,
with his speed and toughness,
he could be a powerful ally.
We'll need to be more powerful than before
in order to fight with that demon.
Something more powerful than
the former Double Black.
That's those two.
Dazai-kun, why do you
value Yokohama so dearly?
My friend said me...
"You might as well side with
the people who save others."
"That's at least a little more beautiful."
Teni Muhou.
The city we protected.
Worthless nonsense.
This city became my home,
with all the people here.