The four-year-olds and under aren't here?
I'm leaving them here.
What you said to me before,
I thought about it...
one more time.
Everything's going smoothly for now.
Everyone above five years old is on our side.
They were surprised,
but I think everything will be okay.
Our next training is under way too.
Thanks.
So, what do we do next? Should we tell them?
The kids four and under.
Would they believe us?
And would they be able to hide it afterwards?
It's not just that.
I wonder if we can really take them.
It's not like I don't believe in Norman's plan.
But it's a cliff, it's winter,
and Norman's not here.
Even after we get out,
there'll be unpredictable situations.
I know it's a little late to say this,
but maybe Ray's thinking is also correct.
So you mean...
If we take them with us,
we can't let them get killed.
But if we leave them here,
they'll get shipped out.
I know! I know that, but...
Even still, I can't leave them.
Ray's right. Gilda's right, too.
But...
I don't want anyone
to get shipped out anymore.
Yeah.
I want to take my whole family.
Let's escape with everyone.
Everyone...
What's wrong?
Well... um...
what about the kids in the other plants?
Is it fine for only us to escape?
We've never seen them, but...
they're next door to us, aren't they?
Not knowing anything, just like us...
A family living happily...
Oh, um, I'm sorry.
What should we do, Emma?
That's right.
After all...
Can you get Phil?
Yes, Emma?
I have something to tell you.
About the House and Mom.
I knew it.
So it's just like I thought.
I was thinking this whole time.
When we were playing tag, I wondered
what Sister meant when she said "harvest".
She was looking through Ray's drawers,
and Emma, when Norman left,
you were really scared of Mom.
I always thought it was weird.
I see.
Norman got harvested.
And Conny...
And everyone...
That's why you...
Phil.
I won't take them now.
Only Phil knows the truth.
The others don't know
about the House or the fire.
I'm leaving that situation to Phil.
Phil, I need you to listen carefully.
I'm hesitating between two choices right now.
Should I take everyone, including the babies?
Or should I leave the kids
who're under four years old?
We only get harvested
when we turn six years old.
Even for Marnya, who has the earliest birthday,
will have at least a year and a half.
And 15 of the older kids will be gone.
If this House focuses on quality over quantity,
then the pace of harvesting should go down.
In order to raise high-quality kids again, they can't
kill the younger ones who have potential.
On that point, the six kids who are four years old,
including you, have good scores.
At worst, I estimate
that we have two years of time.
Emma, do you mean...
I can wait.
So leave us behind.
But I haven't given up.
I'll definitely return within two years.
That's when I'll take Phil and the others,
as well as all the kids in the other four plants.
Phil, where are the other children?
This way!
Mom!
Where is Emma and everyone else?
They're not with you?
I'm going to get them now.
No, don't go!
Don't worry, I'll be right back.
Everyone, make sure to stay here.
This is 73584 from Plant Three.
The children have escaped! Sound the alarm!
It went off earlier than expected.
What do we do? We're still far from the bridge.
Attention all employees.
There's an alert from Plant Three.
Following the fire in that plant,
15 kids have escaped.
Two of the 15 are high-quality.
From this point forward,
it will be dealt with maximum security.
You can kill the others who aren't high-quality.
However, don't damage any of their heads.
Capture them immediately on sight.
Do not let them get away!
Try and escape if you can...
Emma!
We'll cross from here.
Cross?
But at that time, Norman said...
If we're escaping, it'll be through the bridge.
But that's what anyone would think.
There's no way we'll cross the cliff.
That's why we won't go to the bridge.
We'll escape from the cliff.
I checked the distance to the other side
as well as the geographical features.
It's dangerous,
but there's a spot where you can cross.
And you have two months.
You have time.
It'll be okay. We trained a lot.
Trained?
- So close!
- You can do it!
Nat!
Yeah!
Emma, are we really...
It's all right.
As long as the first person can cross...
Whoa, hey!
Yay!
Okay, we're up next!
Ready...
We did it!
All right, come on!
See you later, Ray!
You guys...
You guys... when did you...
Well?
What a smug face. How annoying.
Well, we were able to completely fool you.
You'll show me something cool,
so shut up and come, huh?
And isn't it cool?
Look.
It's a scenery we never thought we would see.
Yeah.
I thought it wouldn't be possible
to take everyone.
I thought they would be a hindrance.
I hesitated too.
But in the end, I made a decision,
and it's thanks to Emma.
Everyone joined with full faith
because it's Emma.
She's reckless and unreasonable,
but she's honest,
and can say we're taking everyone
without a second thought.
You don't have to give up, Ray.
- Did you find them?
- No, keep looking!
Those children haven't appeared
at the bridge yet?
Not yet. Leave no stone unturned. Find them!
Why?
Could they be...
Just five more!
Emma, what should I do?
My hands... I'm sorry!
When I think that there's a cliff below...
I start to think... What if I fall?
Fall?
It's okay, Jemima.
Let's cross together.
Ray.
Emma.
You still have the rope we used
to pull everyone up, right?
Y-Yeah!
Can you tie Jemima to me using that?
Do you know how to go down?
I saw what everyone did.
How about you guys?
Don't tell me you can't do this.
W-We'll be fine!
Y-Yeah, super easy!
Well said.
Let's go, Jemima.
See? We got here, Jemima.
I lose, Norman.
Okay, you're the last one! Let's go, Emma!
Goodbye, House.
Goodbye, our home that we loved so much.
Goodbye... Mom.
Don't go, Emma.
My dear children...
Isabella!
You scared me.
I'm sorry. I was climbing trees
and I heard a beautiful song, so...
Did you compose it, Leslie?
Yeah.
It's a lovely melody.
What's the name of the song?
It doesn't have a name.
It's amazing. Let me hear more of it!
But it's embarrassing,
so don't tell everyone else.
Okay.
I'm going to put you in charge of Plant Three
starting next year.
Yes, understood.
Ray.
How do you know that song?
Hey, Mom.
Why did you give birth to me?
Well, Ray...
it was for survival.
Longer than anyone.
But I guess I've had enough.
I lost.
Go on.
Please be careful.
And I pray that you will find light.
Mom.
Don't worry. They escaped safely.
I'm sorry, everyone.
You must have been cold and lonely.
We did it.
We did it, Norman!
It's the outside! We made it out!
I'll definitely come back to get everyone else.
Today we take the first step.
It's our first morning.