Takeo sometimes puts other people's
feelings before his own,
because he just wants the
other person to be happy...
I think that was the first time I've ever screamed.
You okay?
I'm fine.
I'm home.
My Heart
My cheap, plastic umbrella wouldn't
have kept her dry, anyway.
I'm happy for her.
Yamato Rinko
Takeo-kun?
Hey.
Thanks for coming by today!
No problem.
I thought I saw you in the city today.
Were you there?
No, you probably imagined it.
Oh, okay.
Maybe I just imagined it because
I wanted to see you.
Oh!
What are you doing two days from now?
I don't have a shift that day.
Do you want to go somewhere?
Lately, we haven't spent much time together.
You're right.
Well, honestly, I just want to see you.
Yamato...
I want to see you, too.
I love her.
Thank you.
Yamato-chan, you always look
like you're enjoying your job.
Yes, I'm having fun.
I'm just happy being around cakes all day.
But I guess I've learned a lot I didn't know
about hardships and challenges that
weren't obvious to me before.
Rinko, about the cakes for the competition.
Yes?
I'd like to brainstorm tomorrow
because it's a holiday.
Help me out.
Um, but tomorrow...
Please!
My whole career as a pâtissier hangs on this!
The beach or the mountains?
Which to pick?
Only two options?
Hey, Yamato!
About tomorrow—
Takeo-kun, I'm sorry!
I can't hang out with you tomorrow.
I'm sorry, after I brought it up.
What happened?
Ichinose-san's going to be in a competition.
He said his career depends on it.
I'm supposed to be helping him, so...
Then we should support him.
Good luck prepping for the competition, Yamato.
Okay.
What can you say?
His career's on the line...
Of course you have to support that.
From: Yamato Rinko
The Competition's Right Around the Corner
The district prelims are in one week.
I'm sorry, Takeo-kun.
Thanks.
I did want to see you.
Love you lots  >_<
That's why I like Yamato.
That's the kind of person she is.
I'm a better fit for Rinko for sure!
She just doesn't know there are other
men who are a better fit for her!
Takeo, you're amazing!
Crap, all those guys.
Takeo, can you stand about a meter behind me?
Hey!
What do you guys want with my girlfriend?
Scary                         Is that his bodyguard or something?
You okay?
Yeah.
You're so cool, Osamu!
Thanks.
Love you.
It's weird not having Yamato-san here.
Yeah.
Is it okay
that Yamato's with me?
Other guys would be better for her.
Maybe Yamato just doesn't know anyone.
Of course it's okay!
What do you mean, she just doesn't know?
She isn't an idiot.
She made a conscious choice.
Actually, even if it's true, so what?
Me?
Even if the other guy's someone
who can easily do things I can't,
someone I can't beat,
or someone out of this world...
I don't want to lose her to anyone.
There you go, true love.
I can only make cookies that
are like rice crackers.
Next time, let's come with Rinko!
I can't talk about things that really interest Yamato.
I don't have a car.
And I can't even call her by her first name.
I guess I'm really selfish.
In the future, Yamato might decide
to choose someone else.
But for now...
For now, while she can smile by my side...
I won't let you have Yamato.
You came all the way here to tell me that?
That's right.
You thought I'd give up if you did?
No, but I won't let you have her.
I'll accept that as a challenge.
The outcome's already clear!
No, it isn't!!
No, it isn't!
Sunakawa
Wait, you should be the one being challenged.
I see!
Well, whatever.
We both like Yamato.
There's no advantage or disadvantage there.
You can be more aggressive about it!
Anyway, have a drink.
Yamato-san doesn't know?
Oof
How the pâtissier feels about her?
I don't think so.
He was interesting.
Was he?
Are you sure you can leave her alone with him?
Well...
From: Yamato Rinko
I'm going to work with Ichinose-san
after my shift tonight.
Wish me luck!  p (^ - ^) q
I can't come up with anything that feels right.
Huh?
They're all great.
I know that...
Yeah, none of them are bad.
But none of them call out to me.
...Yes
I don't get the same feeling I had
when I met you and thought you were my muse.
I don't feel like I've met the one...
Let's keep trying!
I'll try hard, too!
I think I understand what
you mean by that feeling!
Did Rinko feel that, too?
A presence...
Rinko, can you pipe out those meringues for me?
Huh?
Sorry to make you come along.
I don't mind.
If I weren't here,
you'd get arrested.
What are you up to?
Did you come to interfere with Rinko and me?
So lame!!
No!
I thought you'd try to pull something
while the two of you were alone.
That's ridiculous!
Why would I spring something before we
feel the same way about each other?
Really?
Go home!
Right now, I want to focus on the competition!
Was it the Japan Snack Competition?
The "C'est Nouveau Pâtissier Competition"!
So you won't do anything?
Well, I'm sure we basically feel the
same way for each other anyway.
Of course not.
I'll take the proper steps.
No, you won't!
I kind of guessed what you were thinking!!
All right.
I trust you.
I'll get the gold medal in this competition.
I'll win it, and tell Rinko how I feel about her.
Ever since she came, things have
been looking up for me.
My whole world's begun to change.
I don't expect you to understand,
but Rinko is destined to be my muse.
When I open my own store in the future,
I want her to be there, as my muse.
That's a grand vision you've got.
I'll prove it to you by winning the gold medal.
The day of the competition
I won't let you have Rinko.
is the last day you'll be her boyfriend.
Good luck at the competition.
Hmph, acting tough, I see.
What was that? Wishing him luck?
He's been working hard every day,
even on his days off.
His career depends on it, too.
I'd like him to win the gold medal.
I have to work hard, too.
On what? Winning a gold medal?
On calling her by first name and stuff.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing, good luck.
By the way, what's a muse?
You look like you're having fun.
Let me try.
Th-These are meringues, too?
They're so wonderful!
Rinko...
Before I met you, I was alone.
I always felt misunderstood.
I was obsessing about how my creations
didn't sell out that one time,
and I was being stubborn.
How it feels to see a great cake and
wanting to make one yourself...
How good it feels to have someone buy your cake...
You're the one who made me remember that...
Remember how important that is, Rinko.
You're my muse.
Huh? What?
Not at all!! I'm so not!!
Don't do anything to her!!
Damn.
Takeo-kun says...
Um, he's my boyfriend, but...
He says they look like they're plastic.
Is she complaining?
His cookies are really assertive, too.
I bet she is.
They were just like him.
I want to eat them again.
They made a big impression.
I get it... They were grotesque.
That's it, Rinko!
Individualism! But a taste you want again and again.
An unforgettable impression...
I think I have an idea! I think it'll work!
Yes!
Oh, it's getting late.
Rinko, you go on ahead.
I'll work to make my idea into reality.
Excuse me.
Rinko, once the competition's over,
I want to tell you something.
Okay, good luck.
I bet we feel the same way about each other now.
It's done!
Yeah.
It's beautiful! It's all sparkly!
I want to try it! But it'd be such a waste.
I'll win the gold medal.
I'm sure of it.
I believe that, too.
I have you as my muse, Rinko.
The day of the competition,
you won't be able to help me.
But can you come to the competition?
Sure! I'll definitely come.
Maki, you're amazing.
This is the day of the snack competition.
If his words sway her, I'll...
Take, can you get that?
Oh, good morning.
Sorry, I'm here way too early.
Not a problem.
We're all early risers.
I texted you, but I didn't get a response.
Sorry, I left my cell somewhere.
What's wrong?
Ichinose-san has his competition today,
but he said he had something to tell me afterward.
I wonder if he's going to ask me if I
want to be a full-time employee.
It'd be so tempting, but I don't know what to do!
I know I'm dense,
but Yamato's something else, too.
He said I'm a source of strength for him
or something like that...
His muse, right?
Right.
How did you know that, Takeo-kun?
Um, just a hunch.
But I'm not a muse.
I don't have that kind of power... I'm normal
Is it pressure?
Oh, yes! It is!
I don't know what to do.
Maybe he means you help him to get
into his work when you're around.
Oh!
Okay.
Now I'm not so stressed about it.
I'm glad to hear that.
Talking to you always calms me down, Takeo-kun.
Okay, I'll get going.
I love her.
I don't want her with anyone else.
I don't want her to leave.
I want her smiling at my side forever.
T-Takeo-kun?
Good luck!
He'll win first place!
You mean the gold medal, Takeo-kun?
That didn't really calm me down.
My heart is pounding.
Want to go to the beach?
You're gonna eat that?
Yeah.
Doesn't that hurt?
What?
What's wrong?
Oh, it's just that you're a normal guy, after all.
I always have been.
Sure.
But seeing you unsure about yourself...
Being worked up for days on end...
Saying stuff about not wanting
to let other men have her...
I'm glad I got to see that side of you.
It'll be fine, I swear.
Yamato-san likes you.
Thanks.
I'm glad I have Suna.
Once you get a girlfriend and worry about
that stuff, I'll laugh at you, too!
You wouldn't laugh, not ever.
Wow, TV stations are here!
Makes you nervous...
It'll be fine.
I have my muse.
Let's win first place!
First place?
Oh, sorry, I meant let's get the gold medal!
Yeah, I'll win the gold medal for you, Rinko.
Huh?
Not for me. I want you to win it for yourself.
You mean, you want me to win it for the two of us.
Okay, got it.
Oh, so once it starts, I can't help you, right?
Yeah.
Is there anything I can help with beforehand?
Let me think.
I feel calm, and there's nothing to worry—
Ichinose
Bare
I left my tools at the store.
Huh?
I was so focused on bringing the ingredients...
There's still time,
How can this be? My muse is with me.
but if I go now, I won't return in time.
I can't ask the owner to leave the store to bring them.
It's impossible. I'm finished.
Don't give up!
You've been working so hard!
I know someone who can help when
something like this happens!
My muse is pretty tough...
Huh? You don't mean...
Oh, hello?
Takeo-kun!
Yamato? What's wrong?
Impossible...!
Um, we're at the competition site right now,
There's no way he'd help me!
Forget it, Rinko!!
but we forgot the equipment.
When does it start?
Huh?
At ten o'clock.
Okay, so in an hour!
Where are you?
The Shuuei Hotel!
What do they look like?
Um, they're in a black case.
My name's on it in white.
Okay, got it!
I'll get them there! Don't worry!
Why?
Okay!
Suna, I'm off!
I'll text you where it's happening.
Thanks!
I don't think he'll come.
Huh?
It'll be fine!
Takeo-kun will make it work somehow!
Could it be
that he's stupid?
He forgot...
Ichinose... his cake-making tools...
Huh?
Oh, wait a minute...
This, right?
He could've just called me,
and I would've come over.
Ichinose-kun must've been
worried about the store.
Oh, I'll give you money for a taxi...
Huh?
He looked faster than a taxi
He said he'd come, but I'm sure he'll run away.
If he helps me, he'll lose Rinko.
Sunakawa-kun? Where's Takeo-kun?
Takeo's headed for the competition
site with the equipment.
There's no way he'd come.
So he'll be there soon...
Takeo-kun will be here soon!
There's no way...
...he'd come.
Sir?
He came?!
Takeo-kun!
Express Messenger?!
Over here!
Did I get here in time?
And did he swim here or something?
What's with all that sweat?
Yeah! Thanks!
Good luck!
Th-Thanks.
Ichinose-san, it's almost time.
Right.
Can you stay, too?
I'll win the gold medal.
Got it.
C'est Nouveau Pâtissier Competition
He's a good man.
I wish him the best of luck.
Somehow, I feel like he's cheering me on.
What an idiot.
He can't have forgotten what I said
about winning the gold medal
and telling Rinko how I feel.
Good luck!!
Fine.
I don't really understand him,
but I'll acknowledge that Rinko's
boyfriend is a good man!
Okay, I'm done!
Everyone's work is complete,
so we'll begin judging.
All the cakes are pretty amazing.
Are you worried?
Yeah, I guess.
It'll be fine.
Ichinose-san will get it done!
Okay.
Takeo-kun?
I need to go to the bathroom.
They're near the entrance!
Okay.
Takeo.
Suna...
Why is it that the things that are so important,
like feelings, hearts, and souls,
are the things you can never see?
Okay, let's go.
Oh, Takeo-kun!
They'll announce the results in an hour!
That soon?
Oh, good job.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I was able to give it everything I had.
It's thanks to you.
I do owe you my thanks,
but I won't hold back.
Okay!
Takeo-kun, did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
It's nothing.
C'est Nouveau Pâtissier Competition
The silver medalists are Suzuki Shinya-san
and Mikura Hiroto-san.
And the gold medal of C'est Nouveau
Pâtissier Competition goes to
Ichinose Kouki-san!
Congratulations!
What inspired you to make this cake?
A flavor that honors individuality,
but keeps you coming back for more...
A cake that makes an unforgettable impression.
And finally, a cake with strength!
Wow.
He worked hard and produced results.
Congratulations! I'm so impressed!
Are you going to sell at the store?
You changed the cake again from when I saw it last.
Yeah.
I want to try it!
I was surprised by that!
I think I'll call this cake "Rinko."
Huh?
I'm dedicating this gold medal to you, Rinko.
Rinko, I love you!
From this day forward, will you
be my one, and only, muse?
Please go out with me.
I need you, Rinko.
Oh, I'm sorry...
That was so sudden, I was taken aback.
Yamato, I'll be fine.
Even if you don't choose me,
I'll support the decision that makes you happy.
But, Yamato...
I hope you'll choose me.
I hope you'll keep smiling with me.
I'd be happy to help you.
I do love your cakes.
But from the very first time I saw him,
my heart belonged to Takeo-kun.
The important things in life,
like feelings, hearts, and souls,
are all things you can never see.
The more you try to reassure
yourself that they exist,
the more you feel they don't exist at all.
But right now, I know for sure that they do exist.
They're so close, you can almost touch them.
You love him, huh?
Yes, I do!
Um, Ichinose-san...
I'm not a muse or anything like that.
I'm just a part-timer.
What helped you win the gold medal today
was your own ability.
I think it was your hard work and talent.
Why do you look like you're agreeing?
So please keep making wonderful cakes!
Of course.
So there you have it.
I know you're a good guy, but I'm
definitely a better fit for her...
Please take care of Rinko.
Got it.
So I was wrong.
She loves him.
Goodbye, my muse. Thank you.
I'm the one who thought wrong.
I'll become the best man in the world that
can make people happy with his cakes.
I'll be off.
Okay.
Suna, thanks!
Takeo-kun?
Did you know what was going to happen?
Yeah.
Since when?
Well... For a while.
I had no idea.
I didn't know how Ichinose-san felt.
Of course, I didn't know how you felt, either.
How you felt about what was going on with me...
I felt that I couldn't lose you.
Thank you for liking me,
Rinko.
Huh?
So this is how she would've looked if
I'd used her first name all this time.
I love her!
Someday, I'll be able to say that
like it isn't such a big deal.
Okay.
Be patient, okay?
Class 2-1
Hey, there's Sunakawa-kun.
That makes school festivals and trips even better!
Yay!
Hey, there's Takeo!
That makes sports festivals and trips even better!
Yay!
Guess we're in the same class for another year.
Yeah.
I wish I could've been in the
same class as Master...
I'm in the class next to Sunakawa-kun.
I couldn't have asked for more.
Please...
Thanks.
How many springs has it been?
Fourteen.
Nee-san...
Quit stalking me.
Nee-san! Nee-san! Nee-san!
Oh, this cake is called "Rinko."
C'est Nouveau Pâtissier Competition
Gold Medal Prize
Wow!
It has the same name as you, Rin-chan.
It's a great cake.
I made it so people who eat it
You'll become happy, too
would have a happy smile.
Suna, I managed not to mess up this time.
But if I lose sight of things again
and start going in the wrong direction...
Punch me, okay?
I think I'd break something.
I'd break me.
Here.
Th-Th-Th-Tha...
There was a giant guy!
Liar.
Seriously, he was like three meters.
He looked like the ogre from the
picture book I read yesterday!
Takeo-kun!
I'll stay on the right path,
so Yamato can understand all
the things that can't be seen.
Thank You for Watching
Thank you for watching!
I love you!