Chaos
SHOGI HALL
Why?!
Unbelievable!
B BLOCK
FINALS
A BLOCK
I clawed my way up to C-1,
the same as you,
driven by desperation and thoughts
of the day I would play against you.
TREMBLE
So why can't we play against each other?
ZA-BAM
Are you being shy, Kiriyama?!
Ugh, so noisy.
Why does he blame me?
BRISK
WALKING
We had more matches together at the kids'
tournaments back in elementary school!
There was no point in becoming a professional!
Then, we'll just have to...
become the winners of the Newcomer
Tournament's A Block and B Block,
and go up against each other in the finals,
otherwise we won't have
a single match together this year!
BRISK
WALKING
STOMP
Kiriyama, don't tell me you're thinking,
"After all, the Newcomer Tournament
is full of newbies, so this'll be easy."
It's called the "Newcomer Tournament,"
but don't underestimate it!
I am not underestimating it.
"KATSURA" ROOM
He made his move.
Kumakura 9th-Dan, Pawn to 2-7.
Um, Kishou Yanagihara, at this current point,
who would you like to support,
Meijin Souya or Kumakura 9th-Dan?
Well, I don't want to support either of them.
Be serious, Kiriyama!
- Arrogance leads to self-destruction!
- Pardon me.
- Hey, Kiriyama.
- Yo.
Yes, you're arrogant!
If I had to sum it up in one word,
it would be "chaos."
I'd go so far as to say
you're both arrogant and pompous!
I don't even know which of them is superior.
Where do you get that from?
But I need something!
A headline for the internet!
From everything!
The prodigy who turned professional
in middle school, destined to become Meijin!
Okay, how about, "The Meijin Battle's
final game is a close contest."
You've been relying on that reputation!
But Mr. Yanagihara...
Ugh, it's so noisy.
Issa, Smith.
Throw those two out.
Yep. At once.
Yes, sir. Right away!
Me too?
COMPACT...
Sheesh. That's what I hate about youngsters.
Don't use words to fight. Settle it with shogi.
Geez.
Whoa. Souya moved his Rook to 3-7.
Well, it's nice to see some enthusiasm,
don't you think?
I wish they would share a little
with their mentor.
You mean Mr. Shimada?
Recently he's been lacking ambition, right?
It's like he's lost or something.
Like you know, what happened to him?
In the Kishou Tournament qualifiers,
he kept making moves
that were unusual for him.
Maybe Mr. Souya sucked the soul
right out of him?
It looks like even his shadow
has become lighter, you know?
In fact, his shadow's not the only thing
that's been thinning out!
Whoa, calm down a little!
Guys who'll never get close to a title match
are so happy-go-lucky.
Gotou.
Instead of worrying
about another player's mental health,
you should worry about your own life,
and the possibility that it could end
without ever being in a title match.
Gotou.
That's a bit harsh.
Oh, Kumakura moved his Silver to 3-6.
As expected. I thought he might do that.
This is also...
...a good move.
Dammit!
Let it go. Come on.
There, you see? They left.
Who cares. Probably went to the can.
What are you going to do about this mood?
It's colder than ice in here now. Geez...
Everyone who's gotten their butts kicked
in a title match
will always lose their composure for a bit.
That's just...
...how it is.
"At this rate, I'll just lose."
That's what they come to realize
in between matches of a series.
They have to break themselves apart, and then
reconstruct it again from the shattered pieces.
They start over from square one.
It's the same for everyone.
Well, by "everyone," I mean players
who've experienced that.
I'm sure if you leave Shimada alone,
he'll just start winning again.
It just disgusts me...
to see people heckling others when they
themselves haven't even climbed into the ring.
And so, you're always slashing up everything
like a knife itself.
You're always so touchy.
What are you, a middle school student?
Geez, act like an adult already.
GLOOMY
Excuse us.
We haven't been in a title match at all.
So how much time is left?
Is this Souya's side?
Sheesh. You don't listen, do you?
Kuma just passed the one hour mark.
Tell me, Rei. What should I do?
I'm...
...scared.
Stay away from my sister for now on!
You're married, aren't you?
What are you thinking?
People who can't cherish their family are trash!
Trash, huh? And also unforgivable?
What are you?
Who?
A god?
This is good. This is bad.
Are you the one who decides all that?
I see.
I don't know.
To me, humans are the embodiment of chaos.
The person
who got mad on Mr. Shimada's behalf
and the person
who makes my older sister suffer
are living in the same body.
How should I...
Oh, he made a move.
Souya moved his Pawn to 3-9,
and promoted it.
What? Does he have time for that?
In that case, Bishop to 8-3.
And then, after that...
Should I hate him?
Or...
What is it, Gotou? You're leaving?
I have a match tomorrow.
Don't make Kouda cry too much.
Why do you always have this fierce stance?
Fierce? Are you saying I look like an ogre?
Then you're already aware of it.
ANGER ANGER ANGER ANGER
What's wrong, Kiriyama?
Oh, uh...
It's nothing.
For some reason,
I suddenly had the feeling she was near.
The last time I saw her was in March.
I thought about calling her after that,
but I stopped when I reached for the phone.
What should we even talk about?
Even if she were close to me,
the one standing next to her is...
Sometimes it'll look simple to unravel,
but other times it looks messed up and tangled.
If I had to put it in one word...
Then Mr. Yanagihara paused
for a moment before muttering...
"Chaos."
Chaos
Kumakura
The seventh game on the second day
of the 69th Meijin Battle.
It's been a close contest that has required
a full set of games, but this is the final game.
This game will decide the winner.
Because of the dinner break,
both players have less time,
but their expressions look calm.
Meijin Souya has won five times, totaling 11 wins.
Will he retain the title of "Meijin" today?
Or will Kumakura 9th-Dan, the challenger
for the fourth time in a row, seize the title?
Ah, Meijin Souya has made his move.
Bishop to 4-4.
This is...
What do you think, commentator Mr. Tsujii?
Tsujii 9th-Dan at The Match's Commentary Hall
This is an unusual move.
Why did he do that?
It's not a Bishop to 3-7 promotion,
nor is it a Dragon to 3-7.
It feels like he wasted a move.
It doesn't have any special meaning.
That's because this is a free-for-all.
It's like saying, "Go ahead, think about this."
It happens.
I don't think even Souya
would know what to do anymore.
I get it. Yes, yes.
Then at this stage, could we say
Kumakura 9th Dan has a slight advantage?
BAM
Indeed! I'm sure Kumakura 9th Dan
will do a dodge move next.
He'll probably make his move quickly.
Wait. This is...
I lost.
What? Oh, he resigned.
Kumakura 9th Dan has resigned!
Meijin Souya has defended his title!
R-Resigned?!
Wait a second! Suddenly?
Hey, get the camera!
- The observer isn't even in there!
- Hello? He resigned!
- Hurry!
- Where's Mr. Nakamura, the observer?
Kumakura resigned. I said, he resigned!
Please hurry!
Huh? Resigned? All of a sudden?
Mr. Kumakura, why?
Wasn't that too soon? He still had moves...
I mean, I thought he had the upper hand.
No. He was checkmated.
At precisely the 17th move.
King, same.
Pawn to 1-4.
Lance, same.
King, same.
It's true.
No one noticed.
But when it's played out, there's no denying it.
At this point, he was trapped,
no matter where he moved.
It's all in vain.
Souya.
Brilliant.
I didn't train enough.
That's all I can say.
For this next year, I'll fight off everyone
in the rank-deciding competitions
and train hard
so I can come back and sit here again.
Oh, man. He's so cool.
K-Kumakura 9th Dan gives me goosebumps!
I want to be like him!
How can he be so calm about it?
Right after a full set of matches?
Ah, Kengo is so cool!
Is it confidence?
Starting at square one and fighting through
Class A, the den of demons, over and over,
swearing that he'll be sitting
in front of the champion next year, too...
Sorry I took so long.
Here, toner, lotion, and they had a new
moisturizing cream, so I tossed that in.
I think that should do it.
Sorry for the hassle. I won't stop sneezing
if I go into places like that.
VACANT
TAKEN
See you. Thanks again.
Want me to go with you?
I'll thank you properly next time.
Later.
Central Hospital.
Hey.
I'm here.
Misako.
You're late!
Why are you here?
Here. I picked these up for you.
You were collecting too many claim checks.
Claim checks? From my wallet earlier!
Enough. Get up.
I'll throw you in a taxi.
PHOOEY
Forget it. I'm staying over.
No way. If I did that,
you would definitely attack me.
A-Attack?
98% BULLSEYE
I-I wouldn't!
BLUSH
Then never mind. I'm leaving!
I'm going home!
Good.
Will you walk me to the taxi stand?
Yeah, sure.
Why don't you at least
put your dry cleaning inside?
Oh, right.
GLEAM
When all is said and done,
your defenses are weak, huh?
That's why I take advantage of you.
Whatever, just go home.
I'm really tired.
That's okay, just go to sleep.
Pay me no attention.
Fine. You're so troublesome. Come here.
PING
SHINE
What? Hey, what is this?
Goodnight.
H-Hey! What is this? Untie me!
How could you!
My clothes will get wrinkly!
And I need to get my makeup off! Hey!
ROLL
GRAB
Deep shadows under his eyes...
He probably hasn't slept well in a long time.
His face is pale.
Ugh... Idiot.
Now I can't get mad at you.
Not after you show me this face.
The next day,
Kumakura 9th Dan took the early morning
limited express train and left Hakone behind.
Um, Chairman, excuse me...
Huh? What is it?
When we entered the room
to clean it this morning...
CRUMBLE
...it was in this state.
RUINED
I thought I should show it to you.
Kumakura! That bastard!
It's not funny!
I see! So he kicked the hell out of the wall.
That Kuma!
He is definitely going to pay
for the damages and a severe penalty!
I'll send him to shogi events on department store
rooftops during sweltering summer vacation!
To think he would
kick a hole in the wall after losing.
Oh, Kuma.
I get it though. It must have been frustrating.
It couldn't have been
anything other than frustrating.
Kumakura
Next Episode Preview
Episode 25
First we both have to clear
the qualifying round.
I didn't know that cool-looking person
has been hiding such passion.
On the surface, it seemed cool,
like a good match for cold, green tea.
Let's see... A duck?
It all brings back memories.
"March Comes in Like a Lion".
Please watch it next time too.
Kumakura! I need to talk to you!