Is that...
...a mummy?
It looks like a princess or something to me.
Cecil!
Th-The body...
Chapman...
Did I get her?
Damn you...
Tilarna!
Get back, Kei!
Shit!
What the hell was that thing?
A lauden neiven. In your language, a "vampire."
A vampire? I thought she was
some kind of weird pervert.
So that shriveled-up corpse turned into
a hot naked chick and attacked somebody?
Not a chance. Did she just
plump up like instant ramen?
It wasn't a body.
Lauden neiven possess
terrifying regenerative powers.
No matter how much damage their bodies take,
they can absorb latena,
the power humans use to live, and revive.
I see. Vampires, huh?
Their race was destroyed many years ago.
But I guess one survived.
If I'd only been more cautious,
I would've noticed sooner.
But I let someone die.
You saved Cecil, right?
But...
Don't let it get to you.
The more important problem
is that the monster's still out there.
We've got an emergency warrant out, but...
You doreany can't possibly catch her.
I don't know about that.
My bullets and your sword
seemed to hurt her just fine.
If she gets surrounded by
a SWAT team, that'll be that.
SWAT?
Those guys.
They're athletic and have great aim.
I don't train at all, so they're
a lot more reliable than me.
Accuracy doesn't matter.
What matters is your sense of smell in combat.
For example, why did you have a fire
extinguisher when you ran down to save me?
Because... I don't know.
It just felt like the right thing to do.
That's what I mean by sense of smell.
You're an unpleasant man,
but in that sense, you're worthy of respect.
Is that a compliment?
Idiot.
I'm concerned about the other "bolicemen."
I see.
Lauden neiven are far too dangerous.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm getting a ride home.
And Tilarna, thanks.
There's been another victim.
Where?
Alamo Park. She killed a truck driver.
We've got witnesses, too.
Alamo? That's outside the cordon we set up.
How'd she get so far?
I called you here to find out.
Can she move that fast
after she got an arm cut off?
I don't know. They're an old race.
"I don't know" isn't good enough.
If we don't find her,
more people are going to die.
How are you going to fix that?
Well...
That's why I was opposed to this.
No good will come of having
a Semanian on the force.
Civilized society has its own set of rules,
and this little girl can't--
I think that's enough, Superintendent.
People are dying while
you're standing here bitching.
What did you say?
If it weren't for the girl,
Cecil Epps would be dead,
the vampire would've gotten out
without anybody noticing,
and nobody would've known
a thing was wrong until morning.
If anything, we're damn lucky
it worked out the way it did.
Inspector Zimmer, what are you--
And Exedilica works for me, damn it!
You got a problem with her,
you come to me first, kid!
Let's go.
I didn't see that coming.
He's just a snot-nosed kid.
He used to piss himself all the time
when he was a new recruit for the LA Police.
What, you got a problem, too?
Nope. Not at all.
Then don't let every damn thing
surprise you like that, idiot.
Aye aye, sir.
Matoba, how would you find her?
We can assume the vampire doesn't
know anything about Earth society.
She can't do anything fancy to escape.
A K-9 unit would be the way to go.
The police dogs are already out there.
We've got one right here.
So she killed the guy while he was driving,
and the truck crashed?
Maybe she's an idiot?
I don't know.
It's possible she didn't attack the witnesses
because she deliberately wanted them alive.
Let's ask.
Her arms? She had both of them.
She regenerated them, then.
She got out of the truck and looked at us,
but then she ran that way.
Was she naked?
I couldn't tell...
It felt like she was wearing
a black evening dress, but...
But it had, like, a haze around it,
and kept shimmering... It was like...
Like flames?
Yeah. Like black flames burning.
That's "Vau e Deie."
"Vau e"...?
What's that?
One of the basic illusion spells.
It can also serve as clothing.
Which means she's got enough
of her power back to use magic.
Can you use this Va... Vau...
Vau e Deie. And yes, I can.
Let me see it.
No. You can't use it
when you're wearing clothes.
And it disappears immediately
if you lose concentration.
I see.
Don't imagine it.
I am not.
No, I could tell you were by your face!
I know you're doing it!
What gives a person of lowly birth like you
--the right to look at me naked?
--Shut up.
We need to deal with the vampire.
Where'd she go?
Oh, yeah. Let me see...
That building.
The shopping mall.
I think she's in there.
That's the opposite of the way
the witnesses said she went.
And the police dogs, too.
But from that building,
you can overlook this area.
So she left the body for us to find
in order to see how the cops would react.
Yes. Now that she's filled her belly,
what she wants most of all
is information about this city.
She probably thinks she can escape
from most people who'd try to surround her...
I see. You're smart.
Was that sarcasm?
Nope. I'm impressed.
No, you were insulting me.
I could tell from your voice.
You're a nasty guy.
It's true! I...
Forget it. Anyway, we're off to the mall.
That's right. I want as many men
down here as you can give me.
But make sure nobody's alone for an instant.
And if you find her, don't try to catch her.
Kei.
Give me a second.
I can smell the vampire's latena.
She went inside from here.
Got it.
Nothing on the security system, it looks like.
She didn't trip the lasers.
You sure?
Can she see lasers, you think?
We'll go after her.
If you find something, call me.
Well?
She's close.
I can't tell what direction, though.
Ambush?
Possibly. Stay sharp.
You're in the way.
No, you're in the way!
It's stronger.
What is?
Her presence. Be careful.
Careful of what?
Kei!
Damn you!
Kei! Kei!
Wake up, Kei!
Why don't you give him a kiss, Tony?
It might wake him up.
Alex, that's sexual harassment.
For you or him?
He woke up!
Tony... Godnov... What are you doing here?
We lost touch with you, so we came to save you!
And we saw you floating in the fountain...
Where's Tilarna?
Not here. What happened?
She was taken...
That goddamn vampire...
I'll get her for this.
You fell from up there?
I'm amazed you're still alive.
Got a smoke?
Nope. I don't smoke.
I'm amazed you're still alive.
You're awake, young swordswoman?
Vampire.
Why have you not killed me?
I have questions for you.
What is this place?
Such strange letters.
How do you read them?
San-Tirysei? No, San-Teresa.
I see. So this is another world, isn't it?
They call it "Earth."
So the greater gate spoken of
in the Book of Niba manifested?
The Book of Niba?
An old legend.
Now then...
Such a noble scent.
Your blood must taste delicious.
Monster!
Oh?
You killed innocent people!
That's what a beast does!
You don't seem to understand what hunger is.
If only we had time...
Tch. It seems we've been interrupted.
Tilarna!
Kei!
Don't resist!
Hands up!
No! She's invincible right now!
Fascinating. How many of you should I eat?
I can't see her!
Get them out of here! She'll kill them all!
What?
We can see her. This'll work.
Keep shooting! She's just like a bear!
Extremely tough...
Shit. She got away again.
Tilarna, you okay?
I'm fine.
Then let's follow her. Come with me.
What are you doing? Hurry!
I know that! Don't yell at me!
Dummy.
Such terrifying weapons...
Who are they?
This isn't just some other world.
Am I in hell?
You'll find a grate up ahead.
Use it to escape underground.
A spell?
Hurry.
Why the hell can't we find her?
We've searched every inch of this damn mall!
So maybe she's not in the mall.
There's a subway 500 meters to the south.
And it's connected to the
mall's ventilation system.
An air duct, huh?
It's faster to go around
to the East Plaza Station
and ambush her than try to go after her.
I'll send you the location.
Let's go.
Damn it, I've been running all the time lately!
It's gonna make me a healthy man.
Sounds great to me.
You won't have to ride in those awful cars.
I can smell her.
I think she's close!
So we were right, huh?
I don't know if that's good luck or bad.
Kei.
What?
I want to capture that
vampire alive if possible.
Don't be stupid!
You saw how strong she is!
We can't hold back on her!
That's why I said "if possible."
Did talking to her make you sympathetic?
You take pity on her for having to run
around in a town she's never seen before?
Well...
Don't forget. She's killed two people already.
I know that.
She almost killed Cecil, too.
I know that!
There's just something I want to ask her!
It's so cold...
An honor to meet you,
descendant of the old blood.
A wizard?
Indeed. I apologize for being so forward.
What do you hope to gain by saving me?
Tell me what it is you desire.
The Book of Niba.
Oh?
I thought you might know something
about such an ancient book...
I understand now.
Were you the one who had me brought here?
Not at all. I wish merely to help you.
I need no help.
Begone.
But with your current strength,
you'll be hard-pressed to escape.
Do you hear?
Those two...
My, my. They take their jobs very seriously.
You know them?
A little. Now, hurry.
I will have this man guide you.
Shocking... I'm disappointed,
bearer of the old blood.
I died long ago in an ancient war.
This is just a brief dream before the end.
And so...
Another body.
A worker? No, but...
Damn you!
Wait! Sheesh...
She's in the way.
Got her!
She's so damn tough!
Is that even possible?
Shit... This is not good!
Get off! Do you want to die here with me?
No man has ever survived
three battles with me.
I see. Perhaps you were the warrior
spoken of in the prophecy.
Now suffer.
Is she... dead?
Looks like it.
She was smashed to pieces, so...
More importantly, Kei,
I haven't heard any thank-yous from the man
who should've been smashed to pieces, too.
I didn't ask for your help.
That again?
What is wrong with you? For one thing--
Thanks...
...is a word you'll never hear me say.
Now let's call for backup.
Next time I'm not saving you!
Not a chance in hell!
No matter what!
Fine!
Anyway, we need to start on those reports...
People who get to rest in a coffin
when the sun comes up sure have it easy...
"Next Time"
Next time on COP CRAFT.