Yum!
Delicious! So juicy...
No sign of the goblins...
Maybe they aren't coming?
We can't lower our guard, Marie.
Crusty's forward strike force has
reached Narashino, right?
They're heading toward the main goblin battalion.
Their fight might decide our fate here.
Serara...
I have a favor to ask.
Kasumi Lake, West
Japan Server
Zantleaf Peninsula/ Kasumi Lake
Field/ Monsters Present
Entry Restrictions/ None
Events/ The Goblin King's Return
Go ahead, open your eyes.
It's starting.
Direct strike to the enemy vanguard's center.
My lord, the main attack force can now advance.
Hill Giant, Lv. 72          Hill Giant, Lv. 80
Rank/ Raid 1          Rank/ Raid 1
Reinforcements. Two hill giants.
Healers should flank both sides.
Start by annihilating the smaller side groups.
Main force, continue to advance.
He is...
enjoying the fight.
But...
Why does he seem so sad? So lonely?
Chasing After Them
Chasing After Them.
Midraunt Equestrian Park
Japan Server
League of Freedom Cities, Eastal/ Funabashi Area
No Monsters
No PVP
Skill Use Permitted
Entry Restrictions/ None
Events/ The Goblin King's Return
Come in.
Resupply team 5, depart.
Continue to advance.
Roger. Departing.
Come in.
Maintain position until further orders.
This is Narashino.
As planned, we've rendezvoused.
Understood. Location confirmed.
The Ocypete has met up with
the second Akihabara group.
Roger.
Come in.
Please confirm location.
Once they complete some maintenance,
they'll set out for Choushi.
Understood.
Seems the telepathy communication
network is working.
Each squad has a leader, and squads
can communicate with one another.
And they have a contact at headquarters
with whom they can speak, as well.
This supports smooth communication among squads.
Crusty and his force are kicking butt, too.
Looks like it's going well, right?
Choushi is the problem.
What's the issue?
Victory isn't going to be overly hard.
But after the battle ends,
the goblins will flee in all directions.
They might attack the People of the Land's villages.
To prevent this, we've been surrounding
the goblins as we attack,
leading them to a single point.
But we must also protect the town of Choushi...
Or our encirclement will be broken.
The town of Choushi is the most
critical point in this plan.
I get it...
My lord...
You aren't going to the battle?
I want to go...
But until all platoons have
deployed, I can't move.
I see...
Are you really all right?
With what?
"With what"?
Of course, I, Rundel Haus Code,
am in perfect shape!
I feel like no one in the world can stop me.
Good, all clear!
I hope it will stay that way.
Don't worry.
If we all work together, the goblins are nothing.
What's wrong?
What is that?
That's more than a few hundred.
A thousand, I'd imagine.
If that many rush into the town together...
I can't let the kids do anything reckless again.
But...
Marielle!
Let's hit them first!
Yes, let's destroy them before
they can reach the town!
Nyanta, let us go!
Meow.
Marie!
Give us the order to fire everyone up!
Everyone, thank you for all you've done.
Help us out just a bit more...
Just one more fight.
I believe in all of you!
Let's go!
Forward!
Everyone, let's split into teams,
to be ready for a second wave.
Tohya, our party will focus on support.
Okay, got it!
Leave it to me!
Shiroe!
The camp group, in Choushi, has just
made contact with the sahuagin.
There are sixty adventurers and
at least a thousand sahuagin.
They're overwhelmed!
Tell the Ocypete to hurry!
135 km Remaining to Meinion Coast
(Half Gaia distance)
Wait.
Right now, our job is to recover our MP.
Naotsugu, here.
Thanks.
Whirlwind Slash!
Tohya has grown stronger.
Yeah. He still has a ways to go...
But he'll get stronger.
Same goes for Serara.
She used to only think about healing...
Please, Wolfy!
But now she's using offensive techniques,
and remembering to summon her companion.
Also, the bard girl and the sorcerer boy...
Dance of Pavane!
They back each other up as if they can
understand each other's thoughts.
Burned Strike!
Rundel Haus is a walking bundle of vigor.
He's putting all his feeling and
emotion into his magic.
And...
Rudy, try to keep your output down.
Roger.
Serara!
We're good on healing.
Go back on attack!
All right!
Guardian Barrier
Eight seconds until Guardian Barrier!
Minori keeps a constant eye on
the big picture as she fights.
Her friends' teamwork,
enemy location,
enemy encounter order,
enemy defeat order...
Like writing each enemy defeat as a sentence,
each battle as a chapter,
and collecting all those chapters
into a book called Tactics.
The way she's fighting is just like Shiro.
To the percent, and in thirty-second increments,
I suppose...
I think he meant that he was fighting by
looking thirty seconds into the future.
One percent is how closely he
tracks his allies' remaining MP.
Tracking the MP of allies in different classes
is impossible without monitoring the status screen.
But he can track it to a percent,
Luceheart of the Seven Prisons, Lv. 95        Mad Carousel Golem, Lv. 82
Bonus Damage: 1000P                                                              Rank/ Raid 1
Move Speed Decreased                                                      Lapis Fly, Lv. 84
Accuracy Decreased                                                          Dodge Decreased
Rank/ Raid 1                                                                              Rank/ Party
as well as the enemy status,
Nyanta
Status/ In Combat
Naotsugu
to predict where the battle
will be in thirty seconds.
He makes everything proceed
the way he wants it to.
That's Shiro's fully controlled combat...
The full-control encounter.
Tohya, move back a bit!
Serara, group heal, please!
Roger!
Of course, we actually live in this world now...
So I doubt he can see a full thirty
seconds ahead, as he once could.
But what Minori's attempting is,
without doubt, an imitation
of Shiro's full-control encounter.
Minori is chasing after Shiroe.
Who knows how many seconds
ahead she can see?
That sound...
It's the druid's special attack
magic, Shrieker Echo.
I had Serara set it up as a warning system!
I'm sure the goblins are returning!
We'll go, master!
Again?
Wait, Rudy!
U-Um, you do your best, too, Nyanta!
Hey, you guys!
Naotsugu...
We can handle the goblins.
Isuzu the bard is with us,
so we have good sustain.
We'll go!
H-Hey!
Minori!
I'll be the operator.
Serara, focus on healing.
But you're the field monitor, Minori...
I'll handle keeping up everyone's MP.
Goblins!
There are a lot.
We need to get them all together.
But the samurai skills aren't fast enough.
Rudy!
Leave it to me!
I shall show you the beautiful
melody of my magic!
Serpent Bolt!
Here they come!
Isuzu!
Right!
Slow Snail's Ballad!
Now, let's go!
Head Splitter!
Frost Spear!
Dis—
Dismissal!
I did it!
I got mine, too!
Same here!
Miss Isuzu, did you see
my lovely magic?
I sure did. Good job.
It sort of feels like you're making fun of me.
Hmm, am I?
Wh-What?
Just kidding.
I'm not making fun of you!
Really?
I can only see five seconds ahead,
in five-percent increments.
If I'm lucky, maybe ten seconds.
I can't do it as well as Shiroe yet...
That close to the town...
Let's hurry!
Shiro!
The Ocypete will be there in an hour.
Hang on until then.
Everyone, reinforcements will arrive in an hour.
Keep it up!
Yeah!
Rudy!
I'm fine.
Rudy's MP is low.
How long will this fight take?
Everyone...
I have a message from Marielle.
A ship carrying reinforcements will be here soon.
When it comes, they'll be able
to send some help our way.
Really?
Just a little more... Let's keep it up!
Good... I was getting worried.
I'm starving.
Rain?
Dire Wolf, Lv. 32
Rank/ Party
A dire wolf!
And it isn't alone...
Willow Spirits!
Emergency Spell: Prayer to the Four Quarters!
Minori
Please stop!
Serara, focus on the dire wolf.
But then I can't heal.
I'll handle the healing!
Two dire wolves and the hobgoblins...
If they attack at once, Tohya won't...
Tohya,
you take the hobgoblins
and one of the wolves.
Rudy! Isuzu!
Prayer to the Four Quarters will
last another thirty-two seconds.
Before it runs out...
Okay!
Roger!
When you encounter a difficult opponent,
there are a number of different strategies.
One example is to eliminate the weaker ones first.
By lowering the number of potential attackers,
you also limit the amount of damage they deal.
Frigid Wind!
Resonance Beat!
Tohya!
Miss Isuzu, we must eliminate
that other dire wolf now!
Yeah.
No!
The healing can't keep up!
Two dire wolves and the hobgoblins...
If Tohya's HP keeps going down like this...
In nine seconds, Tohya will...
Eight seconds until I can cast
Purification Barrier again.
No, a barrier like that won't
work against these opponents.
If Tohya loses...
If he loses...
Rudy!
Mister Tohya!
Leave the doggies to me!
That's crazy!
Rudy, you're a...
Don't worry, Miss Isuzu!
I won't lose to these mutts!
Rudy!
Don't underestimate me... I am...
I am Rundel Haus Code...
An adventurer!
Rudy!
If we don't do something...
I'll do it.
Nature Revive!
The revival spell isn't working?
Why?
Minori, try another!
Soul-call Prayer!
It isn't working.
Why not?!
I'm sorry.
Rudy... Rudy is...
Rudy is...
one of the People of the Land.
He joined our party,
adventured with us, ate with us...
But Rudy is...
Adding you now...
Huh?
Why?
Are you one of the People of the Land?
Would you keep it secret from
the others, Miss Isuzu?
But...
I'm going to become an adventurer.
That's why he worked so hard.
Why he was so desperate...
I couldn't tell him that he
couldn't be an adventurer...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
No way... Rudy is one of
the People of the Land?
Then we can't revive him?
Serara, try another revival spell!
It's still on cool down.
Maybe a healing spell?
When I heal him, it feels like
there's some small response...
But I'm sorry.
If reviving doesn't work...
There's still hope!
Help us, please... Shiroe!
Shiroe, we need your help!
Rundel Haus is dead.
He is one of the People of the Land.
The People of the Land cannot revive.
That is the law of this world.
But to grant Minori's wish,
Shiroe challenges the laws...
For a true friend,
who would travel the world with you to
find a dawn that no one has ever seen.
Contract
Next time: Contract.
We will change the world.