Eat this! Finishing
move: Isshin Zenzanken!
Hup!
Go on back to being a naked ape!
Impossible!
Hup!
Ta-dah!
That's...!
Yep, the other half
of your Scissor Blade!
I pulled this out of your dad!
Wait... It was you?
Yep! It was me!
I was the one who killed your father!
BITCH!
Answer me! Why did you kill my dad?!
EPISODE 12
SPIT YOUR SADNESS AWAY
Dad said that as long
as I had this scissor,
I'd be sure to find the
person who killed him.
And he was right!
It was you that was at my
house that day, wasn't it?!
Yep! Right you are.
Why did you do it?! Why
did you kill my dad?!
You know the reason why.
Me? Don't screw with me!
I don't know the first
thing about my dad!
But you're wearing the reason why.
Wearing? You mean Senketsu?
Yep! Your dad meddled in things
that no human should meddle in.
One of those "taboo" deals.
But taboos, they feel so good, you know?
What is it with this woman's hands?
They're cold as ice!
It's so silky smooth!
That's 100% Life Fiber for sure!
Don't dodge the question!
Don't be that way, I'm
not dodging anything.
We finally got the chance to meet,
so let's do something that's more fun!
Get real!
Why the hell would I play around
with the person who killed my dad?!
Gosh, you're so narrow-minded.
Hate and love are two
sides of the same coin.
It's like a finely-tailored suit
with a good, sturdy lining.
In other words, the deeper the
hatred, the deeper the love grows.
Like hell it does!
Now, now. You're so lovely
when you're angry, Ryuko!
Shut up!
Calm yourself, Ryuko.
Your blood is starting to boil.
You're too worked up!
It's another red thread!
That's its Banshi? This is bad news!
I'm just dying to see you naked!
What the—?
Now!
That's a Kamui for you.
I guess this means that it has
more than one Banshi, huh?
That's right!
I'm not so flimsy that I'll come undone
because of something like that!
How wonderful!
I can't believe he was hiding something
like that! That sly old dog.
He had me completely fooled!
Who are you?
I'm here to play!
To play?
SIX MONTHS EARLIER MATOI
UNDERGROUND LABORATORY
I heard that you've been up to all
sorts of fun things here, Doctor.
So play with me, too!
Ah, I see.
You're here because you
caught wind of my research.
Yep! I gave my word to an acquaintance
of mine that I'd bring it back.
And I have to keep my word.
A Shape Memory Lab Coat, eh?
If it has that ability,
you wove Life Fibers into that
lab coat, too, didn't you?
Yay for me! That means
I can play for realsies!
C'mon, stop holding back.
Go all-out when you play.
Life's no fun if you don't!
This is what I dedicated
my life to developing!
It cuts and kills Life Fibers.
And so, I have named
them Rending Scissors!
RENDING SCISSORS!
Doctor, your taste in names is terrible.
Scientists don't care how
well something goes over!
Not if the results of
his research are sound!
You're pretty good with
those whatever-scissors!
Careful, that's dangerous!
It looks like it takes a lot of
strength to use those scissors.
You really ought to exercise more.
Lay off! A scientist only begins
to hit his stride at 60!
Gosh, these really do halt all
Life Fiber activity, don't they?
That's our Dr. Matoi!
These scissors are a force
to be reckoned with, huh?
How does it feel to
have your life taken
by the very research you
dedicated your life to?
It's the best, isn't it?!
Aren't I nice?
Spare me your drivel...
Well, I need to take these with me.
Dad! Dad!
Dad?
Ah, so half of the Rending
Scissors was stolen,
but he managed to keep me hidden.
I'd expect nothing less from Dr. Matoi.
So it was you that I saw that day?!
It was.
If I'd known a cute thing
like you was coming,
I would've stayed put
instead of running!
Get serious, damn it!
Do you think you can avenge
your father like this?
Nope, nope, nope!
That's the last straw!
Stop it, Ryuko!
It's dangerous for your
blood to get this hot!
If you keep this up, I won't be
able to hold myself together!
Damn! That's what you
were after, Nui Harime?
I'm going down!
Yay, that's more like it!
Now things have gotten fun!
It's no good. She's
completely out of control.
You mean she's been swallowed
up by the power of the Kamui?
Matoi's body can't
handle this for long.
She'll probably die of
blood loss in minutes.
DIE OF BLOOD LOSS
Die of blood loss?!
We have to give her an ablution!
You mean transfusion.
My daddy steals people's blood at
work and sells it for lots of money
so I've seen lots of
death from blood loss!
Hey, wait. What do you mean by—
When people die of blood
loss, that means they die!
That goes without saying.
It does not! Ryuko dying is not cool!
After all, I'm the daughter
of a back-alley doctor,
Stop the dying from blood loss!!
Stop the blood stealing!
Things have taken a
disturbing turn, I see.
Sanageyama!
Oh, you're not dead, wild monkey?
Thanks to you, I got
plenty of data on Banshi.
Until I settle things with Matoi.
I will not die.
Sanageyama... You're...
Put on some clothes.
This is a disaster.
Keep her pinned down for me, Tsumugu.
Understood.
Lady Satsuki, are you all right?
The destruction of the polling
place can no longer be prevented.
I want you four to
evacuate the students.
I had no idea a Kamui had
this kind of power...
I will stop her.
Life Fiber Override: Kamui Junketsu!
KAMUI JUNKETSU
You handle this.
Right!
Wait, Ryuko!
Don't waste it! Blood
is worth lots of money!
Hey, Mako! What's up?
Daddy!
We drove here 'cause we wanted
to see Ryuko's fight in person!
C'mon, Sis, tell us
where we can sneak in!
Where is the arena?
This is no time to be joking around!
This is a job for Mankanshoku,
Back-alley Doctor!
BACK-ALLEY DR. MANKANSHOKU
HOUSE CALL
I don't know what's going
on, but leave it to me!
Wait for me, Ryuko!
You've got the daughter of a
back-alley doctor on your side!
Keep it up, keep it up!
You're turning more and
more into a monster!
This is how Life Fibers ought to be!
As I feared, you've been swallowed
up by your clothing, too.
And what are you?
I don't need to identify myself to you.
You're in my way.
I'm saying you're just
a big ol' nuisance!
A trap, huh?
I knew you could do it,
Tsumugu. I appreciate it.
This is a Special Adhesive Bullet.
To make a long story short, it's
like a powerful starching agent.
But if you use this,
there's no guarantee that the
person inside will survive.
Sorry about this, Ryuko.
She spotted me? At this range?
Impossible... Damn it!
You're not going anywhere!
A trap again?
Honestly, he's so irritating.
Oh, Lady Satsuki! I love your outfit.
Even Kiryuin has turned up?
What's your game, Nui Harime?
I want to see just how
powerful the Kamui
created by Dr. Isshin
Matoi is, don't you?
Or is this revenge against Isshin
Matoi for completely fooling you?
You're mistake was fixating
on the Rending Scissors,
so you failed to notice
the existence of the
Kamui that he had secretly developed.
And he also took your left eye.
That side of you is less than charming.
I'm fine with that.
When you consider something
charming, it never ends well.
On that score, Ryuko is
charming as all get-out!
She's coming after me relentlessly!
Snap out of it, Ryuko Matoi!
I can't get through...
Mmhmm! No point in trying!
Stand back!
If that's the case, it is
my job to put her down.
The job of putting down someone
who has been overwhelmed
by a Kamui's urge to destroy!
I guess this is fun in its own way!
Fall back, Tsumugu! It's not safe there!
Understood!
Oh, wow! Wow!
I could never intrude on this
world that's just for you two!
And it would be amusing if we
happen to kill each other.
That's what you're thinking, isn't it?
No, not at all!
But that will not happen!
A girl who is merely
being worn by her Kamui
is no match for Satsuki Kiryuin!
Let's end this, Matoi!
Don't!
Ryuko!
Ryuko, Ryuko, Ryuko,
Ryuko, Ryuko, Ryuko, Ryuko,
don't!
Don't do this, Ryuko!
This isn't like you, Ryuko!
What's the big idea,
interfering like that?
Oops.
Hold your tongue and watch.
Didn't you say, Ryuko?
You didn't want to avenge your father,
you wanted to know him better.
The way you're acting now, you're
just a rampaging monster!
You're howling and rampaging
and wrecking up the school!
This is just like how I was!
The Mako that soared to great
heights thanks to the Fight Club!
When I was drunk on power,
you were the one who
brought me to my senses!
So now it's my turn!
I'm gonna bring you back, Ryuko!
Mako...
Hey! Cut it out! Ow!
Darn it!
Hey, I'm okay!
Hey, dial it down! Ouch! Cut it out!
Ryuko!
Thanks.
Ryuko...
I'm sorry for dragging you
into my drama, Senketsu.
No, I'm just glad that
you are all right...
You were about to die of blood loss!
Dummy, dummy, dummy!
Huh? Ryuko? Ryuko?
Ryuko! Ryuko! Are you dead?
She's passed out, that's all.
Mankanshoku, she survived thanks to you.
L-Lady Satsuki? What're you doing here?
I mean, you know my name?
I mean, Ryuko, talk to me!
I've got a perfect, all-over tan!
Wow, it's like I got a tanning
salon session for free! Sweet!
That was a close one.
Sorry about that, Tsumugu.
We managed to get by without using this.
I couldn't lay a hand on them.
I couldn't so much as touch
any of those three women.
What else did you expect?
When they get like that,
they're monsters that have
become more than human.
Crap, now I have to go
back and train again.
Aw, the ending turned out
to be a real letdown.
Nui Harime.
You are hereby banned
from Honnouji Academy.
I will deal with both
Ryuko Matoi and the Kamui.
Meddle in my affairs again,
and Grand Couturier or not,
I will show you no mercy.
Aw, don't be mean!
Leave.
Fine, fine, you've made your point!
As if!
SEVERAL DAYS LATER
I see that you are back on your feet.
Where's Nui Harime?
Why do you want to know?
Because she killed your father?
Damn straight.
It was I who ordered her to steal the
Rending Scissors from Isshin Matoi.
If you must hate someone, hate me.
What?!
Why Isshin Matoi was killed and
what the Kamui and Life Fibers are.
I know the answers to
all those mysteries.
Then let's go at it right here.
Can you win in your current condition?
Your body still bears the damage from
your little rampage the other day.
Shut up!
I must thank you, Ryuko Matoi.
Thank me?
Yes, thank you.
As a result of you fighting the
Elite Four, I was able to make
the final adjustments
to my Goku Uniforms.
I can now deploy them in battle.
What?
Honnouji Academy's nationwide
academy conquest will
at last be complete.
That was what you were after
with the Naturals Election
and King of the Hill battle?
Indeed it was.
In one week's time, Honnouji Academy
will crush the western
academy administrations
that still oppose us in one fell swoop!
This is my Tri-City Schools Raid Trip!
TRI-CITY SCHOOLS RAID TRIP
You just sit on your thumbs
here and watch as they fall.
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
What is youth? Youth is "blue spring."
WHY
Why is spring blue?
Because it is immature.
IMMATURE
To be blue is immature.
To make a mad dash for the
new year is also immature!
IMMATURE
I, too, am—
—AHHH!
Next time on Kill la
Kill, "Crazy for You"!
EPISODE 13
CRAZY FOR YOU