Stepped on...
your shadow!
Now I'm "it"!
Come here, come here, crabbity crab!
Step on the crab.
Step, step...
How can we turn Manaka back to normal?
How do you get someone's
heart to love someone?
I do not know the answer.
If the time comes, it may return,
or it may never return.
But...
Hikari, you understand now, don't you?
There are indeed some things in the
world that you cannot do anything about.
Stepped on your shadow, Hii-kun!
Step!
Hikari.
There's something my dad
wants me to pick up...
It's at the Fishery Cooperative.
Will you come with me?
S-Sure.
Want me to come, too?
That's okay.
Could you watch Akira?
Okay!
'Kay! 'Kay, 'kay!
Episode Twenty-Three:
Who Do These
Feelings Belong To?
Don't try to act all mature.
Huh?
I'm sure you thought you'd try
to save me from the situation, but...
Thanks.
You've been a crybaby lately,
so I'll be the adult.
Shut up.
She told me...
As soon as we were done
with the Ofunehiki,
she wanted to tell me something.
Oh, I see.
I've been wondering what
she wanted to tell me,
but I think...
she was going to ask Tsumugu out.
Where did that come from?!
Huh?
It's more likely that
if she says she wants to talk,
and it goes that way,
the person Manaka-san would
want to ask out is...
You think it's me?
Uh...
That's not going to happen.
Huh?
That's definitely not going to happen.
"Definitely"...
Let's talk to everyone
about what Uroko-sama said.
Huh?
Everyone?
Including Manaka-san.
Manaka, too...
Yeah.
Because if it were about me...
If it were me, I'd want to know.
There's no way we can do that.
That's also "definitely"?
The heart to love someone...
There's nothing we can
do about the sacrifice...
But with Manaka,
we may be able to do something,
so I want to think about it.
Will thinking about it do anything?
We're talking about feelings.
It's different from trying
to find the sea village
or trying to wake up Mukaido.
But at this rate...
To be honest,
how much damage could the inability
to fall in love with someone have?
Manaka looks like she's having fun,
and she doesn't seem troubled
because she lost it.
That's not the issue here!
What do you think, Chisaki?
Huh?
I-I...
I might...
actually be a little relieved.
Chisaki!
Anyway, I think that
depends on the person.
I don't think it's something
we can all just solve like we usually do—
Stop being so selfish!
Sayu?
Saying it's better off not having
the ability to love someone... is selfish!
You guys haven't even
asked Manaka-san about it!
Sayu-chan.
What the hell?
She's fine not knowing?
Stop trying to act all mature!
You're still a kid, too!
How stupid!
Sayu.
You know,
there's something wrong with you guys.
What?
It's really disturbing.
Ugh, I'm so annoyed!
Sayu.
How stupid!
Loving someone is important.
It's better off to be
able to love someone...
Right, Miuna?
Wait!
Was it okay to leave everyone?
Yeah, that's enough for today.
Damn it, stupid Kaname.
Don't call Kaname stupid!
You said it yourself...
It's different when I say it
from when someone else says it!
What?
Anyway, I have homework
I still have to do.
Bye!
I'll never understand her...
Sayu...
There they are!
There!
Akira-kun wanted to come find you guys.
I-I see...
Danger: Do not enter
To be demolished soon
Ugh, Akira!
If Akira's with us, we're
never going to make it home.
Well, this isn't so bad now and then.
Manaka-san?
That shining thing...
I wonder what it is.
Hold on one sec.
Rock!
It's from a red-bellied sea slug.
Wow, how nostalgic.
Oh yeah!
I told the red-bellied sea
slug something before.
What did you tell it?
Hm...
Huh?
I wonder what it was.
I can't remember.
Hikari?
Oh, well...
This rock...
if you tell the sea slug
what you're thinking,
it'll tell you what will happen.
If it spits up a white rock,
your wish will come true.
"That feeling is true"... wasn't it?
If your feelings are wrong,
it'll spit up a black rock.
You hold onto this.
Huh?
Make sure you take
really good care of it!
O-Okay...
That's Manaka's rock.
How do you know?
Just a hunch.
Its color and shape:
it's flat and looks like
it has bad coordination.
Rocks have coordination?
Manaka said she told the sea slug
something but couldn't remember
what it was, right?
Yeah.
Meaning the thing that
Manaka told the sea slug
has something to do with
falling in love with someone.
I see.
I guess I'll just have to ask Tsumugu.
What?
If the feelings were strong enough
for her to talk to the sea slug,
I think she'll be able to remember them.
If she has the help from
the person she loves,
it'll happen for sure.
Hikari...
But you know...
If Manaka's ability to fall in love
with someone does come back...
Um...
What?
It's just...
I'm just saying that
I can sort of understand
what Kaname-san and
Chisaki-san were saying.
That's all!
Oh, that.
The "if I can't love anyone,
I won't be sad," thing?
You were saying that the other day...
or five years ago.
Huh?
Oh!
If I didn't love them,
I wouldn't be so sad!
It's true that I don't
know what will happen.
Just like Kaname and Chisaki said,
it might be easier if
she doesn't remember.
But...
Watching you guys made me think
that's definitely not the case.
Hey! Don't get in the way!
You're the ones that showed me.
Dummy!
What?
Hey, wait a minute!
Because you were able to love Akari,
Your butt's hanging out!
this happiness exists.
That's why I want her to remember
what it feels like to love someone.
Hikari...
Manaka-san, I went
ahead and took my bath.
Oh, sure.
I'll take one a little later.
Are you not feeling well?
No, that's not it.
I just keep hearing the sound
of waves in the back of my head.
The sound of waves?
I wonder why Hii-kun told me
to take care of this rock.
Huh?
Hii-kun is trying really
hard for me for some reason.
But I wonder why he's trying so hard...
Why don't you ask him?
Since he hasn't told me,
I'm sure he has something
he doesn't want to tell me.
This rock is pretty,
but when I look at it,
I don't know what's going on,
and I feel weird.
Manaka-san...
Manaka-san's heart to fall in love
with someone has been taken away...
So where her love was,
there is now a hole,
and it's screaming.
It's screaming that it's lonely.
Manaka-san, that rock...
Would it be okay if I borrowed it?
Huh? But...
I won't do anything bad to it.
I'll make it so you can take
even better care of it.
Even better care of it?
Yes.
I promise.
On my life!
You're funny, Miuna-chan.
Y-You think so?
Yeah, you're cute.
Now and when you were little, too.
Hikari is thinking of Manaka-san
more than his own feelings.
You're up early.
Oh, good morning.
It's right before exams and
I'll probably be home late,
so I thought I'd make
extra for dinner, too.
I see.
Even when you go back to the university,
make sure you eat your vegetables.
When you get so wrapped up in something,
you forget to eat.
I know.
Make sure you get sleep, too.
You're not allowed to just
nap on the sofa or the floor.
You won't be able to
relieve any lethargy.
I know.
You sure you didn't need
to tell everyone else?
There's no reason to make a big deal
about me just going
back to the university.
That's cold.
Can I ask you something, too?
What?
Why would you feel relieved if you
didn't have the heart to love anyone?
You're good with your hands, Miuna.
So last night,
I was thinking...
What?
I really wouldn't like losing
the ability to love someone.
Even if it's one-sided,
it's better to have that love.
Sayu...
These five years,
the reason I studied so hard,
the reason I'd cry now and then,
was Kaname.
I'm sure it'd be easier if you didn't
have the ability to love someone,
but I wouldn't be who I am right now.
So...
Sayu...
I'm going to ask Kaname out!
Ask?!
I don't care how it turns out.
I don't care if we can't go out!
As long as I can come to terms with it.
This is my own problem.
S-Sayu...
Oh yeah, I'm on duty today!
I have to write in the log
and take it to Sensei.
Her own problem, huh...
Miuna-chan!
Manaka-san...
Huh?
Where's Hikari and the others?
Apparently they already went home.
I see...
Oh, yeah.
Here.
Is this the sea slug's?
Wow, it's so nice.
It's just like Akari-san's pendant!
You know, the one with all the shells.
Yeah, all of you helped me with that.
Oh, right.
I'm starting to remember.
We all helped make it, didn't we?
I've still got a ways to go.
That's not good.
Hey, want to try it on?
Emergency Exit
There.
It's so cute!
Thank you, Miuna-chan.
I really can take better care of it now.
I won't lose it, and
it'll always be with me!
Won't lose...
M-Miuna-chan, what's wrong?
I'm sorry,
it's just you're so pretty...
Huh?!
You're so pretty, and nice, and fun.
You have everything, Manaka-san.
That's exactly why you
can't lose anything.
I-It's fine.
I'll take good care of it.
I won't lose it, okay?
Okay...
What are you doing?
Oh, letting it be in some water.
And I thought I'd take this home.
Take it home?
You...
There are limits to what
we can research here.
I'm going back to the university.
Wha... Wait!
What about Manaka?
What?
Wait until she gets her feelings back!
She's in love with you!
I want to do whatever I can to
get her ability to love back!
If you were able to
stimulate her feelings...
Stimulate her feelings?
How am I supposed to do that?
Huh?
I-I don't know...
Like take her on a date, and...
Kiss her and hold her?
What are you, a pervert?!
Sorry, but I don't feel
that way toward Mukaido.
You can just act like you do!
It's fine even if it's just a lie!
Are you sure
that it's me that Mukaido
is in love with?
Of course!
When she looks at you,
she gets all red in the face
and says your name all sweet.
And that's proof that she loves me?
You're going to doubt
Manaka's feelings?!
Don't.
My height and my arm strength
are five years beyond yours.
Damn it!
Please stop!
Please give up, Hikari.
I can't lie,
especially if Mukaido does love me.
But why?!
If you were to say that you love her,
Manaka might turn back to normal!
No matter what the reason,
the feelings of love for someone
should never be messed around with.
And I'm in love with Chisaki.
Yeah, but...
Huh?
I'm in love with Chisaki.
Chisaki!
Wait, Tsumugu!
I can't breathe...
But if I lose her now...
I can hear it...
It's like a nostalgic voice...
Mukaido's Ena...
No. That's not all.
So many feelings are
within these waters.
He doesn't even have Ena...
what the hell is he doing?
Tsumugu!
Hey, Tsumugu!
Hikari.
Y-You're able to talk?
I see...
So this is what it
feels like to have Ena.
I see...
Tsumugu.
Sea.
It's...
Sorry, but will you let
me go alone from here?
Huh? By yourself?
But you've never been to the village...
I want to face Chisaki properly.
Otherwise, I can't move forward.
B-But...
Please.
Tsumugu...
I'm scared.
I'm scared to be alone in Shishio.
Or is it...
T-Tsumugu?!
H-How...
Wh-Why are you in Shishio, Tsumugu?!
I came after you.
That's not what I meant!
You can breathe?
Are you okay?!
Ena?
My parents hated the sea.
They left behind Gramps,
who wanted to stay by the sea,
and went to the city.
But I wanted to stay with Gramps.
I wanted to stay by the sea.
Tsumugu.
Do you remember?
Five years ago,
when Hikari mistakenly thought that
Egawa and the others broke the Ojoshi-sama.
Yeah...
That time, you found out the truth,
and tried to defend Hikari.
Because if everyone else
finds out about this,
I couldn't believe how
foolish you were.
Hikari will end up the bad guy.
To think that people can become
so pathetic for others.
You're always so quiet and calm,
and yet sometimes you become so
fierce that I can't handle you.
At that time, I...
thought you were like the sea.
Who do you like, Hii-kun?
Why...
My feelings...
Was I mistaken?
Why just after five years...
Stop acting like the tragic heroine!
This is a talk between guys.
The sound of the sea...
Manaka has nothing to do with this.
This is messed up!
Something I can do...
Episode Twenty-Four:
Detritus