It's finally time to start school...
The first day is so exciting, isn't it?
Exciting, huh?
You seem more nervous
than excited, Hina-chan.
Yeah. I wonder if I'll make friends,
and if I'll be able to get along
with my classmates...
Thinking about it all makes me so nervous.
You're right. That is nerve-wracking.
You're going to be standing on the stage
with the theater troupe soon.
Think of this as another type of training.
You're right.
For starters, if I can get over freezing up
whenever I'm in front of people...
You'll be fine!
Just look! You're talking to us
right now, aren't you?
Yeah... I am!
I'm starting to feel like I can do this!
S-S-S-Sa... Saku...
S-Sakuragi... H-H-Hinako...
I-I'm from the... c-country...
You can do it, Hina-chan!
I'm Hinako!
Mistaken Friend
Fujimiya
Girls'
High
I couldn't do it.
N-No, that was a very unique
self-introduction.
Unique?
Hinako-chan.
I can call you that, right?
So you lived in the country?
U-Um... I... uh...
Th-The... c-country...
Um...
That's right!
I lived in the mountains
and worked as a scarecrow!
Ventriloquism?
That's a funny way to communicate!
They laughed.
So what did you do as a scarecrow?
Oh, yeah! I'm curious, too!
Well, you see...
Chiaki-chan!
Look at this.
Theater Society
Recruiting Members
What's this about?
Well, you see, all the fans of Chiaki-chan,
the theater club ace,
put this together over spring break!
You know, since the club went on hiatus,
we don't get to see you on stage, right?
Right...
That makes your fans really sad.
And you seemed really disappointed
when it went on hiatus, too.
So we thought, if we started
a theater society, you could act again!
Huh? Chiaki-chan?
That ventriloquism talk
went over better than I thought.
Yeah. I wasn't able to say a word, though.
Hina-chan! Kuu-chan!
Miss Landlady!
What's up?
Well, there's something I wanted to show you.
Here.
Theater society... recruiting members?
Miss Landlady, what's this about a society?
My friends put it together to replace
the theater club while it's on hiatus.
So that means we'll be able
to do theater here at this school?
That's right.
So about that...
What do you two want to do?
Of course, I'll join!
I'm with Hina-chan!
Okay, could you come to the
theater club room later?
It's just a society now,
but you'll still need to apply.
Got it!
This is great, Hina-chan!
Yeah!
Hey, you there!
Are you friends with Chiaki-senpai?
Huh?
You were talking to her like you are!
Why? What's going on between you?
Eh... ah... i-it...
Um, I'm sorry, but who might you be?
I just introduced myself earlier!
I'm your classmate, Nakajima Yua!
I want to be an actress, and I enrolled in
this school because of Chiaki-senpai's acting!
Oh, really?
Yes, really!
So...
How can a little shrimp like you
be friends with Chiaki-senpai?
S-Sorry! I might have gone too far!
I guess she's a nice person deep down...
But I still want to know what the deal is!
Argh!
I don't get her at all.
Um, Nakajima-san?
What?!
Hina-chan and I have
somewhere we need to go,
so we'll be going now.
Huh? Hey!
Theater Club
Oh, you're both here. Welcome.
M-Miss Landlady!
What happened?
We ran into someone pretty powerful.
I see. There, there.
I need to talk to you!
Well? Are you really
planning to join the club?
Eh... um... Y-Yes...
I'll never approve of you joining!
Wh-Why not?
Why not?!
A failure of a little shrimp like you...
Jeez, that's hard to say.
Yes! A failshrimp like you isn't fit to be
in this theater club with Chiaki-senpai!
U-Um...
In fact, you're not fit for Chiaki-senpai!
Do you even have the guts
to stand on a stage?
Um...
Are we interrupting something?
U-Uh...
Um, um... well... I mean...
No. Nothing.
I see. So, um, are you
hoping to join the club?
Y-Yes!
What's your name?
Nakajima Yua.
Yua-chan? That's a nice name.
Let's do our best together.
Th-Th...
Thank you for having me!
Well, I'll be going now!
Huh? Did I do something to her?
At any rate, you saved Hina-chan.
Huh?
You make such delicious coffee, Mayu-chan.
Thanks.
By the way, I heard you two
joined the theater club?
Yeah!
It's just a society now, though.
But it's the theater club
at its core, right?
Yeah. All the club members are joining, too.
In any case, Hina-chan's goal of being
in theater at Fujimiya High has come true.
Yeah!
Wait... But we've only just
formed our theater troupe.
Was it okay for us to join the theater club?
Why don't you just do both?
We can do both?
Sounds like you'll be busy.
That's true.
There's another hurdle Hina-chan
needs to get over first, after all.
Hurdle?
I mean getting used to
being in front of people!
I-In front of people...
Then how about working part-time
in the coffee shop?
That sounds good. It's a
service industry, after all.
Okay, it's settled!
Hina-chan, try working here
on your next day off from school.
Ah... u-um...
Don't worry! Leave everything to me!
U-Um...
Okay.
I let Mayu-chan talk me
into agreeing, but...
Let's see...
Theater troupe, theater club,
serving customers part-time...
How am I gonna do this?!
But as long as I don't get nervous,
things seem to work out okay...
I guess all I can do is try my best.
Fujimiya
Girls'
High
"I may be mistaken,
but that's what I think.
At any rate, the bear's gall of
Nametoko Mountain is well-known."
Okay, the next passage...
Sakuragi-san.
Y-Yes!
"I-It cures s-stomachaches
and m-makes wounds disappear.
A-At the N-N-Namari-no-Yu entrance..."
Sensei!
I'll read it for her.
Uh...
O-Okay, go ahead, then.
Sakuragi-san, you can sit down.
O-Okay...
"It cures stomachaches and
makes wounds disappear.
At the Namari-no-Yu entrance,
a sign has long stood that
reads, 'Bear's gall here.'"
Isn't she... that scary girl?
Oh, darn...
Uh... Sakuragi-san.
Y-Yes?
Can you help me carry
the handouts on the desk here?
U-U-U-Uh...
I'll carry them!
Hmph!
Okay... Sakuragi-san.
Y-Yes! Um...
I'll answer it!
Sakuragi-san.
Y-Yes!
Let me handle it!
Sakuragi-san.
Y-Ye—
I'll go!
Sakuragi-san.
I'll answer it!
I'll take it!
Sakuragi-san.
I'll do it for her!
Let me handle it!
Sakuragi-san.
I'll do that!
I'll carry it!
Sakuragi-san.
I'll do it for her!
I'll do that!
Hina-chan!
Y-Yes?
Let's head home.
Okay.
What should we eat on the way home today?
We're having dinner as soon as we get home.
Eating books to hold myself over is kinda...
The desserts there are the best!
Really?
Hmm... Oh!
Wait here a second, okay?
Excuse me! I'd like one of these
and one of these.
Um...
Excuse me, but which way is the station?
U-Um... I... uh...
I'll show you the way!
Please, come with me.
Thank you so much.
You need to get to the station, right?
Just turn left at that traffic signal there,
then go straight,
and you'll see it right away.
Oh, thank you.
You've been such a big help.
This'll show everyone that I can do
what that little failure can't!
How was that? Do you see
what a failshrimp you are now?
The one fit for Chiaki-senpai
is me, Nakajima Yu—
Did I take that too far?
No!
Don't think that way, Yua!
You must harden your heart!
Look nowhere but forward!
She's so nice...
She always covers for me when I fall short.
Maybe we can be friends...
Here you go.
Oh... uh...
Actually putting on that uniform
might be kind of embarrassing...
You need guts, too!
Guts?
Could I work at the used bookstore, maybe?
The bookstore is closed today.
Oh... So that's why she's been
nodding off all morning.
Strawberry parfait...
Don't worry! I'll support you
all the way! Okay?
O-Okay...
Th-Then... I'll be counting on you.
Trust me!
Good luck. With everything.
Hina-chan, you look so cute!
R-Really?
It looks great on you! It does!
Okay, next is this!
N-Next?
This looks great, too!
M-Mayu-chan, is this really a uniform?
It is, meow!
Meow?
You try it, too.
Meow, meow!
M-Meow, meow?
Squee! You're too cute!
Hina-chan, let's move
right on to the next one!
I can't eat any more...
Huh?!
Changing outfits on a doll...
Oops, I dozed off.
Oh, Kuu-chan! You're awake now?
I think I'm still dreaming.
I guess clean and pure really is best.
Well, ready to get started now?
I've never done any work
other than being a scarecrow...
Oh, Mayu-chan, do you have any tips
for serving customers?
Eh?
Hmm... well...
There's greeting them properly,
speaking loudly,
and everything else
can be solved with a smile.
She's so cute!
We hardly get any customers, anyway...
Huh?
I know Mayu-chan said that,
but what if we do get customers?
Just thinking about serving customers
makes me nervous...
You're right! I can't lose my confidence!
Thanks. Sorry I worried you. I'm okay now.
U-Um...
You can talk to birds?
Can that bird talk?
N-No... um...
She's got her hopes up...
Hi there! I'm Toritarou, tweet!
What brings you here by yourself?
Are you on a walk?
No. I got lost and can't find my way home.
What? That's awful!
Oh!
Th-That's awful! Um... um...
Do you know your home phone number?
Uh huh.
Then call your family with this.
I'm sure they'll come for you, tweet.
I feel a little guilty somehow...
Oh, hello? Mommy? I'm at... um...
Coffee Shop Hitotose.
I'm at a place called
"Coffee Shop Hitotose."
Uh huh. I'm with a girl
in a really fancy costume!
Oh, welco—
Huh?
Um, she seems to be lost.
Oh, dear!
Oh, but we've already called her mom,
and she's coming for her.
Really? That's good, then.
Make yourself at home, okay?
Okay!
Hina-chan, you did great!
You were able to talk to her, right?
Oh, I didn't do anything.
It was all Toritarou.
Toritarou? Who is that?
Thanks, Toritarou and the lady!
See you later!
Really, thank you so much.
Y-Y-Y-Y...
You're wellfrm!
We'll be going, then.
Bye!
There, there.
What a tiring day.
I wasn't able to talk to a single
customer the whole time.
I'll completely fail both the theater troupe
and the theater club at this rate.
I really am a failshrimp.
I know! I'll try my hardest
to talk to that girl!
I can't move forward
if I keep talking about failing.
I have to do my best at what I can do!
Okay! Time to take a step forward!
Fujimiya
Girls'
High
Good morning!
Okay, you go on ahead.
Okay.
Oh, Nakajima-san?
Wh-Where'd you come from?!
U-Um... uh...
So you're actually here!
I thought you'd be bawling after learning
that I'm the one fit for Chiaki-senpai,
and maybe you wouldn't
come to school anymore.
Actually, I was wondering
what I'd do if you didn't come.
You've got some guts!
Huh? The landlady? Um, what do you mean?
What do I mean?! You realize
that you're a failshrimp, right?
After all those times I covered for you!
Oh, yeah!
Thanks for helping me out so much.
It made me really happy.
Huh?
So, there's actually something
I've been wanting to say to you...
Wh-What?
I'd like to be...
...f-f-f-friends with you, if you don't mind!
F-Friends?
A-Are you sure you're not mistaken?
Huh?
I wasn't trying to help you or...
Oh, Sakuragi-san, could you...
I'll take them!
Uh...
You helped me again!
I-I did not! That was a
conditioned reflex, or something...
Thanks!
I think we'll be really good friends!
Hmph. Let's just get going.
Hey, Nakajima-san...
Can I call you Yua-chan from now on?
Do what you want.
Thanks, Yua-chan!
Hmph!
The Scarecrow Heroine
I'm so glad Hina-chan
seems to have made a friend!
And the theater society's
activities have begun, too.
It sounds like Hina-chan is practicing
lots of things every day.
Next time: "The Scarecrow Heroine."