Bye, Arata.
Let me know when you're done
watching your friends play.
Thanks, Uncle Motoki!
I'm a little late.
Is their first match over?
Are you going to come tomorrow, Arata?
What?  Just the individual
tournament in two days?!
I was lying.
After I pay my respects,
I'll go watch Chihaya and Taichi.
Wh-Who are you?
Oh, that mole!
Are you Shinobu-chan?
I didn't recognize you because you
looked completely different on TV.
What are you doing to put on
and lose weight so quickly?
Huh?  What's wrong?
You don't need to cry, Shinobu-chan.
Aren't you the invincible Queen?
It's been four years since I last lost,
but I still have much
room for improvement,
so I might end up losing to you,
despite your long absence.
This is the pride of a Queen
and the temper of a Kyoto woman.
Since you quit karuta, you're
never beating me again, fool.
What are you doing here, Shinobu-chan?
Isn't the individual
tournament tomorrow?
Kyoto's not that far away.
Are you daft?
Every year on this day, I visit the shrine
before watching the Lake Biwa Birdman Rally.
You came all the way
out here and you're not
going to watch the team tournament?
Team tournament?
That's for players who
don't love karuta.
That's why you aren't
playing in it, right?
It's strange.
Why do I keep getting matched
against her in the first round?
In fourth and fifth grade, too.
Arata, Shinobu-chan will
surely be a future Queen.
Go beat her again.
You should have started a karuta club.
Team tournament?
That's for players who
don't love karuta.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 9
My
Only
Thought
We won our first match.
How did it go
on your side?
How does Fujisaki look this year?
What's wrong?
Mashima...
Five of their eight registered
members are Class A?
And they sent out all five
of them in the first round.
Five Class A members...
I'll be watching their
second match, as well.
Hey, what should we do for lunch?
How about the soba place
inside the temple?
Sorry.
What's wrong, Komano?
Who's that?  A scout?
He was taking a bunch of
notes during the match.
Hey, if you're spying on us,
then write this down.
In Fujisaki, the girls are
scarier than the guys.
Wait...
Aren't you a guy?
Flat
But the truly scariest of all
are the beautiful, right?
There it is!
Makoto-senpai's trick of holding
matches on his eyelashes!
Wow!  He's got three of them today!
That's a good sign, senpai!
Wonderful!
I-I've known this for a while,
Go, go, Fujisaki!
but the best karuta players
are all weirdos!
Stop that, Chihaya-chan.
Huh?
A girl shouldn't gulp water
standing up like that.
I'm trying to fire myself up.
Is something wrong, Prez?
No, it's nothing.
You people like to talk a lot.
Hokuo will be breezing
through the group stages.
How's it looking for Mizusawa,
number two in Tokyo?
Try not to drop out too early.
We won't!
We'll be waiting for you in the final!
That's fine!
We'll get you back for Tokyo!
We'll take you down!
Arata.
Oh, Murao-san.
What is it, Chihaya?
Did you hear Arata's voice?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
He said that he was only playing
in the individual tournament.
Yeah, but he might be here.
I just heard him...
Chihaya!
Whether he's here or not,
our second match is coming up.
Focus on the tournament.
S-Sorry.
Yamaguchi Mioka, our second opponent,
Fujisaki has five Class A players.
is fielding a bunch of boys
without much experience.
How do we deal with that?
Then there's Hokuo and
First Akashi Girls'...
There are many strong
schools at Nationals.
We don't have time to
think about Arata.
But what if...
...he really is here?
What if Arata comes to watch us?
Wh-What's this about, Arata?
Why are we hiding?
S-Sorry.  Come this way.
Murao-san, you're on the
tournament committee this year?
Yeah, and there are other Nagumo
society members helping out.
I had to wake up at five.
Sounds like hard work.
I don't mind.
There were other people doing
this work when I was a student.
This is my way of paying them back.
We should keep the tradition going.
What about you, Arata?
You're only registered for the
individual tournament, right?
Oh, I wanted to watch my friends play.
Oh, you mean Fujioka West from Fukui?
You have friends there?
Oh, no...
Fujioka West is having a hard time.
They've fought hard in the group stages
with their three registered members,
but how long will they last?
Murao-san!
Oh, sorry.
The team tournament means
more in high school karuta,
but the individual tournament is
where you'll witness true skill.
You should go home and
rest up for tomorrow.
Fukui
Fujioka
Oh, he finally picked up!
Coach, where are you?!
Isn't Tajiri with you?!
We were placed in a
group with three teams,
so we didn't play the first round,
but we'll be up soon!
An accident caused a traffic jam and they're
only at the edge of Kyoto Prefecture.
It'll be at least an hour
before they get here...
I'm sorry, Masaki!
You're the one who went through
LASIK surgery for this tournament!
Shoji?
Are you Shoji?
I'm Arata.
We went to the same middle school.
Wataya!
You were lucky to have a
Master for a grandfather,
but now it's the opposite!
He's the reason you don't
have time to practice!
Wa-Wataya Arata?
Yeah.
Arata?
You ended up going to Fujioka West?
The super karuta player Wataya
Arata who went to Fujioka East?!
Huh?
Hey, does Fujioka West
only have three players?
I thought that Fukui was big on karuta.
Only three schools showed
up for their preliminary.
I've heard that the players all spend
their time at karuta societies instead.
Oh, like the Fukui Nagumo society.
It's famous for being really good.
Wait, doesn't that mean that their
three players could be really strong?
What is this?
What am I doing?
Why am I here?
Okay, we will now begin the second
round for groups H and I.
Please place your cards.
Shoji!  This won't work!
It's going to fail!
What's wrong, Tajiri-kun?
They're gonna find out!
Director Kuriyama from our
karuta society is up there!
Don't worry.
An Arata without glasses is no Arata.
You're Tajiri-kun.
We will now begin fifteen
minutes of memorization time.
You have until that minute hand hits 6.
Why is this happening?
That won't work.
I go to a different high school.
Our schools are right next to each other!
That's not the point!
Arata.
I'm not expecting you to win or anything.
You just have to sit down with us!
It took effort to convince Masaki
and Tajiri to start a karuta club!
We worked hard the past 18 months
to make it to Nationals!
I don't want to go home without
playing a single match!
But if I take off my glasses,
I won't be able to do
anything besides sit around.
I somehow managed to place my cards.
We're up against Jinnan
Academy from Kochi.
The two players who win by default
are staying seated to support their team.
They're serious about this.
My opponent is too.
Time is up.  Let's begin.
Thank you for the game.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
I just came here to watch
Chihaya and Taichi play...
Please, at least, don't let me
get caught and disqualified!
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
I told Chihaya to focus,
but I'm the one who can't
stop thinking about him.
Taichi.
Huh?  What?
Stay focused.
Coming from you?
If Arata comes to watch us,
I want to show off my team,
and how strong we are.
I don't understand,
but I like the idea of
Ayase-senpai showing me off.
This is the second round
of the group stage...
Watch us, Arata.
Not possible
I can't win...
I can't influence the
other two players...
As my love first came to realization,
But that's...
For the cold nights when crickets are chirping,
More tiring than playing normally.
What's wrong with this guy?
Is he even trying?
I'm playing my heart out here.
I'm sorry.
I can feel his frustration...
After making it to Nationals,
you want to play as many
games as you can...
You want to play strong opponents
who will make you better.
Look for the sound of the cuckoo
He's fast.
Crap!
I need to be careful...
My body moves when a one-syllable
card on my side is read.
Even when I can't see the cards...
Didn't this happen before?
When I took cards without my glasses?
My fear is that you will forget
your promise to never forget me,
Where is it?
Found it!
Don't tell Chihaya...
I wanted to play as a team.
Impassionate gods...
Why are you crying?
Masaki!
You're doing good!  Keep on the attack!
You can give us our first win!
I made it to Class A before you did,
but I couldn't win a single match
in any of the tournaments.
Still, when I looked around,
there were other people like me.
Strangely enough, once the three of
us were together, we started to win.
Yep, yep.
We aren't aspiring to become the Master,
and we don't even have five players,
but we can still have fun playing karuta.
Team tournament?
That's for players who
don't love karuta.
But the individual tournament is
where you'll witness true skill.
but from the crystal
white snow of Yoshino
Note that...
The Fukui team needs all
three members to win,
but Kochi is leading all three games.
Here.
Man, they're too weak.
It hurts...
I'm no use here.
I can't help them out
that you pine for me as the Inaba
mountain pines, I shall return to you
because this isn't my team.
Like a boatsman...
Yes!  That's one win for Jinnan!
We're in the playoffs!
Quiet.  The match isn't over yet.
Thank you very much.
I'm not interested in team tournaments.
I'm focused on winning the
individual tournament.
Team tournament?
That's for players who don't love karuta.
But the individual tournament is
where you'll witness true skill.
I wanted to play more karuta together!
Murao-san...
What does it mean
to be good at karuta?
I do not know where
this love will take me
A mountain village...
He got it!
That player has a beautiful swing.
Maybe as beautiful as Arata-kun.
when people and grass grow scarce
Said world grants no change, I pray,
His cover was clean, too.
Reminds me of Arata-kun.
But it'll be hard to make
up a 15 card lead...
He chose the perfect time to be
aggressive when sending cards.
Just like Arata-kun!
It's him!
So fast...
Who is he?
He's going to come back
from a 15 card deficit?
Fujioka West's defeat is sealed.
But...
I want to show respect for my opponent.
I want to tell my teammate
that it's not over!
I want to do something!
I want to let them know!
With all my strength!
Masaki's also coming back!
Amazing!
His power is completely different...
This is...
This is a karuta player who
wants to become the Master!
Thank you very much.
Jinnan Academy defeats
Fujioka West 3-2.
Thank you very much.
Arata...
Thank you...
Thank you, Arata...
Mr. Kuriyama...
What are you doing, Arata-kun?!
Come with me!
You're not a student at Fujioka West!
You aren't a registered
member of their team!
I'm sorry...
What is the meaning of this?!
Well...
It's not Arata's fault!
We begged him to play!
It's against the rules to
use substitute players!
S-Since I caught you in the
act, I can't let this slide.
Fujioka West will receive
a severe reprimand,
and Arata-kun,
you may be barred from playing
in the tournament tomorrow.
Due to worsening weather conditions,
today's birdman rally racing and gliding
events will be postponed to tomorrow.
I repeat.
Due to worsening...
You may be barred from playing
in the tournament tomorrow.