This is... Earth?!
It's hovering!
The situation's level of
danger has climbed by 255%.
I propose a preemptive attack.
Wait, Chamber.
Tell them in words they can understand
that we mean them no harm.
Do not attack.
I-It talked!
We deny hostility.
Is there another one of 'em inside?
We wish you to lower your weapons.
I am Ridget, the Fleet Commander's Aide.
Who are you?
She's asking for your name and affiliation.
Understood.
I am Ensign Ledo, pilot of the anti-Hideauze
annihilation weapon, Chamber.
Ledo...
Annihilation weapon?
What the hell is Hideauze?!
Enemy. Coexistence is impossible.
You are all fellow humans.
Join Alliance.
We request dialog.
Who is your commander?
Chamber! What did you say?!
In their language, I requested a dialog
and told them the Alliance's purpose.
Good. But why are they
acting hostile toward us?
Throw down your weapon! And
whoever's inside there, get out!
What's she saying?
Cannot comprehend.
This machine is unmanned.
What does that mean?
The Planet of Origin
Amy, you're late.
The delivery was late,
so I had to make up time.
So, what's up?
I want to know your impression of that boy.
You talked to him too, Ridget. Right?
You're the one who's come
in closest contact with him.
So what's he like?
Um, let's see...
Normal?
Well, it was like his first time here, so he
was surprised and all, "What should I do?!"
And it didn't seem like
he intended to hurt me.
Although he did kind of touch my butt...
Your butt?!
But I did sort of understand what the person
inside the Yunboro was trying to say...
Why don't you try asking him directly?
You gotta be kidding!
What do we do if he goes wild?
That's the guy who wrecked
the hangar with one stroke!
Pinion.
You examined that Yunboroid, right?
I got no idea what it's made
of or how it's put together.
Couldn't even fit a knife into a seam.
The thing's one tough son of a gun.
How about you, Bellows?
Was there anything unusual
when you brought it up?
I dunno... I just did what
this guy asked me to do,
pull something up
that looked valuable.
Oh, that's right.
The crane's trashed!
I didn't think that Yunboro
was gonna be so heavy.
I'll send you my bill later.
Your skills just weren't up to snuff!
Excuse me?!
Fleet Commander Fairlock...
I'm listening.
It seems that Yunboroid is the
product of high level technology.
I'd like to take it apart
and study it, if possible.
That's right!
That mech's different from any
treasure we've ever dredged up!
Let's bust the thing open already!
Drag out the kid and the guy
inside and deep six 'em both!
We're not going to do that.
What if they have comrades? Think about it.
It could lead to the whole
fleet being endangered.
I understand your line of thought, but...
Man, what a drag!
The Fleet Commander is correct.
We'd be sitting ducks if
more came to settle a score.
I fail to see the logic in your actions.
Please explain the reasoning
behind prolonging this stalemate.
This machine has more than enough armaments
to deal with the current situation.
For the moment, this is the best option.
Reasonable Course of Action:
1. Overpower the armed ones
and bring them under control.
2. Neutralize the nerve center
and suppress any retaliation.
Chamber. Our immediate priorities
in these circumstances
are establishing contact with our
troops and determining our location.
If you can't figure it out, then maybe we
can rely on any archives these people have.
Agreed, with reservations.
What's important is that Earth,
as a planet, supports life.
We're told that abnormal solar activity
made Earth a frozen, dead planet.
But this is the reality.
Agreed.
Securing a habitable planet is
the Alliance's most fervent wish.
With this world's abundant water and air,
it could replace Avalon as our new hub.
Suggestion: I believe that judgment goes
beyond the limitations of your post.
You're probably right.
How about communicating with the Alliance?
I continue to send out a distress
signal, but have received no reply.
If you continue to operate on your own
like this, you won't be able to obtain
necessary military supplies, which will
then bring on trouble with your metabolism.
Reasonable Course of Action 3:
I think you should consider
escaping these surroundings
and going back into suspended animation.
Hey!
Hey! Pinion!
Who's gonna fix my boat?!
Don't ask me, dumbass!
See you!
Yeah! Thanks!
Amy!
What's the merman like?!
Merman?
A boy took you hostage, right?
How old is he? Is he handsome?
People keep bugging me to ask you about it!
Gimme a break! I'm trying to work here!
Hey! Amy!
Don't jump until the wings are spread!
You need to be more careful!
I'm supposed to keep my mouth shut after
Ridget and them snatched my treasure?!
I'll thoroughly search the exact same spot!
Bebel, I'm back!
Hi, Sis.
Sorry I took so long.
Sis, are you okay?
I heard you were taken hostage?
Yeah. But I'm fine.
I'm lucky he wasn't a dangerous person.
Apparently, his name is Ledo.
Ledo... What's he like?
I'd guess he's about my age.
With his slim arms, he doesn't
seem really masculine.
Huh...
And there's one more, still inside a Yunboro.
That one can speak a little bit of our
language, enough to understand him anyway.
Then they should talk things over
with them and become friends, right?
Exactly! That's what I think too, but...
Here. I brought you a present.
Thank you!
Do you think you can use it?
Yeah!
A perfect fit!
Thank you, Sis!
I'm glad.
I wish I could talk to Ledo, too...
After all, he may have
come from the heavens...
From the heavens? Ledo?
Yeah! You know the legend.
About the people who escaped to the
stars when the Earth froze that time...
But that's just a fairy tale!
Besides, that Yunboro was
brought up from the sea.
Uh-uh. I bet they came from space.
The people that escaped into space
long, long ago have come home!
Space, huh? I don't know if they'd
bother coming all this way...
Dr. Oldham said that if a ship
kept going all the way up,
it would take just half a
day for it to reach space!
Someone is approaching.
I don't know about this...
The Fleet Commander said we mustn't
provoke him, which is understandable...
...but we can't just do nothing, either.
And so you chose her?
If we had any other volunteers...
Do you want to take her place?
Yeah, right.
Conjecture: The threat level is minimal.
It's possible that she's been
sent as an envoy to negotiate.
Envoy? She's a kid!
Shall I intercept her?
No, that's not necessary.
Roger.
It's the corpse of an aquatic animal.
Corpse?!
What does she want me to do?!
Conjecture: It is harmless food.
Don't tell me she wants me to eat it?!
Conjecture: It is a friendship ritual.
It's a corpse!
I leave the choice to you.
Chamber, ask her what her objective is.
She seeks conversation.
Alright.
He ate it!
She says her name is Amy.
She asks where you came from.
The heavens?
So you two are soldiers fighting
against those Hideauze?
That is correct.
Then are you stronger than them?
Super... strong.
From space, seriously?
Then Bebel was right...
Earth is different than
it appears in our records.
I seek explanation.
You're getting better and better
at speaking our language.
Interpreting must be tough. Won't
you at least show me your face?
What do you mean, show my face?
I mean, you're inside of there, right?
There is no one inside.
It really is empty...
I am a Pilot Support Enlightenment
Interface System.
System? Then that machine is talking?
Chamber is an artificial intelligence that
aids in battle and maintaining life support.
Wow...
Wow!
Wow! Wow! Wow!
There really is no one in
here! You're a machine!
I repeat the question. About the Earth...
Wow! Wow! Wow!
We're told that it was a giant lump of ice.
But it melted and became a water planet.
Long ago, there were supposedly these places
called "land", but I don't know about that.
Anyway, everyone lives on ships that
are grouped together like this.
Ancient ships and materials are all sunk at
the bottom, so we hoist them out of the sea.
Gargantia, too... That's
the name of this fleet...
It was one of them.
Gargantia?
Uh-huh. Gargantia.
More exist?
Oh, there are other fleets.
Small ones, big ones...
When ships join up, it doesn't
take long to form a fleet.
And there are pains in the
neck, too, like pirates...
Pirates are enemies?
Yeah, I guess you could say that.
No worries.
A Milky Way. Sometimes
it's called a Sea Galaxy.
You have to see it. It's so beautiful.
Thank goodness.
Now we can travel on a new Milky Way.
What is a Milky Way?
It's a glowing path that
runs through the sea.
We wouldn't be able to live without it.
So the ships forge ahead,
staying on the path.
But there's no guarantee that
the path will go on forever.
So when that happens,
we search for a new Sea Galaxy
and switch over to that path.
Lightbugs are what make Sea Galaxies glow.
They're a swarm of itty-bitty
bugs that accumulate electricity.
We get our electricity
from this band of light.
Beautiful...
What?
Well? What's your analysis
of our coordinates?
Due to the existence of an
atmosphere, lack of information,
and the limitations of optical analysis,
further observation is required
to derive our current position.
It's true, I tell you! I think...
You think they'd come up with
a better lie than that...
If that really is a talking machine...
It is!
Even if that's true, come on,
a war with an alien race?
Impossible!
But that aside, let's find out for sure
if it can talk or not by taking it apart!
Then we throw the kid overboard!
Are you serious?!
He's in trouble and has nowhere else to go!
Everyone, listen to what Ledo has to say!
Having undue contact with an outsider
wouldn't benefit either side...
Not the sea... and not space...
Confirming the terrain...
There's no mistake. This is
where the Yunboro was sunken.
Alright! Let's get psyched up and do this!
They've got an abundance of commodities here
and the threat level of these natives is low.
Agreed, with reservations.
If we can't return to the
front under our own power,
all we can do is wait for the troops
to notice our distress signal.
I think the best course of action is
to look for a cooperative relationship.
Agreed.
The front. Troops. The people who live on
this planet don't know what those words mean.
The desperate struggle against the
Hideauze... has no connection to this place.
What is it? What's wrong?
Say, what's going on?!
The salvage ship is under
attack from pirates!
Bellows's ship!
Bellows and the others are...
Oh, hell.
They're surrounding us!
Escort Fleet Commander!
No good! There are too many of 'em!
Salvage team, stand by underwater!
There are several new points of engine noise.
Check it out!
Ledo!
Amy?
Kites?!
The enemy has nine ships
and several small crafts!
They're starting a kite attack!
What about the reinforcements?
I don't know if they'll make it in time...
Enemy attack?
You two are strong, aren't you?!
That's a totally strong Yunboro, right?!
Do something! Help us out!
She seeks assistance.
I'll do it. This'll be
a good bargaining chip.
Activate floater!
Wha...?!
That Yunboro's starting to move!
What?!
What do they intend to do?!
Liftoff.
Are you Bellows from Gargantia?
You got what you came for!
Now get the hell out of here!
Dump that rinky-dink fleet
you're with and join us!
Empress Lukkage recognizes your skills, too.
Don't make me laugh, pirate scum!
What do you think you're doing?!
For your own good, I'd think
twice about refusing...
Bastard!
Identification of main
enemy targets complete.
Request to identify smaller targets.
Do it.
Identification complete.
Deflector beam stand by.
Annihilate them.
What the...?!
What's happening?!
What the hell is that?!
G-Good lord...
What in the world...?