"Live till after noon!"
Live TV till after noon!
Today's topic is: "Is sexiness
necessary for hero work?"
And so, we have these two
in the studio today--
"Pro Hero - Mt. Lady -
Quirk: Gigantification"
A rookie hero who debuted
just this year, Mt. Lady, and--
Midnight, who is currently
teaching at U.A. High School!
"Pro Hero - Midnight"
Thank you both for coming today.
Please, have a seat.
Now, Midnight,
"At debut"
when you first debuted, your costume
was so extreme that it created a stir,
eventually leading to the "Regulations
for Exposed Skin in Costumes" bill
being submitted to the National Diet.
You're known as a veteran
hero who changed the country.
It's still pretty bad right now, though.
Now I'm going for the "ultra-thin" style.
Many say that because of the nature of
their Quirks, clothes obstruct their abilities.
It's not a matter of whether
or not sexiness is necessary,
but rather that the result of
necessity became seen as sexy.
It's just what you like, right?
What's with you?
Trying to pick a fight?
Of course not! It's just, how do
I put it--I think you're amazing!
For your age.
Are you trying to show that your
only redeeming feature is your youth?
Even though you're not that young?
I'm saying that if the
older generation tries too hard,
then it's hopeless for us younger folks!
--You little...!
--Hey, watch your hands!
You, too! Oh, jeez!
"Minoru Mineta - Quirk: Pop Off"
--Stop pulling! It'll rip!
--It's ripped!
What an incredible episode!
"Gear up for Final Exams"
Okay, that's it for class.
"Pro Hero - Eraser Head - Quirk: Erasure"
There's only one week
left until the final exams.
You all are studying properly, right?
I'm sure you already know,
"Izuku Midoriya - Quirk: One For All"
"Katsuki Bakugo - Quirk: Explosion"
but it won't just be a written exam.
There's also a practical component.
"Tenya Iida - Quirk: Engine"
"Ochaco Uraraka - Quirk: Zero Gravity"
Make sure you train your minds
and bodies at the same time.
That's all.
"Midterm: 19th/20"
"Midterm: 20th/20"
I haven't studied at all!
"Mina Ashido - Quirk: Acid"
"Denki Kaminari - Quirk: Electrification"
With the sports festival and
internship, I didn't study at all!
"Fumikage Tokoyami - Quirk: Dark Shadow"
It's true that we had
one event after another, but...
"Midterm: 14th/20"
"Rikido Sato"                "Koji Koda"
"Midterm: 12th/20"
"Midterm: 11th/20"
For the midterms, we'd just started
school, so they didn't cover much,
so I didn't really have
a hard time with them,
but with the back-to-back events
and stuff, the finals will be different...
It'll be tough since
there's a practical exam, too.
"Midterm: 9th/20"
N-Ninth on the midterms?!
And here I thought you were one of us!
Guys like you are only
likable if they're dumb...!
Where's the demand for this?!
The world, I guess.
Ashido, Kaminari!
L-Let's do our best!
"Midterm: 4th/20"
We all want to go to the
training camp together, right?
Yes! As class rep, I also have high
hopes that you'll all be moved to action!
"Midterm: 2nd/20"
"Shoto Todoroki - Quirk: Half-Cold, Half-Hot"
"Midterm: 5th/20"
It's pretty hard to fail if
you just pay attention in class.
Be careful with your words!
"Momo Yaoyorozu - Quirk: Creation"
"Midterm: 1st/20"
You two, I may be able to be of
assistance with the class lectures.
Yao-momo!
I can't help at all with
the practical, though...
"Kyoka Jiro - Quirk: Earphone Jack"
I'm not one of those two,
but can I join, too?
"Midterm: 7th/20"
I'm having some trouble
with quadratic functions...
Huh?
"Hanta Sero - Quirk: Tape"
Sorry, me too! How are you
with classical Japanese?
"Midterm: 17th/20"
Huh?
"Mashirao Ojiro - Quirk: Tail"
I'd like to join, too.
"Midterm: 8th/20"
There's a bunch of stuff I don't get...
Please!
Everyone!
Yes, of course!
All right!
Then, let us hold a study session
at my residence this weekend!
Seriously? I can't wait to see your house!
"bounce bounce bounce"
Oh, in that case, I must tell
Mother and have her open up the hall!
Hall?!
What kind of tea are you all partial to?
Tea?!
In my family, we always
drink Harrod's or Wedgwood,
so if you have any preference, let me know!
Of course, you can
trust me to help you study, too!
I will definitely show you how I can help!
It's like she casually slapped me with
the huge difference in how we were born...
Warm fuzzies... Warm fuzzies...
...but her bounciness is
so cute that I don't care.
Warm fuzzies... Warm fuzzies...
What was that again? Harry's? That's fine.
Harrod's, right?
"Eijiro Kirishima - Quirk: Hardening"
"Midterm: 15th/20"
Look at the difference in virtue.
"Midterm: 3rd/20"
I can do it, too! Want
me to beat it into you?
Yeah, I'm counting on you!
"Yuga Aoyama - Quirk: Naval Laser"
"Mezo Shoji - Quirk: Dupli-Arms"
"Midterm: 10th/20"
Everyone's panicking now,
even though it won't do any good
to cram this late in the game.
"Midterm: 18th/20"
Shouldn't you try cramming a little?
What are you talking about?
What is it?
"Lunch Rush's Eatery"
The practical exam, huh?
It's kind of scary since
I can't tell what'll be on it.
I don't think it'll be anything crazy.
The written exam questions
will come from what we study in class,
so I should be able to manage somehow, but...
"Tsuyu Asui - Quirk: Frog"
"Midterm: 13th/20"
You can manage, huh...?
Seriously, what'll we have
to do for the practical exam?
"Toru Hagakure - Quirk: Invisibility"
"Midterm: 16th/20"
"It'll be a comprehensive test
of everything from first semester."
"Midterm: 6th/20"
That's all Mr. Aizawa would tell us...
Everything we did so far...
So, combat training and rescue training,
and then basic training...
In addition to studying, we'll have
to keep in good physical conditio--
Oh, sorry. Your head was
so big that I accidentally hit it.
"Neito Monoma - Quirk: Copy"
You're from Class B...
Um... Monoma!
How dare you--
I heard you guys met the hero killer.
Just like at the sports festival,
you guys in Class A just have
to have all the attention, huh?
But that attention isn't because
people have high hopes for you.
It's because you keep
attracting trouble, right?
Oh, that's scary.
Someday, the rest of us might also
be caught up in the trouble you bring
and become victims as well...
Like getting cursed by the god of pestilence!
Oh, that's sca--
Monoma, that's not funny.
Don't you know what happened to Iida?
"Itsuka Kendo - Quirk: Big Fist"
Kendo!
Sorry, Class A. This guy's
heart's just kinda, you know.
His heart...?!
You guys were talking earlier
about how you don't know what's gonna
be on the practical exam for the finals, right?
Looks like it'll be combat against
robots like in the entrance exam.
What? Really?!
How do you know?
An upperclassman friend of mine told me.
It's kind of cheating, though.
No, it's not cheating.
That's right, I'm sure gathering information
ahead of time is also part of the test.
"mutter mutter mutter"
I see, I should've asked
some upperclassmen...
Why didn't I realize?
Are you an idiot, Kendou?
We had an information advantage!
This was our chance to get
ahead of the detestable Class A!
They're not detestable!
She's like the big sister of Class B, huh?
All right!
Oh, it'll be easy if it's robots!
Yeah, yeah!
You guys look like you'd have a hard time
controlling your Quirks against people.
Yeah! But I can just let loose
with robots, so it'll be a cinch!
And it'll be a cinch for me to melt them!
Now you just need Yaoyorozu to help
you study, and you'll be set for the finals!
We'll definitely be able
to go to training camp now!
You may one day have
to fight against this great evil...
In order to prepare to face those words,
I have to make everything count from now on.
It doesn't matter if they're people or robots.
They're the same if you beat 'em up, right?
What're you idiots talking
about it being a cinch for?
--Who're you calling an idiot?!
--Shut up!
If you need to control your Quirk,
then control it! Idiot!
Hey, Deku!
I don't know if you've figured out
how to use your Quirk a little or what,
but you seriously keep
rubbing me the wrong way.
Oh, he must be talking about how Deku
was moving like Bakugo the other day.
Oh, yeah!
I don't need another half-assed
result like at the sports festival.
At the upcoming finals,
we'll get individual scores,
so we'll see who's better
whether you like it or not.
I'll beat you with an
indisputable difference!
I'll kill you!
Todoroki!
You, too!
It's been a while since
I've seen Bakugo that intense.
Impatience...?
Or hatred?
Bakugo has gotten worse than I thought.
"Yaoyorozu"
Wow...
I knew she was rich,
but I didn't think she was this rich...
Everyone, I have been waiting for you!
Please, come in.
I feel so out of place,
it's making me nervous...
Me, too...
"bounce bounce bounce"
What is it?
Oh, nothing...
"Written Exam - Day 1"
"Written Exam - Day 3"
Pencils down, everybody.
The last person in each row, collect
the answer sheets and bring them here.
Thanks, Yao-momo!
I didn't leave anything blank, at least!
And so, our three days
of written exams were over.
And then, it was the day
of the practical exam.
"Practical Exam Area - Center Plaza"
Now, we will begin the practical exam.
Of course, it is possible to fail this exam.
If you want to go to the training camp,
then don't make any stupid mistakes.
There are a lot of teachers...
I expect that you all have
gathered information ahead of time
and have some idea of what you will be doing.
We're fighting robot warriors
like at the entrance exam, right?
Fireworks! Curry! Test of Courage!
Too bad!
For various reasons, the exam
will be different starting this time!
"Pop"
Principal Nezu!
Different?
From now on, we want to focus on
person-to-person combat and hero work,
and stress teaching that
is closer to actual fighting.
So...
We'll have you form teams of
two to fight against one teacher!
Against... the teachers?
"Pro Hero - Nezu"
In addition, the pairs and who each pair
will be up against have already been decided.
"Pro Hero - Present Mic"
"Pro Hero - Thirteen"
These were determined at
my discretion based on various factors,
"Pro Hero - Cementoss"
"Pro Hero - Snipe"
"Pro Hero - Midnight"
including fighting style, grades, and
interpersonal relationships, so here they are:
"Pro Hero - Ectoplasm"
"Pro Hero - Power Loader"
First, Todoroki and Yaoyorozu are one team,
and they're fighting me.
And Midoriya and Bakugo are a team,
and their opponent...
"Pro Hero - All Might - Quirk: One For All"
I... will do it!
All Might?!
Work together to beat me, you two!
"Denki Kaminari"
"Quirk: Electrification"
"He can discharge electricity and use it to attack or find enemies."
"Affiliation: U.A. High School Hero Class 1-A"
"Birthday: 6/29"
"Height: 168 cm"
"Blood Type: O"
"Likes: Hamburgers"
"Mina Ashido"
"Quirk: Acid"
"She can secrete acid from her body and use it to attack or move."
"Affiliation: U.A. High School Hero Class 1-A"
"Birthday: 7/15"
"Height: 159 cm"
"Blood Type: AB"
"Likes: Natto"
"A few days ago"
With the connection between Hero Killer:
Stain and the League of Villains,
"Conference Room"
there is the possibility that
the villains will be reinvigorated, huh?
Of course, it would be better
to prevent that before it begins,
but as a school, it would be
best to be completely certain.
If we consider how fights against villains
will continue to intensify in today's society,
then combat training
against robots is not practical.
Originally, robots were
used to avoid complaints
about people being injured
in the entrance exams.
We can just ignore those.
Let them say what they want.
We can't exactly do that now, can we?
I understand why you want to change the exam,
but having the students
fight us in teams of two...
Yes, I think that is a bit unfair.
If we win too easily,
we won't be able to give them grades.
Of course, we would take that into
consideration and give the students a handicap.
Principal Nezu, what do you think?
Of course, I also agree
with changing the practical exam.
What should we do to keep the
students from being in even more danger?
The answer is simple.
We must have the students
themselves become stronger.
That's true.
I have no objections.
Then, to determine the teams--
First, Todoroki.
In general, he's doing well,
but overall, he has a
tendency to use brute force.
And Yaoyorozu is an all-rounder
but lacks the ability to make
spur-of-the-moment decisions and apply them.
Therefore, I will erase their Quirks
and take advantage of
their weaknesses in close combat.
No objections!
"Izuku Midoriya
Hero Class
Aldera Junior High"
"Katsuki Bakugo
Hero Class
Aldera Junior High"
Next, for Midoriya and Bakugo,
I'm leaving them to you, All Might.
For these two, I didn't pair
them up based on ability or grades.
Just on how badly they get along.
You like Midoriya, right?
Please instruct them well.
Aizawa, you're paying attention.
And now, we'll announce the teams and
the teachers they'll be up against all at once!
"1st Match"
"2nd Match"
"3rd Match"
"4th Match"
"5th Match"
"6th Match"
"7th Match"
"8th Match"
"9th Match"
"10th Match"
The time limit for the
exam is thirty minutes!
Your objective is either to
put these handcuffs on the teacher,
or to have one of you escape from the stage!
Capture the teacher or escape...
It's kind of like the combat training.
Is it really okay to run away?
Yup.
But it'll be different
from the combat training!
You'll be up against someone
waaaaaay better than you!
Better... than us?
I can't really imagine it, though...
Dummy! Hey girl, watch your mouth! You hear?
This time, your exam will be
very similar to a real battle.
Please think of us as villains.
Assuming you come across the enemy,
if you think you can win a
fight against them, then that's fine.
However--
In cases where there's too big
a difference in your abilities,
it would be smarter to run away and get help.
Todoroki, Iida, Midoriya.
I'm sure you three understand this well.
Idiot! The hero killer is after me
and that kid in white armor, right?
Don't fight back.
It'd be better if you ran away!
I won't make that mistake again.
I will pass this test and prove that!
Fight and win, or run and win.
That's right! Your decision-making
skills are being tested!
But with these rules, you're probably
thinking the only choice is to run, right?
That's why we had the
support course make these for us!
Ultra compressed weights!
We'll put on about half of our body weight.
It's to give you a handicap.
It's old-fashioned, but it makes it
hard to move and eats up stamina!
Oh shoot, they're heavier than I thought...
By the way, there was a
competition to decide on the design,
and we ended up using Young Hatsume's.
"It's my time to shine"
Hatsume!
To allow us to consider fighting you, huh?
You're underestimating us.
I wonder.
All right, each team will take the
practical exam in order on the prepared stage.
Sato, Kirishima, get ready.
Yes, sir!
Those waiting their turn can watch
the exams or think of strategies as a team.
Do what you want.
That's all.
Ojiro, I would like to see
what we can do with our Quirks.
Of course.
Tokoyami, let's come up with a plan.
Very well.
The problem is how to
strip Ms. Midnight, right?
No. You're such a scumbag.
"Monitor Room"
Well, it looks like
I'll have a lot of work today.
"Pro Hero - Recovery Girl - Quirk: Heal"
Oh?
You're watching, too, Deku?
Yeah.
We don't have many chances to
see other students and the teachers fight.
Besides, even if I wanted
to talk about strategies...
I see.
Well, for me...
It's like there's no point
trying to talk to him.
Aoyama...
That's why I thought I'd try to use
everyone else's fights for reference.
Yeah.
I have to pass this exam
by any means possible.
Team Sato and Kirishima, practical exam.
Ready, go!
For this exam, we'll definitely get a higher
score by capturing rather than running, right?
I think so.
Mr. Cementoss moves slowly.
Let's break through from
the front and aim for a high score!
All right!
Rikido Sato. Quirk: Sugar Rush!
For every ten grams of sugar, he'll be
five times as strong for three minutes!
However, when he uses sugar for power,
his cognitive function goes down accordingly.
You came from the front after all, huh?
Let's go, Sato!
All right!
Not yet.
You can do it, Kirishima, Sato!
They won't win at this rate.
Kirishima and Sato's Quirks are amazing,
but there's a limit to
how long they can use them.
On the other hand, I don't
think Mr. Cementoss has that.
The more time passes, the more of a
disadvantage Kirishima and Sato will be at.
No way...
This practical exam is
pitting students against teachers
they'd have a hard time with on purpose.
I think the key will be how they
deal with their weaknesses to pass.
That's exactly right.
Before your own turns come around,
you should think carefully about your
compatibility with the teacher you'll fight.
I knew it.
This is never ending, man!
No matter how many I break,
they just keep coming!
I'm sleepy... I'm tired...
Hey, keep trying!
I'm sleepy...
I-I'm running out of breath...
You're both extremely weak
in a war of attrition.
Listen, in a fight, you have to see just how
much you can push the things you're good at.
Team Sato and Kirishima retires due
to both members losing consciousness.
Seriously?!
That's...
Kirishima's...?
Oh dear, it's only the first match,
and I already have work?
No way...
It was this one-sided?
Their Quirks were too
ineffective against his.
This exam is much harder
than what I imagined.
On top of that,
Kacchan and I are up against...
"Practical Exam Location 2"
We, the examinees, are starting
from the middle of the stage, huh?
In order to escape, we must pass
through the designated gate, right?
Which means, the teacher's
probably waiting for us by the gate.
Team Asui and Tokoyami, practical exam.
Ready, go!
I forgot to tell you...
We teachers are also trying
to crush you with everything we have.
Prepare...
...your determination and resolve!
It's the preview!
"Preview"
Asui and Tokoyami are up against Ectoplasm!
And Todoroki and Yaoyorozu
are up against Mr. Aizawa?!
The match has been decided
before it even started, huh?
Hurry up and finish it
so we can get to my turn!
Aoyama, before that,
there's still Iida and Ojiro's exam...
That should be finished quickly, as well.
I can't do anything about it!
Next time, "Yaoyorozu: Rising."
I'll say something shocking in
the last scene, so look forward to it.
Go beyond!
"Next time: Yaoyorozu: Rising"
Plus Ultra!