Ms. Miyauchi,
We have 5 Karuta Club Members!!
President 1-2 Ayase Chihaya
Vice President 1-1 Mashima Taichi
Secretary 1-2 Komachi Tsutomu
Equipment Manager 1-8 Nishida Yusei
Treasurer 1-6 Oe Kanade
Thank you very much!
Introductions
I'm going to become a Queen!
Class B jack of all trades.
A very smart rookie.
The roundest player in Class B.
A very reliable fan of
classical poetry.
You have five members, so you want me
to officially sanction the Karuta Club.
Yes! Please!
Hmm...
Very well.
Yay!
However, change the president
to someone other than Ayase-san.
Huh?!
I'll serve as the advisor for now.
Okay, dismissed.
Why can't I be the club president?
Well, I think she made a wise decision.
Speaking of which,
who should be the club president?
Let Mashima do it.
Huh? Me?
That makes sense.
I'm okay with it.
Then that makes Chihaya...
Okay! I'll be the captain!
Captain?
Chihaya Furu
Treasurer Notes
Our budget is 3,000 yen?
There won't be anything
left after we buy cards.
Any suggestions about
how we should practice?
Mashima and I can take
turns playing with Ayase.
The person who isn't playing
can teach Kana-chan and Desktomu-kun.
My name is Tsutomu, Porky.
Desktomu.
Porky.
That should be fine.
Chihaya is Class A,
so she'll be on a different regimen.
Um, is Class A really so special?
It certainly is.
Players start in Class E.
You have to win tournaments
and work your way up.
By the way, Nishida and I are Class B.
It depends on which society you belong to,
but to reach Class A,
you need to place
first or second in two tournaments.
Oh? Really?
Okay!
Today, I get Kana-chan and Desktomu-kun!
You want to play against Komano and Oe-san?
Yep!
Are you crazy?
Beginners aren't going to learn anything
by playing someone in class A!
But we're gonna play!
Huh?
It won't be any fun for them!
But we're gonna play!
There's no point!
Does the president or the
captain have more say?!
Uh, good question...
Verse 9
But I
Cannot
Hide
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
While some dodge the famous waves...
Like the sound of...
She's fast!
Wait, she's not gonna go easy on her?
the thistle and brush are
blown by the autumn wind
All alone, I step...
Chihaya-chan, this won't work.
The gap between us is too big.
Kana-chan.
When I played karuta for
the very first time,
my opponent was someone who
was incredibly strong.
If he had gone easy on me,
I wouldn't love karuta the way I do now.
So, I'm not going to go easy on you.
I'm going to try my hardest,
because I need you guys to become stronger.
This summer,
the five of us will
participate as a team in
the national tournament!
Omi Jingu?
What's that?
Every July, there's a tournament
at the Omi Jingu shrine
in the Shiga Prefecture
to determine the best high
school karuta players in Japan.
It's considered the Koshien of karuta.
First, we need to win the Tokyo regionals!
After that, we'll be in
the national tournament!
Win... National tournament...
Um, how many schools will be
participating in the Tokyo regionals?
A whole bunch.
Tokyo is a competitive region!
W-We can't make nationals.
We just started playing.
It'll be fine!
I'm going to play real matches
against Desktomu-kun and Kana-chan every day!
You better get ready!
Are you sure about this, Chihaya?
Huh? What do you mean?
The tournament.
If you're playing Komano
and Oe-san every day,
you won't have any time
for serious practice.
Oh, that.
I'll be fine in that department.
How will you be fine?
Don't you want to win the
individual tournament?
Yeah.
Don't worry about the club.
You should be practicing
at the Shiranami Society.
Nishida and I will take
care of the two rookies.
Taichi.
Huh?
Do you remember when
the two of us and Arata
Team Chihaya Furu
played in a team match for the first time?
I get it.
Positioning is key.
Positioning?
Yes, when you're placing the
cards on your side of the field.
It's impossible to memorize the position
of every card perfectly every match, right?
If my name were sullied
by such a brief tryst
I already came up with a
method for placing cards.
I'll put my favorite cards
to the lower right.
But, while putting the "So spring ends" and
"So spring nights" cards together
makes it easier for you,
you're also making it
easier for your opponent.
Oh, I'm not saying that this is a bad thing.
It's fine if you have faster
reflexes than your opponent.
The idea is to keep practicing
until you've learned
the positions that are easiest.
The most important thing is experience!
Let's play a match!
Wait.
Huh?
I'm left-handed, so I should place
my favorite cards to my left?
Isn't that too simple?
Are there any theories about how
to position the long shot cards?
There are sixteen cards
which begin with "The"...
Please teach me more
about how to place my cards well!
I don't want to lose to
someone who joined after me!
be as dear now,
those were the good old days
So the flower petals are...
Since the dew atop...
After many, many years...
My own home is...
I hear the beating of cloth...
Huh? A dead card?
Sorry...
You don't need to apologize.
Failure is part of the experience!
While it brings me no joy...
I-I took a card...
and I have yet to visit Amanohashidate
or read my mother's letters
My first card.
That was great, Kana-chan!
Nice job!
I'm so happy!
I promised myself that
I would take this card today!
That's great!
Arata, I have people to play with now.
I'm not alone.
I'm helping to pass on
what you passed to me.
The school is already closed!
Go home already!
Man, we don't have enough time to practice.
There's only enough time for
two matches after classes end?
I need more time!
You won't be able to
build up any stamina, either.
In tournaments, you sometimes have
to play at least four matches in one day.
The Shiranami Society
held a two-day camp
at Lake Kawaguchi over the summer.
That was to help us build stamina.
Camp?
Yes, a camp.
I like the sound of that!
Let's hold one!
We have a long weekend coming
up because of Founder's Day!
That's great!
But where do we go?
We need a place where we can stay
overnight and play karuta.
There are only three weeks until the tournament.
It makes more sense to just practice
instead of wasting time looking
for a good place for a camp.
We can try to use lunch and nights
to make up the difference.
That's true.
I can't think of a place nearby where
everybody could stay overnight.
Oh!
Hmm?
It was a stroke of luck that Taichi's
parents are in Kobe for a wedding.
With Founder's Day,
we can play karuta all weekend!
There's an empty room and extra futons,
but are you seriously going
to spend the night here?
Of course. I'm the captain.
That's right!
Show me your room
before everyone gets here!
Huh?
We used to play games there.
Do you have a new big TV or something?
Let me see!
Now look here...
You shouldn't be running
to a guy's room like that.
I'm not gonna let you in.
Mashima...
For the first time in my life,
I feel like we live in a class society.
What are you talking about?
Anyway, did you buy it?
You bet.
I'm really excited about this camp.
What are we having for dinner?
How about a test of courage?
I like the sound of that!
Is there a graveyard nearby?
These are all Mashima's?
Yep!
Eiken Grade Pre-1, violin,
horse riding, skiing...
That's amazing.
Oh, my parents made me
take all kinds of lessons.
Man, why did Chihaya have
to show them those?
Oh, is this your mom?
She's beautiful.
Uh-huh, but I don't really
like Taichi's mom.
Huh?
She gets mad when he doesn't win.
I called her "Mrs. Pressure."
Aren't you here to practice?!
I have an announcement to make.
The goal of the first Mizusawa High
School Karuta Club camp is...
to play 15 matches today and tomorrow!
F-Fifteen?!
Match Schedule (Day One)
Reader: Taichi      Desktomu-kun vs Kana-chan     Chihaya vs Porky
Reader: Porky     Desktomu-kun vs Chihaya     Taichi vs Kana-chan
Reader: Chihaya     Desktomu-kun vs Taichi     Porky vs Kana-chan
Reader: Taichi     Desktomu-kun vs Porky     Kana-chan vs Chihaya
Reader: Porky     Chihaya vs Taichi     Desktomu-kun vs Kana-chan
Reader: Chihaya     Desktomu-kun vs Porky     Kana-chan vs Taichi
I made a schedule!
Ch-Chihaya-chan, um...
Desktomu-kun and I don't get any breaks...
Yup. The most important thing
right now is to play matches.
Stay focused in every match!
Kana-chan, your swing is too big!
You aren't using the form I taught you!
Desktomu-kun, you should use
a thrust for that card!
Stay focused!
I want you to become better!
I want to help you win!
I want you to win!
Match Schedule (Day One)
Reader: Taichi      Desktomu-kun vs Kana-chan     Chihaya vs Porky
Reader: Porky     Desktomu-kun vs Chihaya     Taichi vs Kana-chan
Reader: Chihaya     Desktomu-kun vs Taichi     Porky vs Kana-chan
Reader: Taichi     Desktomu-kun vs Porky     Kana-chan vs Chihaya
Reader: Porky     Chihaya vs Taichi     Desktomu-kun vs Kana-chan
Reader: Chihaya     Desktomu-kun vs Porky     Kana-chan vs Taichi
For now, we have to practice!
Um, next is Desktomu-kun vs
Porky and Kana-chan vs...
Chihaya.
Huh?
Let's call it a day.
Why? We've only played five matches!
Look.
May I live to see the day when
I long for the agony I feel now
They're both spent.
But it'll be just as hard in a tournament.
That's why we have to keep practicing!
Chihaya!
Do you want to break people
who are trying their best?
That's enough for today.
That hit the spot!
I'm so glad that Mashima is the president!
Huh? You guys aren't eating?
I have no appetite.
Same here.
Although, we have to eat
something or we won't last!
Desktomu-kun!
Let's do our best to eat something!
We have to practice more tomorrow!
Desktomu-kun!
Kana-chan, we have to escape!
Huh?
Just hide!
M-M—
Mom?
Oh, Taichi. You're having friends over?
I thought you were staying overnight!
Rika suddenly said that
she wanted to go home.
No point in me staying if
we weren't going to USJ!
Rika is so fickle.
Whew, that was close...
Let's grab our shoes and go to my house.
Mrs. Pressure would never
let girls stay overnight.
Kana-chan?
Do you want to break people
who are trying their best?
Now that I think about it,
people always used to tell me...
that I was blind to
everything but karuta.
I'm no good.
No good at all.
Huh?
Wh-What?!
Come with me, Chihaya-chan!
Huh?
Hurry!
W-Wait, Kana-chan?!
What is it, Kana-chan?!
Where are we going in the
middle of the night?!
Hey, Kana-chan!
Wait, how far are we going?!
Hey!
Hey, over here!
Taichi? And everyone else!
Sorry about calling you out here so late,
but we had something to tell you, Captain.
Wait! Let me go first!
Sorry about today!
Huh?
I needed to pay more attention.
Everyone was trying their best,
but I kept pushing you too hard.
I'm really sorry!
I don't see any problem
with what you were doing.
Huh?
You just happen to be a pushy person.
Doesn't hurt to have one of those around.
Porky...
That's right!
We have to work hard because
you're so earnest about karuta!
Kana-chan...
I feel the same way!
I still have much to learn,
but I have a feeling that
I'll grow to love karuta.
Desktomu-kun...
Anyway...
Chihaya
Happy birthday!
Now eat this quick,
before Mashima's mom finishes her bath!
Crap! I forgot to bring a knife!
Oh, these are spoons!
Man, just eat it whole!
That's bad manners!
Oh, this is mine!
Oh! Chihaya, here's the nameplate!
Hurry up!
Delicious! What's this yellow stuff?!
That's mine!
Hurry and eat, Chihaya-chan.
Chihaya, as long as you
have a smile on your face,
karuta will always be fun.
That's the truth, Captain.
I really like the tart crust.
Can I peel off the edge?
Sure.
What?!
It's her birthday,
so she can do what she wants!
Yay! I'll help myself then!
It's so good!
Anyway, Mashima's mom is a little scary.
Somebody should go lock her in the bathroom.
Not me.
Me either.
From an unknown number?
Taichi!
I'll give you the last bit of crust!
Just kidding! It's all mine!
Seriously, Mashima's mom really scared me.
There was a message.
Huh?
Ow!
Oh, a shooting star!
Huh?
Where?!
I've never seen one before!
Taichi, sorry about before.
Tell Chihaya happy birthday for me.
Wataya Arata
Sweet sixteen...
Today is the best birthday ever!
Oh, look! Another one!
What?!
Where is it?!
Oh, it was so pretty.
I missed it again!