Roar!
Monster-san, your face.
Noel-chan!
Koharu. Oh, no!
Monster-san is sick!
Sick?
Don't worry about it.
It was getting old.
I was thinking of switching
it out with a new one.
But—
Koharu!
What are you doing?
Let's go!
Sorry for making you pick me up.
Morning.
Noel!
Oh, yeah. Do you want to come with us?
Sorry.
I...
Come on, let's go.
I invited her, too.
I keep getting rejected.
I'll be with Monster-san.
Monster-san?
Monster-san.
What I Lost
Thank you.
This really helps.
Don't worry about it,
it was on my way to work.
Stop showing off.
All right. We're going.
Yeah.
Hokubi Station
Hurry, hurry!
Aren't you going to sit?
It'd be a waste.
I've never been to this area.
I have to savor it.
We won't have time in
our third year to just relax.
And we don't know what to
present at Hokubi Festival.
Don't you have any ideas, Nonoka?
Me?
Cows!
She never grows up.
I know.
But you haven't really
changed either, Koharu.
Me?
Yeah.
You're always pulling Yuzuki forward.
You were the mature one.
That's not true.
I'm just...
But if that's how you saw me...
It's your glasses.
I'd look grown-up with glasses, too.
Are you done looking at the scenery?
I want to enjoy it more.
I have to savor it.
Really, Noel and Shione should have come.
Togawa-san?
Didn't I tell you?
We invited Shione.
But she's like,
"I have a prior engagement that day."
"From years ago."
Oh.
She's just making it up.
She's really not honest.
Pain, pain, go away!
Ow.
Monster-san!
I'm sorry!
It's my fault.
Monster-san!
It hurts, it hurts!
My stomach, I'm going to die!
I'm sorry.
Don't die, Monster-san!
Please, don't die!
Calm down.
Sorry, that was me.
It's my fault that Monster-san...
No, that's not it.
Right?
It was a joke.
A joke.
I was just messing with you.
All right, I'll help you treat him.
Really?
Departure Times
What is this?
Looks like it just left.
There's nothing here.
We have to wait here for an hour?
What can we do?
I know, but I don't like it.
Didn't you say you wanted to savor it?
It's not the same thing.
Maybe there's somewhere we can sit down.
Oh, in that case...
You brought this?
I thought we might need it
for when we eat lunch.
We're eating here?
We might as well.
You're right.
Hey, look.
Wow!
That looks good.
Right?
I brought all the popular
items on the shop's menu.
Oh, you didn't make it yourself.
Mom made it, but I was the
one who arranged it nicely.
Okay, okay.
Toyono
Oh, yeah.
Remember when we all brought our
lunches together like this before?
The observatory?
Yeah.
I think Koharu forgot
her lunch that time.
But Nonoka asked everyone
to share their dishes with me.
And then Nonoka went overboard,
and I ended up with the
most extravagant lunch.
Oh, yeah.
Huh, Nonoka?
What's wrong? Is something troubling you?
That face...
You're in love, aren't you?
It's nothing.
Oh, you're not?
No.
Come on, let's eat.
Is Monster-san going to get better?
We'll figure something out.
Thank goodness!
I'm sure he's happy that
you're so worried for him.
Is there anything I can help with?
Let's see.
Can you hold his arm down
so he doesn't squirm?
Okay.
So, Shorty...
Shorty? I'm Noel.
Why didn't you go with Koharu and the others?
They invited you, didn't they?
Because it's far.
I can't see the saucer from afar.
Huh?
How would you ever leave the town, then?
Come on, hold it down, Noel.
Okay.
Flowers
Are we there?
Mom.
Come look!
Come on.
What do you mean, come on?
Couldn't you say a little more?
Nonoka, you, too?
This place is too big.
How far do we have to walk?
I think we're almost there.
We're going the right way, right?
Yeah, I'm using the map.
Here!
Fourth row,
sixth from the right
Map?
I'm looking for this landmark,
but I still can't find it.
I'll call Dad and ask.
Oh, I saw this earlier.
Really?
Yeah.
Don't worry about anything, Nonoka.
Leave it to me.
She says to leave it to her, so let's do that.
Okay.
Huh?
I don't think this is it.
I-It might not be not it.
Let's go make sure.
Wait!
Wait up.
I think that does it for now.
Is Monster-san going to be okay?
We did what we could.
Does it hurt anymore?
It's still not quite there.
All right, let's bring
him back into surgery.
Are we at the right place this time?
Yeah, I think it's here.
We're finally here.
In the end, it was all Yuzuki's
fault that we got lost.
Leave me alone right now.
I'll go get some water,
so you can take a break.
I'll help.
You're worried about something, aren't you?
I forced you to let me come, but do
you want to be alone with your mom?
No, that's not it.
Actually, this whole time,
I've been afraid to see Mom.
I think I still am.
If you guys hadn't said
you wanted to meet my mom,
I might not have been
able to come this far.
Why not?
I mean, I've only seen her in pictures,
but she seemed so nice.
Yeah, she was really nice.
She was nice, and always smiling.
She'd always hold me.
And she was warm.
But her hand was always cold.
Seven years ago, right
after we moved out of town,
I learned that we moved so
that Mom could get treatment.
And in the end,
she was gone.
I was so sad and lonely.
Everything went dark.
I was miserable.
I think that's when I stopped remembering.
Mom's voice, her smile,
my life living with her.
I told myself over and over
that none of it ever
happened to begin with.
Then I wasn't miserable anymore.
My heart stopped aching.
But I forgot all the important things, too.
Yuzuki, Koharu, Souta,
Noel.
And I hurt Shione.
But you remembered us.
Then—
No.
Mom wouldn't forgive me the way I am.
She wouldn't be proud of me anymore.
Maybe I was never
a child that was worth being
proud of to begin with.
Then why are you here, Nonoka?
Yeah.
You came here to see your mom, right?
That means you made up
your mind to face all of it.
Like I did with Souta.
You'll be okay.
But—
No, trust me.
I won't accept any arguments.
I've been proud to be your friend
since the observatory days.
Thanks.
But can I have just a little more...
Just a little more time, please.
Sure.
We'll be waiting over there.
Is it already that time of the year?
Pretty.
They're like stars.
It's coming down pretty hard.
Huh, Shione?
It's you, isn't it?
Hey, you came after all.
But why?
Wait.
Nonoka's here.
So what?
Why don't you talk to her
again like way back when?
Grave of Ancestors
This is...
Yeah.
Shione.
Nonoka.
Shione just—
Togawa-san, we're all going
stargazing at the lake tonight.
Come with us.
Has Shione met your mom?
Yeah.
It was Mom who gave me an
opportunity to be friends with Shione.
Komiya Family
If you really want to be her friend...
...you have to smile more.
Don't look like that, then.
Come on.
Hey, Yuzuki.
I remember you smiling all the time.
I think your mom would
like to see your smile, too.
I wonder if Monster-san is going to be happy.
Yeah, I bet he's thankful to you.
He's happy.
And Koharu won't be sad, either.
Koharu won't change him with
another Monster-san now, right?
Why would she?
But Koharu said...
This Kirigon is special.
Special?
That's how much she likes it.
Wait.
Can I ask you something, Yuzuki, Souta?
Kirigon
Here.
Yuzuki did the draft drawing,
I cut boards and stuff,
and we painted it with Koharu.
You were all together.
Your smile pushed me
forward a lot of times.
That means
you took what your mom
told you to heart, right?
Come on, buck up.
Here you go.
Mom.
I'm here to see you.
She's probably there with you about now.
Sorry I couldn't be there.
I decided to let Nonoka
go instead this year.
My name is Komiya Nonoka.
Please be my friend!
This is from Dad.
He couldn't make it this
year because of work.
Happy birthday.
I'll be back again.
Thanks, Mom.
Thank you.
Hey, I...
We'll catch up to you.
Welcome home.
Hello.
Noel?
What happened?
I'm thanking Souta.
Hey, you're back.
What's that?
Oh, that.
We worked hard together.
It might not be exactly the same, but—
Monster-san is all better now.
Yeah, this might work.
What? This?
I said it's fine, does it matter?
But...
I'm the poster girl, after all.
Meteor shower?
Yeah.
Not just yet, but we'll see a lot
of shooting stars on that night.
Would you like to see, too, Shione-chan?
It's pretty.
Are shooting stars even more sparkly?
Yeah.
Let's watch together when it comes.
Okay.
The stars are watching you, too.
It's like they're smiling.
It must be because you're both smiling.
Nonoka!
Noel.
Is Shione here?
Nope.
Oh.
Shione told me to tell you, Nonoka.
That she wanted to watch
the meteor shower with you.
I wanted to watch the
meteor shower with her.
Next episode of Celestial Method:
"What She Believes."
Enjoy.
What She Believes