Naminanakai Public Hospital
Episode Fourteen:
The Promised Day
Naminanakai Public Hospital
Oh, Chisaki-chan.
Must be hard, every day.
No... my school is nearby, so...
Kihara Isamu
There's some left over again.
He doesn't seem to have
much of an appetite lately.
I see...
You should come here once you're
done with nursing school.
It'd be a huge help, having
someone as reliable as you here.
Right...
South 412
Yamaguchi Youhei
Kihara Isamu
Tanaka Masaru
Kitagawa Kyosuke
Grandpa, you have to eat!
There's no flavor.
Once you're out of the hospital, you can
eat whatever you want as much as you like.
All right, I'm going to wipe you down.
Sea Salt
Today's the Tomoebi.
Tomoebi...
We all have to be together.
Someone important's coming, huh?
Oh... Yes.
Apparently a professor
from Tsumugu's lab.
There.
If he's from the city, he
probably won't like country cooking.
Go buy some alcohol and meat with that.
Okay.
Oshiooshi Station Front
Hey, Chisaki.
Sayama-kun.
I'll give you a lift.
I was thinking about stopping
by Saya Mart on my way home.
That's perfect, then.
Apparently Egawa's getting married.
What?!
He knocked a girl up.
K-Knoc—
B-But what about college?
Apparently the girl's dad is
the president of some company,
so he's going to quit school
and work at her dad's company.
Talk about a surprise.
That's this year's biggest surprise.
He said he'd be back for the
coming-of-age ceremony,
so we're all gonna tease him.
Everyone's changed so much...
and it's only been five years.
I think you've changed the most.
Huh?
I dunno...
There's a rumor going around like
you're some lonely housewife.
It's oddly hot.
Wh-What?!
You're late, mister!
You were probably out
playing pachinko again.
Just went out for a refresher.
The boss was waiting
quite a while...
Oh, Chisaki!
Hello.
Here, Akira-kun. This is for you.
Where's your thank you?
Fanks...
Stop it, Akira!
He only listens to Miuna so I
don't know what to do with him.
But...
It's all thanks to Miuna.
The people of the sea
can hibernate, right?
Then Hikari-kun and the others
are probably asleep, too.
Right. I'm sure they're okay.
So...
That's not it!
Akari?!
There's no way I can have
the baby right now...
We've been blessed with a baby...
Don't say something so sad...
I'm sorry. Just leave me alone.
Akari...
Just go over there! Please.
M-Miuna?
Miuna...
It'll be a little brother.
You can tell?
A boy, huh...
I'm happy.
I'm happy...
I'm happy that I'll have a younger brother.
Thank you, Mom.
Akari-san?
Oh, i-it's nothing.
Kancho.
Hey, Akira!
I'm so sorry...
He's so obsessed with that lately...
I-It's okay...
Jeez... you dummy!
Come back here!
Oh? Did you get one of your
special kancho attacks in?
I said, wait! Hey!
Run! Run!
Miuna...
Mi-u-na.
Well done, Sayu.
Good morning, Miss Miuna.
Good morning, Teacher.
You look a lot like your uncle.
Huh?
Your sleeping face.
Hikari used to sleep a lot, too.
Oh...
Now, today's the day of
the exciting Tomoebi.
Before, you couldn't see it unless
you were at the bottom of the sea.
And, now it's the moon
rather than the sun.
Tomoebi
Because the sea is frozen,
the ice acts like a prism,
and gathers the light
from the saltflake snow.
That creates an image in the atmosphere,
Tomoebi Before
Only visible from inside the sea
Temperature
Water Temperature
Tidal Current
Sun
Calm Sea Surface
Tidal Current
and makes an illusory moon.
When the moon is low
in the sky, let's see...
I'd say 8 o'clock is probably
the best viewing time.
Sensei, before that...
Oh? Oh, right. Dinner.
After this, it's time to get
ready for the rice feeding.
Having a rice feeding by
the sea with everyone...
Hello, everyone...
It's sort of nostalgic, isn't it?
The main event is the Tomoebi.
Don't forget that.
Yeah...
Having class at night is exciting.
Right, Minegishi?
Oh, right.
Be on your guard, Miuna.
For what?
I totally found out...
When the Tomoebi happens
Minegishi's planning to ask you out.
Ask me out...
Everyone's so lame!
School's a place for studying!
Sayu, you used to hate studying.
I've decided that I'm going
to be a girl living on her own.
It's not like I'm going to
find work in Oshiooshi...
So I'm going to go out into the city
and become an independent woman.
You've thought out your future that far?
Well, yeah. What about you, Miuna?
I'm not sure yet...
But I don't plan on leaving.
Oh...
Miuna.
Huh?
Your hair's gotten longer.
Yeah.
Sayu, Miuna.
The teacher's calling for you.
Oh, thanks.
Hurry up, Miuna!
Yeah.
Don't you guys have to be in school?
I always watched from here...
Just like this.
Akari!
Akari-san!
Mukaido!
Look! The bridge pier!
No!
At that moment, I
decided I wouldn't cry.
Because I knew that Hikari and
the others were in the sea.
I believed that they were safe.
Hikari and the others are still
somewhere I can't go, smiling.
I'm home.
Oh! Smells good!
Sorry I'm late.
I'll help, too.
It's okay. It's my turn today.
You're a little wet.
I went to look at the
sea again for a little bit.
But something's in the
way so it's no use.
The sea temperature's gone down, too...
Is your tummy okay?
It's fine!
We'd always gotten pregnant
and raised our young in the sea.
Well, it's not all bad.
Huh?
He's not alone... Dad's there, too.
And Hikari liked Manaka...
If Manaka and the others had been
left in the sea, and he was alone,
I don't think Hikari
would know what to do...
Hikari... likes Manaka...
Oh, Miuna. It'll spill over.
Safe.
He likes Manaka...
Miuna.
What's wrong?
Sorry! I'm coming!
Even now, I look out from here...
To the sea where Hikari
and the others are.
Professor! Tsumugu!
Why not warm up a little
before the Tomoebi?
Delicious!
The stewed golden-eye is delicious.
You can't get food
like this in the city.
Is that so?
Huh?
N-Nothing. As long as you like it.
The meat is good.
Sorry to barge in like this.
Not at all.
It's lively, and I'm glad.
Because Tsumugu came to our lab,
our research has progressed quite a bit.
There are only fourteen
sea villages in Japan.
Not to mention, we can't step
foot into any of them right now.
Even when we try diving to investigate,
the tide gets in our way and we
can't get close to the location.
There are even specialists now saying
that the sea villages don't exist anymore.
They're just saying
that to get attention.
Hiradaira-san,
I believe that there is a close relationship
between the surface and the sea.
To explain the abnormal weather,
we need to research the
sea villages as well.
I see...
Oh, I'll bring you another.
Well, thank you.
She's a great girl.
Are you sure there's nothing going on?
Of course not.
You guys are at that age and
you're living under one roof.
Not to mention, she's beautiful...
that'd usually mean...
She has someone else that
she's liked for a long time.
Huh?
There...
He can take care of the futon himself.
He's a guest.
That wouldn't be right.
Won't you come see the Tomoebi, too?
I'll pass.
There's no point in seeing the
Tomoebi without the others.
I see...
Do you want me to make some
amazake since it's cold?
Yeah, sounds good.
What are we gonna do?
It really did turn into a huge deal.
Did we find the sea
kids that fell in yet?
This is the first time something
like this ever happened.
To think that the Sea
God was this angry...
What are we going to do about her?
She doesn't have any
relatives on the surface...
Chisaki-chan...
You're welcome in our home...
You can come live with us.
B-But...
You've already got a full
house in your apartment.
And...
I'm from the sea, as well.
Grandpa, the lady next door
wanted to give this to you...
Grandp—
Grandpa!
Please, wake up! Grandpa!
In Surgery
If you're a family member,
please wait over here.
No! Don't take Grandpa away!
Chisaki, calm down.
Don't leave me...
Don't take anyone else away from me!
Chisaki.
Um... Did you pack your underwear?
Don't worry about it, I'll do it myself.
No way. You're not all there when
it comes to stuff like this.
So you're gonna be a college
student in the big city...
Oceanography researcher
is really amazing.
You should be proud!
Sorry that you somehow ended
up taking care of Gramps.
Well, this is my other family.
My precious...
Family, huh...
I'm going to do research in college.
About the sea villages,
about what happened that day...
I'm sure they're tied into what's
going to happen on the surface.
Tsumugu...
I'm sure they're fine.
If everything takes a
turn for the better,
I'm sure we'll see them again.
Yeah.
So good!
What the hell? Mine is all potatoes!
Let's hurry up and eat.
The Tomoebi is about to start.
Minegishi, what about Shiodome?
Huh? Uh...
Come on.
Today's the day you prove you're a man.
Seriously, boys are so stupid.
Your tray. I'll go put it away.
Oh, right...
The currents...
It's about to start.
Yes, it is.
Since that day, the sea has been calm.
Quietly... Quietly...
Not telling me what's
happening below.
Shiodome!
Um...
Are you... asking me out?
Huh?! Wh-Wha...
I'm sorry, I was being
overly self-conscious.
If I'm wrong, don't worry about it.
You're not wrong!
Then let me say this first.
I'm in love with someone else.
Huh?
So... I'm sorry.
I can't!
I've always liked you!
Ever since grade school!
I can't just give up...
I can't... just give up.
I can't give up!
Who is this guy you like?
Tell me!
Well...
Shiodome!
This is the Tomoebi...
It's quite magnificent, isn't it?
Hey, what is that?
Something big is showing up on screen...
Is it a fish?
H-Hey, what's wrong?
Miuna, you...
Hikari!
He hasn't changed at all
from back then... not at all.
He's not breathing!
Um, I don't think doing mouth-to-mouth
on a person from the sea will...
H-Hika—
Manaka!
Who... are you?
She's Miuna.
Huh? Miuna?
Tsumugu?
Hikari's eyes...
had stopped moving in sadness.
Like the lull of the sea.
The reason Hikari came back...
You look like you've seen a monster.
Talk about a turn of events.
I changed from back then?
Hikari... came back.
Episode Fifteen:
The Protector of Smiles