I'm Gouda Takeo, a first-year in high school.
He's Sunakawa Makoto, a friend of mine.
And that's my girlfriend, Yamato.
Takeo-kun!
Yamato!
Shuuei
You must be the first-year, Gouda Takeo.
We need to talk to you.
Don't worry, Yamato.
I will protect you.
I'll be your shield.
My Strength
Please, Gouda!
Help us!
Okay!
You will?
But you have no idea what help you'll be giving.
Men are bowing down to me.
How could I refuse?
And they're second-years, too.
You're so cool, Takeo-kun.
So what did you need help with?
Join the judo club.
Just for a month.
We're begging you!
At the end of this month,
our judo club will participate
in the Shuu-Bi Match.
Shuu-Bi Match?
It's an annual tradition
where we compete with Bianka High School,
our long-time rivals.
So far, our score is 9-9.
We must secure victory in
the 10th match for glory!
Indeed!
There's even a superstition that
the years we lose the match,
we won't make it to nationals!
It's pretty much our Battle of Mt. Tennou!
It's a team competition where we need
to win three out of five matches,
but our champion's been injured,
and we have no one to take his place.
Please fight for me!
The explanation's so long
that you weren't able to take it in, right?
So I just have to try to win the
match happening in a month?
That's right.
Oh, guess you got the gist of it.
Thanks, Gouda!
I'll do it!
See you at morning practice tomorrow!
Right!
We're counting on you!
It's amazing that they'd ask you for help.
I didn't know you did judo, Takeo-kun.
Up till the end of junior high.
You even competed in the nationals.
Eh? Wow!
That's so cool!
Why did you stop in high school?
I forgot to join...
Why bother?
You're strong enough.
No, there are many more who
are stronger than I!
I'm sure you'd rank pretty high,
if anyone ranked all humanity
in order of their strength.
I wonder where you'd place...
I've got a way to go.
Strongest Primate
After all, there are people like Karelin.
I see
Yup
That's good and all, but...
If you're going to train for the match,
doesn't that mean you won't
be able to see Yamato-san
for about a month?
I see...
I'm sorry, Yamato.
I'll be fine, Takeo-kun!
Help the judo club.
It's great that they'd come to you for help.
Yamato...
Besides, I want to see you do judo.
I love her!
If you really want to see me,
just say the word.
I'll come right away.
You will?
Okay!
I'll be cheering you on, so I'll be fine.
Good luck, Takeo-kun!
Yamato,
I know you're looking out for me!
Begin!
Okay! I'm next!
'Kay!
I've...
got this...
Yamato!
Gouda...
All for us...
C'mon, guys!
Right!
Thank you!
Yamato!
Oh, Takeo-kun!
Good job!
Sorry I came without telling you.
Something's in your hair.
Oh.
Earlier...
I thought about keeping it a secret,
but I peeked into your practice session.
You were so cool!
Yamato...
Oh, here. I made this for you.
They're rice balls.
I can make other things, see?
Yamato...
I got a little too into it this
morning and made a ton.
I might have made too much.
Beware of Gropers
Takeo-kun?
Thank you, Yamato.
But you shouldn't come here again.
Eh?
Let's go.
I'll walk you home.
Oh, okay...
It's dark and unsafe.
If anything were to happen to Yamato,
I'd never forgive myself.
Thanks for the food!
This is salmon.
This one's pickled plum.
Cod roe.
Salmon roe.
BBQ beef.
Tuna with mayo!
She made all these different kinds
with those tiny hands of hers.
The rice must've been piping hot, too.
They're delicious.
They're delicious, Yamato!
I love her!
The rice balls are awesome!
Thank you.
Thanks for the food.
Great!
I thought you might get hungry.
Eat up and good luck!
I'm gonna give it everything I've got!
Takeo-kun, how's it going?
Today, there are lots of flowers
blooming at school.
I only know the name of flowers
like tulips and stuff,
but I'd like to go with you to a
botanical garden sometime.
Let's do that!!
Take, you're perfect for this.
I can't see any stars today.
I wonder if it's going to rain tomorrow.
Takeo-kun, don't forget to take an umbrella.
What kind of umbrella do you have?
It's black and huge.
Hey, that's a beach umbrella, isn't it?
I've always wondered about that.
Takeo-kun, don't get hurt, okay?
I'm going to make a wish right now.
Don't get hurt! Don't get hurt!
I can feel the good vibes!
Thanks!
Good luck, Takeo-kun!
I'm cheering you on 24/7.
Thanks!
What's all that?
What is it?
They're scones.
I found myself baking a ton when
I was thinking about Takeo-kun.
That's a bit scary...
Please have some, too, Sunakawa-kun.
Oh, sorry, I guess it might feel like leftovers.
I mean, they are, but...
Well, why not just give them to Takeo?
He wouldn't have a problem
eating them all, would he?
I... I...
I don't know if Takeo-kun likes me anymore.
No way
No way.
But he told me not to come.
It might be because I got ahead of
myself and showed up with food!
Maybe it crossed a line...
No, I think it's just a misunderstanding
or you're overthinking it.
He totally isn't the type of guy to
get mad about stuff like that.
Right...
You're right.
Takeo-kun's not like that, yeah.
Yeah, yeah
Now that I'm calmer about it, I see it now.
Right?
Thanks, Sunakawa-kun.
I don't think you have to work
yourself up over this.
It's the first time I've fallen for anyone.
Meeting Takeo-kun was the first time
that I felt this rush coming up from the
bottom of my heart, you know?
That's when I realized it's what love's like.
Every day, I'm excited about him
and can't stop smiling.
Every time I see him, I know I love him.
Oh, Takeo was my first friend, too.
Wow, we're the same
Having him as your "first" is pretty intense, huh?
I love him so much, I even creep myself out!
I want to calm down already!
I wonder if it'll ever calm down...
I've been friends with him for over a decade,
but he hasn't bored me yet.
Oh, my god... What am I going to do?
Maybe I'll feel nervous for the rest of my life!
Maybe Takeo'd feel that way with
you for the rest of his life, too.
Gouda!!
I really want to see him.
Why don't you wait for him?
No, seeing him will only make me
want to see him more often.
I'll just have to hold back!
I don't want to get in his way!
I don't think he's the type to
think that way, but okay.
When he was training, Takeo-kun was so cool.
He'll be even cooler at the actual match.
I've seen him at a match
Huh?
More than he already is?
He's like a ball of concentration.
He's the type that never
misses a penalty kick
Wow!
That'd be incredible!
I wonder if I'll be okay!
Oh!
That star's just like Takeo-kun.
Huh?
Look... If you draw a line between
that star and the other star,
it looks like Takeo-kun laughing!
Huh... So it's like the Takeo constellation.
Yeah!
Takeo Constellation
Oh, those seven stars look just like Takeo-kun
when he was doing a shoulder throw!
Huh...
Takeo 2
Guess that'd be Takeo 2.
And those over there are when
he saved me on the train.
Takeo 3, then.
I think you can see anything
you want in the stars.
Right...
Oh, that one is when Takeo-kun
escaped from the fire!
I'm starting to see him in the stars, too.
Next!
Takeo-kun, please spar with me next.
And me, after that.
Then me.
Gouda, you're doing this for us...
All for us...
All right! We'll follow suit, men!
Got it!
It's true that I want to give
everything I have to this,
given that a man bowed his head to me
and I've agreed to help.
But it's more because Yamato
wished me good luck.
Yamato...
I haven't heard her voice in a while.
Fight
It's the first time I've gone this
long without talking to her.
Evening.
Can I call you?
Send
Takeo-kun?
It's me!
Yeah.
Is something wrong?
I just wanted to hear your voice.
Huh? My voice?
My voice... Okay.
Okay, I'll talk.
Um, this is Yamato.
How are you, Takeo-kun?
I'm fine!
Yamato...
And, um...
Oh, man...
It's hard to talk!
Yamato...
Oh, your match is tomorrow, right?
Come with Suna.
Okay, I will.
I'm looking forward to it.
Watch me fight.
You're done with training?
Yeah.
The match will be 6 PM tomorrow, at the arena.
Takeo, here.
These are Yamato's!
You're perceptive.
She said she made too much when
she was thinking about you.
Why didn't she bring them to me?
She said she didn't want to bother you.
Like she could!
Right?
You almost lost me there.
Yamato-san was almost passing out
from excitement about the match.
Show off for her, okay?
All right, night.
Yamato...
She didn't say anything like that.
She just wished me good luck.
Yamato...
Good luck, Takeo-kun!
Yamato, this way.
I want you watching from up close.
Takeo-kun...
Hey, Takeo.
Been a while.
Iwayama Tsuyoshi                           Bianka HS
Hey, Tsuyoshi.
Long time, no see.
Good luck today.
He's a buddy of mine. In elementary
school, we went to the same dojo.
Oh, nice to meet you.
I'm Yamato, Takeo-kun's girlfriend.
Girlfriend?!
You've already lost, Takeo!
You were stronger than me until junior high,
but after starting high school,
I've been competing at the national level.
I won't lose to some guy who's been
fooling around with a girlfriend.
Takeo-kun, I think I'll go watch from the side.
I'll be fine outside, too...
Tsuyoshi, girlfriends aren't bad.
What?
Watch right in the middle of the room, Yamato.
Okay!
Good luck, Takeo-kun!
The path of judo is not paved in a single day.
Takeo's been led astray,
wasting his time on romance.
He's lost his chance.
The victory is mine.
Bow!
What does it mean to be strong?
First player, forward.
Put your back into it!
Got it!
Fight!
You've got this!
Yamato...
Everything you make tastes so heartfelt.
Fourth, forward!
Good luck, Captain.
Yeah, I'll fight twice as hard in your stead.
Fight!
One more win!
Begin!
Go!
Fight!
Advantage.
Bianka                   Shuuei
Majority vote.
Two wins and two losses.
The next match will be decisive.
Shuuei High School's Team Champion,
Gouda Takeo, forward!
Sorry, Gouda...
I'm counting on you.
Bianka High School's Team Champion,
Iwayama Tsuyoshi!
Here!
You might be wanting to impress your girlfriend,
but I won't let you.
Go, Tsuyoshi!
Go, go, Tsuyoshi!
You're the best in the prefecture!
Push, push, Tsuyoshi!
Bow!
Begin!
All right!
Come at me! Come on!
What does it mean to be strong?
Judo's been my life.
There's no way I'll lose to Takeo,
now that he's lost his bark!
Wow! This is a match to remember!
There's no way I'll lose.
That's a win!
Not yet!
I can't lose!
Dig in!
Almost there!
There's no way I'll lose!
Takeo-kun...
No way...
Wait!
Penalty!
Damn it.
My heart...
It's on fire.
So this... is your strength...
Ippon!
It's over!
Thank you!
Well, that was awesome to
watch, even for a guy.
Yamato, I love you.
Good job, Takeo-kun!
It was amazing.
You were so cool!
Thank you, Yamato!
It's because you were there, cheering me on.
No, not at all...
Takeo, Yamato-san's already about to pass out.
What does it mean to be strong?
I don't know.
But, Yamato, I want to become a great man.
The stars are beautiful tonight.
Yeah!
Oh, that reminds me!
We found the Takeo constellation.
When you draw a line between
that star and the other,
it's the one with you laughing.
And that's the one where you're
doing a shoulder throw.
I'm surprised you remember all of them.
To me, they look like Yamato.
Eh?
If you connect that star and the other one...
See?
It's Yamato's smiling face.
It's right next to your constellation!
Which one?
Wow!
I'm so happy!
That one's the constellation for
the macarons you made.
That one's for you when we first met.
Oh, it's next to yours again!
Yamato, let's see each other again tomorrow,
That one's for you when you
pushed the beam with me.
and talk about all the little things,
until the sun goes down.
There's Suna, too.
My Friend
Next time: My Friend.