It wasn't supposed to be
like this, head in my hands
Struggling to escape from
this saturated world
Time passes like whispering sand
These circumstances, unchanging
gazing out at a dreamless tomorrow
Wanna say goodbye to the
confusion of yesterday
I try reaching out, as if to resist
We cry millions of times
and then get born again
Let's go with these red eyes
to that pictured future
Come here right by me,
I'm clapping my hands
Where are you? Who are you?
Strain my eyes in the darkness
Can't see anything, don't know
anything, but I'll still go
To the place of shining
light in which you wait
Episode Nine
Kaishou Rinroku's Crime
Inspired by Ango Sakaguchi's
Meijikaika Ango Torimonochou
(Meiji-era Detective Stories)
"Sneering Demon" and "Red Trap"
I recommend turning comments off.
Why doesn't the mainstream press report this?
They went and shot him!
Ouch! Better not fuck with the guys upstairs, eh?
This is gonna get taken down ASAP...
Leaked Company Profit Report
Poster: Full Circle
Suspicious of a Lover?
It seems there are a lot
of uploads like this.
This one and this one and this one...
The posters are Full Circle.
They say the whole
world is "one circle".
I-I don't know anything about it.
Lately, these crackers have
started targeting JJ Systems.
They're on a roll, leaking everything
from in-house accounting documents
to info on Chairman Kaishou
Rinroku's private affairs.
So cute~~
She’s Kaishou's daughter?!
My waifu
Hot damn...
The daughter of the upper crust, indeed...
The horse is so cool!!!www
Cute...
This kind of stuff can be taken down
quickly with automated monitoring, right?
But there are those who
can get around that.
Like they did with a certain song...
Koyama Izumi
Public Prosecutor
Joint Coordinating Dept.
Public Prosecutor's Office
Oyamada Arata
Underground Software Dealer
Do you think nobody noticed?
In the Joint Coordinating Department...
Even you must realize it.
Bettenou is dangerous.
She turns the words of a
certain person into reality...
Or at the very least, she has the
ability to make it seem that way.
It seems that Bettenou escaped?
Why have you come all the way here?
Don't tell me you intend to
acquire Bettenou yourself?
The police and Kaishou are searching
for her whereabouts, too.
We have to find her before they do...
And what do we do when we find her?
Sasa Kazamori
Artificial Intelligence (R.A.I.)
Well...
If what you say is true,
Bettenou isn't human.
And besides, she hasn't
committed any crimes.
Yuuki Shinjurou
Detective
Of course she's committed crimes!
I mean...
Shinjurou, it's not a good idea
to get too close to her...
Inga
Detective's Assistant
Inga...
Shinjurou-sama, you've got mail.
Are you kidding me?!
We already put out the
breaking announcement,
and now Professor Kaishou doesn't show?!
Motoyama Minami
Television Producer
Um, it's Full Circle again...
AD
Motoyama's Assistant
Can I watch anime?
Apparently, Kaishou Rinroku is
going to be on TV right now.
A person that everyone knows
is going to make a last second
appearance live on our show.
The Roundtable
The Chairman of JJ
Systems, Kaishou Rinroku.
This is the man who is working
hard to quickly reconstruct
the telephone and internet systems
that were targeted during the war,
while at the same time solving
a great number of criminal cases
as an adviser to the police.
Mr. Kaishou has requested the
opportunity to speak about today's theme,
legislation to nationalize
the energy industry.
And we're in commercial!
Just a few moments ago, an odd post
claiming to be from Full Circle
has appeared on various bulletin
boards and major social networks!
Oh, this. I see.
It seems our lives are in danger.
"Why is Kaishou Rinroku going
to appear on that TV program?"
"Actually, the other participants
are a politician who's been
critical of JJ Systems,
the owner of a rival company, and a
critic who released a tell-all book..."
"In other words, all enemies
of Kaishou Rinroku."
C-Could Chairman Kaishou's sudden
request to be on the show be because of that?!
Oh, come on!
Are you saying that Chairman
Kaishou of all people
would murder us on a public TV program?
Speaking of Full Circle...
Didn't they recently expose you
Fuwa Jujirou
Solar Power Advocate, Entrepreneur
for putting out government propaganda
news reports during the war?
Well, that doesn't have a
direct connection to this...
So what about Mr. Kaishou?
Is he really going to show?
Kaishou Rinroku
Assuming he actually exists
in the first place...
Chairman Kaishou is here!
Chairman!
Pardon my lateness.
I hadn't taken the train for so long
Y-You took the train?
Kaishou Rinroku
Well, shall we get started?
Chairman of JJ Systems
This should be a heated discussion.
Miss, the Master's program
is about to start!
Kaishou Family Maid (Head Maid)
Kaishou Family Maid
I don't care!
Again with that!
I'm sure you're secretly
going to watch it alone.
Kaishou Rie
Daughter of Kaishou Rinroku, Lives at Home
What am I, a cockroach?!
He looks good on camera,
I have to admit...
We're going to commercial.
Chairman Kaishou!
I'll be right back.
I have a phone call.
From home, you see...
I can't believe this guy...
Maybe he's consulting someone
about wiping us all out.
Like all of a sudden, boom!
Father?
You know I'm not good with machines.
I don't know the difference
between a crack and a hack.
Then why is Full Circle
targeting Chairman Kaishou?
They're leaking too much
personal information.
You're by yourself today?
It's a public holiday.
Thanks to that, I had to drive myself...
Don't change the subject!
I'm at the site...
Oh my god! And what about the Chairman?!
What about Chairman Kaishou?!
The TV station's server is down.
The nearby fixed cameras...
Kaishou Rinroku
Run! Quickly! Quickly!
He may call the house, so stay put!
Check the email, too!
Y-Yes, but...
Please just do it!
You stay home, Rie.
Father?!
But... That was a live show...
I appeared via private
webcam from the house.
Anyway, I'm going to see
what's happening over there.
But... They said it was
a live appearance...
Give me a break!
You think I'll be satisfied
with, "He's not here"?!
Prosecutor! Over there!
Chairman...
Hayami Seigen
Director of the Security Bureau
Metropolitan Police Dept.
Um...
Hospital, hospital...
Bettenou
Eight people have been
listed as missing or dead,
among them the participants
in a live TV program.
Word from the hospital is...
We're told that there was antipathy
between Mr. Kaishou Rinroku
and the president of Solar Field, Fuwa
Jujirou, who's been badly injured.
"Mr. Kaishou Rinroku will eliminate
those who stand in his way."
Strangely enough, Full Circle's
prediction has come true.
He isn't anywhere.
And that was on the floor.
Go to the hospital here
Stupid Inga... Where the
hell did you wander off to?
Keep out! Everyone, keep out!
Explosion during a popular debate television program...
Live from the hospital where the injured are being treated
What's the Public Security
Force doing here?
8 people dead or missing
We're in charge of private
security for Chairman Kaishou!
We dropped him off at a
TV station yesterday too,
but to think this could happen...
Nobody's allowed in.
I've got a fever. Maybe a cold...?
Or it could be the flu...
If I don't get some medicine,
I think I'm gonna keel over...
The Defeated Detective!
You're probably the one who
targeted Professor Kaishou.
Mizuno Sakon
Public Security Force Commander
I'm Mizuno, the commander of
the Public Security Force.
That's Mihara, one of my men.
Mihara Yasutarou
Member of the Public Security Force,
Commanded by Mizuno
As long as we're around, you're not
getting anywhere near Professor Kaishou!
Mr. Yajima! You were here to pay a
visit to Chairman Kaishou, weren't you?
Yajima
Critic
Aren't you a friend
of his from way back?
Yes, and if this hadn't happened,
he would be working now as
always, around the clock.
Perhaps this will serve as
a chance for him to relax.
Was the perpetrator
after Mr. Kaishou? Or...
Mr. Yajima...
It's not certain that
this was terrorism.
Apparently, the station is very old
and I heard it's possible
that this was just a fire.
Please let this person through.
He's an acquaintance of Ms. Kaishou.
Defeated Detective!
Unusually enough, you were successful
with Mr. Yajima's request.
But don't let it go to your head.
Kaishou Rinroku
Everything is just as
Full Circle predicted!
We were almost killed!
And the criminal is in there!
If Chairman Kaishou had taken one wrong
step, he would have lost his life!
Right! He just happened
to leave the studio
the moment before the
explosion occurred!
What a coincidence!
Who would ever believe that?!
Ow! Anyway, I'm not
taking this lying down!
I'm not going to see him.
My father's condition would
get worse if you did.
Then why did you call me here?
I have a job.
About the explosion?
Doesn't it seem like the culprit
is Kaishou Rinroku himself?
Is that what you think?
My father almost died.
Certainly, I can't say
that he's a saint.
But he wouldn't do something as stupid
as gathering together people who
disagree with him and then killing them.
Instead, he would commit
the perfect crime,
which no one would ever suspect him of?
That's right!
Don't tell me this is my fee?
Yep.
What did you talk to her about?
What do the police think?
What was the cause of the explosion?
The military is investigating, too...
But it doesn't seem to have
been a normal explosion.
Who would've thought, me, having
to prove Kaishou's innocence?
Is Inga still lost?!
Hold it!
Not even a member of the
Diet can get through!
Hey!
A Diet summons at a time like
this shows no common sense!
Note: The Japanese Diet has a constitutional power to compel any citizen to come testify before them.
Diet?
Ow...
Kuramitsu Mine
New Diet Member
Thank you.
You're a member of the Diet?
Just a newly-elected errand girl.
I told them it was impossible today,
but they ordered me to get
Chairman Kaishou's testimony.
You mean as a witness to
yesterday's explosion?
No, of course not!
The internal information that Full
Circle released the other day
talked about a system that could be
diverted to part of the military.
It was information from JJ Systems?
We just want him to explain
for some foreign countries
that the system is designed
for peaceful purposes.
Let's see... Microwave transmissions
or something like that...
The live TV broadcast date
has already been set, so...
For the time being he'll need his rest.
Hard luck for you...
The cause was microwaves?
Live aerial footage from the explosion site
Train?
No! Train!
You're saying Kaishou
came here by train?
No! I said he came here by train!
What did he seem like at the time?
There was that thing with Full Circle,
so we were worried, but he was normal.
In the first place, doing it like that,
he would've gotten blown up, too.
Hey! Don't be a pansy about it!
Can't you melt the range?
I'll try it one more time!
What was he doing?
You don't know?
The microwave, it's the microwave.
Everyone's talking about what
happened yesterday on the net.
People are wondering whether the
cause might be military microwaves.
It's the same principle as
putting metal in a microwave
and it crackles with electricity,
suddenly producing high heat.
We're being told that the
cause of the accident
was the dilapidated station building,
so I'm gonna prove that wrong!
It's all scientific-like, right?
I'm sure some people are
saying that JJ Systems
used microwaves to cause the accident...
But there's no way someone would have
that fired at a building they were in.
What?! I'm proving him innocent!
What?!
What is it?!
That day, I saw...
Saw what?
My father... was at home...
My father wasn't at the TV
station. He was at home!
But later, I got a phone
call from the hospital
saying my father had been
injured at the TV station.
The producer says my father
was at the studio, too...
It's just like a doppelganger!
Unless someone disguised
himself as my father?!
Why did you tell me?
I don't know...
What's that?
I'm returning your fee.
Detective!
Do you think my father is the criminal?
Damn it! Damn it all to hell!
What are you doing, Shinjurou?
Inga...
You're back?
I've figured out where Bettenou is.
Many people have testified
that Kaishou Rinroku
was at the TV station at
the time of that explosion.
Yet his own flesh and blood insists
he was at home at the same time.
The same kind of thing
happened once before.
Oh?
It's Bettenou.
The believers in the Bettenou
Society saw what wasn't there.
They even saw hallucinations
through the TV.
If that's what the Kaishou that
appeared at the TV station was...
We dropped him off at a TV
station yesterday too...
I said he came here by train!
It was a hallucination,
so the details conflict.
The day Bettenou disappeared
from the Novelist's side...
Bettenou was still there.
That's enough, stop it...
If Kaishou says "Bettenou isn't
here", then Bettenou can't be seen.
Inga, you too... Damn it!
What are you mad about, Shinjurou?
Mad?! You can use Bettenou to
turn any lie into the truth!
I didn't think Kaishou was the kind of
guy who'd rely on something like that!
I tried to prove that
bastard's innocence!
Well, then... You can't win.
Inga...
Leave him be!
Since it's come to this,
I'm gonna get him!
I'm gonna corner him
where he can't escape!
Diet Member Kuramitsu?
Yes, this is Yuuki Shinjurou,
Kuramitsu Mine
"I'm heading to the future!"
and I'm calling about the summoning
for the live broadcast testimony...
Amid all this, it's been decided
that Mr. Kaishou Rinroku
will be summoned as a witness before
the National Diet's budget committee.
It has nothing to do
with the explosion...
Diet Member Kuramitsu!
Testimony Live from his hospital bed
Kaishou Rinroku Summoned to Testify
The Chairman has expressed a desire
to testify from the hospital,
but will he maintain his innocence?
Um, I'm just a low-ranking
member, so I don't know.
Is it possible to murder
with a microwave satellite?
Remember, the purpose is to have him
answer the suspicions of foreign nations,
and he is not suspected
of murder at all!
Go to hell!
You're going to make a severely
injured man testify?!
Are you ready?
Start.
I'm going to separate the footage
and voice that we record.
Then I'm going to replace the voice
with a computer generated one,
so the real voice of the person
testifying won't be broadcast.
It sounds like Chairman Kaishou's voice,
but it's actually from a
vocal synthesizing program.
Are you sure about this?
It's possible that classified
information will be brought up,
so just in case, I want
to have a time lag.
If Bettenou's power is
controlling people via voice,
then switching that with an
artificial voice should stop it.
You didn't strike me as the type
to talk to a cute stuffed animal.
Was it a present from someone?
I use it in place of a bag.
Thank you.
Sure.
Your advice was right on.
His daughter persuaded
him when I told her
that her father's innocence
should be broadcast on live TV.
But about those conditions...
What's with the set up?
Consider it a good luck charm.
In the pale morning
mist, a whispered prayer
I'm gonna follow this
twisted landscape with you
Looking for the "truth",
"a 'lie' will do" is it?
Tracing it as if we can see through
Looking for, beyond words
Like a falling feather
Looking for, find it
So we can cuddle close together here
Looking for, unravel it
Like a tattered cloud
Looking for, find it
So we can cuddle close together here
The preview this time too is inspired
by "Red Trap" from Ango Torimonochou.
I'm tired of this pattern! It's boring!
The original idea was a segment of me
not being able to read the original
story and riffing on the gap,
and riffing on the gap
between it and modern stuff.
But the scriptwriter has
totally forgotten that
and only just remembered
now, but it's too late!
I laid it out straight! You
got a problem with that?!
Next time on UN-GO: "Kaishou
Rinroku's Funeral".
"Kaishou Rinroku's Funeral"
Inspired by "Sneering Demon" and "Red Trap" from Ango Sakaguchi's
Meijikaika Ango Torimonochou
(Meiji-era Detective Stories)
Yeah, that's right! He's gonna die!
You got a problem with that?!