Sleigh Beggy.
Dear child, with the name
of a neighbor of long ago.
A being nearer to us than the humans,
bearing a burden too great for a human child.
How adorable you are.
What will you find at the end of
your journey with the failure born
in the shadows of the forest?
Show me what you find.
Those are wooly bugs.
Elias.
They consume the cold in the air and
grow fleece on their bodies, like sheep.
That means they multiply during the summer.
There are a lot this year, though.
Are they neighbors?
No, they're closer to animals.
Although very few humans can see them.
Now, let's begin.
Okay.
That's it.
You're good at this.
Their wool is perfect for using
in magic and sorcery tools.
Angelica asks me to do this, too.
Wow.
You can use the leftovers to
make a pillow or something.
You'll probably sleep well.
You might get to have the
dreams you want to have.
The dreams I want to have?
I'll take a little when we're done.
Right.
Oh, don't trim from their
limbs. Just the torso.
Sorry. You could have told me sooner.
That's quite a haul.
I'll go get a bag.
You keep practicing.
Oh, right.
Yes?
If you find one that seems a bit
different, tell me before you touch it.
Okay.
I was going to talk to him
as soon as I got home.
I don't know when I should bring it up.
No, it's that I don't know what to tell him.
Timing...
No?
He's so strict.
Has it always been so hard to talk?
It's different from the others.
Ruth, look.
Chise!
What is this thing?
It's so cold.
Elias said to get him before I touch it.
What happens if I touch it first?
You little...
Shoot, it didn't work.
Chise!
Fire doesn't work, either.
A baby?
Elias.
You're done breeding.
Go back to the fields.
Chise.
Elias, what was that?
A snow bug. Unlike wooly
bugs, they eat warmth.
It took her heat.
I'm sorry.
Chise didn't touch it.
It charged at her.
I know.
It must have been hungry, since
summer is their breeding season.
We need to warm her up.
Eli... as...
Are you all right?
I'm quite a bit warmer.
It's actually too hot.
Where's Ruth?
He went to check on the snow bugs.
Thank you.
I'll get out of the way.
Elias?
It was cold when you were gone.
But it's warm with you here.
I wonder why.
Uh...
Well...
Chise...
Timing...
Chise, how was the land of dragons?
Uh, it was... well...
It was fun.
Yeah?
There was a huge snake-like dragon
in the river, dancing elves,
and flowers that bloom with magic.
Yeah? That's good.
Lindel-san told me a lot, too.
So did Nevin.
Nevin?
They both gave me a lot of encouragement.
Elias, did I look tasty?
Oh, I mean...
You were awake?
I thought it was a dream until
Lindel-san told me about it.
But I was just curious.
Elias?
Eli—
Chise, that's a memory that you don't need.
Understood?
No.
I-It's about someone important to me!
I do need it.
I-Impulse is a scary thing.
You're really not scared of me, Chise?
You seem to think I'm really afraid of you.
Am I not scary to a human?
I used to have family.
A mom, a dad, and a younger
brother who was still very little.
Mom and Dad both had the sight.
They were really close to each other.
I was always terrified of the scary
things that swarmed toward us.
But I was always safe with my dad around.
But,
my dad vanished with my brother.
I think my mom was tired.
So...
She left me and passed away.
I loved my family,
but they didn't take me with them.
So, I didn't want a family anymore.
And yet...
Yet, you called me family.
The future he spoke of always involved me.
So I let myself think that
we had a future together.
I wanted to learn about my family,
but you wouldn't tell me anything.
So when Lindel-san told me about your past,
I was happy.
Happy?
It's not you that I'm afraid of.
It's you letting go of me.
Humans lie.
I can't deny that.
But...
I'll believe in you.
You're my apprentice, after all.
Say, Chise,
how does one feel when
they care for another?
How can you tell?
Well...
As I've said before, I can't empathize.
So even if I wanted to say to you what
you said to me, I would be lying.
I...
I was terribly cold when you were gone.
What would you call that, in your words?
Loneliness, maybe?
I see.
I was lonely.
He really is just a child.
A child that ended up in an adult's body.
I'm glad I bought you.
Now I understand something new.
Then I guess I'm your teacher
when it comes to human things.
That sounds good.
I look forward to learning from you,
teacher of human things.
Likewise, teacher of magic.
Speaking of which, I hadn't gotten
a good look at your wand.
Can you show it to me?
Here.
It's the same color as your hair.
Though I was planning on finishing it.
Is someone else supposed
to do the finishing?
We also use our wands to help
us along on our long journey.
The seniors bless the wands of the youth
so that they can continue their journey.
Then if there ever comes a time to
make a second one, I'll ask you.
I won't be in a hurry.
What are you doing this afternoon?
Let's see...
I think I'll study magic.
Okay.
He still won't talk to me about himself.
Was there anything new while I was gone?
Not really. Maybe a few birds that came to play.
Migratory birds or something?
I would have liked to see that.
This is from back then.
Hm?
No, it's nothing.
I should get to studying first.
Coming.
Hey.
Can I have the usual medicine?
Simon-san.
Right away.
It's elderberry syrup.
Wow.
It's good for your throat.
Thanks.
I just remembered, this is the first
thing Ainsworth gave me, too.
Elias did?
I'm technically his supervisor, after all.
I even used to act the part.
But you know, with this thing
being the way it is...
Shut up.
He's kind, isn't he?
Yup, delicious.
It tastes the same.
A guest? This late?
Coming.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Is the master of the house available?
Ashen Eye.
I'd heard a rumor that
a new mage was born.
I came to celebrate.
This man's been alive for millennia.
He comes occasionally to chat.
Be careful. He isn't human.
You have no reason to be fearful of me.
I don't intend to harm you one bit.
You carry the blood of the Far East.
He smells of sand.
But this hair, those eyes...
Yours aren't quite the same as those of
the inhabitants of that island nation.
I believe your lineage may also carry
a tinge of blood from the western continent.
Sorry, I don't know much about my family.
That's fine.
Bonds of blood are insignificant
in living as an individual.
Humans overthink everything.
You ought to drown yourselves
in your true nature.
Now...
A gift for the youngest born of those
who capture and bind my people!
Ashen Eye!
Chise...
Guided by instinct, are we brought to
a rift between humans and non-humans,
one which we can never overcome?
Humans are so foolish.
And selfish, too.