I haven't seen you here in a while.
That will be normal until the plan to
increase AHSMB production is under way.
Now then, how is Black 6 doing?
Display my battle report.
High battle capacity,
but lacks cooperation.
Right.
It's a common trait in most of the
Cosmopolitan Academy students.
They are skilled and fully
realize their elite status.
They refuse to cooperate with others,
tending to look down on them instead.
Right... Individually, they
may be excellent warriors,
but they are unfit for an army.
Didn't you argue that we should put more
emphasis on teamwork, even
if it meant a slight drop
in their specs, rather than
pursue individual aptitude?
In a battle that relies on one hero,
the front will fall apart
if we lose that hero.
But in the upcoming final battle...
This happened sooner than expected.
What did?
The JURIA-System drastically boosts
the pilot's affinity
with his AHSMB unit.
You're aware of this, aren't you?
I am...
There is a reason for that.
The AHSMB and pilot are
created from the same DNA.
AHSMB have minds of their own!
That's ridiculous!
When an AHSMB unit awakens,
in the worst case scenario,
it could potentially eradicate
the pilot's personality.
The units are that dangerous...?
We have obtained none other
than Prometheus' fire.
I wonder if we should
boost its precision.
He busted it up pretty bad yet again.
We'll lend a hand, so
let's hurry and fix it up.
Our AHSMB just needed
some basic maintenance.
Thank you!
With such a strong forward,
we don't have to worry
about our support unit!
True enough!
It'd be pretty bad if the
support unit got banged up.
Oh, you're here?
This is my team. Of course I'm here!
And we've even got them lending a hand.
Honestly, as long as the pilot is
okay, we can fix up the unit...
Huh?
Here!
Thanks...
Don't mention it!
Let's hurry and repair this puppy
so Izuru can get out
there and kick more butt!
Right!
We'll lose respect as mechanics
if Izuru's unit can't keep up with him!
We've gotta work harder!
It is with help from
behind the scenes that allows
the ace to enter combat.
By Degawa
Too many syllables.
I can't believe I needed saving...
What was that back there?
Dang!
Didn't Izuru's moves totally
surpass his unit's specs?
His reaction speed went
0.73 over the limit!
It's like he moved
before he could think.
What a terrifying thought...
Isn't that incredible?
I wonder what my unit'd look like?
If I pulled that off, would
the girls be all over me?
Izuru!
Kei...
Kei's been worried sick this whole time!
Really? Sorry to have made you worry.
For you to be so concerned,
does that mean you have the hots for me?
He's like a beast... Too cool!
Who, me?
That's not true.
What the heck?!
I'm concerned about two things.
They aren't fatal, are they?
His Harmonic Level is
still elevated and he is
suffering from horrible fatigue.
His Harmonic Level...?
Right. It looks like that's
causing his fatigue.
When an AHSMB unit awakens,
in the worst case scenario,
it could potentially eradicate
the pilot's personality.
Could you give him a
thorough examination?
Is that an order?
It is!
All right.
By the way, have you heard about Amane?
How she got promoted for her
accomplishments in the Battle of Ceres?
Reika said we're going to celebrate.
Is that a must?
Consider the situation!
We'd go nuts if we didn't drink.
Vesta Base.
With the frontlines
constantly pullin' back,
this has become the battlefield.
But it was supposed to
be our rear mining base.
Hey! At least the bunnies have
made our job a bit easier.
And we'll work kinda hard.
I'm counting on you!
Lt. Commander Amane, reporting for duty!
Congratulations on your
promotion to Commander.
But I just became a
Lieutenant Commander...
Additional orders just came in.
As of now, you're a Commander.
Why did I get promoted so quickly?
It shows how short we are
on competent officers.
I know you have just arrived,
but please prepare to depart.
Is it the enemy?
That's right.
The spy satellites around
our frontline bases
have been destroyed.
It's a clear sign that they're invading.
Understood.
Where is the detailed report?
I have already sent it to
your vessel's database.
None of the satellites
sensed anything until just
before they were destroyed.
Indeed.
Lacking intel on the enemy forces,
we cannot afford to mobilize
the base's main force.
I'm counting on you.
Sir! I will set out immediately!
Are you all right?
Yeah!
Drawing manga like always?
Care to take a look?
It's good...
Izuru is acting weird!
Is that really anything new?
His manga was good!
That IS weird!
Yo! Hangin' in there?
I'm fine!
Aren't ya acting a bit different?
Who, me?
I'm still me!
True enough...
Then I guess everything's cool.
What? Leaving already?
Gotta train! I can't let ya show me up.
You've got my back!
I checked on him.
He really was weird.
So are you.
Pickled Squid Guts
He was strangely cool...
No, no, no! There's just no way!
What's wrong?
Well, uh, ummm...
I have some free time.
Maybe I could offer a word of advice.
There was this guy I never
really noticed before,
but now he seems so cool...
What do you think?
Well, could it be the
Suspension Bridge Effect?
That's it! That!
It's a big theory that some
psychologists proposed a long time ago!
They conducted experiments
to see if someone
who was physically excited would
realize that he was in love!
Y-you sure know a lot about it.
I actually study stuff
related to romance.
They said that you notice
your subconscious feelings
for the person after
something special happens.
No, no, no! This can't possibly be love!
Is there a problem...
Kitty?
This is love!
Yo! What's up?
I came to bring this.
How'd you know that I was out of paper?
Kei told me.
Yeah? It isn't easy being popular!
How is it? Any good?
Yeah, it's goo-
By the way, are you okay?
Of course I'm just fine!
In fact, I almost feel too good.
You get knocked down and
pop right back up, huh?
Well, I am a hero.
A hero? I suppose so.
I'm counting on you, Hero!
I'm fighting for you.
No doubt about it! He's weird.
Isn't he?
You're acting weird, too.
They didn't respond until
after it had been destroyed!
Either they truly are understaffed
or their staff is incompetent.
I'm getting something on my sensor!
Enemy attack!
Commence battle!
Roger!
It's good...
A pine?
Potted plants are inauspicious
in a hospital room!
Hey, Kei! You came to see me?
I brought get-well treats,
but you might not like them.
If you made them for me,
anything is awesome.
Izuru, hang in there! Don't die!
May I help you?
Hello? Can you hear me?
He's unconscious! Airway, clear!
He isn't breathing! I
need the respirator!
Beginning cardiac massage!
Chest compression! It's ineffective!
Preparing the AED!
Paddle electrodes, ready!
Analyzing the cardiogram!
This is going to emit
a shock, so get back!
Huh? What happened?
He's alive!
Kei, did something happen?
You had me worried.
His Harmonic Level is back to normal?
We're up against a company that is
breaking formation as it draws in.
Make sure to keep your formation
so individual fighters
don't break through.
Roger!
Tch! These guys are kinda tough!
They're faster than usual!
Patrick, don't leave my side!
Damn it!
I'm surrounded!
Their movements seem random,
but there is a pattern!
There is an enemy company
equipped with optical stealth!
They're hiding behind the other
company while in stealth mode!
Shoot around the ships that stand out!
Roger!
It worked! Bull's eye!
Same here!
This is Doberman!
Enemy reinforcements are
approaching Classified Point 004.
Requesting immediate rescue!
I repeat!
Doberman has sent a request
for emergency rescue!
You are authorized to sortie.
Emergency take off!
Roger!
Engines will transfer from idling
to full drive in 30 seconds.
I've finished inputting
Navigational Patterns A to N.
Take the fastest route!
Roger!
Such is the situation.
The leader this time
will be Toshikazu Asagi.
Izuru Hitachi will remain on standby.
I can fight!
Red 5 is still undergoing repairs.
Ange Kuroki will be the forward.
Everything else will
be the same as usual.
Roger!
We're too outnumbered...
We can't even retreat.
Until reinforcements arrive, preserving
our forces takes precedence!
At least tell us, "Take them all down!"
Overconfidence can be dangerous,
but we should be fine.
This is still within reason!
I'll treat you to dinner
when you come back.
Lucky!
That's a death flag, so don't say that!
If I went out, those enemies would be...
Enemy company sighted!
The target has split into five
groups and is headed for us!
Their relative speed-
They're here!
What?!
Stealth mode!
My sensors can't read them.
Damn it!
Tamaki, fly at full speed and
break the enemy's formation.
Suruga, offer fire support!
Kei, confirm the enemies' locations!
Ange, widen the hole
Tamaki's about to make!
Roger!
Eat this!
They dodged around it?!
That won't work.
Good goin'!
Nice job, Black 6!
Naturally.
I'm doing a good job, too!
I've spotted several enemy fighters!
We're completely surrounded.
You may handle the rest.
Roger!
Damn! You lowly ground beetles!
How dare you?!
Calm down, Ange!
Don't go after them.
Who gave you permission
to call me by my name?!
That's too dangerous! Pull back.
I don't feel alive after
all of this hiding!
What happened?
Our radar and all of our sensors
are functioning properly.
The base is functioning properly.
That must have been a lag from
when we changed power sources.
I see...
Is this it?
Commence verifying
translation and analysis.
It isn't here. I must go deeper in.
A firewall?
MJP?
Ange, where are you?
She's completely surrounded!
Damn it! What should I do?
Pleguzesia...
As I had suspected.
Don't do it, Ange! Don't follow them!
What should I do...?
Reinforcements!
Doesn't that lamata look tasty?
Let me have him!
Please, help yourself.
What a hearty feast!
My fighters are to retreat!
The enemies are swapping out!
This is our chance!
Suruga, fire at the
incoming enemy company!
You can count on me!
Tamaki, fire!
Roger!
Damn nobodies, gettin'
full of yerselves!
There are several enemy
fighters around Black 6.
Black 6's armor integrity
is down by 30%.
Rate of energy consumption is at 22/s.
The unit's temperature
is currently rising!
This looks bad.
Purple 2, new enemies have
appeared at Point: Tango!
Blue 1, prioritize rescuing Black 6.
There are too many enemy fighters.
I can't get near him!
It's like I could keep shooting
and shooting forever!
A second group of enemy fighters
are approaching from behind!
If only I could send out Red 5...!
We only have the core up and working!
I'll go in just the core!
I'm heading out!
I thought so!
It's ready to go.
We figured this might happen.
It's ready for action!
Red 5's core, standby: OK!
Routes, all green.
Take off, ready.
Blast off!
The only thing you stinkbugs have
goin' for you are yer numbers!
Move it, pests!
I'm overheating?! Not now!
Just 'cause I can't move...!
Do whatever it takes to clear a path.
Damn it! If only we could
squeeze in one more attack.
Izuru?
Guys!
He came in his core?!
Now!
You're in the way!
Finish off that small fry first!
You can't have him!
It changed forms!
My lamata...!
Why can't I hit you?!
Of all the little-!
There!
What?!
And once more!
He's amazing...
R-retreat!
The enemy company is pulling back.
They're running away...
Ange, did you get hurt?
No...
I'm glad you're okay!
He willingly flew into
the hunting grounds?
Do the Earthlings act under a different
set of principles from ours?
Congratulations on
becoming a Lt. Commander!
Actually, I just got
promoted to Captain...
What?!
What's this? You jumped two ranks?
Amane, did you die in combat?
I'm not dead!
Wait!
You woke up a Lt. Commander and
you're a Captain by evening?
The GDF must be pretty
darn understaffed.
Well, I did go from the General
Staff Office to the frontlines.
It will allow me to fight closer
to where the actual combat is.
We'll be working together
more often now.
Sure will!
Why the long face?
We hardly ever get to
celebrate, so let's drink up!
Yep! Drink, drink!
External access?
I have finally found our target.
This is our target.
They refer to this location as the
Gurantseere Cosmopolitan Academy.
"Your Hero"