Oh!
Cafe
Christmas, huh?
It pains me to celebrate the
birth of that guy's son,
Realty
but it does sound like a fun event.
Oh, Tohru-chan!
Hello.
Huh? Are you hurt?
I am. I was practicing for the nearby
old folk home's Christmas Eve show,
Roast Chicken
but I hurt my leg badly.
Oh!
How frail.
Right!
Could you put on a show
in my stead, Tohru-chan?
Huh?
Taxes Included in Prices
I feel bad since the folks in the
home were looking forward to it.
You want us to?
Is that all right?
Of course!
You're the pride of our shopping district.
All right!
Leave it to me.
So that's how things turned out.
Are you sure?
Of course!
I'd like to help out too,
but right now I've got work...
Just leave it to me
and focus on your work, Miss Kobayashi.
If you say so.
Now's the time to call for help
from my reliable friends.
Everyone, let's do our best!
Yeah!
Y-Yeah...
Hey, wait!
What is it?
I was told I could eat my fill
of candy if I came here.
I even made time in my schedule
during this busy time of the year!
I've heard from Miss Kobayashi, Elma,
that you're still useless at work.
And that they announced you wouldn't
be useful in this busy period.
B-But I can touch type now!
And I can't afford to
interfere with this world...
You're already interfering plenty.
Umm, where's Kanna-san's mom?
Unlike Elma, Miss Kobayashi's busy.
So let's do this on our own.
You heard her.
Boring.
I heard something important was going on,
but we're just putting on a show for humans?
Well, why not?
Let's watch over her.
Hmph.
Show Ideas
So?
What are we doing for this show?
It needs to be something
the elderly will enjoy.
Does anyone have any ideas?
How about an eating contest?
You just want to eat.
A race.
They might die.
We could play a VR FPS, FFA.
I'm sorry, could you speak Japanese?
All of these ideas require the
audience to participate, don't they?
You haven't proposed anything yourself!
Do either of you have any ideas?
I'm okay with anything.
Then how about a play?
A play?
You mean that thing were
humans act on a stone stage?
Stone stage?
A play sounds great!
Let's do that.
But what play would we even put on?
Since it's Christmas,
why not The Little Match Girl?
What's that story about?
On a cold, cold winter night,
a poor little girl is selling matchsticks.
None of the people passing
by will buy any from her.
So in order to warm her chilled body,
she lights one of the matches.
Then, in the flame, she sees a warm
stove and lots of delicious food.
She lights match after match, and eventually
her beloved dead grandmother appears.
So the little girl continues
lighting her matches
to keep her grandmother from disappearing,
and the grandmother gently
hugs the little girl.
Then the little girl ascends to heaven,
embraced in her grandmother's warmth.
It's a bit of a sad story.
It's famous.
I see.
So what happens to the little girl
after she ascends to heaven?
You idiot. That means she died.
Oh. So she strangled her own granddaughter.
Die!
That's not it either!
Saikawa, you know so much. I'm amazed.
Well, yeah.
Then let's go ahead with
The Little Match Girl.
Yeah!
Will we be all right?
I'm the director, Fafnir.
Since I'll be directing,
I won't allow half-baked acting.
I'm the absolute authority here.
I won't accept objections.
To be blunt, you're only director by
elimination, because you can't act.
It was a good compromise.
First we need to decide on our lead actor.
Each of you try acting out
The Little Match Girl.
Number One, Tohru!
Pleasure to meet you.
Just get started.
Don't disappoint me.
Matches! Need any matches?
Boring.
Really?
Are you able to see them?
The heartless humans
passing before your eyes?
Feel it.
Then your lines will come to you naturally.
Feel it...?
You foolish, inferior humans!
How dare you ignore me?!
You'll pay for that crime with your death!
Fail. Next.
Number Two, Elma. Nice to meet you.
Matches? Do you need any matches?
Nope.
Please! At least hear me out!
I can't go back to the office
until I've sold them all!
What are you doing?
The salesmen that come to our
company are always like that.
Hard life. Next.
N-Number Three,
Saikawa Riko. Nice to meet you.
U-Umm...
I-I-I'm sorry!
None of you are any good.
We don't really understand your
directing policy to begin with.
Me, me!
What is it?
Let me be the director.
Shouta can be the lead.
Huh?!
What are you saying?
Shouta's a boy.
Well, leave that to me.
Shouta, come here.
He looks just like a girl.
Cute.
He passes.
Well, he's not as cute as Kanna-san.
Wha...
Wha?
What are you all planning
to achieve by embarrassing me?!
Shouta?!
Well, that was to be expected.
Cheer up.
What should we do?
I'll be the director.
I'll be better than those two at least.
Right.
Also, what to do about our lead.
Matches.
Buy some matches.
Yeah, this is it.
I'm home.
Matches.
Do you need any matches?
What's going on here?
We decided to perform The Little
Match Girl for the show.
Kanna was chosen to be our lead.
Oh, I see.
That's incredible, Kanna-chan.
Yeah, I'll work hard.
I'll be sure to come watch.
Think you can handle it?
Of course!
We'll get through it easily.
Okay.
Do you need any matches?
She's most dangerous
when she gets like this.
Well, I'm going to go take a bath.
Matches... Matches...
Sure!
Yes, yes.
Hello, this is the Kobayashi residence.
It's me. I thought about
the script some on my own.
So you hadn't given up, Mr. Fafnir?
What did you come up with then?
Matches.
If we stick to the original play,
it won't match the current era.
So I decided to make the
little girl into a magical girl—
Well, time to prepare
Miss Kobayashi's dinner.
Do you need any matches?
Lady Tohru. Is there a
chimney in this house?
Chimney?
No, there isn't.
Saikawa said Santa visits
by coming down chimneys.
Oh, you mean that old man
who's covered in blood?
Hey!
Will Santa be able to come
if we don't have a chimney?
Hmm, all right.
What's this?
Episode 10
Troupe Dragon, On Stage! (They Had A Troupe Name, Huh)
What are you doing?!
No, no!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Hey, you, where are you going?
Tohru! Why would a passerby use
Miss Kobayashi as reason to refuse her?!
Why would I be in a hurry
if not for Miss Kobayashi?
I don't know!
Lady Lucoa! The grandmother wouldn't
try to warm the girl up naked.
But it's warmer this way.
Sir Fafnir, you're out of the question!
A father would never call his
daughter a "mere human"!
Hmph.
Why can't you all stick to the script?
Speaking of, this story
doesn't have enough depth.
Are you sure we won't bore
the elderly with this?
Now that you mention it, that's true...
Then why don't we try changing it up?
What are you suggesting we do?
Well...
Let's make the story more fun.
I agree!
Why don't we try mixing in other
myths too, like the kasajizou?
Have it selling hats next to the girl.
What a mean man.
Why not?
The main character should be a magical girl.
Thank you very much!
She can obtain the power to burn
this corrupt world to ash.
Now there's nothing from the original left.
Oh, 47 Ronin is popular
with the elderly, too.
The one about humans and their quest for
revenge, right? Sounds interesting.
Are there any dragons?
We might as well have some
while we're at it, right?
Hey, Grandma!
Don't make it weirdly sexy.
Narrator, stop grinning.
Kanna.
It sounds like Santa won't be
coming for a while longer.
Does Santa know where we are?
Will he really come?
Who knows?
Ah, I'm beat.
Chimney Here
Good
Girl
This is the home of the
good girl,
Kobayashi Kanna
What's this?!
Merry Christmas!
Take home some cake!
Did we make it in time?
Looks like it.
It's about to start.
Now then, we'll be starting the performance
of The Little Match Girl brought to you
by the Oborozuka Shopping District.
Please enjoy the show.
It was an awfully cold night.
The sun had set upon the street corner,
where a single young girl was selling matches.
Matches. Do you need any matches?
Yet no one would buy her matches.
I can't sell any.
Umm...
Y-Young girl, do you need any hats?
Huh?
Before her appeared an old man selling hats.
My old wife made these.
They're very strong hats.
W-Would you like one?
I don't have any money.
Are you all right?
I'm cold.
That must be hard.
Oh. Then burn one of
these to warm yourself.
They're burning it?!
Even though his wife made it?!
And they're actually setting it on fire!
Then something incredible happened.
From the smoke there
appeared a suspicious man.
Pathetic human.
Who are you? What do you want?
You've been chosen
to become a magical girl with a duty to bear.
What's this turn of events?
Take it. The power to correct
this corrupt world.
Yeah, okay!
That was quick!
Very good. In that case...
W-Wait!
Please make me a magical girl, too!
Oh? Why do you wish to be a magical girl?
To use a magical girl's power
to commit vicious deeds
and get money to feed my sick wife!
He doesn't think to heal her with magic?
You would voice your desires without shame?
Very well.
You are truly human.
This is embarrassing.
Still, it's unfortunate.
I only have one staff that will
allow you to use your powers.
You two will have to fight,
and the survivor shall receive it.
Begin!
Stop fighting!
I'm a magic fairy.
Don't let yourself be fooled
by that suspicious man's offer.
I won't allow you to toy
with the hearts of others.
Leave this to me and go!
I can't just leave you here.
Yeah, yeah!
Thank you.
My time with both of you was very enjoyable.
It was only a few seconds.
No way...
What do we do now?
A magical girl's role is to cleanse
corruption from this world.
Leave it to me.
Where are the rotten people?
How incredible.
The spell cast by the young girl struck
a devastating blow to a nearby mansion.
Let's go look there.
One, two, one, two, one, two...
Are you the ones who set fire to this place?
Wh-Who would do such a thing?
You did.
I'm sorry. I'm didn't mean ill by it.
No, you've been a big help.
I'm Oishi Kuranosuke.
Thanks to this fire I can
sneak into the Kira mansion.
You have my gratitude.
What are you doing?
I've come to avenge my lord and claim
the head of Kira Kouzuke no suke!
Now it's the 47 Ronin?
Avenging your lord? How funny!
So you show yourself, Kira!
If you'd forfeit your life, then come at me!
Hey, hey, seriously?!
That's the source of the corruption.
The enemy of magical girls!
No one can beat me in this form.
I'll turn you to dust!
They're overdoing it!
If they do that, then...!
Amazing.
Is this that CGI thing?
Who you calling a geezer?
I said CGI.
Oh well.
Then I'll have to get serious, too!
What?!
That was incredible.
Kobayashi!
How was our play?
Well...
It was good. You worked
hard all on your own.
Nice work.
Well, care to go out for an after party now?
Let's!
I just received a cake in appreciation, too.
Elma, you're just hungry.
Th-That's not true!
Cheers!
Huh? Where's everyone else?
They just left to head home.
Apparently they're each having
their own parties at home.
And Kanna-chan?
She escorted Ms. Saikawa home.
Hmm.
Would you like a bath?
Or would you like to go to bed as is today?
Well, since it is Christmas...
What a beautiful sight!
You're not cold?
I'm fine.
This is unusual.
You asking to see the view at night.
Is it?
Oh, right.
Miss Kobayashi.
Here.
What? A Christmas present?
Yes!
I got you some medicine that
works well for lower back pain.
Seriously?
That's a big help.
It's a valuable item in the other world.
You grind it down and
apply it to your lower back.
It works perfectly!
Yeah, sure...
Hey, I was worried all day today.
What's this all of a sudden?
To be honest, I was full of
anxiety as I watched your play,
worrying when I should
jump in to stop you.
But everyone enjoyed it.
You really did a nice job.
Thanks!
Oh.
It's a White Christmas.
Here! A Christmas present from me, too.
Huh?
What is it?
Merry Christmas, Tohru.
Miss Kobayashi!
Tohru, settle down! I'll fall!
But!
I can't get close!
Big End of
Year Sale
Oborozuka
Shopping
District
Next Episode
Mr. Fafnir, that was quite the
excellent performance!
Hmph.
Pathetic human.
Stop it.
Oh? Why do you wish to be a magical girl?
Don't mimic me.
Very well.
Episode 11
Year End, New Year! (No Comiket Bit This Time)
You are truly human.
I'll kill you!