Shuichi
Hey, are we there yet?
Almost.
You keep saying that.
This time it's true.
You keep saying that, too.
This place...
Do you remember?
Noel!
What now?
Dad.
This place...
Still asleep, are we?
I don't blame you.
You were up late
packing for the move.
Move?
No, that's not it!
I was with Noel at the
observatory until just now.
Noel?
You know her, too, don't you?
You helped her.
I don't know what to say.
Look, you can see it now.
No way.
Saucerless City
Where's the saucer?
What's gotten into you?
Are you tired from the
long trip from Tokyo?
Is it summer break?
Of course it is.
It can't be.
It was snowing.
Oh, you mean in your dream.
You should probably get
some rest once we get home.
How did this happen?
Stop!
Where're you going?
I'll come home later.
Later?
Hey, do you remember where we live?
Of course I do!
Craft Palace
Kiriyako Scenery
Kiriyako Hot Springs
Hot Springs Rice Cakes
Key Holders                                                                    Mugs
Welcome.
Are you sightseeing?
Koharu!
Um, have we met before?
Don't you remember?
Of course you do.
We were just at the
observatory until just now.
The observatory?
Are you Nonoka?
You do remember me!
Is it really you?
It's been so long.
It's been since we were kids.
Since we were kids?
You left the city
without saying a word.
We were all so worried.
Are you talking about
seven years ago?
It's already been that long, huh?
No.
Don't you remember?
It was winter until just now.
But Noel disappeared,
and the saucer disappeared...
Saucer?
What saucer?
Sorry, I don't know what
you're talking about,
but I'm glad to see you again.
What about Noel?
Noel?
Someone from abroad?
Noel.
Hey, what's up?
Yuzuki!
Nonoka? That Nonoka?
Yeah.
How nostalgic.
We all used to go to
the observatory to play.
Do you remember, Souta?
What we did in the end.
We called a saucer.
We held hands in a circle,
and we made wishes.
Even though there's no
way a saucer would come.
I believed it.
Nothing happened, though.
I know, but...
Haven't you ever thought about it?
What if a saucer really
showed up that day?
I can't even imagine.
Hey, how did you know me?
So you don't remember.
Huh?
Are you Nonoka?
Yeah. Do you remember?
Of course I do.
We played at the observatory
when we were kids.
Huh?
What's wrong?
What's in there?
Want to see?
Tada.
What do you think?
Pretty well-built, right?
Oh, yeah. Let's go launch it at the lake.
We've launched it together once.
When we were kids,
we gathered at the observatory,
and called the saucer.
Yeah, I remember that.
A saucer actually showed up.
What are you talking about?
A saucer came to the city?
I don't remember you
making jokes like that.
What's wrong, Nonoka?
Don't you remember even just a little
about the saucer? About Noel?
Noel?
Yeah.
Please, remember.
What can I say?
It's important, right?
I'll ask Souta, too.
Oh, yeah.
Let's exchange contact info.
Oh, sure.
Right.
Thanks, Yuzuki. I'm leaving now.
Huh? Where are you going?
To see Shione!
Shione is...
Please.
Shione—
Who is it?
Um, is there a Togawa Shione here?
Sorry, there's no one by
that name living here.
I-I see.
Sorry about that.
Why?
Shione, where are you?
Why doesn't anyone
know about the saucer?
Yuuko. Where were you?
Noel.
This can't be right.
I remember Noel, though.
Nonoka.
Dad.
Don't worry me so much.
Sorry.
I moved all our boxes inside.
We'll have a lot of cleaning
up to do tomorrow.
Okay.
Is the saucer gone?
Or did it never come to begin with?
I can't just let this be.
Back there, Noel was
crying.
Two eggs, yolks still runny.
Yeah.
Our next story.
A new hotspot has shown
up in Hokubi City.
I'm leaving.
Oh, the opening ceremony.
Morning.
Maeyama
Observatory
I hope we're in the same class.
Yeah.
I'm sure we will be.
I'm Komiya Nonoka.
Nice to meet you.
Yes.
Komiya-san moved here from
Tokyo because of her father's work.
Everyone, be good to her.
Komiya-san, your seat is in the
far back of the second row.
Oh, good.
I was looking for you.
Too bad we weren't
in the same class.
Oh, yeah. Now that Nonoka's back,
why don't we go hang out somewhere?
Um... I want to talk to you guys.
About the observatory.
Sure, okay.
Do you want me to call
Souta, too, then?
Thanks.
We want to know what
you've been up to, too.
Oh, and Shione.
Shione?
Do you know which class she's in?
Not in this school.
Oh, hello.
Souta, you're free right now, aren't you?
She moved away during
elementary school.
Shione's always wanted to see you.
Sorry, um...
Do you have her contact info?
No.
Yeah.
So we're going to hang out.
Noel?
The five of us did try to call
a saucer when we were kids.
You might not recall now,
but in the city I know,
there was a saucer above the lake
and a girl named Noel.
Are you saying we've forgotten about it?
You've all seen the city
with the saucer, too.
You're an important part of
our time at the observatory,
and you're a precious
friend to us now, too.
So I want to believe you.
But...
I've always thought it'd be
nice if a saucer came down
and granted our wishes, too.
So I want to believe you.
Sorry.
It doesn't matter what.
Something about Noel.
Something about the
time we spent with her.
Her words, her expressions.
Please remember something,
even just a little.
Please!
Otherwise Noel will...
I don't want to be so harsh,
but maybe you're just imagining it.
You're the only one that remembers
this Noel, aren't you?
Well...
Oh, you mean in your dream.
That's not it.
Noel worked really hard
to grant our wishes.
Mine, and yours, too.
You've all seen her...
Sorry, I don't think there's any
point talking about this any more.
Come on, Souta, you don't
have to say it like that.
Souta's right.
Sorry.
Let me be alone for a while.
Nonoka.
Don't worry.
Mom...
Does Noel really exist?!
Keep Out
If I'm the only one
that remembers Noel,
then if I forget Noel,
she'll really disappear.
So
I'm going to record everything
I know about Noel.
Huh?
It should go further.
What am I missing?
Dammit.
Why am I so frustrated?
Shiihara Market
Hey, you've been watching
over this city.
You'd know, right?
Something important
that I might have lost.
Noel.
I miss you.
Noel, I miss you!
Please, come out!
Smile again!
Noel!
Could that even happen?
Could it really all
have been a dream?
Could Noel really not exist?
Could it really be?
Shione.
Long time.
Yeah, seven years, I think.
Do you remember when
we were kids here?
What I remember...
What I remember are that girl's tears
on the night of the meteor shower.
That girl...
Noel didn't like seeing you like that.
Yeah.
From the Starting Sky
Next episode of Celestial Method:
"From the Starting Sky."