The summer vacation I was
looking forward to so much...
Little did I know, our destination
was actually another world!
As for my two childhood friends...
Hero Sink...
Hero Nanami...
Reporting for duty!
Um, what should I do?
Let's just have fun!
Pastillage Joins The Battle!
It appears that both armies'
heroes are going for each other!
Hero Sink is dashing
through the cog area.
I have about 100 days of
experience being a hero.
I can't let that newbie
hero, Nanami, beat me!
That's right, show them your experience!
Indeed!
Nanami, do you think you can
uphold your teacher's honor?
Of course, I mean I am
Sink's older sister!
Hero Nanami is jumping into the
fray with Her Excellency Leon,
but the Biscotti army
moves in to defend!
All right, Sink, I won't hold back!
Ready... go!
The hero battle has begun!
It's on!
Looks like things are
heating up over there.
But still, having the hero battle steal
all of the attention
is a bit unsatisfying.
Leon-sama, may we request a fight?
All right, I shall take
you both on at once!
Would you like a drink?
The items go over here.
I can't believe it!
I know!
They got us!
We need clothes first.
You three! What's with that getup?!
You perv.
Don't look!
Like I would!
Oh, he was good.
My prince.
Oh, Godwin.
How was your fight with the hero?
Oh yeah, that guy's actually
gotten quite strong.
He wasn't lying when he said that
he's been training really hard.
Now that we also have a hero,
things are getting quite interesting.
Quite!
Here in the waterfall area,
Leon-sama and the Biscotti
Combo are fighting!
Yukikaze Ninja Art: Dual Lightning Blossom!
Yuki!
Leon-sama!
Take this!
Too easy!
Lion King: Conflagration Explosive Slash!
That was really close!
I told you: too easy.
Since the Secret Squad's
uniform is made to
maximize mobility,
getting hit is dangerous!
That's quite right...
This is crazy, Sink.
Flonyard-style war is really fun!
Isn't it?
I just knew you'd like it!
Yup! Leon-sama is cute and cool,
and all the Galettians are nice, too!
The Biscottians are all fun and kind...
I'll introduce them all
to you and Becky later.
Okay, but before that,
I'm going to...
I'm gonna...
...win this battle!
Neptune Water Emblem!
Infernal Fire Emblem!
Full power!
Beams! They just shot beams...
Yes, that would be the Emblem Cannon.
It's a finishing move of
the knight class fighters.
That's cold!
I'm just getting started!
Our hero's in trouble!
We have to aid him!
Oh no, Rico-chan's making
a move! Archers, take aim!
Leon-sama herself taught
me this Emblem Cannon...
Both heros' armor have been destroyed,
but like a true hero, the important
parts are still covered!
No worries, showing you this much is okay.
How is that okay?!
It's not underwear,
so it's not embarrassing!
Hero Nanami is not set back!
Still, it looks like the heroes
need to change their equipment.
They are both falling back, for now!
Right, it's still the first half;
we can still make it!
Y-yes...
Farkas, faster!
There's no mistake,
this girl's definitely...
First Half of the Battle - Lunch Break
Fournette Terrace
Jeez, do you know how shocked I was?!
You could have at least explained
some of it beforehand.
Come on, I already said "I'm sorry."
There, there, Becky.
Don't you worry.
All the things you love, like sightseeing
and trying different foods, are also in the plan!
I've also thought of a bunch of things.
You should come to Galette, too.
I'll treat you to a bunch
of tasty fish dishes.
Thank you so much, Leon-sama, Princess!
But you know,
you should also try joining the battle.
Yeah, I wanted you to join, too!
I'm fine, but thanks.
Boo, come on.
Fine. Don't both of you make
the same face at once.
I'm enjoying myself
enough just watching.
Besides...
I want to enjoy my nice conversation
with the princess more.
Me, too!
Let's enjoy our girl talk!
Yes, let's!
Hey! Leo-nee, Millihi-nee!
A bird?
Couvertete? Callaway?
What brings you two here?
I wanted to- Pastillage wants
to join this battle, too!
That's why we've come
to collect that girl!
Yeah, you, Rebecca!
Now that the lunch break is over,
the afternoon activities can begin!
Both armies have ordered their formations
and are perfectly prepared!
Our analysts are joining
the afternoon battle as well!
Leon-sama and Princess Millihi
have taken their command posts
in their respective HQs!
The princess looks so dignified in her battle clothes!
The afternoon's deciding
battle is about to...
Put that war on hold!
It's me, the First Princess of
the Principality of Pastillage,
Couverte Eschenbach Pastillage!
Oh, it's Couverte.
Cou-sama!
Cou-sama, what's the occasion today?
You know exactly what's up, Millihi-nee!
And you, too, Leo-nee!
What? Me, too?
I know war games aren't
that popular in our land,
but it's not fair that only you get
to summon heroes and have fun!
I'd be happy if you wanted to join,
but what should we do about
rules and winning conditions?
About that.
Yes?
My target is her!
I'm going to take our guest from
the other world as a hostage.
I fell in love with her on first sight!
And I'm going to seduce her!
If you want her back,
you'll have to defeat
Pastillage's pride,
the 40 airborne knights...
Hello.
...and 150 Eschenbach High Speed Cavalry
before you can get to me!
For Galette, it doesn't really
matter where Rebecca resides.
Our plan is to simply defeat
both Pastillage and Biscotti,
but I wonder what our hero will decide.
I personally want to
get Rebecca-san back.
Hero Sink, what should we do?
I see, so that was her plan.
It looks like it...
So you heroes have to decide.
I see.
Heroes, what do you say?!
We'll accept your challenge!
This is getting crazy!
Then would the representatives
of the three countries
please signal the beginning of battle?
This battle is going to be a
battle royale between all three countries!
An all out battle for
getting the top score!
The two heroes will rescue Rebecca-san!
The Battle of Fournette Lake,
Afternoon Match, begins now!
So you were able to enter
the fray, Bernard.
I am going to pin Rolan down. Let's go!
The Leader of the Knights, Rolan,
is already heading for the lake area!
General Bernard is also rushing ahead!
I'm counting on you to
delay the heroes, Callaway.
Understood.
Liscia, can you handle that?
Got it, Callaway.
Everybody, load your rifles with Emblem Rounds!
Ready!
Fire!
Pastillage's airborne mage
squad is a real bother...
If they are left unchecked,
our formations will be ruined.
I've spotted both armies' captains.
Initiate focus fire!
Aye!
Rolan!
Yes, Bernard!
Barrier field!
Aw man, it's so hard!
They are unscathed!
That was Iron Defense Rolan's
famous protective Emblem Art!
And!
Heavenly Cannon!
General Bernard's long distance Emblem Cannon!
It's super effective!
No way!
The two captains put up a united front!
Create a path for our armies by cleaving
into the front lines of the mage-knights!
Roger!
On this side, the Biscotti and
Galette knights are working
together from the get-go!
Rico-chan.
Vert-nee, let's go.
But Pastillage's mages aren't sitting idle!
Precision Marksman Squad! Open fire!
Pastillage is the technology leader!
Their magical research is
the best on the continent!
Pastillage's unique crystal magic
shines on the battlefield!
Our fight's on hold,
let's go rescue Becky together!
Of course!
Excuse me, honored heroes.
Rebecca-sama is a valued guest
of my master, Couverte-sama.
Right now, they are having
an important conversation.
Which means that I can't let you pass.
Pastillage's unique Sky Knights
ride on giant birds named Blanchir!
How are the heroes going to
fight against the Sky Knight?!
Emblem Sword Skill: Spinner Fire!
He's fast!
Arc Sign, go!
Wind Slash!
Thanks, Sink!
Nanami, can you use Bright Power Gear?
What? I don't know what you mean.
Then watch and learn.
Materialize the emblem and
gather your Bright Power.
Then try to visualize the shape of it.
Tornader! Go!
There it is!
Hero Sink's Bright Power Gear!
The airboard Tornader!
I think I get the gist of it.
Bright Power... focus...
What is this?
Hero Nanami, too?!
I did it!
She summoned her Bright Power Gear!
Okay!
Galette's the capital of water,
blessed by both ocean and river.
That's why I...
am going to be the surfer hero!
Hero Nanami is flying!
Don't forget about me!
Now, please return Becky to us.
Exactly!
You really are heroes,
but it's not over yet!
Oh, there's something happening in
the central battlefield as well!
Boy, I thought I'd be fighting you.
Come now, fighting together
is quite nice, too.
The "Peerless" and the
"Strongest on the continent!"
The strongest of Biscotti and
Galette formed the ultimate team!
They both seem to enjoy themselves,
so should we just follow them?
Sounds good.
Oh, the leaders of the Imperial Guard and
the Secret Squad are with them, too!
Does this spell certain
doom for Pastillage?!
Just as I expected, our
troops are in a real bind.
Looks like it...
I think we have no choice but
for you to go out there.
B-but you know...
as I said before, I really can't
fight like Sink or Nanami, at all.
Nobody said you have to fight like them.
Listen, Rebecca, when I saw
you for the first time,
my senses tingled.
You have the same eyes as me.
Umm...
You aspire to be like your friends.
"If only I could do that, too,
we could spend more time together."
That's what you feel.
I aspire to be like
Millihi-nee and Leo-nee.
I want to be a wonderful ruler
loved by my subjects, like them.
But, your athletic skills
are on the sad side,
and I'm useless in a fight.
However, in Pastillage,
we have something that allows
even us to do our best!
Our crystal magic, and
Pastillage's Treasure Swords:
Heavenly Spear Culmurth and
Divine Sword Mercurius.
These are the perfect swords
for us mages types.
I'm a mage type?
To be honest, I'm actually still training
to be the next ruler of my land.
Even though I've been
entrusted with the sword,
I still have a lot to learn.
That might not sound encouraging,
but I feel like we can understand
each other better that way.
I want to try a bunch of firsts with you
since I feel like we'll really get along.
I'm honored, but are you
sure you really want me?
Of course!
I fell in love with you!
I want take the skies with you!
Rebecca,
will you accept Pastillage's
Divine Sword Mercurius?
Something's happening on the
...flying terrace.
Everybody, sorry for the wait.
And Heroes from Galette and Biscotti:
too bad, but you're out of time.
Our army's secret weapon has just been born!
Go, Rebecca!
Equip!
I did it!
Behold!
This is Pastillage's
Flying Hero, Rebecca!
Let's go, Rebecca!
Yes! I'll do my best
as Pastillage's Hero!
Hero Rebecca is born!
Wonderful!
I'll do my best!
Three Heroes!
And, Nanami, you need to
put some clothes on!
Don't worry about it.