OSAKA
This is horrible...
That damn Kiryuin, never thinking
about the mess she makes...
I've arrived, too.
Am about to enter HQ.
Welcome back, Mr. Mikisugi!
Is everyone ready?
EPISODE 15
DON'T STOP ME NOW
It's been too long, Missy!
You've become quite
the babe, I see!
And you've become
ever more loathsome.
Though I can't remember
where I met you.
Not since the garden party to celebrate
your grade school graduation.
You don't remember the
Takarada Conglomerate's heir doing
you the honor of appearing in person?
You should feel honored that I have some
vague recollection of your seedy face.
Same as before, you still look down
on everyone like you enjoy it.
But you're sorely mistaken if you think
you're gonna have your way all the time.
What's mistaken is your brain for
thinking you could oppose me.
Purchasing human life
with money?
How were you raised, to be able
to use money in such a vile way?
There's no "clean" or "dirty"
when it comes to money!
Japan is split under two
massive conglomerates:
KANEO TAKARADA SATSUKI KIRYUIN
the Takaradas in the west and
the Kiryuins in the east.
If we don't throw
this money around, who will?!
You seem to have been fixated on the power
of those strange outfits lately,
but let me bottom-line it for you...
Look!
For the right amount, all
these people will fight
and gladly lay down their lives for me!
In any era, it's money
that motivates folks!
The power of the dough!
On that, you're mistaken.
What was that?
Some kind of bluff?
What I struck was their hearts.
Leave us, fools! Or my next
strike will take your lives!
- She's bad news!
- Live to fight another day!
Bye, now!
- We're no match for her!
- Wait for me!
Do you see now, Takarada?
It is not money that rules men.
It is fear.
You think you've beaten me
with that little stunt?
Don't resort to bravado, Takarada.
Your voice is shaking with fear.
Oh, I'm scared!
I'm scared, all right!
I'm not gonna write a check
that my body can't cash.
Not even a pretense of
masculine self-respect?
Just when you couldn't get any lower...
You gotta be kidding.
My value's about to go through the roof!
Say hello to my anti-Honnouji Academy
mechanized weapon, Dotonbori Robo!
ANTI-HONNOUJI ACADEMY MECHANIZED WEAPON
DOTONBORI ROBO
When you're weak, use something
very strong shamelessly!
That's my philosophy
for certain victory!
Pathetic.
How incredibly tacky.
Oh? You can tell that
even without eyes?
Yes. I can sense it by aura alone --
the smell of your overblown arrogance.
I hate holding the check.
What say we go Dutch?
I'm not speaking of money.
I'm speaking of your disposition.
Your opinion...
...don't add up to jack!
Club members! Guard Lady Satsuki!
Archery! Javelin!
Discus! Shot put!
Everyone else!
Jocks ain't worth one red cent!
Good match!
How ya like this, Missy?
Your vaunted Goku Uniforms
don't amount to jack when
the Takarada Conglomerate
decides to go all out!
Go sell 'em all to the
Americamura thrift shops!
They'll take 'em off your
hands for cheap!
One who doesn't know
the fear of clothing mocks it?
What's cheap is your life!
As if! Here we go...
Sen-nari Gourd Missile Shower!
What do you think of my
golden gourd bombardment
I got plenty more
where that came from!
Die! Die! Die!
Die, bitches!
Nobody could've survived that...
As long as Ira Gamagoori draws breath,
I will not allow so much as
a scratch on Lady Satsuki!
You should stop pressing
your luck, Naniwa monkey.
I'll be recording the data from these
new Three-Star Goku Uniforms.
Apologies for the delay, Lady Satsuki.
The Kobe and Kyoto School Raid
Brigades have now arrived.
Good work.
Catch, Sanageyama!
Here's your new Goku Uniform!
Just what I've been waiting for!
What's with the cheapo
hero show crap?
Spare me the commentary!
You face Uzu Sanageyama of
the Honnouji Academy Elite Four!
Three-Star Goku Uniform:
Blade Regalia MKIII!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
BLADE REGALIA MKIII
Oh, brother...
He gets so enthusiastic.
Subjugating Osaka is his mission.
It's only natural that he throw himself into it.
The northern Kanto monkey
versus the Osakan monkey.
It's a monkey battle royale.
Wow, that's awfully clever
coming from you, doggie.
I'm merely using
the Jakuzure glossaries.
After all, the poison of the snake's
flickering tongue is powerful stuff.
Thanks.
Men! Dou! Kote!
Sen-nari Gourd Missile Shower!
Men! Dou! Kote! Men! Dou! Kote!
Men! Dou! Kote!
What the hell?!
Do you think I'll allow you to
continue your pathetic gourd shower?!
You're finished!
Men!
W-What the hell is this?!
That there is crab paste slime!
Once you get it on you,
it never comes off!
You ain't moving any more!
Now you're finished!
Eat-'til-you-drop Fire!
You're baked crab paste!
Flame off!
Now, let's see if you're golden
brown and delicious...
Oh?
He's not here!
Did you think your crab paste
could coat me?!
What the—!
Don't underestimate me!
Tsuki! Tsuki!
Tsuki! Tsuki! Tsuki!
Out!
No, not there!
Anywhere but there!
Not there, not there,
not there!
- Tsuki!
- Oh yes!
I'm dead, I'm dead,
I'm so dead...
You don't value anything
but your life, do you?
Looking down on me again, huh?
You must be feeling pretty good right now.
But this isn't over. Osaka's all
about tenacity and conviction.
That is exactly my intent.
My target here is not you.
What'd you say?
Do you think that I would commit a force
of this size to fight mere students?
Wait... You aren't serious!
Where did you get the power
to stand against Goku Uniforms?
Looks like you're having fun throwing
your weight around, Satsuki Kiryuin.
Wrecking an entire town...
Don't you think that's a bit much?
You've come all this way
merely to tell me that?
If so, your trip
was for nothing.
The fate of any who
defy me is sealed.
I'm going to change
that fate.
You're going to give
Senketsu back.
Ah, so this is what
you are after.
Sanageyama.
Dispose of that fool.
At once!
Mako, fall back
to someplace safe.
Kay!
Mankanshoku?
None of you interfere.
Yes, ma'am!
Can you take it back,
Ryuko Matoi?
Yep.
Helluva defense, as usual.
Spirit is the one and only skill
you have mastered.
Very well, then.
The lioness will use all her strength,
even when hunting a rabbit!
Life Fiber Override, Kamui Junketsu!
KAMUI JUNKETSU
I won't hold back, Matoi.
Why isn't the transfer
student transforming?
Part of her Kamui is in the
possession of Lady Satsuki.
When a Kamui
completely awakens,
powerful bio-energy flows
through its Life Fibers.
If part is missing, the flow is stopped.
That means she can't transform.
It would appear that you cannot
synchronize without this glove.
You transformed knowing that, huh?
That's Satsuki Kiryuin for you!
Always ruthless!
You challenged me, knowing you were
at a disadvantage.
Don't whine.
Nobody's whining!
But you are shortsighted
and reckless!
Him! The ripped mohawk dude!
Matoi, run!
Listen, your objective is the rescue
of Kaneo Takarada and Ryuko Matoi!
When the mission is complete,
withdraw immediately!
Avoid any unnecessary combat!
Launch all units!
Open #4 gate!
That said, our good Miss Satsuki probably
isn't gonna politely let us do that!
Why the change of heart,
Mohawk Man?
I have no choice.
Mikisugi asked me to back you up.
First you attack me, then you protect me?
You must keep busy.
We have but one objective:
To resist subjugation by the
Life Fibers that Satsuki uses.
That is the goal
of Nudist Beach!
That name was for real?!
What the hell
are you wearing?!
I wish I could have kept playing
the lazy teacher forever,
but it looks like that's
no longer possible.
So, we've smoked you out,
you naked fools.
The true objective of the
Tri-City Schools Raid Trip
was to smoke out the rebel force lurking in
the shadows behind the Kansai academies.
That is why Lady Satsuki allowed your
activities to continue, Aikuro Mikisugi!
Goodness, you saw through me?
How impressive!
That's a plan by Lady Satsuki for you.
It worked exactly as planned.
Well, I was the one
who put it together...
We were worried that you wouldn't
show up and
our new Goku Uniforms wouldn't get any use.
Do you think a group with a foolish name like
Nudist Beach can thwart our grand design?
Fade like the dew before
my Blade Regalia MKIII!
Three-Star Goku Uniform!
Shackle Regalia MKII!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
SHACKLE REGALIA MKII
Symphony Regalia MKII!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
SYMPHONY REGALIA MKII
Probe Regalia MKII.
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
PROBE REGALIA MKII
Blade Regalia MKIII!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
BLADE REGALIA MKIII
Honnouji Academy
Elite Four Regalia MKII!
HONNOUJI ACADEMY ELITE FOUR REGALIA MKII
FOUR GENERALS GRAND GARNISH
Four Generals Grand Garnish!
Ryuko!
Mako! I told you to
go hide someplace safe!
Yeah, so I came here.
Right next to you
is the safest place!
Oh, right.
Senketsu, let's transform.
Impossible.
I admit that I can restore my form
with what you have collected.
But without that glove,
the bio-energy cannot flow.
Use my skin to compensate
for what's missing.
No way!
Human skin will not withstand the energy
that flows through Life
Fibers for even a minute!
A minute is more than enough.
Ryuko?
You want to be worn by me, right?
So don't worry about me.
I'm not scared anymore, either.
If you're my friend,
believe in me like Mako does.
Friend...
Yeah.
Very well.
Let's do it, Ryuko.
Right on!
Life Fiber Synchronize: Kamui Senketsu!
KAMUI SENKETSU
Son of a...
What?
Satsuki Kiryuin!
But you're all flash
and no substance!
Are you that eager to die, Matoi?
Nope, this is how
I'll survive!
What?!
Kamui Senketsu!
Now I have it all back.
Snatching life from
the jaws of death, eh?
Nevertheless, you still
cannot best me!
We'll see about that!
Your power has increased?
That's what I'm saying'.
It has! Don't underestimate
Ryuko Matoi who's fixated
by seeing what she wants almost in reach!
That fool!
Fixated on what you want?
Pathetic!
Have you forgotten that you went on
a rampage when you gave in to rage?
Have you forgotten the rage in your heart
that wants revenge for your father?!
I haven't forgotten!
But I'm done wallowing in it.
I'll never make another
mistake like that again!
I'll live for the desire
of what's almost in reach
regardless of the rage that's almost in reach!
The desire to take back my friend!
To protect the friends that are precious to me!
That is why you simply go with the flow
and aim so low in your ambition!
What about your "lofty" ambitions, then?
Look at this scorched wasteland.
Is this your ambition?
A necessary sacrifice?
If this is the way you use
the power of Life Fibers,
Senketsu and I will stop you!
You've had your way
long enough!
If that's the case, prove it
to me with deeds, not words!
Ryuko!
Senketsu Senjin!
What?!
Senketsu Shippu!
Why, you!
Lady Satsuki!
Lady Satsuki, climb onto me!
Right!
Just you watch, I'll catch up
to her in no time!
Perhaps, but like this,
you cannot get a higher
eye level than mine. Can you, Nonon?
Don't be silly.
Ryuko Matoi!
Why you...
Damn it...
Lady Satsuki!
How impertinent!
What?!
Let's go, Jakuzure.
Let's finish this.
Leave it to me.
Matoi!
Now, now. I want to collect combat
data on my Probe Regalia MKII.
Ryuko!
You should be worrying
about yourself, Aikuro Mikisugi.
Ryuko, snap out of it!
Ryuko!
Ryuko, catch!
Stop it, Mankanshoku.
Take your hands off
that scissor.
Otherwise, I'll show you no mercy.
Even if it's you.
Are you all right, Ryuko?
Yeah, somehow.
Do you wish to end this
here in Osaka?
Ryuko, bet on me.
What?
If we are friends, believe in me.
All right. You got it.
Using your Kamui as a blade?
Still, it is a wasted effort.
Junketsu cannot be cut by that!
Oh, I know that!
Impossible!
Nice job, Senketsu.
All the blood I had sucked up
was collected in the blade.
It was an all or nothing gamble,
but it worked.
You heard him. This blade
can cut your Junketsu, right?
Yes, but my Junketsu
can pierce your Kamui.
Mutually assured destruction... huh?
Withdraw your troops, Kiryuin.
Do that, and I'll lower the sword.
Are you sure?
You would be failing
to avenge your father.
I can't sacrifice the lives
of others to do it.
Trade my life for theirs, eh?
I'm insulted at how low
a price you put on me.
Lady Satsuki, please stand down!
Yours is a noble goal!
You mustn't fall here
out of mere stubbornness!
See? He agrees with me.
All students, stand down
from combat!
We are returning
to Honnouji Academy!
Ryuko, you dropped this!
Thanks.
Kiryuin, maybe it's true that you've
mastered that Junketsu of yours.
But you're alone.
And you aren't?
No. Senketsu and I
are two in one.
Implying that you've formed a symbiotic
relationship with the Life Fibers?
That is a fairy tale.
Come again?
I shall leave Bakuzan in your care.
To mark today's battle.
Kiryuin.
What?
The Satsuki Kiryuin I know
isn't so petty a woman
that she'd change an order she'd given
just because she got her sword back.
What the—?
Did you forget about me?
They call us the Elite Four
because there's four of us!
Lady Satsuki, I've destroyed the
Nudist Beach base as per your orders.
Well done.
With that, we have crushed the
group of fools that opposed us.
The objective of the Tri-City Schools
Raid Trip has been accomplished.
There is no need whatsoever
to rescind my order to return home.
I compliment you on your
valiant efforts, Ryuko Matoi.
But your attack was no
more than a sneak attack.
It will not work next time!
This cost us most of
Nudist Beach's' forces.
Still, we should be grateful
that we're alive.
You fought Satsuki Kiryuin to a draw.
That was impressive, Ryuko.
Come with me.
I gave you my word.
It's time to tell you everything.
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
After her battle with Satsuki, Ryuko
learns her father's secret at last!
SECRET
That secret is... Oh, there's
nowhere near enough time!
SECRET
NOWHERE NEAR ENOUGH TIME
For the full story, search online for the
web version of the Kill la Kill preview!
WEB VERSION OF THE PREVIEW
Next time on Kill la Kill,
"The Girl Can't Help It."
EPISODE 16
THE GIRL CAN'T HELP IT