Sloppy... Sloppy... Sloppy...
Omelet rice!
I... can't breathe very well...
Huh?!
Excuse me...
I'd like to buy this.
Episode 20
Love. Kourin Festival
Rock it hard with an unique, mature look
Is Minchi around?
Oh, she left already.
Oh...
So she really...
Um... who's going to do the shopping?
We've still got other
preparations to make...
I'll do everything myself.
Bye.
Something happen?
N-No, nothing really...
Have we ever had omelet
rice on the menu here?
What? Omelet rice?
Not as far as I know.
Do you know how to make it?
Actually, I've never tried.
Ever since I was a kid, my family has
always eaten traditional Japanese food.
Oh, so even you haven't...
You wanna eat one that badly?
N-No, that's not...
I'm off now.
What? Hey!
What an oddball.
Thank you for traveling with us this morning.
This train is bound for...
So, about the omelet rice...
What is it, Nakochi?
You go first.
Nothing, really...
Why omelet rice?
Hey...
We've finished cleaning this area.
Is there anything else
that needs to be done?
Oh, I'm fine.
If you're free, could one of you
clean the entrance please?
I'll take care of that.
Thanks.
I'll help you clean the room where
the customers just finished their meal.
Oh...
Well, thank you.
Morning!
Morning.
I figured you'd be here prepping by yourself.
What do you want?
Well... I'd like to help you.
Thanks, but no thanks.
Besides, isn't the service team
supposed to meet up in the afternoon?
I told you, I came in early, just to help you.
I told you, I don't need your help.
You're so difficult, Minchi.
Don't make me repeat myself!
Have all of today's customers left?
Yes, the group that just
left was the last of them.
How are the two helpers?
They're both wonderful!
Especially their long, slender legs...
Incredible!
They're not geisha.
They're very experienced.
They're a great help.
Although they're on emergency duty,
it's still a part of their job.
Oh, but the Kobayashis,
who frequently stay with us,
were sad that Ohana and
Nako weren't on duty today.
Ah, so there are
customers who say such things.
Well, Ohana's almost worked
here for 6 months.
It feels like she just
arrived yesterday.
How is it? Is this good?
The left side's a little too high.
Got it.
Yup, right about there.
Okay.
Hey... maybe I should
apologize to Tsurugi.
You didn't do anything wrong, Yuki!
Yeah! Tsurugi's the one who
should be feeling bad.
Yeah, but...
Don't worry! Tsurugi will
apologize for sure.
Yeah. You wanna make
omelet rice, right?
Yeah.
Something bothering you?
No...
I've had the feeling that
something's been bothering you
since this morning, Oshimizu.
Sorry...
It's just that someone, who
works at the same inn as me,
is having some problems with her class.
Go and help her out.
But I'm part of this class's committee.
That's why you've been
helping me, right?
I can finish the rest by myself.
But...
She's your friend, right?
Go, be there for her.
Okay.
Thanks.
Oshimizu!
Oh, Yuina.
Your classroom's in the other direction, right?
Don't tell me. You're worried about Princess Minko, right?
I was wondering if there was
anything I could do to help.
Kissuiso's really amazing!
Great teamwork!
It's nothing like that...
But I'd love for someone as
cute as you to be a part
of the service team!
Oh, why don't we trade you for her?
"Her"? Who are you...
No, you can't!
Ah, a "her" was all you needed to understand, eh?
How many do we need to chop?
I never asked for your help!
Stubborn mule!
Balut!
Hey, Ohana?
Aren't you a part of our team?
I was worried about Minchi...
You don't need to worry!
That's not what I meant.
Aren't other people supposed
to be helping Princess Minko?
Umm...
I... well...
I said I'd do everything myself.
Minchi...
Umm...
Why don't we all have lunch now?
Oh yeah, it's about lunchtime now.
Good idea!
You're right, I'm hungry.
What about you, Minchi?
I'm not-
I had forgotten that I'm hungry!
It's all your fault!
What?!
Why is it my fault?!
Because you're doing
unnecessary things!
Let's all have lunch together then.
The cafeteria's closed today, though.
Am not!
Well, there are a lot
of ingredients here,
Are too!
Stop being so stubborn, Minchi!
and it looks like the
rice is already cooked, so...
I can do it myself!
You can't!
Is it okay, Minchi?
Yeah.
Okay, maybe we should test
out tomorrow's menu.
Or is there anything
you lot want to eat?
Umm...
Yes, Nakochi?
I'd like to eat omelet rice.
What?
Omelet rice?
Uhh...
Huh?
Home Economics Room
Are we allowed to just
come and use this room?
I was planning on using it
this afternoon for prepping, anyway.
I've already got permission.
Well-prepared!
I should have high expectations of a lunch
made by Princess Minko, right?
You're really going to
make omelet rice?
That's what Nako wants to eat, right?
I assumed you didn't like
omelet rice, Tsurugi.
I assumed you didn't
know how to make it.
What?
I said it was impossible to
make it with the equipment
we have in the classroom.
You're really experienced at this.
It feels like I'm watching a cook.
When I was a child,
I went to the city with my mother
once a month to shop,
and I always had omelet rice on that day
at a food place called "Grill Sakae" on the
6th floor of a department store.
I know that place!
Yeah, I think it's pretty famous.
Wow.
I think the Milano-style cutlet
tastes better there, though.
I always liked to sit at the counter since you could see them cooking.
I kept watching the kitchen
as my meal was being made.
I watched it being made, and then ate it.
Even after I finished eating,
I continued to watch the kitchen.
The kitchen on the other
side of the counter seemed
like a magical world to me as a kid.
I've seen this at a restaurant before!
Yeah!
Here.
Thanks.
I'll make you all some.
Wow, this is so good!
Hey, Minchi?
Did you decide to pursue a
career in cooking because
you liked the omelet rice at that shop?
N-Not at all.
Then why did you decide to be a cook?
Shut up.
Oh, you're right!
You can't make this using the
hot plate in the classroom.
Oh, right. There's not enough heat.
Time to dig in!
Hey, Minchi?
Is it okay if we make your portion of omelet rice?
How come?
I know we can't make this type of
omelet rice in the classroom,
but I wanted to try a different type.
A different type?
Like ketchup rice?
Yeah!
All you have to do is mix
the ketchup and rice like this.
My little brother loves ketchup,
and my mom scolds him every time
he makes something like this.
It definitely looks like chicken rice!
It tastes pretty good too.
Should we really be serving something
like that to our customers?
We could possibly make
chicken pilaf instead.
Pilaf?
Yeah.
You can cook it using
the rice cooker.
It'll even keep it warm.
That's it!
I heard that there's a maid café
in Tokyo that does that.
Tokyo...
Okay.
Now we just need some eggs.
Oh, I can do that.
The chicken pilaf's ready.
Wow, you're good at this too.
My mother would sometimes come home late
at night and demand omelet rice.
Okay, done!
Wow!
There! Our style of omelet rice.
How is it?
Here's some ketchup.
Did you have to write that?
Yup!
Okay, eat up!
Well, how is it?
It's good.
This is also omelet rice, right?
Okay, let's add it to
tomorrow's menu!
What do you say, leader
of the cooking team?
We'll lend you a hand
if anything arises.
I'll think about it.
Thanks!
Great!
I think this is going to
be a lot different...
Is it harder than you initially thought?
I'll try it again.
Here, Ohana!
I ate the last one, so I'm still pretty full...
You said you'd lend me a hand!
Fine...
There.
I think I can do this now.
Once more.
That's awesome, Minchi!
I knew you could do it!
Here.
I need to eat this one as well?!
I appreciate it.
I'll do my best...
Oh, I want to try too!
What?!
I hear Minko uses a portion
of her pay every month
to buy ingredients she usually doesn't have access to
in order to practice.
At her age, I'm sure she has
other things she'd like to buy.
She's really something else.
She'd already decided that she
wanted to be a chef in middle school,
and came to our inn as
soon as she graduated.
It's crazy to think that
she's already set herself a goal
at such a young age.
But you know, not everyone is like her.
There are those who can decide
on their path right away,
and there are also those who can
only see their path
after climbing high.
You can take a detour or
accidentally take the wrong path.
Those girls are allowed to do that.
I think we're just about done.
So are we.
Now all that's left is to wait for tomorrow!
It's going to be packed with customers tomorrow!
I can't wait!
Hey, you're back.
What are you doing, Mizuno?
There's an area that needs
a painting placed in it.
I miscalculated.
I need to hurry.
What are you drawing?
Oshimizu.
What? Me?
I've been with you for so long that
I don't need you to be here to draw you.
Mind if I take a look?
Go ahead.
Oshimizu!
I made it in time...
Is your class ready too?
Yeah, somehow.
You look happy, Nakochi.
I do?
Oh? Did something nice happen?
Nope, nothing.
Are you sure?
Kourin Festival
Welcome to the Princess Cafe,
where traditional maids
are at your service!
Princess Cafe
What's the menu like?
Everything on it is delicious!
How do I look?!
Really cute!
Thanks for waiting.
Did you make this?
She really showed us.
I hate myself for suggesting to
add that dish to the menu.
Is this the place?
Oh!
Welcome!
Yo, I'm here.
Thank you!
This is our menu.
Okay.
Wow, this menu is really Minko-like.
I'll have the omelet rice.
What?
What? Did I say something wrong?
N-No, one order of "Our Style
of Omelet Rice"!
Okay! One order of "Our
Style of Omelet Rice"!
The omelet rice is done!
Okay!
M-Minchi?
Don't say it...
Thanks for waiting!
Here is a special omelet rice
filled with love from our chef.
What?
Oh, I see.
It's like I'm watching a teen drama.
The campfire is about to be lit.
Want to go down there, Mizuno?
Up to you.
Sorry we're late!
It's because you took
forever to get dressed!
What?
Sorry we're late, Nakochi.
Don't worry about it.
Thanks for coming.
Listen to this!
Tohru visited our cafe.
And Minchi...
Shut up, you balut!
Hey, it's lit!
Hey, let's go!
Yeah, let's.
Then, it's settled!
Let's go together, okay?
Man, you were so amazing today, Minchi!
Yeah...
What do you mean?
Yeah, you really did your best today!
What the heck do you mean?
Not only L-O-V-E, but...
She gave it to me.
Isn't it pretty?
What are you guys talking about?
Friend
Well, Minchi drew this huge heart!
Shut up!
Now, there's no need to be embarrassed.
I'm not!
It's like I'm watching
some teen drama.
What?! Getting married?!
S-So early?!
I like kids.
Tohru likes me?
It's kinda erotic!
Love saves the world!
Episode 21
Rebirth of "Die"