What the hell are you doing?
Keep your filthy hands off!
It's not a kind country we live in, is it?
Lord O'Reilly is renting a room in this building.
He has been meeting with someone in secret,
and our objective is to find out who.
Surveillance, then.
We're not going to tail him?
We're most likely dealing with another spy.
There's a good chance that spy would spot us.
Anyone going in or out of that building
has to take the path in front of the park.
Ange, I want you there.
As for the other post,
we've rented our own room here, across from his.
We can see into Lord O'Reilly's room from there.
Then who will...
I will!
No.
Why not?
Stakeouts can go on for days.
If the Princess disappears for that long,
people will suspect something.
Then you can be me in the meantime.
I'll be keeping watch at the park.
But it won't be for 24 hours every day, will it?
Well, we would trade off at night.
I've had official business nonstop for days;
it's been so suffocating.
When you're a princess,
sometimes you just need to get outside.
Surely, you would understand that, Ange?
If you promise not to take
a single step outside your post.
Alright!
That was hardly fair, putting it like that.
Why do you think Miss Ange
has such a soft spot for Her Highness?
No idea.
Maybe she just can't say no
to someone with her own face.
Honestly! I'm asking a serious question!
It's her again.
You ruddy brat!
Don't come from behind. Come from the front.
It's possible to create blind spots
from in FRONT of your marks, too.
And that's why you're teaching her how to pick pockets?
I only taught her a way to survive.
It's very hard, having to go without food.
It puts you in a dark place.
Doesn't it bring back memories, trading clothes like this?
Of teasing Mrs. Crawford?
Yes! Remember how much fun it was?
And our private fashion shows.
You taught me how to jump rope.
And I learned piano!
We played duets together.
But we could never get on the same page.
But that was the most fun I'd ever had, playing the piano.
You know, I've been meaning to ask you.
What?
Why do you call me "Princess"?
That's the custom on the Black Lizard Planet.
Give me a real answer!
Don't worry.
I don't mean it sarcastically.
Then why?
It's simply out of respect.
It is chilly.
Thank you.
For what?
When I came from the front, it worked.
Nice arrangement.
I'm Julie. What's your name?
Chloe.
Hey, Chloe.
What?
Tell me more about the Black Lizard Planet.
You like stories, don't you?
Uh-huh. Your stories are so good!
Would you like to hear about the flying whales?
Or The Man who Turned into a Box?
There's no royalty on the Black Lizard Planet, is there?
And no poor people like me?
Then it must be a great planet to live on!
Alright, today I'll tell you about
the Princess and the Pickpocket.
It happened far, far away...
Even farther than the New World.
On the Black Lizard Planet.
Once upon a time, there lived a little Princess.
Princess Charlotte!
It's no use trying to run from us!
Come out and show yourself!
Etiquette and manners, language and music.
Horseback riding, dance, history, literature, art.
All she ever did was study.
The Princess had grown to despise her life at the palace.
Outside!
The girl across the wall looked just like the Princess.
The girl started to come
through the wall to visit every day.
Hey, Your Highness.
Let's be friends!
I'm rather a dull girl.
I don't think you would like my friendship.
No, I would!
Why?
Because we're complete opposites.
They played, they laughed...
They traded places, they pulled practical jokes.
It was the first friend the Princess had ever had.
One day, the Princess asked the girl
if she would trade places with her.
She wanted to see what life was like outside the palace.
Her heart soared at the prospect of seeing a new world.
No one would notice her.
No one would ask anything of her.
That is exactly what the Princess wanted.
Ange!
Oi! Ange!
Little brat, why haven't you done your job?
Job?
Don't play dumb with me!
You've been slacking off again!
It'll be another night with no dinner for you!
If you want to fill your belly,
you'll do your job tomorrow!
Look! Princess got the highest score again!
Of course she did!
Horseback riding, dance, and piano, too!
I wish I could be like her!
Thank you for waiting.
If I don't practice every day, I'll lose my touch.
Piano, dance, language, history.
You are a hard worker.
You are worthy of my respect.
You work hard, too, Miss Chise.
I can carry on because I enjoy it.
With you, that does not seem to be the case.
Do I look bored?
You appear as one punishing herself.
You see right through me.
I'll have to train harder.
It's because I'm empty.
That's why I have to build such a thick exterior.
That's her.
That's Ange's signal.
Alright.
I can't make out her face with that on.
It's no use, Miss Dorothy!
She won't take the veil off; I can't read her lips!
It's risky, but I guess we'll have to tail her
until we can figure out who she is.
Ow ow ow ow!
You chose the wrong pocket to pick.
She was so strong...
For such an elegant lady.
Lord O'Reilly was meeting with Gazelle.
One of the Duke of Normandy's spies.
You know what they all look like?
That's normal on the Black Lizard Planet.
Where are you going, Miss Ange?
To destroy the evidence.
Look, I ain't doing this 'cause I want to!
You need discipline!
You need to get it into your head
that you have to work harder!
What do you say?
Thank you very much, Sir!
I am blessed to be able to work
under such a benevolent master.
Very good.
Don't forget that you feel that way.
Wh-who are you?!
How did you get in here?!
Just a passing alien from the Black Lizard Planet.
I fight for justice.
Who do you think you are,
barging into other people's houses?!
I am providing for these children!
Providing for?
I think they're the ones providing for you.
Don't you talk back to me!
Wow.
With just one hand?
P-p-put me down! Put me down!
If you insist.
That's what you asked for.
Y-you little...
That was incredible!
You're really strong!
How did you do that?
But...
He'll be back for revenge.
When the master is in a bad mood,
he takes it out on us.
So I'm sure he'll...
A letter of introduction.
There's an orphanage on Stanford Hill.
Go there for help.
Why are you doing all this for me?
You went after the woman in the black veil,
like I asked, remember?
But I messed it up.
No, you gave me what I needed.
Wait!
Um... Er... I...
In the story! What happened to the Pickpocket girl?
On the day they switched places,
a revolution broke out.
Down with the monarchy!
Damn you and your lives of luxury!
Off with the royals' heads!
The switched princess ran as fast as she could.
Ange! Please be safe!
Ange!
Charlotte!
I'm so glad you're not hurt!
You, too!
Fire!
Let's get out of here!
Ange.
I'm going to be Queen.
What?
When I traded places with you, I learned something.
There are all kinds of walls, keeping everyone apart.
I'm going to be Queen,
and break those walls down.
And then, Ange,
we can be together forever!
That's a beautiful dream.
It's not a dream!
I'll make it come true.
I promise.
So...
Charlotte!
Charlotte...
Your Highness!
Are you alright, Your Highness?
Wait, I'm not her. I'm not the Princess!
You've had quite the scare, haven't you?
You don't need to hide who you are from us.
I promise, we'll keep you safe.
Wait! Listen to me!
The real princess fell down there!
Charlotte! Charlotte!
And from then on, neither of them could ever go back.
That poor Princess.
No, the one you should feel sorry for is the Pickpocket.
Why?
She got to be a princess!
The Princess and the Pickpocket were switched
in the chaos of the revolution.
What do you think would happen
if the royal family found out?
We should mobilize the Army immediately
and crush those rebels!
I heard the Army has betrayed us!
This is why I was against
letting commoners into the military.
She was surrounded by a bunch of bloodthirsty adults,
and forced to fend for herself.
If she didn't play the role of princess perfectly,
they would kill her.
She would have been working extremely hard,
under intense pressure.
Etiquette, manners, language,
music, horseback riding, dance, history,
literature, art.
She had so much to learn.
The slightest misstep
would lead her directly to the gallows.
And under that kind of pressure,
she did it all flawlessly.
This girl who couldn't even read or write
mastered nine languages.
She'd never seen a musical score in her life,
but now she has a reputation
as one of the Kingdom's leading pianists.
And all that
came from her agonizing effort.
A magnificent performance, Princess.
Thank you, Lord O'Reilly.
By the way, how is Inspector Flint doing?
The woman you've been meeting
in your room by the park.
Inspector Flint works for the Duke of Normandy.
Her talk of defection is a trap.
Are you saying that I should turn myself in, Princess?
Not at all.
You don't need to rely on them.
If you like, I could do you the favor
of getting you across the Wall.
Princess, who ARE you?
Just a spy.
It's beautiful every time I hear it.
You taught me how to play, Charlotte.
You surpassed my skill ages ago.
I was desperate, that's all.
I had no knowledge, no refinement, nothing.
I was empty.
No.
When I finally found you,
I said we should run away together.
But...
You said you would change the country.
Just as I once wished to do.
You are a real princess now.
Thank you.
That means so much, coming from you.
And I'm sorry.
For forcing that role onto you.
I know! It's been so long... let's do one together!
I'm not good enough.
The first time you played with me, I was a beginner.
Do you remember what you said?
"I've never had so much fun playing the piano before."
Mm-hm!