It's huge.
When Elder Tale was still a game,
we came here a lot, but...
Yes, it looks quite different in person, my lord.
This is the Depths of Palm...
Reporting... No enemies in sight.
Okay, let's go on ahead, Shiro.
Right.
The Depths of Palm
The Depths of Palm.
It's been three days since we left
Akihabara to save a girl named Serara,
who'd been stranded in Susukino.
Griffons come with usage restrictions.
You can only ride them four hours a day.
Even so, we've managed to travel a distance
that would take two weeks by horse.
The Tearstone Mountains...
My lord, look.
Wyverns.
Just like we thought, Shiro.
Yeah.
Monsters spawn in the same areas
as they did when it was a game.
We'll go underground as planned.
The only way to reach Ezzo,
where Susukino is located,
is to go over these mountains,
then cross the channel.
Walking will take time, and it's dangerous.
So we'll have to go underground.
H-Hey, stop!
It's huge.
The Depths of Palm.
A complex maze of ancient
tunnels and mine shafts.
Once we're through, we'll be on the
north side of the mountains.
This is way more impressive
than it looked on a monitor.
And it's so ancient, it's falling apart.
It wasn't this way in the game...
My lord!
The rat-men...
One of this world's many demihuman types.
Rat-man
Rank/ Normal
They're low-level monsters,
but they can spread plague.
They aren't attacking.
They instinctively know the differential
between our levels, so we should be fine.
But when cornered, they're dangerous.
If we chase them anywhere narrow,
or somewhere without an escape...
If we do...
They'll probably attack.
Should we break through?
I'd like to avoid wasting time fighting.
And we don't want the plague debuff.
Let's take another route.
Yeah.
This area seems safe.
My lord, I just scouted the floor ahead.
Thanks.
Could you tell me what you saw?
I want to cross-reference with my map.
You're being too formal.
S-Sorry.
Naotsugu, why don't you go ahead and... eat...
This nasty food is the one thing
I just can't get used to!
Even when you cook it...
It still ends up like this in a heartbeat.
Indeed...
In this world, none of the food has any taste.
Seafood Jambalaya
Special Seafood Curry
Extra-Spicy Curry Rice
Tomato Vegetable Curry
Just as in the game,
Seafood Jambalaya
Special Seafood Curry
Extra-Spicy Curry Rice
Tomato Vegetable Curry
Combine
Cancel
you can make food from the command
menu, provided you have the items...
But the food all tastes the same.
Even if you have the chef subclass,
it's apparently no better.
But sugar, salt, fruits, vegetables,
and other items classed as "ingredients"
taste like they should.
Or so we found, but...
Today's lunch was salty mush.
Today's breakfast was sugary mush.
Today's dinner is tasteless mush with an orange.
It makes me long for fast food and
convenience store bentos.
Marielle
Crescent Moon Alliance
Welcome!
Incoming Call
A call, my lord?
Oh, it's Marie.
Hi, Shiro! Where are you?
E-Eh?
The Depths of Palm?
You've really gone that far in three days?
How?
And is my Akatsuki safe?
You told me your plan,
but you're still scaring me a little.
Uh, that aside... How's it looking?
Ah, right.
We're in touch with Serara via telepathy.
Telepathy can only be used with
people on your Friend List.
Naotsugu
And you can't add them unless
they're right in front of you.
She says she's hiding with
that nice guy I mentioned,
and that she's okay for now.
I see. That's good to hear.
I guess some good people are left in Susukino.
Yeah.
Someone's helping her, huh?
Susukino
Japan Server
Ezzo Empire/ Susukino
City/ No Monsters
No PVP
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
I wonder what they're like.
Huh?
Serara
You are now a LV 44 maid.
My maid level is 44?
Yesterday, it was at level 42...
Why did I pick such a minor, useless subclass?
I should have chosen crafting,
even if it wasn't going to rise for a long time.
Like weaver or artisan...
I'm so bored, I just keep leveling up.
But maybe I'm not a maid...
I'm a housewife?!
No way, no way!
Maybe I'm a maiden,
waiting for my kitty-husband to come home!
Serara...
I'm home.
Welcome back, Nyanta.
Thank you, Serara.
How was town?
Same as always.
It wasn't good. It wasn't bad.
What's with the cheerful clerk routine?
You think you People of the
Land can take our money?!
If you oppose Brigandia, you know what'll happen?
Oh, that was cool.
Sounded like a signature saying.
Hey, look at this!
That's an exclusive from last year's event!
Finders, keepers!
Anyway, are these really all your ingredients?
This place sucks...
Now, now... Don't think so hard about it.
If you let it bother you, you'll get depressed.
Right.
This house is so clean.
I'm sure you'll be a great wife someday.
Th-That isn't true... Really.
How are those people who
are coming for you doing?
Oh, yeah.
Marielle, our guild master, contacted me.
She said they'll probably arrive
tomorrow, before noon.
So soon?
That's pretty impressive.
I wonder what these people
who are coming for you are like...
Shiro, thanks... Seriously.
Be careful.
Yes, talk to you later.
You didn't tell her we're using griffons?
Guess not.
Right...
By the way, how do you suppose Shiroe
and the others plan to cross the channel?
I don't know...
He said something about figuring
it out once he got there.
He probably has some special plan.
You can tell he was the Tea Party's strategist.
But why would someone like
that refuse to join a guild?
I'm sure he has his reasons.
Um, excuse me.
What is it, Liliana?
Everyone is here.
And? Did everyone come?
About sixty percent.
No reply from ten percent.
Thirty percent refused.
Our guild master will be here soon... Sorry!
Just wait a little longer.
Woodstock W, from Grandeur.
Ichimonjinosuke Akaneya, from Radio Market.
It seems that they and several
masters of the smaller guilds
have gathered in the Crescent Moon Alliance's hall.
Is that so?
Yes.
And as for Shiroe, formerly of
the Debauchery Tea Party...
He seems to be on his way to Susukino.
Susukino?
Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
That was scary!
Hey, this bridge was in the game, right?
Yes.
Was it always on the verge of collapse?
Naotsugu! Akatsuki! Stop!
Come on... Seriously?
We'll have to find another route.
Let's head back!
We'll go back one at a time—
Akatsuki!
My lord!
My lord! My lord!
No...
If I die here,
I'll end up back in Akihabara.
My lord!
Shiro!
I've never been the outgoing type.
Even when I was with friends,
part of me was always alone.
That's when I started getting into Elder Tale.
And then...
Tarareba
Race/ Human
Guardian, Lv. 48
Shiroe, right?
I've heard about you...
They say you're an amazing enchanter.
And the next thing I knew,
I was recognized as an experienced,
knowledgeable veteran.
Thanks, man! I did what you said,
and I got that item!
I followed the route you told
me about and got a rare item!
Thank you, Shiroe!
But...
Kaiganjin
Race/ Elf
Guardian, Lv. 62
Hey, how do I get the Typhon Ring?
Do that new quest in Mogami with me!
Tell me, Shiroe!
Could you take me there?
Please!
Me, too!
Come on, Shiroe.
Pain in the ass.
The best part of adventuring
is experiencing new things!
New things?
Yup, it's exciting and wonderful!
Almost as much as panties.
Naotsugu, don't say that stuff
in front of the ladies.
Shut up!
You're just saying that because
the girls all like you!
Well, that's true, but...
I'll get you one of these days, Souji.
Please don't cry...
Just look at this gorgeous view.
Totally worth the effort!
Right, Shiro?
What are you spacing out for?
Lost in thought again...
Shiro?
What's wrong, Shiro?
My lord!
Shiro!
Are you awake?
Are you all right, my lord?
Where am I?
Thank the shrimp.
After you fell, she jumped in and saved you.
You also jumped in, and pulled us both up.
And don't call me a shrimp!
I see.
Thanks, Naotsugu... And Akatsuki.
Me, too... I mean...
Thank you.
Eh? For what?
You tried to save me...
Okay, let's get this adventure
back on the road!
Right.
Weird, though. I fell into the
water from that height,
but I'm barely hurt, and I'm not cold.
Maybe because your body's level 90?
After all this walking, I'm hardly tired at all.
So where are we now?
We ended up taking the long way,
but we're nearly out.
You really are good at cartography, my lord.
My subclass is scribe, after all.
And back in the other world, I did CAD work.
Come to think of it, that's true.
CAD?
What's CAD?
Designs you make on a computer.
I do it at my university.
I'm an engineering student.
So you're a college student.
A graduate student.
I'm about to graduate...
Or I was.
Oh.
Then you're basically the same age as I am.
Seriously?
Is it that surprising?
You're kidding, right?
I mean, you're totally a little kid—
My lord, may I kick this stupid Naotsugu?
She's in college?
I've told you, ask before you do that!
It's your fault for being rude and perverted.
Perverted? You mean like b—
My lord, may I take this pervert and...
Again? At least let me get another letter in!
Akatsuki, Naotsugu's going to cry.
My lord, did you also think I was a child?
N-No, I wouldn't say "child"...
How do I answer this?
A kid, huh?
It looked like they joined some guild.
I wonder if they're okay.
When I'm back in Akihabara,
maybe I'll find them and...
What are you thinking about, my lord?
Nothing, really.
That isn't true.
Whenever you're thinking, your brow furrows.
Right here.
You look like an old man.
What are you laughing at?
Well... You heard her!
Naotsugu!
Where did this come from?
Lag?
No, we switched zones.
My lord, above us!
What is that thing?
It's blocking the stairs...
Was that in the game?
A subspecies of rat-man?
Doesn't seem to have a specific name.
Which means...
It's one of the new Novasphere monsters?
It's huge, but it's level 68.
Rat-maso
Rank/ Party
Looks like it's mostly status debuffs.
Is it the reason the dungeon's falling apart?
Probably.
It's a little risky, but we have no choice.
Let's eliminate it.
Okay!
Let's make this quick, strategist.
Over here, big boy!
Stealth Blade!
Cross Slash!
In Combat
Naotsugu Akatsuki
No matter how used to it you are,
fighting in real life is different.
You can't apprehend size, breath,
or stink through a monitor!
Here I go!
Thorn Bind Hostage!
Its defense is pretty high.
Three left... Get it, shrimp!
Don't call me shrimp!
I'll ensure you don't miss.
Mind Shock!
First you add a confusion debuff
that lowers dodge and agility.
Then amplify the attack power
of your allies' weapons.
Keen Edge!
Thank you, my lord!
Now it'll only take one more hit.
Assassinate.
Death
Wow.
The wind is cold.
But it feels great!
We're finally through the tough part.
It's beautiful.
Amazing.
The best part of adventuring
is experiencing new things!
New things, huh?
When Elder Tale was a game,
lots of players passed by here at dawn.
But...
We're the first ones here.
We're the first adventurers in the world
to see this.
That's right.
I've never seen anything so amazing,
even in Elder Tale.
It's our first prize for victory.
Sorry... There's no escaping Susukino!
How many times have you tried?
Get a clue already!
N-No—
That was a big wagon, but there isn't much inside.
Hey, why are you just standing there?
Pick stuff up.
I don't think I can do this...
Then you're headed for the Cathedral.
Demikas?
It's just a game... It's all virtual.
They'll just come back to life.
If you're still freaking out over PKing,
something's wrong with you.
Hey, don't forget to strip his equipment
before he disappears.
Right!
Don't drop that.
Keep a tight grip on it, Person of the Land.
What a riot!
Hey, I found some more.
Did those players back there hire them?
Even non-player characters cry?
Was that part of the game?
I don't care.
Do we take them, guild master?
I don't care if they're People of the Land or not.
They bore me.
So, Londark...
Where are the cat and the girl?
I have men looking for them, but nothing yet.
Why are you still fooling around?!
Find the girl and the cat!
Y-Yes, sir!
This is my world.
I won't allow anything to go against my will.
Just wait, Serara!
Brigandia, a guild that runs Susukino via force.
Its guild master, Demikas, rules by fear.
Shiroe's party meets with Serara,
and tries to escape them.
What strategy does Shiroe have?
And what does Akatsuki see during the battle?
Next time: Escape.
Escape
This is our reality.