Mashima-kun is still down by 5 cards!
He can't catch up!
That early mistake is making a difference.
He stabilized midway through the
game and made some good plays,
but his luck is still terrible!
The last five cards
have been on my side.
Should I focus on defending
the seven cards on my side
instead of attacking the
two on the opponent's side?
Living Ghost
I don't need you, Dr. Harada.
When in trouble...
As the years pass...
Go lower right!
Yes!
Thank you very much.
Two wins for Fujisaki!
Good!
One more win!
One more win for the championship!
Yeah!
Mizusawa's down 0 to 2.
They're strong.
That makes it a five-peat for Fujisaki.
I'm sending a card.
the cresting waves almost look like clouds in the skies
A multi-syllable card?
"My only thought as I" was already read,
so this is now a two-syllable card.
You won't be able to surprise me.
I'm sticking to my usual playing style.
This is painful.
It would be most gratifying
if Mizusawa was able
to secure a single win from
the dominating Fujisaki.
Three wins.
We're getting three wins, guys.
Chihaya Furu
Episode 19
I do not
know
where
this love
will take
me
We're getting three wins.
Don't bother bluffing.
It's possible you won't even get a single win.
Mashima...
Mashima went there.
Three wins, when we're cornered like this...
He's always let his actions speak for him.
He's careful and has a lot of pride.
He's always thinking about
what happens when he loses.
Even when he volunteered
to play their captain...
I'll play their captain.
Mashima...
is trying to change!
Excuse me.
Again?
He keeps wasting time.
I have six cards.
My opponent has two.
There are plenty of dead cards left.
"After many," "The emotions,"
"The hazed early dawn mist,"
"The sight," "May it," "My life,"
"When I," "Nothing," "Silent,"
"Gust," "I feel," "As my,"
"Since I," "For you I head."
My opponent won't make
any memorization errors.
He's aware of the changing unique syllables.
Excuse me.
I don't need you.
What?
You're the only coach I've ever had.
When in trouble,
go lower right!
the cresting waves almost look like clouds in the skies
Come on!
Come on!  Come on!  Come on!  Come on!
Read it!  Read it!  Read it!  Read it!
Give it!  Give it!  Give it!  Give it!  Give it!
Come on!  Come on!  Come on!  Come on!
My only thought as the boat
takes me out to sea is that
It was read...
It was read.
It was read!
Mashima sent the multi-syllable
card to give himself a chance.
The Fujisaki captain is
very good at covering,
so he has a habit of covering
multi-syllable cards.
Even when it's not necessary?
He's open to attack then.
He's using my data!
He's only down three now!
Huh?  What?
He was on a roll...
It is hard to decide what card
to send towards the end,
but this isn't the time to stress over it.
I'm sending a card.
which shines over Mount Mikasa
the cresting waves almost look
like clouds in the skies
The storm blasts autumn...
to set the Tatsuta River ablaze
which shines over Mount Mikasa
Eromu went for the "The sky
may" on his own side?!
A fault!
Even better!
Double fault!
Eromu-senpai committed a double fault?
First time I've seen that happen.
He rarely commits faults,
let alone a double...
I needed to refresh my memory.
Wait...
He knew exactly which card
he was going to send.
He pretended to take a long time,
so he could reinforce what the
field would look like in his mind.
This is the first fault he's made.
I know you have to be tired.
Five matches lasting over nine hours.
And also, the Tokyo regional champions,
Hokuo,
would have made you work for your win.
I guarantee it!
With that double fault,
the Prez removes one card from
his side and sends another...
the plum blossoms still smell the same
It's 3 to 3.
He's caught up!
I'm sending "In order for."
Amusing.
The battle in the middle is getting fierce.
It's 5 to 1...
The Mizusawa player
only has one card left.
When did that happen?
Yamashiro-san panicked
and committed a fault.
Neither of them are using
any sort of strategy.
This is a battle of sound and reflex.
The difference between
them is barely perceivable,
but it exists.
Enough of a difference for
one to emerge victorious.
Hang in there.  Hang in there.
Where am I?
The Urayasu room in the Omi
Jingu Learning Center.
to set the Tatsuta River ablaze
Right next to the reader.
In the seat that assures victory!
Rion!
Thank you very much.
Is something wrong?
Oh, it's okay.
Try not to disturb her.
Huh?
She's asleep...
What about you?
No call to announce
Mizusawa's first win...
I'm sending "No more."
What are you doing, Kanata?
He's clawing his way back
from the early deficit.
What's going on?
As the game drags on, his guesses
have been more accurate.
It takes experience to be able
to feel the flow of the game.
I've been playing karuta since I was five.
I've been playing longer
than anyone else here!
Compared to becoming Queen,
it's much harder for us to
become best in Japan together!
Chihaya's right.
and by no fault of mine
Said world grants no escape
Eromu-senpai got it!
He's so fast!
He's quick when it comes to cards
that are now one-syllable.
Still, I can't lose here!
Chihaya...
We'll have plenty of chances to
try to become Master and Queen,
I'm moving "Like a."
but we only get to play as a team
during our three years in high school.
The sky may hold...
Damn!  He defended it!
I'm moving my card.
It's down to luck-of-the-draw.
In both games...
I don't believe this.
Both of them are in
luck-of-the draw situations.
I do not know where this love will take me
Mizusawa synchronized their cards!
There's no guarantee that we'll make
it back to the finals next year.
We'll probably never get
another chance like this!
I do not know where this love will take me
The famous Sone no Yoshitada poem...
Like a boatsman adrift at the mouth of the Yura, I do not know where this love will take me
Of all cards, this is the
one the Prez gets...
No more can we hear the sounds of the waterfall, but its legacy continues to spread
The opposing captain has "No more."
I like these poems much more than
the ones that are more technical.
The mouth of the Yura is
where river meets ocean.
There, love lost its oar in the waters,
left with no idea where it will go...
Chihaya,
wake up...
I want you to watch
my fate.
It's over if "Like a" is read.
I didn't expect Mizusawa to
synchronize their cards.
Surely they didn't...
It must be coincidence.
I wasn't expecting a luck-of-the-draw,
but Emuro-kun has strong luck.
This match will end 4 to 1.
This was no coincidence.
They were setting this up.
I'm sending "In order for."
I'm sending "No more."
I'm moving "Like a."
They understand how
to play team matches.
What?
Two of their games are
down to luck-of-the-draw?
They synced their cards!
They pulled it off!
It's 50/50.
We have a 50% chance of winning...
A 50% chance of our cards being read.
But...
I've never seen...
Mashima have his card read
in a luck-of-the-draw.
How long has it been since
Eromu's last luck-of-the-draw?
Did Eromu relax because he was
up against a Class B player?
It's still okay!
Eromu-senpai's card will be read.
I can visualize my "No more" being read.
Sealing Fujisaki's five-peat!
I don't think my card will be read,
but I doubt I can take the last card
from a player who's
such a good defender.
Remember to breathe.
I can't give up yet!
I do not know where this love will take me
"Like" is a one-syllable card now,
but "Nothing" hasn't been read,
but its legacy continues to spread
so he can't take "No more"
on the first syllable.
Do I attack?
It won't work?
But if I don't attack...
which shines over Mount Mikasa
For you, I head out to the
fields to pick spring greens
Nishida also went on the attack.
They intend to attack the opponent's
side in a luck-of-the-draw?
Since I could not hide...
Still nothing.
His guard is so low.
There's no opening to attack.
Damn...
Damn!
It's too much!
I'm too scared!
I can't take this!
Mashima-senpai!
The one card I need won't be read.
It never is.
Is that how my life will go?
Is everything I do futile?
Six more dead cards.
"After many," "May it," "My life,"
"Nothing," "Silent," "Gust"...
Is it futile to keep remembering these?
Still...  God...
I beg you...
I don't care if my card is never
read in a luck-of-the-draw again.
So please...
Just today...
This one time...
Just this once...
Like a boatsman adrift...
W-We did it...
We did it!  We did it!
We did it!
Yes!  We did it!
Quiet.
The match isn't over
until the second verse has been read.
...adrift at the mouth of the Yura,
I do not know where
this love will take me
Hey.
You've got tatami marks.
The winner of the team
championship is Mizusawa,
by a score of 3 to 2.
Thank you very much.
We lost.
Second place.
We came in second.
This loss is my fault.
If I were the god of karuta,
I would have sided with Mizusawa
for their valiant display.
It's my fault for building a
team solely based on strength.
I looked down on my opponent
for spending an entire year
kicking around Class B.
That was my mistake.
That guy's on his way up.
Ri-Rion?!
You're not supposed to show emotion!
Wait...
Rion, listen to me.
None of our players are capable
of defeating Ayase-san.
It's not your fault that you couldn't win,
but you need to realize that you
lost despite having the advantage.
Learn some humility.
It's on you to make sure that we don't
lose a single match next summer.
The ceremony will be on the
first floor in 10 minutes.
Please prepare as necessary
and proceed there.
Don't forget anything.
We had some excellent matches this year.
So Mizusawa is our champion.
If you become the best player in Japan,
you'll be the best in the world.
I'm not interested in team tournaments.
I'm focused on winning the
individual tournament.
Well, let's head downstairs, Ayase-san.
D-Did you watch?
Huh?
Were you watching?
My team is the best in Japan.
I became the best in Japan
without becoming Queen.
It's because we were playing together.
Don't say that you're not
interested in teams!
And then there's the
"Impassionate gods" card!
Wataya-kun said that the card
has the same name as me!
The three of us will
win together, right?
Yeah.