Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm eating properly.
No, I don't need it.
You're busy, too, aren't you?
I figured.
It's far.
Snow?
Why would it snow?
Okay.
Bye.
Friends
Where Memories Live
First!
That was quick.
Of course.
You were second.
What? No way!
Who was faster than us?
Whose group?
Mizusaka's group.
Your brother.
Sensei, quick! Give me the stamp!
We're going on, too.
Your team has four people, right?
Are you all here?
Oh, come on.
Koharu, you're too slow!
There's no hurry.
What are you talking about?
It's a battle!
We have to win!
I don't think orienteering is a battle.
Don't mess with orienteering!
And where are the other two?
Nonoka is...
What're you doing?
Togawa-san's not here yet.
Jeez.
Don't you all want to win?
I think I'm happy just having fun.
Nonoka!
You're the group leader.
You have to call Shione.
Idiots.
All right, third one down.
So, where's the next place?
Oh, I know this place.
It's behind the hotel by my house.
Oh, yeah.
I think my shop is a checkpoint, too.
My parents met with the teachers.
Umm...
Right, let's go.
Yuzuki, you shouldn't rush it.
You'll run out of energy.
Isn't this cheating?
It's just a home field advantage.
We've been living here with that
stupid saucer this whole time.
We deserve this privilege!
Privilege?
Besides,
they have the same conditions.
What are you going on about?
I'm not going to lose!
She's rushing ahead again.
We're enemies for now, so we'll be going.
See you.
Don't you guys need this checkpoint, too?
We were planning to go there later!
Objective confirmed!
I'll go report!
I'm technically the group leader.
It's okay.
Part of your duty as the leader is
to make use of enthusiastic troops.
That's true.
Thanks, Koharu.
Motorboats
If I'm not mistaken...
She's totally avoiding me.
Did something happen with Shione?
I can't think of anything
I might have done.
Guys, hurry up. Let's go to the next one!
We're running now.
The enemy is right there!
Aren't we at Koharu's place yet?
You know where I live, don't you?
You should have paced yourself.
Oh, goddess.
It's that thing's fault!
It's taking my strength!
With some mysterious, invisible something.
You seem fine still.
Anyway, it's not my fault.
It's all the saucer's fault!
You're right.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Togawa-san.
Shione-san!
I can hear you.
That's good.
Do you need something?
Not really,
but you know, I haven't had a
chance to talk to you much yet.
Why did you say that
thing when we first met?
Why did you bother coming back now?
I don't like you.
Hey, Shione-san!
Try calling me by my first name again.
Try it.
Wh-What?
I'll slap you.
Why?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I don't think it's your fault.
Shione's not really the
talkative type to begin with.
She wasn't like that when
she was little, though.
Have you known her for a while?
Yeah, Shione was born in this town, too.
Come on, what are you doing? Hurry!
That's it.
I don't want to be hated
when I don't even know why.
Koharu, thanks for worrying for me.
I'm still going to try to
be friends with Shione-san.
So I'm going to go again.
Okay, good luck.
Shiihara Shop
Hey, Togawa-san,
I heard you lived here a long time ago.
I did, too.
I was little, so I don't
remember about it, though.
I knew it.
Shione-san?
Nonoka.
Y-Yes?
You're an eyesore.
Disappear.
Without a trace.
And here's our promise.
What happened?
It's nothing.
Yeah?
All right, then.
We're finally here!
I'll go report to the teacher.
Oh, okay, thanks.
Sensei, hurry, stamp!
Noel?
What're you up to?
Nonoka!
Oh, my.
Noel!
I'm sorry, monster-san!
Noel, are you all right?
Here, wipe your face.
Nonoka!
Noel.
Nonoka, are you done with school yet?
No, I'm doing extracurricular work.
After school?
I still have school.
Sorry.
Okay.
She's so cute!
Where'd she come from?
Is she your sister?
Can I keep her?
I told you about her, remember?
She's Noel.
Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you.
Who is that?
Shione,
let's go to the next spot.
What?
Why are you so cold to Nonoka?
I hate her, that's all.
Haven't you noticed?
Apparently.
You wouldn't think she'd
be back now, would you?
Enemy units spotted!
We'll catch up to them.
There's five of us now!
Why do you have more than before?
I dunno.
Let's go, Noel.
Let's show them our power!
Sucks to be with the noisy
one, huh, transfer kid?
What do you mean?
Not at all.
She thinks we're stupid.
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
The rest are past that
mountain over there.
One more?
Yep, should be.
It's a bit far, though.
Aren't you tired, Noel?
Noel is great!
You look the most tired
of all of us, Yuzuki.
That's not true!
Huh, where's Togawa-san?
She was walking behind
us until just now.
I wonder if she got lost.
She might just be slow.
I'll go find her.
You guys go ahead.
Nonoka!
Shouldn't we look for her together?
Nonoka, me, too!
Don't worry, I'll be right back.
Stay with the others!
Yuzuki, take care of Noel for me!
Sure.
Do you think Nonoka's okay?
It's been a while.
What are you doing?
Shione!
Where's Nonoka?
I wouldn't know.
How did you even get ahead?
Maybe she took another route?
Seems that way.
Nonoka!
Wait, Noel!
Noel-chan.
Togawa-san!
I guess now I'm lost.
Noel!
Nonoka!
Yuzuki.
Oh, Souta.
What?
We're already finished.
Good for you.
Koharu, we're looking for the latecomers.
Where's the transfer student
and that little kid?
Well...
Kiriyako
Kindergarten
I never knew this was here.
Kiriyako Kindergarten
I wonder if they found Shione-san.
I keep messing up.
Komiya!
Nonoka!
It's been a while since we've
all been together, huh?
Oh, yeah.
We were all in separate classes
until last year, right?
Yeah, it'd get complicated with
two twins in the same class.
Hey, do you remember
back when there was—
Stop!
If she hadn't said what she did...
We wouldn't have called the saucer.
Obviously.
You can't forgive her?
Of course not!
She's the one that called the saucer!
Then why are you being nice to her?
Found you.
That song...
I'm pretty good now, right?
Is it really you
from seven years ago?
Is Tokyo really far away?
There you are.
What's up?
They asked me to find you.
They're going to eat them.
They are?
Yeah, hurry.
They're left over. Why can't I have them?
You can't. It's one each.
Here, catch!
Eat it, quick!
Good!
Case closed.
Come on.
Hey, hey.
The saucer?
Remember we talked about it?
If we all wish for it,
a saucer will come down.
Yeah, it said so in the saucer book.
Let's try it.
I want to do something with you guys.
Why?
I might
not be able to see you once it's winter.
Oh, yeah.
It would be hard to come
here if it snows a lot.
Yeah.
So, before it snows.
Nonoka is that girl?
There's no way that's her.
Why couldn't she be?
Nonoka's my friend.
She's helping me get rid of the saucer.
Besides...
Besides, she used to live here.
She said so herself.
Is that true?
She made us help her call the saucer,
and then she left town.
For the past seven years
you've regretted it every time you've
looked at the saucer, haven't you?
Why did I do this?
She comes back now,
and she calls us friends?
She thinks we're stupid.
But...
But, we don't know if
that was really Nonoka!
Yuzuki.
Hey, I found her.
I remember now.
I said it first.
To call it.
You did.
You called me.
'Cause...
I'm the saucer.
Next episode of Celestial Method:
"A Fragment of Emotions."
Enjoy!
A Fragment of Emotions