Wh-what?!
That's my secret technique, the Sweets Canyon!
Sh-she let one box of candy slide
so it would take down that whole mountain of them!
UMR stuck it to us again!
Wow!
Her techniques are as Godlike as ever!
UMR, that was a fine play, indeed!
You think?
How about we go somewhere and eat these?
U-um, in that case...
Hm? Do you know someplace good?
H... H...
How about coming to my house?!
Huh? To your house?
What do you say?
Come to think of it...
all I've seen is her living room and the study.
Sure, I'd be glad to!
Okay!
Huh... so this is your room, TSF? It's really big.
If you keep eyeing it like that,
you'll make me embarrassed, indeed!
So many trophies...
Oh! And look at those goods from Anumate!
She even put up the photos
from when we went to the amusement park...
Being in a friend's room is fun
because it brings back memories, huh?
Sbrite is the perfect accompaniment for snacks, UMR!
Wh-what?!
I like to watch anime while enjoying snacks
and drinking Sbrite!
She's just like me!
So, Sylphin has been having "feasts" of her own.
Actually, I'm pretty particular
about that sort of thing myself.
Why don't you show me how it's done?
Really? I suppose everyone does this!
Did you know? Switching between chocolate
and potato chips makes them extra delicious.
Oh, really? Indeed, I have never tried that!
So, Bamboo Shoot Mountains
are the only ones you like?
Hmm... Bamboo Shoot Mountains are the best,
but... Ah! Pokee can be good, too.
"Pokee," you say?
They're the standard when it comes to snacks.
They're just so crunchy and delicious!
I know of them! I've heard that in Japan,
friends will engage in a Pokee game!
Huh? A Pokee game...?
Do you know what sort of game it is, UMR?
Huh?! Uh, I think so...
Impressive, indeed!
In that case, I would like to do it with you,
this so-called Pokee game!
What?!
U-uh, no, no way! That's not a game that we would play.
Why not?! I wish to do it with you, indeed!
The thing about the Pokee game, is, um...
Ah! You have to do it with someone
who's really SPECIAL to you.
But I think of you as a MOST special friend, UMR!
I-I think the same of you, but there's NO WAY
we're playing the Pokee game!
Oh. Sorry for raising my voice like that...
it's just, I don't think that's the kind of game
that friends play with each other.
No, it's all right. It's my fault for getting carried away
at having a friend over.
Oh. I see...
it's nice having this big room and all,
but I bet it's lonely having her snack feasts all by herself.
Really, I'm the one who's sorry.
Um... you're a great friend, TSF!
Yes!
For some reason, I'm SUPER embarrassed!
Oh, yeah. Let's watch some anime.
Hey! Let's play the Pokee game!
Ah! They play the Pokee game even in anime.
I wonder what sort of game it is, indeed!
Well, here goes. We each take one end, and then...
But, we're getting closer and closer!
U-um, so, that's why... we can't do it, right?
The Pokee game.
A-agreed! My apologies!
Oh, hi there, Hikari.
S-sorry to put you out, Big Brother.
She really did come for bread day, Big Brother.
I'm glad I made enough for the three of us.
Today, I've made curry and naan.
The deuce, you say!
It's nice and chewy!
It is!
Glad to hear it...
So, Hikari, Kanau knows you've been coming here, right?
Yes!
Like I thought, she doesn't know...
Kanau!
Taihei?! C-can I help you?
Sorry about before. It took longer
than expected to wrap things up.
Huh? Wrap up...?
Note: Kanau mistakenly confuses the meaning of "to get someone home,"
for the homophone "to return something."
Did I lend you something?
Huh?
Hmm?
Umaruuun!
Hikari, is it possible you've been coming here without
saying anything? That would make your sister worry...
Say, Big Brother, why don't you call her?
Gah! Th-there's no need!
Well, it IS more dangerous at night,
and she's probably made dinner already...
My sister works overtime on Tuesdays.
I've just been eating on my own.
Oh, really? Well, we don't mind at all!
I'll be working late tonight,
but I've made dinner and put it in the fridge.
Huh? I've gotta eat alone?
Well, fine, if there's no other option...
Huh?
Hurry up or it'll get cold.
Okay.
You sure you don't need me to walk you home?
No, I'm meeting someone, so I'll be fine.
U-um, Big Brother? Is it all right if I come again?
Well, yeah, I guess.
Come whenever you like, Hikari.
Okay!
Just don't make a habit of coming every week, yeah?
I shall.
Hey! What are you doing, Hikari?!
I'm home, Hikari.
Welcome back, Big Sis.
Hikari! You went out tonight, didn't you?!
Liar! I know you've been going out
on Tuesdays when I work overtime!
I-I only went to get something to eat.
It's dangerous to be out this late, okay?!
I thought for sure you'd object when Hikari said
she wanted to come over again.
N-nah, I don't really mind...
Oh, my!
Hm? What is it, TSF?
UMR, didn't this used to be a beauty shop?
Hey, you're right! TSF, had you been here before?
No. But it had an old-timey feel, and I liked it, indeed!
It's indeed a shame when a shop you like goes away...
You do like retro-style buildings,
don't you? I do too, I guess.
Still, you sure know a lot about old-school
department stores and candy shops,
even though you lived in Germany.
I do! Such things are nostalgic, indeed!
"Nostalgic"? You've got
the same kind of stuff in Germany?
Well, no. But I'd been to Japan once before.
When I was six, I made quite the fuss
until I was brought here for some sightseeing!
Making such a fuss that they brought her
from Germany here to Japan is pretty impressive...
And when I came, I saw an old arcade
with a beautiful lake and a giant swan.
It's a wonderful memory, one that I've kept to this day.
Well, do you want to head out there today?
That's all right. I don't remember where it is,
and I doubt it exists anymore.
No, it's still there.
Hm?
I think it's probably that mecca for retro gamers.
I'm somewhat afraid, UMR.
Hm?
If the scenery has changed from how I remember it...
I think it would be a bit of a shock.
Don't you worry, TSF.
Staying the same is what makes the mecca a mecca.
Whaaat?!
I-it can't be...
It's completely unchanged!
Exactly.
Sagamiko Park hasn't changed a bit.
The buildings are the same...
Even the signs are the same!
Welcome.
It's the same store employee!
Look! It's the all-important pinball!
Indeed, even that is the same as back then!
Ah, there you are!
Big Brother!
Hurry up. The Swan Boat is gonna leave!
Okay!
TSF, there's a rare game over here
that I've never seen before!
Okay!
It looks like most of the people
on those boats are couples.
Yes, indeed!
Sylph, why don't you want to leave?
Because after today, we'll go back to Germany!
And I... I won't be able to see Big Brother anymore!
Sylphin.
Brother?
She hasn't said a word since I mentioned couples...
TSF? What's the matter?
UMR, let's ride one of those boats!
Huh?!
THAT'S where this conversation led to?
Hup! Whoa! This thing is shaky!
This is the first time I've been on a boat.
You're my all-knowing hero, UMR. You'll be fine indeed!
I'm hardly all-knowing. I only knew about
the Sagamiko arcade because it's famous.
UMR!
Hm?
Thank you so much for coming for me!
Don't you mean, "Thank you for BRINGING me?"
I think it's perfectly fitting, indeed!
Let's do this again. I'll come for you.
Okay!
Tests start tomorrow, huh?
It's been a while, indeed!
Are you feeling confident, Umaru?
There sure is a lot we have to know this time...
Hm? What is it, Ebina?
I think I'm going to fail tomorrow's tests...
I might not even make it to the next grade!
Huh?
What did you mean, you won't make it to the next grade?
B-but this is the day before exams!
Why are you only now...?!
The timing just didn't feel right.
I hope I pass along with the rest of you, but maybe I...
Ebina...
If that's what is at stake here, then this where I come in!
We shall hold a study group, indeed!
Th-this is one amazing library...
There is a wealth of books here,
and the silence most certainly lends itself to study!
What do you think, Umaru?
I-it's great!
I've never even been in here...
I'm thrilled at the idea of having
a study session with you all!
Um, I don't think this is the right time to feel "thrilled."
Ebina, what would you say are your weakest subjects?
A-all of them.
All of them?!
Well, let's just see how things go.
Ebina...
You have a pretty decent grasp of this.
U-um...
This will be enough to get you
about an 80. Thank goodness.
Ebina, I think you have performance anxiety.
That time before when we studied together,
you did just fine...
But later, when we took the test,
it looked like you didn't do so well.
Everyone gets so serious when we're taking tests...
it's like a totally different classroom!
It's as if I'm the only one
who gets left behind by the flow of time...
Reckon things could go wrong at the drop of a hat,
and I'd just wanna up and go back to Akita!
I know, right?
Th-that must mean some seriously bad grades!
S-so then, so long as you're not nervous,
you should be able to get a passing grade, right?
Yeah, but... what should we do?
I personally think of people as vegetables
or something and purge them from my mind.
She always does that?!
You know, you may be able to relax
if you think about something you like.
Something I like...
Th-th-that might make me worry even MORE!
Did she imagine something?
Still, this is sort of vexing. The test is tomorrow,
but we haven't found a way to solve things.
You all have your own studying to do,
but you're taking the time to help ME...
I'm sorry! I'm just dragging you all down.
I-in any case, right now
we need less tears and more ideas!
Indeed, that's right! We're sure to find
a sound solution if we put our heads together.
Come on, Ebina. Wipe those tears.
E-everyone, why are you...?
Because we're friends!
Y'know?
Indeed!
It's only natural, wouldn't you say?
Okay, let's start memorizing, Ebina!
Sylphin, that's not the subject for tomorrow's test.
In that case, learn THIS!
That's not right, either.
Jeez... Sylphin, you're hopeless.
My first day at a new school...
I-I'm kinda nervous!
So, you're from the Midwest?
That's right. It's nice to meet you!
I'm from the Northwest!
Those girls over there've already made friends!
I-I want some friends too.
Reckon I gotta talk to someone!
Maybe I'll try talking to her.
That Motoba girl kinda lost it
at the entrance ceremony, huh?
Got that right. They say
she kicked some guy, a grownup!
Oh. She left...
Maybe I'll try inviting her out for lunch sometime.
Hm?
It is a pleasure to meet you all!
My name is Sylphinford Tachibana, and I shall become
the greatest "player" in this classroom, indeed!
Shbafeeeen!
Sh-she's... like... outta some magazine!
I think I'll be able to talk to her, though.
U-um, it's nice to meet you. Ebina is my name.
"Ebina S. Maineim"? That's a rather unusual name.
Um, no, I...
It's "Ebina."
And yet! You're quite courageous to be the first one
to come talk to me. That is the spirit, indeed!
I challenge you, Ebimori!
It's "Ebina"...
U-um, a challenge?
Yes, at whatever you would say you are best at.
Come at me with anything!
Maybe challenges like this are normal in Tokyo.
As for what I'm "best at"... I'm no good at studying,
though I'm not bad at cooking and household chores...
Still, I can't do those now.
I can eat a lot of akitakomachi rice!
But we don't have any akitakomoachi...
Have you decided?
Um...!
'Morning.
Umaruuuun!
She...
Reckon she's like a princess and all!
You are Umaru Doma, yes? I heard you took
the top spot in the entrance exams.
Um, I don't know if I was at the top or not...
You will now challenge me, please!
Huh?
So her name's "Umaru Doma."
Come now, be quick! It's a challenge!
A challenge, indeed!
Wonder if maybe one day me
and these girls can be friends...
Ebina?
Huh? Um, what?
You okay? It looked like you were spacing out.
Ah! I'm so sorry!
Hm? What is it? What's the matter?
It's because Sylphin keeps acting all weird.
So now I am the cause?
It's nothing. Really, it's nothing.
Umaru...
Hm?
Kirie...
Huh?
Sylphin...
Yes?
Let's all study together!
Okay!
All right, start your tests.
Even more...
Now and forever...
I want to be with my friends!
Ebina, let's go home together.
Sure!
Kirie, I'll race you to that utility pole over there!
Wh-why would I want to do something like that?
Because seeing who comes first
would be a challenge indeed!
H-how about we all go eat some crepes or something?
Thank you for being so welcoming with my sister Hikari.
No, please, it's nothing.
We have yet to spend
any proper time together yet, have we?
M-maybe we can go have tea or something.
Um, s-sure.
Awkward...