How do you like it?
ULTRA GOKU UNIFORM
CENTURION CAVALRY FORMATION
This is the Ultra Goku Uniform
Centurion Cavalry Formation!
Charge!
I'm just getting started!
It's the High Velocity Life Fiber Jammer.
It spins tiny Life Fibers at high speed to--
It's a big, rubber barrier!
- Ow...
- Sanageyama!
That's what you get for running
ahead by yourself!
You never learn, do you?
We have to turn off
that jammer!
We're stopped in
our tracks, huh?
Hup!
And hup!
You are always in my way...
Now, allow me to show you
just who the master is.
- What on earth?
- The stars are gone!
Shinra...
...Koketsu.
Absolute Submission!
EPISODE 24
PAST THE INFINITE DARKNESS
What's wrong, Senketsu?
It's no use, I have no strength!
Whenever I'm hit by that light,
my body is paralyzed with fear!
Shinra-Koketsu is the master
of all Life Fibers.
Life Fibers who rebel against it tremble
in fear and are rendered powerless.
This is absolute submission.
ABSOLUTE SUBMISSION
These are images from around the world
captured by the communications satellite.
Look, the people of the world are all
wearing clothing made by REVOCS.
When I unleash the power of Absolute
Submission across the world,
the dormant Life Fibers inside
REVOCS clothing will awaken.
Every last human being will be
swallowed up by their clothing,
and the Earth will be covered
in a single piece of cloth.
The Earth will become
a Cocoon Sphere,
and the new Life Fibers that will be born
will be scattered across the cosmos.
How wonderful...
This is the fundamental truth
of the universe.
You no longer have any
means of opposing me.
We're still here to oppose you!
We're stripped down to...
...our bare Nudist souls!
Ultimate Double Naked DTR!
ULTIMATE DOUBLE NAKED DTR
Beneath my notice.
Oh, you aren't going
to kill them?
Not yet.
After all, these people are precious energy
sources for the Original Life Fiber.
The Original Life Fiber...
It's still alive?!
The Original Life Fiber will absorb you
and your friends and be restored to health.
I am sorry, Ryuko.
The ploy you risked your life
for was all for nothing.
Not yet!
We aren't done just yet!
Gamagoori? Mako? Guys?
Oh, my!
You must have superhuman strength
to be able to move in the
Absolute Submission field!
But it's no use!
Humans are slaves to clothes!
That relationship
will never change!
That's not true!
That isn't true at all!
I mean, with Ryuko and Senketsu,
neither one of them is the boss!
They have a lovely partnership
between human and clothing!
I've had enough of you, too.
Die, already!
S-Senpai!
Honnouji Academy Disciplinary
Committee Chair Ira Gamagoori!
I protect Satsuki Kiryuin and all
students of Honnouji Academy!
Know that I am
a living shield that...
Ugly, ugly, ugly!
You ugly ape!
Like hell you will!
Bitch!
I may not be able to use my Kamui,
but I can still fight on my own!
Thanks to the Life Fibers
inside my body!
What?!
I'm not a human, and I'm not clothing.
I'm something in between!
But right now, I'm real grateful
that my body is the way it is!
Cause it looks like I'm the only one
that Absolute Submission
field isn't working on!
Senpai! Gamagoori-senpai!
Are you safe, Mankanshoku...?
Then it was worth it...
S-Senpai!
Gamagoori!
Harime... Damn you...
You bastards...!
Right here, Ryuko.
The Absolute Submission
field is being powered
Right here, she says!
by Hououmaru as she sleeps here.
Right here!
This is where you
need to aim.
Don't screw with me!
But even knowing that,
you can do nothing!
Ryuko! It's too dangerous!
Calm down, Senketsu!
B-But Ryuko will--
I understand how you feel.
But she wouldn't be Ryuko if
she stopped when told to.
Satsuki, you... You can hear me?!
Yes, I can hear you.
So that's it...
Lady Ragyo.
Yes, I suppose it's time.
And now, with this,
humanity ends.
Guys!
I will begin with your friends.
They will all become part of the
uniform cloth that will cover the Earth.
H-How?
Like Ryuko, I am neither
clothing nor human!
Shippu Senjin!
- What's going on?
- I can move!
This must mean the Goku Uniforms
have their strength back!
It does indeed!
Life Fiber Override! Kamui Junketsu!
KAMUI JUNKETSU
Mankanshoku!
I never imagined I would
be saved by you...
There's no need to thank me.
Way to go, Senketsu!
Did you see that, Ragyo?!
This is the power of those
you ridiculed as shams!
How can this be...?
A mere Kamui knock-off...
It's because he is a knock-off.
When Satsuki heard my voice,
that's when I realized it.
I realized that I had been given
the same power as Ryuko!
- Not human...
- ...and not clothing!
This is true...
...Life Fiber Synchronization!
Ryuko!
The rest of you,
see to the transmitter!
On it!
Hup!
Nope! Nope, nope, nope!
You'll have to go through me!
Mon mignon prêt-à-porter!
What are you talking about,
you low-grade, mass-produced crap?!
It's not even worth
collecting data on you.
There's no end to them!
At this rate...
...we'll never reach the transmitter!
You just leave the transmitter to me!
You're alive, Senpai?!
Yes! Just to be safe, I was
wearing a titanium-steel
belly band made at my relatives' metal works!
It hurt, but the wound
isn't serious!
Don't act tough when
all you did was pass out!
I will atone for my shameful
behavior through my actions!
Shackle Regalia: Persona Unleashed!
SHACKLE REGALIA
PERSONA UNLEASHED
Behold the power
of my freed ego!
The shackles undone (bakukai)
and all pride cast aside (gouteki)!
Taste the wrath of Bakukai-Gouteki!
BAKUKAI-GOUTEKI
We'll take it from here!
If we Nudists don't strut our stuff,
we'll have gotten undressed for nothing!
You get undressed because
you like to, and you know it!
What?!
Impossible!
Your plan for the Cocoon Sphere Nativity
has come undone, too, Ragyo!
Have they, now?
Nui! Sacrifice your body.
Oui, Mama!
What the hell is that?
Nui, my poor daughter, the Life Fibers
in your body were too powerful,
preventing you from
ever donning Life Fibers...
But in the end, you were
able to wear them!
The ultimate dress that is
the Original Life Fiber!
No, Lady Ragyo,
you are wearing me!
Magnificent... You feel
so wonderful on me, Nui!
Of course I do! Still,
I'm happy that you think so!
Nui, leave the rest to me!
Hey, come back here!
I've determined Ragyo's objective!
Her destination is the REVOCS
communications satellite!
So Ragyo and Koketsu are trying to
hook directly in to the satellite
and broadcast the Absolute Submission
signal around the world?!
Yes, but since this is an awakening signal,
it can't render our Goku Uniforms powerless.
We will be able to counterattack!
Now...
Awaken, all you slumbering
Life Fibers!
Take on your original form...
...and cover this entire planet!
Shinra-Koketsu, Absolute Submission!
- It's begun?
- I'll go.
I'll go.
Ryuko! Let's go on a date!
Listen! When you get back,
let's go on a date!
You're making this a world
where girls can eat ice cream
and go shopping while wearing
a cute dress and cute accessories
and can wear whatever
clothes they like
and get all dolled up
without fear!
Without fear... without fear...
You're on.
It's in your hands now.
The survival of the human race--
for the sake of girls' fashion!
You can count on me!
I'm going to put on all
of your Goku Uniforms!
Senketsu-Kisaragi!
SENKETSU-KISARAGI
Beautiful...
Truly beautiful. This truly is
the Cocoon World Nativity...
What?
That's far enough, Ragyo!
Ah, I see.
You made a patchwork garment out
of all the available Life
Fibers to come up here.
But you are too late.
Look at the surface.
The signal has reached
the Life Fibers all across the world!
Humanity's conversion into
fabric cannot be stopped!
I can't give up that easily!
I have a date to go on!
You and your nonsense...
Chew on this!
What's the matter?
That Scissor Blade is also
made of hardened Life Fibers.
It is powerless before Absolute Submission,
which is master of all Life Fibers!
No way...
Still, you must be punished for the
sin of turning your blade
against this grand cloth
which is the equal of any god!
Ryuko, hang in there!
Yeah, I'm okay!
I'm still good to go!
My poor daughter who was entangled
in Soichiro's dying wish...
With all your power, why
do you not understand
the fundamental principal of the universe?!
Look, Ryuko, at that blue world.
At the shining sun! At the twinkling stars!
This is the cosmos.
But even this beautiful vista
will one day be destroyed.
Creation and destruction.
They have been preordained
since this galaxy was born.
The Life Fibers work in the same way!
They are part of the law of the universe!
When are you gonna
quit monologing?!
How can my very own daughter
be so dense?!
It ain't like I was
raised by you!
Oh, yes! That was a mistake!
It'll take more than that
to do me in!
I must be subconsciously
pulling my punches.
It would appear that I still have
a bit of humanity left within me.
In that case, I'll just
have to rid myself of it!
This ends now!
I'll decide my own ending!
I don't take orders from you!
Your regeneration speed
is accelerating?
The strength of your Life Fiber
compatibility is a precious thing!
If it's so precious,
how about going easy?!
Ryuko, this is bad!
We're running out of time!
I know... This will end it!
What is going to end?
Your life?!
You're the one who's finished!
What?
Did you forget?
The closer I come to dying,
the stronger I bounce back!
You... deliberately took
the brunt of my attack?
Yep. I gritted my teeth and took it
as a dose of tough love from Mom.
And I will until Senketsu and I
max out our growth!
Perhaps, but Life Fibers
cannot injure me!
Even if I absorb that
Absolute Submission field?!
Impossible...
Dad's ultimate weapon wasn't
some stupid Scissor Blade!
It was me and Senketsu!
What?!
It's the infinite absorption
ability he gave us!
I realized it during our battle
with Shinra-Koketsu.
The way I absorbed Life Fibers
was meant to nourish my power.
I am evolving.
I have free will, and I can make
myself understood by humans!
True, we're neither
human nor clothing!
NEITHER HUMAN NOR CLOTHING
But at the same time, we are
both human and clothing!
BOTH HUMAN AND CLOTHING
We are everything!
EVERYTHING
People can't become clothing!
People are people!
Clothing is clothing!
PEOPLE ARE PEOPLE
CLOTHING IS CLOTHING
What's this nonsensical
garbage you're spouting?
WHAT'S THIS NONSENSICAL GARBAGE
Nonsensical is our thing!
NONSENSICAL IS OUR THING
Listen up, all you Life Fibers!
People are people,
and clothes are clothes!
Turn all humans
back into humans!
They did it!
Yes. I am now free of the
past karma of the Kiryuins...
Impossible...
This can't be happening...
Everything is returning to nothing?
That's right, Mother.
The Earth will never be a Cocoon Sphere now.
Come peacefully back to Earth.
Pathetic.
I will decide how I die!
I will carry out your words first!
No!
Ryuko, this is not the end.
Life Fibers are continuing their
advance across the cosmos.
More will come to this world!
Of that you can be sure.
Even if they do, people
will go on being people.
Of that you can be sure.
Let's go home, Ryuko.
What's wrong, Senketsu?
Shinra-Koketsu's power appears
to be greater than I thought.
Wait, are you--
Hurry! There's not much time!
Senketsu, don't do anything crazy!
Coming from you,
who has done nothing but?
Senketsu!
Even so, this is fine.
I am sure that your father is satisfied.
I had a wonderful time, meeting you.
Idiot, stop sounding like
you're wrapping things up!
Don't cry, Ryuko...
The time comes when a girl
outgrows her sailor uniform.
From now on, wear whatever you want.
Clothing that is cuter than I.
You got it... I'll do that.
I'll wear clothes that'll
make you jealous!
Senketsu!
Snap out of it!
SNAP OUT OF IT, RYUKO!
RYUKO!
Ryuko!
Matoi!
Big Sis!
Welcome home.
Good to be back... Sister.
What'll happen to
the remaining Life Fibers?
The same thing as
the cloth-form Covers.
Once they're decoupled from people,
they'll lose their energy source
and eventually die off on their own.
Nudist Beach's purpose
is now complete.
We can finally get dressed?
Cleaning up this mess is going
to be a lot of work,
but that's a job
for us adults.
Those girls have a date.
THE END
KILL LA KILL