Class 7 Special Hazard Organisms.
Everything has been thrown
into chaos because of them.
Including your plan
to liberate Dorssia?
I was once asked by Captain Cain to secretly
investigate you since you're a formal royal.
Rejoice, H-neun.
X-eins' flesh will soon
belong to my comrade.
Bastard!
I think it's time for
a gun salute, don't you?
Was that... It can't be!
It is. It was Captain
Cain who killed H-neun.
I want to avenge H-neun...
I want to avenge my friend!
It's too much for them!
We'll make it, don't give up!
Oh, crap!
Carmilla?
It's Unit 4!
Miss Rukino's back!
We'll be okay now!
We're saved!
They say that Unit 4's back!
I hear Tokishima's with her.
Haruto? He's back?
Looks like we made it
back just in time.
Yeah. All that's left is...
Wow, this thing really took a beating.
That's not surprising,
after fighting a Valvrave.
Hey, are you okay?
I've got a survivor here!
Send some people over!
Let's get the pilot out of there!
I want to create a country where
humans and Kamitsuki can live together.
And to do that,
we need territory, huh?
Hey, it's going to take more than
land to make that work, you know?
All we can do right now is get things
underway one step at a time.
Even so, it's just not possible!
Not with just four Valvraves.
Module 77 is being guarded by
40,000 Allied Forces soldiers.
I'll go.
Don't get swept up in the excitement.
Think it through carefully, and—
I want a place where
I can belong, too.
Akira...
We can win.
L-elf is already
infiltrating them.
A simultaneous attack
from inside and outside.
Between us and L-elf,
this plan will work.
We can trust you, right?
Yes.
You can count on me. I'll get
our home back no matter what.
Switching places with an injured soldier
to infiltrate an enemy position.
That's the same gambit you used
in the New Guinea Conflict.
You weren't the one
who gave me this.
Why didn't you say anything?
If I had, would you
have believed me?
I no longer bear you any ill will.
That said, you are
an enemy of the state.
However, my beloved homeland is being
gnawed away at in secret by monsters.
And so, L-elf, I want you to
assist us with our mission.
Mission objectives?
The elimination of Captain Cain
and all parties related to him.
Our interests are aligned, I see.
I hereby sanction Special Forces
Lieutenant L-elf's return to duty.
Blitzendegen.
So, how much do you remember?
I asked Professor
Kibukawa about the Runes.
Our memories will fade away, right?
And in the end, we...
Everything's fine! I can still
remember everything just fine.
There's nothing to worry about.
Don't put on a tough
act, not to me.
Your "We'll win for sure" speech back there
was also to put everyone at ease, right?
Sometimes you have to
put on a brave face.
For others and for yourself.
Haruto...
Let's make a deal.
Neither of us gives up
to the bitter end.
If I don't give up,
will he also see how I feel?
What?
Forget it, it's nothing.
I have no idea what the outcome will be,
but if we give up, it'll never happen.
Deal.
I'm gonna borrow this, Senpai.
You always slack off when it comes
to defense, Yamada. You need it.
It ain't a problem! I punch them
before they can punch me.
And for the last time...
it's "Thunder," damn it!
Put some effort into defense, you hear?
Get off my case, man!
We're talking tens of
thousands of enemies!
I'm not sure if even the Valvraves
can win against that many, so—
My glasses...
Don't worry about me!
I'm coming back!
After all, I got new
friends now, right?
Thanks.
Is that enough?
Yeah.
You sure?
Um... It's okay, Akira.
Eat me if you want!
Akira! I shouldn't
have said that!
Akira!
You're such a jerk.
In regards to the disposal of the Kamitsuki,
the Council supports your plan.
I am of the opinion that surprise attacks
should be as sensational as possible.
Thanks to your plan, the public has
directed their rage at those students.
Plu, this will make it easier
to retrieve your sister.
We never would have known
of those artificial Magiuses
if you had not informed us
of the Valvrave Project.
You have our gratitude.
You have mine as well, Cain.
You rescued me when I was lost and adrift.
I'm sorry, Miss Sashinami, Professor.
I'm supposed to be the adult here, but...
Don't say that,
just get some rest.
Haruto Tokishima is coming!
He's asking for permission to land.
What do you want us to do?
He's come for revenge!
After what we did,
can you blame him?
Turn him away, Shoko.
But without the Valvraves
to protect us, we're as good as—
You've got to do something, Sashinami!
You're the prime minister, aren't you?
It's Haruto!
He's alive!
- I knew it, he really is a monster!
- Why's he here?
This is a ship for humans, man!
Murderer!
Shoko, I...
Thank you for saving us all
from the Allied Forces earlier.
That said, please restrict
yourself to this hangar.
As prime minister, I can't let you in,
not when I can't be certain you are not a threat.
I shouldn't have lied to you.
If I'd been honest with you,
even if it meant getting hurt,
maybe we could've found a way
to work through this together.
With that in mind,
I'm at least
going to expose the lies
of the world to you.
Expose the lies?
Of the world?
I don't get humans at all.
You don't?
That human was sitting
in here for ages, crying.
Saying, "I'm sorry,
Haruto. I'm sorry."
Sometimes you have to
put on a brave face.
Why can't we catch a break?
Citizens of the world!
This is a historic day!
Because on this day, our two countries, which could
not be said to have ever been on friendly terms,
have joined together in common cause
to exterminate the shared enemy of all mankind!
The nerve of him, making us
out to be the bad guys!
It's because the key to making people
get along is to have a common enemy.
Was it a good idea
to let them go?
We decided to trust them and wait, didn't we?
They said that if we went, we'd only get in the way.
It's all right.
They'll be back.
They'll be back, count on it.
Four Valvraves have
appeared on my scope!
So, they've come.
Harakiri Blade complete.
Let's move in to engage them up close.
Proceed according to plan. Deliver Unit 6
to satellite Nice 052 by 1950 hours!
We're here to act as her shield
and cut a path through these guys!
Inuzuka-senpai, I'm gonna
need your help on this one.
They're falling back?
Hit and away...
They're biding their time?
They know our
weakness all too well.
The Ardor Grips seem to
be doing the trick.
They're letting us fight without worrying
as much about heat management, but still...
Deploying in depth defense
formation per your orders, Captain!
Waiting for Valvrave thermal runaway!
This plan of theirs is
reckless beyond belief.
They can't possibly break
through with just four units.
I suppose not.
I'll let you handle this.
Captain?
Million to one shots do happen.
Besides, I want to dispatch Unit 1 personally.
Message from A-drei's Kirschbaum.
He says they are leaving to assist
in the defense of Module 77.
It's working. Inform the escort ships
in the front and at the harbor.
Three Valvraves are breaching
#8 defensive perimeter!
Is the Kirschbaum squadron on its way?
Haruto! Be careful!
You are leaking Runes!
What? But I still...
Shoko... Shoko!
Oh, no!
Haruto!
They have that many
humanoid types?
Leave them to me.
I'll scatter them!
The rest of you, go on ahead!
Don't! We have to fight together!
We made a deal to never give up,
remember? I'm going with our best bet!
Understood. I'll leave you
some Impact Boosters!
Thanks, Haruto.
I know that you guys can't use
that attack in quick succession!
Now you're stuck!
A second line?!
Valvrave Green is disengaging!
It has withdrawn
at attack speed 14!
So this was too big
a risk after all?
We'll enter the sea.
Keep going in that direction, and it will
take us to the heart of Module 77.
I know.
Our analysis has determined that they are
military weapons artificially created
by the leaders of Old JIOR.
There was likely a spirit of patriotism in
the environment that gave rise to such monsters.
But make no mistake!
We must place the love of humanity
as a whole above the love of any one state!
Our scientific ability progressed too far
and created monsters like them.
Aren't Haruto and the others there yet?
They aren't showing anything
about the battle on TV...
They can only be described as a threat...
Shoko!
I don't want to forget.
I don't want to forget, but I...
But I'm going to fight anyway!
Because if we run and hide,
there's no future for us!
L-elf!
Nice 052!
I'm latched on!
Now I can...
You're finally here!
Yamada?
Your shield!
Don't worry about that, just concentrate!
Nobody but you can do this job!
Yamada...
Senpai, keep Akira
safe, you hear?
Hey, you're good!
I'm having a blast!
I don't regret becoming
a Kamitsuki, not one damn bit!
I was able to get my revenge
and keep my friends safe!
It's the best!
Akira-chan! Hurry!
Even ARUS Splicers?!
Your ass is mine!
Sucker.
Yamada!
We're done here!
Hacking successful!
I did it! I did it, Yamada!
Yamada? Y-Yamada!
No! Yamada!
I can hear you...
You pulled it off, huh? Good deal...
See ya around, Akira.
My buddy Nobu gets lonely, see...
Put some effort into defense, huh?
I guess you were right about that, Otamaya...
Yamada!
L-elf!
He did it!
Now they'll see!
The wound, it...
It healed!
This can't be happening!
Don't show this!
What are you doing?! Hurry,
have them cut the transmission!
It's no use! The communications
satellite has been hacked!
We can't control it!
So that's what the Valvraves were doing!
I'll defend this transmission with my life!
Spread! Spread!
It's just like he said...
The truth of the world
has been exposed?
Next time, episode 24.
"Liberation Towards Tomorrow."
Valvrave the Liberator... The system that
will expose the truth of the world.