Sun       Mon       Tue       Wed       Thu       Fri       Sat
Training
Camp
VS Nekoma
All right.
I'm off.
Have a nice time.
Four more days 'til the
practice match against Nekoma.
In our matches from here on out...
That spike...
That receive...
They're going to be on our side!
It's kind of amazing.
All right. It's training camp time!
First-Year Class 1
Hinata, you're too restless.
Do you need to go to the bathroom?
Episode 11:  Decision
All here?
Yeah.
The practice match against
Nekoma is in four days.
Inter-High preliminaries
will be soon thereafter.
We've got no time,
but you guys are full of holes.
Since that's the case,
there's only one way for you to win.
Practice.
And practice.
Save the ball, even if you have to barf.
Yeah.
He barfed already.
Front, front.
Hey, how many does it take
for you to get it right?
Concentrate!
One more.
Here goes.
Nice receive.
Nice, Yamaguchi.
That's five successful receives. Next up.
Next!
I'm ready.
Good job.
All right. Spiking practice next.
Yeah.
All right.
Nice kill.
Looking good.
May I go next?
Sure, sorry.
Okay, let's get going.
Yeah.
Wow! This is where we're staying?
You need to calm down.
But this is my first time at training camp.
I have to hang all day
with this slovenly bunch.
What's so fun about that?
Tsukishima, you bastard...
Kiyoko-san's within a 500 meter radius of us!
How can that be slovenly?
How pitiful that you can't understand
how refreshing this space is!
It's like this wellspring
in the Ou Mountains.
Shimizu's home is nearby,
so she's not staying here.
What are you guys doing?
Take-chan...
We can't... go on...
Thank you for the food.
Seconds, anyone?
Yes, please.
S-Sure.
It's first-years' turn to bathe.
What's up, Hinata?
There...
There's a stranger among us.
There shouldn't be.
We're the only ones staying here.
It's...
...a child.
It can't be.
You must've seen your reflection
in the window or something.
Maybe.
I must've made a mistake.
Of course...
It was a mistake.
What are you screaming about?
Daichi-san will get mad.
It was just Noya.
Noya-san? B-But...
Noya-san grew shorter!
That's true. Your hair adds to your height!
Ryu, you bastard!
It's not funny!
Don't make so much noise...
Daichi will get mad...
It's me. It's Asahi.
You guys shut up!
You're stalling. Don't swing your arms.
Yeah. One more.
Nice, Hinata.
That's five successful receives.
All right. That's the whole rotation.
Next, running.
Yeah.
Hurry up, moron.
They sure have a lot of energy,
Shut up.
even though they have to train
during summer vacation.
I saw Kageyama jogging at dawn.
Oh, Hinata-kun was, too.
He said it's because there's no
mountain crossing at the lodge.
Mountain crossing?
That's why he's got all that stamina.
Are you...
...worried about picking members
for the match?
I'm undecided...
...about the setter.
In terms of ability, Kageyama is my pick.
Sugawara's is experienced and has played
with an ace since his first year.
However, Kageyama is talented enough
to surpass all that experience in no time.
Sugawara has been playing all this time.
His teammates depend on him.
Perhaps the reason why you
can't decide, Ukai-kun,
is because Sugawara-kun is in
his third year. Is that so?
The third year is his last year.
That's why you're thinking...
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm overstepping my bounds.
No, I think you're exactly right.
When...
...I was in my third year of high school,
I was a starting member only once,
when our younger official setter couldn't play.
I remember the anguish I felt,
that I wasn't picked to play.
But as long as I'm the temporary coach now,
I can't base my decision
on a player's feelings.
Hinata.
Don't yell unnecessarily.
It'll sap your strength.
Hey, where are you going?
Nobody's coming.
Did I get lost?
A bright red jersey.
You don't see those around here.
What are you doing?
Um...
I'm lost.
You're from out of town?
Yeah.
Is that thing fun?
Not really.
I'm just passing time.
Oh...
Are you a volleyball player?
Huh?
Those are volleyball shoes.
Oh. Yeah.
I'm in a volleyball club, too.
I'm Hinata Shoyo.
Kozume...
Kozume? That's your name?
...Kenma.
So you're Kenma. Are you in high school?
Yeah.
What year? I'm a first-year.
I'm a second-year.
Crap. You're older than me.
Pardon me.
Don't worry.
I don't really like that kind
of status stuff in athletics.
Oh, is that so?
Um... do you like volleyball?
Not particularly. I kind of just do it.
I don't dislike it,
but I don't like getting tired.
But my friends play, and they
probably can't do without me.
I think it'll be more fun
if you get to like it.
I don't care.
It's only while I'm in high school.
What position do you play?
Setter.
Really? You're a little
different from our setter.
Our setter is a little more... intense.
I'm middle blocker.
Wow...
Do you think it's kind of weird?
It's a position for tall guys.
I guess... but I don't think that.
I get told stuff a lot when I go to matches.
They say: "The setter position is for
the most talented player, so why him?"
Because I'm not very
athletic to begin with.
Oh... Is your team good?
Well, I heard we were good a long time ago.
But we fell into decline.
Recently, though...
I think we're pretty good.
What's your school?
Kenma.
Oh. Kuro.
Bye.
See you soon, Shoyo.
Don't go wandering off by yourself.
Sorry.
We're strangers to this place.
You have to be careful.
See you... soon?
Hinata.
Man, I was looking all over.
I'm sorry.
I was dashing, then got lost.
Hinata, you go all out
in every practice, don't you?
Yes.
But I still need lots more training.
I don't have enough strength yet.
It makes me mad I'm treated
as a set with Kageyama,
and not as a full-fledged individual.
Regardless, I want to play in the match.
I want to stand on the court.
Me, too.
I want to stand on the court, too.
So I'm going to fight
my own battles, my way.
Come on, or you'll be late for lunch.
Yeah.
Miyagi Prefecture
Tsukinokizawa High School
Don't you think their setter
is kind of small?
Yeah, and he's kind of unsteady.
Maybe he's a backup setter.
I've never heard of this school.
Nekoma
That unsteady shrimp
you guys are talking about
is the backbone of Nekoma. He's our brain.
And our heart.
Ukai-san.
What?
We third-years are done after this year.
That's why our desire to win
is double that of the others.
We want the ticket that will
take us to our next stage.
If it's Kageyama who deserves
that ticket more than me,
you should give it to Kageyama
without a second thought.
Daichi, Asahi, and I have been playing
together since our first year.
I'd like to stand on
the court with them,
and play as much as I am able.
If Kageyama gets tired,
or if something happens,
I want to fill that void,
or be a substitute.
Even if it's out of pity
because I'm a third-year,
as long as I get another chance
to play in a match,
that's all that matters.
I don't care if I'm not the official setter.
I won't give up my desire
to play on the court.
So I want as many chances as possible.
I'm sorry for being so presumptuous.
Sugawara.
I think I've been underestimating you.
To be honest, I'm amazed at you right now.
What?
I'm not an experienced coach yet, but...
I will do everything in my power
so you guys can go on winning.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I'm going to get fired up.
We'll win as many as we can.
Yeah.
Thank you for the food.
Where does that appetite come from?
Hey, eat. Eat even if
you can't eat any more!
It's midsummer. Just look at you guys.
You're eating more than usual today, Suga.
You'll shrivel up and croak if you don't eat!
You think so?
I'll eat a lot, and give it my all.
Yamaguchi, you're not eating that?
Hey! Let Yamaguchi eat his own food!
For the Nekoma battle, this
will be our starting order.
WS Sawamura        MB Hinata         WS Tanaka
WS Azumane   Li Nishinoya-MB Tsukishima   S Kageyama
It's a configuration you're barely used to,
so I'm not expecting you
to synchronize right away.
We now have an amazing libero,
and the ace has returned,
but don't rely on those facts
or think victory is assured.
Victory goes to the team that connects.
Let's see how this configuration works
in the battle against Karasuno's
long-standing rival, Nekoma.
Equipment room
Yeah.
Asahi-san.
I needn't mention Suga-san of course,
but you're probably
feeling sorry for Ennoshita-san
and the others, too, aren't you?
What?
The strong stand on the court.
That's how it is.
Um, Asahi-san.
I can't say I've always
been a devoted player.
There was a time I quit, even. So...
If they become stronger than
the ace in mind and body,
they will rightfully steal the regular
position out from under you, Asahi-san.
Right, Chikara?
Huh? I wouldn't go that far...
Or if a regular position were to be stolen,
maybe it would be Ryu's first.
You've got some nerve!
Throw the first punch, Ennoshita!
Nishinoya, that's enough!
You've made your point!
There.
Um, Ennoshita-san...
Hm?
What you said before practice...
Oh, about quitting once?
You've heard that Director Ukai
came back for a while last year, right?
Yes.
It's pathetic, but there were a few of us
who couldn't keep up with his training.
The club was just for fun 'til he came back.
Then it suddenly became a club
for the purpose of winning.
Those of us who were just casual players
got scared and quit.
But we still wanted to play volleyball,
so we decided to come back.
By then Director Ukai was already gone.
We're pathetic second-years,
but we came back.
So we want to do our best,
and not get left in the dust by you guys.
So we'll say it one more time.
We look forward to playing with you.
Yes.
Sensei.
All set?
Yes.
Washed, folded, and all set.
Uchisawa
Cleaning
It's the uniforms.
Wow...
Karasuno
It's the one I saw on TV.
Huh?
Here.
But only Noya-san's is orange. You stand out.
Thank you very much.
Of course. After all, I have the leading role.
Leading role?
The libero goes on and off the court
frequently during a match.
He's the only one that
needs to be noticeable. Idiot.
I know that. I totally know that.
Kageyama is one notch higher than me...
I knew he was going to say that.
Just be grateful we first-years
get to wear a uniform at all.
I know that.
Yeah, I guess you don't
remember that number,
because you saw it only once on TV, right?
Huh?
The Little Giant wore #10
when he went to nationals.
Was this your thoughtful idea, Coach?
Nope, just a coincidence.
Then, it's destiny.
It's a coincidence.
Don't be jealous, Kageyama-kun.
Why would I be jealous?
By the way,
The Little Giant that Hianata admires
played on the best team Karasuno's ever had.
But even then, Karasuno never
defeated Nekoma. Not even once.
It was one loss after another.
I want you to turn the tables on them.
Yeah.
Okay, let's start practice.
Nekoma must be very good.
What's their team like?
I don't know about now, but in the past,
the team has had very solid receivers.
It's not that they had outstanding players.
They just had no holes.
They were the opposite of our team.
They lived up to their "Neko" name...
They were flexible.
What the heck?
We spike and spike, yet the ball
never drops on their court!
Nekoma       Shirato
All right.
It's not like there's a genius player
among them, in offense or defense...
Why are they so good?
About our destined opponent, Karasuno...
Do they have a female manager or not?
I bet a yakisoba bread that they don't.
What? I'd prefer that they did,
so my bet is that they do.
Me, too.
Jackasses. We don't, so won't
it make you mad if they do?
Uh...
What if they had a beauty for a manager?
I won't ever forgive them!
I never will.
And if that's the case,
you'd better watch out, Karasuno!
Shut up, Yamamoto!
Hey, Kenma. What do you think?
I don't care either way.
I knew you'd say that.
But...
Huh?
I'm kind of looking forward to it.
Our match against Karasuno.
Kenma, who has no will to play,
is looking forward to a match?
Yamamoto, you seem full of energy.
You can practice double
the amount if you'd like.
S-Sorry.
Hey, Hinata.
They said it's our turn to bathe.
Hey. Don't get all worked up again and barf.
I won't barf.
I know it goes without saying,
but even if they can't play in the match,
I know they still want to play.
I'm only allowed to play
because of your toss.
It's frustrating, but I wouldn't
be allowed on my own merit.
I'm taking a bath and
going to sleep right away.
Damn you, bastard...
That was a false start!
Why must they compete to see
who can bathe the fastest?
They're morons.
I get tired just watching them.
Hey! Who's running?
Karasuno High School
Volleyball Club
Next Episode Preview
The match against Nekoma
is around the corner.
I must say, that pudding-head,
and that comb-head...
They're a bunch of unidentified critters.
Don't worry. They're not that tall.
That means nothing, coming from you.
Episode 12: The Neko-Karasu Reunion
Next time on Haikyu!!:
The Neko-Karasu Reunion