Mashima-senpai!
What's this atmosphere?
I can't lose...  I can't lose...
I will win...  I will win...
I'll beat Mashima
and make Class A!
Chihaya Furu
Episode 23
To
see
the
beautiful
cherry
blossoms
In order to restore my faith in this world,
I-I can't find my rhythm...
Emuro-senpai's being dominated.
While it brings me no joy, the
road beyond Mount Oe is too long
The two of them are on a
completely different level.
I'm moving my cards.
He's confident that he can win
his cards after moving them.
Against a strong opponent,
he constantly moves his cards,
so Emuro-kun is unable to get in a groove.
And his timing is always the worst.
The Queen is so fast that you
have to wonder if she's psychic.
No.
Wakamiya Shinobu is bonded to the
cards by a very unique rule.
What is that rule?
Hayashida-san, you are
recording everything, right?
Yes.
Machimura-kun, I need you to
capture the entire match.
Yes, ma'am.
Sakurazawa-san, are the
Class A matches almost over?
It looks like our captain's going
to lose to Wataya-kun from
Fukui's Nagumo society.
I'd love to know what
training you provided him.
Please...
You were a top player, and now
you're a top coach, Midori-chan.
Were there any other notable
players this tournament?
Yes...
Excuse me.
You shouldn't be sleeping here.
S-Sorry...
This injury happened when you were
playing our Yamashiro Rion, yes?
Are you okay?
I'll bring Yamashiro over to apologize later.
Oh, no.  It's okay.
Don't let Yama-chan...
Yama-chan?
Don't let Yama-chan know about this.
My coach said that, in most
cases, injuries are caused
by the player's own bad swing.
I need to practice more.
Wait, it's already dark out?
Where's everyone else?!
Wataya wins by 12 cards.
Yes.
Wakamiya by 14 cards.
As expected, the Class A final will be
Wataya Arata against Wakamiya Shinobu.
Oh, so we're the only ones left.
The other players must be tired after
playing in the team tournament.
I'm glad I was able to luck
my way into all those wins.
I just need my luck to help
me through one more match.
Wh-Why?
Ten minutes until we start?
No, hold on.
Why, Arata?
We're waiting for the other
Classes to finish up.
Why are you smiling about
playing the Queen?
Why?
I want to watch Arata play Shinobu-chan!
I need to secure a good spot up front!
Ayase!
Chihaya-chan!
How did everyone do?
Haven't you been checking your e-mail?
I lost in the Class C semifinal.
But Desktomu-kun made it to the final!
That's great!
And...
President Mashima's in the Class B final!
They'll both be playing on the first floor!
Let's go!
They're playing in different places...
Wait...
Is the Class A final between
Wataya Arata and the Queen?
Seriously?
Sorry, but I'm watching the Class A final.
What?
Aren't you going to do the same, Ayase?
What?  That's heartless, Porky!
The Prez is in an important match!
He's going to win.
He doesn't need us there to support him.
Desktomu-kun might need the help,
but Mashima is a different person today.
He doesn't need any support.
He's the one who
wanted Ayase to focus on
practicing for the Queen match.
He would tell you not to come see him.
Line up, boys.
Explain why none of the Hokuo
players made it past the Top 8!
A hundred flicks to each forehead!
I'll be in it, you fools!
Sudo-san, what about Retro?
He doesn't need it.
He lost to someone who he thought
was his rival by 18 cards.
He doesn't need the flicks.
Mashima...
I've never seen him like this.
He was completely different.
Mashima was completely calm in a match.
Are all players here?
The finals for each class will begin at 5:20.
Mashima-senpai,
you should get some
water now while you can.
You too, Komano-senpai.
The other club members are
really taking their time.
The match is about to begin.
Did Ayase-senpai fall asleep again?
Maybe she's not coming because
she's watching Wataya-san's match.
She's not coming.
Huh?
The Class A final is probably
between Arata and the Queen.
She won't be watching this match.
B-But...
Your opponent for the final is...
This sucks...
Why do we have to cheer
for Yamashiro-san?
This is such a drag.
She's the reason we lost the team match.
She guaranteed that we would win.
Everyone hates Rion.
It's because you're always
giving her a hard time.
Oh, well.  Nobody else is left to root for.
This was a bad year.
Who said that?
Excuse me!
Um...  Um...
I'll do my best to win Class B!
Please cheer for me!
The Fujisaki karuta club is strong
because we've delivered results every year.
Once the third-years are gone,
Ri-Rion?!
we'll lose most of our Class A players.
I have to win.
It's on you to make sure that we don't
lose a single match next summer.
I have to win all five matches
and bring home a victory!
I have to become a champion!
It's now time to begin the
finals for each class.
Good luck.
Huh?
Why?
This is the final...
What am I doing here?
Why haven't I been able
to defeat five Class B players in a row?
How can he be so calm
when we're in the final?
Excuse us.
Can you let us through?
Wha—
What are you doing?!
I'm positive that the Class A final
is between Arata and the Queen!
The two opponents you care most about!
Right now, I care the most
about Taichi making Class A.
I-I seriously don't get Chihaya!
His breath...
She's such an idiot.
I have to win this match
as quickly as possible.
I need to take a huge lead
so Chihaya can watch
Arata and the Queen play!
Mashima lost control!
Learning Center 2nd Floor  Urayasu Room
Wait, the room's already full?
Can't they squeeze together more?
We can't get in?
It's a good thing we only have the
Class A final in the Urayasu room,
since the Class B final has a lot of
Fujisaki students in the audience.
The Queen is certainly attracting
a lot of attention.
But...
The tournament's management is watching...
Eternal Master Wataya Hajime.
I used to play him all the time.
How will his grandson
fare against the Queen?
Is he capable of dethroning
Master Suo Hisashi?
That's me...
This brings back memories.
Shinobu-chan has a somewhat unique card
placement and memorization method.
She must have been playing with
these cards by herself all this time.
Ah, there you are.
I'll come get you.
Two more minutes of memorization time.
Arata.
The strongest karuta players are
those who faced the cards alone.
Let's make it clear once and for all.
Neither you nor I
need any friends.
Are you sure about that?
Ayase's an idiot.
I can't believe she's not watching this.
Let's begin.
Good luck.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
How well can you do against
the unbeatable Queen, Arata?
Here comes spring, now
the flower blooms
Wakamiya Shinobu has
the speed and accuracy
to take cards on the edge of her vision.
Here comes spring, now
the flower blooms
Since the dew atop the blades...
Who got that one?
The Queen.
As my love first came...
Who got it?
The Queen again.
So the Queen's dominating again?
Dominating?
Don't be absurd.
They hit both at the same time.
Her incredible speed in every direction
and her accuracy
haven't changed a bit.
Those are Shinobu-chan's strengths.
Arata, remember this well.
You break an opponent by
attacking their strengths.
Though my hatred has waned and the
tears have dried from my sleeves,
That was fast!
What just happened?
That was a perfect cross...
The Queen is so fast that
she can take "Though I" and
"Though my" on the first syllable,
yet he moved before the first syllable!
This reminds me of the nasty style
of karuta Master Wataya played.
Against the Queen, he's lost two
cards that they hit at the same time,
and now he's taken one of
her best cards with a cross.
The Queen knows that she must
be careful against him.
Defending every card is risky.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Today, I'll have to choose
which cards I can save
and which cards I can't.
Shinobu-chan, I'm taking you down.
Learning Center 1st Floor  Asahi Room
Said bed was cold...
Bah, a fault!
May the time spent...
A fault!
How many faults have they committed?
This is a mess.
What?
Mashima-senpai wasn't like
this in the semifinals!
It's like he's a different person.
Actually, this is what always happens
when his matches go wrong.
Damn.
I need to win this match quickly,
so Chihaya can watch Arata's match!
Ta-Taichi...
Fortunately, his opponent,
Yamashiro-san, is also struggling.
The reader isn't very consistent.
I wonder why.
Three certified readers!
Is this the reader's final exam?
for there is no one else out here
Excuse me.
H-He's definitely failed.
Win!
Your victory is a victory for Fujisaki!
Now that I think about it,
I've only ever looked at
the reader during a match.
He has no rhythm.
for there is no one else out here
His tempo is uneven.
But each syllable is very clean.
—the misty bridge...
This is the speed Chihaya barely beat.
She was like Master Suo.
Yama-chan's game sense...
Taichi...
Gust of wind...
Would this old palace courtyard...
What is it that she's hearing?
There are people who can hear
certain letters before the
sound is fully formed.
How am I supposed to play
against this kind of talent?
You can't let Yama-chan
get in a groove, Taichi!
You'll lose control of the match!
You'll start losing cards
you're supposed to win!
What am I doing?
I have to win quickly... I have to build
a lead before the Class A final ends.
How am I supposed to beat
someone who has talent
rivaling Master Suo?
Excuse me.
I'm tensing up because I'm
comparing her to Master Suo.
Compare her to Chihaya.
Excuse me.
I'm moving my cards.
He split all of the similar cards.
I've never beaten Chihaya,
not even in a practice match.
But...
In order to restore...
After I heard you say...
The similar cards he split!
He's winning three-syllable cards!
He got it!
—lent waves creep closer...
That was fast!
The emotions experienced...
The fall paddy shacks...
There's nothing flashy
about his playing style,
but he's taking cards against an
opponent with good game sense!
He's refusing to be drawn
into a battle of speed
and taking cards with accuracy.
Only one "My" card and one
"As" card on the field.
Go straight for them.
I have five "The" cards on my side.
I've split them up.
Stay calm if she attacks
on the first syllable.
Use the upper left.
Draw my opponent's attention here.
Keep my hand lower, lower.
If I cover the multi-syllable card at
my lower right, she can't take it.
When cards are split, go for
the opponent's side first.
I have a fifty percent chance of taking it.
Make sure my memorization is fresh.
Double check every card that's moved.
Unique syllables are
changing every moment.
Keep building and confirming
my memorization.
Give up on all of the one-syllable cards.
Doesn't matter if I look lame.
Eyelashes, karuta comes down
to talent and game sense.
However, at the same time,
karuta is about taking
10 cards from your opponent.
And keeping 15 of your own!
Forget winning by a lot.
By just one card is fine.
That one card is all I need.
I want to beat Chihaya one day.
Impassionate gods...
Thank you very much.
There's too much I'm lacking.
Rion doesn't have the
necessary stamina.
She's never won five matches in a row.
Mizusawa's leader performed well.
He's trained hard.
He's prepared to battle against talent.
Mashima by 9 cards!
I won by 9 cards!
Don't just stand there!
We're going to the second floor!
The Class A final isn't over yet!
The Queen and Arata are playing!
We have to—
You made it to Class A, Taichi.
Congratulations.