Oops!
Isn't this...?
You there, Rikka?
I am.
Can I come in?
Yes.
Sorry. I heard a noise, so I
thought you went out again.
The air is thick and heavy. Danger.
Defense turn.
I don't know what's wrong, but go to sleep.
We have to be up early.
At that time, I was still completely unaware.
I was unaware that Rikka was on
the verge of losing her power.
SUN BLOCK
Schwing! This year I have put up a barrier...
...to protect me from the
attack of the light beings!
What happened last year will be repeated!
EPISODE IX "Resort - Last Resort"
This place sure is crowded.
It's oozing with rotten commoner scum.
Enjoy your petty potato-scrubbing existences.
Ahoy! Togashi! Rikka!
THE NAPPING PLACE
Wow, this place is pretty big.
This cafe was named with you
in mind, Upperclassman Kumin.
THE NAPPING PLACE Beach Cafe
Hero!
Shichimiya! You're here?!
I invited her.
What?
The more reinforcements
the better. And besides...
Besides?
It's nothing.
I'll introduce you. This is my aunt.
Pleased to meet you.
Thank you for looking after Kumin.
These are all my friends.
This is Togashi and his little sister Kuzuha.
And these are Rikka and Deko.
Shichimiya and Mori Summer.
Mori?!
H- Hello, I'm Nibutani.
This brings back memories, Mori Summer!
We once attempted to summon a
siren at a beach just like this!
You just keep quiet!
Thank you for coming out all
this way just to help out.
My silly husband put his back
out. He is such a scatterbrain.
No, we should thank you for
letting us stay at your house.
I'm actually worried whether
we'll be any help to you.
Don't worry. We have all the things we need.
And besides, we never made much
money from this venture...
...so don't worry if we don't get customers.
I'm leaving it in your hands!
Yes, ma'am!
She is everything I expected your
aunt to be, Upperclassman Kumin.
Okay! Let's all get cracking!
Let's see. So here's the menu.
Shaved ice, juice...
Okay, I think I'll...
Big brother, you go over there
and do the prep work. I'll help!
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, then Shichimiya, Takanashi,
and the freshman will...
Do not order me around!
Leave it to me! Today, the devil is confined!
I am a magical girl working
for the happiness of others!
It's... It's Kyle.
Later!
Get your cold juice and shaved ice!
Get our special yakisoba...
...and all your boat and
inner tube rental needs here!
WELCOME
Mommy, I want to have that!
Behave yourself.
They're all very good.
What do you say?
We'll give you a freebie with your order.
Really?
How could we not, Lady?
You're too sweet to resist!
Oh, please!
She's always been skillful
at negotiating like that.
It's the truth.
Hmm, maybe I will have one.
This is a lifesaver!
What? Really? That's
great! Thank you so much!
Deko and the others are also working hard.
COLA
Your order is served! Dark
gunpowder discharge juice!
COLA
Your order is served! Dark
fried netherworld crustacean!
Don't change the names of the merchandise.
It will be ready shortly.
That's amazing.
Everyone said that her yakisoba was
good when they had it at our house...
...but I didn't know it was this good.
I'm going to help out a little.
Oh, thanks.
So, what exactly are you doing?
Done.
Dark Niflheimr Mountain.
What are you putting on that?
Dark breath of Kraken.
Squid ink?
Some call it that.
Don't give me that!
Stop playing with food and
work like the rest of us!
Excuse me, can I have a cappuccino?
Mom, I want the fried squid!
Squid again?
Why don't you give octopus
a try once in a while?
But I like squid!
You are Toka, aren't you?
Toka Takanashi!
Ow.
Do not shout out people's names like that.
So it is you.
You qualify. Want to come to Italy?
What?!
Please do not determine the
future of my little sister.
When did you arrive back in Japan?
You could have called.
It seemed like too much bother.
Is that the famous priestess?
No, she may be an imposter.
We cannot rule out the possibility
she is a detached separate entity!
You're wide open!
Master, are you all right?!
Toka!
Cute!
Um, who is that girl?
Who, this?
She's my daughter.
THE NAPPING PLACE Beach Cafe
What?!
She'll be seven this year.
S- Seven?
How old were you when you had her?
Let me think. I must've been 17 or 18.
Y- You are joking, aren't you?
I am.
It's an Italian joke. Surprised?
Why don't you laugh?
You can't laugh at that!
Your training manager's daughter?
Her name is Cento.
She nuts about Japanese historical dramas.
She demanded I bring her along
on one of my trips to Japan.
You're mine!
So that's why she talks like that.
Toka! What is that? Is her eye hurt?
No, she's just stupid.
Ooh, stupid!
That is the Wicked Lord Shingan.
It contains incredible hidden power.
The Wicked Lord Shingan is all-powerful.
Wicked Lord Shingan, I challenge thee!
I knew it. You are my foe.
This sword can drive out evil!
Try to block it if you dare!
It can drive out evil?!
You are an assassin from the Mage's
Association sent by the priestess.
I, Dekomori, am joining the battle!
For some reason, the conversation
flows so smoothly between them.
Here I come!
Look out!
I thought I was gonna be death-ed!
No! That's not how you intercept it!
You go like this!
Like this?
Surely that is an easy task with the
power of the Wicked Lord Shingan.
Actually...
THE NAPPING PLACE Beach Cafe
And she doesn't know how to answer?
Well, of course.
Okay. I, Sophia, will accept
that sword challenge...
...to illustrate the power
of the magical devil girl!
Who, you?
Hold it! Do not steal our thunder!
My master's Wicked Lord
Shingan is all-powerful!
It is not your place to interfere!
Isn't that right, Master?
What? Y- Yes, of course.
Master, show her how it's done!
What? Uh...
THE NAPPING PLACE Beach Cafe
Shouldn't you ought to step in?
She's up against a little
kid. She'll be fine.
I am coming.
My master can catch that blindfolded!
Give it your best shot!
W- Wait!
I will release my power so
you may know to your peril...
...the terror of the Wicked Lord Shingan.
Ooh, Master! Are you actually serious?!
I can witness the true power of
the real Wicked Lord Shingan!
A- All battles must be treated
seriously in any situation.
Dekomori, stand back and watch.
Come.
I am coming.
Be destroyed, real.
Blow up, synapses.
Banishment...
...Zuiss World!
Thank you for your hard work today!
I'm sorry it's so cramped.
Please don't mind us.
Mjolnir tornado!
Ow! What the hell?!
Mori Summer! Do you want this
hypnoworm I caught on the beach?
That's a wharf roach!
No, it's a hypnoworm.
Rikka?
You okay?
Yeah.
I see.
Well, I'm going to sleep over
there. See you tomorrow.
You aren't wearing your eye patch.
You never put it back on when
you took it off this evening.
Just rest up tonight.
INCOMING TEXT/NTOKA
Toka?
You're here as well?
You're late.
What is it that couldn't wait?
Well, I don't come to Japan very
often, so I thought I'd ask.
What do you intend to do after this?
From what I can see, not much has
changed since I left for Italy.
Rikka is still the same, and so are you.
I came prepared for all sorts of scenarios.
Prepared?
Of course.
I permitted my little sister
to live with her boyfriend.
True, but something did change.
Really?
She gave me a peck on the cheek.
And you're satisfied with that?
Nibutani asked me a similar question.
When I became aware of what Rikka sees...
...and what she persues, it made me think.
The elusive thing that she is pursuing...
...is probably the same thing I gave up on.
It's probably the same thing that I lost.
That's why I want to be around
to see what she does next.
I think that's what I like about her.
You're very easygoing.
Do you think so?
Yeah, it makes me sleepy.
Say.
Yes?
Are you disappointed? Or are you relieved?
Good question. I'm disappoint-elieved.
Be destroyed, real. Blow up, synapses.
Banishment, Zuiss World!
My power isn't working.
You look perplexed, Wicked Lord Shingan!
Shichimiya.
Let me guess. Is your power fading?
You summoned me the last time because
you couldn't fight then either.
No, that was merely a compatibility issue!
Don't try to fool me.
Not only are you losing your power...
...at times the Wicked Lord
Shingan fades into oblivion.
Tell me I'm wrong.
A little more drains away each time
you seek out the netherworld...
...at night with the power of the moon.
I...
I knew it. I was the same way.
That's why you invited me, right?
Yes! What'll I do?
You admit it?
But my power really is fading!
I sometimes forget about
the Wicked Lord Shingan!
It's tedious to contain
him! I want to take it off!
Then take it off.
Take it off, and trade your power
for a stronger lover's pact.
But I...
That may be what Hero wants.
Yuta?
I understand. I was the same.
Sophia.
Do you want to revive the Dark
Flame Dragon above all else?
Do you want to regain the power
of the Wicked Lord Shingan?
I am under contract with
Yuta from time immemorial.
I must.
The token.
I found it in Yuta's room.
Listen, Wicked Lord Shingan.
Let me see how you truly feel.
Show me your true power!
Then I will let you have this.
Sophia.
However, in order to revive
the Dark Flame Dragon...
...and in accordance to the logic
of the world and its natural laws...
...you need to be prepared to stay
the Wicked Lord Shingan for eternity.
No goodbyes are final, no
transitions are permanent.
Time passes in conformance
to the Samsara Corridor.
To accomplish this, you may be required...
...to obliterate your present
emotions towards Hero.
Just as I did.
Make your decision.
I will be waiting tomorrow morning.
What do I want?
THE NAPPING PLACE Beach Cafe
Time for another day's hard work!
Togashi!
Buy a bikini and we'll strip off 30%
Buy a bikini and we'll strip off 30%!
What do you think?
That's pretty clever, but...
We're gonna rake in the cash today!
Are we making all that?
They were raving about this so
much yesterday, we sold out.
Don't worry. I've put the
word out on the street.
THE NAPPING PLACE Beach Cafe
TAGS: GOURMET, LUNCH, FOOD
See? This is our big opportunity!
Don't you want to become the
best beach cafe on the beach?
Not really.
You lack greed, girl!
You're just like Togashi.
He's too easygoing. Too laid back.
Mori Summer is pumped up.
Yes, and Kuzuka likes to
take things in stride.
In stride?
She looks very determined to me.
You think?
Today I really will catch
that deep sea monster...
...and murdalize it once and for all!
Dekolumpy!
I am here, Dekolumpy!
Today, I am your opponent. Come at me!
It's you, priestess's assassin!
I will avenge my Master!
Hey.
Hello.
Is that all there is to your love?!
They're very perky first
thing in the morning.
Yes.
Come on, we have customers!
Oh, right.
Ooh! My master may need help!
Master, Dekomori is on her way!
Wait, you!
What's wrong? Is that all you
feel for the Wicked Lord Shingan?
Is that your definition of all-powerful?!
No.
Aren't you under contract with Hero?
Move it, lowly commoners!
This is not a show for your amusement!
Mjolnir Hammer!
Master!
Good god! Perfect serenity!
Now, are you prepared?
Are you emotionally prepared to force
the Dark Flame Dragon to manifest?!
I am...
I am who I am now...
...because Yuta was there for me.
Be destroyed, real!
Cherubim aria.
Blow up, synapses!
Seraphim, descend!
Banishment, Zuiss World!
Physical Linkage!
What is this?
My master's consciousness is flowing in.
Yuta once told me that
our contract is unique.
I will hesitate no longer!
Personal engine activation
confirmed. System released.
Pressure rising. Pressure increase,
connection within acceptable levels.
System all green.
Commencing core energy supply.
Lock bolt partitions one
through three released.
Bio energy injection. Commence EQ connection.
Wicked Lord Shingan reinstall
completion countdown.
3, 2, 1...
Rikka Takanashi, entering renewal mode.
Master.
Upgrade!
What?
Full armored Wicked Lord Shingan
Schwartz Crustacea is here!
I caused you all to worry.
I became dependent upon the
Dark Flame Master's kindness...
...and I was on the verge
of losing my own power.
I very nearly lost the precious thing...
...I only found with his help.
But I will never let it go again!
Yuta believed in me, and so
I will believe in myself!
I release the New Wicked Lord Shingan!
Super-dimensional Purgatorial Fascination!
The Wicked Lord Shingan
is gracefully restored!
Ooh!
The idiocy is spreading.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
That's Satone Shichimiya.
She's my childhood friend.
She's kind of like my chunibyo guru.
ITALIAN YAKISOBA VS JAPANESE YAKISOBA
- YAKISOBA EVENT (URGENT!!)
Can we really leave them to it?
Yeah. I think that they were
harboring feelings of rivalry.
Kuzuha may not look it, but
she has inner fortitude.
Really.
Torpedoed!
Aw, c'mon! Stop that!
Restored! The Wicked Lord Shingan!
New and improved, from
all-powerful to ultra-powerful!
Yeah, that power was amazing!
Now, accept this. This now belongs
to you, Wicked Lord Shingan.
Are you really prepared for it?
If you collect all three tokens and
revive the Dark Flame Dragon...
...you may have to live out your entire
life as the Wicked Lord Shingan.
Not as a lover.
No. Yuta told me.
The contract you and I are bound to...
...is not the so-called
lover's pact of the mundanes!
It is the lover's pact of
the Wicked Lord Shingan!
I will be the eternal Wicked
Lord Shingan, plus lover!
That is the ultimate form of the
contract between Yuta and I.
You can't do that.
I can! Yuta said we could.
He is certain we can fulfill this pact!
I see. So you can fulfill this pact.
I will back up your statement,
as a magical devil girl.
What is it?
I just felt a stabbing pain right here.
Maybe it's static electricity?
Oh, no! I will heal it with
the Wicked Lord Shingan.
And so, I stayed clueless
as Rikka regained her power.
And, still unbeknownst to me...
...something else had begun.
Yuta.
What if...
What if back then...
...I had taken your hand
instead of that token?
It could have been me.
Huh? Ow.
What? What?!
TO BE CONTINUED