Kochi kite hayaku! Kochi kite suguni!
こち来て早く! こち来てすぐに!
Hurry over here! Come over here now!
San-nin mou jishitsuwase
三人も実質わせ
We need all three of us!
Jugyou no ato de Sensei ni Bye Bye!
授業の後で先生にバイバイ!
Say "Bye Bye" to the teacher after school!
Taisou fuku wa motte kaeru
体操服はもって帰る
Get my P.E uniform and go home!
Koutei Shugo asobimasuka
校庭しゅご遊びますか
Wanna play in the school yard?
Demo demo datte iiwake shinai no
でも、でも、言い訳しないの
But but I won't make any excuses
Shukudai nante hottoko yo
宿題なんでほっとこうよ
Who cares about homework!
Tetsudaushu to mawarimasu yo
手伝う週と回りますよ
Take turns on clean-up every week
Rando suruwa sou akai tsuyoi
ランドするわ、そう、赤い,強い
Let's run a few rounds.
chiku chiku attaku
ちくちくアッタ
mitsu dara dete nijuukai mo yaru!
三つだら出て二十回もやる
If it's us three, then we can even do twenty!
houkago wa dashu!
放課後はダシュ!
After school, you dash!
Ah! Kore de wasurede genki dashite
あ！これで忘れで元気出して
And forget all about it!
Sen Nou!
セン、ノウ！
One, Two!
Anosaa, ochiro sono ato mawaru!
あのさあ、落ちろその後回る！
Drop down low and round you go!
Koutei Dai-shugo!
校庭大しゅご!
Schoolground big parade!
Watashi wa dare deshou?
私はだれでしょう？
Who the hell am I?
Tanoshii de mainichi ookiku nare ba
楽しいで毎日、大きくなれば
If you have fun and grow up everyday.
asobetaino, shiritai, shiranai, shiritai!
遊べたいの、知りたい、知らない、知りたい！
Do you wanna play? I wanna know, I dunno, I wanna know!
Tanoshii de mainichi chiisai na koto de!
楽しいで毎日小さいな事で!
Enjoy all the little things everyday.
warai aidara sore wa sore de ureshii
笑い会えたら、それはそれで嬉しい
Just seeing a smile makes me happy!
sore mou kore mou dore mou
それも、これも、どれも！
Like this one, that one, and that one too!
sanningoko setsuwase wow!
三人五個せつわせ！　ＷＯＷ！
Then it's the same whether it's three or five!
Our first Release!! Any Comments are welcome :D!
Come visit us at http://www.rave-anime.com/fansub/  !!!
Hi, everyone.
I've finally become a teacher at a Primary School.
I'm Yabe Satoshi and I'm new here.
I look forward to working with everyone.
I'm the Infirmary nurse, Kuriyama Aiko.
I hope we get along.
Ah!
My glasses...my glasses..
They're here, Kuriyama-sensei.
Ah..Thank you very much...
Y..You're welcome..
The Class I'm in charge of is Year 6-3
I can't wait to see what kind of children are in my class!
Marui Family! Good Girl, Bad Girl, Scary Girl!!
We're still doing this?
Yeah! It's do or die...
That's right, we just have to kill before we get killed..
Take this!!
There's no end to them...
This is...this is...
This is war!!!!
Well?! Who's next?
W..Wait a second..
Eh?
This..isn't supposed to be a war..
It's Nandemo Basuketto right?!  (Nandemo Basuketto = Anything-goes Chair)
Oh..so it's not this kind of game!?
Of course it isn't!!
Nandemo Basuketto is a game where you form a circle using enough chairs for all players, except for one.
The person without a chair is "it", he or she stands in the middle of the circle..
And...
People with glasses!
picks a theme, then everyone with that theme gets up and change chairs.
The next person that gets left without a chair is the next "it".
Nandemo Basuketto (Anything goes)
When someone says "Nandemo Basuketto", everyone has to change chairs.
Anyone that becomes "it" for three times gets a punishment! Sounds fun doesn't it?
By the way..the punishment this time is three times the homework!
It was just a game to start off the class with and it ended up like this..
But it's still too early to be surprised..
Why? Well that's because..
I..I'm ashamed!!
I tried to show my good side to you, but I got carried away!
I'm always living life to the fullest!!
I will reflect upon this!!
There's no need to kneel on the ground...but she sure is an honest kid..
Ha?!
You're supposed to kneel like..THIS!! Right?!
Wait!! What the hell are you doing?!
Oh that's right.. there's supposed to be another one..
Hey you..don't just sit out!!
In this class, there's three super-problem-childs..
Japan's Most Dissimilar Triplets..
The Marui Three Sisters!
Ok! Reflection finished!
Uwaah! I can see your panties!
Don't get up so suddenly!!
Aren't you guys supposed to be in reflection?!
I'm now reflecting on the color of her panties!
Marui Futaba (Second Daughter) Kinda-Perverted Muscle-Girl)
Ah! Found an empty seat!
Woah! Close one! Guess you shouldn't let your guard down..
Huh? who's it?...
That's weird..I'm sure I put the right number of chairs..
Oi!! Mitsuba!! Don't sit on your classmates!!!
Tch..He should be grateful that I let him be my seat..
Marui Mitsuba (First Daughter) Kinda Precocious Sadistic-Girl)
Even if he's grateful, you can't!!!!!!!
What an insolent dog...
I'm your teacher!!
What the hell!!! ;-;
Hey! That's not fair!
In a game, theres only winners and ME!!
W..Well then....people with tied hair..
Hey your hair's tied too!!
Oi!!
No Fair!!! Hey yabe-cchi! She's breaking the rules!!
Ya..Yabe-cchi..?
Oh right...
Hey now..you shouldn't cheat.
Ah! Lucky!
Umm..Hitoha-chan..?
Urghh..ignored?!
(BG: Feels Ignored)
Aww! Enough reading for now..confiscated!..
Eh..?
S..She's so strong!
Eeee...S.Sorry!! Um..I'm really sorry!!
Marui Hitoha (Third Daughter) Kinda Mysterious Gloomy-Girl)
Ehehe..Hitoha's "it"!!
Eh..I.It's my fault..
Well..what are you going to choose!
My friends...
Then..Nandemo Basuketto (Anything goes)
That's too quick!!
Oh!! I..I'm your friend!!
Haha..I'm "it" again eh?
Hmm..What should I choose...
Hurry up and pick!
Well then..Everyone with the surname "Marui"!
Allllllrightttttttttt!
Bring it onnnnnnn!
Why are you guys getting so serious?!
and You could be a little more serious!!
W.What's with this tension.. (atmosphere)
Ah! Futaba! Look theres a pair of boobies outside!
Eh?? Where where?!
Haha..how simple-minded!
Ha?! You tricked me!!
Uwaah..What's wrong, mit-chan?
Ah..What should I do..
Should I let her..?
B..But then I'll lose all my respect from her..
I'm going to show my dignity as a teacher!!
Ee..I'm sorry! Hitoha-chan!
T.This is!!
I..I'm sorry..
Uuu..Why am I doing the homework?
Am I really going to be okay as a teacher?!
Let's play together!!
Yeah! Be more like a homeroom teacher!
T.This is playing?!
Th..This..You guys are being strange!!
Ah..umm..Yabe-sensei.
Yes!
What's up, Kuriyama-sensei?
You sure are getting along well with your students!
W..well
Oh..What's that rope for?
Ah..I.It's my necktie!
Kinda looks more father-like..hehe..
That looks fun!
It's Romance!!
Those two..Hmm Can we do something to get them together?
Impossible..That guy's a virgin.
Huh? What's that?
Haa...a guy that's been living a sad life..thats what.
In that case..lets get Yabe-cchi to have a taste of that sweet nectar.
You're useless...hey, Hitoha..you think of something too!
Ohh!! She's got a bright idea!
Kuriyama-cchi is the school nurse..
Which means..
Ah!! I got hit between the legs!!
Oh no! We have to treat it quickly!
I'm so ashamed!
Ah..Ah!! What a yummy looking..Southern Sweets!
I'm so glad, Aiko...
No way!
It's love bound at the crotch isn't it!!
What kind of love is that?!
What are you girls talking about?
W.What are you doing?!
I missed..
But this time I'll get it for sure!
What are you doing..
I'm aiming for his crotch for the sake of his romance!
If YOU aim for it, there's going to be nothing left there!
Well that's alright too, but if I do it gently it'll be fine!!
Just like wrapping around something!
You're not convincing anyone here...
Wait..now's not the time for this!
Let's go!
Geez..I only have idiot sisters..
I'm the only one who's this reliable and cute!!
Besides..if you aim for a spot like that..
(Ahh!! Not so hard!!)
Th..That's n..not...love....Hee.heee..
Geez, That Futaba...
Ahh!! Even Hitoha-chan..What are you doing?!!
Be quiet!!
You're pretty nimble huh..
What the hell are you guys doing???!
Why are you guys aiming for my crotch?!
SO close!! I nearly got him!
We're gonna follow him!!
Wait up, Yabe-cchi!
What..What in the world..
Why's my crotch being targeted?!
Just give it up, Yabe-cchi!!
That's what you get for being an insolent dog!!
Nuuuuuuu!
It's all for your romance!
M..My Glasses....
Yabe-cchi!!
Well..It turned out alright!
Tch..That's so boring!! I had something planned too..
Come on, Kuriyama-cchi!
Eh?
This needs urgent treatment!!
Hurry up and take it off...
Eh?..well...
Sorry!!
So..What grade are you in?
Ahh!! She can't see properly!
Where are her glasses?!
Hmm..about 4th grade?
Waa...It's so cute!!
Let me touch it too!!
Ah! It's eating a seed.
Ahhh! His cheeks look so squishy!!
Class 6-3 decided to look after a hamster.
Well actually I was the one who bought it for them.
It would be nice if the children could learn the value of life and the joy of looking after something.
It's so cutee!!!
I wanna SQUISH him and SQUASH him into goo!!
Hitoha-chan, You seem to like him alot.
Well then, maybe Hitoha-chan can be in charge of taking care of him.
Sensei, what's his name?
He doesn't have one yet.
Hai!! Let's call him Boobies!
W-Why?!
If you close your eyes and touch him around his tail, it kinda feels like a nipple!
You're imagination is abit too good!!
Here Hitoha, try!
Nipples..
I think she likes that name.
Arghhh!! Perverted sisters!!
From that moment on, Hitoha-chan thoroughly cared for the hamster.
It feels as thought her gloomy aura has dissolved a little.
(A few days Later)
Yabe-cchi...umm...
(My) Nipples is feeling strange...
HUH?!
That kind of thing...I..I'm..
Ah...you mean that nipples...
He isn't feeling well..
He's not eating much and stays in his house all the time...
Hmm..maybe it's the change of surroundings and perhaps you guys are petting him too much.
Well, Don't worry about it too much, he'll get bette...
Ahh! It's not like it's your fault Hitoha-chan..
That's right! It's Mit-chan that has been stressing him out!
That's just a joke!!
It's alright, he'll get better soon!
Hey Nipples!
Are you feeling good? (Maybe put well lol, but 'good' is like kinda a joke? XD)
What's your problem?!
We're just checking on him!
No way! Futaba actually lost?!
I dunno..I guess the third daughter is actually the strongest..
Hauuu..I can't wait!!
Al..Alright, we get it!!
Hurry up and turn the page, Hitoha!!
Hehh..your class is taking care of a hamster..
Well, I bought it for them...
Oh?!...
Wh..What are you guys doing?!
Yo..You pervert-teacher!!
I..It's not what you think, Kuriyama-sen...!!
..You were hiding there all along?!
Well..what's wrong, anything you want to tell me?
(Board: I'll look after Nipples at my house)
..that's what she said...
That was just a mis-understanding right..I have to apologise to Yabe-sensei..
I want to touch (your) nipples more!
Eh..N..Nipples?!
You're kidding, don't just hog him!
We all want to touch nipples!
Yeah! I wanna see more nipples too!!
Well, (your) nipples aren't feeling too well recently..
It's because everyone keeps stroking it and pinching it too hard!
It's gotten too sensitive!!
It's all because you guys have been toying with my Nipples as you wish!
What do you mean yours?! It's everyone's!!
I've always been gentle!!
I want to see it grow bigger!!
But everytime you gently stroke Nipples, it seems to feel so comfortable!
Yabe-cchi.. Why don't you let everyone take turns looking after nipples?
That sounds good.
Hitoha-chan, try have a little more faith in everyone!
That's right, let me have a turn at your nipples!
Trust me with your Nipples!
Me too!
Everyone's going to protect your Nipples!!
Nipples!! Nipples!! Nipples!!
Everyone likes Nipples as much as you do. Of course, I like them too!
Nipples...
Nipples is standing up! (Getting erect LOL)
Your Nipples..Can I touch it?
It all ends well, right?
Class of perverts!!
Nipples are the best!! It's so soft! Ahh that looks ticklish!
Kotei ni yuuhi ga ochite
校庭に夕日が落ちて
The sunset reflected on the schoolgrounds.
te wo futte ie ni kaeru
手を振っていえに帰る
Let's hold hands and go home.
bedo no naka de mata konya
べドの中でまた今夜
Laying in my bed tonight.
kyou no kimi ni aitetara ii na
今日の君に会えたらいいな
It would be nice if I could meet you again.
ikou! Nemurou!
行こう！眠ろう！
Let's go! Let's sleep!
Asa made matte nai
朝まで待ってない！
I can't wait till morning!
totemo suteki sa
とても素敵さ
It's really wonderful,
sora motomeru no sa
空求めるのさ
just wishing upon the sky.
kimi to te wo tsunai de
君と手をつないで
Just holding hands with you,
Mune ga itaku nata
胸が痛くなた
makes my heart beat
Yume no naka demo
夢の中でも
Even though it's only a dream
Yume iro no Koi
夢色の恋
It's a lovely dream.
No way..This actually became an anime?!
That means my greatness will be shown on anime as well!
Next Time: "Can't stop the triplets!" Look forward to it!
I wonder why no one stopped them...