A date...
A date?  With who?
Shizuku.
Oh, you guys are together now?
That must be nice.
Make sure she has fun.
I know what to do during the day,
but what about at night?
Huh?
I'm not so sure about doing
it outside our first time.
Is that such a good idea?
Shizuku's the one who
suggested it though.
She's pretty brave.
Haru...
Just let me say this.
Your night plans will
probably shock Shizuku,
so you should reconsider.
Why?
Yoshida Family Matters
Revolt of Taira no Tadatsune        Bald with chest hair
Taira no Kiyomori,                Hot woman with a thin waist
Chancellor of the Realm
How have you been?
Well, we saw each other every day.
There you go.
Good morning, Haru.
Yo, Shizuku.
You're early.
It's the second term.
I was here at six.
Six?
I woke up when I realized
that I get to see you every day, again.
You never picked up the
phone over summer break.
Is he hitting on her?
All nonchalant?
First thing in the morning?
It was September and
still warm outside.
Second term was starting.
Good morning.
Are you sick, Natsume-san?
Yes, I actually have a fever,
but I forced myself to come to school.
Really? Don't give me your cold.
Don't make me sick.
Try to keep it to yourself.
Oh, Natsume-san.
I have pictures from the fishing trip.
Wait, are you doing trig?
Oh, let me see.
Wait, that's second-year stuff.
You're that far ahead, Mizutani-san?
I've been wondering...
When do you even study, Haru?
Aw, my eyes are rolled back in all of these...
Huh?
I don't.
Don't lie!
And why are these all pictures
of my swimsuit, Sasayan-kun?
How can you know the answers
when you don't study?
No, it's true.
I mean, I've already learned all
of the high school material.
Um, why are you laughing?
I didn't go to class in middle school.
I used all that free time to study.
I'm trying to be serious...
Feels like it's been forever...
Anyway...
A-About that date, is there
anywhere you want to go?
The library.
Y-You still want to study?
You never stop!
Japanese History
Good morning...
I didn't go to class in middle school.
I used all that free time to study.
Stop trying to pry.
How much is he willing to reveal?
Where does he draw the line?
I don't understand.
I want to stop by the
library on our way home.
Would that be considered a date?
Wow, he's so hot!
Wait, who is he?
Is he waiting for someone?
If he isn't, you should talk to him.
No, you talk to him.
Shizuku-chan.
I'm glad I caught you.
I was about to leave.
People kept looking at me.
What are you doing here,
Haru's big brother?
You can call me Yuzan.
Haru just disappeared a moment ago.
Bye.
Oh, hold on.
I'm here to see you.
I just realized that I should
have grabbed Shizuku
and left through the back gate!
Damn!
Huh?  Aren't you...
Hey.
Can you do me a favor?
Well, is he there?
He's not.
Are you positive?!
His hair is slimy as an eel.
Uh-huh, I don't think he's there.
Really?
Good.
Message to Class Representatives
Syoyo High School Student Council
Are you a class rep?
Huh?  Uh-huh.
That's awesome!
The class rep is the most
popular kid in the class,
who everyone looks up to, right?
Er, really?
I don't know about that.
I have a feeling I was chosen
because I wear glasses.
Glasses?
I see. That could work.
I don't know how I'd look
with glasses on, though.
Oh, um...
You'd probably look fine.
Huh?
With glasses on.
You're a nice person.
U-Um...
Then...
Something's come up.
Bye.
O-Okay!
It's been a long time
since someone said
I was a nice person.
In Japan, we have a tradition
of paying close attention
to the seasons.
I believe that tradition is
embodied in the sweets we make.
You know how they
say you can taste the seasons change?
For example, I like desserts
like cake with plenty of
whipped cream and tarts,
but in the summer, I prefer
mousse and gelatin.
They look a lot cooler.
Oh, speaking of cool treats...
I've only had it once,
but I still remember it.
It's a traditional Turkish
pastry called Baklava.
Pie crust covered in lots of syrup.
When you take a bite,
it melts in your mouth!
Yeah, I'm really craving
sweets after all that talking.
You've made me sick.
Didn't you want to talk about Haru?
Right, Haru.
Haru always says that he
doesn't like sweets...
Yeah, I can't hold myself back!
Can you wait here, Shizuku-chan?
I need to go buy something sweet!
He'll be here very soon.
I'm sure it won't take him very long.
This is your brother.
I'm having a drink with Shizuku-chan.
Isn't the weather lovely today?
Can you guess where we are?
Damn!
Where the hell are you?!
How am I supposed to know?!
I wonder what Haru's
big brother is up to.
Did he just want to talk about sweets?
Sorry about taking so long.
I had to wait in line.
I've always wanted to
try the donuts here.
There isn't one of these where I live.
Here.
So about Haru...
Oh, right.
Sorry about taking up
so much of your time.
Are you Haru's girlfriend?
N-No.
What?  You're not in
love with each other?
But you're together all the time.
Are you sure?
I told him I loved him, but he said
he didn't feel the same way.
You did?
So what did Haru say?
He loved me, but it wasn't
the same kind of love.
So I'll wait for him to
fall in love with me
before saying it again.
Well, I know what it probably is.
He cares so much about you that
he's scared of losing you,
or something.
It happens all the time!
All the time!
Good luck!
Also, you have bizarre taste.
So, let's get down to business.
I need Haru to quit school
and go back home.
You know that Haru's living with
Mitsuyoshi right now, right?
Huh?
O-Oh, yes.
Our dad is pretty strict.
He kicked Haru out of the house
before he entered middle school.
He was a pretty big troublemaker.
I don't know why Dad's
changed his mind,
but he suddenly wants
to bring Haru back.
So I was sent to convince
him to return.
Haru hates both of us,
so I can't get close
enough to talk to him.
Has Haru said anything?
Based on what Mitsuyoshi said,
Haru doesn't intend to return.
"Screw that!"
was his answer.
Well, there's no helping that.
So there you go.
I'm sure you'll be lonely if Haru
goes far away, Shizuku-chan.
Can you help me out?
Huh?
Um, I don't understand what you mean.
Didn't you come here to take Haru back?
Yep, but that's what our dad wants.
Personally, it would be
very inconvenient for Haru
to return now.
What?
If he comes back, we'll end
up killing each other.
What's that supposed to mean?
Dad and I both gave
up on Haru long ago,
but now he's actually
going to high school.
It sounds like there's
been a few incidents,
but he's still going to class.
Why is that?
Ta-da.
Because you're there.
Haru won't quit school
as long as you're there.
That's the only way
I can keep Haru here.
Well?  What will you do,
Shizuku-chan?
Haru!
Bastard!
What do you think you're doing, Yuzan?!
Sorry, I saw you coming.
It's been a while since
we last talked, Haru.
You doing okay?
I don't know what you and Dad want,
but I'm not going back now!
If you want to make me quit
school, go ahead and try it!
Let's go, Shizuku.
Haru...
Wait, Haru.
You should hear Yuzan-san out.
He said that he isn't
here to take you back.
What?!
Sorry, but I don't want
you to quit school.
I can't trust what he says!
That's a mean thing to say...
You stay out of this!
Now, now.
You should listen when your
darling asks something of you.
Plus, I didn't want to say this,
but if you keep running away,
she'll have to take your place.
Like today.
Fine.  Start talking.
I'll listen.
What do you want me to do?
It's very simple.
I just need you to promise
me that you'll go to school.
Huh?
Dad didn't think you'd
start going to school.
Now he wants you to quit
so he can enroll you in a
school he can influence.
But if you've learned how
to function in society,
there's no reason to
force you to come home.
I can convince Dad.
Well?  Sound like a good deal?
Okay.  I promise.
Huh.
Great, there we go.
Let's go, Shizuku.
Oh, uh-huh...
Don't let me see your
face again, Yuzan.
That was the plan.
But...
If Dad changes his mind again,
we'll have some
decisions to make, Haru.
Haru going far away...
I never considered that possibility.
Why were you with Yuzan?
Wh-Why was I with him?
He said that he wanted to talk.
Sorry.
I wanted to know more about you.
Don't go near Yuzan again.
Huh?
If you see him, run away.
I can never tell what he's thinking.
Got it?
I can't promise you that.
Why not?
You don't have the right
to order me around.
This is for your own good!
No.
Just listen to me!
I refuse!
I thought you said you loved me.
Y-You're going to bring that up now?!
Let's go home.
Yeah.
On our way home,
Haru shared some rare
revelations about his past.
I used to hang out with Yuzan.
We would play hero and such.
Yuzan would be the hero
while I was the monster.
Isn't it usually the other way around?
Really?
It sounded like he had
fun at Mi-chan-san's home
Mi-chan's crazy when he gets mad.
while he was skipping those
three years of middle school.
I almost died three times.
That's when Mi-chan's mom
brought a chimpanzee home.
Its name was Sayuri.
It was really cute.
Haru, do you actually want to go home?
Huh?
Oh, not really.
That place is a den of evil.
Hmm?  What is it?
I read that when people feel anxious,
they crave human contact.
Can I touch you?
What?!
O-Oh...
That's what you meant...
If you leave, I'll probably be sad.
However, if there's somewhere
else you'd rather be,
you should admit it.
Don't lose sight of
what you really want.
Yeah.
I want to be with you.
I can no longer remember
what I used to think,
or how I used to feel.
Hey, Shizuku.
Good morning.
Make some noise!
Sasayan!
Hey!
When did I
grow accustomed to seeing this?
Shouldn't you go home?
For some reason,
I feel like trying harder
when I don't feel well.
It makes me remember Haru's words
when he said he was scared
I would leave him.
I think I understand
what he meant now.
I don't want to lose him.
Huh?  Your face is red, Mitty.
Were you thinking about
something embarrassing?
Or did you catch my cold?
Yo—
Yoshida-kun!
Hey, class rep.
Thanks for helping me out yesterday.
The glasses were a good idea.
U-Um, so...
Th-Thank you for defending
me on Sports Day!
I-I missed my chance to
thank you yesterday...
I'm sorry it took me this long!
Okay.
Hmm?
Preview
It was a time of peace in the town of Edo.
Lines were being drawn.
In the capital,
an intense turf war between gangs
was brewing!
Let's party, boys!
Kill anyone who tries to
stop the Mizutani Clan
from building its school!
Yeah!
Why do they fight?!
We're gonna teach you to
fear the Yoshida Clan!
Sweet
Sake
Why do they love?
Ma'am.
Eat sweet and spicy foods
in equal proportions?
That's a fruity idea!
Fruit
is
sweet
Wait.
That was pretty clever.
A fruity pun about sweets!
Harunosuke!
Oshizu!
My Little Gangbanger
Opens Summer 2013
Opens Summer 2013?
Oh, it's from Yuu-chan.
Next Episode
Girls Feeling
Melancholy