The old man's missing?
What happened here?
Looks like someone broke in.
Maybe he was kidnapped?
Yukimura-sama? Are you kidding?
They must have been quite skilled
to accomplish this without us noticing.
By the way, has anyone
seen Rokuro this morning?
No.
I don't care.
Rokuro, too. This is serious.
Yukimura-sama was not kidnapped.
Yukimura-sama left at dawn.
He gave me a letter.
A letter?
"Good morning, warriors.
While watching the sunrise,
I suddenly felt the desire
to take a bath,
so I decided to take a
trip to the hot springs."
To thank you for all the
hard work you've been doing,
I'd like to invite you
to my private baths.
I've drawn you a map,
so come as soon as you can.
Rokuro and I will go on ahead.
See you at the hot springs.
Yukimura.
Hot springs, hot springs.
Hot springs?!
Rokuro's with him?
Then this room's a mess because...
He left suddenly without tidying up.
That old man's unbelievable.
Much Ado About Nothing
Everyone's been doing whatever the
hell they want since we got here.
Where'd Isanami go?
Delicious!
Miss, you've got quite an appetite.
She's far too relaxed.
If an assassin showed up now...
Kakei-san? What're you doing?
He is incredibly strong.
Who?
The dine-and-dasher.
When I tried to stop him,
he went berserk.
You're wrong!
I am a servant of the Buddha.
Therefore, my actions are
the Buddha's actions.
Men are meant to happily serve
sake and food to the Buddha!
What are you talking about?
You're just stuffing your face!
A servant of the Buddha is hungry.
Do you not wish to feed him?
What? Are you dim?
Just pay for your food.
I have no money!
That's not something to say out loud.
You are the definition
of brazen ignorance!
I bet you've been eating for free
all over the place, you bum.
I am no bum!
I am on a holy journey.
Behold!
I am searching for
my younger sister.
That's obviously a personal journey.
My name is Miyoshi Seikai Nyudo.
I have been traveling across the land
in search of my long lost sister.
I bet your sister's a monster.
She's not here. Go try somewhere else.
I see.
I'm surprised he accepted that.
Hold it right there.
I cannot let a brute like you walk free.
Kakei-san, you'll just
complicate things.
Stay and work to pay for your food
and the property you destroyed.
Pay for them with your own money.
If you had not been knocked off your feet so easily and broken the wall,
this never would have happened.
What did you say?
You are too weak.
I have had enough of your insolence!
Kakei-san.
I will show you which of us is weak.
Forget about this moron.
A warrior cannot allow
himself to be insulted.
I will beat some sense into him.
It is a sin to point
a gun at the Buddha.
You're no Buddha!
S-Sa-Saaya?
He bent a gun with his bare hands.
Wait a minute...
You named your gun, Kakei-san?
Watch out!
Tenbatsu!
That's enough, monk.
Obediently accept your divine judgment!
Cut the crap!
He deflected them with his muscles?
You must seek the wrath of the gods.
I will grant you your wish and destroy
you with the power of the Buddha.
Kakei-san!
Saaya, what did he do
to your beautiful body?
He's hopeless.
Rokkon Shojo!
Namu Amida Butsu!
You monster!
Looks like you're having fun.
Let me in on the party, Saizo.
You owe me one.
Kamanosuke, let go!
Huh?
Are you a friend of these heretics?
I will teach you the way,
so come down here!
Bastard.
You can't beat his strength. Let go!
Repent!
Ow.
You muscle head!
I told you to let go.
Begone, evil spirits!
You unscrupulous moron.
Where do you think you are?
They keep coming one after another.
What is this? Am I being tested?
That's it. I hear the voice of the gods.
I must overcome this obstacle
and improve myself.
Gods, I accept your challenge!
This guy doesn't make any sense,
but he's not someone to mess with.
My, my. What's going on here?
Ana.
I thought I heard fighting.
If you don't do something soon,
the inn will be destroyed.
Then help us.
No.
What?
I have an aversion to men like him.
Ana.
I bet he's slimy.
You...
I will handle this myself.
Unbelievable.
Knock 'em dead.
Come. Bring on the challenge.
What's all this racket?
Looks like our boys are here.
Looks like it.
Who is that monk?
He has a strange aura about him.
I shall attain Nirvana! Amen!
Kamanosuke, go for his feet.
Don't order me around.
Kamanosuke, now!
Don't order me around!
Not bad.
How can you be so laid back?
Looks like I was right after all.
They're already acting with
Saizo as their leader.
Die!
Otsumuji!
You moron! You can't do that here!
Gotcha.
Hannya Harami!
Idiot.
Heretics.
Gods, Buddha.
Get back, Sasuke!
Believe, and you will be saved!
Taizan Meido!
Sorry.
Your weakness is...
Give up.
You haven't got enough
muscles in your head.
Who're you gonna pray to
for help now, you turd?
Well done.
Hey, guys!
I won the dango eating contest, too.
I won a mountain of dango.
Jeez, you're loud.
You can each have...
Who is he?
That hairpin... Could it be?
Is that you, Isanami?
How do you know my name?
Who are you?
I'm... I'm your...
...big brother!
Who?
I've been looking for you, sister!
Oh?
My dango!
You may not touch Isanami.
What's wrong with a brother
hugging his sister?
Right?
You pervert!
Absolutely not!
What are you doing hugging
someone you just met?
I thought you said you didn't
have any living relatives.
I don't know this guy.
I wasn't lying.
Besides, we don't look anything alike.
What's the big idea?!
You're too close!
Don't get too close to men!
They'll sully you!
Who are you to tell me what to do?
I'm your brother!
No, you're not!
You made me drop all my dango.
No, I...
Isanami.
Right?
Yeah.
I told you, you're too close to him!
No!
If you're really my brother,
stop attacking them.
They're all my friends.
Oh, okay.
And what do you think
you're doing, anyway?
You look like a common thug.
It's embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
Yeah. You should be ashamed.
Okay.
Fix what you broke.
Once you've cleaned this place up,
I'll at least listen to your story.
R-Really?
All right!
He really will do anything for his sister.
If that's the case,
let's get this place cleaned up.
You guys help, too.
Don't be ridiculous. Do it yourself.
Let's go. We'll wait at the hot springs.
Yes, sir.
Hey, are you all right?
I'm not sure I should wake him.
Come on, hurry up.
Sure thing. Your brother's got this.
But damn...
I'm surrounded by freaks.
Isanami and I do not look similar
because we are not related by blood.
We were both orphans raised
by the priest at Izumo Shrine.
The priest...
By the way, I found you under the
torii when I was eight years old.
You're kidding.
You don't seem to be a threat,
but you certainly don't look like a monk.
I left Izumo at fifteen
to travel the country.
After learning the various
teachings on the gods,
I arrived at one conclusion.
All gods are the same.
The more you believe in,
the more you will be saved.
You have no principles.
What was that, heretic?
It seems you haven't seen
each other in quite a while.
How did you know it was Isanami?
I knew as soon as I saw that hairpin.
Isanami is the only priestess
of the Kushimitama.
He's serious.
But I really don't remember you.
Considering how strong I have
grown during my travels,
it is not surprising you
do not recognize me.
This is what I looked
like when I was fifteen.
My brother! I remember now!
You finally remember.
Let us embrace!
No!
Why?
I understand. This must be fate.
If you wish, you may serve me.
Thank you.
Yukimura-sama brought that
slimy-looking guy with him.
Hey, I can kill that guy, right?
Right?
Now this is impressive.
Oh, thanks.
Take your time.
It's not bad, is it?
How about a drink?
That'd be great.
There's food, too.
This place has everything.
Didn't I tell you?
I'm rewarding you for your hard work.
This is amazing.
I haven't had a bath in six months.
Go rinse off before you get in.
Purify me!
Are you sure you belong
in the men's bath?
Quiet. I'll finally confirm my
suspicions with my own eyes.
I'd never bathe with you guys.
I don't need your bath.
The river's good enough for me.
Oh, well.
Was there something you
wanted to see, old man?
You and Kakei are no fun.
Speaking of Kakei-san,
I haven't seen him since we got here.
He just left.
He left?
He said he wanted to travel
the country and train again.
And he's got to get his gun fixed, too.
But he left so suddenly.
He knows how to take care of himself.
He's a samurai.
Maybe he won't come back.
I'll deal with it when it happens.
He's only working for me until he can
find a master who can give him more.
A man is happiest...
...when he's risking his life
for someone he loves.
That's how we are.
Sounds like a line used to keep
your subordinates in line.
Your followers won't always
fall in love with you.
You're too much for me, old man.
What the hell is this hair?
Where'd this come from?
Sasuke!
You bastard, don't let
your animals in the bath.
Why not?
They're filthy! We're eating.
They are not filthy.
This is their territory.
There is no problem.
There's people in the bath
right now. Get them out.
I refuse. Yukimura-sama
gave me permission.
What?
Hey, old man!
The marks are gone.
What was that?
No... No more...
Ana, aren't you getting in the water?
I don't really like hot springs.
What?
Why are our bodies so different
even though we're both girls?
It's not easy having big breasts.
It gets so hot under
my boobs when I sweat,
and they make my shoulders sore.
Are you bragging?
Of course not.
It must be easy having small boobs.
I wish mine were big!
What was that?
This steam's too much.
Would you like some cold water?
Oh, that sounds...
The steam's getting in the way.
Yukimura-sama!
Having fun, Isanami?
You pervert!
Don't worry. I'm not interested in you.
Isanami!
Did you call your brother?
What do you think you're looking at?
W-Wait, Ana. I just...
Iga Ice Technique!
Gokuhyokan!
Yukimura-sama!
Sir.
I'm not staying in this cold bath.
This is no fun.
I thought there'd be more to get my
blood boiling if I stayed with Sanada.
That bitch always gets in the way
every time I try to fight Saizo.
What are you doing?
I thought you were taking
a bath with your friends.
I'll do what I want.
What are you doing?
It's got nothing to do with—
Did you really go bathe in the river?
I like to keep clean.
You're freezing. Are you stupid?
Your nose is bright red.
We can't warm you up since
Ana froze the baths.
Don't be ridiculous!
I'll be the one to kill you.
Remember that, damn it!
You're telling me now?
What is this? What is this?
Why am I getting so worked up
even though he didn't do anything?
Wait. Calm down!
That's it.
I'm just frustrated because I
haven't been fighting lately.
Damn it. Why do I feel like this?
Amaharu.
Amaha—
Damn it!
I'm so pissed!
Amaharu?
I've finally calmed down.
Amaharu.
This is Saizo's fault.
It's because he touched my hair.
I've never felt that before.
Such a gentle and warm touch.
I don't think of him as my friend.
Saizo's not like that.
I don't want to be his friend.
All I want is to fight him.
I know that feeling.
That incredible ecstasy.
I want to experience that with Saizo.
He's the only one who can give it to me.
But that feeling just now...
...was something totally different.
I don't get it!
Wait, what are you doing here?
Amaharu. My...
Amaharu?
Oh, this?
He feels nice, doesn't he?
Can I kill and skin him?
No!
My head's pounding.
You stayed in the bath too long.
No, it's probably because,
after Ana froze me,
you punished me with your own ability.
What shall we do?
I'll have to go.
You'll come with me, of course.
You want me to go?
This will be a long journey.
Invitation
You want to summon everyone so
you can show off your power, huh?
Sounds like that old man's...
...finally ready to do something.
Fine. Let's see...
...what Tokugawa can do.
To the capitol.
Ana, what are you doing? Hurry up.
No. He just walked by.
What?
Ana, Saizo, what are you doing?
The party's getting started...
Isanami, calm down and walk—
Why is this hallway so slippery?!
I told you he seemed slimy.
Seikai, wipe down the floor!
The next episode of Brave 10
is “Sword and Fan.”
Sword and Fan
Bring it on!