Kanda-kun, two letters came for you.
Thanks.
Wh-What is it?
Aoyama-san, you wear contacts?
Huh?
I forgot I was still dressed like this!
Kanda-kun, don't look at me!
Why just me?
Nanamin, you look cute with glasses!
Let me see you! Let me see you!
No, Senpai! Please stop!
We're both girls, so what's the big deal?
Well? What are those letters about?
It's fine! It's fine!
Oh, right.
No! The boys are watching!
Kanda Sorata-sama
"Let's Make a Game!" Screening Committee Member
Then, should we continue this in your room?
Or maybe in the bath?
Neither!
Okay, let's do it outside!
What?!
You need some surprises in your life!
No surprises, no life!
I passed...
I passed the first screening!
"Let's Make a Game!"
Instructions for Candidates Who Have
Passed the Initial Screening Process
They want me to go and do
a presentation on the 31st!
Really?!
You did it, kouhai-kun!
He did it, Nanamin!
You're so soft, Nanamin!
Good job, Sorata.
Get off me already!
Yeah!
So, what's in the other one?
Teach me about love.
What is this?
Do you know about love?
Teach me about love.
#08 Set Off a Huge Firework
Sorata.
Teach me about love (koi).
I knew it was you!
Koi are freshwater fish
that live in lakes and rivers.
The value of decorative koi
depends on their markings,
and expensive ones can
go for millions of yen.
I see.
No, you don't! You actually
wanted to learn about fish?!
Sorata.
Make my heart pound.
Don't say that so nonchalantly.
Make my chest tighten.
I can't handle such huge responsibility.
Fight.
You try showing some fighting spirit!
Anyway, why are you suddenly
so interested in love?
Ayano told me:
"The best way to learn how to write
about love is by falling in love."
She said that anyone could write
one love story in their lifetime.
Your editor doesn't have any trouble...
coming out with embarrassing
statements, does she?
There's a meeting to pick out new
serializations on the 31st.
The 31st?
Sorry, but I've got a
presentation that day.
Instructions for Pitch Presentations
for the Second Stage of Screening
A presentation?
My presentation for the "Let's
Make a Game!" competition.
I passed the initial screening,
so I need to prepare for it.
I'll help you.
No thanks.
They're both on the same day, huh?
Let's both do our best.
Mashiro!
You're in a boy's room
without pants on again.
You can't do that.
Why not?
Well, because...
Because boys are perverted creatures.
Don't act as though I represent all boys.
Come on, hurry.
Not yet. I still haven't
learned about love.
No, it's not like that!
You saw this, didn't you?
Shiina's editor told her to find out.
B-But that doesn't mean
mistakes won't happen.
What am I, a brute?
Let's just go.
How can you...
Kanda-kun has to prepare
for his presentation.
You'll get in his way.
I'm not bothering him.
Huh? I mean, she isn't
getting in my way, but...
But?
She's not bothering me.
That's fine, but...
But?
Why are you trying to
pick a fight with me?
I'm not picking a fight...
That's right!
I'm the one who's going
to fight kouhai-kun!
I think pudding is a beverage!
At least stay on topic!
Listen, that's why pudding
shakes are evil!
Hey, Nanami.
Nanami, do you know about love?
Sorata-sama has logged on.
Kanda Sorata: Akasaka, do you have a minute?
Maid-chan
Ryunosuke-sama is currently
deep in contemplation...
about what would happen if
you opened both doors...
of a two-door refrigerator
at the same time.
I see. In that case,
you'll do, Maid-chan.
Do you have any advice on
how to do a presentation?
In that case, you'll do, Maid-chan.
Do you have any advice on
how to do a presentation?
Maid-chan
How should I punish you
to death for suggesting...
that anyone would do (lol)?
You answered your own question!
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Wear a suit. That is all.
You're there suddenly?!
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Also, practice your presentation
skills with the residents of Sakura Hall.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Fortunately, you have plenty of
unique individuals here to test them on.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Also, practice your presentation
skills with the residents of Sakura Hall.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Fortunately, you have plenty of
unique individuals here to test them on.
Ryunosuke-sama has logged off.
That's all?
Do you need any help?
Yes, please.
Let the training begin!
Kouhai-kun Training
Uh, due to this system, um...
I believe that it wouldn't
just be core users...
who'd enjoy this game; it would
attract a lot of new players, too.
20 minutes, 53 seconds.
That's too long.
I tried using Fujisawa Kazuki's
award-winning pitch as a template.
Explain it so there's clear progression
from introduction through conclusion.
You're not acting like your usual self,
and it's not interesting at all.
Your choice of words
is a little awkward, too.
You're including too many elements,
so it's hard to tell what
your main point is.
Kanda-kun...
I'll try improving it tonight!
Please listen to it again tomorrow!
He's serious.
You can do it!
If it goes well, Nanamin says
she'll give you a kiss!
No, I won't!
On the cheek.
Where isn't the problem!
My concept is simple and fun...
No, simple as well as...
No, exhilarating...
Shiina, what are you doing in my room?
Designing characters.
Why are you doing that in here?
If I do it here,
I feel like I'll understand
what it means to love.
Should I leave?
No...
Do you want me to leave?
If Aoyama finds you, she'll be annoyed.
Then, I'll stay.
Huh?
You always think of Nanami first.
What are talking about?
Never mind.
Well, whatever.
Take care of yourself
The sun rose and set again.
After rewriting my presentation,
I made everyone listen,
and then, I'd rewrite it
and practice again.
Red Brick Road Shopping District
After repeating the
process ten times...
I greeted the morning
of my decisive battle.
Okay!
Sorata.
Victory
Where did you get this?
I went yesterday.
With who?
I looked it up, asked some
people, and walked a lot.
Did you go by yourself?
Sorry. You'll find out if your work's
going to be serialized today.
I'll be fine.
See you later.
I'm off!
Entry: Kanda Sorata
School/Employment: Suimei University of the Arts
Kanda Sorata-san, please begin.
I-It's a pleasure to meet you!
Fujisawa Kazuki!
Can I ask you something...
before we jump into your presentation?
Huh?
What do you think you need
to do to become a creator?
Uh, um... w-well...
I need to tell him something.
Something...
Um, uh...
I can't do it.
My mind's gone blank.
Evening Fireworks Display
Starts Today!
That's what I'm thinking.
N-Next, um... u-uh...
Hey, you're Kanda's kid!
What's with the getup?
You're looking sharp.
Are you going on a date?
N-No...
Hey, what's wrong, kid?
Kanda Sorata-san...
Kanda-san...
Kanda-san.
Y-Yes.
I regret to inform you that
your pitch has been rejected.
Sorata.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
How did the meeting go?
I'm going to be serialized
starting in November's issue.
I see.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Well, you'd better start drawing.
Please go.
Sorata...
Don't stay here. Go draw.
Please go.
But...
Shiina...
If you don't, I...
This isn't the way forward.
I'll start to...
He was rejected, huh?
Well, it's not an easy world to enter.
He was prepared for that.
Yeah, but...
Are you worried about
him, Nanamin? Kiss...
I won't!
Okay!
Let's throw a welcome
party for Aoyama-san!
What?
I agree! Good idea, Jin!
That's a nice idea!
Hold on! Why would you suggest that?
Today's the only day it could be.
In that case, I've got just the thing!
There's something I've been
saving for a special occasion!
It'll start at six! Everybody had better be here!
Wh-What? Wait!
Presentation Materials
"Let's Make a Game!"
Instructions for Candidates Who Have
Passed the Initial Screening Process
Treasure Chest
Kouhai-kun!
Hey, kouhai-kun!
It's finally here!
The fateful day mankind
has been waiting for!
Hey, which one do you like best?
What's all this?
Underwear.
What?!
Just kidding. They're swimsuits.
Oh...
Why's your reaction so different
for underwear and swimsuits?
It's a mystery.
Stop thinking about that.
Why are you scattering
swimsuits all over my room?
I figured we could have a pool
party to welcome Nanamin!
Now?
Let's go, kouhai-kun!
Me, Nanamin, Mashiron and I will
all be waiting for you in our swimsuits!
Splash!
You mentioned yourself
twice, didn't you?
Anyway, are pools even
open at this hour?
You're forgetting the school pool.
Hey! You're not suggesting
we sneak in, are you?!
It's okay! Jin...
I ran the idea by Chihiro-chan,
so there's no problem.
...said it's okay!
Really?
Wait, Senpai!
I don't want a welcome party...
Good timing.
Pick one out for yourself.
Or would you rather I chose for you?
What's going on?
We're throwing a welcome
pool party for you!
What?!
Nanamin, which one do you want?
Kouhai-kun said he likes this one.
I didn't say anything!
Kanda-kun?!
It's not me you're
supposed to be fighting!
Your enemy is this alien!
You should go with a string bikini.
Mitaka-senpai!
Jin-san?!
That's enough from both of you!
I haven't even said I'm
going yet. Besides...
Presentation Materials
I'm not going to the pool.
Hurry up and clear these away.
What?
Let's go, Nanamin and kouhai-kun.
No. School starts tomorrow.
Yeah, exactly!
We can't end our summer vacation
without wearing swimsuits!
Yeah, yeah!
I see...
Huh?
Let's go.
Let's go to Aoyama's
welcome pool party!
The sea is calling me!
All right.
You should warm up first.
Where are Aoyama and Shiina?
They should be done changing soon.
U-Um, how do I look?
Too plain.
Mitaka-senpai, I'm not asking you!
What?
No, don't say anything!
I think you look good.
Really?
I-I know it's not as bold as
Kamiigusa-senpai's...
but this is the most I can manage.
It's my first time
wearing anything like this.
I didn't know what I'd
do if I looked all weird.
No, it looks really good on you.
You're speaking with
a Kansai accent again.
Sorata.
Do I look weird?
Wh-What do you mean?
Sorata, you idiot.
You complimented Nanami.
Okay, okay. It looks good on you.
Really?
Yeah.
Kanda-kun?
Take this!
Kickboard cutter!
K-Kanda-kun?!
Kanda-kun?
Huh?
Why you little...
Let's go, Aoyama-san.
Let's jump in.
Huh?
Hey, wait!
Killer Niagara Tub Falls!
Let me practice my aim.
You idiot!
If you're going to cover
anything, cover your boobs!
Oh, come on!
I can't get it undone!
I declare this territory
Kouhai-kun Land!
Give them back!
You pervert!
That was terrible...
Here.
Pool parties are all about
wardrobe malfunctions!
No nip slip, no life!
You brought this all the way here?
Come on, kouhai-kun! Eat up!
You can't have a Sakura Hall
welcome party without hotpot.
Curry-flavored.
Thanks for the food.
Hey! What are you kids doing here?!
Run.
That was quick!
Mitaka-senpai, you said
you got permission!
There's no way the school would
give us permission to do that!
What?!
I knew it!
Just hide!
I'm gonna go change!
Hey! Where'd you go?!
Come on out!
You pool thieves!
Splish, splash, making a racket!
Th-This situation!
Don't move, Kanda-kun!
Shush, quiet.
No matter what happens, don't look up!
No matter what!
Don't move, Shiina!
A new charm.
The embroidery is prettier
than the last one.
Easy Delivery
Thanks.
Now! Run for it!
I thought you'd be sadder.
I am sad.
They're beautiful!
Fireworks?
Shiina?
Don't stop running, Sorata.
That man has a scary look on his face.
Huh?
You kids!
You're from Sakura Hall, aren't you?!
Enjoying your youth with
no regard for anything else!
You won't get away with this!
Oh, man...
I'm starting to have fun!
You can cry, you know.
I won't cry. I'm not you.
What?! What's your problem?
I'm just trying to...
Being all serious about
something is crazy, isn't it?
When I came home...
and heard that Shiina's work
was going to be serialized,
I felt like I had been rejected.
I felt like my heart
was going to shatter.
Because I was serious about it,
I couldn't hide from my
regrets or my frustration.
But that's why it's so easy!
You've just gotta do it!
The only way to get rid of
these feelings is to do it.
Even if I fail over and over,
I just have to do it.
When I thought of it that way,
I started having fun!
What are you talking about?
You're a masochist?
It's better than being considered normal!
Spoken like a true resident of Sakura Hall.
And now you're one of us!
I like people who have goals.
I like people who try their hardest!
Huh?
N-Nothing!
You two are too slow!
Let's race to see who
reaches Sakura Hall first!
What?!
What?! I'm starting in last place?!
I can't believe you didn't bring...
your underwear to the pool, Nanamin.
Just forget that already, will you?
So future generations
will remember this...
let's call this the No Panties
Nanamin fireworks welcome party!
Don't call it that!
Don't remember weird things!
Don't worry. It was just a little
run without any underwear on.
That's right! No panties,
no life! Here!
Please stop saying "no panties."
Do you want one?
Mashiro...
What?
I think I understand a little...
about love.
Hello. I'm Rita, from England.
#09 The Fall Storm is Here
Sukiyaki and sushi are delicious.
Hey, hey, look at me!
I'll impersonate a boss.
Hey, you. Feel like flying north?