Rei Kiriyama
Zero? What a weird name.
But it suits you.
Isn't that right?
You don't have a home.
You don't have a family.
You don't go to school.
You don't have any friends.
See? There's no place for you in this world.
TAKABASHI
SHOGI HALL
The calm mind is the way.
How have you been, Rei?
Sure is hot, huh?
We're not even in the rainy season yet.
JS CHILDREN'S
SHOGI TOURNAMENT
Well, what am I saying.
It's a time like this and all I can do
is comment on the weather.
JS CHILDREN'S SHOGI TOURNAMENT
Well, let's begin.
CHILDREN'S SHOGI TOURNAMENT
There's nothing.
Nothing.
I lost.
You've gotten better.
Are you eating properly?
You left so suddenly...
Ayumu and Kyouko are worried about you.
That's a lie.
Next stop: Tsukishima. Tsukishima.
New Message: 1
Inbox
Hinata Kawamoto
From: Hinata
Title: To Kiriyama
Good work today!
We're having
curry tonight,
so come over!!
We'll be waiting
See you! \(^o^)/
*Hinata*
For: Hinata Kawamoto
Re: To Kiriyama
Thank you for
the invitation.
However,
I'm feeling
under the weather
today, so I think
I'll stay h...
New Message Received
Akari Kawamoto
Oh no, Rei
We're having curry,
but we don't
have any
pickled vegetables!!
Could you please
buy some at the
convenience store
on your way over?
Eggs, too!!
Thank you!
SUMIYOSHI SHRINE
Rei is here!
I bet you're tired. Dinner's ready!
Rei, hurry up! I'm hungry!
Rei, did you get ice cream?
Hey, Momo!
I bought ice cream, and pudding, too.
- Ice cream!
- Pudding!
Hyay!
Hina, you too?
Milk pudding!
ZOOM
Oh my, you bought all this?
Thank you.
I'll make room for the ice cream!
BLOOMPH
But I'll pay you back for it.
This must've been expensive.
Don't worry, it's a gift.
But sorry, I didn't know which one to get,
and ended up buying a lot.
Me is happy with this.
Oh, that's right. How did your match go, Rei?
Akari said it was an important match
for your club.
I won.
Oh, that's great!
- Sis, feed me! Please feed me!
- Feed me, feed me! Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Oh, I'm falling! I haven't had anything
but water since yesterday!
That's a lie.
Ah, not when I'm holding the pot!
Hina, feed the kitties!
And please set the table!
Okay!
Sis, Rei said he won!
I see.
So good! Nummy, nummy, nummy!
All right, let's eat.
Hold it, Hina! You're putting curry
on the altar as an offering?
Oh, I shouldn't?
But, Mom and Grandma loved curry.
But still, putting curry...
But they did really like it.
Well, I suppose it's correct.
Momo loves curry, too!
Mom, Grandma, tonight's curry has pork in it!
Well, everyone, shall we eat?
Thank you for the food!
Put egg on Momo's plate, too!
Yes, yes. I wonder
if you can finish a whole egg?
Sure I can!
And now our next story.
On the 16th in Hibiya City, police found
the body of Shizuo Unagawa in his home
bludgeoned to death by a blunt instrument.
His eldest son Tadashi,
a second-year university student,
who had been reported missing,
was arrested.
According to the authorities,
Tadashi is suspected of murdering
his father by beating him
with a hammer dozens of times in the head.
Suspicion of beating his father...
It's unfortunate for Mr. Kouda.
His league entrance after all this time
was riding on that.
And to think his own son
would beat him so easily.
Although maybe he was satisfied after all.
...with a hammer dozens of times
in the head.
Well, that's only if he was his real son.
Every move...
...felt like I was punching
with my bare hands.
It's so vivid, it's like I can still feel
the warmth of the skin that I hit.
Dad...
Rei, what's wrong? Are you cold?
Are you all right? Maybe you have a cold?
Want something warm to drink? Like milk?
Zoom
- Emergency! I'll warm some up for you!
- Uh, um...
I'll bring medicine, too!
Um... Sorry.
That's all right.
You don't have to eat everything.
Just take your time.
But you should eat a little.
Okay.
Hey!
What, the boy's sleeping already?
Talk about rude. Ate and nodded off, did he?
He laid down after he finished eating,
as if he passed out.
How'd his match go?
He won, apparently.
But he was pale when he got here.
And he only ate a little bit.
Yeah, can't blame him.
I bet he couldn't get any sleep
last night either.
Well, let him rest here for the night.
I'll go back to the shop and sleep there.
Tomorrow's bean roasting day.
Don't forget to lock up.
Right. Goodnight, Grandpa.
We'll help you stuff the pancakes tomorrow.
Yeah, please do! Alright, good night.
I brought you a blanket.
He left his glasses on.
Goodnight.
Rei Kiriyama.
That's my name.
In a small town by a big river
is where I'll be living.
Rank C-1, 5th dan. Seventeen years old.
Profession: pro shogi player.
Rei Kiriyama
The Town Along the River
STARE
O-Owl?
No, it can't be, right?
A magnificent white owl wouldn't just
show up at somebody's house.
And plus it's standing on the tatami mat floor...
You're a cat, aren't you? I think...
Oh, no! I'm gonna be late!
Good morning, Rei!
G-Good morning!
ZOOM
- Here!
- Ah, yes!
BED HEAD
Please stir it!
- E-Eggs too, please!
- Y-Yes!
BLUNT
Well, I woke you up like I said I would.
Let's go, Momo.
- I'm getting up now, don't worry.
- See you later!
Even though Sis woke me up...
...why did I fall back asleep?!
I'm gonna be late! But this is delicious!
Oh no, I don't have time.
But one more bowl!
What? You're gonna have more?
Rei, take this!
Your lunch! It's a little big, but I pressed it
together tightly, so it should be okay!
Th-Thank you!
And this is a strange side dish as a whole,
but it's good!
BA-BAAAAM
GRASP
Th-Thank you!
I have morning practice,
so I have to go! Take your time!
Ehhh?!
U-Um, what about the key?
Here! Please lock up when you leave!
Thank you!
W-Wait a second, if I have your key,
you won't be able to get in.
Don't worry, we'll find a way in somehow!
BAAAAM
GONG
But, that's wrong.
SILENCE
STARE
I guess I'll try going...
...to school.
Huh? What the heck, Kiriyama?
That's a huge rice ball.
Or a soccer ball?
- Mr. Hayashida.
- You're lucky to have rice.
I'm broke until the end of the month,
so this is all I can get.
So Kiriyama, do you guys get paid monthly
for your matches?
Or do you get paid right after each match?
Monthly.
They make bank deposits at the
end of the month for all matches played.
I've been following you online.
You've been on a winning streak,
so you must have a lot of matches.
Let's see, the Kiryuu Tournament, the Jeweled
General Tournament, the Rookie Tournament...
One, two, three...
Hey, Kiriyama.
I don't want to think about it, but...
...is your monthly income more than mine?
Dammit!
CHOMPALICIOUS
I'm not going to eat lunch with you anymore!
What?! Actually, I never asked you to...
If you don't like it,
hurry up and make friends here at school!
I'm an adult, so I'm really busy!
Even though he became a professional during
middle school and considered a genius,
here, he's just a 17-year-old
with issues like anyone else.
I wonder what he's thinking about.
MIKAZUKI-DOU
Welcome!
Oh, Rei! Welcome back!
Was the rice ball good?
Perfect timing.
Can you help us with something?
I'll tie the ribbons on,
so could you put six in a box, and stack them?
Ah, sure.
That'd be a great help.
Go ahead and wash your hands first.
EGG / CHUNKY
Three each of egg bean paste
and chunky bean paste.
Got it.
CELEBRATION
Cute wrapping paper, isn't it?
It's not printed, right? It looks expensive.
Actually, Hina made it. Surprising, huh?
It's potato print.
I carved up sweet potatoes
and stamped them on. Cute, huh?
They're for Grandpa's calligraphy teacher friend,
who's celebrating his 70th birthday.
The big 7-0.
"Spirited Away"
All right. Who did this one, I wonder?
He taught Hina for a little while
when she was in elementary school.
Me!
So this is her present to him.
Hahaha, I suspected it was you, Hina.
Someji is very fortunate to have
grandchildren who are willing to help.
That's right. Someji is a lucky fellow.
What are you talking about?
The little one tags along annoyingly,
and she's so loud I can't stand it.
Grandpa, look! I folded it myself!
That's amazing! Origami, huh?
You're so clever, Momo!
Sorry. Grandpa is a bit of a softie
when it comes to his grandkids.
Just a bit, huh?
Well, I'm off to deliver all this.
After that, I'm staying for the party,
so take care of everything else. Bye!
MIKAZUKI-DOU
Well, shall we go?
Rei, you'll eat dinner with us tonight, right?
Thank you. But I'll be going home tonight.
I have another...
another match, so I'd better practice.
- Oh?
- You have a lot of matches. Good luck.
Good luck!
Also, thank you for the rice ball.
It was delicious.
Then here. Our baked "Crescent Moon."
Just out of the oven, so it's really good.
Well, goodnight.
Come over anytime! We'll be waiting.
- Goodnight!
- Good luck!
It still hasn't come.
Is this what you're looking for...
...Rei Kiriyama?
Mr. Rei Kiriyama
MATCH NOTIFICATION
CHUB
CRISP
To Be Continued
Next Episode Preview
Episode 2
I see...
Kiriyama prefers cup noodles
over the food Hina and I cook?
Don't put me off like that, Kiriyama!
We're friends, aren't we?
Oh, it's Rei!
Help me, Hanaoka!
I found Rei!
"March Comes in Like a Lion."
Don't miss the next episode.
I'm counting on you.