Zombie House of Terror
It's time for your shot.
Come Down to
Syoyo Festival!
Come Down to Syoyo Festival!
Come visit class 2-D's Asian Cafe!
Want your fortune told?
Welcome!
Come visit our house of terror!
Zombie House
of Terror
Honest Pricing
Haven't seen you in a while.
Yeah.
We got three customers.
Please come this way.
It's time for your shot.
What are you doing, study bug?
There's a step, so please watch your footing.
It's time for your shot.
Why do you keep talking about shots?
Hey, are you listening?
This room used to be...
Uh... And now, you can
see the former owner
walking around in search of blood.
Fountain of Love
Make a Wish
Hey, this nurse isn't even trying.
Boobs
500 yen to enter
Why is she dressed like a nurse?
Goodbye.  Best of luck to you all.
Man, she's starting to tick me off.
Just kidding!
Yo, Haru.
What was that for?
Hey!  How'd you like my blood spray?
How are we supposed to pick up chicks now?
You have to introduce us to some chicks now.
Chicks?
Oh.
I'm going home!
I lost control of my emotions and yelled at him.
In hindsight, there was no reason for me to get upset.
I just have to change your mind.
But... Haru was so casual about it.
When did I become so indecisive?
I used to be firm in my decision making.
Great People of the World
Because my decisions were always right.
If...
I were still alone,
would I be doubting myself like this?
I like cultural festivals.
Don't you, Mitsuyoshi?
What are you up to, Yuzan?
Hmm?
You promised not to show your face around here.
But I heard that Haru was up
all night working on this event.
Red Bean Donuts
100 yen each
Excuse me, can I get two red bean donuts?
You bet!
When I pictured how upset he would be
if I were to show up,
I absolutely had to come!
Then don't bring me into this.
I'm just kidding.
I doubt that.
Yo.
Hello.
What are you doing?
Me?  I'm on my way out.
Bye.
This school is too big.
Is he lost?
You could have asked someone for directions.
I don't like asking other people for help.
Okay.
You're the one who's lost.
Oh, there you are.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Yamaken-kun, want to join us?
You've got it totally wrong!
Nagoya
You're supposed to introduce us to some girls!
Not a rooster!
How've you been?
Sorry, I was worried about him.
Nagoya
And what's this all about?
There are a lot of creeps in this world.
So I made this to keep people away.
I named it Mizutani Shizu—
Don't use my name for that thing.
Hey, Yamaken!
Where'd you run off to?
He got lost behind the school building.
I wasn't lost.
Haru, Sasayan-kun needs you to go back.
Why were you with Yamaken?
Co-Coincidence?
Why won't you look me in the eye?
Hey, Haru.
Don't be so forceful with a girl.
It's pathetic.
What?
Let's play pretend-Zelda!
Hey.  Wait a sec, Shizuku.
I get to go next!
You told me not to touch you without permission,
so why don't you say anything to him?
Huh?
Er, I'm not...
That's obvious.
She doesn't mind my touch,
but she can't stand yours.
Get away from Shizuku!
Not so fast.
Whoa!  Haru just socked the study bug!
That was brutal!
Oops.  My bad, Shizuku.
It was an accident.
Say you're sorry, Haru-kun!
The hell? You're out of control.
You need to say you're sorry!
This is all your fault!
What?  You're gonna blame me?
Haru.
Huh?!
From now on,
stay two meters away from me at all times.
Mitty!
Wait!  Please wait!
Are you mad?
He didn't mean to hit you.
I'm not mad.
Whoa!
I just think it's stupid to let him influence my life.
He's like a spoiled child:
arrogant and selfish.
So why can't I break free of him?
I-Is she asking me for advice?!
W-Well, you know what they say...
You can't end a relationship that easily!
Everyone's always looking for that best-of-only-one!
Haru is fixated on me because
he doesn't want to be alone.
Huh?
I happened to be someone
who was easily accessible.
Mitty, you don't trust Haru-kun?
Nobody wants to be alone.
It only makes sense to care
about the people you're closest to.
Don't you feel the same way about Haru-kun?
I do.
But Natsume-san...
That's none of your business.
That study bug is so cold.
This is all because Yamaken had to provoke Haru.
Huh?
How is this my fault?
Hey, shouldn't we go comfort her?
No, it's a bad time.
Mitty, you don't trust Haru-kun?
Why would she ask me that?
Hey.
Take this.
I don't want the blame for
what happened to your nose.
It was clearly your fault.
Poor kid.
Haru's all alone again after pissing you off.
Again?
Want me to tell you why
you can't break free of him?
You heard that?
Because of the expectations you have.
Because his words and actions
fulfill some of your own hopes.
That's why you can't break free.
You want him to meet your expectations,
but you never meet his.
That's cruel, Mizutani-san.
Ice
If you refuse to give me my
personal space, I can't be with you.
That's none of your business.
Did I hurt them?
What?
Are you feeling lonely after
chasing everyone else off?
Except that I've always been alone,
and I've never felt lonely.
Stupid.
You can't feel lonely if
there's no one else around.
That makes sense.
You're smart.
Huh?
Yuzan-san?
Did you...
Huh?
What is it, Yuzan?
Oh, it's nothing.
O-Ow...
Damn, why is he here?!
You know Yuzan-san?
Both brothers used to go to Kaimei Academy.
Huh?
You're scared of Yuzan-san?
Stupid!
Nothing scares me.
I just had a traumatic experience.
Your pride will be your undoing, one day.
Lay off.
Yamaken-kun, get off me.
Just to be clear, I don't feel
even an itch for you!
Hmm?  What are you talking about?
Hide!
Wait, wait, wait!  What?
Oh, it's a girl.
Um, wait.
Yo-Yoshida-kun?
Dammit!
That slimeball didn't keep his promise!
Huh?  Er, what?
Was that the slimy hair
person you mentioned before?
Man, today just sucks.
Oshima.
Would you be unhappy
if I said that I like you?
Huh?
What?!
Wh-What should I say?!
Every time I tell Shizuku how
I feel, things only get worse.
I think I have to resort to force.
Oh...
You keep telling her how you feel...
There you have it.
Do you have anything to say
about that, Mizutani-san?
No comment.
I-In that case...
If I told you that I like you,
what would you do?
Th-That came out of nowhere.
I think you're pretty swell.
Y-Yeah, thank you,
but that wasn't what I meant...
I meant that in a...
...female attracted to male kind of way!
You mean to do it?
You want to do it?
Let's go.
No, not like that.
We shouldn't be listening to this conversation.
Hold on now.
I was thinking something more platonic...
Things are getting interesting.
Wait!
Yo, Haru.
Why are you guys here?!
I see.
You tried to give Shizuku-chan some advice,
but she gave you the cold shoulder.
Haru is fixated on me because
he doesn't want to be alone.
It felt like she was reading my mind,
so I came out a little accusatory.
It was the first time she'd
ever confided in me, too...
But you were angry, right?
Nothing wrong with throwing a fit.
If girls get in a fight,
it's over between them.
Natsume Asako is finished.
No, you're not.
It comes down to how badly
you want to be friends.
Don't be scared.
Sh-She's the first friend I've ever had.
I don't want to let her get away.
That's the spirit.
Good girl.
Spunky Zombie House
But I'm not going to apologize.
Oh, there you are.
What are you doing, Natsume-san?
You're pretty stubborn.
Why are you crying?
It's a long story.
Hey, baseball boy.
I didn't know you were here.
Are you by yourself?
No, I'm with Yuzan.
I was about to leave.
Come on, Haru.
We have an audience now.
Shut up!
Stay back!
Do you want to cause another scene?
Haru, are you really willing to hurt that girl?
Haru!
Poor thing.
Are you okay, Oshima-san?
Uh-huh.  Thank you...
Sorry about my little brother.
Huh?  You're brothers?
Perfect timing.
Shizuku-chan, I wanted to—
Excuse me.
She's busy showing me around.
Oh!
Aren't you the Yamaguchis' son, Kenji-kun?
You're all grown up now.
Here you go, Shizuku-chan.
Haru left his shoes behind when he ran away.
Can you give these to him?
I'll take you back to your classroom.
Oh, okay...
Hey, you forgot part of your costume.
Oh, thanks.
I'll see you around, Shizuku-chan.
Oh, there you are.
We've been looking for you.
What are you doing with the study bug?
Nothing.
Out of my way.
Smells fishy.
Bye, Mizutani-san.
Shut up.
Okay...
If you feel bad, you should
start thinking before you act.
I screwed up again.
I made a mistake.
Yes, you need to reflect on your mistakes,
since you're stupid.
But...
I'm just as stupid.
I keep making mistakes.
Didn't you say to stay two meters away?
Sorry, can I take that back?
I realized that it was
pointless to establish rules.
Oh, you finally came to your senses?
Who do you think you are?
I'll go apologize to Oshima first.
Uh-huh.
Once you've recognized your mistakes,
it's easy enough to correct them,
I think.
I'm sorry.
You were just trying to offer some advice.
My reaction was unwarranted.
I wanted to apologize.
I-I'm...
your friend and Haru-kun's friend.
It's not none of my business.
Yeah.
You're right.
Oh, whatcha doing?
Ah!  There you are!
Spunky Zombie House
You guys need to get back to work!
Sorry about making you wait, Haru.
He's asleep...
Oh, it's you.
Don't scare me.
You scared me.
What were you trying to do?
Huh?
I was going to touch your hair.
Huh?  My hair?
I don't understand you!
You say you don't love me,
but you act like you do!
Then you tell me to stay away.
Do I have a chance or not?!
Wh-What do you want me to say?
Right...
Haru is always sincere.
You're hurting my wrist.
But I haven't been honest with him.
Whenever you confront me,
I start wondering...
"Why do I feel this way?"
"Am I making the right choices?"
If I make the wrong choice...
will I go back to loving you so much,
my grades start suffering?
So I decided to focus on studying.
Wow, you scared me.
That's what I've been up against all this time?
It was awful.
I can't let that happen again.
I need to be able to concentrate on studying.
Shizuku?
If I don't study, I have...
Wh-What are you doing, Haru?!
I don't know!
I'm not sure...
I-I feel so hot.
My heart is...
What's going on?
This has happened before...
Oh, I remember.
When I woke up then, I could feel
the warmth of another human.
A sense of security both
comforting and heartrending.
At the time, I didn't understand
what this feeling was.
Haru.
C-Can you give me a little more time?
I need to think about our relationship.
I have to face
myself, and Haru.
The rest comes after that.
She used to be this adorable little thing,
but, these days, she just ignores me.
It must be genetic.  It's in her blood.
Makes me feel so ordinary.
Next Episode
0 x 1
Huh?