We need to become the MVPs.
We're stopping the Quest
Dorm from getting shut down,
and Souta from getting expelled!
Yeah!
Yeah.
If Her Flag Breaks
Flag 4
We're Almost to the Goal. The Track Meet'll End Just Fine.
So this might be a bit late,
but what do we need
to do to become MVPs?
Well, of course,
we need to get a high total score,
but the score's not the only thing.
There's a lot of emphasis
placed on special points
you can get for teamwork.
So basically, whoever stands
out the most, wins.
Anyway, I've chosen which games you
should be able to get the most points in.
Huh?
We're doing all these?!
Sports Week
Daytime
Monday
Tuesday
This does go on for a whole week.
A proper schedule is the key to victory.
Looks like it's time for me to go already.
I have the 100 meter preliminaries right now.
The women's preliminaries
are still a while off.
Ta-da
It's time for our special Sports Week
program, If I Don't do It, Who Will?
I'll be your host, Seiteikouji Mimori!
My guest here is Hatagaya Academy's own
walking dictionary, Ryuukishibara Tsumugi!
Hi.
When I was young,
I was the anchor for a bucket relay
when the town was on fire.
Our program will pick up
any news-worthy events
that happen around the clock.
First we had Hatagaya Academy's
first martial arts tournament!
Surrounded by tough competitors,
only one could stand on top!
And Eiyuuzaki Rin-kun was that woman!
I'm not sure you'd see that at a track meet...
Next we had the heavyweight
cat-gathering competition!
The android everyone's talking
about, Ninjabayashi Ruri-kun,
used the speaker in her mouth to broadcast
a sound which only cats could hear,
and gathered them all up.
I don't even know what this
is supposed to be now.
And we had a teacher massage contest!
This was just a throw-in for the teachers...
It's still the first day and
we've hit the ground running!
The Quest Dorm team is
really tearing it up.
Everyone cheer the Quest Dorm on!
What's up with her?
I'm sure she feels responsible.
Oh, you did a good job, Nanami.
You got first in the princess race.
Oh, that...
Only real princesses can participate...
Why would there be an event like that?!
All right.
We're going to start our
penalty shoot-out competition.
What's a penalty shoot-out?
It's where you do soccer
penalty kicks over and over.
It's a contest that measures one's
state of mind and composure.
Can Souta really handle that?
Y-You can do it, Souta!
The left!
I see.
This worked well for Souta.
You were great, Souta!
You're moving on to the finals, Sou-kun!
Indeed. Good work, Souta.
You're able to read people
better than anyone.
I'm sure you'll win tomorrow's
finals just fine.
Megu!
You just called for me, right?
Megu! They must have screwed up,
because they just announced
you set a new course record!
I did just get a new record.
Huh?
You guys didn't know?
She was constantly a contender in the
middle school championships
for track-and-field.
That's amazing, Megu-chan!
I didn't know you were
in track-and-field!
Oh, I'm not in track-and-field anymore.
What are you in, then?
The home ec club!
Totally should have expected that!
Gallop, gallop.
Souta-kun!
Why are you on a horse?
I was just in a horse-riding
competition.
I won!
Wh-Why are you still riding?
I just kind of felt like it.
What's your next event?
I'll take you there.
I-I'm fine.
Looks kinda scary.
Oh...
H-Hey.
What's going on?
For safety's sake, hold on tight!
Huh?
White King, hiyah!
You all did great out there today.
We're currently in first place now.
However, we still have a long way to go.
Those that have night events
will sleep after eating.
I will not have anyone oversleeping.
Night events... Early morning events...
That student council president
never does anything right.
But this is kinda fun.
It kinda feels like we're
on a club trip somewhere.
It's always felt like we were
all on a trip together.
I guess you could say we're having a
"strengthen our friendships" camp right now.
Your poems are always so wonderful!
Stop saying poem!
I take that back!
We've all become one to help you, Souta-kun.
We really are strengthening our bonds!
Yeah, we're putting our friendships
on the line to get that MVP spot!
I'm not really a friend,
but an older sister,
so I'm not really becoming closer
friends, but loving him even more.
All of you can love him more, if you'd like.
Wh-What about you, Akane?
I think you get along with him best.
What? I-I think that
Megu-chan is best for him.
N-No, it can't be me.
I-I think Rin-senpai is best.
She's known him since they were kids.
Y-You think so?
No, I don't think...
They're all trying to
hand him to each other...
We've decided to leave the love part to you,
Nanami-chan, through process of elimination.
Now you're just pushing it on me!
I'm not going to let this go!
Living like this is spoiling me,
and it's causing me to forget everything...
I...
Time for the shoot out finals!
If he stops this shot,
the Quest Dorm team wins!
Souta-kun, we're here with you!
You can do it!
Stop it with sheer willpower!
Oh, crap!
Goal!
The handicraft team wins!
We're currently in eighth place.
The last day is tomorrow...
I didn't think we'd have such a hard time.
The men's teams are coming after us,
like they're getting revenge
for their little brothers.
I wonder why.
I kind of understand.
Don't worry.
We're going to save Souta-kun's Quest Dorm.
Yeah.
Souta-san.
I am a machine whose
purpose is to help humans.
Ruri, what are you saying...
Akane-san and the others are
experiencing a dip in their morale vectors.
I have inferred that this is
strongly connected to the current decline
in your morale vector.
It is fatal if someone's morale vector
drops below a certain point.
My "pursuit of human happiness" program
suggests that this issue be resolved.
You don't have to worry.
The reason everything is
like this will be over soon.
Is that because you've
resolved yourself to defeat?
Ruri, let's talk where no one else is around.
I'm...
going to die soon.
I cannot comprehend the concept of death.
I am aware that humans instinctively
fear death, however.
I'm scared of dying, of course,
but there's something
I'm even more afraid of.
When I die,
everyone else may feel
sorrow because of that.
I'm going to make those that
care about me feel that way.
I'm most afraid of that.
If I leave the school on my own,
then the wounds I inflict
will be much less deep.
I want to clean things up after I leave.
Is there no way to avoid your death?
No.
I understood how to destroy other people's
death flags in an instant,
but my own flag...
Oh, I know. That letter.
Princess knight,
magician,
bishop, ninja...
First Flag secret code: entry confirmed.
White hacking mode released.
Connecting directly to server.
Direct access to kernel space granted.
R-Ruri...
It seems you wish to proceed
to the "shadows" of this world.
Do you wish to make any corrections?
Yes or no?
The "shadows" of this world?
The first gate that will be
opened by the four heroes that
fly the Royal Banner is connected to
the "shadows" of this world.
There waits one will destroy the
flag of death that eats
away at the Royal Banner.
The flag of death? Will destroy it?
So does that mean I can get
rid of this death flag?
But... who...
Have you heard of a girl named Sakura?
I do contain some data
of a word close that one,
however I am unable to
learn more at this time.
I see...
Then do you know where
this "first gate" is?
Searching for a readable cluster.
Would you like to project the program?
Yes or no.
Please do.
This is the Quest Dorm?
What's wrong, Souta?
Huh? Nanami?
Don't just stand there.
You are the Royal Banner.
Huh?
Akane, and Ruri, too...
So this person is the bishop?
Let's get going.
Right.
Where are we going?
This is most likely the first gate.
I will give you my power.
And in exchange, you must
learn the ultimate truth of this world.
That was...
Last updated: 1938.
The record was created
by Ninjabayashi Ruri.
Ruri, you've been around that long?
No, I began test operations
two months ago.
I must assume it was
someone by the same name.
Then was there anyone
at Hatagaya Academy
with a word meaning
"bishop" in their name?
Searching database.
Zero results.
We don't know where this data came
from, or even if it can be trusted.
But
if that door really does exist...
Then I can't leave Quest Dorm.
The ultimate truth of this world...
If I can reach it, then I won't die.
The others might not have to suffer.
Ruri, I need you.
I want you to help me.
You need... me?
There have been plenty of
people who tolerated me.
But for someone to say they needed me?
Hatate Souta-san, you're the first.
This is the last day for Sports Week!
The last event is an obstacle
relay race around the school!
If you manage to use your teamwork to
get around the various obstacles
laid out in this large course,
you might be able to get MVP
from an underdog position!
So if we win, we're MVPs.
That makes things easy.
I wonder if this'll work...
The final runners have to
run in pairs like this.
It's fine.
The victory flags've been raised.
On your marks...
Ready...
Souta-kun...
What's wrong?
Akane...
Please win.
Do you think that I wouldn't try?
Thank you.
I'll have to make it up to you.
Oh, then could I ask something of you?
Sure. Anything's fine.
Th-Then it's a promise.
Pop.
It's a promise.
Kikuno-senpai!
Okiku-nee,
I'm sorry for making
you worry all the time,
and being such a terrible
little brother character,
but I want you to win.
You're not a little brother character.
You're my little brother.
Pop.
Older sisters are invincible when
it comes to their little brothers.
Megu-chan!
Megumu...
I'm not sure how to say this, but...
Is this...
I understand... I understand, Souta-kun!
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pop!
Men don't need words to promise
something to each other.
Rin-senpai!
Rin-kun, thank you for
trying so hard for me.
I'm truly grateful to you.
N-No problem.
I've always been best friends with you.
Yes.
You could never be replaced in my heart—
you were my hero.
Souta...
Pop, pop, pop, pop.
So I want you to show me how
cool you can be, once again.
Just you wait, Souta!
I see.
I was wondering why you were
running around all over the place.
I was just using everyone.
But still, I...
Ridiculous.
They fall head over heels for you,
and you're worried about that?
By the way, I don't really
care about this MVP stuff.
I just don't like losing to others.
Yeah.
I don't know how to get your victory
flag up, even though I knew the others—
Huh?
You know, I've never seen a flag of hers.
Does Nanami not have flags?
Souta!
Take it!
Let's go, Nanami!
We're going to stay in the lead!
Yeah, we're going to be MVPs!
We're almost there!
I know!
Fight!
You can do it!
Show us what you're made of!
You're almost there!
Quest Dorm team is in first!
All they have to do is put
their ice on the table,
and run to the goal!
All right. Let's go.
Nanami, are you okay?!
Just a small scrape.
Don't push yourself.
We can go to the infirmary.
No, there's only half a lap left.
Let's go.
Why are we the anchors if we can't deliver the sash,
containing everyone's feelings,
to the finish line properly?
Fine. Let's go, Nanami.
Yeah, it's the last spurt!
You can do it!
I'm sorry, Souta...
No, you saved me from...
Not that...
If I had a victory flag, too...
Nanami...
Will I
only bring sorrow to everyone?
Is it right for me to just disappear?
I'm sorry, Nanami.
Let's go.
But I still want to be...
...with everyone...
...there at Quest Dorm...
I want to be with everyone!
Quest Dorm team is catching
up at a crazy pace!
Go!
Who got to the finish line first?!
Quest Dorm Team
Baseball Team
Hatagaya Academy
Around the school obstacle relay
Photo finish
Photo finish.
First is...
1st Place: Baseball Team
2nd Place: Quest Dorm Team
First is the baseball team!
The Quest Dorm team is a close second.
So what does this mean...
We lost.
Does that mean Souta-kun is going to...
That can't be...
Thank you, everyone.
I'm really glad I got to work so hard
towards something with all of you.
I'm at fault here.
If I hadn't been hurt...
Souta-kun...
Huh?
We were moved!
These are the people on the board
that were complaining about you.
You had an accident, and you still
carried your friend to the finish line.
You believed in your friends
to the last minute,
and called out to them, cheering them on.
This is true friendship, true teamwork.
But it doesn't change the fact that
Souta will be kicked out of the dorm!
Second place and better are pretty
much guaranteed to get MVP.
Huh?
So that means...
Quest Dorm gets to stay?
Yay!
I guess I was wrong.
You again?!
Hatate Souta...
I see. So he's the one...
Roar! Gawo!
The athletic festival's finally over.
At least, that's what everyone thought...
Don't set up a continuation flag!
Ignoring Mimori's nonsense,
what are you planning to do for break
now that the festival's over, Nanami?
Well, I've been busy lately,
so I've been thinking
of relaxing at the dorm.
At least, that's what everyone thought...
Don't keep setting up these flags!
Flag 5
Believe and Wait for Me.
I'm not Going to be Late for My Date With Everyone.
Roar! Gawo!
If Her Flag Breaks
I hope you watch us next time!
Illustration: Hikawa Hekiru