Excuse me!
Ohana!
Hey!
Haisai!
An Okinawan dialect, right?
Yup!
A circular notice, right?
Give me just a moment, please!
Hot Springs
Anything interesting?
Um, yeah!
Listen to this.
Yunosagi is going to be covered
in the next issue of that magazine.
Wow.
Then are you going to
have to go through this, too?
The Mystery Guest Evaluation Ranking?
Yeah, I bet.
Our staff are really worried about that part.
I guess a high ranking toward the top
means more customers will come, right?
Something like that.
So it has an effect...
All right! Kissuiso needs to work harder, too!
What should i do?
if they come and my picture
ends up in their magazine?
Maybe I should go to a beauty salon...
There's no way that'll work.
It's probably the worst
plan you've ever come up with.
But Takako said that
advertising is the first
Free Inn Pass
One night stay with two free meals
and the most important thing to do in our business.
If you're free, lend me a hand!
So, you do realize that we're free.
It's the weekend,
yet we only have a single group of customers.
I know, that's why I'm making complimentary passes...
Hello, you've reached Kissuiso.
Yes, we're pleased to
hear from you again!
A room for two?
Of course, we'll be waiting!
Was that...
Mr. Tsuji, a frequent customer!
We're lucky today!
Hello, you've reached Kissuiso.
Yes, thank you.
A reservation for tonight?
Yes, it's possible.
And how many people will be staying?
Episode 8
Run
Minchi!
It's rare to see you do the shopping.
Apparently, we suddenly
have a lot of customers.
Wow! Let me help you!
It's okay.
Seriously, I don't mind!
Hey, did you hear?
Yunosagi's going to be
covered in a magazine!
Nope.
Apparently, they're gathering
information for the rankings right now!
Yeah?
Don't you think it'll
be crazy if Kissuiso gets
ranked number one
and the inn fills up with customers?
Stop dreaming.
If that really happens,
Madam Manager's bitter
face will finally smile!
Here, girls.
Thanks for working
so hard all this time!
Now, go and have
some fun with this money!
Yes, Ma'am!
And we'll go to a hot spring...
Hot spring!
Eat yummy food...
Yummy!
Why not including old maid?
Old maid!
That doesn't differ from
what we normally do, right?
Aren't you off work today?
Nope, Nakochi is.
How many customers
did you say are arriving?
Seven groups;
twenty customers in total.
At this time of day?
Our frequent customers booked the
same period as the other reservations.
But there's no way
we can refuse a customer
when we have free rooms, right?
If we're unable to give
the customers our full attention,
you will have to learn to turn them away.
You're right.
So, have you informed Mr. Ren yet?
Yes.
Tohru's taking the day off today,
but he says it'll be fine regardless.
So, the only area we lack in is...
To be honest,
I'm not confident that Ohana and I
will be able to serve
this many customers.
Don't worry about that.
If it's necessary, I'll rush in and help too.
Really?
Why are you surprised?
After all, I once used to be a waitress too.
She looks like she's having fun.
Yeah.
Man, I want a day off too!
Don't you have days off as well?
I don't need them.
You're so dedicated.
I just want to hurry up
and learn all my tasks.
Oh, but maybe if you keep
working during all your breaks
Tohru will be overjoyed
and fall in love with you!
Minchi...
I'm sorry! Was that balut-like of me?
Wait, Minchi!
Hang on!
Shut up!
Hi, Beanman!
You have a bad habit
of suddenly walking fast.
It's not a habit.
Madam Manager! Madam Manager!
Are you okay?!
Madam Manager!
I'll call the young master!
An ambulance!
Idiot!
What...
Are you okay, Madam Manager
Please don't yell
when you're in this condition.
She was feeling all right lately too...
Well, it happens fairly often,
so I'm sure she'll be fine.
Aren't you going to go?
How can we run this inn
if both of us are gone?
There's a lot of customers today.
I need to do my best!
You're awesome, young master!
Hello? Takako?
What?
Ms. Shijima?
Are you Ms. Sui Shijima's relative?
Y-Yes!
We'll perform another
examination tomorrow morning.
Take care.
Th-Thank you.
I couldn't instantly respond to "Ms. Shijima."
That's right.
She's my grandmother.
Ohana?
Oh, you're awake.
Return to work.
What?
We suddenly have a lot of customers.
I bet everyone's having a
hard time without a full staff.
But you're also having a hard time!
When you get this old,
things like this happen
every now and then.
Still, why didn't you
let me call an ambulance?
Idiot.
If someone were to call an ambulance,
what would the customers think?
All I ever hear you say is "the customer."
Because that's
what this job is all about.
Now, go back to work.
I won't come here and visit you again.
That's fine.
Oh, right. The account book...
I was on my way to get is in my room.
Actually, never mind.
Just go.
What?
Ohana.
Yes?
Good luck. I'm counting on you.
Okay.
Hi, you've reached Sakki's cell!
Please leave your
message after the tone,
and keep it under 20
seconds please!
Mom, Grandma is...
Ko...
If I were to call him right now,
what would I say to him?
From Ko
H-Hello!
O-Ohana?
It's been a while.
Have you been well?
Yeah.
What's wrong? You don't sound normal.
Did something happen?
Nah.
Yeah.
What's that supposed to mean?
No, what I meant was...
Thanks, Ko.
No problem.
Actually, Ohana...
Yeah?
I'm actually on a train, on the way to see you.
What? I can't really hear you.
Like I said, I'm on a train.
Are you on your way to work?
No, listen...
What?
We're here.
Oh, thank you!
No signal
I have the feeling that Ko
said something about coming to see me...
But there's no way...
Are you ready, Ohana?
Yeah, I am!
Then can I get you to take
some snacks to the Wisteria Room?
Sure!
My apologies.
What?
My apologies. I have the wrong room.
What on Earth are you doing?
I'm in the middle of
an important mission.
Oh, he's back.
Indeed.
Why is everyone gathered here?
Oh, you're back from the hospital.
Can you join this meeting then?
What?
I'm kind of in the
middle of something...
And that's exactly why
we need to brainstorm.
Br- what?
Excuse me,
but I also have work to get back to...
It'll be finished soon.
Go on, Mr. Jiro!
I've worked for 15 years
in order to become a writer.
It looks like it's finally
time for my well-trained
observation abilities
to see the light of day.
Stop being a show off. Let's hear what you've got.
S-Show off?!
Anyway,
the ones that are suspicious are
the two women in the Moon Room
and the man in the Wave Room.
Our target is one of those two groups,
no doubt about it.
What are you talking about?
Mystery guests.
Mystery... Oh!
That's right!
There must be a reason
that so many customers...
are showing up during the off season.
It's logical to assume that there are
mystery guests working
for magazines staying at Kissuiso!
There is no time like the present!
Let this chance go and there
won't be a next time!
We'll find out who
the mystery guest is
and show them
the time of their life,
resulting in us scoring
high in the rankings!
So, you're saying we should
prioritize customers?
Of course. Why not?
B-But what about the other customers?
Oh, well...
We'll be giving the other customers the
same kind of service we've
always given them.
We're just going to be giving
the mystery guests better service.
Is there an issue here?
Professionals always
prioritize their work.
Only amateurs let emotions
get in the way.
It's our only chance to
revive Kissuiso, Ohana!
But Madam Manager wouldn't...
We've got no time to lose!
You're all going to follow my plan.
Roger!
Sure, whatever.
I'll need you to get
ready as well, Mr. Jiro.
You've got it!
Hey you,
can you take me to the kitchen?
What?
Dinner is the key?
What do you mean?
Don't tell me you're telling us to give
the potential mystery guests a better meal?
That's right.
It starts with a meal
and ends with a meal.
The meal is the key!
Tonight's dinner
is the most critical time for Kissuiso!
The battle we cannot lose is...
That's right!
Tonight's dinner!
And the person who'll make it...
...is you!
Yes, you.
M-Me?
Please take care of it.
I'm counting on you.
The dinner is the key...
Mr. Ren?
N-Nothing.
My hand slipped, nya.
"Nya"?
Yes, that one is very popular.
And this is one of them.
Wow...
So pretty.
During this season, I'd say...
I wonder if this is okay.
I feel like something is off.
Is Madam Manager okay?
Are you worried?
Beanman.
If you're worried,
go and check up on her.
Nah, if I did that, she'd let me have it.
"What are you doing? It's busy today!"
Besides, she told me she
was counting on me.
Now that I think about it,
she was saying
something about an account
book in her room...
I'll take care of that for you.
Thanks, Beanman!
This must be it...
How organized.
I wonder if everyone from
around here is like this.
Wow...
she's got so many details written down
about each customer.
What time are the Ariyoshis
checking in again?
What's wrong?
Mr. Ren seems to be acting strange.
He's working,
but he's not acting like himself.
He's actually
bad at working under pressure.
At this rate,
we won't be able to prepare
dinner for all the customers in time!
What are we going to do?
You're asking me?!
The solution is simple.
We prioritize those two groups.
What?!
There's no other option.
You're right!
That's probably the best option.
Well, if there's no other option...
No.
Ohana...
No. If we were to do
something like that,
we'd be scolded by the Madam Manager.
What do you know?
A lot, precisely because
I've been scolded by her lots!
What?
All customers are equal,
thus, we need to treat them all equally.
That's what
Madam Manager lives for!
That's what Kissuiso stands for!
But, Ohana, we don't have enough time,
nor do we have enough people.
I called for more help!
She called me, saying,
"We're in trouble. Please help!"
I see...
What about Tohru?
If I recall,
he's attending a marriage
today in the city.
Let's contact him anyway!
He didn't answer.
I tried calling him earlier.
You did?
Well...
I can help out with the
preparations for cooking,
but I can't cook anything yet, and I...
I can't be of any help,
so...
Sorry to make you all wait!
Nako...
Please take care of this, Nakochi.
And lend me the key to your bike.
Huh? Sure.
Thanks.
Minchi don't worry. I'll get Tohru!
Hey, wait!
I'll be right back!
Ohana?
I said, wait!
You balut...
Something I can do...
Something I must do...
What I'm doing right now
was well thought out...
but I'm still a bit uncertain
without Madam Manager here.
5 Missed Calls
Ko
Ko?!
Sorry. Hang on just a little longer.
All right!
Damn...
I don't know where exactly Tohru is...
That just means I'll need to look everywhere.
Where are you, Ohana?
I'll do it. Please let me!
So this is what a boy's
hair smells like?
Thank you so much, Ko.
Episode 9
The Longest Day at Kissuiso