I'm Gouda Takeo, a first-year in high school.
Back in the spring, I started dating.
But now that it's fall, I even have a disciple.
Saijou, what am I teaching you, anyway?
Y-You're basically a master of the heart.
I see!
My Disciple
Suna, what do masters do?
Where's this coming from?
Yesterday, Saijou told me that
she liked me as a person,
and that she wanted to call me "master."
Likes you as a person, huh?
Do you have anyone you'd call "master"?
Master...
A long time ago,
I got carried away and played
after sundown and got lost.
After walking for a very long time,
I reached the city and was
able to go home, but...
The mountain let you come home!
Don't you ever forget it.
No man can win against nature.
The mountain?
Back then, was that the awe I felt?
My master is nature!
That's pretty expansive.
She likes him as a person?
Oh! I can see that!
I like Rinko's boyfriend as a person, too.
Thanks.
You don't need to worry.
He even said he isn't popular with girls, right?
Yeah.
But I fell for him, so...
You're such a worrywart!
By the way, you guys are trying
to get into Hakutou U, right?
Text Inbox
Yamato Rinko
Subject: Are you free this weekend?
Takeo-kun, are you free this Sat or Sun?
Hakutou U's having a school festival.
Want to go?
Maybe Sunakawa-kun, too?
Suna, Yamato sent a text asking if we want
to go to Hakutou U's school festival.
Are you free this Saturday or Sunday?
Both days are fine.
Hakutou U?
Master, you're trying to get in there?
Yeah, are you, also?
Huh?
Um... Yeah.
Do you want to come, too?
Huh?
Wait, isn't it a date?
I'd just be in the way.
Wait, I'll ask Yamato.
It's fine!
That was fast!
Wait, is it really okay?
Takeo-kun!
Gouda!
Hey.
Hello, Saijou-san.
Oh, hello...
Sorry, I hope I'm not being a bother.
Not at all.
Hakutou University School Festival
Wow! What a big festival!
There's a stamp card.
Want to try it out, Takeo-kun?
Sure!
This is beef stew made from a secret recipe.
Secret!
Secret.
Yamato...
Why do you need to keep
cooling it down so long?
I love you.
Oh, I'm really sensitive to hot food!
Oops, did everyone finish theirs?
Sorry, I'll finish up right now.
It's fine.
Cool it down as much as you want.
Two more stamps to collect...
Hakutou U Festival
Stamp Card
They're really far.
Their campus is huge!
Just take a break here.
I'll go get the stamps.
Oh, really?
Yeah!
I'll go, too.
You'd just get lost.
Yeah.
Saijou-san, what do you like about Takeo-kun?
Huh?
Sorry...
At the chicken coop,
I happened to overhear you tell Takeo-kun
that you like him as a person.
So I was just curious!
He was helping me practice for the relay.
Right, right...
I fell during the race,
and I blanked out.
When I looked up, he was waiting for me.
Everyone else had left him behind,
but he was still waiting for me...
And when I passed him the baton, he was
super fast and got first place,
Roar
even though he entered the final lap in last!
Wow, amazing!
Yeah, isn't he amazing?
He left all of them in the dust, too!
Wow!
Takeo-kun's amazing!
But it didn't really matter if he
finished first or not.
I was just happy that he ran
with everything he had...
I know just what you mean!
Oh, sorry.
I didn't mean to lean in so close.
Which one of you asked the other out?
Oh, it was me.
I see!
Earlier this year,
for the first time in my life, I ran into a groper.
Seriously?
Yeah, and Takeo-kun happened to be in
the same train car and helped me.
Oh, that sounds like him.
Afterward, the guy said something
about how I was asking for it.
What a jerk! That's awful!
Takeo-kun got mad for me.
He really yelled at the guy...
He's cool.
Yeah.
But he punched the guy.
Huh?
What's going on? Looks like they're having fun.
Was that when he was on probation?
Oh, Takeo-kun!
Saijou-san and I really get along!
Oh, that's good.
I got them all stamped.
Thanks.
Oh, I brought a mille-feuille today.
Huh? You made this, Yamato-san?
Ta-dah!
Oops, I can't believe I just said that.
She said, "Ta-dah."
I love her!
I love you, Yamato!
Takeo-kun, you got cream on your face.
Huh? Here?
Here.
Here?
Here!
Got it.
You have some, too, Yamato.
Huh, here?
Here.
Did I get it?
Yeah!
This is dangerous, getting on people's faces.
Yeah, it's a dangerous cake.
What should we do next?
We've gotten a good look around.
Yeah...
Oh, I think I'll just go hang around town.
Later.
Oh, okay.
See you later, Saijou-san.
This was really fun!
The school festival was really fun.
What was the prize?
Oh, a washcloth!
Okay, I'll also get going, then.
Handshake
Hang on a sec.
Huh?
No, that isn't it
Okay.
Huh?
Wow!
There are a lot of pine cones here.
Yamato and pine cones...
Don't pines have male and female trees?
Oh? Was that ginkgo trees?
Well, it isn't a big deal!
When I'm with you, I think
I just ramble, Takeo-kun...
I see.
You're still so much taller than I am.
Yamato and the rock...
Yamato and the stars...
Bye-bye!
See you soon, Takeo-kun!
I love her.
It isn't as if there's anything specific
making me think that, but I do.
I wonder where this feeling comes from.
Star
Dust
Hey...
How does it feel to like
someone as a person?
Huh?
Well, you know, it happens...
Sunakawa, you're his friend, too.
So you know what makes him a good person.
Sure, though I don't think
of him as a master.
But I didn't want to stop talking to him
after the sports festival ended...
I mean, you also like Gouda, don't you?
Sure.
But you don't want to hold
hands with him, right?
No.
Then that's it! That's what it's like!
I'm just like you.
That's what it means to like
someone as a person!
Sure.
I get all that,
but I think your feelings are
different than mine.
I'm not popular with girls.
I wonder why Yamato's always worried.
No girl's ever going to fall for me.
So what if they are?!
Don't tell him, ever...
If you do...
If I do?
I'll do something super horrible to you!
Make sure to include what
you felt and experienced
Not even junior high students make
hallway bulletins anymore.
Huh? My junior high did.
Seriously?
during the field trip.
If this is a bulletin, we need a four-panel manga.
If there's space.
I want this...
Anyone have a spare ruler?
Yep.
Thanks.
We're kind of short on pens and stuff.
Want to get some today?
I have club practice.
Oh, I'll go.
Why not have your "master" go along, too?
Okay, no problem.
Suna, you come, too.
Sure.
I think there's a stationery store
in the shopping district.
Oh, but I guess bookstores
also carry the same stuff.
Which do you want?
Whichever's fine.
You seem in a pretty good mood, Saijou.
Huh? Do I?
I'm just my usual self.
Oh, it's Yamato.
Do you have any plans today?
If you're free, I'd like to see you.
Today, huh?
What? She wants to see you?
Yeah.
"But I have to do something for
school with Saijou today."
Master, if you put water on it,
this ink will disappear!
What?
It disappears?!
Not that we need it.
Wow.
Wow!
Books
I'm sorry about today.
You missed a date because
of this shopping trip.
It's fine. I'll see her later, anyway.
Oh, okay.
Takeo-kun!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Yamato.
It's okay.
Wow, Takeo-kun's umbrella is so big
Oh, you're alone?
I thought you might bring Saijou-san
and Sunakawa-kun...
You got rained on.
I love her.
The other day, I had a great
time talking with Saijou-san.
I see.
Oh, my friends all said they
like you as a person, too.
I see.
But I'm not popular with girls, so don't worry.
I'm not so worried all the time!
It's only sometimes!
Sometimes...
There's really no need to worry.
How can I help her understand?
It's from Yamato!
Huh?
She said she had a great time
with you the other day.
She'd like to see you again.
Oh, okay...
Till next time!
Yeah, I know I'm a cheat!
I'm taking advantage of him
because he doesn't know,
and of her because she's a nice person.
I'm duping both of them.
I know, okay?
You don't have to guilt-trip me so much!
Do I really have to tell them the truth?!
That isn't what I'm saying.
Isn't this hard for you?
Unless you tell them, those two will
never doubt you, so they'll be fine.
But if this keeps up, you're the one being hurt.
I was just wondering how you were doing.
Oh, you aren't going home?
I'm waiting for Suna.
Oh, okay.
Later.
Yeah.
She doesn't even have to worry
about it "sometimes."
Hey, what's up, Saijou?
I just can't even...
What?
Well, isn't that just a ploy by your girlfriend,
to make sure everyone knows
you have a girlfriend?
You don't go to the same school, so...
Is it?
Maybe it is.
But she has nothing to worry about.
I guess she's still worried...
I'm not popular with girls.
I wish I could somehow reassure her.
Master, I like you.
Right!
As a person!
That isn't what I mean...
I like you as a man!
I want to be your girlfriend!
Saijou, I'm sorry!
No... I knew, of course...
I mean, you already have a girlfriend.
It's too late.
That isn't it.
I love Yamato.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for lying this whole time.
I'm sorry for being dishonest.
You aren't dishonest!
You don't need to apologize!
I wasn't lying when I said I like
you as a person, too, master.
I'm not popular with girls, so don't worry.
Looked like you needed some extra.
Thanks.
You know, Sunakawa...
You're too savvy.
It's annoying...
There's another box,
if you want.
I mean... When I first called him out,
he had no idea I was going to confess.
How could I tell him?
And I knew he had a girlfriend...
I mean, look at his cell phone.
I had no chance...
Asking him if I could call him master
was so pathetic.
I wanted to call him "Takeo-kun,"
not "master," too!
Waaaah
I loved him!
What?
Why is she crying?
How much were the tissues?
It's fine.
Having a broken heart must hurt.
Not that I really
understand what
it's like, but...
You don't need to worry about the small stuff.
I wonder if I can like someone again.
I'm sure you can.
When?
Eventually.
I'm sick of this!
I want to now!
But I can't right now!
You like girls who smile a lot
and get along with everyone.
That's right.
That's how I've always been.
Until I met Yamato.
But when I first met her,
Yamato was crying...
She still thanked me.
She can't eat hot food.
And she's a slow runner,
even though she can move fast.
She laughs a lot.
I like all of that.
She's so cute, I can't even say it.
I don't know when I started feeling this way.
But when I thought she liked Suna,
I remember how I felt crushed
for the first time in my life.
Takeo-kun!
I wasn't expecting you!
What's wrong?
It isn't just that I like her!
I really love her!
Yamato, Saijou told me that
she likes me as a man.
Huh?
I apologized to her and turned her down.
Not because I have a girlfriend...
Not because I have you...
I'd never go out with any other girl.
And that isn't because I'm
not popular with girls...
It's because I like you, Yamato!
You're the only one for me!
So it's going to be fine.
Don't worry anymore.
Okay.
Let's go home.
No way...   He's her boyfriend?!   Huh?    What?!
Is he a bear?!   A gorilla?!   Mountain gorilla?
Huh?
What's wrong?
I'm... I'm just happy.
I knew it, you know?
I knew it.
But when I thought about
how you really like me...
I love you!
I feel like there are tons of reasons why,
but also no reason at all.
But every time I look into your eyes, I feel it.
I love you, too, Takeo-kun.
My heart's always telling me that I love her.
I'm sorry I said not to worry because
I'm not popular with girls.
I made you worry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, is that why I was worried?
But it's okay now.
I'm not worried.
I don't blame Saijou-san for anything.
I think both she and I fought for what we wanted.
So we're similar that way.
Even though we can't be friends,
I like her.
Yeah.
I only realized how I felt
because Saijou told me how she felt.
Suna, you knew?
Sorta.
I knew it. It happened again.
I wonder why I'm so oblivious
to everything around me...
Maybe because you're always looking up.
But that's what everyone likes about
you, so you just have to accept it.
Just accept it, huh?
I wonder what it was like,
confessing feelings to someone
who already had a girlfriend.
Damn it!
He's in knots about not responding to her
feelings, though he'd like to somehow.
He'd like to make her feel better,
but that wouldn't work.
He's upset that he can't do anything.
Isn't there anything I can do for her?
Like I said, you just have to accept it.
I see...
I'd like us to stay friends,
but I guess it can't work out that
way between a guy and a girl.
Master, good morning!
Huh?
Saijou...
I know calling you that is weird,
but it's become a habit.
Can I keep calling you that?
Sure!
Thanks, Saijou!
He said, "Thanks."
Last night, he had a hard time sleeping
because he was torn up about not
being friends with you anymore.
I think, just now, you made him happy.
Thanks, Saijou.
Thanks for liking me.
When you fall for someone next time,
I want to help you in any way I can.
My Christmas
Next time: My Christmas.