There's something I've felt since I first met you.
You give me a really nostalgic feeling, somehow.
Sorry, that was a weird thing to say...
See you.
Narugino!
Hey, Narugino! Come on!
These?
Hang in there, Narugino. I'll be right back.
Punch Line
Brazilian High Kick
Thanks.
But how did you know
where my medication was?
Hey, Narugino,
could you please stop becoming Strange Juice?
Why?
Isn't it obvious?
Your body...
can't...
So you knew...
But I can't stop.
Why not?
There are people waiting for me.
But if you die, what's the point?
Even Ishigata-san...
I don't think even Ishigata-san
would have wanted that.
Wait... Wait!
How do you know about Ishigata-san?
Unbeijini nyopurasara,
I'm going to put a spell on you...
That song... How...
I'm...
Pine.
And this body is yours,
Chiyoko.
Why?
Why did you keep it from me all this time?
I missed you, Pine.
Pine!
I see...
So Ishigata-san saved you
after you fell into that dam.
I looked for you and Guri-chan, too, but...
Yeah, I guess in that rain...
It was the next day that
I realized I'd switched bodies.
I had no idea what was going on.
I was so sad, I couldn't stop crying.
I think I would have gone crazy
if it weren't for Ishigata-san.
So that's why you came to an
apartment in Tokyo with him.
You know that, too?
We lived in that apartment for about a year.
But one day...
They're here.
It's the people from the lab.
Escape from the window.
But...
In my condition, I'll only slow you down.
I can't do that!
I need you!
Don't worry.
As soon as I take care of them,
I'll come right after you.
You promise?
Yeah, I promise.
But that promise was never fulfilled.
Ishigata-san liked cinnamon.
Like, cinnamon toast and apple pie.
He loved this cinnamon tea, too.
I thought it was candy at first, so I bit into it.
Ishigata-san laughed so hard.
Every time I smell this scent,
I remember those days.
I remember the apartment,
and Ishigata-san's smile.
Hey, Chiyoko.
Can you try to think about it one more time?
What did Ishigata-san want?
Why did he sacrifice himself to save you?
Hey, Pine, by the way,
do you remember that ring?
I got in a fight over it with Guri-chan.
That takes me back...
Hey, Meika!
Are you out?
I'm coming in.
Now it's time for the weather.
Cold air will be blowing in
from the Sea of Japan,
Where'd Meika go?
making this evening quite chilly.
Please dress warmly if you go outside.
Did you see it?
See what?
Oh, that's not why you called?
What are you talking about?
I sent a picture to your phone
this morning before I went out.
It's a day late, but call it a Christmas present.
Huh?
Never mind.
So what did you want?
Where are you?
Earth.
Quit messing around.
Jeez, you're no fun at all.
I have something important
to talk to you about.
It's about Narugino's condition.
I'm at the station.
I had some mechanical problems.
I'm on my way to buy replacement parts.
Can you come to my room
when you get back, then?
All right.
Later.
May this Christmas
flip your skirt up~
That idiot!
That's foolish.
Operation Intercept is
fundamentally doomed to fail.
Nuclear weapons are powerless in space,
as they don't produce blast waves there.
But with a few dozen missiles...
Heated Debate!!           TV Debate
The US Military's Asteroid Interception Plan
Proceeding in Secret?
That's nowhere near enough to destroy
an asteroid two kilometers in diameter.
Of course, with a few thousand,
it might be a different story.
The United States has secretly
launched a military satellite into orbit,
equipped with several dozen nuclear missiles.
The goal of Operation Intercept
is to use these missiles
to destroy the incoming asteroid.
Was everything he said a lie?
Hey, Rabura!
You're not here?!
Wh-What do you want?
At least knock, will you?
Where's Rabura?
She left early this morning.
She said she had an urgent
request for an exorcism.
The number you have dialed—
Damn!
Wh-What'd you do that for?!
I thought I'd make a proper
ghostly appearance for once.
So, any leads?
I spent all day going around
universities and research labs,
talking to physicists and space
engineering specialists and stuff.
And they all said...
Foolish.
That's nonsense.
There's no way you can stop
it with nuclear weapons.
But don't worry.
The chances of that asteroid
hitting Earth are slim to none.
In other words, Gliese was lying.
She must've been crazy to believe
everything that sketchy guy said.
Then that thing about him being from the U.S.
Department of Defense's intelligence bureau?
He probably made it up.
Anyway, tomorrow's the big day.
Gliese visits, Miya Ken attacks.
I finally understand
why Miya Ken attacked Gliese.
Wait a second.
Could it be...
Shoot, I have to go!
We'll continue tomorrow.
Bye!
What's up with him?
Why are you dressed like that?!
I'm a little under the weather.
I feel so hot, it's like I'm suffocating.
My cooling unit's been acting
weird since that guy hit me.
Give me a break, would you?!
What's the problem? We're both girls.
I'm a guy!
Sure, sure.
I am!
Never mind, just put this on!
What the heck...
Okay, it's on.
That's even hotter!
Is this better?
So, what do you want?
What do I...
You were the one who called me.
You wanted to talk about Narugino.
She collapsed last night.
On the rooftop, after the party.
It was one of those attacks.
It seems like she's having
them more often lately.
I think she might be getting a lot worse.
You heard from Narugino, huh?
Hey, Meika,
can you give her a physical
checkup as soon as possible?
I want to know how she's doing right now.
All right.
Shouro Meiko.
December 27, 8:40.
I'm back!
I just got home from Utapiro
with Moena and the others.
All-night karaoke is so exhausting.
I'm getting old.
Looks like she's not dead yet, at least.
In the other history,
it was early this morning
that Meiko's body was found.
But I broke Tomoda's limbs, so now...
Did I scare you?
What do you want?
To continue where we left off yesterday.
About Gliese.
And?
You're not thinking about beating
up Gliese or anything, are you?
I knew it.
Just so you know, I won't
let you get away with it.
Why not?
Is your head a vacuum?
Because it'll change history, of course!
You have to get beaten up by Rabura,
or the history where everyone
gets into a fight won't happen.
A bond without pain isn't a bond.
The more you make amends,
the stronger your ties become.
So you're saying it's important
that they make up after fighting.
I told you,
the cooperation of the tenants is
vital to the success of the
Human Preservation Project.
Are you telling me to just let Gliese go, then?!
Exactly!
The critical moment comes
tomorrow morning at 4 AM.
That's the moment of truth.
So you need to do as I say until then.
Gliese visits
Miya Ken attacks
Got it?
I see. So that's what this is.
You tried to use me.
You thought you could get to
Meika by getting close to me!
Is that right?!
Rabura-san, please don't misunderstand.
It's just about time.
It's true that I was attracted to you—
Don't lie to me!
You wanted to make me happy, my ass!
There!
Don't give me that crap!
He certainly is full of it.
Wh-Who are you?
I have a little something to say to you.
To me?
Is there atmosphere in space?
I'd love to hear your thoughts on that matter.
You're not getting away!
Special attack, Clam Bomb—
Wait, is it really okay if
I give him a flying kick?
In order not to change history,
I have to kick him into the pond
and make everyone get into a fight.
But then, he'll...
I can't.
I can't do it.
There's someone in front
of me who knows the truth.
I can't just let him get away.
Just wait. I'll catch up to you!
There!
Panties!
You got me.
I seem to have broken a few ribs
after slamming into this rock.
It'll be your fingers next if you
don't answer my questions.
Just what do you want to know?
First, who are you?
I'm from the U.S. Department of Defense...
Lie again and I really will break your bones.
Why do you think it's a lie?
Because everything you said
to Rabura was total crap.
So you were eavesdropping.
Yeah, twice.
Twice?
You don't need to understand.
Why did you run?
Anyone would, if someone like you
just showed up out of the blue.
I'm starting with your pinky.
After I'm done breaking the other
nine fingers, your molars are next.
Fine.
It won't impede the project if I tell you now.
I'm a leader of the Qmay Group.
I'm in charge of everything
regarding the project.
True, a few nuclear missiles won't destroy VR-1.
It'll merely change its trajectory by a bit...
toward a collision course with Earth.
The question is how to get into
the impregnable AFSPC servers.
Not even the most brilliant hackers
in the world attacking all at once
stand a chance against it.
That's why we looked towards...
Meika?
Her hacking skills are beyond human.
Meika isn't going to give in to your threats.
Who said we're threatening her?
She'll infiltrate the AFSPC
servers by her own will.
She's not going to ignore the
pleas of her best friend.
That's why you needed Rabura?
Once she opens the gate,
all I need to do to get into
the server is to tap the wire.
The critical moment comes
tomorrow morning at 4 AM.
That's the moment of truth.
I injected you with this while
you were falling down the ledge.
Your sense of pain is dulled
while you're Uberfied.
It's no wonder you didn't notice.
Don't worry, it's just an anesthetic.
You'll wake up in half a day or so...
Though, you're more likely
to die from the cold.
Shit!
You bastard!
Ubermensch is impressive indeed.
To have so much strength even with
that powerful anesthetic in you...
But don't get cocky.
You're not the only one with that ability!
No, a Face Maker!
I got that through Chichibu Rando.
It was so useful, too.
What the hell are you?
Man, you don't give up.
Would you go to sleep already?
I thought so.
It looks like you've figured it out.
No...
It can't be.
You're...
I guess I can't say it's been a while.
We met just six days ago, Pine.
Guriko...
Yes, I'm Guriko.
And this body's supposed to be yours.
So how do you feel? Embarrassed?
I won't force you to believe me.
Human history is nearly over.
Living with your eyes averted from
that reality isn't a bad option.
Why?
People change after nine years.
You're the ones who are odd,
for not having changed.
No.
The Guriko I know...
Guriko...