Where's Noel?
Yeah.
Noel!
Nonoka.
Koharu
Noel!
Where Wishes Go
Noel.
Noel!
Nonoka.
Noel.
Why?
Things get bad when I'm
far from the saucer.
You said you'd be okay.
I'm... Sorry.
Tell me, what should I do?
How do I save you?
Take me where I can see the saucer.
The saucer?
Nonoka, what happened?
Should we go back to town?
Is Noel there? What about the saucer?
Sorry, Koharu.
I'll explain later.
Hang on, Noel.
Nonoka.
Dad, you came by car today, right?
Help, please.
Don't worry, he's coming.
Where's Shione?
Noel.
Noel!
Did you find her?
No. I can't find her.
Maybe they aren't at school.
What do we do?
If only I'd paid more attention...
Souta!
Don't make that face.
Maybe they went on home.
You're right.
Right.
I can't see the saucer from afar.
How would you ever
leave the town, then?
She's fine, I'm sure of it.
She found Noel-chan!
See?
But something didn't seem
right over the phone.
Don't worry.
We're almost there.
Hang in there, Noel.
Are you sure we just need to bring her home?
Yes, please.
You should call if you're worried.
I think Nonoka will call
me when things settle down.
Nonoka
Incoming Call
Nonoka, how's Noel-chan?
Yeah.
Yes.
So she's okay, then?
Where are you now?
Noel.
You were watching over me so my
wish would come true, weren't you?
So that we can always keep smiling.
It's because you were by my side
that I could have my
precious wish again.
Thanks, Noel.
Coming!
Have these with Noel-chan,
if you'd like.
Saucer Rice Cakes
These, too.
This'll make her better.
Thanks.
I was so shocked when I
heard that she collapsed.
Don't freak us out, shorty.
Thank goodness. Seriously.
Hey...
Nonoka, I'm leaving you
to take care of Noel.
Honestly, I'd like to be
there all night with her.
Yeah.
And I'm sure Shione really wanted
to come to the Hokubi Festival, too.
Something must have come up.
I think so, too.
Thanks for today,
everyone.
Nonoka, what happened to Noel-chan?
She probably got exhausted
at the Hokubi Festival.
I'm worried about Noel, too.
Souta?
If you know something...
Noel can't leave this town.
That's why she collapsed.
What's that supposed to mean?
Noel is the saucer that we called
seven years ago.
Saucer-san, Saucer-san...
Please grant my wish.
My wish.
Please grant our wish.
Noel is the saucer?
She's trying to grant
that wish from way back?
Wait, Koharu, Souta,
how are you both convinced
that she's the saucer?
How could that be Noel?
I made Noel help get rid of it.
Noel was happy that she was giving
you help when you needed it.
Because she's a friend.
I'm sure that's what Noel would say.
Oh.
You're right.
Noel is the saucer,
and she's our friend.
Oh, so nothing's changed, then.
Yeah.
Soft.
Cold.
Noel.
Noel!
Morning, Nonoka.
What's wrong, Nonoka?
What do you mean, what's wrong?
I was so worried.
Everyone else was, too.
Worried?
About me?
Nonoka, where's Shione?
Did you smile together?
Don't worry about us for now.
You didn't?
Nonoka,
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault, Noel.
Wait.
I...
Smile with Shione again.
Why?
You were back to being friends again.
I thought so, too.
I know.
When I talked to her,
she said she's happy when
she can smile with you.
What did I do wrong?
Is it because I ate rice omelet?
Or because I jumped into
the hot spring bath?
Because I passed on a message?
Because you gave me tickets?
Because I'll disappear
if your wish comes true?
Morning.
Morning, Yuzuki.
You seem down.
Did something happen to Noel?
No, that's not it.
That's good, then.
Don't hide anything about
her from us, all right?
Yeah.
Nonoka, the telescope!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thanks, Souta.
And Yuzuki.
You scared me.
I brought rice cakes.
Are you okay, Koharu?
Thank you, Souta.
What about me?
You, too, Yuzuki.
Good, you're all here.
There's someone I want you to meet.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Togawa Shione.
Shione is
my precious
friend.
I can finally go home!
Sensei!
About Togawa-san.
Oh, about her transfer?
Transfer?
No?
No, it's nothing.
Nonoka.
Hurry up, go.
She's a precious friend, isn't she?
I'll take the telescope home.
Come to the store later.
I'll be the one carrying it, don't worry.
Okay.
Thanks.
Shione!
Please.
Let me talk to you once more.
I don't want us to part like this.
I heard from Noel.
Once our wish comes true, Noel...
Shione.
Is it true you're moving?
I'm just going to be
living at my dad's.
Is that for Noel?
It is, isn't it?
What does it matter?
I hope we can all smile forever.
I love all of you.
I don't want to lose you anymore.
So let's think about
what we can do.
Stop.
There's no reason to think.
I'm not as attached
to the observatory as you.
I just went because you invited me.
I leave, and Noel stays.
What's the problem?
Are you okay with that?
Leave.
Of course I'm not.
I love all of you, too.
What am I supposed to do?
Shione is my precious friend.
She's my friend, too, then.
No fair, Onii-chan.
Me too.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah!
Liar.
Nonoka!
Noel.
Do you feel okay?
Yep.
See.
Right?
I'm glad.
I really want to grant your wish.
Is that because we called
you to this town?
At first, yes.
At first?
I realized after I watched you guys
that your wish is really,
really beautiful.
That you can smile,
and always be connected.
That your hearts would
always be together.
That's such a beautiful thing.
So I want to see you all smiling.
But...
But that means...
We're closed for the day.
You're in the way.
Go home if you're
not doing anything.
Come on.
I'm waiting for Nonoka.
That's it?
I want to ask about Shione.
Something's wrong with
her these days, I swear.
Shione!
Shione.
Thank goodness.
I wanted to talk to you.
Go back to Nonoka's.
Shione?
Sorry, we're closed for...
What?
You! Where were you all this time?
We were worried.
What happened?
Where's Nonoka?
I wanted to talk to you.
About Noel.
I have to get the telescope.
Mom,
what am I supposed to do?
Everyone smiling.
I don't want Noel to disappear.
So...
So get out of my life.
Does it have to be Togawa?
It's okay as long as the
five of us aren't together.
Then I could just be
away from you guys.
Wait!
I caused so much trouble
about the saucer, so I—
How could we leave it to
you, Yuzuki, you idiot?
Come on, stupid Souta.
Please stop, you two.
Souta...
What's wrong, Yuzuki?
Hey, wait.
Why?
Koharu.
Here.
Thanks.
Did Shione tell you?
I can't stand it.
Noel.
I heard your voices in the sky
above the observatory that day.
Your voices calling for the saucer.
Calling for me.
That's how I got to meet you.
I knew it was you
as soon as I met you, Nonoka.
I was so happy.
I spent time with you, and you
taught me a beautiful song.
And the meals you
made were so tasty.
Yuzuki and Koharu,
Souta and Shione
are all so kind and warm.
I smiled lots and lots.
I know now.
What I want to see
is you, Shione,
Koharu, Yuzuki,
and Souta smiling.
Because I love you all.
That's why
I have to part with you now.
Next episode of Celestial Method:
"Night of the Meteor Shower."
Enjoy.
Night of the Meteor Shower