This is the International Rescue Fleet
of the Norma Administration Board.
Normas, thank you for your
good work fighting the DRAGONs.
We will hereby begin your rescue.
Angelise-sama, it's a rescue!
They're here to save us!
Please abandon your weapons
and prepare for evacuation.
Don't listen to it.
It's bullshit.
Take anti-air defense positions.
Yes, ma'am!
Arzenal is arming its anti-air weapons.
Oh, dear.
I was hoping to go about this peacefully.
Emperor Julio the First to all ships.
The Norma have just now rejected our rescue.
This is a clear act of treason
against us—against all humanity.
We cannot turn a blind eye to this.
All units, attack!
Girls, they're coming!
Shit, I was late.
Please be safe, Ange.
Arzenal in Flames
They're attacking us.
The rescue was a lie.
Everyone, they're humans.
They have no intention of helping us Norma.
They intend to gather us up
like possessions and
assign us to fight elsewhere.
Those of you who want that, surrender.
But if you want to resist, follow me.
Arzenal command hereby
rejects human administration.
We will now begin our rebellion...
Operation Libertus.
Those who wish to join us should take arms
and gather at the lowest level of Arzenal.
That is all.
What will you do?
We'll come with you,
Commander.
Salia,
do not fail to bring Ange.
I understand.
When did this get so...
Pamela, you sit in the pilot seat.
Hikaru, you'll take radar.
Olivier, on comms.
All systems engaged.
Prepare for take-off.
Yes, ma'am!
Rebellion? What are they talking about?
It's die following the commander's orders,
or be killed by the humans, I suppose.
Hilda here.
Awaiting orders.
I despise and hate the humans.
It's a good time to fight back.
The second wave of enemies is approaching.
Use the Para-mails to engage them.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll go, too, Hilda-chan.
We have to protect what's precious to us.
There's no way we can
survive defying the humans!
We won't know until we try.
Right, Ange?
The Villkiss is our top priority.
Ready the ammo later.
Take it to the emergency elevator.
Mei, are we ready for take-off?
Eh? Yeah, ready when you are.
Us, too.
I, Tanya, and my group are
ready to sortie, Captain Hilda.
Good.
First Troop, sortie!
Are we really going to fight humans?
What's that?
Retreat!
What was that?
Shit.
C-Captain!
What is it, Tanya?
The unidentified machines are everywhere!
Help me!
Captain!
Ilma! They took Ilma!
They took her?
What?
Generators are not responding.
All power to the base has been lost.
Activate auxiliary power.
Was it battle damage?
We've been infiltrated.
No matches.
Are we really going to kill them?
Priority One is Angelise.
Priority Two is Villkiss.
Priority Three are Mail riders.
We are to destroy the rest.
Enemies are inside Arzenal.
Their objective is to eliminate all personnel.
All units, retreat!
Run!
Ersha.
Sorry, I'll be right back.
Dammit.
All units on deck.
The enemy's objective is Villkiss.
Bringing it to the lowest
underground level is your top priority.
Maintenance crew, gather!
We'll move Villkiss down manually.
Yes, ma'am!
Your top priority is to transport
the severely injured.
Don't complain about a little spilled blood!
Help me! I'm not a Norma!
Idiot!
Are you trying to get killed?
We've been overrun.
Retreat.
Vivian!
Match found. She's a Mail rider.
What are you trying to do to her?
Vivian!
Onee's gatling gun!
Bastards!
It's over.
We're going to die.
We're the infamous First Troop.
We can't die now!
It's too late to act like a captain now.
Fine, fine.
Look out!
Son of a bitch!
Hilda...
Why?
No one dies. We don't allow it.
That's what the First Troop is about, right?
Villkiss is still on the maintenance deck.
I'll go back up as soon as I deliver Ange.
It's dangerous here, isn't it?
Is this really time to prepare an escape?
I told you, I have an important mission.
You and the Villkiss must escape unharmed.
It's probably going to be...
...my last mission.
And for that, you'd give
up your friends' lives?
What else can I do?
You're just like that woman.
Paranoid and drunk on fanciful ideas
and a meaningless sense of duty.
It must be awful to be someone
who gets killed over you people.
You don't understand anything, do you?
How important, privileged, and special you are!
I don't even want to understand.
Hold your breath, please, Angelise-sama!
What the hell is this?
Ange, where—
I'm glad I had it on me so I
could cook whenever I needed to.
You've gotten pretty bold.
You're rubbing off on me, Angelise-sama.
Salia, what happened?
Ange escaped.
Capture her.
Commander, we have a
message for you from the outside.
Outside?
Frequency 153.
Patch it through to my line.
It's been awhile, Alektra.
Tusk.
Is Ange safe?
She just now ran off.
Will you assist in her capture?
All right.
Be safe, everyone.
Angelise-sama, I think we
can get out from here.
Angelise-sama!
Water...
I'll get some water.
You only realize what
matters to you after you lose it.
This fact has remained true through the ages.
Such a heinous deed.
I don't remember permitting this.
No, it was your brother
that ordered this massacre.
He's fourteen kilometers away, north-northeast.
He's come to make mincemeat of you.
These girls were,
in effect, collateral damage.
You did this?
Under Onii-sama's orders?
You—Angelise!
Wait, please!
I was just following the
captain and Julio's or—
Angelise-sama.
It's okay.
I'm here.
It's okay now.
I have to go.
The elevator shaft!
We can't bring Para-mails down now.
What's the plan, Hilda?
Freaking hell.
Momoka.
Yes.
Ange!
Where were you, you idiot?
Take care of Momoka.
Hey! You can't use the runway now!
Fine.
She's so violent.
Course clear.
I won't let you.
Hilda.
I have to go, too.
To save everyone...
I'm topside at Arzenal.
Where's Ange?
Well...
Jeez! That crazy woman...
Potato chips...
Shit! Let go!
Let go!
We've captured a few Mail riders.
Captures reported from within the base, too.
And Angelise?
Priority One is Angelise.
Priority Two is the Villkiss. I told you!
Object inbound, fast!
It's Priority One and Priority Two!
Angelise...
Come back, Ange!
Come back and do your duty!
What's your problem?
You were chosen!
By Alektra!
My role, my place—you took all of it, so face it!
I liked it.
I liked it here.
This wretched, shitty, atrocious place...
Everything tasted like shit.
But I liked it.
I liked living here.
And he destroyed it.
That's why I'm going.
If you get in my way, I'll kill you.
Ange!
I won't forgive you.
I won't let you run off with the victory.
Ange, you fatass!
Hilda, ready for take-off.
Roger.
Let's go, Captain.
Hilda Squad, let's go!
Yes, ma'am.
Chris!
Hang in there, Chris!
We'll save you!
Thanks, Rosa—
Chris.
God damn it.
I'll kill all of you!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
A light barrier.
Then...
Sink!
Defiant and Mariposa are down!
Fortunate and Olbert destroyed!
What are they doing? It's just one—
Angeli—
Call off the massacre, now!
If you don't want to die, then do it now!
Holy Emperor Julio the First here.
All units, cease fire and retreat.
Retreat?
What about the Norma?
I stopped them!
Now get me a doctor, now!
Wait!
That wasn't the deal!
I apologize.
I'll do anything you ask.
I know, I'll reinstate you
into the royal family.
Angelise!
Come on, that's not a bad offer, is it?
Please, don't kill me!
You worthless scum.
Go to hell!
You're—
Embryo-sama!
Get her! Kill Angelise!
Do it now!
Embryo?
Ange, you are beautiful.
Your anger is pure and white.
It rages, its heat unsurpassed.
You are like a burning flame,
rising up against injustice and absurdity.
A noble, beautiful flame...
I cannot let such a flame be tarnished
by burning up things of no value.
So I will do it instead.
I will carry the burden of your sin.
The flames of countless lives,
Fall through and become stars
That's...
...the "Endless Song"!
I know this song.
They fly beautifully,
Me, too.
It can't be.
And fade away in the cradle of life and death
Embryo.
The same weapons as the Villkiss...
Begin irrigation.
Beginning irrigation.
No life signs within Arzenal.
All survivors have been relocated.
Main engine critical in ten seconds.
Water levels up 80%.
All floodgates closed.
Transmit our encrypted rendezvous
coordinates to the Para-mails in combat.
Roger.
Full gauge.
Release the restraint arm.
Open the gates.
Ease ahead.
Aurora, take off!
What?
What are you?
Ange, that man is dangerous!
Tusk!
Get away!
Now!
What a turn-off...
Sing, sing, the two wishes are now
No!
Strongly, strongly shining in heavenly gold
Tusk!
Ange!
No!
It speaks of eternity
What a boring plot.
But not bad...
Preview
Where have we ended up?
I don't know, but it looks like w-we're alone.
Stranded on a deserted island again?
If you do things, or touch me funny,
or suck on me again, I'll kill you.
Ange and Tusk
So... pinching?
Die!