May I ask a question?
Queen to F3.
Shoot.
King to G7.
Is it a good idea to send me into battle?
Rook to E4.
If I die, the Deucalion's Aldnoah will shut down.
I'm aware of that.
Rook to D8.
But we'll worry about that
when we have to.
Do you want to be removed from the
front lines, Ensign Kaizuka?
No.
I'll go into battle.
Queen to F6, check.
King to F6, king takes queen.
We're in agreement, then.
Bishop to E5, check.
I'll put it on the monitor.
Did you come up with
that move yourself?
Or is it something that analytical
engine of yours cooked up?
It's mine, about 70-30.
About 70-30?
I'm assigning tasks to unused brain cells
to try to optimize its processing.
So it's both the device's suggestion
and my own idea at the same time.
This ship and her crew
both owe you our lives.
If you want to fight, I think
we should support that.
I don't deserve any special treatment.
Did you hear that Aldnoah activation
tests were conducted
using blood samples that had
been drawn from the princess?
King to G5.
Result, failure. Blood alone was not
sufficient for Aldnoah activation.
So you could be considered
a special case indeed, Ensign.
When you resuscitated the princess,
the activation factor transferred to...
no, infected you.
Then it was fully activated when you
came into contact with royal blood.
Over the past ten months or so,
we've obtained plenty of intel on
Aldnoah and their Kataphrakts.
But they still have the overwhelming
edge in military strength.
There's no guarantee that we'll
win if we keep on fighting.
But if we do, Ensign Kaizuka...
I'll put my money on you.
Bishop to G7.
Do you resign?
Was that move yours?
Or your left eye's?
I'll leave that to your imagination.
I suppose not even the Tharsis
can see that far into the future.
See to it.
Yes, sir.
Welcome back, Milord Slaine.
I clustered my shots in the region
that you calculated, Mr. Harklight.
Let us pray that they won't be influenced
by some unexpected wind.
Ah, I thought I smelled something.
A dog has snuck aboard.
A rather grubby one, at that.
What are you doing here?
Good day, Count Barouhcruz.
Count Marylcian.
I rushed here so that I might
join in the battle as well.
Terran dog...
Mind your tongue!
Count Saazbaum!
Slaine Troyard here is my vassal.
If he has given some offense,
I offer my apologies.
However, if this treatment is unwarranted,
Count Marylcian,
it will not go well for you.
If this Terran were merely your pet,
it would be eccentric, but tolerable.
But to appoint him a knight?
Is that not taking
your game too far?
Count Barouhcruz, it is not your place
to offer opinions regarding my vassals.
Perhaps, but him fighting alongside us
is another matter entirely!
One cannot take to
the field of battle
with someone who might
turn traitor at any moment!
If that is your concern, please
strike me down right here.
You are entirely correct.
If I go into battle with you,
it might very well be me
who is attacked from behind.
How dare you!
Men!
Hear me, all of you!
By the grace of the emperor of Vers,
I name Slaine Troyard my son
right here and now.
All of you here are my witnesses!
Milord Count...
Stand, Slaine.
From this day forth,
you are my son.
Will you raise a hand to him
even now, Count Marylcian?
If you are prepared to go
to such lengths, so be it.
But if his behavior is the least bit suspicious,
I will put him down without mercy.
Forgive me. I have put you
in an awkward position.
It is fine. I had decided
to do this long ago.
I, too, take to the field of battle.
I must have a successor just in case.
From now on, think of me as your father.
Congratulations, Milord Slaine!
The count's heir... This puts you one
step closer to your dream.
That's enough, Mr. Harklight.
I don't have any dreams.
It's almost time.
Yes...
Who do you think
will win, Eddelrittuo?
Th-The glorious Vers Imperial Forces
will emerge victorious, of course!
Oh? Doesn't that trouble you?
You have friends aboard a United
Earth Forces ship, don't you?
Perish the thought!
Friends on Earth?
Of course. Let's have a wager, then.
A wager?
If the Vers Empire wins, I bet...
Let me think...
My sister's life, perhaps?
I'm joking.
What are you dreaming
of right now, sister?
Have you seen Inko?
The electromagnetic catapult, I think?
She's probably with Rayet.
Thanks.
Don't get lost.
I'll try.
Sweats?!
You're too greedy, Yutaro-chan.
Tharsis. Details of its abilities, unknown.
High rate of attack evasion reported.
Confirmed pilot...
...Slaine Troyard.
A good luck charm given to me by a dear
Terran friend when we arrived on Earth.
Animals that fly through the air...
It is just as you said, Slaine!
Is he equipped with a neuro-linked
analytical engine too?
Indeed. But I don't
have enough data.
It dodged my attacks as though
it could see the future.
If that's true...
it could be a problem.
You monologuing?
I was talking to myself.
That's what monologuing means.
The warrior god Odin, rider of the
mythological, eight-legged Sleipnir,
drank of the waters of Mímisbrunnr
and was granted vast wisdom.
But the price he paid for that
wisdom was his left eye.
Norse mythology.
Know-it-all.
Don't make fun of me!
After the battle in Russia,
I wanted off the ship.
I was terrified.
But then it hit me that if I did, I'd never be
able to look Okojo in the eye when I do die.
If your steed is ever acting up,
come see me day or night.
I'll fix it up in a flash.
I'll hold you to that.
Okay, why don't we grab a bite before
the battle? There's still some time.
I'll pass.
When I was shot, my stomach
was empty, apparently.
They say I would've died if my organs had
been contaminated by stomach contents.
Oh. Sure.
But I might not get another
chance, so maybe some tea.
What are his reel selections?
He's got a #1 through #3, a #10 for
emergencies, and one on the left and right.
It's specced out for high-G pivots.
Long, thin wires aren't cut out for that.
Found you!
Hey, it's Team Deucalion.
So you're the Aldnoah unit that
everybody's talking about, huh?
I hear one of you is a Martian.
Don't get in our way on
the battlefield, little ladies.
What was their problem?
Bunch of jerks!
They're not wrong, though.
All Martians are the enemy.
I know that better than anyone.
You're so adorable, Rayet.
You've got the "tsun" part down pat.
Huh?
I wish you'd show a little
more "dere," though.
What are you talking about?
Want some candy?
I'm gonna deck you.
We will enter defense airspace in 30 minutes.
Please launch.
Good hunting!
Is my steed ready?
The fine-tuning has been completed!
Good!
Dioscuria II, launching!
Slaine Troyard, launching in the Tharsis.
Stygis Squadron, launching!
Martian Kataphrakt squadron approaching!
Calling all forces!
Commence operation!
Message from HQ!
Deucalion, launch!
We will provide support for the attack
platoons as a guerrilla force.
All hands to battle stations.
Our shipboard Kataphrakts are
launching from Trident Base.
Mustang 11, cleared for launch!
Roger. Mustang 11, cleared for launch!
Blastoff!
Blastoff.
Target merge. Commencing attack.
Attack incoming!
Hold your fire! They can't hit us
in this wind, anyway!
Hit them when they get in close!
Hit them when they get in close...
My umbrella's been hit!
Mustang 11!
I'm fine, but the debris is not! I can't
get a clear shot with all this shaking!
Mustang 00, moving to assist.
Inaho!
Hey, what about your umbrella?!
It's just a drizzle. I don't need it.
Stop pulling crazy stunts, darn it!
I wouldn't be able to use it
in a dogfight anyway.
Inferring gravitational shifts.
Data compensation, ready.
Fire.
Commence attack!
Why you!
Pivoting via wire swing-by.
Returning to combat airspace.
#3, shoot.
Pivot complete in 4, 3, 2, 1... Release.
Inaho Kaizuka...
Slaine Troyard...
Marineros Base will make
next approach in 30 seconds!
Main guns ready to fire.
Attention, all platoons!
Get clear of our line of fire!
Rayet!
This is Rhinelander 22!
Crap, I've got one on my six!
Roger. Mustang 22, moving to assist.
The Martian!
Marineros Base now in firing range.
No friendly units in line of fire!
Main guns, fire!
Marineros Base beginning to move away.
Issue disengage order to attack platoons
and guerrilla unit! Put them on defense!
Inaho, we've been ordered
to disengage! Come back!
Inaho!
That's some accurate shooting.
I knew it, he's using predictions, too.
#1, pivot.
I'll wait until the instant
he comes out of the rocks.
He'll attack the instant
I come out from the rocks.
Coordinates confirmed.
Two minutes to impact.
Let's do this.
Fire.
I hit him?
That's—
Are you all right, Slaine? Fall back.
No, I can still fight!
Don't overdo it.
The orange Kataphrakt...
I owe him some payback!
Looking for the gap in my barrier?
I took the liberty of
changing its location.
Fly, my servants!
Energy joints, linked.
Blade field, engaged.
Sword drawn.
There's no escape.
Inaho!
I'll cover you! Get away, Inaho!
Stay back, Inko!
No!
Stay there!
Right at that position!
Prepare to meet your maker, Terran!
Right kick thruster jettisoned.
Fire!
The flames aren't being sucked in!
The barrier gap!
You won't get away! Slaine!
What's that?
A high-speed debris cluster.
I picked up a debris cloud closing in
at high speed on my 3D Doppler radar.
Thanks, Inko. A split second later,
and I'd have been caught in it, too.
Impossible! My Dioscuria,
brought low by mere debris?!
That wasn't debris.
It was bullets.
I fired them off before the battle began.
They were aimed so that they
would swing around the Earth
and land at that spot right now.
Slaine?
I had originally meant it as a
trap to defeat Inaho Kaizuka.
The trick was to disable
your dimensional barrier,
but I thought that if anyone
could manage it, it was him.
Slaine...
Shut up!
Did you honestly believe that
I would swear fealty to you?
To the man who pulled the trigger
against Princess Asseylum?!
Did you think I would forgive you?!
My second volley will arrive soon.
Goodbye...
...Father.
Not too shabby.
On this day, I have lost
my second father.
He was also a great man
who devoted his life
to the prosperity
of the Vers Empire.
I hereby announce my resolve
to carry on both my fathers' legacy
and fight for the even greater
prosperity of the Vers Empire.
Lords of the Vers Orbital Knights.
This is no time to be squabbling
amongst each other.
As knights of the noble Vers Empire,
should we not work
hand in hand to eradicate
Earth's resistance forces?
In the name of Her Imperial Highness
Asseylum Vers Allusia!
Let us punish the Terrans who
dare defy the Vers Empire!
He isn't lying...
Her Highness Asseylum is biding
her time at our lunar base!
I knew it... She's alive.
In hopes that she may remain—
Milord, you must be exhausted.
Mr. Harklight, you were born into
the third class, weren't you?
I was.
Though they were poor
and of a low class,
my father and mother
worked hard to raise me
and used every means at their disposal
so that I could serve the Orbital Knights.
Milord Slaine, it is for that reason that
I have the utmost respect for you.
You, who have attained the rank of
count even though you are a Terran.
This new era will be
for people like us.
Let's begin, Harklight.
Yes...
...Count Slaine Saazbaum Troyard.
Pivoting Trap