The Principality of Pastillage
The opening of the joint event
between the three countries
is drawing closer.
For those discussions,
the princess from Biscotti
and Leo-sama from Galette,
are making their way toward Pastillage.
Castle Eschenbach
Of course, the heroes are all
accompanying their lieges...
So today, the three of us will
be reunited in the castle.
Pastillage's Hero King Legend
All right, let's begin
the final discussions.
Then let's decide on the pending issues.
I have to say, ladies,
you are looking especially...
...fine today.
So are you, Cou-sama!
Your tail is looking
especially luxurious.
That's because Rebecca is brushing
it so gently all the time.
That's how my hair and my
tail have become so fluffy.
Wow!
I see.
Truth be told,
Nanami has been treating me
to Earth-style oil massages.
It makes my skin resplendent!
This morning, Sink played
with me at the lake...
and, after that, he even braided my hair!
Ah hah!
That hair-style does look very cute!
I even put in my favorite ribbon.
Hmm, it looks like the leaders
of the three countries
have worthy Heroes looking after them.
That's right.
I'm so happy.
You can say that again.
Leo-sama is so cute.
I'm so happy!
My Cou-sama is really cute, too.
She's so healthy and happy
and she loves to be spoiled.
Loving your ruler deeply
is a cornerstone of herodom, young ones.
Sounds like someone's
talking down to us.
As if you weren't totally smitten
with the Princess yourself.
I am a Hero, after all.
What's with the gentleman act?
That reminds me.
How is Isuka-san doing?
He's doing fine.
Right now, he's at Fuugetsu Lodge.
He's going to build a
workshop in the area
and stay there for a while.
Lady d'Arquien and Yuki were
quite happy about that.
That's good.
Oh, do we really not
have any work to do?
That's what I heard.
Oh, but Sink, will you come talk
to Cou-sama a little later?
Just me?
Come in.
Oh, Hero Sink!
Is the meeting already over?
Yes, it went very smoothly.
Right now, Millihi-nee and Leo-nee
are in the hall with the press.
What are Rebecca and Nanami up to?
They said they were going to take a bath,
in the palace's great bath.
Then that's perfect!
There's a place I'd like to take you.
Look!
There it is.
This is the "Hill of the Hero King"
Hero King?
The founding father of Pastillage.
My ancestor.
A long time ago, demons
appeared in this land
and endangered the peoples' lives.
The ruling lord used the
hero summoning technique.
The Hero who came defeated
demon after demon,
until he finally defeated
the king of the demons
and thus brought peace
back to these lands.
Unfortunately, the ruling lord
lost his life in battle,
but his will bestowed the crown
on the head of the Hero.
They called him the "White Hero King"
and he brought hope back to the people.
So this place is...
That's right.
This is the resting
place of the Hero King.
It is also the place
where they sealed
in the demon king.
Even while he sleeps,
the Hero King makes certain
that the demon king
stays sealed.
Another legend claims
that a miracle will happen
when the descendant
of the Hero King touches this monolith.
Just watch and see what
happens when I touch it.
It reacts like this, but that's it.
I made Nanami and Rebecca
touch it earlier, too,
but nothing happened.
I thought maybe you could try it.
Okay.
I'll try.
Maybe if I do it with you.
It's resonating.
Will a miracle happen?
Descendants recognized.
Unlocking the seal.
Damn it. I was enjoying my sleep.
Was it you?
You woke me?
What happened?
I can't see a thing!
Um... well....
Where is Adel?
Well... uhh...
Waking up without Adel
is a once in a lifetime opportunity!
What?
All right.
Hey, you kids.
Come here.
And you are?
My name is...
Valeria Calvados!
But I guess you humans
call me the Demon King.
The Demon King?
You kids...
For this brief freedom of mine...
you shall forfeit your lives!
Kids nowadays have a
lot of bright power.
Now...
I'm full, so let's get to it!
Not bad, not bad at all!
This way, baby.
They saw me.
Someone's peeping!
Outside the window!
Peeping is a crime!
Aim!
What a sight to behold!
And on we go.
Rise, storm!
The view is superb!
I don't know why the
Demon King rose again,
but I'm sure he's headed for Pastillage.
We can't let the others
fall into danger.
That's right!
Full speed ahead!
Look!
Somebody's up there!
Don't panic, my girls,
just show me your skin!
Ex Machina!
Form Boomerang! Slash!
Are you even trying?
Palette Set Shoot!
Neptune!
Boiling Water! Fist!
Being a pervert...
...is a serious crime indeed!
The weather is so beautiful.
It sure is.
What the...
For my first bath in ages,
that was a little on the lukewarm side.
What is that?
He looks hurt.
There you are!
Are you two okay?!
Yes.
Your Excellency! Princess Millihiore!
We've got an intruder!
Oww. Hot, hot!
You there!
You are arrested on charges
of lewd behavior and peeping!
Huh?
Peeping?
Who are you calling lewd?
Listen to me, humans!
This is...
I am Calvados, the Demon King.
Fear me. Worship me.
Millihi, are you all right?
Yes!
This is the ribbon Rico
gave me last year.
It's my favorite.
Really?
Can you feel the fear
rock your very core?
Are you prepared to grovel
and beg for forgiveness?
Excuse me, Cou-sama.
I'm going to leave your side for a bit.
I am the Demon King!
I don't care if you're the
Demon King or whatever,
but there is nothing
worse than a man who...
threatens girls, causes grief,
and then has the gall to laugh about it!
You will apologize to the
princess, to Cou-sama,
to everyone you have terrorized!
Sink...
Is everyone okay?
You little...
Don't underestimate me!
You, Demon King.
It would be for your own
good if you just apologized.
It looks like you all really
want to piss me off.
Demon King Seal!
Everybody, run!
Dark Circle of Absorption!
I can't move!
My power is draining away.
Thank you kindly.
Did you see?
This is the strength of the
Demon King's power,
the power that once ruled this world!
A bright power drain spell, huh?
What I'd expect from a demon king.
Still, we won't be defeated!
You might be a demon king,
but I am the descendant of the Hero King!
I will protect my country,
I will protect my guests!
Just you watch!
The Hero King is not here.
Nobody is here to save you.
Except for us!
What?
For the countries and
the masters we love...
Rebecca!
We will always come in an instant!
Nanami!
We three Heroes are right here!
Sink!
Just as expected, he's tough...
He is the Demon King.
How do we seal him?
They say the Hero King
was able to seal him in back then.
"A heart that won't give up"
and "a summoning voice" confirmed.
What is this?
All summoning conditions fulfilled.
Summoning Adelaide, the Hero King.
I don't believe this!
I can't see a thing!
My heart of courage is fully charged.
Your emotions are my strength!
I will always respond to a
call for justice and hope.
I am...
Adelaide Grand Marnier!
The Hero King!
All right?
The Hero King?
Adel?
Valerie?
Or should I say, Demon King Calvados?
Your evil deeds stop here.
Now just a minute, Adel.
Why am I accused of evil deeds
when they started this fight?
Be quiet!
You have disturbed these peaceful people
and what's more, you sexually
harassed all these girls
without caring or knowing
who they were!
But that's...
Your excuses are futile.
Prepare for divine retribution!
Wait Adel, if you do
that, I'll die.
It really will kill me, no joke...
Repent in the light!
No, no, no, no, no!
Grand Marnier Hammer!
Huh?
So this monolith was the summoning
point for the Hero King?
That's right.
I had it erected so that
I could be summoned,
should the power of the
Hero King be necessary
in an hour of need.
I am gathering miracle
power while I sleep here.
Valerie.
Did you apologize to all these
people you inconvenienced?
Yeah, yeah. I did.
Once again, I am so deeply sorry!
I won't do it again!
It seems he is repenting
his wicked ways.
Please find it in your
heart to forgive him.
Um...
Well, as long as he doesn't do it again.
Then the two of us will
return to our slumber.
That means you, too.
Damn, I wanted to have some more fun.
Hero Sleep Routine, restarted.
Couverte, couldn't we keep the Hero King
and that Demon King a little longer?
It would be nice if the
Hero King could stay a bit
and see our current
world after all this...
It looks like the Demon King
isn't so evil after all.
And then...
More than anything...
After everything,
you're still the cutest...
Which of your tongues is speaking?
Which?!
I really want to know what kind of
relationship those two have.
You two don't have to be in
such a hurry to get back.
We're too old to stay long
in the country of young people.
This old man and old
lady are signing out.
It made me really happy to see
my cute descendants and princesses,
as well as the new crop of
healthy, young Heroes...
Okay, farewell.
Huh?
Problem identified in Hero Sleep
Routine's magic circuitry.
Repairi- repai- re- re- re
Did it... break?
Looks like it.
What?
Well, looky here.
Now what do we do?
So, how is it?
Apparently the wear and tear
of the many years have left their mark.
I heard that the repairs will
take quite a long time.
What about those two?
They'll be staying in
Pastillage for a while.
Even the Demon King agreed
to be on his best behavior.
I'm so glad I was able
to meet my ancestor.
It's good that she's such a nice person.
Yeah.
I have to thank Sink later.
He was pretty cool today.
Maybe just a little.
Sink, you really are my Hero!
I love you!
Th-Thank you, Princess.
I wonder why the princess is so happy.
I'm glad, but I don't get the reason.
Oh well, whatever. She's cute.
There, there.
I am the Demon King!
I can't see anything!
Cou-sama, you mustn't look!
Battle at the Cave of Sealing!
Let's fully charge our hearts
with courage again, next time!
Okay?