What is this, my lord?
Evans /Person of the Land      Pursall /Person of the Land
They're all People of the Land.
Jessica /Person of the Land                 Belna /Person of the Land
Sleeping?
They're all asleep!
Are you okay?
What happened?
Sh-Shining wings...
Shining wings?
Guild Hall/ Cafeteria B
Japan Server
Akihabara
City/ No Monsters
No PVP
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
The fifty-four People of the Land who fell
asleep are being kept at the guild hall.
The same phenomenon occurred in Maihama.
Lord Sergiatte is still asleep and won't wake up.
Silver Sword says Susukino is safe.
Then only People of the Land fall asleep?
Yes.
Belna /Person of the Land
Their MP falls to zero and doesn't
recover fast enough naturally.
Belna /Person of the Land
So their MP is being continually drained?
Eyewitnesses suggest it's due to a
moth-like monster with shining wings.
A moth spirit, probably...
There wasn't any monster like that in the game.
For now, it appears our best move
is to keep investigating and
to strengthen our defenses.
What about Shibuya?
Shibuya?
Regan told us that the remains of the
broadcasting station in Shibuya
may still be functional.
Shouldn't we investigate that immediately?
And ignore the moth spirit?
It may seem cold, but if only People
of the Land are falling asleep—
No way!
That's just how much stress the
adventurers are under right now!
The Royal Guard's rampage.
The flavor text coming true.
And now this...
And there are signs of impending
war with People of the Land.
We don't have the energy to
spend on anything else.
I do understand how you feel, but...
Yeah. Even if we can go home,
it's not going to happen right away.
Right, Shiroe?
Yes...
But that doesn't mean we can do nothing.
Let's keep an eye on the situation
and see what we can do.
Sleep of the Eternal Moth
Sleep of the Eternal Moth.
There aren't many people today.
Yeah, with the moth spirit running around...
Tohya.
What did Chief Nyanta say?
He's going to patrol with us tonight.
All right.
The People of the Land who fell asleep
show no signs of waking up yet.
I'm worried about them.
I'm going home.
Are you thinking about your home?
Rudy?
Even if we're apart, I don't think
our relationship will change.
I might not be able to see you anymore.
Even so, if you have a place
to go home to, you should.
There are some people who can't,
even if they want to.
Rudy...
Okay, we're going to head out on patrol.
Yeah.
Chief, take care of them.
Shiro!
Shiroe! Look!
They're here! They're here!
A whole swarm of moths!
Eternal Moth
Eternal moths?
So many of them!
This is bad.
Could this be...
I hate bugs!
What the hell is this?
The shed scales are passing through
the city's defense magic?
Just draw their attention!
Push them outside the walls!
The southwest side's about to be breached...
Team 2, cover them!
Roger!
Don't you have to go to your wife, Demi?
I'm having her lead People of the Land to safety.
I won't let a single one of them into our town!
All the Royal Guards fell asleep?
That was unexpected.
An attack from outside the zone...
Get the People of the Land to safety!
Right!
This is going to be bad.
Marielle, there are more here!
This is bad!
Bibiko /Adventurer     Tarosa /Adventurer
Juggler /Adventurer     Stacy /Adventurer
Even adventurers?
It isn't only People of the Land?
It's dangerous to be outside!
Everyone, get inside the guild building!
At last, adventurers have also started to fall, huh?
It seems that if shed scales get
on you, you fall asleep.
It may be that your Psyche, your MP,
is drained from your body.
Psyche
Perhaps we should call it "Missing Psyche Disease."
Missing Psyche Disease
But some people are fine.
We don't know the difference between those
who fall asleep and those who don't, but...
You don't die, do you?
Right.
If you die, you can revive at the Cathedral.
But once you fall asleep...
How did it go?
I've found the eternal moths' nest, Shiro.
Where is it?
Town of Shibuya
Japan Server
Shibuya
City/ Monsters Present
PVP Permitted
Skill Use Permitted
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
In Shibuya.
It's really bad.
The player town of Shibuya
has turned into a dungeon.
And where is the moths' nest?
In the remains of the Shibuya broadcast building.
It's a raid zone.
Its new name is the "Calling Fortress."
Calling Fortress
Japan Server
Shibuya
Dungeon/ Monsters Present
PVP Permitted
Skill Use Permitted
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
What's this?
It's a prototype based on the
game's capture functions.
But if you use it for more than
ten minutes, it explodes.
Until last week, it was completely normal.
It seems there's a seal on the entrance.
Is it possible that monster eggs
or an eternal moth cocoon fell
from the moon and was drawn by
that device you call an antenna?
From the moon in the sky?
On the moon is a community of Observers
whom we're trying to contact.
And the monsters called "Geniuses"
were there, as well, right?
So are those eternal moths a type of Genius?
Then why would they want everyone's MP?
Roe 2's letter did say that the Geniuses
are collecting something they called "empathions."
I didn't understand what they were, though.
Is it MP?
That's highly likely.
The eternal moths appeared at the same
time yesterday and the day before.
The same time the moon rises.
18:22, precisely.
A third wave is certain to come tonight.
The first time, it was People of the Land,
and the second, it was adventurers, too.
Their numbers are increasing.
To prevent damages, we'll probably
have to destroy the antenna.
But that's the only thing in Yamato that...
Yes.
And according to legend,
an antenna is necessary for
communication with the stars.
If we destroy it, Shiroe's plan may
be impossible to execute.
No way.
What about the other servers?
We don't know.
We have barely any information
on the foreign servers.
Even if the facilities do exist somewhere
else, they may be nonfunctional.
But if we don't do something,
we'll have even bigger problems.
Maybe we'll just have to give up this time.
So what do we do?
The Calling Fortress is a raid zone.
Even if it appears to be in front of us,
it's impossible to attack from the outside.
We'll need to go inside from the main
entrance, and head for the goal.
We'll dispatch a raid team immediately.
Shiroe      Naotsugu      Tetra
Party 1     Akatsuki     Marielle     Kushiyatama
Party 2     Serara     Nyanta     Nazuna
Soujirou     Korou     Henrietta
Party 3     Fragrant Olive    Richou     Rieze
Tohya     Minori      Yuzuko
Party 4      Rundel Haus Code     Isuzu     Hien
Shouryuu     Isami     Kurinon
Some of them don't have very high levels.
I selected them from people who didn't fall
asleep when exposed to the moths' scales.
Of course, there's no guarantee
they'll withstand the next attack.
You don't want to investigate the fortress first?
There's no time.
So we're taking a gamble, huh?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You're coming, too, old man?
Yes. Apparently, there's a special seal
on the Calling Fortress's entrance.
Shiroe asked me to release it.
That's not the only reason, right?
This situation is a first in the world's history.
As the bearer of the Miral Lake name,
I have a responsibility to see it through.
We may not be able to protect you.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of myself.
Facilities across Yamato have been knocked out.
I've heard what's happening in Shibuya, too.
I shall see what decision you adventurers make.
Take care of Akihabara for me.
You take care, as well.
Einz...
Yes?
I'll believe
that you're a member of the Round Table, too.
Our target is the raid zone deep in the
Shibuya Dungeon, the Calling Fortress.
We will destroy the antenna there to stop
the spread of the eternal moths,
and then wipe them out.
Let's finish this by moonrise!
There are six hours until moonrise.
Eight moon rabbits from the old Dougenzaka area.
Moon Rabbit
Average level 91!
Keep pressure on them while heading
toward Old Center Street.
Six rabbits from two o'clock,
and six from ten o'clock.
This is just so strange.
This happens right when we start thinking
about communicating with the moon?
Shiro!
From ahead of us, too!
Nine more!
Party 2, draw them to the front.
Party 1, front line, head to the front and...
No, split the group to the rear!
Richou and Tohya, support group 1!
Roger!
Yuzuko, Olive, support each party.
Forward, group 4, secure a path!
Understood.
Minori, was it?
She's so cute!
It's called "Abbreviated Full-Power
Controlled Combat."
She learned it directly from Shiroe!
There are just too many!
Here.
I'll heal you, Naotsugu.
Tetra's healing will work
better than hers, Naotsugu!
If they know what we're doing,
this is exactly what they want.
Olive, get back!
No, cover Richou from the right!
Whoops...
Shiroe?
Ah, sorry!
Shiroe!
More enemies!
New enemies incoming from eight o'clock.
Sh-Shiroe!
A minotaur!
That's a surprise I'm not at all happy about!
This is an ambush!
You're kidding me!
We may really lose our hope to get home.
Shiroe?
Two minotaurs!
Your orders!
Center around parties 2 and 4
and break through Old Spain-zaka!
Whoa, there... Take care.
Nyanta...
Wow, they're all monsters I've never seen.
This is very interesting...
Watch out, old guy!
Party 1, fall back and focus on healing!
But we can't abandon this world,
or the People of the Land, to this state.
Maintain formation and keep going forward.
No, right at the next corner!
This is a mess.
This isn't like him...
We didn't have time to investigate in advance.
It can't be helped.
Still...
This is pathetic.
My lord respects him as the
Tea Party's famous strategist.
I wondered how good he was...
This is the Calling Fortress.
Four hours and seven minutes left.
This is a complicated seal...
Okay, here you go.
Nice panties!
Way to go, skeleton-guy!
Oh, I know. I'm awesome.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Our phantom-beast scouts have
given us some information,
but as we head for the top,
we'll confirm the situation on each floor.
Each party's back ranks will keep their distance,
to prepare for the unexpected.
Votive Sword Kogarasumaru!
Man, I can't see Sou...
More enemies! Six rabbits!
I won't let the captain be the only one to fight!
Samurai's Challenge!
Fighting girls are so great...
The shining sweat!
The West Wind gets along well, don't they?
We're partners. Of course we do.
I love it!
Huh?!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Don't worry about me.
All these corridors look the same...
It's literally a labyrinth!
A dead end?
It's sealed with cocoons!
Same over here, my lord!
I can't see past it!
Shiroe!
The west corridor is overflowing with moon rabbits!
Fragrant Olive     Nazuna     Kurinon
Minori     Yuzuko
The way we're running through
MP could prove fatal.
But...
We'll head back down for now.
After coming this far?
Shiro?
Head down and into the central courtyard!
As long as we defend the two exits,
we can hold our position here.
We'll take turns recovering MP.
If we only had a safe zone...
The mob levels are high.
This is tougher than I expected.
Shiroe!
A minotaur!
Another set of two!
Six black ogres from above!
Twelve moon rabbits from above!
Split up and get ready!
No time to rest, huh?
Raids are always like this.
Well, ever since I decided to go with
you, I've been ready for this.
You're always the one at the very front.
You don't think I'm some kind
of bad luck charm, do you?
You'll make me cry.
I'll make you cry later!
Serara!
Chief!
I-I'm sorry!
No! Tohya!
I can't keep them delayed...
Okay, I'll use an Aura Heal—
Hey!
You can't just push an idol away—
Tetra, heal everyone!
Marielle!
New enemy.
Half-moon venom hydrangea.
Shiroe, we've lost three!
Our MP won't last.
I'm prioritizing Richou's group.
Hang in there somehow!
Roger!
AoE attack!
Everyone split up!
No, use the shrine priestess's four-way barrier!
No one has the MP!
Korou!
Bad status...
Rot! DoT!
It's no good! Our HP won't last, either!
Three lost. Five dead.
We've lost a third in such a short time.
We can't keep going! This is really bad!
Shiro...
Give the order to withdraw!
Shiro!
My lord...
Flip Gate.
Where are we? A studio?
Calling Fortress
Safe Zone A
Japan Server
Shibuya
Dungeon/ No Monsters
No PvP
Skill Use Restricted
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
So this is the revive point...
Not the dungeon's entrance?
Marie, I'm sorry...
I couldn't protect you.
It's fine.
I just fell down the hole and ended up here.
Does it hurt?
Want to see my panties?
No, I'm fine.
It's only a scratch.
Um, thanks for your help back there.
It's fine.
You had more MP left than I did.
I didn't even think about it!
Marielle!
I haven't been on a raid this tough in a long time.
That tickles!
Hey, get away!
Um...
Everyone...
I'm sorry.
Shiroe...
Shiroe?
H-Henrietta?
My lord...
Um, Shiroe...
We're staying in this world!
I know what you're thinking.
You're worried that if we destroy the antenna,
we won't be able to go home, right?
It isn't that I don't want to go home,
but I wasn't really sure about it.
If I can have time to think it over,
that's just as good.
It doesn't mean we'll never get home, does it?
And we can't just leave the People of the Land.
It didn't
go well for us in Safil...
Even if they thank us and say we saved them,
some people will never make it home.
I don't know if we'll be able to go home.
But being able to go home makes you happy, right?
So we need to make everyone happy!
We can go home after we do that!
You lack resolve, guild master.
Just focus on what you can do!
I don't know what I can do.
But I won't let you bear the burden alone.
We...
I will bear it with you!
So...
You heard them.
Shiroe...
But...
It's okay.
You'll be fine, no matter what.
Akatsuki...
Yes?
Hey, you're safe?
We couldn't reach you with telepathy,
so I got worried and came to look—
Wait.
Someone's in front of the antenna.
I can't see his status from here.
But most likely...
Understood.
Woodstock, you return to Akihabara
and bolster the defenses.
The raid boss.
He wasn't there when we investigated, right?
Maybe he spawns when the moon rises?
Like the eternal moths?
What a pain.
Which means if we defeat him...
The moths might all disappear, too!
I don't know if he'll be that easy to handle...
But the weird parts of this are still a game.
Thank you, Henrietta.
You're welcome.
Antenna... MP... Raid boss, huh?
Meow.
There are thirty-four minutes until moonrise.
There's no time—
Thirty minutes is plenty.
It was never possible to choose
either the world or the antenna.
Pick one? That's impossible.
So we won't choose.
We'll just tear apart this nonsense.
Let's save them both.
The world and the antenna.
I'll show you what "two birds
with one stone" really means.
The counterattack begins.
Shining glasses and sharpened minds.
Friends you can believe in.
They won't pick just one anymore.
They'll protect everything.
That is their answer.
At the end of the battle, they reach a place
where Shiroe takes on a new quest.
For the two worlds he loves so much.
The Pioneers
Next time: The Pioneers.
Cross over the horizon.