How can this be?
My granddaughter Asseylum, assassinated,
and we go to war against Earth without
so much as a declaration?
Surely they knew what would come
of harming a goodwill ambassador.
Knowing that, why?
What is going on there
without my knowledge?
We are told that the assassination
was a terrorist act.
But does that not imply no hostile
intent on the part of the UE?
It is obvious that anti-Vers
factions exist on Earth.
To allow this assassination
in spite of that
leads me to believe that her
security was deliberately lax.
There is also the possibility
that the assassination
was perpetrated by the UE government under
the guise of a terrorist attack.
To what end?
Her Highness is of royal blood, one able
to summon forth the power of Aldnoah.
That bloodline is the very foundation
of the Vers Empire's might.
This is baffling.
Inform the UE government that we
are suspending hostilities.
And then uncover
the truth.
Yes, Majesty.
How goes the war,
Count Cruhteo?
All goes well.
Tokyo and its surrounding cities
have been conquered,
and Shinawara, where Princess Asseylum
fell, is already in our hands.
Well done.
Incidentally, where is
Sir Trillram?
Is he still out distinguishing himself
on the battlefield?
As to that... I regret to inform you
that he has fallen in battle.
Fallen in battle?
Is this true?!
Yes. It is most regrettable.
He was caught in the meteor bombardment
that some ruffian launched on my territory.
That is not possible...
Odd. I informed him
of the bombardment.
He should not have been
caught in it unawares.
Sir Trillram served me well
as my guest.
To think that he should be taken
from us in this manner...
We shall pray for the soul
of our brave warrior.
On that note, did anyone
witness his end?
What should I do?
They knew Princess Asseylum
was alive, and yet...
If I do nothing, she really will
be assassinated sooner or later.
I want it repaired immediately!
Don't just stand there!
The Argyre... Its head!
Thank goodness you
are unharmed, Sir Vlad!
You call this unharmed?!
My honor has been tarnished!
Was your opponent
that powerful?
No. I was made a fool of by some
orange, impudent cur!
What are you doing here?
Should you not be at
the Count's side?
I was disciplined.
For speaking out of turn.
Speaking out of turn?
I said that I wished him
to send me into battle, too.
You're just like them, I see.
You're a Terran. Impudent.
You are that eager to distinguish
yourself in battle and win favor?
Pathetic.
It's not like that! I just...
Her Highness, I want to...
Pathetic.
Oh, I get it.
This puts it on autopilot.
What are your names?
Nina Klein.
I'm Yutaro Tsumugi.
Kisaki Matsuribi.
Wait, are we going to
be sent into battle?
No way. These are just
supplementary lessons.
Just to cover our bases.
Gotcha.
They're covering their bases...
You're the one who drove off
the enemy Kataphrakt, Amifumi?
Yes, Capt. Magbaredge!
Actually, it was this boy
who planned the operation.
Operation?
Go on!
I don't think it was elaborate
enough to call an "operation."
You were the pilot
of that trainer?
Yes, ma'am. I'm Inaho Kaizuka.
Kaizuka?
Yes, ma'am. Warrant Officer
Kaizuka is my sister,
That was fine work, Inaho.
Your efforts saved the lives of many
of my crew, as well as the civilians.
Your sister must be proud.
If you were enlisted, I'd be tempted
to put you in for commendations.
Commendations?
Medals.
That's amazing!
We could get medals!
Amazing? Is it?
Of course it is! I've never
seen anyone with a medal!
That's only because nobody's seen
any real fighting for so long.
Instructor Marito!
"Instructor"? Does this look
like a school to you?
My apologies, Lt. Marito.
Medals are gonna be a whole
lot more common soon.
We're in a war. Honor is about the
only reward they can hand out.
Well, dying for honor
isn't such a bad thing.
Because it's hard to survive
and live in misery.
Lt. Marito.
Do you have a moment?
Hanging out your shingle
on a military boat, Doc?
Those who do not work
do not eat.
I can't say that I appreciate you shattering
those kids' illusions, Lieutenant.
You aren't hitting
the bottle, I see.
I'm so touched
that you trust me.
I thought you might be picking on
those kids because you were drunk.
Maybe I am under the influence.
Of my lot in life.
The Tanegashima Report,
you mean?
Sins you've committed cling to
your soul and haunt you forever.
And sins that have gone unpunished
aren't forgiven until you die.
Humeray...
Your hands are clean.
On the contrary, you saved his life.
Is that what I did?
Hey, what's up?
It's from Mars!
They say they've announced
an armistice!
Attention, foolish people of Earth.
Rayregalia Vers Rayvers,
noble emperor of the Vers Empire,
has issued an armistice declaration
to the United Earth government.
Even as we feel intense shame in
our common ancestry with you,
We can barely transmit at all... All we get
are these pirate broadcasts of theirs.
our desire is that this act conveys to
you, the deeply sinful people of Earth
So what's this mean,
the war's on hold for now?
who took the life of Her Highness
Princess Asseylum,
Grandfather must be trying to put a stop
to the knights' outrageous behavior.
the profound compassion
of His Imperial Majesty Rayregalia.
The emperor of Mars?
I repeat, Rayregalia Vers Ravers,
noble emperor of the Vers Empire...
What is the meaning of this?
They say that His Imperial Majesty has issued
an armistice declaration to the UE government.
Over our heads?! Without so much
as a word to the Orbital Knights?
I must offer counsel
to His Majesty...
I shall use the
audience chamber!
Call the moon base!
Yes, Milord!
He was not killed in the
meteor bombardment, then?
No, Milord.
The Nilokeras appears to have been
damaged in battle and then deserted.
There is someone whose actions
I wish to look into.
Infiltrate Castle Cruhteo
and continue your investigation.
Yes, Milord!
They open hostilities without warning
and then stop just as abruptly.
This whole thing doesn't
make any sense.
Do you suppose that means the enemy
isn't monolithic, either?
Has anyone tried
to contact us?
No, ma'am. The jamming
is still too strong.
Where are you going, Milady?
To speak with
this ship's master.
I shall tell her
who I really am.
Princess, you-
And then I shall have her
inform Vers of my safety.
Doing so will end this war.
It's too dangerous! The rebels will come
for you before word reaches His Majesty!
Which is exactly why this armistice
provides us with the perfect opportunity.
Don't underestimate them.
They aren't the sort to obey
the terms of an armistice.
You'll just get yourself crushed.
But the longer this war drags on,
the more casualties there will be.
If you want to die,
that's your decision.
But leave me out of it.
An attack?
But there's an armistice!
It simply won't do
for the war to end
without me having a chance
to redeem my honor!
Bastard... He wants revenge?
Lieutenant! Where are you going?!
Launch Kataphrakts! Intercept!
Captain, I suggest
relocating to CIC.
I'm fine here.
Unacceptable!
What is His Majesty thinking?!
His own flesh and blood
was killed!
Assemble a fact-finding mission.
As per His Majesty's orders, we shall uncover
the details of the Princess' assassination!
Yes, Milord!
I can... I can use this
to speak to His Majesty!
I'm back on-
Come! Let us pick up
where we left off!
Draw sword!
Aldaniti Platoon, prepare for launch.
Raising elevator #2.
All units, don't use HE rounds.
Engage using AP rounds.
Bastard!
Wait!
He's using the bridge
as a shield!
Nao!
Draw sword.
What are you doing?
Come down from there!
I could say the same to you, Yuki.
You're injured.
We're short on pilots!
Then it'll be just as good
if I go out instead.
Where are my pajamas?
The ones with the patches.
Majesty!
Who are you?
Slaine Troyard, Majesty.
Slaine? Ah, it has been
a long time.
It has, Majesty.
What is the purpose
of this visit?
There is a matter that I must
inform you of, Majesty.
The truth is, Princess
Asseylum is alive.
I have seen her
with my own two eyes.
It was the Orbital Knights who made the attempt
on her life in their lust for war with Earth.
But their attempt failed,
and Princess Asseylum is alive
somewhere on Earth!
So, you show yourself,
my nemesis.
A trainer?
I don't believe it, is that-
Inaho?!
A tactical suit isn't gonna
protect you against that!
There is no armor my blades
cannot slice through!
This will be over
in an instant!
Inaho!
Yeah!
Reactive armor. Armor plates
that are made of explosives.
They were originally designed to detonate
and deflect incoming enemy fire.
Damn you!
He's using the blasts to disperse
the blade's plasma?!
Control! Tilt the ship!
Mizusaki!
Flood ballast!
Open well dock hatch!
Unhand me!
I'd be glad to.
Backpack dumped.
Bailing out.
What the-
Inaho!
What just happened?!
Steam explosion.
The massive amount of thermal energy in those
blades flashed the seawater to steam
and the impact from the high
pressure steam destroyed him.
Inaho Kaizuka... He hardly
seems like a student, does he?
No, ma'am. He's a surprisingly
useful boy.
Mizusaki. Shall I tell you
why you can't get a date?
Don't partners prefer
a forthright personality?
Yours isn't forthright.
It's unfiltered.
Let's go pick him up!
If what you say is true,
it is most regrettable indeed.
I beg you, Majesty, please stop
this war without delay.
And please rescue
Princess Asseylum.
I shall see to it at once.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I shall take my leave.
It is exactly as you said,
Count Saazbaum.
The Terrans are not
to be trusted.
They have spies everywhere,
and are scheming to overthrow Vers if
the opportunity should present itself.
It is scandalous that they would try
to deceive Your Majesty with lies!
You, whose heart is grieving the
loss of your beloved princess!
My Emperor.
I ask that you smite this foul race
with the iron fist of justice.
In the name of Rayregalia Vers
Rayvers, Emperor of Vers,
I hereby renew my
declaration of war.
Attack the Earth!
Those who would do harm
to my flesh and blood...
...must burn!
Slaine Troyard, you mean
harm to our cause...
How ironic...
Is it not, Dr. Troyard?