Great, great, Issei! Push it,
push it, Issei! One more time!
Karasuno                 Wakunan
Sorry... I'm gonna go to the bathroom...
So go on ahead.
He's really pumped about
going to the bathroom.
He must need to take a shit.
Say "poop!" You're so vulgar, Kageyama-kun!
Crap.
I don't think he actually
went to the bathroom...
Poop.
Crap.
Poop!
Ukai-san...
I'm sorry for wasting my chance.
"How effectively you serve
will determine if you can win or not."
I heard your direction during the
Fukurodani match and understood it...
And I understood my role.
And then I thought I wanted
to be able to fight, too...
But...
I ran away at the last minute.
Please...
Give me one more chance.
Oh, shut up already. I know.
Please put me in.
Haikyu!!
Kyotani, get one more in!
Sorry! It's long!
Mattsun!
Episode 22: "The Former Coward's Fight"
All right!
Damn it. Sorry!
Aoba Johsai                Karasuno
This isn't good.
Seijoh's #16 is finding his groove.
Great, great, Issei! Push it,
push it, Issei! One more time!
They're ahead by five...
Karasuno, fight!
Let's move back a little.
He's probably not going to drop it up front.
Yeah.
Right.
Nice serve!
Bring it, bring it, bring it...
Tanaka!
Yeah!
Aoba Johsai             Karasuno
It's only just begun!
Shoyo, nice serve!
Hey! That guy...
Pardon me. We're switching players.
Oh, there he is. The scaredy cat pinch server.
Right. The guy who was in
the match with Wakunan, too.
Though I totally understand
getting freaked out.
I would hate having to serve during a pinch.
He's the one that got all stiff and
failed miserably last time, right?
Yeah...
Yamaguchi, get 10 points!
That'd end the match...
I'd forgive you.
G-Give it to 'em good, Yamaguchi!
R-Remain calm... Calm.
Nice serve!
Nice serve.
Give it your all!
Right!
One, and...
Yamaguchi, one more! Nice serve!
Eight seconds...
You know there's time after the
whistle blows for you to serve, right?
Yes.
You basically get freaked
out by the whistle and then
do your serve toss almost every time.
Don't be so panicky.
Yes...
Well, all that's left is this.
You went to Ukai's, right?
Yes.
On your own.
Then you're already a
completely different player.
Go out there and do
what you want to do.
All of their players have the
nerve to get serious...
Out!
All right!
All...
...right!
He did it...
Tadashi!
Nice serve!
It got in!
We're...
...supposed to be...
...cheering for Aoba Johsai.
Wait, what? Isn't that a bit overboard?
Yamaguchi, nice serve!
That's just one point.
That's it! Get one more!
A no-touch ace!
Go and catch up!
I'm sorry.
Don't mind! Don't worry about it.
It changed a lot...
Even I thought it was out.
This is why I hate jump floats.
That was awesome, Yamaguchi!
Why, you little...
R-Right...
It's not that surprising.
There you go again...
In these five months,
he practiced serving more than anyone else.
Why you little...
Aoba Johsai                         Karasuno
Yamaguchi, one more!
Give it all you've got!
Give it all you've got, Yamaguchi!
He'll be fine.
You always feel worse
after you run away.
I'm pretty sure Yamaguchi
feels that way, too.
A shot to break through the skin...
Yeah, and...
The start of our counterattack.
Cut it off!
Yeah.
In volleyball, where it's important
to connect with your teammates,
the serve is the only solitary play.
Yeah...
It can also be said that it's the only play
where you can score on your own.
As volleyball evolved,
the serve's power and motive has
evolved more than anything else.
And in modern volleyball,
the serve is a powerful attack
that won't get caught by the
wall known as the block.
Kyotani!
Damn it!
A s-second service ace!
Yes!
All right!
Yamaguchi!
Nice serve.
What the heck is that serve?
That was awesome.
Yamaguchi-kun!
Yamaguchi!
One more!
Bring it!
Got it!
You catch jump floats
with an over-handed hit!
Makki, nice.
He picked it up! They're going to attack.
This fear when you change from being the hunter to becoming the hunted...
Iwaizumi!
He received it with his body?!
Not yet... Not yet.
I'm not going to let you serve just yet!
Cover!
Thanks, Kageyama...
Tsukishima, get the last!
All right!
Tsukki...
A wipe!
They used that block really well.
Tsukishima!
Aoba Johsai                             Karasuno
Now they've gotten three consecutive points.
One more.
Yeah!
Oh? Seijoh's taking a time out.
They're physically stopping the momentum.
All right!
Making Seijoh take a time out
is amazing, Yamaguchi!
Yamaguchi!
Th-Thank you...
That #12... made a really bold receive.
That was just luck, though.
Wow...
It hurts a lot...
All right! Let's win this!
Keep it up!
I want to be able to control
my body like the other guys!
I want to be able to control the ball!
I want to fight head-on
with strong opponents!
All right!
Yamaguchi!
One more!
Keep your eye on the ball!
Right!
Listen up, Tadashi.
You can't give them the
chance to take the ball.
Aim straight through, as close
as you can get to the white...
...and hit!
I only have one weapon:
my serve.
The chance I received
is just one service chance.
I'm going to fight putting my pride and
the flow of the game into that shot.
I am...
a pinch server.
It's in!
Is luck on our side now?
No, it's not just that.
Now...
Aoba Johsai               Karasuno
We're tied.
Haikyu!!
Aoba Johsai               Karasuno
Now they're tied!
Karasuno caught up!
Yamaguchi!
That same net drop happened during
the Wakunan match, too, right?
Tadashi's a lucky boy!
Yup, yup!
It might be a net drop,
but it's completely different from
the one during the Wakunan match.
During the Wakunan match,
Yamagauchi, one more!
Tadashi was thinking about whether
or not the ball would go in.
Yamaguchi, nice serve!
Right now, he's thinking about
where he's going to serve it.
This net drop was a result
of switching to offense.
How awesome, Tadashi!
Though I'm sure he's entirely
comfortable with that.
One more, Yamaguchi!
The serve toss keeps getting really low.
Right!
Let's calm down, now.
I am calm.
That one couldn't be helped.
We'll get the next one.
That's it, you guys!
You guys are too great.
It makes your captain sad.
It's got a loose spin!
It's not changing direction!
Got it!
Nice receive!
One-touch!
Nice one-touch!
Azumane-san!
Nice, Kageyama!
Three blockers!
And a very high block...
Back!
Out!
All right!
Tanaka, nice call!
H-Hey, seriously?
They...
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
Karasuno's at match point!
One more! Nice serve!
Yamaguchi-kun...
...is the hero of this match.
Just one more point...
Just one more point and we win!
Get it in! Please, get it in!
Tadashi!
Yamaguchi! Just one more!
Get it in there!
Feels good...
I'll get it!
Damn it, they're good.
Nice, Watacchi!
Stop it!
Stop it, please!
All right!
Nice kill!
Great, great, Hajime! Push it,
push it, Hajime! One more time!
We finally cut it off...
How many points did he get, anyway?
That was magnificent!
Good job!
Thank you.
You did great, Yamaguchi!
All right!
Thanks!
That was awesome!
Concentrate on the one!
Next time,
I'll get 10 points.
I'm not gonna lose!
Hanamaki, nice serve!
The chance that Yamaguchi gave us...
Daichi-san!
We're not gonna let it go to waste!
All right!
Nice, Azumane!
They're there again!
Match point!
Go!
All right!
They got it back so easily.
They managed a quick even though
they're being cornered right now.
Not to mention, right up front.
If it were me, I'd be relying on the ace.
Yeah!
Aoba Johsai                  Karasuno
Nice receive!
There're two!
All right!
Tsukishima, nice kill!
Hey, your movements are stiff, Kindaichi.
Yes! No!
Which is it?
This is a critical moment for us.
We can't make this the
third-years' last match.
Don't think about anything unnecessary.
No matter what, you only need to focus on
the ball in front of you.
Right!
Asahi, get this!
Nice serve!
It's long! Get this!
Great, great, Yutaro. Push it,
push it, Yutaro! One more time!
All right!
Nice kill!
Thanks!
I guess that's to be expected of Seijoh.
The next one is going to be huge.
But...
And...
...in modern volleyball, the
serve is a powerful attack
that won't get caught by
the wall known as the block.
That was basically a spike...
All right!
Great, great, Toru! Push it,
push it, Toru! One more time!
Aoba Johsai                      Karasuno
Seijoh turned it around into a set point!
Are they going to get the set?
Damn it!
This isn't possible with just the two of us.
Asahi, please. We're counting on you.
Yeah.
Azumane-kun's going to be
receiving the serve, too?
If that's what Sawamura and
Nishinoya decided,
then that's probably best.
It appears that Oikawa's serves
focus more on power than control.
Rather than them scoring a no-touch,
touching and getting the ball
up in any way is better.
We received plenty of Ubugawa's
and Fukurodani's serves.
It's okay. We can fight.
Bring it!
Nice serve!
Daichi-san!
Good!
Tanaka, nice!
Kageyama!
Asahi!
Asahi-san!
Nice receive!
All right!
Aoba Johsai                 Karasuno
They got the set back.
I thought Karasuno was just
going to win straight through.
And we had them cornered!
Don't mind!
We're just getting started!
Damn it! That third set is gonna be rough!
Let's change it up!
Right!
His serve really is amazing.
You were awesome, too, Yamaguchi.
He's much more experienced than I am.
That might be obvious
because he's a third-year,
but I don't think that's the only thing.
Not the only thing?
A jump serve is a serve that balances
a lot of power with a high risk.
To be able to add force to his serve
and still have it land in when they
were cornered like that...
He's something special.
Yamaguchi!
Those were nice serves!
Th-Thanks.
But I've still got a ways to go.
Only half of my serves were any good.
Then be super happy about
the half that were good!
Even if you put aside regret,
you'll end up feeling it anyway.
Right now, you need to make sure
you grasp this good feeling
and never forget it.
Grasp really hard.
And do it again next time, too.
Yes!
So we ended up getting a full set...
Our first practice match,
the Inter-High prelims...
And now...
We're having our most intense match yet.
Difficult opponents...
Troublesome opponents...
We didn't even have much of a connection
with them until last year...
They were supposed to be beneath us...
But apparently we're fated
to play to the fullest.
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
The final set...
Rule the Court
Fly
This is our last battle!
That was amazing, Yamaguchi-kun!
Th-Thank you very much, Yachi-san.
Just in case, I had an AED,
stretcher, and coffin prepared,
but they weren't necessary at all!
Huh?! Wasn't there something that
didn't belong at the end there?
Episode 23: "Team"
Next time on Haikyu!!:"Team."