Black Mist
After our class came back from the trip,
things took a slightly strange turn
in our classroom.
Huh?
I don't have a single piece of chalk.
There were several pieces just this morning...
Fujiwara-no-Teika
Traces of Beauty
Graceful
Hey! Who threw that eraser?!
Well?
LANGUAGE PREP ROOM
It's gone... It's gone...
It's gone.
It's not here.
LANGUAGE PREP ROOM
Excuse me.
I'm here to prep the classroom.
What's wrong?
Oh. You're on duty today?
I'm missing my timeline.
Timeline? Is it that scroll you always use?
The green one.
Yes.
That's right. What should I do?
It'll be troublesome if I don't have it.
What's been going on recently?
These incidents keep happening...
Is it just my imagination?
She looks like she's lost a lot of weight.
I'll just have to do without it.
Oh, the bell's about to ring.
Scroll, scroll...
Where could that long thing have gone?
It would stand out if it had fallen on the floor.
I've got it!
PING
Teacher, I might know where it is!
- Huh? Ms. Kawamoto!
- I'll be right back!
WHIZ
That's right. Now, even the black mood
that was taking hold of the class
had tried to engulf the teacher.
Teacher!
Oh, thank goodness. Where was it?
It was mixed in with the historical timelines
in the social studies room.
You found it for me. Thank you, Ms. Kawamoto.
I'm impressed you figured it out.
Oh, I thought they all had the same shape, so...
Brown-noser.
That's what she says,
but Kawamoto is probably the one who hid it.
That was Ms. Takagi's voice.
Would you stop muttering insults about me
that are just loud enough for me to hear?
Ms. Takagi.
Huh?
Excuse me?
Did I say something?
Don't, Ms. Kawamoto!
Did you think I was going to hit you?
Of course I wouldn't do that.
Because that would be playing
right into your hands.
Answer me.
What do you mean, I hid it?
Please, Ms. Kawamoto...
Why did you say that?
Ms. Kawamoto, stop it!
Teacher, you heard what she said, didn't you?
Why are you stopping me?
Do you think I'm the one who hid it?
Stop it, already!
Do not raise your voice!
What should I do?
Even I can imagine what happened.
I'm sure Ms. Takagi and her friends hid it
and then blamed Ms. Kawamoto, right?
But so what?!
There's no proof.
So how am I supposed to prove it?!
I've had enough. I can't take it anymore.
Don't get me involved.
Every year, every single year...
The students change, but every time,
there's someone who gets left out and bullied.
And I'm just sick of it.
How can you have so much free time
to be harassing your classmates?
Are you stupid?
Tell me, Ms. Takagi, how is it
that you have that much free time?
Stop torturing your classmates
and study more!
In the first place,
who do you think you are?
Involving everyone else in your nonsense...
Think about how you're disrupting the class.
Everyone's studying for entrance exams!
Do you understand?
As if a dam had burst, Teacher kept talking.
But her words became less articulate.
After falling silent for a while...
Her face darkened...
and she collapsed.
She never returned to school after that.
It was announced that
she had been hospitalized due to anxiety.
What? So Teacher's become a shut-in?
Unbelievable.
What's going to happen to our class?
And we've got entrance exams.
This is a royal pain.
And like, whose fault is it?
And so, until your new homeroom teacher
is decided, I'll be teaching this class from today.
I'm Mr. Kokubu, the head teacher.
July 10th (Thursday)
On Duty
It's almost summer vacation.
For you third-years taking
high school entrance exams soon,
you understand that how
you spend this summer break
will result in a turning point, right?
It's unfortunate for you to have a change
in homeroom teachers during this period.
Plus, I heard some of you complaining.
But there was bullying so bad in here
that a student transferred to another school,
and yet, out of 38 kids,
no one raised their voice except certain people.
So this is the price you're paying for ignoring it.
That being said, before summer vacation,
I'd like to resolve this to some extent,
so I'll be talking to you individually.
First Takagi, and then Kawamoto.
The new homeroom teacher's clear,
reasonable manner of speaking
made the class fall silent.
When you're called to stay after school,
report to the faculty room.
ATTENDANCE RECORD
That's all.
Then, to sort out the situation,
each of our parents were called in.
Parent-teacher-student conferences.
Yeah. He asked me a lot of questions.
It seems Teacher knew
what was going on the whole time.
But she'd been a teacher for a long time,
and the same thing
kept happening again and again.
And her class would be
thrown into chaos every time.
She kept seeing situations
she couldn't do anything about,
until it reached the point
where she couldn't even get involved.
Sis, what should I have done?
It went so far that
you have to come in to the school.
I...
Hina, come on.
One cup of French toast!
With plenty of fresh cream!
BOOM
Here, hold this.
All right, next!
Sir, I'll take two beef croquettes!
One just as-is, one slathered in sauce!
Sure thing! Coming right up!
The depth of the water fluctuates.
Please do not step in.
You sure?
You're always warning me
about spoiling my dinner.
It's fine.
If you don't get to eat what you like at a time
like this, when will you eat it?
Hina, I'm going. Be it
a parent-teacher conference, or whatever,
I'll always be on your side.
Okay.
Come on, let's go grocery shopping
and then go home.
What do you want for dinner?
Stew. Can I have it over my rice?
Sure. I'll put it on my rice this time too.
Black Mist
Light
CRESCENT MOON
I'll go.
No, I'm going.
How could I not go?
I'm going to go and give those selfish,
rotten parents a piece of my mind!
You can't!
Tuesday is when you have
that important catering job, remember?
HISS
It's for an important tea party
to celebrate the 60th anniversary
of Shoueidou's founding, our valued customer!
SHOUEIDOU
Everyone is looking forward
to your sweets, Grandpa!
You know that better than anyone!
Damn it!
This... This is a big deal
for my granddaughter, and I...
Grandpa, it'll be okay.
I'm going to have a good talk with her teacher,
so it'll be all right.
Leave this to me!
I promise it'll be okay!
Akari...
Akari, I'm sorry...
I...
I've put you through so much...
Don't talk like that.
Don't worry about Hina and Momo.
They'll be okay.
It's all right. I'll protect them
from the both of us, Mom.
That dream again...
What should I do? I keep waking up.
I need to get my sleep.
The conference is tomorrow.
And I made a promise...
to Mom and Grandpa.
Well, goodbye.
Okay, Ms. Kawamoto, please come in.
- Teacher!
- Mr. Kokubu!
What is it? What's wrong?
- Ueda was screwing around...
- and broke the window with a mop!
Huh? Was anyone hurt?
- Suzuki!
- His hand is bleeding!
What? What was that kid thinking?
Sorry, Kawamoto, can you
wait in there with your sister?
I'll be right back!
For crying out loud!
These kids are always causing trouble!
I'm suddenly in charge of two classes
and they don't even let me catch my breath!
Hey, Kobayashi! Go ahead of me
and tell everyone to stay away from the glass!
Well, we'll be on our way.
Okay. We'll go inside, then.
Oh, that's right.
You know, for us, the most important thing
this year are the high school entrance exams.
So I think it's better not to make any waves.
Well, going forward, if you would
advise your little sister to watch it...
Then for us, I wouldn't have to...
Well, you know...
What do you mean by that?
My daughter told me
everything I need to know.
It seems your little sister has various issues.
As far as I'm concerned...
I don't think my sister has any issues.
In fact, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
No issues, you say?!
She spread rumors
about my Megumi being a thief!
What does she have against my daughter?!
This is so upsetting!
Mrs. Takagi!
Do you have honest conversations
with your daughter?
Do you properly understand
what she's thinking right now?
Your daughter is the one who's been a bully.
Shut your mouth!
I've heard enough false accusations!
How low can you be?
WAAAAA
They're clashing?
This is why I scheduled them at different times!
RUN RUN
HUSTLE
Fine, then let me ask you this.
The proof that my daughter did it...
Where is it?
Proof?
Go ahead and show it to me!
Otherwise, I can't put credence in it.
Isn't that right?
To begin with,
my daughter says she didn't do it.
I believe my daughter.
Proof?
Proof...
Proof of that...
That's right, proof.
Proof!
You don't have any?
No proof? Then I think we're done.
It'll be okay, Mom. Leave it to me.
I promise to protect Hina and Momo.
What should I do?
What should I do? I promised her...
I can't...
think of what to say...
Mr. Kokubu, I'm sorry!
My sister isn't feeling great right now,
so can we take a break?
You must have been so nervous.
You're as white as a sheet.
Here, drink this. It'll calm you down.
Thank you very much.
Thank you...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Hina.
I couldn't respond to her...
I-I was pathetic.
After I told Grandpa and Mom
that it would be okay, to leave it to me...
A-After I calm down,
I-I'll go back there once more.
I'll sit down and talk to your teacher...
Sis.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for being on my side.
That alone makes me really happy!
HINATA KAWAMOTO LOVES GUYS
PERVERTED GIRL
BITCH IDIOT
Sis, I understand now.
No matter what, they would never admit it.
They don't even think they did anything wrong.
And it's just like with Chiho.
When it's over and done with,
they'll just forget about it.
I don't have a single reason
to waste my life on people like that.
I swear I'll come to school to the very last day!
I'll endure being ignored!
But if they do something to me,
I'll yell at them to stop!
I refuse to keep my mouth shut!
No matter what happens here,
if I just survive and graduate, I win!
Honestly, I don't know
where this is coming from.
Calling my Megumi a bully is a false accusation
of the highest order!
When there isn't even any proof.
True, there is no proof...
I mean, of course there's no proof.
What?
Right, Ms. Takagi?
The person who does it will never admit it.
The people around the bully know that if
they snitch, they'll be the next target,
so they keep their mouths shut.
There's no way proof will appear,
not with bullying.
It's only natural that there's no proof.
The only person who can say
there's been bullying is the victim.
So when Kawamoto said she was bullied,
that right there is the proof.
You have to be kidding me!
What if that girl is lying?
That's not proof!
She could say anything, right?
Then where's your proof...
that Kawamoto is lying?
Well, where's the proof?
Until you show me that,
as a representative of the school,
I can't accept your grievance.
Sis, it'll be all right.
Thank you.
I'm going to hang in there.
Thank you, Sis.
Excuse me.
Oh, Mr. Kokubu.
Miss, how are you feeling?
I'm really sorry.
Um, I feel better now, so—
No, no, stay right there.
Uh, Mr. Kokubu,
I was being quite rude earlier...
Um...
Miss, you have nothing at all to be sorry about.
It's okay.
More importantly...
Well...
Why don't we talk about what to do next?
Light
Next Episode Preview
Episode 35
Hey, Teacher...
How long are you going to
keep calling me here?
You don't understand how I feel.
So, tell me what's really going on.
All right... I'm ready.
- Hina!
- It's from Chiho!
ILLUSTRATION:
HIDEAKI NISHIKAWA
Don't miss the next episode of
"March Comes in Like a Lion."
I'll do whatever I can for Hina.