Hyakuzawa, nice kill!
Whoa, that angle's insane!
Nice kill!
Let's play!
He looks so intense up close.
You look like you're doing well again today,
Hyakuzawa-kun, so we're set.
Oh, right.
By the looks of it, no one over there
matches your height.
Oh, right.
If you get confused about the rules again,
make sure you ask.
I think I've got the rules by now.
You can see how their
#3 and #9 serve,
so let's keep the ball in the air
and cover our positions.
This team was able to give
Seijoh a hard time,
but that doesn't matter.
We will just fight, taking
advantage of our strength.
Let's go!
Kakugawa          Karasuno
Yeah!
If we win this match,
we get through the prelims.
Who the hell cares if they've
got a guy that's two meters tall?
We're gonna win no matter what!
Haikyu!!
Episode 13: "A Simple and Pure Strength"
Tsukishima, nice serve!
Musshi!
Got it!
Hyakuzawa!
A daring, straight, head-to-head competition!
Hopefully the ace's first
shot will set the mood.
Three blockers!
Although, it's not like it matters.
From above?
All right!
He hit that from above the block...
Hyakuzawa, nice kill!
Seriously?
There's no point in even blocking then.
Kakugawa          Karasuno
Coming in from the left!
Hyakuzawa!
Sorry, cover!
Hinata, get the last!
If I hit it, it'll get caught...
A dink?
All right!
What incredible height...
Normally, that would have been
able to go above the block.
One more!
But he's sort of ridiculous...
Right.
Listen carefully, Hyakuzawa.
Sorry! The ball was a little low.
No matter how weird that
#10's movements might be,
Don't worry about it.
when you're blocking, just follow the ball.
Next! Next!
All right, let's get one.
Right.
Yes!
There're even more people now.
See? That's the two meters guy.
Wow, you weren't kidding.
Wow, he's big.
Oh, Mikako-sensei.
Oh? Hello, Onoya-san!
This is my neighbor.
Mikako-sensei is the adviser
for a junior high volleyball club.
One of the players on the
opposing team is really tall.
Everyone on my team is so small,
so I can't help but cheer
for the smaller team.
No need to worry.
That big guy's got nothing on Karasuno's #10.
Right, Ukai-sensei?
It's true that he's got a disadvantage.
Like with height and speed.
Once a simple and pure strength
grows past a certain level,
it becomes something that
overwhelms an ordinary person.
In head-to-head competition, at least.
What the heck?
Why are you moving your
fingers like a pervy old man?
I'm not imagining it...
The ball seems to fit in my hands better.
Kakugawa          Karasuno
Up! Above the net.
Push it in, Hinata!
It's impossible.
There's no way that Hyakuzawa would
lose in a pushing match above the net.
All right!
Out!
Hey, Karasuno finally got a point.
All right!
Only because the other team messed up.
I've never heard of Kakugawa,
but they're making a name for themselves.
Only because of their guy
that's two meters tall.
It's basically a one-man show.
Crap! Did he hear us?
We already know that.
Like we care.
What?!
Come on. #9 is serving.
We're gonna get one.
Kageyama, nice serve!
It's off!
Got it!
As long as we can get the receive up,
everything becomes a chance ball.
All right!
I see... We're gonna have
to do something about that.
Nice kill, Hyakuzawa!
Oh, right.
But...
Sensei.
Right.
A time out, huh?
All right!
Looks like Karasuno doesn't stand a chance.
Th-That's not true!
You're on a roll!
This is your first official match
and you're doing awesome!
Oh, right.
Don't worry.
Just like other teams have aces,
we have Hyakuzawa.
The more Hyakuzawa scores,
the better we're supporting him.
Even if it doesn't seem like we're doing much.
We just have to look smug at the
fact that Hyakuzawa's on our team.
Indeed.
We just have to do our best to ensure
that Hyakuzawa performs his best.
Even if they call us a one-man show,
that is our winning style.
What's wrong?
Their #10...
I sort of feel bad when he's so
small and trying his best to jump.
Hey, are you trying to be mean?
Not really.
Well, it's true that
Hyakuzawa will be too tall for him, even though
he's only played volleyball for six months.
It sucks for him.
Passing in volleyball is hard...
but it's...
Simple.
No matter how high I jump,
he keeps hitting from above me.
What do I do?
Well, calm down.
Shoyo,f
volleyball isn't just about mid-air battles.
Huh?
I've noticed something.
Kakugawa          Karasuno
Left, left!
Hyakuzawa!
Here he comes!
After watching their previous
warm up, and how they play,
it appears that Kakugawa's #9 can't
hit the ball any way he wants.
He can only hit in a cross direction
that his body is facing.
Judging from their practice,
it seems that their #9 only
recently started volleyball.
So, like Lev from Nekoma?
However, he lacks the speed
and senses that Lev has.
If you put it another way,
Kakugawa's #9 only has his height,
but that alone is far beyond everyone else.
So when that #9 is going to hit,
let's abandon straights.
All right!
It's the thing where he jumps diagonally!
Go!
All right!
He somehow managed to get it by.
Kakugawa          Karasuno
That's amazing, Karasuno!
They managed to successfully deal
with that two-meter guy's attack.
It all depends on how they're
going to attack next.
Tanaka, your serve.
Right.
I'm...
feeling good today.
What?
Sawamura-san.
Yeah?
I'm feeling good today, so
can we try the new quick?
Excited
Nervous
Calm down, Hinata.
Huh? He's really sparkly.
He looks just like my dog
when it's really hungry.
Minamida!
Got it!
Hyakuzawa!
All right!
No matter how weird that
#10's movements might be,
when you're blocking, just follow the ball.
Just follow the ball...
There it is! Their super quick!
It's actually a bit different
from that, you know.
Yacchi, your face is all weird.
Yahoo! That little #10 is amazing!
He's probably the tallest player
in the prelims at 201 cm,
but the one who'll toying with him the most
might be only 162 cm tall.
Haikyu!!
Passing in volleyball is hard...
but it's...
Simple.
How?!
I'm 201 cm, and he's only 162 cm!
Why is he above me right now?
All right!
Kakugawa          Karasuno
Another quick from that #10.
How many is that now?
Hell yeah!
Are we at the top of our game?
Are we at the top of our game, Kageyama-kun?!
Shut up, you guys.
As long as we can get our quicks in,
S-Sorry.
we're back to being Karasuno.
Not exactly, Sensei.
You're thinking of the old Karasuno.
Hinata, relax!
He's in that corner.
Sugawara-san said it was so
I couldn't aim with my serve.
Well, it's not like I can do that anyhow!
It's not unusual for spikers
to concentrate just on attacks,
but for Kakugawa's #9,
it appears that the rest of
the team is protecting him.
I feel at ease when their
#9 is on the back line.
Nice receive!
We can't let our guard down, Sensei.
Two blockers!
Ack!
It appears you're right.
It's coming back! Hit it directly!
Rather than practicing how to
defend or figuring out how to hit,
I'm sure that #9 just practiced hitting
the high balls as hard as possible.
Go, Makado!
Even then, while their #9's in the back,
when we have mid-air battles at the net,
we have the upper hand.
#10! #10!
All right!
Kakugawa          Karasuno
Set point!
Yeah, we got it.
Just one more point!
Get it in one shot!
Sensei!
Is Sho-chan's quick also first tempo?
Do you remember your tempos?
Yep!
Nice receive!
Doing a slow running approach
to match a high toss and
then spiking the ball
is third tempo.
Kakugawa          Karasuno
All right!
Nice, Hyakuzawa!
Doing a running approach at the same
time the toss goes up and then spiking
is second tempo.
All right!
Nice, Musshi!
When the spiker first does a running approach
and then matches up with the toss
is first tempo.
Nishinoya, nice serve!
When you say you're going
to defeat a block,
it means you're going to hit the ball
from a higher point than the block.
Shrimpy versus two meters.
The one who gets to the top first, wins.
Shrimpy's quick actually isn't a first tempo.
By the time the setter
is about to set the ball,
he's already done his running
approach and has already jumped.
It's a minus tempo.
Kakugawa          Karasuno
All right!
Minus tempo!
Don't go trying to copy him, either.
Huh? Why not?
The only people ridiculous
enough to pull that off
are that duo, with their quick.
Hey, you asked me if I was actually
scared before the match...
Was that because you knew the
quick would go well today?
No. Well, I knew I was
doing better than normal.
Then why did you say that?
Well, I mean, you trained
plenty hard in Tokyo, right?
Things other than the quick.
Though your first feint quickly got denied.
Shut up!
Rather than running around
trying to match their #10,
let's focus on stopping the others.
Yeah.
It's true that Karasuno's #10 can't
be stopped by our blockers,
but the same goes for Hyakuzawa.
We'll try to score more.
Nice receive!
Here comes #10!
Cover!
Hyakuzawa!
All right!
Damn it.
Don't worry about it!
They got a point, so we'll get two.
Right.
That's exactly why we upped our arsenal.
Sensei.
If I were to go up against a player that big,
would I have to do attacks like
Sho-chan and the others to win?
No way.
If you can't win alone,
Nice receive!
you just have to add a few more.
Hey, four of them started moving at once!
It's a synchronized attack at first tempo.
All right!
Their #10 is plenty troublesome on his own...
Nice, Tanaka!
I'll get that back!
That's all I can do.
Kakugawa's #9
should be getting pretty tired,
but he keeps getting more intense.
Front! Front!
Nice receive!
It's true that I have basically
no experience, but...
Hyakuzawa!
I can score points!
Sorry, it went too high!
Technique doesn't matter.
Hyakuzawa, it's direct!
Steal it!
Smash it into the ground!
All right!
Karasuno          Kakugawa
Yeah!
Tanaka, nice kill!
Match point!
Right now in Karasuno's rotation,
the blockers are short,
so it's Kakugawa's opportunity to catch up.
Even average height looks
tiny next to two meters...
I feel like that's what people are saying.
What?!
They heard us?
No way!
Listen up.
If you can't stop it, then just receive it.
It's up!
Hyakuzawa! We're counting on you.
Not yet! Hold it for a bit.
If a wall doesn't work,
we'll use a plate.
A soft block!
Asahi-san, nice!
Nice, Tanaka!
If it's not a quick,
I win!
Spiking doesn't just involve
slamming the ball into the ground.
Karasuno                       Kakugawa
All right!
We did it!
We won even without a fujikujira!
All right!
Fujikujira?
A wipe?
Was that by chance,
or was it planned?
I got a point with something
other than a quick.
Good job, Hinata!
We made it through the prelims!
Inagaki-san.
Line up, Hinata!
What I said about volleyball being simple...
Oh, right.
I take that back.
Kakugawa's two meters...
is going to be really scary next year.
Kiyoko-san! We'll hold your things!
They already got most of it.
All right. Let's go.
Oh, I'm going to see if
anything got left behind.
You go ahead, Hitoka-chan.
Right!
Jeez. Even if your attacks are getting
better, your receives are still crap.
What the hell was that "ack"?
W-Well, it went up, didn't it?!
Ack!
By the way, you guys got your summer
break homework done, didn't you?
Ack!
You remember me saying that
I wouldn't help you, right?
Ack... Ack...
Ennoshita-san's so strong.
Is something wrong, Hinata?
Now we're finally on the same level
as the Great King and Ushiwaka Japan.
Huh?!
I forgot my lunch box!
Come on, just your number!
Sorry...
Whoa, she's getting hit on!
Sorry, I have people waiting for me.
Not to mention, they're scary looking!
It only takes a second
to give me your number.
And Tanaka-san and Noya-san already left!
I'm sorry.
Well, I'll just get it
from your phone real quick.
Whoa!
Sorry! That's my lunch box!
Let's go! Hurry!
Wait up!
We were still talking.
Hinata!
Do you have a smartphone?
Or an older one?
Excuse me!
What the hell's with that jump?
Karasuno
Karasuno...
Sh-Shimizu-senpai is our precious manager,
so um... um...
Huh...
So you guys beat the two-meter guy.
Huh? Well, yeah...
Aw... And I was looking forward
to playing against the two-meter guy.
Play?
Matches are super fun, aren't they?
Um... Did you get through the prelims?
Prelims? We didn't play in the prelims.
Huh? So you guys were in
the Inter-High quarterfinals?
Ah, I think it was the semifinals.
S-Semifinals?!
See ya.
If we manage to bump into
each other at the qualifier,
let's have some fun and play.
Have some fun and play...
Ah. A-Apparently he doesn't
need your number anymore.
Good.
Looks like you got his attention, Hinata.
Sorry about that, and thank you.
Here. You forgot this.
This lunch box wrap is cute.
This is Natsu's... My little sister's!
Not at all mine!
Isn't Kiyoko-san a bit late?
Shall we go check?
The hell are you looking...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You're late, dumbass!
Kiyoko-san, thank goodness you're safe!
Did you find anything left behind?
A cute lunch box wrap—
You don't have to tell them!
Someone tried to hit on Kiyoko-san?!
We've gotta keep our guard up!
We mustn't let her out
of her sight from now on!
We'll just have to take turns
going to the bathroom.
Yeah!
I'm pretty sure the harder you try,
the further away Shimizu-senpai's
heart is going to go...
Episode 14: "Still Growing"
Huh?
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Still Growing."