My younger sister, Umaru, is hot and popular.
Umaruun
She's kind, smart, and gifted
with many talents.
Beloved by all,
she's the perfect high school
student, without any flaws.
At least, that's what everyone seems to think...
This is Umaru when she's at home.
My lazy, careless little sister,
with no interest in socializing...
Himouto
My Himouto.
Episode 1   Umaru and Onii-chan
Look at her, sprawled out like that...
Hey, Umaru.
Stop messing with the computer
and eat your dinner.
I'm busy going through wiki sites
about me, so feed me, Onii-chan.
Get up!
Aw, man...
Whoops...
This fried rice is cold.
That's because you didn't eat it sooner!
But we always have bread on Tuesdays.
Today's Monday.
Oh, it's Monday...
No wonder school was so tiring today.
Monday?!
Whoa.
Why are you screaming all of a sudden?
Jumpu comes out today!
Jun Piece ended at a really
awesome spot last week!
J-Jun Pi...?
Please, Onii-chan. Go to the
convenience store and buy me a copy.
What? No.
Why not?!
I'm exhausted from work.
Why don't you go buy it on your
way to school tomorrow morning?
Then everyone will see me with it!
While at school...
"I'm not allowed to read manga at home,
so I'm not very familiar with Jun Piece.
Oh, but this reindeer character is so cute."
...is my backstory!
So annoying...
Why do you even have that backstory?
Well, things got to a point
where I couldn't back out.
Somehow the rumors took
on a life of their own...
Like saying I read books of
poems in our library at home...
We have a 1DK...
Anyway, no!
You'll just have to wait until tomorrow.
No! No, no, no!
I wanna read it today! I wanna read it now!
Buy it for me, Onii-chan!
Hurry up and buy it!
I wanna read it now!
Please, Onii-chan! It has to be today!
My younger sister,
who's about to turn sixteen,
is rolling around and throwing
a tantrum over a manga...
This is not good.
It's been a year since
Umaru came to my apartment.
She's grown more and more lazy and selfish.
This is my responsibility.
At this rate,
Umaru will be a failure of a human being
who won't make it in the real world.
Huh? He usually caves in by now.
Have the effects of my
tantrums started to wane?
Then...
Please, Onii-chan.
No!
I wanna read it, I wanna read it,
I wanna read it, I wanna read it!
Shut up!
Go buy it for me, Onii-chan!
I'll never ask for anything again!
For the love of Umaru, please!
Thanks, come again.
This isn't going to happen all the time, all right?
You need to learn some self-control.
Sorry, Onii-chan.
I'm at the good part right now,
so could you pipe down a bit?
Actually, as long as you were
at the convenience store,
you should have bought me some potato chips.
Look, you...
Cut it out already!
Give me back my Jumpu!
Yes, my little sister...
Huh? What's the matter, Umaru-chan?
Your eyes are all red.
Yeah, I got in a little spat with my brother...
But I'm fine, so don't worry.
I'm so curious!
What in the world happened?
What a terrible older brother!
...is a terrible Himouto!
Squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak?
Are you talking to the hamsters?
We've been having a great time talking...
About how your feet stink when
you walk across the floor.
Don't say that. It sounds too real.
Oh! And they want to eat steak tomorrow.
That's just what you want, isn't it?
Sometimes hamsters want fatty foods, too.
No, not really...
Well, the part about us
talking was my way of joking.
In reality, I was teaching them tricks.
Tricks?
Videos of pets doing tricks
are really popular on the Internet.
Ah, so cat videos are popular.
Animal
Video
Contest!
Enter Now!
The pet that ranks 1st
in number of views...
Wins
1 Million Yen!
Oh? Looks like there's a contest going
on for whoever can get the most views.
The one million yen is mine!
She's trying for that?
If I win the million yen,
all those things will be mine...
She's being ruled by her greed again...
Well, regardless of the one million,
my true goal lies in teaching them tricks.
Your goal is looping...
Umaru's Ambitions
No. 1
Hamjirou, bring me a cola.
Hamsaburou, bring my potato chips.
Good work.
Teaching them to bring me stuff.
Hamsters won't be able to do that.
Even better, if I can tame
about a hundred hamsters...
Umaru's Ambitions
No. 2
To the bathroom!
Maybe I could leave the
room while lying down!
Onii-chan! Let's go buy another 98 hamsters!
What the hell?
Why don't you buy them with your million?
Oh! Good point!
Well, regardless of her motives,
taking care of pets is a good thing.
Come to think of it,
it's been about six months since
I bought her the hamsters...
Umaruun
Onii-chan, buy me one!
No. You'll get bored with them fast.
Onii-chan... I'm lonely.
I can't bear waiting at home
alone for your return
any longer!
I-I have to work! I can't help that!
Hey, he just made that girl cry.
Such a pretty girl, too...
That guy's a real jerk!
Then I'll take these two.
You'd better feed them and clean their cage.
I know. Squeak, squeak.
Brings back memories.
To think Umaru actually has been
feeding them and cleaning the...
Cleaning...
Umaru! You haven't cleaned the cage once...
One million...
Wouldn't this get you more views?
All this racket... I should have woken her up!
Winning Video
It's Umaru-chan.
Check out that body.
Her face is so small and cute!
She's like a celebrity.
Is something the matter, Ebina-chan?
Huh?! No, it's just the looks from everyone...
I mean, um, I know everyone is just staring
because you're so pretty, Umaru-chan, but...
What? That's not true.
You're very cute yourself, Ebina-chan.
U-Umaru-chan...
I actually passed!
Augh! I got a C instead of a B!
Shupaan
As to be expected...
of me!
Time for the showdown,
Umaru-san! Your score is...
How disappointing!
Nothing less from my rival!
Next time, I, Tachibana Sylphynford,
shall be victorious!
You're amazing, Umaru-chan.
Huh?
My score's horrible...
Oh, no, I just got lucky.
It's so great how she doesn't brag.
Yeah, totally.
Motoba-san.
I-I'm fine...
You're amazing, Umaru-chan.
I can't believe you beat
Motoba-san from the swim team!
Oh, no, I was just having a good day today.
Huh? Where's Ebina?
It's beautiful...
What a splendid tone!
It's as though each of her
fingers has a will of its own!
You're so amazing, Umaru-chan...
Ebina-chan?
You're academically at the top of our grade,
you're great at sports,
and you can do anything.
I wish I were like you.
Oh, stop it...
See you later, Ebina-chan.
Okay, see you tomorrow, Umaru-chan.
I have returned!
Umaru in lane 4 is blazing down the track!
She's passing the other racers, one by one!
Oh, and there's her special
screw swimming style!
The computer's in front of her!
She's fast! She's just too fast!
She's already turned it on!
And now she's put on a hood.
Just what is she planning to do?!
There it is! Her supersonic blind touch!
It's as though each of her fingers
has a will of its own!
What's this?
Looks like she's spotted a
featured item on a net auction!
Umaru pecks away at the keys!
I wonder what she's thinking about
when she stares off like that.
I'm sure it's something so amazing,
we can't even imagine it.
Maybe I'll
have curry today...
Today's menu...
Cola, potato chips, chocolate bamboo shoots,
pudding, cheese codfish, and dried squid.
My feast is about to begin...
The junk food that I spent an hour carefully
choosing at the convenience store...
This time, my menu consists
of things to go with cola!
Now, then, what shall I
pair these snacks with first?
Depending on what I watch,
it could be poisonous or medicinal.
I must choose carefully.
Manga
Movie DVD
Anime DVD
Variety Shows
Nica Nica Douga
Tuesday Variety
Game Center DX
Movie DVD
Anime DVD
Today will be a combo of anime and a movie!
Preparations complete!
Make sure to dim the lights
when watching a movie,
and get as close as possible!
~Please Don't Do This At Home~
And... Play!
Though I chose these snacks
to go along with my cola,
I haven't laid a finger on my cola yet.
First, I open the potato chips and
the chocolate bamboo shoots...
So salty!
So sweet.
By eating these two things alternately,
I can enjoy both flavors without
getting tired of either.
It's a combination you can enjoy forever.
And now, I'm getting thirsty.
The cookie part of the bamboo shoots
has dried out my mouth.
This is where I chug the cola!
The carbonation tingles
against my dry throat!
And now, potato chips again!
And then, right away, cola!
Bamboo shoots, chips, chips,
bamboo shoots, and cola!
Chips, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, cola!
So good!
Nuhahaha
My potato chips are all gone.
The pairing of potato chips
and chocolate is amazing,
but cheese and squid together
is superb, as well.
The texture of the suckers is exquisite.
The sourness of the squid
and the mildness of the
cheese offset each other.
And they're great with cola, too!
Eating delicious things and
watching fun things...
I'm so happy.
At this moment, I am truly alive!
Umaru. Umaru!
Wake up. Dinner's ready.
Onii-chan?
I told you not to fall asleep with the TV on.
Come on, eat.
You kept whining about how much
you wanted to eat it yesterday,
so I made you a jumbo Hamburg steak.
I'm full...
What?! Why?!
The Jumburg steak was deliciously
consumed by my brother.
Hurry up and reload, Onii-chan!
H-How?!
Ah, behind you! Behind you!
Huh?
Aw, you lost.
Onii-chan, you won't survive
the ruthless war like that.
Leave me alone! The controls are hard!
What should we play next?
It's already two o'clock...
I've got to go grocery shopping.
What? Why? We just got started!
Well, I have to buy groceries for the week.
You just went last Sunday!
Those were groceries for last week!
Why is she mad?
Umaru, you didn't have to come with me.
You can stay home and play video games.
First, I've got to find dinner for tonight.
Umaru, what do you want to...
She's seriously someone else in public...
Look how gorgeous she is. Is she a celebrity?
I wonder if the guy with her is her boyfriend.
He's too bland. He's probably her manager.
Why?
Anyway...
She really is mad.
She keeps shooting angry looks at me.
Well, I'm sure she's just
being fickle, as usual.
Okay, for today...
First, some chicken...
Umaru.
We've still got snacks at home,
so I'm putting these back.
Hey, don't keep adding more.
Damn you, Umaru...
No, getting mad will just
have the opposite effect.
Umaru, want to go to the food court
and have some ice cream?
Uh-huh.
She's eating it while she's still angry...
Oh? has her mood improved?
Don't blame me for that!
H-Hey, Umaru...
It's your snacks and drinks that are
making these heavy. Give me a hand.
Onii-chan, this is heavy.
I'm tired.
You said you wanted curry, so the
least you can do is help with that.
Then, if you promise to game all day
with me next week, I'll forgive you.
Why am I the one being forgiven here?
It's decided!
Umaru.
Want to continue our gaming when we get home?
Yeah!
Onii-chan, you suck at this. It's no fun.
You're too good at it!
Just how much do you play?
For crying out loud. My little sister...
is truly an unbelievable Himouto.
Our anime's finally started, Onii-chan!
Yep.
You should take this opportunity
to stop lazing around.
What? I don't want to move around
just because this is an anime.
You just negated the whole point of anime...