I have gathered you all here
today for one reason.
I want all of us to overcome...
the grave situation afflicting
Sakura Hall together.
The subject of this Sakura
Hall meeting is:
the Shiina Mashiro-san sitting here.
This morning, by the time I'd
helped her put on her socks,
and fix her bed hair, we were late...
This is heaven.
I'm in hell!
Shiina, where are you?
On our way to school, we got lost,
Hurry up!
and finally arrived at school
halfway through second period.
Shiina's a little different,
so she isn't capable of
leading a normal life.
We should create a system where
we take turns in looking after—
I was just thinking...
"Notebook PC" and "no panties"
kinda sound similar, don't they?
What are you on about?!
Well, her parents did tell her...
that she needed someone
to look after her.
That's why we decided to have
her stay in Sakura Hall.
Look after her?
Then, Sensei, take responsibility for her...
and take care of her!
You're getting crumbs everywhere!
We're holding this meeting
for you, you know.
You got some up here!
He's perfect.
Yes, indeedy!
Okay, so Kanda will
be on Mashiro Duty.
What's that? Mashiro Duty?
It's decided! It's decided!
Akasaka Ryunosuke: I do not have time to waste on your mundane, pointless meeting.
Ryunosuke-sama has logged out.
The dragon agrees too!
It's unanimous. Then...
Meeting adjourned!
Good work, everybody.
I need to go over to
Noriko the nurse's place tonight.
Hey, wait.
What? I can't ignore that!
Absolutely not!
Sorata.
What is it?
I hope we can be friends.
Yeah, me too...
Kanda Sorata will be on Mashiro Duty! You can
do it, kouhai-kun! I'll be supporting you!
— Secretary Kamiigusa Misaki
Wait, this is crazy!
#02 I Drew a Picture
Cabbage, cabbage...
Kanda: Mashiro Duty
Gotcha!
When you sigh, your happiness escapes!
Let's put it back!
Say, "Ah."
Stop that!
I can't be on Mashiro Duty!
I'm planning to leave
Sakura Hall soon...
What? Really? Why?
You're asking me why? Because...
Sorata.
I-I can't believe you're
dressed like that again!
Put some pants on!
Are you trying to seduce me?!
Misaki told me you'd
like it more if I didn't.
That's right, Mashiron!
Listen, you!
Do you have any idea how hard...
I'm working to train Shiina?!
Chihiro-chan said we've got
to work hard while we can.
Imitating Mashiro
Oh, gimme a break! I don't
have time for breakfast now!
Quickly, back to your room!
Were you planning on going
to school without underwear?
Hey, what about this cabbage?
We'll pick up something
from the store for breakfast!
I see, I see.
I see!
Oh dear. Jin-kun, do you have a cold?
No... What was that?
I felt a sudden chill.
Leave it to me!
Pain, pain, go away.
Ow!
This is painful.
Salads are 380 yen each.
For the two of us, that's 760 yen...
This is tough on my wallet.
Sorata, are you ready yet?
Thank you very much.
What's wrong?
Um, Shiina-san? What are you doing?
I'm eating a baumkuchen.
Why?
I like them.
If that's all it took to get off
the hook, we wouldn't need police!
You have to pay for that!
What kind of life have
you been living up to now?
I drew pictures.
What else?
Can't you say anything else?!
See you later.
Aoyama?
Kanda-kun?
Do you want one?
You opened another one?!
Conveni-Mart
Thank you very much.
Sorry!
I'm really sorry!
Like I said, don't sweat it.
You paid for it, so it's all good.
Anyway...
We're talking about you.
Her name's Shiina Mashiro.
She's a second year art student
who transferred in this year...
She's living in Sakura Hall now.
You're living in Sakura Hall together?
You two must be really close.
No, this is...
Sorata is my first boy.
What?
What do you mean your "first boy"?! What?!
N-No! Hey, Shiina, you...
I'm glad Sorata was my first.
What?!
Un—
Unclean!
Wait, Aoyama!
In England, I was surrounded by girls.
You're the first boy I've
become friends with.
You should give the context first!
Context? To her, you mean?
Oh, forget it.
All right, time to eat.
I'm going to get that fried rice roll today!
Mayu, your lunch is so adorable.
Huh?
Nanami, have you seen Sorata?
No!
What? Did he do something again?
Do? D-D-Do?!
Huh? What?
What's this?
Why are you all by yourself at lunchtime?
Are you a pariah now?
I could only afford one bread roll.
I'm filling up on water.
How sad!
All my money went down the
drain buying Shiina snacks!
Sensei, aren't you
Shiina's legal guardian?
Reimburse me!
By the way, I hear you haven't...
turned in your career plan yet.
Trying to change the subject won't work!
Anyway, Shiina is—
Just put that you want
to be a pilot or something.
What am I, a grade schooler?
You should try to be
more like Kamiigusa.
Career Plan: Art
Third Year: Kamiigusa Misaki
"My future's so bright, I can't even see it!"
You're so narrow-minded...
I'm being ambitious!
She's an alien.
An earthling could never act like her.
Quit whining over nothing.
Just writing the words
"continuing my education"...
will put the faculty office at ease.
But...
It's only a career plan,
but watching you makes me think
it might actually mean something.
What? Are you saying it's
meaningless for most people?
They must do it to pick out the students...
who don't write that they're
"continuing education for the time being."
The only thing you need
"for the time being" is beer.
What?
See you later.
She managed to change the subject.
I got my fried rice roll!
Woohoo!
She just does whatever she wants.
My career plan...
Hey, Sorata.
Where have you been?
Look at this!
They're in here again.
Kamiigusa-senpai and
Mitaka-senpai's interview!
That pair of geniuses
are childhood friends!
Yeah...
"A prodigal high school
girl has appeared," it says.
She seems like a run-of-the-mill weirdo,
but she's actually really talented.
It's seriously amazing,
isn't it? Isn't it?
Yeah, it's amazing.
Kanda-kun!
Someone's here for you!
Huh?
Sorata?
Who's that?
She's really cute!
What's wrong?
I'm going home on my own today.
Huh? What?
I'm going home on my own.
But... if I'm not with you,
who knows what you'll get into?!
Be careful.
Listen. Don't eat any merchandise.
I understand.
Who's the cutie?
Don't go hogging all the
good luck, you jerk!
I'm not!
There's something wrong with her!
She's not normal!
You said it. She's abnormally cute!
Damn it, you always get the breaks!
Stop it!
Aoyama's definitely
got the wrong idea...
Shiina?
Ayano, where's your car?
I took it to get serviced.
Serviced?
I won't be seeing my
beloved baby for a while.
It's hard.
Really?
Shiina-san, what about you?
Is it hard being so far from
Rita-san in England?
I have Sorata.
Sorata?
A boy.
A boy, huh?
Ayano.
Conveni-Mart
Thank you very much.
Welcom—
Welcome.
Um, uh...
In England, I was surrounded by girls.
Sorata is the first boy
I've become friends with.
Huh? Wh-What are you talking about?
In England, I was
surrounded by girls...
That's not what I meant. What are you...
Sorata told me to tell you the context first.
You're kidding!
I was just imagining it all?!
Oh no!
What am I supposed to say
to Kanda-kun tomorrow?
Oh, um... sorry, I...
Um, you're called Shiina-san, right?
Do you want one of those?
I like them.
You're not going to have one?
Sorata said I can't unless I pay for it.
Two baumkuchen, please.
Ayano.
Ah, okay.
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
I'm home.
I wonder if Shiina made it home okay...
Hikari. Are you here to greet me?
Well, having someone like
you is never a bad thing.
This is...
The Cabbage Road of Honor...
It's my birthday today.
Jin-san.
I had a feeling this would happen.
I was right to come home early.
For my birthday last year...
Misaki decorated herself
with whipped cream,
Jin.
and waited for me in my room.
You have my sympathy.
But why cabbage?
How should I know what
goes on in Misaki's head?
But you're childhood friends.
What I mean is, the
thought process of a genius...
is a mystery to ordinary men.
What? If you're an ordinary man,
what does that make me?
Well, if you'll excuse me...
What kind of person are you...
to make me open this
dangerous box by myself?!
It probably won't explode,
so you'll be fine!
Probably, is it? Probably?!
Jin, happy birthday!
Jin!
Ow... Misaki-senpai...
Huh?
Jin!
Happy birthday!
Oh?
You're tempting me!
Cover up already!
Jin, you're so shy.
After all the effort I took to
celebrate your birthday.
Well, anyway...
I'll leave you guys to it now—
Hold it.
The staff will have to eat
this delicious cabbage.
You'll help me, won't you?
I'm not part of your staff!
Sorata!
Jin!
Happy birthday!
No more! Enough already!
I can't waste any more time.
I need to leave Sakura Hall before...
my common sense is eaten away...
What's important is the courage not to miss your chance.
– Fujisawa Kazuki
It's not that there isn't
anything I want to be, but...
Following his original theory...
that programmers must sleep
eight hours every day,
Ryunosuke is currently resting
in a dreamlike state.
From: Maid-chan, who
wishes she could sleep...
alongside Ryunosuke-sama.
Who can be in a dreamlike state
in the middle of this ruckus?
Oh, Shiina. You're home...
Come.
Shiina?
Take off your clothes.
I want to see you naked.
Why do you want to see that?
I want your body.
That's not an answer!
Take them off.
I refuse.
Why?
You're asking me why?
Because... it's embarrassing.
I'm not embarrassed.
It's embarrassing for me!
Ayano advised me to do this.
Ayano?
Last year, I entered the
New Manga Artist Award competition.
You won... an award?
I didn't win.
But Ayano saw my work,
and said that the art style was good.
Oh, right. An editor...
Ayano advised me to do this.
You're starting from there again?
She said, if delicate expressions of emotion...
are difficult for you...
then why don't you try
more extreme depictions?
I see.
So that's why you want
to see a naked man...
Shojo manga can be
pretty extreme sometimes.
If I take my clothes off,
will you take off yours?
Don't do that!
Okay, I'll take off my clothes!
You just want me to
take them off, right?
I won't take off my underwear, though!
That's my only condition!
I will take off your underwear.
You're crazy!
Hey!
Don't move.
It feels hard and heavy.
Your heart is beating.
That's because I'm alive.
Your pulse is quickening.
Whose fault is that?!
Sorata.
What?!
Hold me.
Like hell I will!
More.
Sorata.
What now?
Have you had sex?
Sorata?
Don't surprise me like that!
No, I haven't!
But you have a nice body.
What kind of reasoning is that?!
My body's only like
this because I played soccer...
in grade school and middle school.
What about now?
I don't play anymore!
Can't you tell just by watching me?!
Did you get injured?
There are plenty of reasons
to quit other than an injury.
I don't understand.
I wasn't good enough.
I wasn't particularly good at it.
I kept at it for nine years,
but I guess you could
say I saw my limitations...
I guess that's why I lost my passion for it.
There came a point where I stopped
caring whether we lost or not...
and I subconsciously learned
not to try so hard.
It happens all the time, right?
That's enough.
Hey, Shiina?
Huh? Am I supposed to just
sit here like this?
I see.
It's not interesting?
Oh, it's not that...
Ayano told me it wasn't.
You can get rid of it.
What? But...
It's okay. I'll redraw it.
New Manga Artist Award Entry Requirements
Redraw it?
Are you going to apply for
the new artist award again?
You must really like drawing manga.
Don't put your clothes on.
What?
We're going to keep going.
Hey, wait.
What more do you have planned for me?
I won't let you sleep tonight.
Try to sound a little
sexier when you say that!
I won't let you sleep tonight.
That sounded exactly the same!
Sakura Hall
Good morning.
You sure had fun last night.
I didn't have fun at all!
Senpai, did you manage to get
Jin-san to eat that cabbage?
That's what you choose
to ask about, kouhai-kun?
Uh... I'll go take out the garbage.
I don't really understand
their relationship...
Hey, you're early.
Are you on your way to work?
Y-Yeah. Good work today, Kanda-kun!
What? You're not angry anymore?
I-I wasn't angry in the first place.
Huh? But... Aoyama, you speak...
in Kansai dialect when you're angry, so...
I-I-I just told you I ain't angry!
That girl I met yesterday is
pretty weird, isn't she?
She's an art student, isn't she?
You mean Shiina?
Yeah, she wants to be a manga artist.
She's good at drawing,
but her work's a little strange.
She works hard, though.
I guess you could say...
she makes me want to cheer her on...
Same goes for you, too.
Working so early in the morning so
you can become a voice actor...
is pretty amazing.
I respect that.
W-Well, anyway, I've got to go!
See you at school.
Yeah!
They really are amazing.
Both Aoyama and Shiina.
They've both found something
they can be absorbed in.
I might not be as good as Misaki-senpai...
and the others, but...
Still, I wonder if I'll be able
to find something someday.
She left her stuff out.
That's a beautiful drawing.
Thank you.
Why are you thanking me?
Because I drew that.
What?
What? You mean you didn't know?
Jin-san?
Look at the cover.
Chihiro-chan must not have told you.
I'm sure you must've at least seen
her face on TV or in magazines.
Shiina Mashiro
After all, Shiina Mashiro is...
"Special Exhibition: Contemporary Artist, Shiina Mashiro"
"The prodigal girl who has descended
upon the world of contemporary art..."
"Something she can be absorbed in?"
What was I thinking?
She isn't on Misaki-senpai
or Jin-san's level.
Shiina is...
Suffer more, little one.
Mashiro-chan, come eat some—
Is it good?
Cabbage!
I'm going to give away the ribbon....
#03 So Close And Yet So Far...
(There is no actual prize for our viewers.)
I used to wrap myself up
as a prize to our viewers!
Write to us at...