Once the festival's over, Shiina will...
Message Received
Shiina Mashiro
Are you awake?
What?
I want to see you.
You...
I want you to stay with
me until I fall asleep.
Keep it down.
We'll get in trouble if
Aoyama or Rita find out.
Okay.
Good night, then.
I'll sleep on the floor, too.
Why? There's no point if you—
Sorata...
What?
Did I hurt you, too?
But why did you have
to make your debut?
For a long time, I compared
myself to Shiina,
and got depressed over it...
But if it wasn't for that,
I would never have
confronted my own feelings.
That's right.
If Shiina returns to England, I...
We have to make Nyapollon
one of our best memories...
Mashiro, I...
It ends like this again, huh?
One of our best memories, you say?
#12 The Power of Love in the Culture Festival
What?! We attracted
this many people?!
It's only natural considering
the talent of the development team.
Is it your place to say that?
It looks like you've got quite a crowd.
Oh, Student Council President...
It would be unfortunate if you
failed to live up to their expectations.
After all, this is an exception...
Those of you who couldn't get
into the theater room,
please follow the
directions of this guy...
with the Student Council armband!
What?! Mitaka!
Why me?!
Stop pushing! Form a line!
Jin-san, you're evil.
Isn't ensuring that the
festival runs smoothly...
the responsibility of the Student Council?
I have a feeling I understand why...
the Student Council President
looks at you the way he does.
I'm not exactly thrilled to
have guys fall for me.
He hates you with
every fiber of his being!
Okay, okay, member of staff
coming through.
What's this?
Maybe it's used for
synchronization controls.
It's good to see you again.
Wh-What are you doing here?
Why am I here? I just came to see...
the fruits of my Sakura Hall kouhai's labors.
Nekosuke-san!
Oh, crap. My heart's going
to jump out of my mouth.
If that happens, I'll just cram
it back down your throat.
Kanda-kun.
Yeah.
This is what a cat girl
should look like.
It looks good on you.
You finally complimented me...
Huh?
I've finished making adjustments
to the equipment.
The audience have taken their seats.
Then, gather 'round, everyone!
Gather 'round, friends!
We're already all here.
Okay, kouhai-kun has some
wonderful words for us!
What? I do?!
You're the director. Of course you do.
I adjusted the balance
to your preferences.
If they say it sucks,
it'll be all your fault.
Did you have to say that now?
Ignore him. Come on, Kanda-kun.
Let's enjoy ourselves for
the next thirty minutes!
What?
Enjoy ourselves? What are you...
I'll have fun.
Right.
All right!
Let's have some fun!
Yeah!
Milky Way Cat, Nyapollon!
Milky Way Cat, Nyapollon
This is the story of
the love and courage...
of the people who
confronted the invaders...
from the planet Nyangoro to
protect mankind and Earth!
Amazing...
Sakura Hall's crazy...
Nekoko here!
We've just arrived
at the rendezvous point!
You're Nyapollon's pilots, right?
You'll be piloting the armed
cat robot Nyapollon with me.
Come!
Pick up the glow sticks
that were on your seats!
When piloting Nyapollon,
an icon will appear on screen.
Move according to the instructions.
Raise your right hand.
Raise your right hand!
Ready and...
That's it!
Now, let's move out to the
galactic battlefield!
That's it, Aoyama. Stay calm.
The alien monsters who landed
on Earth are 5,000 meters long!
Aoyama plays the part of heroine, Nekoko,
They destroyed the entire UN
peacekeeping force with one blow!
onstage and keeps the crowd excited.
Don't be ridiculous!
Aoyama is a storyteller, a performer,
and the game's guide.
Quit meowing!
The first synchronized
command is coming up.
Nyangoro aliens...
I'll send every last
one of you to Hell!
Raise both hands.
Let's go, everyone!
Ready and...
All right! It's a success!
The alien behind this
invasion of Earth is...
Nyangoro's commander,
Ein the Hunchback.
In the past, Ein killed
Nekoko's lover, Nekosuke.
Nekosuke-san!
Nekosuke-san...
A world without you
holds no meaning...
Do I have to keep defending it?
Interspersed with dramatic scenes,
we appeal to the audience's emotions...
and using battles
against minor enemies,
we increase their anticipation
for the final battle.
Clap your hands. Clap your
hands. Clap your hands.
Come on, everyone! Stand up!
Here we go.
Lower your hands.
Ready and...
It's finally time for...
Nyapollon's final battle against...
the enemy commander,
Ein the Hunchback.
Ein's surprise attack!
The audience receives
Ein's surprise attack,
and takes significant damage.
This isn't a result of
the audience's mistake,
but rather, is part of the story.
That coward!
Burn hotter and hotter
and hotter and hotter!
Nyapollon's energy gauge is almost empty.
At this rate, we're going to lose...
What should I do, Nekosuke-san?
Hey, what's going to happen?
He got us...
That's it!
Please, everyone!
Share your love with Nyapollon!
Shout your love!
Shout your love!!
What?
The most powerful feeling you've
got inside you right now.
It can be anything.
I need you to shout it out!
Your passion will fuel
Nyapollon's power!
Nanami's performance is so passionate!
Please, let this work...
Come on! All together!
C-Come on! Shout!
Your love! Shout all of your love!
Shout out our love? But...
Yeah...
What should we do?
There's no way I'm doing that.
Why?
This isn't good. The audience is confused.
Shout your love!!
Please! Shout out your love!
Love, huh?
Why don't you do it?
Maybe they shouldn't have done this...
What?
Shout your love!!
No matter how good the production,
this development is too high a
hurdle to force on an audience.
It requires the impulse of a creator...
But when that becomes...
forcing your own emotions on someone,
you elicit a negative response...
and it leaves the audience behind.
It's my fault...
Sorata.
The best memories...
The best memories Shiina wanted...
I wanted to make memories with everyone...
Shiina?
Thank you for everything!
Shout your love!!
Mashiro?
What was that?
Thank you?
Was that Mashiro-chan?
I'm going to do it, too!
Jin! Look at me instead of Fuuka-chan!
I'll do it, too!
Ryunosuke! Give me your email address!
What?!
Don't shout something so stupid!
That kinda looks fun.
It's a festival. Let's shout, too!
Nyapollon, fight!
Yosuke-kun, I love you!
Masui, don't be so stupid!
Suganuma, give me back my money!
I like you!
That hurt.
Shout your love!!
A little more, a little more!
Your love is gathering
inside Nyapollon!
Mashiro.
The truth is,
there's a lot more I
want to say to you.
But...
Mashiro, I should be
the one thanking you!
Shout your love!!
Love energy: Max!
Let's go, everyone!
Shout! Meatball Beam!
Ready and...
Meatball Beam!
And so, Earth was saved from
the evil Nyangoro aliens.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, Nyapollon.
May this beautiful planet
of love endure forever...
Fin
The staff's supposed to go greet
the audience onstage now!
I'll never forget.
I'll never forget this day.
I wouldn't expect any
less from your students.
Thanks.
Would it be all right if I stopped
by Sakura Hall sometime?
Of course it wouldn't.
Director: Kanda Sorata
Produced by the Friends of Sakura Hall
I made something with my friends...
and saw it through to the end.
I'll never forget this day.
That was super exciting!
I'm still throbbing
to the very core!
I can't quell this libido!
In that case, put that libido
to use by cleaning up.
Okay...
By the way, that thing you
said during Nyapollon...
Fuuka's my ex-girlfriend.
Currently, she's just a childhood friend...
who I've had almost no contact with,
and she's your older sister.
That's all.
Huh?
This necklace...
You weren't buying it for Mashiro...
What?
Nothing! Where did you get this?
A store some other class was
running forced me to buy it.
Jin, put it on me!
Do it yourself.
What?
Hey, Misaki!
That's...
There you are, Kanda-kun!
What's up, Aoyama?
I can't find Mashiro anywhere...
Rita-san, either...
Mashiro has people waiting for her.
Mashiro will return to
the place she belongs.
She's already heading back to England?
England?
Isn't that just something
Rita said without...
You're kidding! Why?
Kanda-kun, why didn't you stop her?!
Because if that's Shiina's decision,
I'm not in any position
to speak my mind.
Besides,
I already got to say what I wanted to...
You wanted to thank her?
You heard me?
That's all you wanted to say?!
That can't be all!
Kanda-kun, what do you
want to do right now?!
Of course I want to stop her!
Kanda-kun...
She said she was going to
become a manga artist...
She worked so hard and even
got her work serialized...
What is she doing?!
Don't be ridiculous...
We spent six months together.
How can she throw it away so easily?
Her manga and us...
Kanda-kun, isn't that what you...
really wanted to tell
her during Nyapollon?
Then, you have to tell her.
Let's find Mashiro!
I'll go check inside the school!
It's no use. She's not answering.
Nanami.
Miyahara-kun!
Have you seen—
Nyapollon was really great!
I was really moved
by your performance!
Th-Thanks... So, um...
Sorry, I'm...
Did you hear what I shouted during...
the Meatball Beam part?
What? What did you say?
That I...
love you.
Oh, um...
I-I'm sorry, I...
I've never thought of you that way...
So, um... I'm...
I'm really sorry!
I can't... I...
Mashiro, I...
Kouhai-kun! Mashiron and Rittan left!
What? They're already
going to the airport?!
Aoyama-san told us what's
happening! Get in!
International Airport
Okay then, Mashiro...
Yeah.
Mashiro, don't go.
Sorata.
Don't go...
Don't go, don't go!
Not anywhere! Don't go anywhere!
Sorata, you're repeating yourself.
Stay at Sakura Hall!
I'm not going anywhere.
Yeah!
I came to see Rita off.
What?! Wait, what?!
It's true what they say:
The plainer the man,
the more flamboyant
his actions, huh, Sorata?
R-Rita! You tricked me!
That's not a nice thing to say.
You said Mashiro would return
to where she belongs.
Don't you think Mashiro
belongs in Sakura Hall?
What?
Rita-san, are you saying...
I'm glad I came to Japan.
I'm going back to England.
Please take care of Mashiro for me.
Rittan, why didn't you tell us?
We didn't even throw a
farewell hotpot party!
Take this with you, former freeloader.
It's Kanda's email.
Why mine?!
You play hard to get, don't you?
What do you even think love is?
Love is a bug in the brain's
electrical functions.
You should throw your unnecessary
emotions in that garbage can.
Looks like you need to be punished!
It's futile. That attack
won't work against...
Goodbye, everyone.
Take care!
Exploding with Youth!
Rittan!
Rita-san, we'll see
you again, won't we?
So, she can smile like that, after all.
What's wrong?
It feels weird, right here.
It's been throbbing for a while.
A while?
Since you told me not to go...
O-Oh, that's...
And you held me...
Forget about that!
That's impossible.
I can still hear your voice in my ear.
I can still feel your body.
Don't be so graphic!
What happened to me?
Is this...
love?
Hikari is happy Nyapollon's
show went well.
#13 One Step Before Winter
By the way, Hikari... What is love?