So, Taihei... can I come by your place for dinner tonight?
Sure. Not a problem.
Say, why don't you come as well, Alex? Sometimes, it's-
No, thank you!
I'm home!
Hey there, Tanukichi.
Ah! Hi, Bomba!
Wait, who's THAT?
This is Alex. He works for me.
Pardon the intrusion.
Ugh, I am STARVING!
Sorry for dragging you along...
It's fine!
You're pretty clueless, man.
This was your BOSS asking you out.
I feel kind of like...
like I've seen him somewhere before.
Whoa!
Hotpot, huh?
Everything's pretty much in season,
so it should taste good.
Well, autumn is the time for eating!
"Autumn"!
Tonight's a parade of autumn specials!
Autumn variety shows! Autumn anime!
The Anime Song Festival!
Autumn variety shows...
Autumn anime shows!
Sing it! It's the anime song festival!
YAY!
Yay, yay, yay, yay-yay-yay, yay!
He doesn't even live here,
but he's really getting worked up! Hold on...
I know this feeling, of someone being all excited
but not caring about ME. But from where?
Japanese animation is cute and cool!
My older brother loves it, too.
Could this be Sylphyn's brother?!
Indeed!
In-
Gah! Now that I look closely, he TOTALLY
seems like he could be her brother!
But, wait, that's too much of a coincidence!
I don't watch anime at all. Isn't that just for kids?
What are you talking about?
Anime is a part of Japanese culture!
This HAS to be Sylphyn's brother!
Indeed!
I think... therefore I am!
You know what I think? This was a quality show,
and I'm sad to see it end!
Huh?! I've been a fan of the show too!
Oh, really?
I've got the merch and the Blu-rays and everything!
M-me too!
Whoaaa!
Only, yappari Japan ga suki desu wa
Only, sure enough, I love Japan
Yay!
Ichiban ga ichiban oniai no
Only the best for the best!
Pow, pow!
Kisoiai futari, yuujou wa
Our friendship, the two of us competing
Yay!
Utsukushii mono desu wa
Is a beautiful thing
Yurinchi!
Looks like they've suddenly become friends...
Yay!
I guess that's...
Pow, pow!
...the power of anime.
If you'll excuse me, I should get going.
Umaru, you certainly know a lot about anime.
You're no slacker yourself, Alex.
They're already this buddy-buddy?!
Is it all right if I come by with some
of my favorite Blu-Rays sometime?
Well, of course!
Have a good evening.
Thanks for that, Umaru.
It looked like Alex had a good time too.
Huh? You think?
Even at the office, Alex just seems sort of OFF, right?
Well, they did bring him on as a special hire...
Huh? Wait, why WAS he a special hire?
Beats me.
Hello? This is Alex.
I have made contact... with Umaru Doma.
Wait, what? Isn't your reaction sort of LACKING?
Acting like spies should be more fun, right?!
H-hey!
C'mon, Umaru. If you're going to use my ear pick,
you could at least give it back.
Yeah... I know...
I told her to give it back...
I guess I'll just... buy one on the way home.
It's gone!
Gone, gone, still gone!
My ear's all itchy, but the ear pick is gone!
And it should be right here!
Something's making me feel all creepy-crawly!
She suffers! Yes, she suffers!
Looks like we won't be seeing
that stick today, huh, Boss?
The time has come for her to know how much
we despise that stick's daily intrusion!
Go and give her the greatest itch you can. Do it!
Yeah!
Woo-hoo! Woo-hoo!
Yay!
Go, go! Go, go!
Yeah, yeah!
Woo-hoo!
HELP ME, BIG BROTHER!
Whoa, you're out early.
I have some shopping to do.
I stepped on my ear pick and broke it.
Your ear pick?
Umaru used it and left it lying out...
Tanukichi must have it rough right now, huh?
What? She just used it yesterday.
But it's right after you use it that the itching is worst.
Right, Alex?
Now that you mention it...
My ears itch! Help me, Big Brother!
My ears aren't right! They just aren't right!
But my finger can't go all the way in!
I'm home.
B-Big Brother!
See? I told you Tanukichi would be suffering...
It's your own fault for not putting things away, Umaru.
Whatever, just hand it over, Bomba!
Here.
Whoa!
We bought one of each that they had at the store.
Bomba said he wanted to try out some different kinds...
Who knew there were so many different ear picks?
Check this out. This thing looks AWESOME.
Whoa!
The Screwdriver!
It's effective not just in one direction,
but in ALL directions!
I don't like this!
Three tiers of wires!
Each twist has three times the results,
which means less work!
Help me, Boss!
A FLASHLIGHT!
This will let you see the deepest parts of your ear,
for maximum focus yet little strain on your aural orifice!
And there are other options as well!
Yeah!
We did good, huh? She looks happy.
You're going to pay me back for all this stuff, right?
Which one's easiest to use?
I haven't tried them all yet, so I'm not sure.
This sure takes me back...
The only time someone cleans your ears
for you is when you're a kid, right?
And your mom does it...
Yeah.
I guess you're right.
Say, Taihei, do me next.
Do it yourself.
Hey, have you heard?
Heard what?
They say Umaru's brother
is some totally handsome actor.
Huh?!
And supposedly, her dad is German!
That's awesome!
She really is cool, huh?
My dad's German... and Taihei is a handsome actor?
I know, right?
So cool!
Yeah!
Totally!
I don't know where these rumors are coming from,
but they keep spreading and changing...
UMR!
Shwpa-pa-pa-pa-pa...!
Shbwaaa!
I've kept you waiting indeed!
I wish to ask your advice on something...
You know, I didn't think Sylphyn would be the type
to sit down and talk like this, but...
sure enough, you can't trust every rumor you hear.
So, what do you think?
Huh? Sorry, I didn't catch what you said.
UMR, I would like to invite you over
to my house today. Indeed!
This is the place!
It's so Japanese...
And we have hopscotch stepping stones!
One, two, three! One, two, three! One, two, three!
One, two...
One, two, three!
I am sliding indeed!
This place is so big...
It seems like it has some history to it.
This is...
Anime is a part of Japanese culture!
OH, yeah... Sylphyn and Alex
are brother and sister, right?
It's a weekday, so I guess he's not here.
It's right down this stairway, UMR!
Wh-what's going on?
Is she going to try something
down there in the basement?
Wow! Look at all these books!
Indeed, we should study for our tests!
What?!
It's almost time for midterm exams.
I assume you have them at your school as well.
We do, but... wait, we're at the SAME school.
This time, I WILL get a better score than Umaru!
You really think you can beat me?
The "Umaru" you're talking about
is right here in front of you...
Like, I read poetry in our house's library.
But this is a one-room apartment
What's your score?
This is what it will take to beat me!
I always study in our private library.
Nice to meet you. I am Sylphynford Tachibana.
My father is German and my mother is Japanese!
They say Umaru's house has its own library.
Wow... I wonder if she studies poetry.
Wait, are you serious?!
What's the matter, UMR?
No, it's just... you can't trust rumors, can you?
Rumors? I would like to hear more of this indeed!
So, what sort of rumors are these, UMR?
UMARU!
Gah! What, what happened?!
Big Brother, I swear.
It's not even time for spring cleaning yet!
Listen closely, Umaru.
Gah!
This isn't just about cleaning:
It's about your attitude,
and how you don't care how dirty things get.
This is a detox, for the soul!
Wh-what I mean is...
I clean every week, but when
the weekend comes, it's dirty again.
It's because you're being lazy! You think it's okay
to leave things messy and I'll clean it up later.
But if I didn't make a mess, you'd have nothing
to do on the weekends, right?
Why do I look all shriveled up?!
Anyway, we're doing this.
Fine...
Cleaning Technique No. 1: Decide What Goes Where!
This place gets messy because
things are just left scattered all over the floor.
That's why we have to decide
where each and every item goes.
I'd like you to use the bookshelves.
Roger that!
I wonder where Big Brother learned his technique...
From THIS, huh?
We've pretty much figured out where things go, huh?
But there's a whole bunch still left over.
Cleaning Technique No. 2:
Store Whatever Remains Left from Step 1!
If you can't come up with a place for something,
it means you don't use it much and you should store it.
Let's box up volumes
of the same size and genre together.
But Big Brother, what "genre" is it
if you've got a DVD inside of a game case?
Why do you have things all mixed up like that?
It's a pain to keep pulling discs out and
putting them back in, so I just put them wherever...
Put them back in their proper cases!
Okay, that's everything nice and stored.
But if there's no more room to put stuff?
Presenting Cleaning Technique No. 3:
You toss it!
HUH?! No way! That would be a waste!
I mean, look how cute this doll thing is!
You call that "cute"?
Listen closely, Umaru:
All things are destined to meet their end!
Out with the old and in with the new!
This is the natural order of things!
Hup, hup!
THIS!
That includes this, right?
The sticky note on this page here
says the same thing that you're saying.
M-maybe I could keep that
stuffed doll of yours on my desk...
You don't mind?!
Looks pretty clean, doesn't it?
Yeah!
Flying leap!
All that's left is to see
if you can keep things nice and neat.
I'm bored of this game... oh, I know!
I'll play one of those retro games
that turned up yesterday.
It's fun to play these once in a while.
Why do you have things all mixed up like that?
Which case did this belong to...?
Umaru... You can leave things a LITTLE messy...
He's all shriveled up.
Are you going somewhere on Sunday?
We're going to the movies!
This is a big crowd indeed!
It's been a while since I've seen a movie at the theater.
What do you think? Should we watch it first, or...?
Well, it is almost lunch time.
Yeah, that's true.
Sylphyn has already bought popcorn
and is standing in line!
Shbwaa!
S-Sylphyn! You're already in line?
And I've bought popcorn for everyone!
We were talking about getting something to eat first...
Shwaaaat?
Y-you were?
Sylphyn, I swear...
U-um, maybe we COULD see the movie first.
Huh?
There sure are a lot of movies out, huh?
Which one should we see?
That hasn't come out yet.
It's so sweet and delicious!
I can't stop eating it!
They all look good... it's hard to choose one, isn't it?
"Master Detective Nacon" seems pretty popular.
Whoa! 4.5 stars!
I used to watch Nacon when I was in elementary school.
I would like to see Precuare!
Wow! You already bought the promotional booklet!
That caters to an even younger audience...
Okay everyone, let's all raise our voices!
Precuare!
I think I'd be a little embarrassed...
What? But I spent last night watching
the old shows and practicing for this.
So long as I can be with the Master...
I'm totally fine with this.
Let's just go with what everyone wants to watch.
I will see Precuare with UMR later!
Huh?
Is that a foreigner?
Is it a DJ?
This is comfy indeed!
Huh? What happened to the popcorn?
We were lucky to find such good seats.
I never thought the four of us would be
hanging out and watching a movie...
Still, I'm glad we were all able to become friends.
A-are you okay, Kirie?
I-I'm fine! I'm just a little scared of the dark.
But I'll be all right. Please, enjoy the movie!
Sorry, but I will...
An incident this week! An incident next week!
He goes to the movies and a bomb goes off!
Today, too, his deductive powers will leap into action!
He is Master Detective Nacon!
And catastrophe awaits him at the restaurant!
Wow... so this is the restaurant run
by that friend of Zonoko's uncle, huh?
I hear a scream!
Well, well. This is an interesting start.
However! I'll be looking at all the clues
that they drop and I will figure out the culprit!
I wonder what the others think...
Hey, Sylphyn's asleep!
But I spent last night watching
the old shows and practicing for this.
Don't tell me she stayed up till morning
watching all those seasons of Precuare!
I have solved the crime.
Wait, already?!
The culprit added poison to...
the "Mediterranean Breeze Course Menu"!
Wh...
What was that?!
Wh-what should I do? My stomach is about to growl!
I can't let that happen here - it's too embarrassing!
I'm gonna blow this restaurant up!
No, stop!
Light!
I-I fell asleep...
Thank goodness. It looks like everyone
was focused on the movie.
So bright...
Nacon did a better job than me
at figuring out the culprit, but...
That was a lot of fun!
My ears are itching again!
We earwax shall destroy you!
Your ears will itch and itch again!
You know, not even I have seen an anime
that has earwax in the next episode preview!
Those of you watching, you will be reduced
to a piteous state and made to itch as well!