Reverse, all stop!
Well?
For now, it doesn't look
like there's any danger.
But are we really gonna be okay after this?
Yeah, sure. That tin can
wipe out the whalesquid.
D-Don't tell me...
Tin can! Ledo!
So how'd it go?
Confirmed: All Hideauze inhabiting this
area of the ocean have been exterminated.
Alright! Great job!
Hey! Get out the Yunboros!
The legendary treasure is ours!
Yeah!
Island of Ambition
Alright! Stop!
The shaft is over there!
Go ahead! Take it slow!
Alright, alright!
Alright! We're okay over there!
Pinion! Come here a second!
Sure!
This looks promising, huh?
Yeah.
Bro...
I wanted to drink this together.
Pinion...
What do you think? And this
is just the beginning.
So this is the grand legacy of our ancestors!
Yep. There's even more incredible treasure
waitin' deep inside the whalesquid nest.
It's just like my big brother said.
It's not rotted out at all. And there's an
unlimited supply at the bottom of the sea.
This is it, the treasure that will bring
the former civilization back to the world!
Restoring the world?
We're the ones that found
it! So it's our treasure!
W-What are you saying?!
I thought we could use this legacy to enrich
the lives of as many people as possible!
What's the point of the whole damn thing
unless we enrich our own lives first?!
If we keep it to ourselves, people
will show up to try and steal it.
We've got tons of weapons and ammo!
There ain't nothin' to be afraid of!
That's not the issue.
We'll sink anybody that gets close to us!
Hey! Send out a radio message!
Spread the word that the whalesquid have
been annihilated and that we got the treasure!
We can't! It would only stir
up other ships in the area!
It'll be a warning for them to stay away!
We're gonna send it out as far and
wide as possible! Get it ready!
This is a message to all
ships that can hear this!
We wiped out all the whalesquid that
were livin' in the Sea of Mist!
All the pods, all the nests, everything!
This is Pinion! Remember me
as Pinion of the Sea of Mist!
Any bastards out there after the whalesquid
nest treasure, you're too damn late!
Don't get any funny ideas!
The treasure is all ours!
This is a warning to all ships! Any boats
that get close will be sunk without mercy!
Pinion has a valid point.
Even you?! What's going on here?
That being said, I'm sure pirates will
target us. We'll need to prepare for that.
Why do we have to assume
that we're going to battle?
Mr. Flange!
You have a package.
Come.
Thank you.
Is there anything else?
I heard that Ledo killed
all the whalesquid...
Yes. It's true.
Are we going to be okay?
I don't know.
Do you agree with all this, Mr. Flange?
Hey!
Of course not!
With Ledo and Chamber around, we can
search deep into the whalesquid nest.
I'm fine with that.
But not even trading what we
bring up with other ships,
and spouting threats to
attack if they draw near...
You can't stop him?! At this rate,
we'll be treated as outcasts!
The shipmasters that I led
have begun to follow Pinion.
Certainly, making use of the salvage
requires his skills as a repairman.
So there's little that
can be done to stop him.
No...
Ensign.
Why aren't you givin' us a hand?!
You can take care of the salvage yourselves!
The shaft is blocked up with salvage.
I want the tin can to move the stuff!
Forget it!
What's wrong with you, Ledo?!
What're you afraid of?
Afraid? Me?
Go to hell!
I annihilated the Hideauze! I fear nothing!
I fear...
Joe, let's hang it up for the day!
Alright!
Fleet Commander, has the reorganization
layout been finalized?
Yes. The shipmasters were very cooperative.
Now all we need to do is
reset the interlocks.
Though it's a major undertaking...
Fleet Commander, have you
heard Pinion's broadcast?
Yes, of course.
What do you think, frankly speaking?
Until we have any factual evidence for
his claims, there's no need to respond.
However...
Has word already spread across the fleet?
There's likely not a single
soul who doesn't know about it.
I see...
Of the shipmasters who believe it, there may
be some who are envious and wish to leave.
And if there are?
I'll respect their wishes.
Dr. Oldham, is it true that Ledo
destroyed a nest of whalesquid?
Yes. That's what Pinion
said on a radio broadcast.
That's terrible...
It's stupid.
What a stupid thing to do...
I swore I'd get revenge for my big brother...
You said it was just a dream, remember?
Amy...
I hope Melty's okay.
It's alright, right? After all,
it's only Pinion talking...
Come on, Amy...
How would I know about that?!
I don't know...
Ledo... Why...?
Do they look like they're gonna surrender?
No. But they're probably out of ammo.
Keep attacking.
Seriously?!
We've got plenty of ammunition left.
Besides, they started it.
You're telling us to sink them?!
Unless they put both hands up first...
Oh, that's right! Repairs on the
treasure should be done by now.
Let's try it on 'em!
Alright, alright!
Okay. Good enough.
Everything's set!
Alright! Fire!
"Fire", he says...
This one? Or this one?
What are you doin'?! You got lousy aim!
They're radioing that they surrender!
Shoulda done that before, dumbasses.
Yeesh. You wasted time and ammo.
You got some guts pickin' a fight with us.
Hey, help us!
We'll give you all our cargo,
just let us join up with you!
If we accepted every plea like that,
this place would get huge...
Wait a second. If the fleet expands
like this, we'll be invincible.
And there's no end to the stuff
we can raise from the sea bottom.
Alright! Anybody that wants to can
bring your things and come over!
G-Got it!
Old man, we've come to an agreement.
Hey, lock this guy up somewhere!
Ledo...
I want the tin can to check
out the stuff we salvaged.
What do you say?
The ensign's permission is required
for anything outside of military duty.
Yeah, fine. It's okay, right?
Do what you want.
Then we're good to go! Follow me!
I can't do it without you!
You too, tin can top dog! Let's go!
Come on, drink!
Good work, everybody!
When a ship picked a fight with us, we
made it fly the white flag in no time!
The wind of fortune's been blowin' on us
ever since we made this our base of operations!
But it's all thanks to Ledo and Chamber!
Everyone, kiss this tin
can's ass in gratitude!
What am I doing?
What am I doing it for?
Who am I doing it for?
When did it start?
When I first became conscious
in this strange land?
Or the first time I got inside
Chamber... this Machine Caliber?
Or since I was born?
Well?
It is a rudimentary electromagnetic weapon.
Electromagnetic? What the hell is that?
Its basic structure is no different than
the beam armament that I am equipped with.
Seriously?!
However, I estimate its power
output to be 1/50th of mine.
Even 1/50th of your power is a big deal!
Its power output is approximately 76 times
greater than that of this whole fleet.
Alright, alright! Is this thing still usable?
It is possible to restore its
functions through repairs.
However, a great amount of electricity
is required to operate it.
Electricity, huh?
Would it work if we harnessed the lightbugs?
That hypothesis requires investigation.
Then do it! I'll go tell Ledo!
I have discovered evidence to back
up the Hideauze video recording.
It is the lightbugs.
Lightbugs are nanomachines and actually
comprise the Hideauze shell.
They absorb electromagnetic waves and
transform them into energy with high efficiency.
At the same time, they are self-replicating
and through carbon bonding,
function as a durable exoskeleton.
This is proof that the Hideauze are the
results of directed evolution by the human race.
You...
How can you be like this?!
Even though it thoroughly refutes the meaning
of the Galactic Alliance's... of my battle!
You recognize an error in your knowledge.
Can I fight the Hideauze if
they're the evolved human race?!
Is there a point to fighting them?!
If not, then I can't fight!
I can't murder those creatures...
Unacceptable.
Your cognition refutes the
significance of our existence.
You saw them too, didn't you?! The
forms of newborn whalesquid...
We're the same human race and
we're killing each other!
That's the true nature of our war!
Even after obtaining this information,
there is no reason to give up
on annihilating the Hideauze.
That's only you!
But for me...
Negative. The Hideauze bring fundamental
destruction to the human race.
Helping to avoid that is your sole mission.
But we're all humans!
I've had enough of the Alliance's brainwashing!
Negative. The parallel link between
the Alliance and myself has been lost.
I have arrived at this conclusion
independently, based on information analysis.
What?
The human race and the Hideauze will always
be antagonistic toward one another.
The reason for this is they are beings who
have rejected civilization as a whole.
What do you mean?
If the human race were equipped with strong,
versatile bodies like the Hideauze,
it would not have been necessary
to develop Machine Calibers.
My system is the crystallization of
the intelligence of the human race.
But we are also necessary to
offset the fragile human body.
Conjecture: Humans are beings
that surpass their own limits,
develop their intellect,
and build civilizations.
The existence of civilization is what separates
the human race from all other primates.
But the Hideauze have thrown away their
human forms and have no physical limits.
If living beings only seek out
happiness and gratification,
it isn't necessary for them
to have a higher intellect.
But the human race relies
solely on Machine Calibers.
That is to say, we are the crystallization
of pure intellect, a product of civilization.
And by overcoming even that
intellect, the Hideauze
have reached an extreme state of existence.
You're saying the Hideauze
are an extreme life form.
And so, you and I
must battle, with the dignity
of the human race at stake.
In a war with something that shares
the same building blocks as you,
failure means certain extinction.
One side seeks out civilization.
The other abandons it.
The war between the Galactic Alliance
of Humankind and the Hideauze
is a conflict between two
different survival strategies,
one in which being culled is all
that waits for the losing side.
Culled...
As long as you wish to exist, you
don't have the luxury of a choice.
Fight and impose our ways?
A machine like you is
telling a human like me...?
I am a Pilot Support Enlightenment
Interface System.
By achieving more and more results, you
will realize the importance of existence.
Receiving polarized photon sequence.
It is a Galactic Alliance standard
encrypted communication wave.
What?!
Identified as an allied mech.
Allied mech?!
Commander Kugel...