Episode 6
"Punch"
Kakeru-kun.
Oh, morning.
How about some tea?
You should take a break.
Morning.
Did I wake you up?
No.
There you are.
I was looking for you.
I've always been here.
I'm still a little sleepy.
There was a line in a movie:
"If a girl of age is sleeping on her stomach,
it's because she's in love."
Though, I think a parent
can tell regardless.
But...
There aren't any romance movies
called "You Know What Happens Next",
are there?
You know what happens?
No, I don't. But what if I did?
Would it be boring?
I don't know what you're talking about,
but if you did, you could enjoy it twice.
Wow, Mom.
Even if you knew about
a future that's a bit sad,
at least you can prepare for it.
So many perks.
"Enjoy it twice," huh?
That might be nice.
I could enjoy the feeling of
making a good piece twice.
And in love...
In love—
Are you okay?
I'm fine. It was a bug.
I think.
A bug?
Just a bug, huh?
She's a good girl, being that she's our girl,
but she's of age, so, y'know.
Of age?!
Hello, Touko?
It's Okikura.
Can you talk?
Yes!
I never got a chance to hear what you
wanted to talk about the other day.
I, um, I'll call you back.
I hung up.
What's up?
She just hung up on me.
That girl from before?
I'll make coffee.
Did you mess up?
I can't experience my first kiss twice.
I can't do it.
I can't.
My heart will burst.
Okikura-kun, sorry about earlier.
Sorry, it's Hiro.
Are you okay?
I wanted to talk to you
about the get-together today.
Huh, are you listening?
'Sup.
Breakfast's ready.
Okay.
Crap, I can't be like this forever.
How am I supposed to present myself?
Morning, sleepy-head.
You couldn't hear Mom calling?
I was getting changed.
Oh. Breakfast's going to get cold. Hurry.
Hey.
What?
I have to swing by somewhere
before we go to Kazemichi.
Got it.
I actually
had you come early, Touko-san.
Me? Really?
Yeah.
About before—
I heard you were at Sacchan's place.
Maybe she wanted me to know about you.
But she couldn't say it straight out.
Y-You think so?
But don't tell Yukinari
and Yanagi-san about it.
What? Everyone already kno—
I want to tell them myself.
Sure, of course.
It's so hot.
Got it.
I did it. I confessed.
Good for you, Yana-chan.
I like how you're missing
just a little bit of tact.
How've you been?
I don't like the heat.
Hey.
Let's get straight to it.
Where's Sachi?
Yeah, it's about Sacchan.
So it's a surprise?
Yep.
Remember when she couldn't go
to the fireworks with us last time?
So I thought, maybe we could set up
fireworks so that she could come, too.
Don't you think?
I do. I like that.
Let's do that.
We have exams coming up.
I think we're having too many outings.
Oh well.
I'll let Sacchan know.
Sorry.
Hello?
She could talk here.
Maybe she can't.
I wonder who?
David, probably?
Dude.
Oh, we can get a hold of him.
Why don't we invite him, too?
You mean, get Touko to invite him?
Why don't I, then?
I will.
Huh?
I know where he lives, I think.
Why, though?
Sorry.
Touko-san, we were saying
maybe we should invite David-kun.
Why?
It just kind of happened.
Yes?
I'm Imi, Okikura-kun's—
Hold on.
I'm surprised you found my house.
Okikura is a famous name around here.
Want to come in?
If you have time, I want to talk outside.
I'm a complete idiot.
Hello, Okikura here.
My name is Fukami.
Is Oki... Kakeru-kun—
Kakeru just went out.
I see.
Is Imi-kun a friend of yours, too?
Yes, well...
I didn't really want to invite you.
Then you don't have to.
What's the problem?
You can't just do the things that you want
to do. That's not how the world works.
I see.
So, what?
We're going to the fireworks,
the usual group.
I'm inviting you.
I see,
so you didn't want to invite me,
but you didn't have a choice.
Yeah.
Then I'll decline.
No reason to cause a stir.
You caused a huge stir
the moment you arrived.
I figured.
Are you doing it on purpose?
Somewhat.
Are you enjoying it?
Of course not. It's circumstantial.
Just like you, I'm not doing
it because I want to.
What are you talking about?
What's your relationship with Touko?
Haven't you realized how Touko feels?
I haven't heard anything from Touko.
And I have no reason to tell you.
You...
Hey, wait!
Did Takayama confess to you?
You mean to tell me you
haven't answered her yet?
I think we should skip
inviting Kakeru-kun this time!
What happened?
Let's just say it hurt.
Why did you—
No...
No! No way. Was it Yuki-kun?
Yeah.
Oh, no.
No, I said too much.
It seems Takayama told him how she felt.
I wonder if I'm being awful to Yuki-kun.
I don't know.
Honestly, there are a lot of things
I don't understand lately.
We all chipped in.
Fireworks.
I like those.
Good thing I bought a lot.
We set up the festival for you, after all.
But this...
was supposed to be a surprise.
I can tell you're being thoughtful.
Welcome ba—
What's wrong?
He's not coming to the fireworks.
What happened? Tell me.
Nothing.
Two guys going after Touko...
What am I?
Sorry.
I don't want you to apologize.
I know we can't just leave things like this.
I'll figure it out.
Want to come over?
My father's home.
Sure.
These are all my CDs.
I guess. I'm a fan.
What's wrong?
It's my mother.
I'll head home for today.
Touko.
Have I found it?
Your mom is that pianist—
Where are we going?
I feel calmer when I'm here.
I know what you mean.
What's your mother like?
Well...
I guess she's someone who
doesn't stay in one place.
I don't know if it's because of her
work or because of her personality.
She must be an active person.
When I was young,
it always looked like she was doing
the right thing no matter what.
I suppose that makes me a mama's boy.
No way.
Sometimes I feel that way, too.
I called you twice already.
Will you tell me what you
were calling me about now?
Sorry we couldn't talk either time.
Sacchan's being hospitalized.
She says it'll be fine,
because it's just for tests.
But I've seen her future, in the hospital.
You're worried.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Hello, Yuki-kun?
Touko,
sorry, there's something I
need to talk to you about.
About you punching Okikura-kun, right?
You met up with him?
I'm with him now.
Come to the school yard.
Let's settle this.
You're on my side, right, Touko?
Yana-chan, stop them!
It'll get really bad if they meet!
I apologize for punching you.
My bad.
Yana-chan.
If you really think so,
let's have a race.
We have a perfect field here.
Run?
You? Against me?
Running is about the only thing you
can take seriously, is it not?
If you win, I'll never see Touko again.
If I win, Touko is mine.
You have Takayama.
I don't mind if you lose on purpose.
You don't even intend to run, do you?
I don't know what you're after,
but you're the worst for
what you chose to do!
Let's go.
Let them go!
Fireworks festival postponed?
Maybe David-kun couldn't make it.
How about just a mini-fireworks festival?
Is it true what Yana-chan said?
Yeah, I never intended to run.
There's no way I could have won.
Then why?
What was I thinking, starting a fist fight?
I don't know.
That's awful.
That doesn't explain anything.
It doesn't.
Maybe I just wanted you to say
that you're on my side.
What are the future fragments to you, Touko?
Preparation so I can enjoy things twice?
You sure are interesting.
I called them "fragments"
of the future because
they seemed like pieces
of me that were missing.
Pieces that I need
to make my fractured self solid and whole.
But those pieces were
just weak sounds or voices.
Nothing more.
Until I met you.
I'm slowly starting to understand.
What I want
isn't those mysterious pieces.
It must be something clearer,
more tangible.
Do you mean—
All I can hear is
your voice.
I keep seeing you, too.
Have I found it?
I don't like David.
The future can't be changed.
What is my relationship with Kakeru-kun?
I'm going home for now.
Episode 7
"Bicycle"
Please don't look bad.