The opening battle of the Union Fest
was the one-on-one between Ecle and myself.
Right now Biscotti has the lead in points.
Up next are Biscotti and Pastillage:
it'll be the Princess versus Becky!
I'm going out to get some battle points.
Nanami, I'm counting on you, too!
Okay. I'll do my best.
One-On-One In The Skies and On Land
Harlan and Pickle are
ready for take off!
Front and rear safety check complete!
Chief, Princess, we're ready.
Yes!
Ruler of Biscotti, Millihiore, and...
Chief of the Royal Research
Institute, Ricotta...
are moving out!
Indeed!
Bring it on Millihi-nee, Rico!
We'll fight this one out in the skies!
Biscotti's and Pastillage's
representatives will clash in the sky!
General, thank you for escorting me.
Don't mention it!
Hero and general, this
is an unusual combination!
Biscotti's 3rd Battalion
The size of their army...
I see, they want to completely
crush our 3rd Battalion here.
My assault team and I will take on
the small fry from your 3rd Battalion.
And d'Arquien, you'll
be facing our Hero!
Hina-sama! May I fight you one-on-one?
If you're specifically asking for it,
how could I refuse?
Biscotti's 3rd Battalion and myself
accept your challenge!
Don't hesitate! Charge!
All right, our 1st camp's pushing forward.
General, your orders?
Yes, to the main Galette force:
Attack and crush
Pastillage's front lines!
All units! Advance!
Galette's entire main
force is advancing.
They look ready to annihilate.
Jaune, you take command here.
Yes, sir.
Vert, you come with me.
We're going to take down
Pastillage's Sky Knights.
Roger that!
Congratulation for
clearing this section.
Here's your award ribbon.
Those soldiers who make it
through an obstacle course,
conquer a defensive position,
or who defeat multiple opposing soldiers
will naturally get their normal bounty,
but this time they'll also
get a special prize
from each land's support organizations.
Wonderful prizes have been gathered
from all three countries!
Food items, the latest household wares,
event and travel vouchers
are just a small selection!
So our soldiers,
please do your best to win them all!
Now, let us take a quick look
at the situation in town.
Are people getting excited in the
town beneath Firianno Castle?
That's quite involved.
Of course.
These kinds of large scale
mega events are broadcast everywhere.
The knights, Heroes, and rulers
are all loved by the common folk.
Well, I guess it's good that the humans
are living in peace.
That way, both the Demon King
and the Hero King can slack off
without having to worry about anything.
But it looks like this Hero
King can't really handle it...
They don't look like they can control themselves.
Adel.
Why don't you just go and join the fun?
It's not like that!
I just wanted to see what
war's like these days!
Besides, it wouldn't be good if old folk
interrupt the young people's festival.
Princess!
We were able to make
it, just as promised!
Rebecca-san! Thank you!
I'm really happy!
No, I have to thank you!
Usually those two are best friends,
but today they're enemies!
But still, they're
going into it smiling!
Even if we're friends,
we won't be holding back in this fight!
Let's show them the Biscotti
aerial fighting style!
Sounds interesting.
Rebecca, let's open fire!
Yeah!
Palette card, ready!
Flow Light Barrage!
Fire!
Explode!
That's our bullet rain
that pierces the skies!
Can you dodge that?!
Let's return fire.
Roger that!
Deploying counter-fire... barrage!
And... go!
So pretty...
Indeed.
This was an wonderful opening
exchange of attack and defense!
Princess, Chief, what were
those moves just now?!
Special bullets from the Royal
Research Institute and...
My emblem sword that
I practiced for today!
Both the Princess and Rico are amazing.
Yeah.
Rico and the Princess have
been working very hard this whole time.
One...
For Biscotti's victory...
for a war that's even more fun.
Then we have all the more
reason that we have to win.
Yeah!
Move forward!
Don't fret! Charge!
I see. I can tell you were Sink's teacher.
We've been working hard
together since we were little.
Even if my opponent is you,
the strongest in the land,
aiming to win is Galette's style!
I will go all out!
I look forward to it.
Here I... go!
Tempest Slash!
Ex Machina, Form Change!
Boomerang Slash!
Neptune Fist!
Bright Power Charge!
Freeze!
Link active!
Here I go!
This is...
Finishing blow!
Lupine God Void Fang
Demon Sealing Judgement!
That was close...
Oh, no...
Wow! Lady d'Arquien's
armor was destroyed!
Hero Nanami's boomerang flew
down from above and hit!
Even though Hero Nanami went down,
this was excellent!
Galette Spirit...
Biscotti's strong in both one-on-ones
and in the group battles.
We're going to ride this
high and push through!
High's don't matter!
Fighting with skill and
power is Galette's style!
I'm going all out!
Transform!
T-Transform?!
Who are those hotties?
The details are secret,
but this is their special move!
Apparently this is a
hypercharged mode where
all their powers gain in potency!
Is that okay?
Using that in public?
Yes, I actually recommended it.
That's another proper way that will lead
to giving people hope and joy.
That's fine, but you need to calm down.
Furious Lightning Strike!
You're annoying, Rico!
You bet I am!
Ecle really gave her best today!
I have to show the princess
and the Heroes that
I am capable as well!
The same goes for me!
Pastillage's people are watching!
I cannot lose this fight!
Harlan, here we go!
Both of them are incredible...
Yeah...
Truth be told, I was a bit nervous
about this vacation.
Sink had told me that he
really loved this place,
where he made tons of new friends...
I was afraid that there'd
be no place for me there.
That'd never happen!
You're an important guest!
Yes, I was truly welcomed
from the first day,
and Cou-sama even made me a Hero.
I was able to become
friends with such a
nice and cute Princess as you.
I'm glad I was able to come here.
I'm really glad I was able to
become friends with you!
I feel the same way, Rebecca!
Wouldn't it be really
fun if the two of us
could have a fight
during tomorrow's war?
Hero versus Princess.
Yes, certainly!
Cheering on and watching over
someone you love is fun...
but being able to compete
with them is even better!
Because you're somone I love,
I want you to see...
my passion and my unrelenting courage!
Here I go, Princess!
Witch Cannon - Asterism Strive!
Right, Rebecca!
Excelide!
The Princess's and Rebecca-sama's biggest
attacks just clashed!
Both were finishing moves!
Who was victorious?
Princess!
I'm coming right away!
What? Seriously?!
Princess, Princess, wake up!
Huh?
We're falling! It's bad!
Oh no! We have to save them!
Yes, indeed!
That was a good fight,
but you have to stay safe.
It'd be really bad if
either of you got hurt.
Sink...
Hero Sink has gracefully
saved them in midair!
It appears that he went to save them
right after he defeated Prince Gaul!
I didn't lose!
I let him have this one!
Umm... Thank you, Sink.
Thank you very much!
The Princess' and Hero Rebecca's
armor was destroyed!
Now we did it...
I'm sorry!
Looks like they need
our rescue after all.
Yes, indeed.
Hero Nanami's back!
Biscotti's got the most victory points!
Can Galette catch up?
Shut up, we'll overtake them now!
Right!
Will Pastillage, currently in
last place, be all right?!
Pastillage Main Camp
The point gap keeps growing!
Will there really be a
chance for an upset?!
Your motherland's in danger.
Don't you have to go save them?
If you don't want to show
your true identity, use this.
People of Pastillage!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
For justice!
For hope!
Here to aid Pastillage, I am Hero Mask!
Yup!
She's really into it.
Adel-sama's wonderful.
If the Hero King, I mean...  If Hero Mask's our opponent...
The three youngsters from Biscotti...
Will rise to the challenge!
Sounds good, bring it on!
Union Fest, the event that takes place
when the three countries are united.
The first day of the war
was intense and fun....
but it was just still just beginning!
The festival fun will still go on!
If I got bigger with a Hero Crystal,
I bet I'd look like this.
No way, you're already...
Change My Heart
Gaul! Shhh!
See you next time.