Are you free on 3/14?
Let's meet up if you aren't busy.
White Day??
I said it!
I was trying to pretend I didn't know.
But I did notice—so much for that.
Takeo-kun!
Oh, I'm so happy!
Thanks!
This box...
Oh, wait...
Did you make this?
Wow, she can tell just from looking at the box?
I want to see!
Can I open it?
Sure.
Sorry...
When I baked them for the specified
time, they looked a little pale.
But when I baked them a little longer,
they looked okay at first, but then they
got scorched and hard-looking.
I can't eat these!
They're too precious!
But I want to try one!
Can I?
Sure.
Isn't it rock-solid?
It's super good!
Takeo-kun?
Oh, I was just thinking it's nice to have
someone eat something you made.
To have the girl you like happily
eat what you made...
That's what it's always like for me!
I see...
The Letter and Me
Did she like the cookies?
Thanks for helping me
Yeah!
I hope you'll find a girl you like soon!
And I hope that girl will like
home-made rice crackers.
Rice crackers?
My bad.
If it's a girl who'd smile and eat cookies,
That was way off
which are as hard as rice crackers, with you...
Suna, you go on ahead.
Okay, later.
You need something?
Hey, do you need something?
To Sunakawa Makoto-sama
A letter?
I wanted to give it to Sunakawa-kun...
Suna?!
Sorry!
What?
To Sunakawa Makoto-sama
I don't need anything in return,
so please like me.
To Sunakawa-kun
I don't need chocolates in return,
so please like me.
Sorry that I misread you.
And I saw this.
So this is the girl who's been sending Suna
anonymous letters all this time.
I'm sorry for what happened to your letter.
I can just write one again—
No!
Let me make it up to you somehow!
Tell me how.
Okay, just let me know if
there's anything I can do.
Later!
Oh...
T-Takeo-kun!
"Takeo-kun"?
Th-Then, can you please hear me out?
Let me tell you about Sunakawa-kun!
S-Sure...
Oh, of course you don't recognize me.
We were in the same cherry class, in kindergarten.
I'm Amami Yukika.
Amami Yukika...
Argh...
Y-You don't have to try so hard to remember.
I think I remember!
Haze
Amami Yukika-chan!
Right.
Why isn't she saying anything?
Does she need some opportunity?
Should I just say something?
I'm not good at this sort of thing, either...
But no, I should try...
Give me all you've got!
Sorry.
No, I'm sorry for making you worry.
I'm just not very good at talking with boys.
I see.
Even all the way back in kindergarten,
boys would tear up the sandbox, even if
girls were playing house there.
I might have done that.
Boys would bring bugs and stuff to class.
I've done that.
They'd be muddy, even in the morning.
That'd be me.
Their socks were all dirty.
That was also me.
But Sunakawa-kun was different.
He had this presence.
Presence... Presence?
He was often reading picture books.
I'd read the same books,
just to learn what kind of books he liked.
He was always so tidy when
he ate school lunches, too.
And he was good at dodgeball!
He was really nimble on his feet.
He'd always be the last one standing.
I was so amazed by him.
But just once...
Sunakawa, you're out!
I was behind Sunakawa-kun, so I didn't
see the ball being thrown at all.
If Sunakawa-kun had dodged the ball,
I think it would've hit me.
That sounds like him.
Afterward...
Um, I'm so sorry.
You got hit because of me.
I just thought you might get
hurt if it hit your glasses.
I really fell for him! Hard!
I can see why.
That's the last time I ever
talked to Sunakawa-kun.
You haven't spoken to him since?
That was back in elementary school, right?
No, kindergarten.
Kindergarten?!
Since I'm in high school now,
that makes it ten years ago.
Ten years?!
What have you been doing all these years?
Watching.
During sports festivals...
Or even when nothing is happening.
I've been watching Sunakawa-kun live his life.
I also gathered all the information I could,
and tried to read his fortune.
She's a fortuneteller?
But you could've at least tried to talk to him.
I can't even talk to a normal guy!
How can I talk to a guy I like?
Then what are you going to do?
There's nothing I can do.
I don't have the courage to talk to him
or tell him how I feel.
All the way through kindergarten, elementary
school, junior high, and high school,
every time Sunakawa-kun turned
down a girl, I'd feel relieved.
If he can't be mine,
sometimes, I don't want him to date
anyone for the rest of his life.
Is that a curse?
Still, every time Valentine's Day comes around,
I consider telling him how I feel.
But I can never find the courage
to write my name.
Since I'm not brave enough to talk to him,
I'm always just circling him.
I see...
Ten years... That's amazing.
Your girlfriend, Yamato-san.
She seems like a nice person.
Y-Yeah!
Why did Yamato come up suddenly?
Seeing you two so happy together,
it makes me envious.
It's nice when two people feel the
same way about each other.
I couldn't write my name this year, either.
so I was hoping to give him the letter in person.
But I just ended up carrying
it around for a month.
To Sunakawa Makoto-sama
I don't have the courage to hand it to him.
Sunakawa-kun is always so calm and cool.
He never does anything strange.
That isn't true.
He does some pretty random things.
What are you doing?
I just thought it'd be fun if she started calling
you "brother" in English out of the blue.
You're right.
When he's with you, he often laughs.
I'm jealous...
I wish I lived next to him.
Then we would have ridden
the same kindergarten bus,
and we could've taken baths together.
Not that we do that anymore.
You could take each other's photos in the bathtub...
We never did that!
I've been envious of you for a very long time.
I see, sorry.
But I need Suna, too.
It's true that Suna's cool.
Oh, yes.
He is.
He really is a perfect ideal.
Ideal...
Sure, he's cool, but he's a normal human being.
He trips sometimes.
Are you sure you haven't idealized him?
I haven't.
It isn't that my ideal is Sunakawa-kun.
Sunakawa-kun became my ideal.
Takeo?
What are you doing?
Oh, well...
She vanished!
No, I can still sense her presence.
What's with your wet pants?
Well...
You aren't going home?
Yeah, I am.
Let's go home.
Your feet are really big.
Take!
When are you going to stop
getting your clothes all dirty?
It isn't that my ideal is Sunakawa-kun.
Sunakawa-kun became my ideal.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Memories
She's in photos with him a lot
more than I expected.
Field Trip
Suna, maybe people
all have a hot, molten core inside their hearts,
and they just live their lives,
never showing it to the world,
as if nothing is really going on.
Yeah.
Though maybe not everyone's like that.
Takeo-kun!
You aren't hiding?
We're in the same high school...
Um, I think I'll talk to Sunakawa-kun, after all...
I see.
And I want your help.
Okay.
I thought of a way to start a conversation
with him as naturally as possible.
Will you hear me out?
Sure.
Can we make it
so that you got lost, and I helped you out?
S-Sure...
That's really roundabout.
I don't have the courage to tell him how I feel,
but I want him to acknowledge me, just once.
My world and his have never crossed, so...
All right.
Would tonight, early evening, work?
Around once every three days, Suna goes
to the convenience store.
Right, I know.
Suna!
I got lost at the train station!
This nice girl helped me back here.
She's a very kind girl.
Girl?
You mean Amami-san?
We've been in the same school since kindergarten.
O-Oh, I see.
I love you.
I love you, Sunakawa-kun!
I don't need anything, so please like me!
Hey!
Love
Longing
I thought you didn't have the courage
to tell him how you feel!
Well, not that it matters...
But why are you running away?
Watch out!
Don't give me that!
I thought you were going to fall.
I wish I had...
I want to fall in and cool my head!
It isn't that kind of river!
I wasn't planning on telling him...
Yeah, I was shocked, too.
I didn't think he'd remember me at all.
But when he did...
I got so overwhelmed, I just blurted it all out.
Well, just let it go.
You can't undo what's happened.
Can't I wipe his memory somehow?
Nope.
Can't I fudge it somehow?
Nope!
Yukika-chan, are you okay
letting things end this way?
Don't you want to tell him properly?
Do you think what you've felt for him
over the years really came through?
Don't you want it to?
I've been stalking him for ten years...
You don't think he'll find me creepy?
He'd never say anything like that.
I'll go tell Sunakawa-kun how I feel.
I'll go tell him properly,
and I'll go get turned down properly.
I'll end it.
He's still there!
Amami-san,
were you the one who always gave
me chocolates for Valentine's
with an unsigned letter?
Yes!
I see.
If you'd signed your name,
I would have responded.
Amami-sa—
Um, do you not like me?
No, it isn't like that.
Isn't it?!
That's it...
You don't know enough about me
to feel one way or the other!
So I don't want your response right now!
Yukika-chan?
So...
Please learn more about me!
Please give me your response after that.
I see.
That's one way to think about it.
But you've changed your mind again, Yukika-chan.
You're right. Okay, I understand.
Then I'll give you my cell phone number.
Okay!
I'm pretty flexible with times.
There are times that won't work, but...
Okay, thank you!
You don't have to be so polite.
Then, I'll get going.
Are you okay?
H-How could I've done what I just did?
I scare myself!
You were really persuasive
Yeah, I was shocked, too.
But I'm happy for you.
It isn't over yet.
Right!
If you liked someone for ten years,
of course you wouldn't want
things to end so easily.
I'm glad you weren't turned down.
Why?
Suna, why didn't you turn her down?
The pressure...
Were you persuaded or something?
Well, I guess.
You guess?
Stare...
Maybe I'm more of a pushover than I thought.
Maybe?
Actually, why were you with Amami-san?
Oh...
It was like this, this, and that.
I got the gist of it.
I guess you were good at dodgeball.
At dodging, anyway.
Ah...
Yukika-chan told me.
Oh, I see.
It's hard to know what Suna's thinking.
What?
Oh, I was just remembering
how you played dodgeball.
Me?
You only targeted the really strong players.
There! There!
You'd end up being in a showdown
with the strongest player.
Even if they threw the ball at someone else,
you'd fly sideways to catch it.
Shingo! Shingo!                            Takeo! Takeo!
In the end, you made it into
a totally different game.
I did stuff like that?
Yeah, you did.
I see.
Suna's really observant about people.
But I guess he didn't notice the incident
that made Yukika-chan fall for him.
I won't tell him,
because it's something Yukika-chan
should tell Suna in the future.
Presence Detected
Yukika-chan's here!
Takeo?
No, it's nothing.
Why doesn't she come and talk to him?
Does she need an opening?
Is that it?
All right!
Yukika-chan, Suna's coming that way!
Thanks
What're you doing?!
Suna, wait here for a sec.
Okay.
Yukika...
There you are!
Don't give me that!
What're you doing?
Weren't you going to let Suna
learn more about you?
I'm sorry.
Go!
Go make him learn!
O-Okay!
Suna!
Here's Yukika-chan.
Walk home with her.
Oh, okay.
Let's go.
Is this on your way home, too?
Y-Yes.
Good luck, Yukika-chan.
I hope you can get through to him.
Huh?
Why is she so far from him?
Amami-san, you live around here?
Yes.
And he's walking really slowly today.
I'm going to take the train from here.
What about you, Amami-san?
No...
Okay, see you later.
Yes.
Hey, weren't you going to have
him learn who you are?
I... I'm sorry.
Being right next to him, I could
barely remember to breathe.
Sunakawa-kun was...
The Sunakawa-kun was talking to me!
Sunakawa—
Keep it together!
Grab
Takeo-kun?
It's me.
Where are you right now?
I'm at Shuuei Station now.
Really?
What were you up to?
I'm—
A girl!
A Girl
Hang on a second.
Sure.
Sorry, but can I tell Yamato what's going on?
I'm not good at keeping things under wraps,
and I don't really want to.
Sure, please tell her.
Thanks.
Hey, Yamato?
I was just talking to a girl named
Yukika-chan who likes Suna.
Oh, okay.
Um, is that okay for me to know?
I'd even like her to give me advice!
Your explanation was easy to understand.
Yeah.
I thought you'd talk to Suna like you've
talked with Yamato and me.
But you didn't talk to him at all.
It's impossible...
I barely managed to walk with him
without dying, then and there.
Yeah, I know.
I was super nervous when I first
talked to Takeo-kun, too.
Standing in front of his apartment,
I couldn't ring the doorbell and
stood there for a long time.
When I called him,
my heart was pounding so hard.
I see...
I didn't know any of that then,
but I was a lucky man.
To Sunakawa-kun
I don't need anything in return,
so please like me.
If you can't talk to him, how about smiling?
I don't think I can smile that well...
How about letters and texts?
If it's anonymous, I can write...
I see...
Hmm!
How can I help?
Why not go somewhere together?
That's fun enough, in and of itself.
That's right!
Nice idea, Takeo-kun!
Going somewhere with Sunakawa-kun!
Suna!
Did you get any texts from Yukika-chan?
No.
Oh, just got one.
Sender: Amami Yukika
Subject: Good Evening
This is Amami.
Thank you for earlier today.
Would you like to go to the zoo sometime?
Gouda-kun and Yamato-san can accompany us.
If you'd like, please let me know what
dates and times work best for you.
She's so formal.
Why are you reading it?
It says Yamato-san and you are
also invited. Is that okay?
S-Sure.
Great! Just great!
Do you know something?
Huh?
Well, whatever.
Okay, let's all go together.
Okay.
Nice job, Yukika-chan.
Suna, are you really okay with this?
With what?
If you don't want to go,
I think you can say no.
How you feel is what's important here.
If I didn't want to, I wouldn't go.
Then you want to?
I guess.
Isn't that amazing?
Maybe.
I'm fine to go whenever.
When you reply, be sure to tell her that.
Okay.
He said he wants to go.
Good luck, Yukika-chan.
A Letter to Me
Next time: A Letter to Me.