Okay! Cut!
Wow, the staff around
Yunosagi are very capable.
I hadn't expected you to
bring such large-scale equipment with you.
The cameraman works in
the special effects department,
so he's actually better at filming stunts like this.
All right! Let's film the next scene!
Do you have a moment, Madam Manager?
Come in.
Thanks.
Take this.
Thanks!
Hello?
Oh, Mom?
Well, well...
Are you feeling homesick,
after your recent visit home?
Let me get straight to the point.
You received an offer for a movie to be shot at the inn, didn't you?
Yes.
You didn't accept that offer, did you?
If you haven't accepted it yet, that's good.
I've left Enishi in charge of that.
What are you saying?!
I'm telling you,
something is fishy about the whole thing!
You can call it off right now
by just opening your mouth!
This time I don't plan
on interfering at all.
But, Mom!
How do you feel about
inheriting this inn?
Actually, no,
Enishi will be the one.
That's right.
Enishi will be the one
who inherits Kissuiso, Mom.
I've just said something
pretty foolish, haven't I?
It wasn't foolish.
But it is all in the past now.
Bye.
That's your job, young master.
Right.
Th-Then, shall we?
Okay.
Please excuse me.
We were watching you from up here!
That was excellent!
I hear that they're shooting a film here?
What you were doing
was very interesting!
Don't worry,
we'll still be at your service as usual.
It's okay.
I know how well
you've been taking care of us.
Were you the one who jumped
from the building just then?
No, that wasn't me.
My heart nearly stopped!
In that case,
you might want to refrain from
watching what's coming next.
Okay, that's a wrap!
Umm...
Yeah?
What's this movie supposed to be about, precisely?
The proposal said,
"waitresses in their youth."
Yuina...
Yeah...
I heard...
Hmm?
That all the madam managers in
the union don't like
this upcoming movie.
Well, I think everyone gets a little
uneasy when trying out something new.
Even though they're
not the ones staging it?
Yeah.
Wouldn't you be jealous if someone became
successful at doing something new?
I mean, people say that,
but there aren't exactly many
scenes in this film where lots
of madam managers appear.
Oh!
All the madam managers can go to
a hot spring for a work trip.
And then they all become zombies.
What?
A meal for two in the Paulownia Room, please!
Okay!
I'll take this to the Wisteria Room.
The meal with the red tag
has no green onions in it.
Okay!
Ohana.
Yes?
Oh, that explains it.
Explains what?
A customer in the Wisteria Room
kept staring at my face earlier.
You know...
I'll be on my way!
Hey! Get back here!
The next time we're here, we'll be shooting for real.
We'll be waiting.
I'm counting on you, Mr. Isami.
Yes, hello?
Expect great things.
I'm turning this on, young master.
Do it.
I hear it is a scam.
Oh, my!
I had my suspicions from the start!
A scam?
This has got nothing to do with you.
Leave.
The folks at Kissuiso have
really done it this time.
Takako! Takako!
You still haven't managed
to contact Mr. Isami?!
No, I only received an
e-mail from him saying
that the project had been called off.
I'll try calling him again later.
I had my suspicions
about this from the start!
What?!
You're telling me this now?
Didn't I tell you?
"Don't rush the payment and
only pay them once you've
confirmed that it's safe."
Y-Yeah, but...
Anyway, the contract is under your name, Enishi!
But you're the one who told me
about this in the first place, Takako!
I know...
I know that...
What's going to happen
to the young master?
I have no idea...
I did hear he paid them a lot of money, though.
It's his fault for
listening to that dumb woman.
Don't say such things.
I get it!
"Isami Tetsuo."
The characters in his
name must stand for,
"Stepping out of the ring and
following someone's mistake!"
I'll peel the white radish.
I knew that Tohru was tactless,
but I still think that a good
chef can be.
Oops...
Hey...
Oh, did you hear?
The movie's been called off.
Too bad we didn't get to act in it.
Yeah.
It's too bad.
What are you going to do now?
Man, I was really excited.
I was thinking that this would
be the summer break to remember.
Nakochi was also really excited.
What a shame.
I rushed here
because I thought
Kissuiso would be in a mess,
but I'm glad to be wrong.
I'm heading back now.
What? But you only just got here!
Later!
I guess she doesn't know much about it.
Hello?
This is just me talking to myself.
Isami Tetsuo.
He's run from debt twice
in his life before,
and he was laid off by
the people in his industry.
I'm pretty sure he's used
the money to pay off his debts,
so it'll be too difficult
to get it back.
The actors and the staff who
mistakenly got involved with him
are probably going to be
in trouble for a while.
Sorry for the sudden call.
Sis-
Hello?
I don't plan on crying over spilled milk,
and I still don't believe
that what I was trying
to do was wrong.
Yeah?
But just remember that the
investors are responsible for the result.
I know that.
I know you know.
But you're also responsible for
the staff and the customers.
You're strict as usual.
Well, I mean,
everyone makes mistakes.
Thanks for the info, Sis.
You're welcome.
Strawberry flavor is the best after all.
What are you doing, Ohana?
I figured I'd clean the
area surrounding the pool.
But the movie's been called off.
I've been cleaning the pool every day recently,
so it's sort of become one of my tasks now.
I just can't stand not cleaning it.
Then I'll help you.
Oh, you two are going as well?
What?
Minko's already gone ahead of you.
But why?
For the same reason as you.
That pool isn't only for the movie.
Let's go.
Wait for me!
Takako!
Takako, wait!
I'm going to Tokyo.
I've got a lot of things
which I need to take care of.
Yes, I know. I want to go with you.
I don't have time to
babysit you any longer!
"Babysit"?
I thought we were partners...
Partners?
You're the one who's
responsible for this incident.
I'm just an adviser.
An adviser. Do you understand?!
But, Takako, we handed him
the contract together!
We discussed it and decided together!
Oh, that's right. That-
Why don't you...
Why... Why...
Why don't you go and ask
your beloved sister for help then?
Don't you dare say bad
things about my sister!
You're exactly like Madam Manager.
What?
Sorry, it was a reflex.
Th-
Th-Th-
That's right!
You're a woman
who's able to strike back!
Talking about who's responsible
here won't help us at all!
I want you to show
me how cool you are!
The Takako I always see!
"We strike back."
"I shall"-
No...
"We shall return!"
What nonsense are you spouting now?
Just because it's English doesn't mean
you can just say anything.
She's right about that.
I said, don't mind me!
Wait, Takako!
Takako!
Takako, just one more time-
Ta-Takako-
Hey...
What's going on?
Help... me...
Do you want me to
hold on or let go?!
Which is it?!
Umm... umm...
I can't decide...
I can't do this anymore!
I'm at my limit!
Max limit!
I can't stand this any longer!
Can you hear me, young master?!
I'm also a professional!
It isn't over yet!
I won't let this be over yet, do you hear?!
Why don't you try standing?
For God's sake...
Here.
What is your problem?!
This is my battle gear!
What? Battle gear?
Yes! And you're paying for it!
Look what you've done!
They were expensive!
So you were wearing your battle gear...
What?!
Like I said, they were expensive!
So, you were serious, Takako?
What?
Thank you, Takako.
You're not at fault.
You tried your best!
What the heck are you saying?!
I've always said that your independent and
peculiar way of thinking is
one of your major flaws-
Thank you!
What?
Thanks, and don't worry.
Let's start again together.
Let go of me.
This time, we'll do it together.
Only thinking about themselves.
Let's go.
What?
We shouldn't watch any more.
You can keep going.
But your clothes...
I don't mind.
Where are you going?
I thought I'd act like
a mother for once.
Kissuiso's got a lot to take care of now.
Well, I hate to say this,
but they brought this upon themselves.
They were walking on air, weren't they?
Hey, it felt good.
I did walk on air when
I leaped from the second story window.
Bang! Bang! Bang!
There was also a scene like that.
Welcome.
Sorry to hear the bad news.
I thought it would be best
if I let you, the representatives of Yunosagi,
know of our current situation.
The meal for the Wave Room is ready.
Okay!
Is the sashimi for the
Crane Room still not ready?
Nope, it is!
I'll be taking this.
Welcome back, Madam Manager.
What's with that outfit?
Well...
Come to my room.
Okay.
How's everyone doing?
They're all doing well.
Madam Manager,
I should've been the one to go and explain.
Thank you very much, and I apologize.
But Ms. Kawajiri really had
Kissuiso on her mind,
and did her best to make things work.
No matter what you say,
Ms. Kawajiri will have to take
her share of the responsibility.
Be prepared for that.
Madam Manager...
You can call me "Mom."
Oh... okay.
Mom, I'm not defending her or anything.
She really was trying her best.
You can tell me this later.
More importantly,
I'm happy that you've grown enough to be able
to defend someone so much.
I never understood
whether you were simply
stubborn or just clumsy.
Are you talking about the piano lessons?
During high school,
I seriously thought that being
able to play an instrument
would get me the girls.
But you kept refusing to take
lessons in elementary school.
If only you'd put a collar on me
and taken me to those lessons,
my teenage life would have
been a lot different.
You were a terrible swimmer too.
I still am, Mom.
Mom!
Mom...
Ohana!
Look! It's done!
What a funny looking cloud...
Episode 17
Pool on the Hill
If I were a mermaid princess...
I wouldn't admire a prince...
because... land is scary.
Episode 18
A Mermaid Princess and a Shell Bra