Ange Kuroki. Age: 15.
"AHSMB's Shadow"
Apparently this is a real problem child.
As a pilot, Ange is highly skilled.
Ange is taking full advantage
of the unit's capabilities.
But there are considerable
problems on the cooperation
and social skills end.
We need to see a bit
more mental stability!
That very issue has the
other five members
of Team Rabbits terrified.
It's a good thing Izuru is the leader.
Anyone else, and I imagine
the team would be in even worse shape.
It looks like we're forcing
another toughie on him.
Excuse me...
Uh, Officer Ange?
Whoa!
S-sorry! I didn't mean to startle you.
N-no, I'm sorry!
I tend to get lost in my own
world when I'm concentrating.
I-I know!
You were like that on the
battlefield yesterday...
I'm sorry!
I said a bunch of rude
things back there.
Uh, hey! Don't worry about it!
I'm sorry!
Say, Officer Ange?
Please quit calling me that!
I'm younger than you...
Uh, th-then how about Officer Kuroki?
No, not that either...
Then how about Angie?
Don't you ever call me that!
Then what should I call you?!
By my name without any titles...
Y-you won't get upset?
I'll be fine!
I think...
Okay, Ange.
Thanks!
Um, how may I help you?
What was I doing here...?
No point in asking me!
Oh, now I remember!
I came to invite you to train with us!
We have morning training!
Training?
You want me to train with you?
Uh, I guess you don't want to?
Even at school, I always
trained by myself.
And you're handling Black
6's maintenance alone?
Right. It's less stressful this way.
Plus it helps me memorize
the unit's frame.
But we're a team, so we really
should train together.
I will if it's an order!
I-I've been meaning to
ask you, Officer Ange.
But, um, are you a guy or a-
I have to get changed,
so please go on ahead!
So you never asked if
Ange is a guy or a girl?
Yeah... It's hard to work
that into the conversation...
I'm afraid I'll accidentally step
on a landmine and set
him off like yesterday.
Haven't you been through something
like that once before?
Do you have any good
ideas or suggestions?
Don't look at me...
Isn't Ange a funny, vivacious girl?
I'm dying to become
friends with her so I can
go to her room and have sleepovers!
Only if Ange is a girl, right?
Didn't you call her a
"hot guy" just yesterday?
I did?
So I was thinking, why
don't we show him
that video Randy gave us a while back?
Good idea!
We could figure out Ange's
gender based on his reaction.
Yep! I think it's pretty normal
for guys our age to
be interested in sex.
How could you say that
with a straight face?
If we're going through with this,
let's borrow something more inten-
Scum balls!
I forgot how good her hearing was...
Sorry!
I didn't mean to take so long.
Ange!
I still can't tell if Ange
is a guy or a girl...
Well, this is our chance
to show off and shine!
What's the matter? We've only run 10km.
But we've got 3G pressing down on us!
What are your heart and
lungs made out of?!
Hang in there, Ange!
Asagi is really good at this,
so don't let your guard down.
Right! I'll do my best.
Okay! Ready, go!
First I need to set up my formation.
Game over!
Ange wins!
I don't believe it!
She actually beat Asagi in a simulation.
She concentrated her fire, broke
through his central forces,
attacked from behind and annihilated
the surrounding forces.
The speed of the maneuver
determined its success.
Sorry! I got caught in
the heat of the battle.
I accidentally went all out.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
This is my current baby!
It's the Scissorhands 16401,
a prototype made by the
GDF's Development Team!
They equipped it with a totally new
energy unit type that has beautiful
mechanical functionality that
prioritizes practicality.
As you can see, that gave
it a fresh new design!
And it applies the same idea
behind how the AHSMB work!
Just like my Gold 4, you can attach
a bunch of stuff to this
hottie's core block.
Naturally, you can use it as a sniper
rifle or as an assault rifle.
It also functions as a missile
launcher, a laser gun,
a taser grenade launcher, a phonon
maser and a high-performance air rifle!
It kills me when I think
about how I coulda shined
if I had this puppy with me
when we infiltrated that enemy ship!
Naturally-
You don't take very good care of it...
Sure, it has a nice design,
but its performance as a
multi-purpose rifle still
has room for improvement.
Wha-?!
Since it can be applied to anything,
each gun is only B-rank.
In space, a phonon maser
has no practical use.
And switching scopes from gun
to gun is hardly acceptable.
It's said that military
technology tends to fall for
the lure of making weapons either
too massive or too versatile.
I think this falls under that category.
To be honest, my Black 6 is
a new generation of AHSMB
made by focusing on the unit's
heavy armor and armament.
However, I believe that this era
calls for pursuing simplified,
specialized weapons and arms.
Amazing!
You know more about weapons than Suruga!
Nah, this is simply what
we learned in school.
Didn't you attend Instructor
Suzukaze's classes as well?
S-skill beats rote memory
any day of the week!
M-my stomach...
It's ready!
We have snacks after
our training sessions!
I-I've heard that Officer Ange
was also good at Home Ec.
So when I asked him to make something,
Kei decided to pitch in...
You shoulda stopped her!
What are you mumbling about?
It tastes best when
it's fresh, so eat up!
Isn't this three times
more potent than usual?
Isn't it just a blob of sugar?
Mine's ready, too!
Help yourselves.
It has a refined taste!
And it's soft on the tongue.
And best yet, it's not too sweet!
It isn't sweet at all.
Nah, you're the only human
out there who feels that way!
Izuru?
Teoria?!
What are you doing here?
I am allowed to walk
about more freely now.
It seems that the GDF's
officials have realized that
I have allied myself with
the people of Earth.
Of course, I am not
allowed to speak with
just anyone as of yet.
But they said that I may hold brief
private conversations with
those aware of the situation.
And you're the first
person I wanted to see!
Y-you came to see me?
Yes!
All the way out here?
You are my friend, after all.
B-but I don't remember
anything about you, Teoria!
All of my old memories have been erased
and I'm not allowed to
revive those memories!
Then please tell me
about your current life.
Aren't you the team leader?
Right!
Thanks to everyone's help and
support, I'm managing somehow.
But I'm a truly horrible leader...
Earth is losing the war,
but I can barely handle
the missions I'm on!
I still can't control my
AHSMB unit worth squat.
And who knows when that Jiart
guy is going to show up again?
I'm sure Asagi and Kei
must feel apprehensive.
They just keep it to themselves.
And I can't do a darn thing...
I want to be a hero and
protect everyone, but...!
I'm sorry!
I know dumping all of
this on you won't help.
You haven't changed, Izuru.
Before your memories were erased,
you often told me the exact same thing.
"I want to become a hero."
Did I really?
There was one other thing you said.
You'd say, "I will protect you, Teoria."
It made me so happy when you said that!
Izuru, in my eyes, you were a hero.
Y-you've just made me happy.
I'm glad you thought of me that way!
So I want you to promise me something.
Izuru, no matter what happens,
promise you'll come back alive.
You are my hero.
Okay! I-
It's my emergency pager!
This mission is called
Operation: Goliath.
Rather than engage in battle,
you are to rescue a
supply ship in distress.
The supply ship that Team Doberman
was temporarily operating
got trapped in the irregular gravity
belt, the Ship Grave Attracter.
They are currently unable to break free.
Normal ships cannot get
close enough to help them.
Team Rabbits, you are to
repair the supply ship
and help them get out! That is all!
This is a pretty peaceful mission.
Can't believe we're helping
a ship in distress.
A mission is still a mission!
Let's do our best to save
our senior officers!
Why are you so pumped up?
All six units have blasted off.
The path to their target is clear.
Red 5's Harmonic Levels are high.
I wonder what happened.
Ship Grave Attracter is composed
of cascading gravitational rapids
created by the spatial distortions
made by celestial bodies.
As the name implies, it
is a graveyard for ships
that have gotten caught in the past,
so look out for debris.
Officer Ange, how is Black 6 holding up?
Sir, everything looks good!
Looks like she hasn't snapped yet.
Don't let your guard down!
Who knows what will flip his switch?
We're entering the
irregular gravity belt.
Be careful!
It's like a waterslide!
I'm getting swept away!
No, I'm falling! I can't tell!
Debris!
Dodge around it!
Just kick back an' go with the flow ?
This is really stinkin' pathetic!
You just had to suggest
taking that shortcut!
What?!
And without our Rhinos,
our hands are tied!
You agreed with the idea 'cause
you were eager to get back!
But I wonder who they'll
send to help us...
Everyone is understaffed
the way the GDF
is reorganizing the fleets.
This is Team Rabbits.
Izuru?
We're here to help!
They sent you guys?!
Randy, guys, did any of you get hurt?
Everyone is okay!
But we've got some debris caught
in the engine and can't move!
We'd love to give you a hand,
but we can't go outside.
You'll have to clear
the engine on your own!
The first and third boosters
have suffered minor damage.
Once we repair these two,
you should be able to muster the
propulsion needed to break free.
Purple 2, issue the repair orders!
Black 6, watch the perimeter!
Roger!
Enemies approaching from above!
I've been waiting for you, Earthlings!
Surprise enemy attack!
Multiple incoming fighters!
It's the one that fought Red
5 in the Battle of Ceres!
Not good!
They're only lightly armed
for the rescue mission!
Gold 4 and Rose 3, continue
with the repairs!
Everyone else, intercept the enemy!
Roger!
Hurry, Tamaki!
She's so cute!
Patrick?!
Seriously?
Isn't that unit-?!
That is my only lamata!
Do as you will with the weaklings!
Black 6 is intercepting!
Show me a good time, my lamata!
I'm intercepting!
Officer Ange!
Now you've done it, you bastard!
He snapped!
Don't take me lightly!
Get back! He's only after me.
Outta my way!
Don't run from me, coward!
Hit me from the front if you're a man!
Black 6 can't keep up?
Black 6, fall back!
You can't out-maneuver him!
Quit flappin' yer damn traps!
Leave me the hell alone!
You are undeserving to be my lamata.
Your genes are hardly worth harvesting.
Ange!
If I could get in my Rhinos,
I could have gone to save him!
Can't we offer fire
support or somethin'?
The turret's control unit is dead.
It won't rotate.
Hey! You hear that, bunnies?
Hurry and finish the repairs!
I'll give ya an earful later
if ya don't hop to it!
Last one! Ready and here I go!
Nice! Leave the rest to me!
Consider it an honor for
me to hunt you down.
Izuru?
Izuru?!
Red 5's Harmonic Levels suddenly spiked!
It's just like when they
went on their first sortie.
Izuru, calm down! Pull back for now!
That's it!
This is what I have been waiting for!
He's fast!
Finished?
But you put on a rather good show.
So I want you to promise me something.
No matter what happens, promise
you'll come back alive.
Red 5's frame just changed?!
Izuru?!
What the heck?!
Is that another new AHSMB?
Red 5's Harmonic Level has
reached its former peak level.
No...! I don't believe it!
I see.
So you are not yet done
bringing me enjoyment!
You make my genes boil!
Is that really Izuru?
Red 5's body can't keep
up with Izuru's commands!
What's going on?!
It's too much for the unit!
But he's already maximized
Red 5's motor abilities!
Izuru?!
There! The repairs are all done!
Thank you, Tamaki!
Propulsion System: OK!
Sweet!
Turn to three o'clock!
Point the turret at the enemy fighter!
You're finished!
Yet another nuisance!
I've run out of time.
But this only serves
to whet my interest.
Izuru! Are you okay, Izuru?
Izuru! Izuru!
Izuru!
"Defending Vesta"