Akiteru, how long are you able to stay?
I have to go back to work on the 14th,
so I'm heading back to Sendai
the day after tomorrow.
You didn't want to go to Kei's game?
When I mentioned that I was
thinking about going yesterday,
he looked really annoyed...
Oh, yeah.
Mom, about Kei's glasses...
I'm home.
Welcome home.
How was the game?
Oh. Well, we won.
What were your opponents like?
Two meters.
Huh?
They had a first-year that was 201 cm tall.
Two hundred... And you won?
Apparently, he'd just started
playing volleyball.
Seriously?
Our blocks were absolutely useless, though.
Ah...
What?
You think it's only obvious
if you lose, don't you?
Huh? Yeah.
I mean, he was two meters tall.
Why don't you come over and
join my team's practice?
Haikyu!!
Episode 14: "Still Growing"
All right, start your
individual practice now.
We now have less than two
months until the qualifier
at the end of October.
Work hard on improving individually.
Yeah!
K-Kageyama-kun, what are you doing?
You could tell it was me?
Yeah...
Damn it!
Was that supposed to be a disguise?
Um, uh...
There's a team that we might face during
the qualifier for the prefecture,
and I wanted to check them out before that.
I see. So you were going
to shoot a video of them?
No. There's an unwritten rule that you
can only record official matches.
So nothing is actually going
to happen by me watching,
but summer vacation's over
and there's less than two months
until the prefectural qualifier.
I felt like I should
definitely check them out.
Um...
If you don't want to stand out at a
school after school hours,
I think it's best to just
wear plain training gear.
Bus Stop
And like...
That's too funny.
I'm a student here...
Setter Soul
Natural... Be natural.
All right. We're about to start.
Setter Soul
We're gonna be switching out members next.
Right!
Nice serve!
Hey, can you stop Ushiwaka, Tsukishima?
Of course not.
Even if it was pure luck, he's the ace
of a team in the national Top Three.
Well, if someone doesn't stop
Ushiwaka, we won't be able
to beat Shiratorizawa.
We're middle blockers.
You're already thinking about
taking top in the prefecture?
You're sure taking this lightly.
Anyway,
we have to beat everyone,
so it's the same thing.
You piss me off.
Why?!
If you can't do it,
I'm gonna do it!
Thinking that you can't do
it yourself is one thing,
but having someone else tell you
that you can't is irritating.
Huh?
Especially when it comes from you.
You pushed the diarrhea pressure
point! Curse you, Tsukishima!
I'm leaving.
Hey, this is Kei.
I'm heading over today.
Ow!
Sorry!
You made it back alive, Kageyama.
How'd it go?
I...
I may never be able to defeat Oikawa-san.
What are you talking about?
Quit messing around!
What did you see?
I think Seijoh was having a match against
a college that had some of their alumni.
When I got there, they were on break,
and they were about to start a
new match with different members.
I'm Oikawa. Pleasure working with you all.
Oikawa-san went onto the
college team as their setter.
It looked like there were a
lot of people he had just met.
That's Seijoh's captain, right?
He's pretty gaudy.
But...
After just a few plays,
Oikawa-san was a part of the team.
Even I could tell how
lively the spikers felt.
The ability to draw 100% out of anyone...
Most people can't do that, even after
spending lots of time with them.
But with Oikawa-san, it didn't
matter if he disliked the player,
or if the player had certain habits.
I'm sure
that he could use them freely.
No matter where he is,
Oikawa is a setter that can bring
the absolute best out of his team.
So are you saying that you're freaked out
by the Great King again, Kageyama-kun?
Yeah, I'm really freaked out.
Right now, Seijoh is what it is
because it's had Oikawa-san
for the last three years,
and our only chance to fight them
again is at the Spring Tournament.
We're going to beat them, as a team.
I'm going to defeat you, Great King!
That's my line!
Achoo!
I just got a chill...
If you catch a cold, I'm going to punch you.
That's going way too far!
Two blockers!
All right!
Adults definitely have much more power...
What the hell?
You're such a twig!
You eating properly?
Can I go home now?
Now, now, Akaizawa-san. Just watch.
My little brother will
show you a thing or two.
Like I'd lose to this puny
little high schooler.
Kaji Wild Dogs
He loves riling people up.
Forgive him.
Hey, can you stop Ushiwaka, Tsukishima?
You think it's only obvious
if you lose, don't you?
Maybe that's because you suck.
Tch.
Um...
Is there a way to stop an opponent's spike
when they are taller or stronger than you?
Aoba Johsai Private High School
Hey!
Now that you've finally decided to show up,
you should at least announce yourself!
Now, now, now.
Calm down, Yahaba.
Oikawa-san...
It's been a while. I've been waiting for you.
Welcome back, Mad Dog-chan.
Haikyu!!
Wait, who's this Mad Dog?
A second-year named Kyotani Kentaro.
Oikawa-san just decided to call him Mad Dog.
He was pretty famous in
junior high, remember?
Oh, yeah. I remember.
Minamisan Junior High was
strong just that year.
Izumitate               Minamisan Jr. High
He was never a team player,
but his abilities were superb for our grade.
As soon as he joined the club,
he had a chance to be in a practice match...
But he suddenly butted heads
with the third-years.
What he said may have been accurate,
but the way he said it...
The toss is too far from
the net and hard to hit!
You could have totally followed
up on that! You suck!
His attitude toward the
third-years didn't change,
and he eventually stopped showing up.
What the hell?
There are still third-years around?
I thought all of you would have retired
after losing in the Inter-High prelims.
You're as funny as always, Mad Dog-chan.
I wish you'd stop calling me that.
"Ah, I'm so happy I got to play
on the team while Oikawa-san was still here."
I'll make you feel that way.
His natural instincts are making
him cautious around Oikawa-san?
Metropolitan Nekoma High School
So, with the prefectural
qualifier in October,
we'll only be able to go Kanto
two more times, including this trip.
Let's make the best of this chance.
Right!
Hey, Tsukki!
Jump block for me! Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
This chapter is titles, "Boku Gets Rejected
by a Student From Another School."
Yes. Thanks for working with me.
What?!
Why are you so surprised when
you're the one who asked him?
Is there a way to stop an opponent's spike
when they are taller or stronger than you?
What do you think is most
important when blocking?
Height?
It's timing.
To put it simply, if their
hands are above the net,
even a grade-schooler could
stop one of Tanaka's spikes.
What?!
Provided their timing is perfect.
Of course, how you have your hands out,
and reading the course of
the ball is important, too.
But even if I can explain this verbally,
I'm not good enough to actually show you.
Someone nearby with good individual skills
who is a good example when it
comes to blocking
would probably be Kuroo from Nekoma.
Lev!
Timing...
Having the top of the block up
right when your opponent is
about to hit their spike.
I-I'm going to make it through next time!
Hey, Tsukki.
How long are you just gonna watch?
Sorry.
Pardon the intrusion.
Shinzen                  Karasuno
It appears that the quick's
success rate is still about 70%.
All right!
Nothing's going to fix that
except more practice.
Lev! I told you not to block
with your arms spread out!
They got through your block!
Your arms need to be together enough
so the ball won't go through!
Right.
Karasuno    Neighborhood Association
Karasuno General Athletic Park
Indoor Gymnasium
Tokyo Training Camp
Qualifier Matches
Karasuno                 Nekoma
Front! Front!
Sorry!
Got it!
Center!
Hinata!
Out!
Karasuno                 Nekoma
Damn it! Sorry about that!
At long last, we can't let our
guard down around them.
Yeah.
The nights are cold, even in Tokyo.
That's because you didn't put
on a jacket after sweating.
I can't wait for the match!
Yeah...
I've been thinking lately...
What?
You're entertaining, Shoyo,
so I'd like to play a game with you
that's not a practice game.
Huh?
A game where it's immediately
"game over" if you lose.
Let's do it.
A match where there is no rematch.
This is our last chance for the
Battle at the Garbage Dump.
Let's see each other at the Tokyo Gymnasium.
Yeah.
Hey, hey, Tsukki.
You better make sure you beat Ushiwaka.
Why is that?
Because I've had complete victory over you,
so if you have complete
victory over Ushiwaka,
that means I'll have complete-complete
victory over Ushiwaka.
Complete-Complete Victory!!
I'm sorry. I'm not entirely
sure what you mean.
Karasuno Volleyball Club
Then I'll be the best!
Hey, hey, hey!
You make it sound so easy...
Qualifier Matches
Left!
Akaizawa-san!
The receive was off, so the attack can only go left.
The toss is a bit far from the net.
Akaizawa-san is going for the
course that he's best at, a cross.
Right as your opponent
is about to hit the ball,
you complete the block.
Yeah!
Hey! Wrap it up already!
You're really gonna feel this tomorrow.
What? Already?
But I don't feel like I've hit enough.
For crying out loud...
That feeling, that you haven't hit enough...
Why don't you save that for tomorrow?
I see!
Right!
Kageyama! Let's race to see who
can pick up the most balls!
Bring it on!
Good job, Yachi-san.
All right, let's take down the net.
Right!
Qualifier Matches
We're here!
Back at the Sendai Municipal Gymnasium again!
We're gonna get our revenge!
Don't you dare false start, you dumbass!
It's like Hinata and Kageyama
live on spinal reflex alone.
They're like insects.
Johzenji High School
Huh?
That means...
Glasses-chan! Be sure to
tell me your number today!
She's so cute when she gets shy.
Hey!
Stop it!
Ugh... I'm so sorry about that!
Hey, they stopped.
They're stopped in mid-air. That's awesome.
Well, see you in the first match.
So they're...
Johzenji
Karasuno
The team that was at the Inter-High semifinal.
This goes without saying, but...
They're all here.
Right here.
We're gonna beat them all!
They're so hyper.
That just calms us down even more.
I'm well aware...
That the bathroom is where you
run into dangerous people.
Carefully... Carefully...
Whatcha doin'?
Th-The Great King and Seijoh's ace!
I heard you defeated the
2 meter guy. Well done.
Yes! No!
Which is it?
This little shrimp is a
handful during matches,
so why don't we go bury him somewhere now?
P-Pardon me!
Hey!
Ow!
Hinata Shoyo...
And Oikawa and Iwaizumi.
What's with this timing?
Hell if I know.
So this will be your last
tournament in high school.
I wish you well.
You seriously piss me off.
We're going to nationals,
so it's not going to be our last.
Only one team from the
qualifiers can go to nationals.
The fact that he's not
saying that just to be mean
is even more infuriating.
What's going on?
Whoa! It's Shiratorizawa and Seijoh.
Did we just walk in on a tense situation?
Who's the guy in the middle?
It's that one guy!
From the team that beat the
two-meter guy, Karasuno!
It's the #10 from Karasuno!
Is he trying to pick a fight
with Seijoh and Shiratorizawa?
Holy crap!
A-Anyway, Karasuno's going to win... Eek!
U-Um...
Date Tech
I-I'm so sorry!
It doesn't matter who it is.
We'll gladly accept your challenge.
O-Oh, hi.
Go, go, let's go! Let's go, Date Tech!
Rule the Court
Push it, push it, push it, push it, Seijoh!
With Intense Force
Shiratorizawa Academy
Shiratorizawa!
Go, go, let's go! Let's go, Date Tech!
The Iron Wall of Date
The first match has Seijoh on the B Court,
and Shiratorizawa on the A Court.
Karasuno                    Johzenji
We're up next!
Let's go!
Yeah!
All right...
We're gonna play more than anyone else here!
Yahoo!
Wha?
There they are, the party team.
Johzenji!
Curse that playboy from Johzenji!
We're gonna have to switch
to 24-hour surveillance.
We'll protect Kiyoko-san,
even if it means our lives!
Tanaka and Nishinoya are
saying something again...
Episode 15: "Place to Play"
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Place to Play."