The beach!
Take this!
What? You're not swimming?
I don't wanna get sunburned.
Why not?
Nakochi said
that you bought a really cute swimsuit.
Come on, we came all the way out here too...
Oh, I get it!
You don't wanna show anyone other than Tohru, right?
Y-Y-You balut!
I'm never gonna escape that word, am I?
Aren't you two going to swim?
Minchi doesn't wanna get sun-
T-That's so cute!
That's such a waste, Tsurugi.
We didn't travel all this way on this field trip for nothing, you know.
Mind your own business.
Ohana!
Put her in a full nelson!
Roger that!
Now, stand!
Up!
What's your problem?!
Heave-ho!
B-Balut-
Episode 14
This is My Way of Life
Kourin High School
Field Trip Group
Seriously? You're gonna try asking her out again?
Yeah.
I just can't give up on Tsurugi.
I see...
Dear Lord...
Things to learn:
Welcoming the customer upon their arrival
Escorting them to their rooms
Setting a table
Setting a table...
What else...
The correct posture while
answering a customer's questions!
Spirited, aren't you?
We only finished working yesterday.
It's my first time visiting another hot spring inn.
I'm just so excited!
I'm going to learn so much from them!
Thank you! I'll be here all week!
Next up is Ohana!
What?
I haven't heard you sing yet.
That's true!
We've never been to karaoke together.
I wanna hear you sing!
Here.
All right!
I'll sing Grey Heron Romance: Wintry Landscape
Why on earth are you singing enka?
A customer taught me this the other day!
You're so funny, Ohana!
This song goes straight to my heart.
Oh, Mister Grey Heron, why do you cry?
It's bigger than Kissuiso...
Of course it is.
Just look at how many there are of us alone.
Welcome.
Thank you for coming all this way.
Welcome to the Fukuyo Inn.
Thank you.
Please, come this way.
Allow me to show you to your rooms.
This feels so odd...
What?
Usually, I'm the one escorting the customers,
so I'm feeling a little uneasy.
Come on, we're the customers here!
What's with those nails?!
Didn't you read the manual?!
"Employees must have short, trimmed nails
and must not wear any nail polish"!
What? But...
Remove that stuff immediately!
You're also wearing too much make up!
My bad.
You mean "I'm sorry!"
What's the point of him yelling?
I'm glad he's not my boss...
Hey, it's Yosuke!
Yosuke! Howdy!
Yuina?!
It really is you!
What a surprise!
I never imagined that the group
staying here today was from your school!
You're not the only one who's surprised!
Just look at your outfit!
Oh, you mean this?
Last year, I was promoted to head clerk.
But don't get me wrong. I've still got a lot to learn.
Looks like you were born to be the heir of this inn!
I'm so proud of you!
Who the hell is he?
He's calling the princess by her first name!
Y-Yuina!
Sorry, I'll be right there!
Well then, we're in your care, Yosuke!
No problem!
So... who was he?
Yosuke Hiwatari.
A distant relative, and the heir to this inn.
Oh, he's also my fiancé.
I see...
F-
Fiancé?!
Here I go!
Her family runs a long-established, first-class inn.
She's the idol of our class, and has a great body.
She's also got a fiancé.
I'm also... of a Madam...
yet I'm nothing like her...
But the inn your grandmother runs
is in no way inferior to hers.
But that does mean that
in terms of everything else I've just listed, I am inferior.
Hey, check that out!
You're kidding?!
What's going on?
He's probably gonna ask her out.
She has a fiancé.
What's he thinking?
If you like someone,
you shouldn't allow yourself to be asked by anyone else.
Is that because you don't want to make Tohru sad?
I'm not talking about myself here!
Can I talk to you for a sec, Tsurugi?
Hey, look over there!
Is someone gonna ask Tsurugi out too?
I'm heading back to the inn.
Wait, Tsurugi!
No.
I...
My feelings won't change! I like you!
Are you going out with the guy you spoke about last time?!
If you're not, then...
You balut!
What does that mean?!
Does that mean you'll go out with me?!
No!
"Balut" actually means something quite different.
Smelly and...
What was it again?
Huh?
Tsurugi!
Lonely?
Wait!
Stop!
I'm gonna catch you!
No, you won't!
Yes, I will!
They're definitely enjoying their youth...
Ko...
See ya.
A Shijima woman never gets depressed!
I asked him what he liked about me,
and he replied with "Everything."
That's an invalid answer, don't you think?
Oh...
And so, I turned him down!
You seem pretty calm about all this.
What do you mean?
When a guy told me that he liked me,
I drifted off and my heart started beating really fast.
And then, I exploded.
I'm not sure I understand,
but I know what you mean by your heart beating faster.
Hearing someone say they like
you is a good feeling, don't you think?
But don't you have a fiancé?
That's got nothing to do with this.
What?
That's because hearing someone say that to you makes you happy!
Hey, it's Yosuke!
Hey!
I don't really understand you, Yuina.
What?
Why not? I'm kinda hurt!
Your class went to the beach
on the first day, right, Ohana?
I'm so jealous of you.
Where did your class go, Nakochi?
We toured the livestock industry and some ruins.
Sounds exciting...
Not really.
I wanted to swim.
But I'll be swimming tomorrow!
I even brought the swimsuit
I wear in competitions with me!
What happened to Minchi?
Someone asked her out!
You don't need to tell people that!
So, what was your answer?
Don't ask about it!
Looks like everyone from Kissuiso's really close.
Okay, everyone!
Let's dig in!
Gladly!
This is so good!
Yeah!
There are so many of us in here...
Yeah, we never see anything like this at Kissuiso.
Really?
This happens quite frequently at Fukuya.
There's no way we can serve this many customers at our inn!
It'd be midnight before we even finished the place settings!
We probably wouldn't have enough tables and plates...
The kitchen would explode.
They're incredible...
It only took four of them to set up all the tables.
Hello?
Long time.
Don't take calls during your shift!
Hello?
Turn it off!
Never mind, I take it back.
The food was great!
Yeah!
And now, the bath awaits us!
There we go!
You don't need to do that
when you're on a field trip, though...
Well, it eases our minds.
Right?
Yeah.
It's kinda like swimming
freestyle and breathing on your left stroke.
I have no idea what that even means.
I got so sunburned!
Me too!
Oh, no! I forgot my lotion!
You can borrow mine!
I wonder what the bath is like.
I bet it's huge!
It is!
That's as long as it's the same as when I last visited a long time ago.
Oh, right! You're this inn's fiancé!
You can't be engaged to an inn.
I'm so jealous, Yuina!
If I had started studying this as a young child,
I'd be a full-fledged waitress by now!
What?
You want to be a waitress, Ohana?
Yeah!
Huh?
What?
Wait...
Do I?
What are you talking about?
I don't really know either,
but I wanna fest it up,
so I can do my work at the inn properly!
That's how I feel right now.
Oh... "fest it up."
Yes?
You said that to me before.
What does it mean?
Let's see...
It's kinda like wanting to work towards a goal.
Whee!
In that case,
I'll fest it up in the hopes of becoming friends with you!
W-We're not friends?
I wanna become even better friends - fest.
You're using it wrong!
I wanna become even better friends!
Bath.
What was that?
Hurry up and take these dirty plates away!
They're waiting to clean them!
Okay...
Could you move any slower?
Hey! Why are you staring?!
I-I'm sorry!
You're so scary, Yosuke.
Oh, it's you, Yuina!
Yosuke, these are Ohana and Tsurugi.
They work at Kissuiso.
H-Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Kissuiso?
It's an inn in Yunosagi.
Never heard of it.
Mind if we take a look around here?
Not at all. Feel free.
So you carry all the dirty plates around in this?
It's the same as the one we use.
It was installed last year to reduce our labor costs.
It's really made our jobs a lot easier.
It can carry so many plates,
so we only need to employ part-time waitresses who work short hours.
Wow! You're already thinking about the management at such a young age!
Well, yeah.
Oh, that's right, are you free now, Yuina?
Huh? Sure.
Good, let's go outside then.
Hey, I'm leaving the rest to you.
Okay...
Sorry about this, guys.
The moon is really nice tonight...
That head clerk...
I get what you mean, but it's none of your business.
What are you doing?
That's...
Bath.
I'm sure it was around here!
Huh?
Ohana?
Nakochi.
What are you doing here?
Well, I thought you were a kappa...
It's been a while since I've been out on the beach at night!
We used to play out here a lot when we were kids.
We took fireworks with us, remember?
I remember studying the dialect out here!
The Miyazaki dialect!
Yeah, I remember that.
Nankurunaisa!
That's Okinawan dialect!
I wonder if they came out here to swim.
You're probably the only one who would, Nakochi.
I'm amazed.
You've gotten so pretty.
You're pretty handsome yourself in that head clerk outfit.
I've got a lot to learn still.
I need to work a lot harder to make our inn
the best in Japan.
That's a big dream right there.
Hey, I'm also gonna need your help!
"I'm gonna become Yo's wife,
and also the best waitress in Japan!"
Isn't that what you said?
I think I remember that!
Promises made during your childhood
are nice and cute, don't you think?
I really believed that everything I promised
back then would come true!
I plan on making it come true, though.
Along with the dream of
making our inn the best in Japan.
Say, Yuina...
How about coming here after you graduate?
I'll make this inn better than Fukuya.
I'll be the CEO, and you'll be Madam Manager.
Together, we'll make this inn even better!
I'll... be Madam Manager?
I'm going to be working at an inn?
Hey, Yosuke?
Do you like working at an inn?
What do you mean?
Do you?
Well... I guess.
Right.
Huh?
Okay, I better bathe!
See you tomorrow!
Hey! What about your answer?!
I'll save it for a later date!
Jeez...
She's as mysterious as ever.
Do I like working at an inn?
Come in.
What is it?
Do you have a moment?
Have you finished cleaning?
No, not yet.
I need to talk to you about something.
Then, finish cleaning first.
I told you. The schedules are absolute.
I need you to follow the manual I handed you.
I'm in charge of the futons this morning!
Huh?
We're on a field trip, remember?
I could've slept longer...
What should I do until breakfast?
Just go back to sleep.
I'm already awake.
Are you getting up already?
Oh... sorry for waking you.
Employees at an inn wake early, don't they?
So where did you go last night?
I was with a kappa.
Kappa?
Oh... it's nothing.
You're so funny, Ohana!
I'm starving.
Huh?
What's the meaning of this?
We've already decided.
What's wrong, Yosuke?
Yuina.
The part-timers suddenly decided to quit.
What?
You can't just quit on us like that!
It wasn't sudden at all.
I tried to tell the head clerk last night,
but he didn't want to listen.
The head clerk made us do all the work
while he went to chat with his girlfriend.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, it's unbelievable.
I can't work here any more.
I don't really enjoy it.
Really, it's a lot of work for little pay.
Yeah, screw this place.
We don't like the head clerk's attitude either.
Wait!
Spouting all this rubbish...
You can't blame them.
Working in an inn is hard.
People who aren't interested aren't going to keep working.
Even if someone's being paid,
they can't keep doing something they don't like doing.
You can only fest up something you like doing.
Hey, there are lots of things I want to do.
I'm going to pick the one I want to
do the most and make it my career.
Yuina...
Running an inn is not on that list.
This is my answer to the question you asked me last night.
Yuina...
You're right! I've never worked before!
You're more unbelievable than I am!
What? You're the only one, Ohana.
D-Did you bring us any gifts?
Episode 15
Sunny With a Chance of Beans
That's what you're worried about?