Hamu, how's it going?
Hamu?
Yes, sir. This is Hamu. As ordered,
I brought those two here.
Those Drifters appear to be two old men,
but they are in the midst of a heated fight.
Thief! Thief! Why the hell
is this two-bit thief here?!
Who're you calling "two-bit thief"?!
You are the one who should be called that!
Justice lies with the victor.
Shut up! You stole it from me, idiot!
You copied my strategy from Cannae
and used it in Zama, moron!
What are you talking about, you old fool?!
Why don't you show me you can win, then?!
Grrr, why are you talking
like a chosen one, you idiot?!
I didn't steal it, since I won
the war fair and square!
That's why I hate the Romans!
When I go back, I will salt all of Carthage!
When I go back, I will cross
the Alps one more time!
What would you like me to do, Grand Master?
Stop them.
Yes, sir.
The issue is that their intentions...
"The Octobrists"
...are unclear.
We must find out what they are somehow...
...otherwise...
...this world will be destroyed.
"Act 2
Footsteps"
You two, I've told you so many times!
You guys went to that deserted
castle again, didn't you?
I've repeatedly told you not
to get involved with Drifters!
I've warned you about entering the forest,
going to that deserted castle,
and associating with Drifters!
If the lord and his men ever
find out, they will kill you!
But he was dying.
No buts!
Stay away from them, got it?!
Am I understood?!
Damn it! It's before the harvest. Well, let's go!
You've noticed, huh?
What is...
...this smell?
Is this the smell of battle?
There's fire.
They are the "Elves."
There must be bandits or brigands.
The Elves are under attack. I smell the battle.
What are "Elves"?
They are the strange folks
who live beyond the forest.
The ones with long ears who dragged you here.
Hey!
Hey! Wait! Are you going over there?!
I don't know where I am or what's going on!
I don't know if this is a dream or reality!
So, the only thing left for me
is to charge forward!
He's the idiot, not me.
He was dying not long ago.
Is he a human bullet or something?
Are they on the move?
Let's go!
What are they going to do?
What will happen to them?
You're slow, too slow, Nobunaga!
What's wrong with you,
Demon King of the Sixth Heaven?
Shut up! I'm already fifty, you idiot!
How old are you, Lord Toyohisa?
I'm thirty.
"Nineteen"
What's with that smug smile?!
This punk is completely different from the character in the
chronicle of the Genpei War.
He-Help...
Hey, kids!
Leave your head with me! All right?!
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Are you the Drifters in the deserted castle?
I don't understand you. I don't know
what the hell you're talking about.
Speak Japanese.
If you can't speak Japanese...
...you must die!
You two have strange-looking ears.
You two saved my life,
didn't you? Now it's my turn.
"Mutter mutter mutter"
Are you okay with these two?
They can't speak Japanese, either.
Why don't you tell them to "die," too?
"Help!" Repeat after me. "Help!"
Say it! "Help! Help!"
Help, help, help!
Good! That's that, then!
"Rumble rumble rumble"
Way to force the conclusion you want.
I've just witnessed fast-talking
on par with that of the Ikko sect.
They are very well equipped.
They can't be brigands or bandits...
Regular soldiers? Are they the lord's forces?
These idiots. It's like they're
asking me to seize their land.
Okay, now.
Let's claim the village.
"Claim"? Did he actually say, "claim"?
Yes.
Instead of saying "take back,"
or "help them," he said, "claim," right?
That's their nature,
and it's innate and pathological.
It's their most powerful ability.
No. It's the only ability they have.
No matter when or where they live,
they have only one governing principle.
They want to conquer territory.
Line up!
What on earth is going on?
What are you accusing us of?
You entered the forest and
saved a Drifter, didn't you?
Entering the forest, making bows,
and associating with Drifters...
These are all serious crimes for Elves.
Th-That was...
In order to save a dying man, the children...
Children? Is that the reason
you're asking me to overlook this?
You Elves are really disgraceful and insolent.
The administration of Drifters is a job for
magicians of the Octobrist Organization.
It's a serious crime for
demihumans like you to get involved.
Did you think we didn't notice?
Shut up!
First of all, you've been unreasonable!
We wouldn't be able to get firewood
or nuts without entering the forest!
Or even hunt!
You've forced us to work as serfs and
have taken our women away from us.
Now, these children save a
dying man and you call it a crime?!
Are you telling us Elves to die?!
That's right. You all should just die.
If you want to curse at somebody,
put the blame on your ancestors who lost the war.
Someday, Elves, Dwarves, Hobbits,
and all demihuman races will be extinct.
Isn't that right?
Wh-What are you doing?!
I'm just culling your population.
How many shall I take?
I was told I'm allowed to
eliminate up to 50% of you.
Stop!
Take my life instead. Kill me!
No! You're still young.
You have to take care of yourself.
You have a future... as a pathetic serf.
As for your brothers who saved
the Drifter, they're finished.
They started this whole mess.
They're probably corpses by now.
They'll become feed for
the insects of the forest.
It's an emergency!
What's wrong?!
There is a fire in the wheat filed.
What the hell?!
It's before the harvest time!
I'll lose the tax money!
I've been telling you to keep
an eye on it, haven't I?!
You set fire to their field?
Yeah. Those without dignity can
survive if they have food to eat.
Those without food can endure their
hunger as long as they have dignity.
But those who have lost both stop caring
and desperately cling to anything.
That was the tactic the Ikko sect
kept employing against me.
It's the best way to steal a country.
You're a frightening person.
The fire still looks good!
It reminds me of Ise Nagashima.
Our field...
What are you doing?! Put out the fire! Now!
It's impossible. It has spread too far!
What on earth...
Dr... if... ter!
One!
What?!
What the hell just happened?!
H-How could...?!
Two!
Three!
Stop running! I'll kill you!
Four!
That's a commander's head.
You're the commander, right?
You, leave your head here!
That's the head of the commander, huh?
This must be a Drifter.
What the hell is he saying?!
That is... a Drifter!
Brother...!
Brother!
Masha! Mark! You're alive!
That man...
That scary-looking man saved our lives.
That Drifter!
What on earth?!
What are Drifters?
Drifter, are you interfering with me?
How...
How dare you?!
I don't want your head.
Just leave your life here!
I don't know what on earth
you are talking about.
You, a barbarian who can't even speak!
We'll talk with swords!
Come, Drifter!
Aram is not an ordinary soldier.
He is a real knight backed by the magistrate.
Even a Drifter can't...
Indeed! Are you afraid?
Pitiful!
Here we go!
You're pitiful.
The Kumite style anti-armor technique
with the sheath of a sword...
That's nasty!
Wow... scary.
Is it finished?
Yes.
The enemies who were fleeing are no more.
That guy is scary, but so are you.
Well, what is he going to do now?
S-Stop...
Kill him.
Finish him off.
No, kill him. Kill him.
You must put an end to his life.
I don't know where we are or who you are,
but this is the revenge you must take.
This kid is telling you to avenge him!
They can't understand his words,
but they know what he's been telling them.
He is quite something...
Stop! You damn Elves...
Stop! Stop!
Don't you know the consequences...?!
I was wrong... S-Stop!
Help!
Good!
Well done...
All right!
Where the hell were you?
You know I'm still recuperating!
Well, we've been busy with other things.
"Rumble rumble rumble"
Yes, indeed.
Well, well, you must be tired.
Please take a seat.
I was going to sit down,
but I'll let you take my seat.
"Gleam"
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh! I can't believe this!
Grand Master, those guys...
Those guys!
"Shimazu Toyohisa Seizes
Control of Elf Village?!"
You're still wasting your time
struggling, huh, Murasaki?
No matter how hard you try,
no matter how many Drifters you send,
I'm going to win.
No matter how much effort
you make, it's all futile.
Get out of here, Easy.
The wrongs must be righted.
Get lost, Easy. I won't let you have your way.
Pathetic woman.
You're the pathetic one.
If you think you can do it, go ahead and try!
"Black King Commences Southern Invasion"
There's no way your Drifters
could possibly beat my Ends!
This is Semu, this is Semu!
Grand Master, they finally seized the village!
It's dangerous to let them run loose!
I'll bring them there immediately!
No, that won't work. There's no time for that.
Don't bring them here. Don't you come, either.
What?! So then...
Yes. It's begun.
It's already begun!
"Northern Wall"
"Urinary Incontinence"
"Great Escape"
"Act 3
Army of Ours--Sortie at Dawn"