These the massive, hostile creatures
who traverse space-time, known as "DRAGON."
To protect human territory
by intercepting and destroying them
is the task of the Norma at Arzenal.
We Norma are allowed to live in this
world only as weapons that kill DRAGONs.
Let's not forget that as
we give our all to fight them.
Yes, ma'am.
Understand, Ange?
We have a lot of
learning and training to do.
The Empire of Misurugi will
send a release order for me soon.
And once you're ready, you'll serve
the humans as riders and mechanics.
Officer, we're done educating Ange.
We're assigning her to First Troop today.
That will be your purpose in life.
First Troop?!
Zola has already been informed.
Let's go.
Let go.
So that's the princess
everyone's talking about.
The pure-bodied princess...
She sounds sweet and delicious.
You don't care as long it's somebody new, right?
What, are you jealous?
You girls are so cute.
Captain,
take it easy with the skinship.
We get complaints about how hard
you "massage" the newcomers.
Fine, fine. I'll be careful, Deputy Chief.
She's an older newcomer,
but be nice to her, you two.
R-Right.
Hey, Salia, time for a quiz!
Who's going to die first?
It's our job to teach them so they won't die.
Ow, ow! I'm going to die!
Getting along well today, too, I see.
Disobedient Soul
Salute the commander.
You handle the rest, Zola.
Yes, ma'am.
Welcome to the First Troop of death.
I'm Captain Zola.
Deputy Chief, introduce her.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm Deputy Chief Salia.
And this is our assault soldier, Vivian.
What's up?
And Hilda.
Rosalie is our light artillery.
Are these...
Are these all Norma?
"These?"
We Norma are treated as things.
You bitch!
Yep, we're all Norma, just like you.
We'll be good friends, okay?
I am not!
I am the Empire of Misurugi's First Princess,
Angelise Ikaruga Misurugi.
I am in no way a Norma.
But you can't use Mana, right?
Th-The Light of Mana just
doesn't reach this far.
In the State, I assure you...
Damn you, Captain.
You brought us a crazy one!
She's not even aware of her situation.
She's defective.
So the defect is being condescending?
Oh, ouch.
What a burn.
You're the defects!
Know your place,
Burn Princess.
Come on, people, let's leave it there.
What? We need to smack the
delusion out of ugly bitches like her.
Exactly.
Yup.
True, but...
Ange isn't that ugly.
You're always too soft, Ersha.
Salia, you take care of
her. Teach her everything.
That's why the newcomers always act tough.
Yes, ma'am.
Be nice to the promising newcomer, everyone.
We're all Norma here.
All right, we're starting training.
Ersha, Rosalie, Chris...
Come with me.
We'll be doing long-range attack patterns.
Yes.
Salia, Hilda, Vivian,
you're training the newcomer.
Buckle down.
Yes.
Go.
Yes, ma'am.
This way, Ange.
No one may give orders to royalty.
Here, your superiors' orders are absolute.
Got it?
Here's your Rider suit.
Get changed.
That's too scandalous for me.
What's this?
Oh, that's the previous owner. She's dead.
I-I'm wearing a dead person's clothes?
If you want a new one,
you'll have to buy it yourself.
I'd rather be naked than wear that.
Oh?
Ew, what's going on?
She's naked? Seriously?
Open up! Hurry!
You'd rather be naked, wouldn't you?
They're just like the Institute said.
How barbaric and crude and violent!
What are you doing?
Help me, please.
You've never put your own clothes on before?
Man, you're worse than a kid.
My, my, you're swollen red.
It's so tender.
Does it hurt? Does it?
It does, doesn't it?
You smell like alcohol, Maggy.
Jasmine, how's it going?
The outside bolts are all wrecked.
I'll replace them with ones
from the Empire of Misurugi.
It'll cost a bit more, though.
Let command pay for it.
Why, thank you.
Couldn't you be a bit more careful with it?
It's not as durable as you are.
Sorry. That bitch got unruly.
The princess?
Is it really a good idea
to put her in First Troop?
If not, she dies. That's all.
Para-mail destroyer mode
simulator initializing.
Plenum chamber charging.
Plenum chamber charge complete.
Release arresting gear.
Arresting gear release complete.
This is the main throttle.
This is the indicator.
Just what is this?
A Para-mail simulator.
Para-mail?
Coffins, for us Norma.
I don't expect you to be able
to do this on your first try.
First, you need to get
a good feel for flying.
Requesting lift-off.
Coco, request confirmed.
Beginning lift-off.
Miranda, confirmed.
Just what do you expect me to do?
Ange, confirmed.
Mission 07, start.
What is this?
Don't let go of the controls.
Climb!
Turn!
Look ahead.
Real battle is worse than this.
On to nosedive training.
Begin nosedive.
You're going to hit the ground.
Nose up!
This feeling—
Hurry, Ange!
I knew it, this sensation—
Ange!
I knew it.
Iaria!
What's up with this kid?
The Princess was impressive.
She didn't wet herself
on her first simulation.
Right, Rosalie?
Ah, my first time was, well...
Sounds like you like her.
Yeah, she's not bad.
Hey, Salia, what is Ange?
She's so much fun.
This is your room.
You can have it to yourself
until we have new soldiers.
Buy what you need with this.
Roll call is at 5 tomorrow morning.
Onee-sama.
Mother, Sylvia.
Momoka, ready my horse.
Momo—
It's cold, Momoka.
That newcomer—
Her basic fitness, her reflexes,
her combat adaptability,
her understanding of military theory—
She's above average in all areas.
She's impressive.
For a Norma, that is.
Noteworthy Para-mail piloting ability, huh?
You're keeping it again?
I want to keep some for later.
It's just pudding. You're such a kid, Coco.
You aren't my older sister.
My, my, the Burn Princess.
Oh, dear. You're so good at everything,
but you're picky about food.
That's not good.
You better eat up,
or you won't be able to fight.
Nope, not good.
How can you eat that stuff?
Oh, is it not good enough
for you, Burn Princess?
Get off your high horse.
You—
Stop, Rosalie.
Here's a warning, Burn Princess.
This isn't the world you came from.
You better figure that
out quick, or you'll die.
U-Um...
...would you like this?
Oh, so you didn't remember my name.
I'm Miranda.
This is Coco.
Come on, this is your
chance to get to know her.
B-But—
She's infatuated with you.
But Ange-san's so amazing.
You're fast, and strong, and pretty.
She can do everything.
I thought princesses were
only in fairy tales.
Well, we're all new soldiers.
Let's stick together, okay, Ange?
Ask me if there's anything you don't know.
Then—
Thanks for the business.
Here, and the change.
You can get more cash by
making military gains.
So how did you shop outside?
I got everything I wanted.
I could have anything I wanted,
and I could be anyone I wanted to.
There's no inequality,
violence, or discrimination.
Nothing bad ever happens.
That's our Mana-filled world.
So there really is a magic nation.
Thank you.
Well then.
U-Um...
See you tomorrow, Ange-sama.
It's Angelise.
Okay, Angelise-sama.
What's wrong, finished already?
Please, let me rest a little.
Pathetic.
Where're you going?
I'm not satisfied.
It's an invocation of my
entitlements as royalty,
and a petition for my immediate release.
Please have this delivered
to the heads of all states.
Right away.
You still don't get it?
What a problem, you are.
She's so thick-headed.
She's been poorly educated, Zola.
I apologize, Commander.
You'll do.
I'll be borrowing the room.
Approved.
Let go of me.
Yes, Arzenal Command.
You won't survive in the field
if you don't understand your situation.
I am returning to the Empire!
If I can't tell you,
I'll have to teach your body.
Submit, and I'll teach you
pleasures you've never known.
Good, good. That's how Norma have to be.
I-I am not a Norma.
Lose an eye, lose an arm,
and the will to fight still runs through you.
That's us, the Norma.
Hitting me gets you excited.
That's not it.
This brings back memories.
You were sick of it, too, weren't you?
Of that hypocritical, shallow world.
No.
Stop.
It was just getting good!
This is the real deal, Ange.
Connect all power.
Arquebus, Glaive, start engines.
Hauser, hurry up and load weapons.
Type-1 encounter alert.
You're on the one in
the back, at the far left.
Singular opening expected
at south by southeast, 4400.
One Brig-class enemy signature detected.
Go!
No further details available,
due to lack of response.
Para-mail First Troop,
respond as appropriate upon contact.
First Troop, acknowledged.
Okay, little girls, it's your first battle.
You're providing support from the rear.
Don't break formation.
Stay calm and respond as necessary.
Do as you were taught, and you won't die.
Yes, ma'am.
Is this that—
All units, ready for liftoff.
Air traffic controllers evacuating deck.
Runway clear. Ready for lift-off.
Zola Squadron, sortie!
Reactor internal temperature,
two million Kelvins.
Igniting plenum chambers.
Air traffic controller evacuation confirmed.
Expand barriers immediately.
Zola Squadron, Salia, liftoff.
Salia, liftoff complete.
Ignite reheat system.
Ange, liftoff complete.
All First Troop units,
ascend to engagement altitude.
How do you like the real Para-mail?
Don't get shaken off.
Yes.
All units, maintain altitude at 1200.
I'm outside.
Distance to the Singular is 10,000.
All right, all units prepare for battle.
Assume formation.
Yes, ma'am.
Take position, Ange.
Ange's breaking away.
Breaking away?
We're almost at the battle zone!
Come back!
Ange!
My name is Angelise Ikaruga Misurugi.
I am returning to where I belong,
in the Empire of Misurugi.
I warned you.
You'll be shot if you disobey orders.
Angelise-sama!
Angelise-sama, take me with you.
What are you talking about, Coco?
Take me to the magic country!
The Singular is opening.
We've lost Coco.
DRAGONs have made contact.
What is this?
What the hell is this?
Next Episode Preview
This week's story was terrible, too!
The food's awful, the rooms are dirty,
I lost my first kiss...
Why do I have to go through all this?
Isn't this a bishoujo robot anime?
Villkiss Awakens
Be nice to me! I'm a bishoujo!