Okay! Let's adjust the suspension.
Good work.
With this, the interlocking is complete.
I appreciate this.
Anyway, you've got an incredible fleet here.
Thank you for informing us about the pirates.
You're welcome here.
Thanks.
I know we're in good hands.
Fleet Commander, the interlocking
process is complete.
Good. And what about him?
Actually...
The Flute of Recollection
Alright! Tighten the wire!
Chief! That's in the way! Move it!
Hey! You don't just set it down
wherever you feel like it!
Where... to move it?
Over there!
See? By the other cargo!
Okay. Move it over there.
Roger.
W-What the...?!
I told you not to fly!
C-Chamber!
Hey, are you alright?!
Idiot! Don't cut that rope!
Hey! Can you get yourself out of this?
We haven't decided how to handle
your right of residence yet.
So if you don't mind, please use
this area as your quarters for now.
Here?!
Is there a problem with it?
This place is a dump!
This... is fine.
Chamber... nearby. Convenient.
That's all you care about?
No problem...
And one more thing. Here's your invoice.
In...voice?
A demand to pay for damages incurred
to the hangar while rendering service.
Wait a second, Ridget! Ledo is the
one who drove the pirates away!
The destruction of the hangar
has nothing to do with that.
But Ledo just got here!
He doesn't know the rules!
We're exempting him from electricity
expended while staying here, water fee,
and the freight charge of hauling
this oversized cargo around.
So it's not just a one-sided deal.
Ledo! Are you okay with this?
Query: What is the specific
nature of this "deal"?
Hey! This Yunboro's in the way!
Move... where?
For cryin' out loud... Get the next load.
Put it in the same place as before!
Chamber, move it over there.
Roger.
Stop flying, dammit!
That's an impressive Yunboro...
Does it understand when other
people besides you talk to it?
Understands...
Could it do what I say?
Based on the allowable
scope of military protocol,
it is possible to transfer command authority.
In other words...?
Possible...
I see. Alright...
Chief! I got a good idea!
Alright! Good enough.
Delivery for you!
Thanks.
He's working hard...
Huh?
What the hell's his deal? He makes the tin
can do all the work while he slacks off!
I wonder what happened...
That's a dimwit if I ever saw one! Like I
said before, he should just be deep-sixed...
He might be just taking a break, right?!
That's the way to do it!
I fail to see any meaning in your behavior.
It's nothing more than a meditation tool.
Still, hot as it is, they're
sure wasting a lot of energy.
There's no discipline at all here.
What's their instructor doing?
Conjecture: Children's drills
here do not have an instructor.
Then how can they be raised as
productive members of society?
Query: What is the next order?
Hold on!
I'm first!
No fair!
Say something!
Fly up to the sky!
Obstructions prevent completion of duties.
Query: Permission to clear them away?
Granted. But take care not to hurt anyone.
Roger.
Ledo!
How's it going?
Standing by...
"Standing by"? Oh...
What's that? Are you making something?
I... don't know.
You're making something but you don't
know what it is? How strange.
That's an unusual material.
Hideauze nail. No have... on this planet?
It's so beautiful!
If you want... I give.
Are you sure?
Say, would you like to take
a little walk with me?
This'll be a great souvenir
for my little brother.
Little... brother?
Uh-huh. His name's Bebel. He's
really good working with his hands.
What does "little brother" mean?
"Little brother" is a brother
who's younger than you...
Um... in your family...
Fam...ily...?
In ancient society,
that label was applied to societal units
comprised of mates and blood relations.
They had that custom?
You don't have a family, Ledo?
Inefficient. Unnecessary.
Inefficient...?
It sounds like you lived
in a rough place, Ledo.
Bebel wants to ask you about space.
About... space?
Yep. He's really interested in the stars and
vehicles you use to travel through space.
But his body is weak, so he
can't walk around as he likes.
Body... is weak?
He's got like a disease... in the chest.
In the Galactic Alliance, frail humans
are eliminated and disposed of.
Humans who cannot participate
in battle are useless.
Useless! That's... Ledo,
were you okay with that?
Don't... understand... question.
I see...
Will I be able to gain useful
information by talking to that person?
Information?
In that case, why not meet Dr. Oldham?
Old...ham...?
He's a doctor, but people
call him "the Sage".
He's the smartest person in all of Gargantia.
Over here!
Hello! Dr. Oldham!
Amy!
Doctor, Amy's here!
Hello.
Doctor...
Hi, Amy.
I brought someone here today.
Could it be that you're Ledo?
He says he's got something
to ask you, Doctor.
Well, I've still got work
to do, so I'm taking off.
You're busy, huh?
Ledo, I'll come by to pick you
up later, so wait downstairs.
I would like you to provide information.
I've heard the rumors,
but is that the voice of the
machine that can understand words?
That... is correct.
Lost technology. I never imagined I'd be
able to lay my eyes on the real thing...
Can I... ask question?
Of course, although I'm not sure I'll know the answer.
Please, sit.
What do you want to ask?
I would ask about how to return
to the Galactic Alliance.
I'm afraid I don't possess any
knowledge pertaining to that subject.
As you can see, we've lost the
majority of ancient wisdom.
Particularly regarding the technology
of traveling to the stars...
Currently, this is the knowledge of
the heavens that's been left to us.
I doubt this is what you're looking for...
I apologize for being of no help.
It... can't be helped.
Can I ask... one more question?
Certainly, go right ahead.
I would ask for your explanation
of the structure of this fleet.
Explanation?
This fleet is inefficient.
The chain of command and training
of children are defective,
while the behavior of the
citizenry is disorganized.
And I cannot comprehend the
purpose of caring for the weak.
I see. So that's how it looks
to a visitor from the stars.
I beg your pardon.
This efficiency that you speak
of has a rather narrow range.
Let's see... I think you should meet Bebel.
Will I attain any useful information
by conversing with that person?
Whether it's useful or not
is up to you to decide.
I see. So even the doctor didn't know...
Bebel! I'm home!
Welcome back, Sis.
He's Ledo?
He really is your friend, Sis!
You're awesome, Sis!
Nice to meet you. I'm Bebel.
Nice to... meet you.
This is Amy's "little brother"?
Sit down, if you'd like.
Ledo said he wanted to meet you, Bebel!
Really?
That's... right.
I would like you to provide information.
Is that...
Uh-huh! This is Chamber's
communications device.
Wow! It really can talk!
Chamber...
I am an artificial intelligence
created to aid my pilot.
Cool! You understand Earth language, too!
Amy, are you in there?!
We don't have enough people,
so we need your help...
Oh?
Huh? The hottie?!
Already inviting him home?
It's not like that!
Sorry, I have to work again.
See you later.
Just when it was getting good...
When what was getting good?
I told you, it's nothing like that!
Well, Bebel, take care of Ledo, okay?
Don't be in such a rush that you trip!
I know...!
Amy!
Sorry, my sister never stops moving.
I... don't mind.
Ledo, are you really from space?
I've always wondered!
What's life like in space?
With the Galactic Alliance, the main
mission is fighting the Hideauze.
Hideauze...?
An alien life-form that threatens
the existence of the human race.
Have you always been fighting them?
The war has been going on since the
formation of the Galactic Alliance.
Wow...
It must be totally different
from how life is here.
Doesn't it wear you out?
The only exhausted people are dead.
Dead... I see. It's rough, huh?
Are you used to things here?
I cannot comprehend the organizational
structure of Gargantia.
Organization?
Query: What is the reason for running such
an inefficient and useless operation?
The fleet isn't an organization.
It's just everyone coming together.
Sometimes we fight, sometimes help each
other... And that's just how we live.
Query: What is the significance of that?
As long as everyone can live free
of worry, that's all that matters.
The answer is unclear.
The behavioral objective of the human race
is subjugating the enemy, the Hideauze.
Without that, the human race
has no stable development.
Really?
Humans like you are culled immediately
by the Galactic Alliance.
Culled...
But if that's the case, what would
become of the Galactic Alliance
if the Hideauze are beaten completely?
What are you going to do, Ledo?
I would stand by until I
receive further instructions.
Then what if those instructions don't come?
I will just continue to stand by.
Then you're the same as us, huh?
Same?
After all, "standing by" means
continuing to live, right?
Ledo, I heard Joe took your Yunboro away?
It's a shame, the hero being sidelined.
Ledo?
Query: Are my actions beneficial?
Yours, Ledo?
You routed the pirates, remember?
Right now, all I am doing
is observing Chamber.
You're just not used to it here.
I am unable to determine
my own course of action.
Course of action, huh?
First of all, why don't you knock off
that kind of military-style thinking?
Knock... off?
That's right. Be more flexible with...
Rain!
Collect the rain!
What is this?! What's happening?!
Weather phenomena. It is not poisonous.
This is an emergency situation!
Have your Yunboro gather the rain!
Fresh water is precious!
What... should I do?
There's a tarp over there! Spread
it out to collect the water!
Chamber!
Roger!
Right! Just like that!
There is a change in your brainwaves.
I'm just wondering about how
our side is doing in the war.
Given the present circumstances,
such consideration is meaningless.
I know.
I spy the handsome guy!
He really is good-looking...
But I kind of feel sorry for him, all
alone in a place he knows nothing about...
I can tell, he'll be fine!
Right?
You're worried about him,
aren't you?! Get over there!
Ledo...
You're soaked. You're gonna catch a cold.
Dry off at my place.
Sure seems like it was some squall.
That was my first observation
of concentrated rain.
Is there rain in space, too?
No.
Are there oceans?
And people who are sick, like me...
Do not exist.
But I don't think of myself as unnecessary.
I...
I have my big sister.
Amy?
My sister needs me.
Somebody must need you, too, Ledo. That's
why you've been able to survive all this time.
In the war, only those who can be
of service are needed to survive.
Then what about the opposite? Isn't
there someone whom you need, Ledo?
My sister and I need each other.
And more than anything, I need myself.
That's why I'm alive.
I...
To the Alliance, a useful existence
has no attachment to survival.
Then what was this to you, Ledo?
That...
Sis told me you were making it,
but didn't know what it was.
This has to be a flute, right?
It's not necessary at all for war.
Flu...te...?
Yeah. It can produce a sound.
Ledo, what's wrong?
You're crying.
This is...
Did I say something wrong?
No! I... don't know...
Why...?
You must have recalled something sad.
Oh... really?
Bebel...
What?
I... want that... one more time...
Of course!
I made some tea!
Saaya's recommendation. It's good!
Chamber, you still don't
know our coordinates?
Lack of observational data.
More time is necessary.
I see...
It looks like I need to learn a
little more about this planet.
Unnecessary. Eventually, you
will rejoin the main unit.
Yeah. I know.