Manatsu-kun will be staying in the
hospital for a few more days.
I'm fine now.
You hit your head...
You still have more tests.
You should have them check you out thoroughly.
Pitz says so, too.
You know animals aren't allowed
in the medical center...
Akari taught me a magic spell to
make you feel better, Daichi!
You don't mean...
Don't, don't, don't—
Belly Button Forte!
D-Don't do that! Hide it!
Restraint! Restraint!
You don't feel better?
No... When you're wearing a dress,
Belly Button Forte is more of an
offensive spell than a healing one.
Yes, this is Shibuya.
Yes, he's here.
Yes. That's fine.
Yes, understood.
Teppei, Commander Nishikubo
wants to see you.
Right.
I hope we can all live together again!
And make dinner and stuff!
Y-You're right.
It was only a little while ago,
but it seems like the distant past.
Right now, it feels so far away from me.
Hana...
Did I do something bad to you?
Thanks to you, I found out who I really am,
something I had wondered for so long.
Did you know the Machine Goodfellows
operated off of Orgone energy?
Pitz told me.
Didn't you think I might be your enemy?
Nope.
I knew you would save Daichi.
Next time I return to the Kiltgang,
I might turn into a different person.
Teppei?
Don't have so much faith in me.
Teppei!
Speed is of the essence.
Registration code 10878F.
This is one of the members selected
to participate in the Kivotos Plan,
currently in cold sleep in
the Tenkaidou's Ark block.
They are attempting to capture him.
We want you to protect him.
I've decided you are appropriate for this mission
due to your combat training.
Who is he?
He is a prisoner undergoing sentencing
for assault and attempted murder.
A prisoner is a Kivotos Plan member?
Well...
His genes appear to have been
the reason for his selection.
His name is Eiji Arashi.
"Arashi"?
He's the one who gave you,
a designer child, your genes.
You might say he's your father.
Is this mission being undertaken in
conjunction with the Tenkaidou?
That should mean there's no
need for me to go to space.
I've decided not to give headquarters the
information about you and the Kiltgang.
You understand what that means, right?
In other words, it's a top secret mission, correct?
Starry Sky's Picture Book
This is the Red Papillon.
I will reach the Tenkaidou in fifteen minutes.
This is Tanegashima. Roger.
Are you sure it's okay for
Akari-chan to come along?
It's a dangerous mission.
Getting permission to capture one of the
Kivotos Plan sleepers would be difficult.
Especially with a commander
who belongs to the Intercept Faction,
which opposes the Ark Faction.
If they're going to resort to
violent, illegal measures,
we'll have to take the initiative and capture him.
And for that, we need a reason to
send Teppei to the Tenkaidou.
So you invented a reason about
Akari-chan wanting to see her mother?
It's quite logical.
I'm amazed she didn't get mad,
being used for a mission like that.
She thought it was funny.
Maybe she really did want to see her mother.
Well, she's her daughter, after all.
But aren't they going after Eiji Arashi
because after the last battle, they began to suspect
the relationship between Teppei and the Kiltgang?
Teppei is quarantined at this base,
so they can't touch him.
That's why they're going after
his gene donor, Eiji, right?
And we're sending Teppei
straight into the middle of it.
And that isn't logical at all.
But...
You have a plan, right?
Well, at this point, we're all in this together.
I'm sorry.
Red Papillon is about to rendezvous
with the Tenkaidou.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I'm so glad you came!
How rich do you have to be to travel
into orbit just to see your mom?
Well, Governor Yomatsuri hasn't been
down to the surface in years...
They probably made an exception.
You've really grown up.
Well, yeah.
I was so happy that you said
you wanted to see me.
Parents...
This seems kind of strange to me.
That young pilot is kind of cute.
Hey, now...
I hope we'll have some time to talk later.
Hey, there was another shuttle at the dock.
Where'd it come from?
That's the regular supply shuttle.
Regular?
There are twenty-five containers.
We've brought them all aboard.
Container loading confirmed.
Thank you.
Yo.
Time for work, huh?
I'll help you.
You don't want to talk to your mother?
This seems more interesting.
And...
If you're going to use this, you need me!
The corridor to the Kivotos Plan cold sleep
block, also known as the Ark block,
is protected by dozens of bulkheads.
On the outside, it's a long-distance
spaceflight staffed by volunteers.
But in reality, it's a secret plan for
carefully chosen elites to escape Earth.
If this got out, there could be panic and rioting.
Supposedly, my mom's requested that
I be in the third group of sleepers.
The Ark Faction thinks anyone who
stays on Earth will be destroyed.
They're too pessimistic.
I'm definitely with the Intercept Faction.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Some of this sector's alarms have been shut off.
Someone else sneaked in.
I think spies sneaked in from
the supply shuttle at the dock.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm here, we have the advantage.
Logical, logical... Open sesame!
Let's hurry.
Hey, how much do you know...
You can call me Akari, Teppei.
How much do you know
about this mission, Akari?
If you mean that the target was your gene donor,
they didn't tell me, but I know.
You learned it all through hacking?
Well, yes, but...
When I looked at you,
I suddenly wanted to meet this person.
Number 10801F to number 10900F.
This is it.
It's finally time.
Teppei...
Number 10878F.
I'm unloading it.
This man is my gene donor?
He looks more like a boy than a man...
This is bad...
They've entered the area.
That was faster than I expected.
They'll be here before we can wake him.
Doesn't this sector have emergency blast doors?
Yeah.
Can you close them without triggering the alarm?
It's impossible...
For normal people.
Leave it to the magical girl!
We'll use the time to wake him, and take him
through the emergency hatch in the back.
Calm down.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
This is not part of the
original Kivotos Plan program.
You've been awakened early for another reason.
Do you feel all right?
I'll ask again.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
You're Teppei, aren't you?
How do you know my name?
I gave it to you.
I could tell with one look.
Damn, you've grown up.
We have to hurry.
They'll unlock the door soon.
Am I the target?
You seem to be a good hacker, miss.
Give me a line in, and I can do anything!
After all, I'm a magical girl!
That's wonderful.
The target's gone.
Looks like someone got here before us.
Come to think of it, there was a
Tanegashima shuttle here, too.
I can't believe they beat us.
I hope that'll get them off our trail.
I'm impressed you came up with this.
Sorry to bother you.
Okay, let's go.
Wait!
Thanks.
Sure...
Is she your girlfriend?
No, she isn't.
At your age, your mom and
dad were already in love.
My "dad"...
By the way...
What is a "dad"?
I don't have a dad.
An ambush, huh?
Just one, I think.
I'm amazed you could tell.
Do you have any weapons?
This is a tranquilizer gun.
Okay.
Guess we'll use that... and these.
Empty spacesuits?
Are you okay?
Thanks.
There's a high probability that
they know where we are now.
Staying here is dangerous.
Let's look for spacesuits.
You're going outside?
The external hatches aren't
electronically controlled.
You need a key.
Here it is.
Plastic explosives?
We can use it to go outside, reach
the dock, and steal their shuttle.
But we have our own shuttle.
Given the nature of their operation,
their shuttle will be ready to
leave at a moment's notice.
Stealing it will be faster.
With your magic, we can take over
their navigation system, right?
That's crazy!
Do as your dad says.
Trouble with bulkhead 1883.
What?
What's this?
What's wrong?
That's their shuttle.
He's definitely armed.
What?
Hey, Teppei, your dad—
Listen.
Would you stop calling yourself that?
I don't know what you may think,
but I don't see you that way.
And it isn't like that.
I'm not who you think I am.
I'm sorry...
I didn't even get to read you a single picture book.
I really regret it.
That isn't what I'm talking about!
My tranquilizer gun?
When did you...
Teppei!
Why?
Aren't we stealing the shuttle?
I'm sorry.
I lied.
That shot wounded me worse than I thought.
I can't protect you two.
They're pros...
I can tell they're a lot like me.
But they're after me, so if I
surrender, you'll both be safe.
Of course, if they're after my genes,
their real target would be Teppei, right?
I don't know why Teppei was sent here.
But maybe someone wanted him to see me?
Either way, I'm sure it was
something the adults wanted.
But if a girl like you is with him,
I don't need to worry.
Take care of my son.
Teppei's dad...
I like the way that sounds.
You don't have to worry about me.
After all, I'm a criminal.
His assault and attempted murder
were both to protect Teppei.
He tried to stop Teppei, his child,
from being used as a test subject
by Macbeth Enterprises.
Was having Teppei meet him your true goal?
You really are a romantic.
This was Commander Nishikubo's order?
I lied to you for the sake of the mission.
I'm really sorry.
Whatever your reason,
I'm sure you can't imagine
how happy I was to see you.
When she looks at you,
Governor Yomatsuri seems so kind.
Ah... I'm sorry.
That was a weird thing to say.
He looked at you the same way
that my mom looks at me.
It seems the group that kidnapped the
target was under Salty Dog's influence.
They've denied it, of course.
I'm sorry.
The mission was a failure.
Ultimately, it all worked out.
Once the shuttle arrived, Eiji Arashi escaped.
His whereabouts are currently unknown.
Good work.
Get some rest.
I'm sorry...
I didn't even get to read you a single picture book.
My dad, huh?
The Kivotos Plan was proposed as the
last hope for the survival of humanity.
But many conspiracies lurk in the background.
And Hirosue, from Salty Dog,
tries to kidnap Hana for the Kivotos Plan.
Next time, on episode 6 of Captain Earth:
Kivotos Plan
Kivotos Plan.
Earth Engine, expand!