FIVE YEARS AGO
REVOCS CORPORATION BUSINESS
STRATEGY WORKFRAME
The Revocs Corporation.
They account for 70% of global
apparel industry sales.
STOCK RATING
That's amazing...
Oh, it's a company that's part
of the Kiryuin conglomerate.
Now I get it. That's interesting.
But one genius is going to alter
the destiny of that company...
MIDDLE SCHOOL THIRD YEAR
STUDENT HOUKA INUMUTA
Uh-oh, their stocks are in
a freefall! How terrible!
Crap! I've been found out?!
How'd they manage to pinpoint
my location so quickly?!
Not so much as a warning?!
I'm sorry! What I did was wrong!
It was a middle-school
scamp's harmless prank!
Please forgive me!
No leniency? Dude, seriously?
A middle-schooler you may be,
but you have trespassed into
territory you shouldn't have.
A girl?
Then again, you are a man
who can breach the tightest
security in the world and illegally
access the Revocs site.
Calling yourself a middle-school
scamp at this point is pushing it.
So you're the big boss, huh?
Why did you do this?
The fact that it's the tightest
security in the world
makes it worth tackling.
- How limited.
- What?
If you're changing the system
anyway, don't you think you
should alter the real world's system
itself, not the virtual one?
ADMISSION PERMIT HONNOUJI
ACADEMY HIGH SCHOOL
Honnouji Academy High School?
That is the place where you will
change the world, Houka Inumuta.
EPISODE 10
I WANT TO KNOW MORE ABOUT YOU
The second of the Elite Four...
Quit pushing! Quit your damn pushing!
Sheesh, whose TV do you think this is?!
Look at this crowd!
Nobody'd notice if I walked
off with a nice set!
Mataro, I'm going to knock you out.
I'm sorry... Sorry...
Is Ryuko gonna be okay?
If I was allowed to be her assistant,
I'd be right there looking after her!
G-Gamagoori! And you're half-naked!
Don't be afraid, Mankanshoku.
I am now a No-Star,
the same rank as you.
To observe this battle, it is
only fitting that I do so from
these spectator seats where
the No-Stars are gathered.
Lady Satsuki, Ira Gamagoori will
surely work his way back
up from this shame!
I won't allow your kindness
towards me to be in vain!
Oh, I get it!
You want to fight me right
here and now, right?
I'm cheering on Ryuko
with all I've got,
so I won't let anyone
interfere, not even you!
How amusing!
Even with you cheering her on,
Lady Satsuki's stronghold
won't budge one iota!
But it did budge! You lost, remember?
Inumuta, win!
Trounce her thoroughly and utterly!
Ryuko, take him out!
- You can do it!
- You hear me, Inumuta?!
Time to hit the noise canceller...
I'm not interested in hearing
a beaten dog yap away.
Now she's showing mercy
to the vanquished.
What's our mighty queen up to?
You have doubts about Lady Satsuki?
Honestly, ever since
you lost your sight,
that obnoxious intuition of yours has
gotten even sharper, Mr. Wild Monkey.
If you doubt her, it's your own
footing that will become unsure.
I hate to break it to you,
but I have a different relationship
to her than the rest of you.
That Kamui transformation
was most fascinating,
but you overexerted yourself in your
fight against Gamagoori,
don't you think?
You are breathing heavily, and
your heart rate is elevated.
Don't you worry about me.
Let's get this started!
Round Two... begin.
SECOND BATTLE
BEGIN FIGHTING
Understood.
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM PROBE REGALIA
Three-Star Goku Uniform: Probe Regalia.
"Probe Regalia," huh?
Seems more restrained than the others...
And yet, it makes me uneasy.
As if I am being stripped naked.
Figures, he is their intel chief.
We don't know what his deal
is, so let's be careful.
Life Fiber Synchronize, Kamui Senketsu!
So, she's starting off with Stage
1, her standard combat mode, eh?
Ah, I see.
She's even faster than I predicted?
I know your type.
You guys are always spouting crap like,
"I've analyzed all your capabilities"
or "I can anticipate all your moves!"
There's only one way to
beat somebody like you:
To be reckless!
I see.
That's why you exerted yourself
right away and boosted
your reaction speed
higher than I predicted.
Boosting your Life Fiber link
through force of will, eh?
The methodology is the same
as that of the Goku Uniforms,
but, given that yours is 100% Life
Fibers, its effect is that much greater.
But I wonder, how long can
your body keep this up?
It ain't about if I can or
not, I will make it last.
I expect nothing less from Ryuko Matoi!
Why is it that the human
body can move like that
simply by putting on clothing
made of Life Fibers?
Show me the reason why
with your actions!
What the?!
He vanished?!
He disappeared!
When Houka Inumuta's
Goku Uniform shines,
white butterflies flutter and
come to rest on a snowman.
He did not vanish!
OPTICAL CAMOUFLAGE
This is optical camouflage!
Nuh-uh! There's no
butterflies in winter!
They die when it snows!
I should have known, Mankanshoku.
You totally missed the point.
When it comes to haphazard attacks,
the most effective thing
to do is dodge them.
What's more, if the target
is counterattacked,
the psychological damage
is all the greater.
There's nowhere to run!
If I can only gather
obvious data like this,
I'll be very disappointed!
Senketsu, time for Plan #2!
Get Really Reckless!
Understood!
Eat this!
What?
That eye is totally huge!
If I can't see where you are,
I'll just have to attack
everywhere at the same time!
EVASION IMPOSSIBLE
E-Evasion...
...impossible!
I can see him!
Oh, dear. It looks like
the shock of that attack
has wrecked that hide-and-seek
ability of his.
That's what happens when
you rely on your eyes.
Yeah, just like a certain somebody!
See that?
Make a crazy attack even
crazier, and it'll hit.
Let's do it, Senketsu!
Your blood is boiling
even hotter than usual.
Yeah, 'cause I can't stop here!
DOES NOT COMPUTE
I'm at at the limits of
my processing capacity?
Houka Inumuta hereby
forfeits this battle!
FORFEIT
What are you up to?
If I continue fighting, the data I've
gathered so far would be damaged.
Say what?
What I want is data.
Not victory.
That data-lover is
grandstanding again...
Still, Lady Satsuki is allowing it.
Jakuzure. Prepare for battle.
What's the matter?
What are you so flustered about?
I thought you two went back further
than any of the rest of us.
Oh, shut up!
Hey! I'm the one who's
going to fight next!
I know that.
But I have to go break in my Three-Star
Goku Uniform: Blade Regalia MKII.
What are you saying?!
You're assuming that I'm
gonna lose?! Nobody mocks me!
She's cleared the second one, too...
That's way better than
I expected, but still...
10 MINUTES / $1
A dollar per 10 minutes?!
Where do you get off, mac?!
The electricity to run those
TV's ain't free, you know!
You're gonna pay for it!
- You greedy old fart!
- What the hell, man?!
Yes, yes!
You don't like it, go somewhere else.
Don't mess with us, you senile old fart!
Son! Come here, boy!
We'll pay, we'll pay!
10 MINUTES / $1
You're here, too, Inumuta?!
I'm just like you.
I'm going to observe
the fight from here.
I won't broach the topic
of you forfeiting.
The way each man fights
is his own path to choose.
But Inumuta, why are you
wearing a tracksuit?!
Have you no shame?!
The loser is stripped
of his Goku Uniform.
Still, I don't recall there being
a rule about having to go naked.
Surely it's more important
to know the rules
than it is to know shame, Mr.
Disciplinary Committee Chair.
Oh, my apologies! Former
Disciplinary Chair!
Thank you for your kind advice,
Former Information and
Strategy Committee Chair.
What's with all this tension?
The spectator seats have turned
into a battleground, too!
Fine, I'm not gonna lose,
either! Go for it, Mako!
Stand strong, Mako Mankanshoku!
Hooray! Hooray!
Your friend has finally
started cheering for herself.
It sure look that way.
Still, that's classic Mako.
Your pulse and respiration
have returned to normal.
So, she's the key to
getting you to relax?
Entrance march! Under the Double Eagle!
What the hell?
She knows how to make a cheery entrance.
Sorry for the wait, transfer student.
This won't be like the clumsy fights
you've had with those boys so far.
Prepare to be pummeled cheerfully,
jauntily, and utterly one-sidedly!
Three-Star Goku Uniform:
Symphony Regalia Grave!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
SYMPHONY REGALIA GRAVE
That's huge! On what planet
is that a uniform?!
I can get a better sound this way.
Okay, for my first song,
Light Cavalry Overture!
She's gonna fight while playing music?
It's so loud it's hard to do anything...
We can't have that, can we?
Let's do it! Life Fiber
Synchronize, Kamui Senketsu!
Her attack packs a whallop...
The bass really
reverberates, doesn't it?
Next up is a really sharp performance!
Ow!
Dance harder!
The music is lacking a
certain something, you know?
Oh, I know!
It's missing your screams,
transfer student!
In that case,
I'm gonna wring a better
performance out of you!
SYMPHONY REGALIA PRESTO
Symphony Regalia Presto!
That huge thing is flying?!
Yes indeed, this big thing is flying!
That's my power!
The other Elite Four
could never do this!
I'm the one who can best
use this Goku Uniform,
this power you got your hands on!
Isn't that right, Satsuki?!
TAKABISHA (HIGH-HANDED) KINDERGARTEN
You know, I sure would like a castle...
This sandbox belongs to me!
I won't let the other kids use it!
Except for you, Satsuki!
We've been best friends since forever!
I'll make a castle for you, too!
No.
My sand is right here.
Is that all?
This sand was left over from that.
My sand became concrete and was
transformed into that skyscraper.
From the top, even a child
can look down on any adult.
A castle that vanishes at the
first gust of wind is worthless.
Don't you agree, Nonon?
But all buildings fall down eventually!
Then you should build
it in inside your mind!
A skyscraper built within your mind...
...will never fall down.
You don't need any dumb sand!
I'll hold your hand! For ever and ever!
Ever since that day,
I've promised myself that
I would always be with you.
That I would always look out
from the same height as you!
Actually, I guess my view
is higher right now.
Now listen to this! The
William Tell Overture finale!
Hey! I thought you were disqualified
if you left the battle area!
Not if you leave it, only
if you fall out of it.
I'm flying, so no problem!
You weasels are always making
up rules on the spot!
Goodness, it seems like you
have time to spare to complain.
Let's give you something a
taste of something bigger.
Let's see you dodge jauntily!
If you can, that is!
Like I said, on what planet
is that a uniform?!
A flying weapon fired a flying weapon!
Damn it, how is that fair?!
Chew on this!
In that case,
I'll just have to bring
you down to my level!
I'll cut those...
...flimsy ropes of yours!
Each part of Senketsu's body
is a bundle of Life Fibers!
You think you can cut him that easily?
Attagirl, Ryuko!
It's true, cutting Life
Fibers is difficult.
But what about the ground?
Right! So let's see how you like this!
I can withstand an explosion like this!
It's no use, the ground's
giving out beneath us!
Oh dear, she's fallen.
LOCATOR NO RESPONSE COMMUNICATIONS OK
The communications search
system is offline, huh?
That's most kind of
the Naturals Election.
You're the last person
I expected a call from.
Is this about the girl in the Kamui?
Yeah, I guess you could say that.
Ryuko is trying really
hard, but, well...
Senketsu, can you do something
that's really, really reckless?
I'll do my best!
You're finished!
It evolved into a flying
configuration in so short a time?
That's my Senketsu! You can
do anything if you try!
Did you see that?! Senketsu Shippu!
SENKETSU SHIPPU (GALE)
...she's trying a little
too hard, you see.
It's evolving too quickly.
You're telling me to assume a
worst-case scenario, is that it?
I suppose I am.
Understood.
The sky is my world...
The kid gloves are off,
you stinking bitch!
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
As the battle against Nonon
Jakuzure reaches its climax,
HONNOUJI ACADEMY
a girl appears at Honnouji Academy!
GIRL
Her name is Nui Harime!
NUI HARIME
Be careful, Ryuko! A girl who
uses her name as an eyepatch
EYEPATCH
GIRL
is insane for sure! Watch out!
Next time on Kill La Kill,
"I'm Not Your Cute Woman"!
EPISODE 11
I'M NOT YOUR CUTE WOMAN