What are you looking at?
What can you see?
Hey, girlie, are you waiting for someone?
Come to think of it, I saw you here yesterday, too.
Have you been here the whole time?
Maybe she's a doll.
Oh, she blinked!
Whoa!
She moved!
Huh?
What?
Found you.
This isn't good...
Dazai's gone missing?
He's not answering his phone,
and he hasn't returned to the dorm, either.
He's just floating in some river again.
Or he could be in prison this time.
My guess would be that he went
off somewhere with a woman.
But it's true that he's targeted by the Port Mafia.
It could be that...
That man's ability to sense danger and stay alive approaches nightmarish proficiency.
Just think about how he's as healthy as can be
despite so many suicide attempts.
I doubt the Mafia alone will
be enough to get the better of him.
But...
I'll go look into it.
Are you all better now, Tanizaki-san?
Yes, thankfully.
I was really worried when it all happened.
I'm relieved you're okay.
I'm sorry I worried you.
So you're finally recovered.
It's all thanks to Dr. Yosano's treatment.
So, how many times did she get you?
F-F-Four times...
That many...
Atsushi-kun...
As long as you remain at the Agency,
remember to never get injured.
Okay...
If you think you're at any risk, run.
You should cultivate your ability
to sense danger on a daily basis.
For example, ten seconds from now...
Oh, Dr. Yosano.
Good morning.
Oh, Atsushi.
Are you hurt anywhere?
Oh, I'm fine.
Darn.
Darn?
I was hoping to have someone
come with me on a shopping trip,
but I guess you're the only one around.
What?
Is this what he meant by
the ability to sense danger?
D-Dr. Yosano, you're still not done?
Don't you dare drop anything.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
You good-for-nothing!
Hurry up and send my car over!
Ow...
U-Um, are you okay?
What's the meaning of this, you little twit?
This is a custom-made suit from a European brand.
S-Sorry.
I'm very sorry.
Were you hurt?
Don't touch me.
I'll be lodging a complaint with your employer!
Hey, what's your job?
Are you a tea server?
A receptionist?
Or perhaps you're something
a little more specialized?
Hmm...
Ow!
I'm a doctor, you pervert.
Oh?
You have two arms... That's way too many.
Would you like me to take one off?
Episode 8
Teaching Them To Kill; Then To Die
I'm sorry about... um... earlier.
The packages are in a sorry state, too.
Nothing to be sorry about.
By the way...
What?
Is this punishment?
Hmm, nice leg.
I heard your leg was bitten off
by the Port Mafia when Tanizaki got injured.
Not signs of scaring or fusion...
It's more of a restoration than a regeneration.
The tiger did this instantly?
Um...
Is there a problem?
Oh, I'm just sad I couldn't treat you.
But there's no reprieve next time for you.
What?
The Mafia are known for surprise attacks.
You should watch yourself at night.
You never know when they might strike next.
That's right.
I'm their prime target.
I should know how to protect myself on my own.
Testing, testing. This is your train conductor.
We apologize for the inconvenience,
but we will now conduct a minor physics experiment!
The topic: Evaluation of Explosive
Reaction and Sensory Response
in a Non-Inertial Reference Frame.
The test subjects will be our current passengers!
We greatly appreciate your cooperation!
So, without further ado,
please listen to this!
Maybe two or three of you
already died from that one?
But that will pale in comparison to the next one!
We've rigged enough explosives
in the front and back cars
to blow everyone clear to the moon!
Now, test subject Atsushi-kun.
Unless you surrender yourself,
all passengers will go straight
to heaven, much less the moon!
But...
Speak of the devil...
Wh-What should we do?
Option one, turn yourself in.
Option two, jump off this running train with several dozen passengers to escape.
Option three...
Beat them up.
Excellent.
After all, we are the Armed Detective Agency.
Okay, Atsushi.
Let's split up and look for the bombs.
I'll take the front.
You take the rear!
What if we run into the enemy?
Terminate with extreme prejudice!
Roger!
A bomb threat, on a train with civilian
passengers, in broad daylight...
That's tantamount to suicide.
Even for the Port Mafia, this plan's pretty bold...
Or, rather, obsessive.
I wonder who's behind this.
Our warmest welcome to the decisive lady from the Detective Agency...
and our most regretful farewell!
Well, well...
If it isn't a celebrity we've got here.
Ah, you're alive?
What a surprise.
Ladies are so resilient these days.
It is an era of equal rights for men and women.
From where I stand,
it's a greater surprise to find a wanted
criminal like you in a place like this.
Kajii Motojirou!
While being a member of the secretive Port Mafia,
you are a surprisingly well-known
terrorist bomber...
Port Mafia
Operative
In the recent Marizen Building Bomb Incident,
Kajii Motojirou
Ability: Lemon
Bomb
you killed 28 civilians.
That was most wonderful.
The slowing of the pulse,
the hypoxia of neurons!
Lactic acidosis...
Death is the collective music of
infinite changes in states!
Ah, then comes irreversible death...
So you're saying death is an experiment?
Science, in its ultimate form, is God and death...
Both exist and cannot be overcome by science.
That is why we are drawn to them...
So...
What color is your blood?
See for yourself.
If we can't remove the bombs, these people will die.
But can I do this?
Hey!
Don't go that way! There's a bomb!
Please go back to the central car.
There's a bomb in the rear car...
Um, you...
Your duty is to protect the bomb at any cost.
You're...
You're the one I saw...
Use your ability Demon Snow
to kill anyone who interferes.
What?
Port Mafia
Assassin
Izumi Kyouka
Ability: Demon
Snow
Shred your enemies,
Demon Snow.
Shred your enemies, Demon Snow.
Sh... She's too strong!
Wh-Why?
Why would a girl like you...
My name is Kyouka,
an orphan like you.
I like bunny rabbits and tofu.
I hate dogs and lightning.
After being taken in by the Port Mafia,
I killed 35 people in six months.
Protect the bomb,
and kill anyone who interferes.
The Agency isn't as formidable as I've heard.
Oh, well.
So you're about to die, but tell me this before you do:
What does it mean to die?
What did you say?
Oh, it's just scholarly interest.
I'm an avid researcher, you see.
All the reasons for human death,
including hypoxia of neurons in the brain and telomere degradation,
are simple and reversible processes
in laboratory settings.
Yet, why is death irreversible?
Why must all humans die?
You don't even know why?
So the Mafia aren't so formidable, after all...
You claim that someone who's a meddling private eye
would know something that I, a seeker of science, do not?
Sure I would.
The reason for that is simple.
You're just an idiot.
Thank you for your valuable opinion.
I think you would know this,
being well-read and all...
but even after the body dies from blood loss,
the brain and the conscious mind are said to survive for eight hours.
Afterward, I'll ask your corpse this:
"You're dead now. How do you feel?"
Well, take your time.
It's impossible.
I can't win.
Am I going to die here?
Are people going to die again because of me?
Just because they got on the same train as me?
Just for that simple reason, they will all die...
That is your karma, weretiger.
You will cause ill for everyone
around you, just by being alive.
Get out, you good-for-nothing!
The world would be a better place if
you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
We don't need worthless louts!
Why are you alive?
You accomplish nothing,
and cause inconvenience and
misfortune for everyone around you.
Those who can save no one do not deserve to live.
Just then, an idea popped into my head.
It was a stupid idea.
But I couldn't shake it off.
If I...
If I could save them...
the passengers here...
If I could get them back safe
and sound to their homes...
Wouldn't that mean...
that I...
Wouldn't that mean it's okay for me to live?
Stay away.
Sorry.
I can't do this anymore!
She's too fast...
I guess I can't do this, after all.
If I could only use my ability...
All right.
I wonder if she's nice and cooked
all the way through now.
Let's see.
Hmm, that was underwhelming.
I was hoping you'd go flying a bit farther.
H-How?
That little sparkler wouldn't kill me.
Which side did I punch you on just now?
I-I-I-If I had to choose, maybe this side?
Impossible!
You were on the brink of death just before!
I may not look like it, but I'm a doctor.
I've seen a hundred times more
deaths than you, at the very least.
What's death, you ask?
Let me tell you...
Death is the loss of life.
No matter how hard we doctors try,
our patients' lives just slip through our fingers...
Death, the ultimate form of science?
What a load!
I'll kill anyone who doesn't value life!
I... I remember now...
So you're the Armed Detective Agency's physician,
Yosano Akiko...
My ability, Thou Shalt Not Die,
can cure any wounds.
Even my own wounds, as you can see.
But the necessary conditions are harsh.
It can only cure lethal injuries.
What an inconvenient ability.
If I want to cure moderate injuries,
I have to half kill my patient first.
Oh?
You're hurt, aren't you, boy?
Would you like me to treat you?
This is...
It's over.
My name is Kyouka.
I've killed 35 people.
Where's the bomb?
My last victims were a family of three,
a father, a mother, and a boy.
Demon Snow slit their throats.
What have you done?!
Who are you?
I can't feel any emotion in your words,
or even in you, yourself.
You're like a killing machine.
If you feel anything, you should put it into words.
Otherwise, an idiot like me won't get it.
Is something like this what you really want to do?!
This is the train conductor's office.
Atsushi!
You still breathing?
Dr. Yosano?
According to this weak-ass bomber here,
your bomb has a remote detonator.
If you make one mistake trying to defuse it,
it'll explode in a matter of seconds.
You'll have to use the remote detonator's stop button to deactivate it.
The Mafia agent there should have it.
Do you have it?
Give it to me.
What?!
You pressed the button,
Kyouka?
You pressed the button, Kyouka?
Deactivating the bomb is unnecessary.
Die along with the passengers
and show the hapless masses that the Port Mafia should be feared.
Take the bomb off!
How much time do we have left?!
There's no time!
What?
I am an idiot, after all...
I only realized once her
slender arms pushed me...
that her ability is always activated by a voice from her cell phone.
She is unable to control her own ability.
My name is Kyouka.
I've killed 35 people.
I don't want to kill anyone else!
Atsushi!
Um...
No matter how powerful it may be,
a pawn is just a pawn...
What about you?
Are you a pawn or the master?
Or are you a pawn who is waiting to be crushed?
She didn't kill people of her own free will.
Gifts don't necessarily bring
happiness to their wielders.
I know that better than anyone!
But if I hand her over to the police,
she'll be put to death for sure.
Where are you taking me?
That's... um...
Oh, let's go on a date, for starters.
Huh?
A date with you?
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs, Episode 9:
Episode 9
The Beauty Is Quiet
Like a Stone Statue
The Beauty Is Quiet Like a Stone Statue.
Boiled tofu is delicious.