This Scissor Blade was left behind
by the person who killed my father!
You're going to tell me!
Who's the owner of this
scissor, Satsuki Kiryuin?!
You said your name is Ryuko Matoi?
You're Isshin Matoi's daughter?
You know who my father is?!
You're bleeding too much, Ryuko.
I thought you wanted blood.
At this rate of blood loss,
you will lose consciousness
in five minutes.
Don't sound so calm about it!
We'll have a leisurely chat
another day, Satsuki Kiryuin!
Don't let her escape!
After her! After her!
Don't bother.
B-But milady!
She'll be back. Leave her be until then.
Lady Satsuki... You're
as dazzling as always.
Your tea, Miss.
A girl in a Kamui, eh?
EPISODE 2
SO SEXY SHE MIGHT PASS OUT
Oh, wow! It's a nearly naked chick!
You pervert!
You dare make a move on me knowing that
I'm the Kanto Vagabond,
the Guitar Case Drifter!?
My scissor! My scissor's gone!
Ryuko!
Thanks! Be careful, Mako!
This perv tried to—
Dad, what do you think you're doing?
"Dad"?
Dad?!
I'm so sorry!
Wow, I really felt that one!
You've got a great punch, Miss!
Of course she does!
I owe her for saving my life!
BARAZO MANKANSHOKU
You were totally bad-ass,
swinging that scissor around half-naked!
MATARO MANKANSHOKU
Nobody in their right mind
could fight dressed like that!
Bite me! It's complicated, all right?
That hurt, damn it!
I was the one who carried you here!
If belting my husband or Mataro
makes you feel better,
feel free to belt away!
SUKUYO MANKANSHOKU
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR MANKANSHOKU
How did I—
Daddy treated you!
You'd never guess it, but
he's a back-alley doctor.
If you compare the number
of people he's killed
versus those he's saved,
he's killed more!
That's a bad thing.
Don't worry about it.
The dead ones don't sue you.
Oh, right!
I know it's nothing fancy,
but eat all you like!
Go ahead, Ryuko! Don't be shy!
It's unidentifiable stuff
made into croquettes
and unidentifiable stuff in miso soup!
Oh, you! I use only
non-poisonous ingredients.
Better dig in before I eat it all!
Down, Guts! Your food is out there!
GUTS
We call him Guts 'cause
he eats with "gusto."
You were anemic, little lady, so eat up!
Don't just sit there, eat!
The masses... Fools, all.
They're swine in human clothing,
domesticated by the establishment.
They must be governed.
By Satsuki Kiryuin
and Honnouji Academy.
It is we who shall pave the
way to humanity's future.
The Goku Uniforms are
weapons meant for that end.
The uniforms that this country
makes its students wear
are based on military uniforms.
The raised collars on boys'
uniforms comes from the army.
Girls' sailor uniforms are
just that – naval uniforms.
This country is a state that
chose to make its youths wear
military uniforms during
their education.
In which case, we at Honnouji Academy
shall treat them as combat uniforms.
They shall be symbols of our control
over the pigs in human clothing.
You of the Sewing Club are the
chosen elite of our Human
Conquest and Liberation Project.
Take care as you work.
Thank you for your kind words.
Tennis Club Captain Omiko Hakodate,
Third Year Class T,
reporting as ordered.
How are preparations for the
Hokkaido interleague match coming?
Milady. All club members are devoting
themselves entirely to training.
Those northern bumpkin bears
will learn down to the
marrow of their bones
the might of Honnouji Academy
and Lady Satsuki Kiryuin.
This is armed suppression in the
guise of an interleague match.
If the Tennis Club is successful,
our control of northern
Japan will be complete.
Don't fail us.
I understand.
This is a Tennis-spec,
Athleticism-augmenting Two-Star Goku Uniform.
A gift from Lady Satsuki.
At last, a Two-Star Goku
Uniform of my very own!
Thank you, Milady!
Carry out your mission.
Without fail, Milady!
The entire Tennis Club shall
pull together and redouble
its efforts and train even harder
for the interleague match!
Why do you not wear
a Goku Uniform, Miss?
This sword is more than
sufficient for me.
Perhaps no uniform is worthy of you.
Hey, are you awake?
What the hell are you, Senketsu?
Quit your quibbling!
All right, I'll make
you wear me by force!
W-What kind of perverted
outfit is this?!
This is me.
Don't be so matter-of-fact about it!
Get off me! Come off, damn it!
Anyway, just get away from me,
you perverted sailor uniform!
Where'd that power come from?
This power is yours and mine.
I drank your blood and awakened.
Whenever you put me on,
whenever I am worn by you,
that power will be manifested.
What are you?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You just finished calmly
explaining how you worked!
I am able to explain phenomena
that are occurring right now.
However, there is much
that I do not know.
My memory... Yes, in your
language, you would say that
there are gaps in my memory.
Don't you remember anything?
I do know that the man
who constructed me
had a beard, an eye patch,
and wore a white lab coat.
He was stooped, wore sandals, had a
cane in one hand, and had a mouse.
That could be only one
man — my father!
Father?
Yeah, Isshin Matoi. He's my father.
I'm Ryuko.
My father made you?
But if I have you, I might
be able to beat them!
You're coming with me
for a while, Senketsu.
"Senketsu"?
It's a hassle if I don't
have anything to call you.
If it was drinking my
blood that woke you up,
your name is going to be
Senketsu — "fresh blood."
SENKETSU "FRESH BLOOD"
Just you wait, Satsuki Kiryuin!
Ryuko! Wake up!
We have to hurry up and eat breakfast!
If I'm late for school
again, I'll be expelled!
There's a pretty distinct
gap between rich and poor.
Well, it's a city ruled by Lady Satsuki.
THREE-STAR
TWO-STAR
ONE-STAR
NO-STAR
Top-tier students get put into
the exclusive residential area.
Lower-tier students
like us get the slum.
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT
Your position at school also
determines where you live?
HONNOUJI ACADEMY
Yep! Pretty straightforward, huh?
Oh, that reminds me.
Ryuko, Mom said that if
you need a place to—
Mom said that! If you don't
have a place to stay!
You can stay! With us!
She's already filed the paperwork!
Is this any time to be
talking about that?!
What's the big idea?!
Ah, you're the transfer student who
was rude to Lady Satsuki, as I recall.
Stay out of this.
I'm Girls' Tennis Club
Captain Omiko Hakodate.
GIRLS' TENNIS CLUB CAPTAIN
OMIKO HAKODATE
Club member Mako Mankanshoku
has failed to fulfill
her club obligations.
She is being purged as a result.
What did Mako do wrong?
She skipped yesterday's club practice.
Our rule is that anyone who fails
to come to practice will suffer
the 110 Million Cannonball Serves.
An outsider has no right to complain
about internal club policies.
Yesterday? Mako was being
held hostage yesterday!
Of course she didn't come
to your stupid practice!
The issue is that she was taken
hostage without permission.
Begin.
Cut that out, damn it!
Go on ahead, Mako!
You'll be expelled if
you're late, right?
Yeah!
Thanks a bunch! I'll
see you later, 'kay?
Yup!
So, you're saying that
you will take us on?
I owe her for a meal
and a night's lodging.
How amusing.
Don't get too full of yourself
just because you defeated
the Boxing Club's Fukuroda.
I'm gonna make quick work of
those Goku Uniforms of yours!
Let's do it, Senketsu!
Hey! Hey, let's get to it, Senketsu!
Hey, what's wrong with you?!
Are you kidding me?!
She's talking to her clothes...
How thoroughly disappointing.
Wake up, damn it! Hey!
What's your problem?!
Die!
Screw you! There's a reason—
What, a love game?
No challenge whatsoever...
Oh, dear...
You awake, Ryuko?
Wait, aren't you a teacher?
That's right.
I'm your homeroom teacher,
Aikuro Mikisugi.
AIKURO MIKISUGI
Talk about your crazy
extracurricular lessons...
Hang on, you didn't
undress me, did you?!
Yes, I thought I would
teach you a few things...
about your body.
You perverted son of a bitch!
Wait, what?! My body won't move!
Calm yourself.
What did you do?!
Anesthetic acupuncture.
You seem a little hot-blooded
at the moment,
so I'm going to draw a little.
No, don't! I hate needles!
Allow me to tell you why your
Kamui didn't activate earlier.
More! Feed me more!
Feed me more blood!
You awake, Senketsu?
Ryuko?
Dumbass, why didn't you
wake up when I needed you?!
Now, now, calm down.
You understand now, right?
Understand what?
This Kamui is awakened by your blood.
What's this "Kamui" thing
you keep talking about?
You mean this sailor uniform?
That's right.
It's a uniform constructed
by your father,
Isshin Matoi, whose power surpasses
that of the Goku Uniforms.
Only someone who can master wearing this
can fight against Satsuki Kiryuin.
Who the hell are you?
Prove to me that you are someone
who deserves an answer.
Come again?
The first order of business is
Tennis Club Captain Omiko Hakodate.
If you can't master this
Kamui and defeat her,
you don't stand a chance
against Satsuki Kiryuin.
Better get a move on, afternoon
classes are starting.
Use this Seki Tekko from now on.
It will make it easier for
you to provide it with blood.
SEKI TEKKO
Fine. I'll pound that tennis
club president into the dirt,
and then you're gonna tell
me everything I want to know.
Looking good, Hakodate.
Thank you. It is all thanks to this
Tennis-spec Goku Uniform I
received from Lady Satsuki.
The Tennis Club shall subjugate
Hokkaido without fail.
What's that about?
We have an unmotivated club
member, so we are purging her.
Not so fast, people!
Ryuko!
The transfer student...
You've come for another beating?
As if!
This time, I'm gonna knock
you all on your asses!
Let's do it, Senketsu!
That looks both painful and
embarrassing, you masochistic exhibitionist!
Bite me! I'm not an exhibitionist!
Quit splitting hairs.
Let's begin! 110 Million Serve!
Fault! You're disqualified,
transfer student!
What?!
True, you evaded Hakodate's attack.
But slicing balls in half is
against the rules in a match.
In other words, you've won
the fight but lost the match!
Listen up! What you're standing
on is a tennis court!
Which means that you
can't say you have won
if you didn't win according
to the rules of tennis!
Hey! Why are you getting all picky now?
What about yesterday?
That was yesterday!
This is crazy! When
we were boxing, we—
It doesn't matter, you're disqualified!
No, she won!
Ryuko won! She won!
What?
Ryuko rescued me!
She may have lost the match,
but she won with friendship!
Winning with friendship
means winning at life!
Listen...
If you're going to be like
that, you leave her no choice!
Ryuko will win.
Even in tennis! Even in tennis!
Even in tennis, she'll win!
So, you're saying that
you want to face me,
Tennis Club Captain Omiko
Hakodate, in a tennis match?
Here! Do your best, Ryuko!
All right, all right...
Let's do this!
Special rules!
The match is one game!
Decide who serves first!
I'm watching, Ryuko!
She's a rookie. I'll let her decide.
I'll take you up on that and
go ahead and serve, then!
I won't hold back!
Weak!
She's fast!
Ryuko, that was awesome!
Love-fifteen!
Not bad.
I'm just getting warmed up.
You're only now beginning
to learn the might
of the Tennis-spec,
Athleticism-augmenting
Two-Star Goku Uniform I
received from Lady Satsuki!
Interesting!
That won't work this time!
Nice!
Love-thirty!
That happened because I anticipated
that you would do that.
I put a special spin on it.
Ryuko, you naughty girl!
Okay, I'll put my own
special touch on this one!
Here we go!
Fault!
Oh, come on!
Double fault! Love-forty!
Ryuko, this is your last shot!
What's the matter, transfer student?
Hurry up and serve!
Ryuko, use the Scissor Blade!
Only the Scissor Blade can
withstand our strength!
SCISSOR BLADE
Got it!
Mako! My scissor!
Catch!
Right, then...
This'll work!
You can't be serious!
Faul—
It's all right.
Play along, Hakodate.
Show her the power of your Two-Star.
Yes, Milady!
As you wish!
Satsuki Kiryuin, you're
watching from on high,
issuing orders to your
lackeys, same as always.
It's creepy.
You're going to show me
just how much of that Kamui's
power you can tap into.
You bitch...
You know that this thing
is called a Kamui?
Not so fast. Your
opponent is over there.
I'm going to use you as
a live-fire exercise to
loosen up for the Hokkaido away series!
Show me what you got, then!
On the court, you can
only count on yourself!
Nobody gets it!
SENI-SOSHITSU
Seni-Soshitsu!
You did it, Ryuko!
Oh, dear. It looks like
the match can't go on.
Don't get too full of yourself, bitch.
Wait, Sanageyama.
The victor of the match is that girl.
Lady Satsuki!
So, are you going to tell me?
Are you the Scissor Blade Woman?
What?!
If you wish to know the answer,
ask the question with your skill!
Ryuko, if you're going to
fight, win within two minutes.
Otherwise, you're going
to pass out again.
That's because you drank too much blood!
SECRET SWORD BAKUZAN
Secret Sword Bakuzan.
This blade can cut even a Kamui.
Its edge is even keener
than that scissor's.
The pressure's incredible...
Her spirit is amazing...
Mark my words!
Next time, I'll finish
this once and for all!
Let's go, Mako!
'Kay!
Forgive me, Milady.
I underestimated the transfer student.
Hakodate is demoted to a No-Star.
As for Hokkaido, set up an interleague
match with the Sumo Club.
As I expected, a Kamui
is most formidable.
To think it could turn away my blade...
I shall remember this day, Ryuko Matoi.
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Satsuki Kiryuin...
SATSUKI KIRYUIN
ANOTHER
Another owner of a Kamui.
KAMUI
Before that overwhelming power,
Ryuko and I are helpless.
OVERWHELMING
RYUKO AND I
HELPLESS
Can we win, Ryuko?
RYUKO MATOI
EPISODE 3
JUNKETSU
Next time on KILL la KILL, "Junketsu."
EPISODE 3
JUNKETSU