Kiss Him, Not Me
Christmas in the Holy Land
Let's do a Chri-Pa, guys! A Chri-Pa!
Huh?
A Chri-Pa! You know, Christmas party!
Oh. Sounds good.
Right? We can reserve
a karaoke room or something.
Does Christmas Eve work?
Sure.
It works for me.
Same.
Um, sorry.
I'm going to Comiket on
Christmas Eve, so I can't.
Huh?
Wait! It's Christmas Eve!
It's the day everyone looks
forward to the most!
Tell me about it! It somehow
fell on the same day this year!
That's not what I mean!
I mean, what is Comiket anyway?
Apparently it's the country's
largest doujinshi exhibition sale.
Oh. You said you went during
summer break, too, right?
Yup.
What the hell? If you went over
summer, isn't that enough?
Christmas Eve only comes once
a year! A perfect end to the year!
I'm sorry, but my year isn't
complete until I attend Comiket!
Shi
Nana
Iga
S-She's made up her mind.
Oh, look. There's a history
study group there, too.
Sounds interesting.
Oh, thanks.
Yes! It's super fun!
These days, there's more there
than just manga and anime.
It's spread to other genres,
too! Like songwriting and foreign dramas!
I want to see them all!
I know.
How about we all go?
That way, we can close out the
year and have a party, all at once.
Th-There goes that airhead again!
Oh, but Serinuma-san, were you
already going with someone?
Oh, no.
The friend I always go with has plans,
so I'm going alone.
If you could all make it, I'd be overjoyed!
Overjoyed...
Overjoyed!
All right. We'll go to Comiket,
and have a party on the way home!
Sound good?
No objections here!
December 24th: Early Morning, Christmas Eve
Takami Station
Good morning, everyone!
G-Good morning.
Why are we meeting so early?
I woke up at 5 A.M.
If we don't go early, all
the books will be gone.
So sleepy...
Guide to Comiket
Okay! This guide has what you need
to know, like proper etiquette and history.
So make sure to read it on the train.
Onward! To the holy land!
We might be the first on board.
Let's hurry up and buy books so
we can come back and party after.
Kokusai-tenjijo Station
Wha...
What's up with this crowd?!
Are all these people going to Comiket?
No way...
It's still only seven in the morning!
The train was packed,
and the platform had so many people...
Here! Don't push! Don't
force the doors open!
Don't throw away your hope!
The staff workers are screaming like crazy.
What the heck is all this?!
Mu
Nana
Shi
Iga
I wonder if it's because it's Christmas Eve.
I think there's fewer people
this year than last...
Th-This is...
...fewer people?!
C'mon! We don't wanna get separated.
Those in general admittance,
please come this way!
We'll wait here until the doors open.
At 10, wasn't it?
And it's 7:30 right now, so...
T-Two and a half hours?!
Oh, right! Here, take these!
Waiting out here will get cold,
so feel free to use them.
Thanks.
We can wait.
Ba-dump
Two and a half hours...
...is a cinch!
But little did they know...
Plus One Hour
After the doors opened,
there'd be another hour
before they could enter.
Exhausted
All right, then.
As we discussed, let's split into three
groups and finish this shopping list.
What an incredibly thorough map!
Are you really all right
with helping me shop?
Well, we don't have anything
we want for ourselves.
We can get everything faster if we split up.
Thanks. I really appreciate it!
Everyone, thank you so much for helping
me out, even though I'm acting so selfish.
And also...
I'm sorry!
Right. The stuff she wants is BL.
Two hot guys!
That, and I think these girls
are picturing something funny.
Are they a couple?
Um, can we have the new issue
that went on sale today?
Sure!
Amazing!
He's perfectly mastered that "this
is just for someone else" look!
Listen, Nana. You lose if you let
something like this get to you.
Thank you very much!
All right, Nana. Let's keep going like this.
Uh, yeah. The next one is...
Huh? It's the next next booth over.
Um, the newest issue, please.
Yes, sir.
The next one's right here, too.
Please take a look.
And the next one.
Thank you very much.
Next.
We have a new issue.
Thank you very much!
It's like they're carpet bombing the place.
They're doing the crab walk.
They must love these comics.
We don't!
Give me all the new issues!
Coming right up!
You're very skilled.
Oh, uh, thank you very much!
Did you make this all by yourself?
Y-Yes!
Amazing. I can't draw,
so you have my respect.
A-An angel!
He's radiant!
My eyes! My eyes!
Come on! Enough with the idle
chatter! Let's get this over with!
It wasn't idle chatter.
Besides, it's a while before our meetup time.
I want to finish this up
quickly and get out of here.
Why? Isn't this fun?
Not at all!
There are too many people, the books are
heavy, it's cold outside, but hot inside.
The place is dusty, too big,
and we're walking too much!
What's more...
It feels like I could lose you at any second!
Sorry.
Are you a child?
Then how about I try this?
You know what? After we're done, I'd
like to go see the history study group.
I suppose this is better
than you getting lost.
Let's go.
Wh-What was that?
Adorable!
Look at this haul!
Guess the others aren't here yet.
We did say we were meeting at 2:00.
I've gotta thank them all properly.
I wonder what would be good...
Nice, very nice! Can you strike a pose for me?
Please stop! I'm not a cosplayer!
Aw, what a waste!
Just lemme take a few shots!
Don't move.
That's bad manners, sir.
Not a gentleman, I see.
What's your problem?
If you call yourself a photographer,
shouldn't you carry yourself with decorum?
It's not at all acceptable to take
photos of a lady who refuses.
You understand, don't you? Look.
You're being rude!
People like you give us a bad name!
Apologize!
Everyone's upset with you.
On your knees! On your knees!
U-Um!
I'm fine!
Y-You're not going to do this
sort of thing again, right?
I-I get it! Sorry!
That was a shock.
You're letting him off with that? That's kind.
Thank you very much!
Trouble-making punks like that crop
up from time to time. Be careful.
Y-You're Sebastian from Gray Butler right?
Yup.
Amazing! It's perfect!
You look just like him!
Thank you.
There she is.
Sorry. We got a bit lost.
Our phones had bad reception, too.
Thanks for all your hard work!
What's this? You already
have so many princes.
You guys should keep a better eye on her.
Huh? Who are you?
Oh, well, he just helped me out.
Well then, I'll leave the rest to your
princes, and excuse myself, my lady.
Adieu.
What the heck was that?!
Serinuma-san, did he do anything to you?!
N-N-No! That's not it!
I got tangled up with a creep
earlier and he helped me!
Tangled?
Sorry. If only we weren't so late...
That's not it! Don't worry about it!
You're the ones going along
with my selfish whims.
I'm the one who's sorry!
I really appreciate it!
Thank you!
All right! Shall we party?
Yeah!
We just have to go back now. Easy.
It was my first time, but I had a lot of fun.
But, little did they know...
The traffic on the way back was an
even worse hell than when they came.
So, by the time they arrived
for their closing celebration and Chri-Pa...
all the boys had the energy level of corpses.
Exhausted
Give me a break.
I'm going to die.
Closing Ceremony
That's what happens at your first Comiket.
It takes a lot out of you.
Isn't it funny? I'm weaker
than them, yet I feel great!
Well that's because you had moe power.
Moe energy! Got lots of it!
Oh, yeah!
There was a super cool Sebastian there, too.
Got any pics?!
I don't, actually.
Ugh! If only I had taken one!
I'm honored to hear that.
How about taking one now?
No way! How? You're a student at this school?!
Yup. I'm in class 1-F.
He's a—
I'm Nishina Shima.
Pleased to meet you, Senpai!
He's a girl?!
Kiss Him, Not Me
Y-You!
Hello.
Allow me to introduce you.
This is Nishina Shima-chan. She's
a first year-like you, Shinomiya-kun.
You didn't know about her?
There are six classes. I can't know them all.
More like, she was a girl all along?
I thought she was a male
cosplayer at the winter Comiket,
so this was a big shock.
But after talking to her, it turns
out we get along perfectly.
Yup!
So I guess that...
Doesn't count.
Nishina-san.
You haven't gone home yet?
What are you doing for New Year's?
When third semester starts, come
hang out with us third-years again.
Nishina-san!
Help us with the first match
of the new year again!
Not fair! We asked first.
What's with this feeling of defeat?
You know what this is, don't
you? The Takarazuka effect.
Even if that is the case...
If we say anything, we lose!
In any case, it's definitely a surprise
to see you here in our school.
But it can't be just a coincidence.
Right. I had heard various rumors
about Serinuma-senpai before Comiket,
but meeting her there
truly was a coincidence.
Indeed. It is too good to be true.
A coincidence that's too good to be true...
Some may call it fate.
I want to value the bond we have.
Please, allow me to invite you over to my house.
We'll talk the night away about Mirage Saga.
Talk the night away about Mirage Saga?!
I'm in!
Hold it!
We're going, too!
We also really want to all
night about this Mirage Saga.
Right, Shinomiya-kun?
Yes, you're right! Let's talk
until our throats are raw!
Then count me in, too.
It sounds like it'll be fun.
You're all interested in Mirage Saga now?
I'm so glad!
Well, you know, now that
I've gotten a taste for it...
You know it!
Well then, you're all more than welcome!
But I'd appreciate if you could
listen to a small request of mine.
A-Amazing!
Welcome home, Lady Shima.
Please come in.
My room is on the third floor.
This girl...
really feels like she popped
out of some 2D universe.
I get what you're trying to say.
Take a look.
This room is mainly for my figure collection.
Amazing! Amazing, amazing, amazing!
You have so many Shion figures!
They're all so beautiful.
Every Shion is an angel!
I bought this one from last
year's Wonder Festival.
I've heard of this one!
This is by that super famous sculptor,
and it's a completely
made-to-order garage kit model!
And the painting? Did you...
Yup. I did it.
What? Amazing!
It's like a magic spell.
Magic Spell
Iga
Shi
Nana
Gorgeous!
It's Tsuruga Castle. And
this one's Hikone Castle.
Did you make these, too?
Yes, they're just plastic models, though.
You're amazing.
Oh, not at all. I'm still learning.
M-Mutsumi-san's down!
Be careful, you guys!
She's a tough one!
Roger!
These two really get along.
This is my costume room.
These are all the clothes
I've made up until now.
You can make just about anything,
can't you, Shima-chan?
Oh, please.
The dress you made for
Shinomiya-kun was simply marvelous.
How did you know?
I saw the play.
Shinomiya-kun, you were very cute.
Don't call me cute!
Huh? But you really were cute.
I told you not to say that!
Are you making fun of me?
You tell her!
I would never make fun of you.
You were very beautiful.
It was marvelous.
W-Well, thanks, I guess.
You idiot, you're too easy!
I just told you to be careful!
Easy, there.
She is quite the smooth talker, however...
Now, then. The room I want to
show you the most is this way.
Comics, novels,
light novels, special bound
books, limited books,
doujinshi!
These shelves are like
the perfect BL collection!
Amazing!
Can I see them? Can I?
Please.
It's a Zebra Stripe book.
She's got all of them. Even
the old ones that I don't have!
Isn't that the author we
lined up for the other day?
Oh. That's my circle.
That's my circle. I draw manga, too.
You god damn liar! You can't
be good at that many things!
What's the matter, Serinuma?
Why the pigeon impression?
Just lay into her!
Are you serious?! Are you
really Yokojima-sensei?!
Yes. Wait just a second.
Will this convince you?
Are you some kind of god?!
Sh-She's good!
I-I...
J-Just love Zebra Stripe's books.
I-I always buy them.
Y-Yokojima-sensei,
m-may I shake your hand?
Serinuma-san, calm down!
Thank you.
If it makes you happy,
I'll draw for you anytime.
Hold me.
Cut it out! Get a hold of yourself, Serinuma!
I can draw just as good!
I got a 3 in art class!
A 3 is a perfectly average grade!
Shut it!
How's that?!
No good!
She's rich, beautiful, smooth
talking, able to do anything.
It's like she's a walking life hack!
I can't beat her in any way!
Wow!
This is Shion, isn't it?
I'm so happy!
Can I keep this?
No way. I mean, it's garbage, isn't it? I suck.
That's not true at all! It's
super cute! A great Shion!
Oh. Well, if you're happy with it...
How's mine?
I tried drawing him, too.
So cute!
She's fine with anything as long as it's Shion.
Now, do you all remember
how I said I had a request?
Yeah.
Come this way.
What are we doing?
I want to use you as models,
since you're all here.
Huh?
You just want to take our pictures?
What do you mean by "since we're all here"?
Shima-chan.
You mean, "since all these hot
guys are here together," right?!
Yes!
It's definitely good to go back to basics.
Indeed. It seems they are
unaware of it themselves.
Maybe even some senpai-kouhai stuff here.
Simple is best. Simple is best!
Okay! Everyone, get into pairs.
Igarashi-kun with Nanashima-kun.
Mutsumi-senpai with Shinomiya-kun.
What were you two discussing?!
Looking good!
Bring your faces closer.
Lean into each other a bit.
Part your lips just a tad!
Good!
Perfect!
Now how about resting your
chin on his shoulder?
Like this?
Shinomiya-kun, you use the
same laundry detergent as me.
It smells good, doesn't it?
Stop!
This is heaven.
Next, please lay your head on the other's lap.
We're not gonna do that, idiot!
What? But you promised.
I think we've already done enough.
Shima-chan!
It'll be faster if we
show them how it's done.
Huh?
This is how you do it!
Shi    Iga    Nana    Mu
Gently lay your hand on their face,
and subtly portray love, which is good.
Plus, it's eye-catching.
Shi    Iga    Nana    Mu
Wh-What is she talking about?
Then, bring your face
closer to your partner's,
and with your eyes open...
Whoa! I-I'm sorry. I'm so embarrassed.
Senpai, you're so cute.
Iga
Mu
Shi
Nana
What the heck are you doing, Nishina?!
Huh? Was that, just now...
Tone the practical jokes down!
Just now, I...
That wasn't a joke.
S-Serinuma! That one doesn't
count, okay? It doesn't count!
Hey, idols do that stuff
in music videos all the time!
Y-Yeah! I've seen that before!
I said that wasn't a joke.
We'll have a problem if you
don't start taking me seriously.
This girl!
Serinuma Kae, 17 years old.
Her first kiss is with a handsome girl.
Serinuma-senpai, you always make food
look so delicious when you eat it.
And the way you eat is very pretty.
Really? Thank you!
I like eating with you, too!
I can eat quite a bit, though.
But you're not fat at all.
Don't tell me you're on a diet.
I haven't done anything special.
Everyone in my family's the
same way. Just good genes.
My brother is actually skinny.
Oh, maybe that's because when I was little,
I used to steal my brother's
candies and eat 'em all up!
Next time:
Back to My Original Self!
What Should I Do?
Look forward to it!
When it comes down to it,
you're pretty fond of your bro—