Christmas is just
around the corner, huh?
Do you guys already have plans?
I'm not doing anything.
Listen, Master Raku...
My father won't be home
on Christmas Eve, so...
I'll be home...
Uh, I mean, of course I'll be
spending it with Honey!
My, how callous!
Hey, since we are here, why don't
we throw a Christmas party?
You know, get together
and have a blast?
Sure, as long as the event
planner's a no-show.
Even though it was my idea?
So? What are we gonna do for real?
In our case, we really do have to...
Ch-Christmas?
Chitoge?
"Need"
Your mom's coming back?
That's right.
Every Christmas, my mom comes home,
and it's just the three of
us over the holidays,
so it doesn't look like
I can attend that party.
Why does that
make you hate Christmas?
Come to think of it,
where is your mom usually?
I mean, she doesn't
seem to be living with you.
She's traveling all over the world.
She's still working as
a high-powered female CEO.
That mom of mine...
...is incredible!
She owns companies all over the world,
and I've heard that her annual
income once topped 10 billion dollars!
Her schedule's crammed
for the next ten years,
and it's even been said
that the Nikkei Index fluctuates
according to my mom's mood that day.
She seriously sounds
like a total badass.
But most incredible of all...
She's scary when she gets mad!
Absolutely terrifying!
That scary? Really?
But she sounds like a good mom.
Spending Christmas with you
every year when she's so busy.
Is she... really?
I'm a little uncomfortable with her.
Mom had me when
she was really young,
but she's been wrapped up
in her work ever since,
so as far back as I can remember,
I've only seen her a few times a year.
Honestly, I don't really know
how it feels to have a mom.
Why should I have to
tell you all this stuff?!
You're the one who brought it up...
Dad
Incoming call
Huh? It's from Dad.
What does he want?
Whaaat?!
What's wrong?
He says Mom's
coming home tomorrow.
What? But it's not even Christmas yet.
And also...
He wants to introduce you to my mom,
so he told me to invite you!
Hey! Where the hell's
that wine I ordered?
How's the decorating going?
Is the food ready yet?
We're doing it now!
Wow...
They're unusually nimble today.
Looks like they're on high alert.
Hurry the hell up!
Madam Flower will be arriving soon!
Madam Flower?
They're talking about my mom.
Since Mom's first name is Hana Kirisaki.
I see you came dressed
in a suit, like I told you.
Do we really need to go this far?
It's just your mom coming home, right?
Don't be such an idiot!
Look, you...
try saying or doing something
funny in front of Mom!
You won't live to tell the tale!
How scary can she be?
Be on your best behavior, all right?
I'm introducing you to her
as my boyfriend, after all.
Yeah, yeah.
Still, no matter how
dressed up you get,
you wear that ribbon
no matter what, huh?
You didn't change ribbons like
you did the other day, you know?
Well, sure, I have
other ribbons, but...
But this ribbon is special.
Because Mom gave it to me years ago.
Hey, Raku! Long time no see.
Oh, hello.
Sorry to summon you on short notice.
Have you been doing okay?
Yes.
It's just been so hard, finding
time to introduce you to her.
You're welcome here.
Not at all.
Listen, Daddy has
a stomachache all of a sudden!
Would you mind
taking over from here?
You can't do that to me, Dad!
You stay right here with me!
How freaked out are you two?
Madam Flower has arrived!
She is here for real, guys!
Take your positions, everybody!
I'm home.
Welcome home, Madam!
So this is Chitoge's mom?
She's a real beauty!
I mean, she's got this amazing aura.
But... even if she had
Chitoge at a young age...
...come on, she can't be this young!
If she told me she was her
big sister, I'd believe her!
Hey, Hana...
It's been a long time!
I've missed you so!
Welcome home, my beloved wife!
Adelt!
I'm home, Adelt!
I've missed you, too!
You must be worn out
from all that hard work.
I think you've lost some
weight, haven't you?
How long can you stay in Japan?
I'll be here till Christmas night.
Although I'll only have 2 hours
and 36 minutes for myself.
Hey. What's this?
She actually looks pretty nice.
Though you weren't joking
about her crazy schedule.
Can you take a short break, maybe?
For today, we've prepared
all of your favorites.
Sorry, but it's right back
to work for me.
By the way, Adelt...
Do you remember?
Two months and 15 days ago, I asked you
to do something for me, didn't I?
Since you said you knew one of
the directors of that brokerage in Rome,
I asked you to arrange
for a deal with them.
Whatever became of that, I wonder?
W-Well, Hana, the thing is,
it's pretty complicated, so...
I'm asking you a question, Adelt.
Did you get it done?
Or not?
Which is it?
I haven't done a thing!
Lock him up in the library right away.
If you don't get it done by Christmas,
I'm going to gouge your eyeballs!
T-Terrifying!
I mean, that is a gang
boss she's talking to!
Jeez, the old guy's a total
henpecked husband!
Now, then... Is Chitoge around?
Y-Yes!
Long time no see!
Have you been well?
Uh...
how old are you now, again?
Uh, yes!
I am now sixteen years old! Mother!
"Mother"?
I see. You've grown up a lot.
What about school?
Uh, yes!
I was ranked fifth in our grade
after a test the other day.
I see... fifth?
Chitoge?
That really doesn't
make sense, does it?
That junior high you graduated from was
one of the top schools in the U.S.
And you graduated first in your class.
As for the high school
you're attending now,
I hear that it's quite average by
Japanese academic standards.
So what's wrong with this picture?
I promise to study harder!
Chitoge's so freaked out,
she's vibrating like a cell phone!
But still, this mom of hers is deadly scary.
The intimidation factor is mind-blowing!
Oh, my...
Who on earth is this?
Mother! Allow me to introduce him.
This is my boyfriend.
P-Pleased to meet you!
I'm Raku Ichijo!
Boyfriend?
Ichijo?
Ichijo, as in... surely not...
Yes. It's probably what
you're thinking of...
Ichijo as in the Shuei-gumi.
Oh, but I assure you,
I'm seeing your daughter in the most
impeccable, honorable way imaginable.
Oh? Is that right?
Please look after my
daughter, little boy.
However...
If you ever hurt her in any way,
what I'm going to do to you...
Can you imagine it?
Y-Yes.
Rest assured!
Because I'll exceed anything
you might imagine.
She's scaring me at
every turn, this woman!
Still, a boyfriend for you, eh?
My, how time flies!
So you've reached that age, have you?
What's this...
That ribbon...
You're still wearing that thing?
It's completely frayed.
A ribbon like that, I can
buy you as many as you need.
You're a girl, after all.
You need to be more stylish, or
you'll chase your boyfriend away.
Wear a prettier one, will you?
All right.
Now, then, that's it for me today.
Chitoge?
We'll have a nice chat
on Christmas Eve, all right?
I have to admit, she really was a terror.
Like a storm.
Madam, we have a problem.
Another secretary has collapsed.
Again? How many does
that make this month?
I swear, it's a mere
72-hour shift... how pathetic.
Any backups?
Actually, all of them are
still in the hospital.
Is that right? That is a problem, then.
I know.
Hey, little boy!
Starting now, till Christmas,
work as my secretary.
H-Hold on!
Mother, are you serious?!
My, my! Of course I'm serious.
I have no intention of allowing
my daughter to date a do-nothing.
The timing couldn't be better,
and I'm thinking it will give me the chance
to see for myself if he's worthy of you.
No, but that doesn't mean...
But seriously...
your secretary, all of a—
If you're not up to it, then
that's fine with me, too.
In that case, I'll have you
drowned in Tokyo Bay tomorrow.
That said...
If you do manage to gain my approval,
I'll reward you two with a night in an
ultra suite at a five-star hotel on Christmas Eve.
All right, let's go.
Carry him to the car.
Seriously?!
I'm seriously doing this?!
Ichijo... right.
That kid from ten years ago, eh?
Now, then, let's see
how you've grown.
Well, well! You do clean up nicely.
Uh... am I really gonna do this?
It's so out of the blue.
But of course!
Don't worry.
All you have to do is follow
my every order, to the letter.
For starters, skim through these.
That's my schedule for today,
and also a manual for what's
expected of you as my secretary.
Excuse me...
Memorize it all in five minutes, okay?
Yes, very well.
Put together your proposals
on how the 5 EU corporations should
make inroads into new markets.
What did the research yield?
Unbelievable... Look at
all these documents!
Is this really just her
schedule for today?
I've never seen a minute-by-minute
schedule before in my life!
Not only that... though
I can't be sure about this...
That meeting she's
been taking part in.
As far as I can tell, she's speaking in
at least five different languages!
What kind of a high-spec
mom is she, anyway?!
All right!
What's first on the agenda
today, little boy?
Oh, right!
Today, you're going to head over to...
RAKU
This company's gigantic!
What are you doing?
Get yourself over here!
I am sincerely sorry for summoning you
here on account of our blunder.
Please step on me.
Not happening! That's revolting.
The president of a major
corporation is prostrating himself!
Putting me to so much trouble
when it was your own mistake.
You certainly have some nerve.
Please accept my sincere...
She stepped on him anyway!
Just what kind of a hotshot is she?
Uh, excuse me...
Mother?
Hey...
I think it's still too early
for you to call me "Mother."
Then what should I call you?
Let's see...
As a special privilege, I'm going to
let you call me "Ms. Hana."
Th-Then Ms. Hana...
What am I supposed to do, exactly?
Right.
Okay, your first task, little boy...
Go buy a Coke
somewhere around here.
Within the next three hours.
A Coke, did you say?
Yes.
If there's anything else I need,
I'll let you know later.
This might actually be an easy job.
Hana Kirisaki
Connected
Hello? It's me.
There's something I'd like to add
to your shopping list. Do you mind?
Ms. Hana?
Yes. What should I get?
You see, the daughter of
one of my clients in Canada
is absolutely pining for a stuffed animal
that's only available at Disney*** in Japan,
so could you go get one?
Also, I want you to buy the entire line of Japan-only
limited editions of Chan** handbags. Also...
H-Hold up! Hold up a second!
Dis***?
Excuse me, but do you know
how long it'll take to travel?
Oh, but that's not my concern.
Figure it out somehow.
You can charge as much
as you need on my card.
Just make sure you do your best.
Figure it out, did she say?
And let me remind you,
I expect you to be punctual.
If, by any chance, you're late...
Killing you will only be
the tip of the iceberg.
Also, a friend of mine in L.A. has a favorite
Japanese sweet, so please get some of those, too.
Also, the son of *** in Paris wants
a figurine from Akihabara...
What's up with all this?!
I got what you asked for!
Somehow, I made it back in time!
Good job, little boy.
Kudos to you for making it back.
But what a shame.
You're thirty seconds late,
did you know that?
The fact that you were late
by thirty seconds, see...
Means that my schedule will
get pushed back thirty seconds.
A deal that could've been struck
if I'd had thirty more seconds
will end up not being
struck, in other words.
Do you understand?
My motto is, "Time is not money."
Money can't buy time.
Am I right?
Y-Yes.
As long as you understand
that, it's fine.
All right, what's my next appointment?
Right! Um...
A product meeting at AB Corp.
Well, well! That's
one of my subsidiaries.
It's the building next door.
Oh, then I'll have them
bring the car around.
That would be wasting
too much time.
Wait there for a second.
It's me. I'm coming over there
now, so do your thing.
Understood.
Um... Ms. Hana, what are you doing?
Ms. Hana! Don't tell me you're...
We've been waiting for you, Boss.
Let's start this meeting.
Just now, I thought I heard
Raku's voice from up above.
But really, look how the whole
city's in full Christmas mode.
Incoming call
Raku
From Raku?
What does he want?
Connected
Hello?
H-Hey... is that you, Chitoge?
Why do you sound like that?
I finally got to go on
a short break now, see.
But hey, I have to say...
Your mom is way
beyond demonic, huh?
I get that a lot.
So, what's up?
Oh, nothing.
I just thought you might be feeling down.
Why would I...?
Yesterday, what you really
wanted was for your mom to say,
"It makes me so happy to see you
still wearing that ribbon." Right?
It has nothing to do with you!
You know it does. It totally does.
I don't know how serious Ms. Hana was
about letting us spend the night together
on Christmas Eve if she approved of me,
but you...
What you really want is to spend
Christmas Eve with your mom, right?
I'm worried.
That the truth is my mom doesn't
have the slightest interest in me at all.
Well, this is what Mom always
asks, every time I see her.
"How old are you now?"
She can't seem to remember,
no matter how many times I tell her.
And when I do see her,
all she does is yell at me.
She never praises me, not even once.
And she's always only cold to me.
Even this...
I bet she said that as she doesn't
want to spend Christmas Eve with me.
You know that's not true!
There's no way she wouldn't
want to see her own daughter!
Hey, don't worry.
That lady's so swamped,
but she's always made a point of
coming home for Christmas at least, right?
This time, you invite her.
Tell her that you want to
spend Christmas Eve with her.
If you're honest with her about how you feel,
she might come through for you, right?
You... think so?
It's gonna be all right.
She's your mom, isn't she?
All right. I'll give it a try.
Right. Good luck to you!
Th-Thank y—
Raku
Connected
Sorry, Chitoge!
I'm getting a call from Ms. Hana!
I gotta get going!
Okay, give it all you've got!
Bye.
Be honest, huh?
Hello?
Uh... Um...
Mother? It's me.
Chitoge? Well, how unusual.
Um... Listen...
What do you want?
I'm busy with work right now,
so if we could pick this up later...
I'm sorry! This won't take long!
Um...
about letting Raku and me spend
Christmas Eve if you approved of him...
I'd like you to call that off.
Oh? But why?
M-Mother...
I... I'd like to, um, spend it with you.
Oh, that's all right.
Don't think about me.
You'd rather spend
Christmas Eve with him, right?
N-No, I...!
And besides, I've switched my schedule
to get some work done on Christmas Eve,
so either way,
it's not going to work.
Is there anything else?
No? Then I'm hanging up.
Why did you turn her down?
What are you talking about?
That call just now... it was
from Chitoge, wasn't it? So why?
Because I have work to do.
I thought I wouldn't be
spending Christmas Eve with her,
so I scheduled some
appointments beforehand.
Then at least get her
a Christmas present!
I'll go out and buy
whatever you want!
No need for that.
Never mind that,
I need to get this work done now,
since I have another appointment.
Is your job that important to you?
Why are you so into it?
Because no one can do it but me,
and because I'm needed.
If you have the ability, it's your duty
to exercise it... that's my way of thinking.
As long as I'm needed, I'll
continue to exercise my abilities.
Come on, your hands are idle, little boy.
Get those documents filed, please!
What the hell is that?
"Because no one can do it but me?"
"Because I'm needed?"
Don't you see that the person closest
to you is the one who needs you the most?
My bad, Chitoge.