Sensei! I came to play!
Huh?
Sensei!
Sensei?
Hey, you got here early.
Did you get my calligraphy?
It arrived ages ago.
STAR
Seishuu
Handa
As huge as it is, it sure looks grand.
Yeah.
STAR
Are you saying it wouldn't
look grand if it was small?!
That's how you took it?
Even if you're still an apprentice,
you're something of an art dealer, Kawafuji.
Are you only praising the size
because you don't know any better?
Or is the size the only
thing praiseworthy about it?
He's still a real pain in the ass...
Well, calm down.
The director should be here soon.
The d—!
M-May I please have a glass of water?
You're way too nervous.
Are you all right?
I Am in Tokyo
Translation:
Yoseo
What am I supposed to say to the director?
An apology, obviously.
You returned because he said he'd forgive you.
The rest depends on your state of mind.
For what it's worth, I bought a
cell phone strap to give him.
A cell phone strap? He's not
a high school girl, you know.
Exclusive
Baramon-kun
And these aren't cute at all.
If you keep sighing like that,
you'll bring me down, too.
The director is going to
look at my calligraphy soon.
What'll I do if he lambastes
it before I exhibit at Naruka?
I'll never be able to recover!
I don't think he'll do that.
You brought it because you felt
confident about it, right?
As someone who's known me
a long time, what do you think?
Would you be able to tell I wrote that?
STAR
Seishuu
Handa
When you ask me that way,
I'm not sure how to answer...
Seishuu
Handa
STAR
But I think it's good calligraphy.
Very bold and eye-catching.
I never would've imagined you
writing anything like it before.
That's my point!
Huh?
I don't write calligraphy like this!
It's too good!
Sorry, but I don't get what you're trying to say.
How do I put it...?
It just doesn't feel right!
I mean...
It just happened! I don't know how I did it!
10 Minutes Later
In short, you're saying it's a fluke?
Don't put it so simply!
But that's exactly what it is, darn it!
Anybody could write something like
that if they went to the island!
There's nothing odd about that, is there?
You don't have to beat yourself up over
using a different style than usual.
You could just describe it as
"a little experimentation."
If I keep doing that, I'll never
find my own calligraphy style.
If you're studying to be a farmer,
going fishing on a whim and catching a
hisan iwo doesn't make you a fisherman!
I want to find my own flower
and raise it until it blooms!
A flower unlike any other in the world!
The one that was always my special "only one"!
Huh? What are you talking about?
Are you implying that you
don't have to be number one?
A farmer cannot become a fisherman, you say?
That's a very amusing analogy, Handa-kun.
Director!
With both calligraphers and artists,
the successful ones are those who
perfect their own idiosyncrasies.
I'm sorry I didn't come to see you in.
No, I came to meet with Handa-kun.
No need to trouble yourself.
Now, are you doing well?
Yes, very well, sir!
Oh, no need to be so formal.
You spoke more naturally with me before.
No, I went too far last time, sir!
Calm down, calm down!
I need to properly apologize and get his forgiveness.
A cane...
The director has a bad back.
Why, thank you, Handa-kun.
Don't mention it.
No matter how upset I may have been,
how could I have hit someone who's like this?
I'm a horrible person.
What I did was truly inexcusable.
I should have apologized much sooner.
Both for punching you,
and for returning once I
knew I would be forgiven,
I am truly...
I am truly very sorry!
Director...
The truth is, I wasn't planning on forgiving you.
I only said that to lure you back here,
so I could give you a long lecture on human morality.
But it appears that won't be necessary.
Just refrain from behaving
so impulsively in the future.
I forgive you.
Handa?!
Thank goodness...
I wasn't sure what I'd do if you didn't forgive me.
Truly, sir, thank you very much.
Good for you, Handa.
Now give him the cell phone strap.
You know this isn't the time for that!
Now then, Handa-kun.
Yes, sir!
I wish to see your calligraphy up close.
Could you lend me a hand?
R-Right!
STAR
So this is what you wrote
after taking time to mature?
Yes...
U-Um...
It's...
Uhh...
Handa-kun.
This calligraphy is—
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
And I just told you not to behave impulsively...
Don't laugh, don't laugh, don't laugh...
This calligraphy is a test work!
That's right! I drew it for practice!
My submission for the exhibition is still
packed up, so I couldn't bring it here!
I see!
True, it is unreasonable to expect to see
your work this close to the deadline.
Y-Yes, sir! I'm sorry that I showed
you this trashy calligraphy!
Hey, Handa...
Well then, I'll appraise this as a test work.
You've written something so interesting,
I wouldn't have recognized it as yours.
The character is one you'd see
in a grade school assignment,
but in it, I can see the stars of the night sky.
It shows the hopelessness of
being left behind in the dark,
along with the light that's only visible in darkness.
Although I wouldn't be the only one to judge it,
I would deem it worthy of a grand prize.
Thank you very much!
Now I really look forward to it.
If this is a test work,
then I should see some even more
wonderful calligraphy at Naruka.
This has been a most fruitful day.
I'll stop by again.
Oh, Director, let me call you a taxi.
Now I've done it...
Kawafuji House of Art
Director...
I don't need a taxi.
My ride is waiting for me.
Oh, I see...
Thank you very much for coming!
So he came by car...
Isn't that car...
It appears that sending Seishuu-kun
to the island was the correct decision.
He still has a long way to go.
Wh-What's wrong?
I'm sorry, the engine stalled.
I'm not very good at starting up slopes.
We're both awkward,
my son and I.
I-I'm scared! I'm scared!
Hey, Handa!
It looks like your dad was...
Hey! What's wrong?!
Ship me back to the island...
Hello!
My, it's been quite a while, Kawafuji-kun!
Handa, I'm coming in.
You're late...
Guess I'll leave...
Don't run away, cold-hearted jerk!
Judging by how you look,
I'm guessing you haven't gotten anywhere.
Right.
What's that on your head?
An attempt to get back the
form you had on the island?
Right.
I thought it'd give me at least a little inspiration.
The deadline for the exhibition is tomorrow!
This isn't the time to be doing stuff like that!
Do you have to scold me like that?
I tried writing "Star" in the same way as before.
Yeah, with that flavor,
you could aim for grand prize!
If you wrote it the exact
same way, then it's a cinch!
STAR
Seishuu
Handa
Now it really is like a grade school assignment.
I knew you'd say that!
I tried to write it exactly
the same way, but I can't!
No matter how hard I stare at the night sky,
the city lights are too bright for me to get anxious!
I can't write! I can't! I can't!
That makes it this much different from before?
It turns out I'm more influenced
by my environment than I ever knew.
So you were only stable before
because you'd never had any
major distress in your life.
But you've always entered
exhibitions before, haven't you?
So make it work.
It's not that simple!
Would I bother calling someone like you
over if I could manage this by myself?!
"Someone like you"? How could
you say that to your only friend?
There's nothing I can do f—
Wrong!
There is but one thing you can do for me.
Wai—
Sei-san, the tea is ready.
What is the point of this, again?
Hold still! I can't tie it if you're moving!
Sensei, who am I supposed to be?
I don't even like children that much.
Shut up!
All you have to do is keep quiet and cry!
B-Bondage?!
Oh, might you be Sensei's mother?
Pardon the intrusion!
What? Mom?!
Sei-san...
What on earth are you doing?
Oh! This isn't what it looks like!
It's to help me write calligraphy!
Incidentally, Kawafuji-san is playing Naru-chan,
I'm telling you, it's not like that, Mom! Mom?!
while I'm a crybaby first grader!
Mother
He used to be a good boy.
Though never very sociable,
he was kind at heart, the type young people
would call "prickly-sweet," and beloved by all.
And yet, now he's become "prickly-stupid"?!
Neither part of that is lovable at all!
This is all because he went to that island!
Wait! Mom?!
That's not what...
You all right?
I'm not, but...
this just felt very reminiscent of the island.
But isn't it simplistic to
expect to write good calligraphy
just by reenacting things you did on the island?
Don't get in my bed!
Just ditch the calligraphy you could only write
on the island, and hurry back here to Tokyo!
Hey! Quit digging around!
I knew you had a porn stash!
Hey!
For real?!
Calligrapher
Don't throw it out!
If you're not in the exhibition, Sensei,
then I don't feel like doing it, either.
The prize money isn't all that much,
and it's not like it'd make me really famous.
Maybe I'll write a bunch and
hold a one-man exhibition...
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you realize how much I have
riding on this exhibition?
Sure, it's not a major exhibition.
But to me, it's a crucial first step
toward a new start in life.
I will definitely take that step.
Sensei...
Hey! What are you recording?!
My famous quotes collection!
Why did you call this kid over, anyway?
I thought just Naru wouldn't be
enough to bring out the mood.
Sensei!
He's irritating me!
Well, thanks to him,
now I can see how serious you are.
Here's some help from me.
A phone call?
Incoming
In Call
Hello?
Well? Is he on?
Sensei?
Oh, did he answer?
Sensei! You good?
Hey! Put me on, too!
Why are you guys...
He's on!
Hello! Sensei, you doin' good?!
Kawafuji-san asked us to talk to
you because you seemed lonely.
Hey, Akki! Ain't ya done talkin'?!
So we all gathered at the store.
Sensei! Are you well?!
Kawa-san may be nice,
but Hiro-nii is deeply worried about you, too!
Why're you talking like that?
Tch!
Hello?
Since you left without saying anything,
My turn!
it's been nuts over here.
Gimme it!
I see.
Sorry about th—
Sensei!
Are you doing well?!
Quit sayin' pointless stuff!
Or I'm gonna feed ya my fist!
What you need most are friends, right?
You should thank me.
Hey, me next!
Ow! Quit it!
In Call
You're on my foot!
Yeah.
Sensei! Are you well?!
Thanks.
He actually thanked me.
That hurts my ears! Take turns talking!
Sensei, yer comin' back, right?
When're ya comin'?
I thought up a good punishment for
ya leavin' without sayin' anythin'!
You guys...
This is Akki.
Hi, Akki.
I heard you were distressed over
not being able to do good work.
I can't believe how considerate you are.
Your consideration would put adults to shame.
I think I'll be fine, if I can stir up some
inspiration by remembering the island.
Yeah... Y-Yeah, yeah.
He's seriously discussing his worries with a child.
Well, I'm not exactly in a slump,
but when I need to write, I just can't do it.
I don't understand.
Hey! Tell me before you switch, you guys!
They're messing with him.
Looks fun.
Sensei...
Is this Naru?
Yep.
It's borin' without you here, Sensei.
There's still gobs of stuff I wanna do with ya.
An' so...
Please come home real soon.
We're waitin' for ya!
Think you can write now?
Yeah.
I think I had...
Sensei, are you looking for something?
Well, I'm not sure if I brought it with me or not,
but since it was from the last
job I did there, then maybe...
Here it is...
A list of names?
Ink...
Grind me lots of ink!
Kanzaki, go buy paper for writing practice!
Why do I have to do it?!
At last, he's taking action.
I just hope he doesn't do anything strange again.
I was against this from the beginning.
I don't want him going to that island again!
In that case, you should persuade him not to go.
You're so cruel!
He's already decided he wants to go!
Are you telling me to hurt him?!
You're so cruel!
Cruel! Cruel! Cruel! Cruel!
We also share the responsibility for
Sei becoming "all work and no play."
It's not for us to dictate
our son's direction in life.
If leaving here will allow him to grow,
then all we can do is watch over him.
Dear... If that's the path a man must take...
Whoa! It's Handa Seimei!
He's so dignified! So cool!
Will you quit it?!
Hey! Wake up, Kawafuji!
What time is it?
It's finished.
A work done using all my ability.
Well?
Isn't it incredible?
I've never done calligraphy like this before.
What's the title?
"Stone Wall."
I heard they've displayed our summer
vacation homework in the hallway!
Let's go check it out!
It's come...
Yes, the time has come.
I can't wait to see it!
I bet we'll win gold prizes!
Sensei would be so thrilled if we did!
Let's get double-gold and
give him a big surprise!
Sensei'd better thank God for
givin' him such capable disciples!
Yay!
Gold Prize
Class 2-1 Arai Tamako
Learning From the Past
Class 2-1
Yamamura
Miwa
Silver
Later, Miwa-chan.
I'm going to the restroom.
Why only Tama?
Miwa-chan, just snap out of it already!
It's all over...
I can't face Sensei now.
What's wrong with a silver prize?
It's still second place.
There's a world of difference
between first and second!
You're that mad?!