How does Chimera look?
She is eating, but I still think
she's under the weather.
Maybe we should take her to the vet.
She probably just ate too much.
I don't know.
Although Rikka was feeding her lots
for what she called "Project Super-Size."
Honestly. So, where is Rikka?
I think she's still sleeping.
Arise, Wicked Lord Shingan!
The time of awakening is nigh!
The Light! The Light Beings are
roasting me alive!
Yuta, give me darkness!
Roast to your heart's content.
What is it?
Nothing.
Togashi, morning!
Good morning.
It's the start of the second term.
Yeah!
Where's Rikka?
Well, we were leaving for school...
The Superior Contract...
of Twilight
and she ran off by herself
saying she was going ahead.
Really.
Buongiorno!
Nibutani?
Nibutani.
Ciao! How was your long vacation?
Nibutani, you know...
You seem to get a little weird
every time there's a new term.
See you in second term!
They're talking about you, Nibutani.
Morisummer is as funny as ever!
Kumin-senpai.
Huh?
Yes, I only have eyes for you.
Yikes! Really, who are you?!
I only have eyes for you, Kumin-senpai.
I am devoted to you, Kumin-senpai!
An exchange student?
Probably.
Bye.
See ya.
See? She wasn't like this before
summer vacation.
You probably shrank.
Hey, Togashi.
Yo.
What are you staring at?
Yikes!
You stare longingly after
Rikka without saying a word to
each other right after summer vacation.
Did you break up?
No!
Did your love cool off in the hot summer?
You're wrong! If you wanna know,
it's the opposite!
The opposite? Do you mean,
you spent the entire summer...
Did you defile my master?!
No! Where did you come from anyway?!
How about it?
Why are you in this press corps?
And you're back to normal.
It's all right. There's no need to be shy.
Statistically speaking, the second year
of high school is when...
I-i-is that true?!
That's just what the statistics say.
I don't want to discuss
it! Anyway, you're wrong!
Then what's the deal?
Nothing.
It's just that Rikka's been
acting off all morning.
You didn't treat my master cruelly, I trust?
Hey, did you talk with Shichimiya
in an overly friendly way again?
No, no, no! I know I'm dense,
but I know better than that.
In fact, Rikka practically goes over
to visit her every day.
Really?
They've really hit it off since then.
Rikka! Hey, Rikka!
Togashi wants to whisper
sweet nothings to you.
Wha-?!
Rikka?
Master.
I see what you mean. She is a bit off.
Nah, anyone would wanna run from that.
Blow to smithereens, fruitful offline life!
You mean Wicked Lord Shingan?
Yeah.
Do you know anything about it?
You just go home.
Ow!
You go home!
Who is in the most pain?
Did she mention anything out of the ordinary?
She always comes with me on my angel hunts.
She's helping out since I helped revive
the Dark Flame Dragon.
But...
But?
She said she was thinking of entering
a Superior Contract with Hero.
Superior Contract?
Yeah. Now that the Dark Flame Dragon
has been revived,
she thinks it's necessary
as a contract holder.
Superior Contract?
If memory serves me, those two
are bound by a Lover's Contract.
An Superior Contract would have to mean...
Wh-why are you turning red?!
Get your mind out of the gutter!
What's that?! You're the
one who's turning red!
You sure have a dirty mind for a freshman!
Moron! I do not!
My mind is clean!
I know you're lying!
I bet you were imagining Takanashi
taking off her clothes and...
Yuta.
Don't say it! Don't say it! Don't say it!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Not that.
She meant kissing.
O-of course.
I'm home!
Welcome back!
How is Chimera?
She's acting the same as earlier.
KISSING, HOW BOYS FEEL
Rikka?
Yes? What?
Nothing, just seeing if you were here.
You didn't have to come along, Togashi.
How come?
Because we have girl talk to do.
Isn't that right, Takanashi?
Yes.
So, this is the famous Faerie Spring?
Any type of spirit may live here. Caution.
I got it, Wicked Lord Shingan!
I hope you're not planning to butt in
where you're not wanted again.
Did you hear anything?
Maybe! C'mon, Takanashi. Let's go.
Yes.
So, why are you here?
Huh?
Was there any particular reason
we needed to come to a bath house?
It does the job.
This way, Togashi can't interfere
and Takanashi can't run away.
Plus there are no weapons to attack with.
Eat this!
Although I didn't factor in
that this idiot might come along.
It serves you right.
Deko, come over here. They have funny baths!
What? What is it?
Ooh, it's a sonic training area!
Master, you must come!
When my meditation is done.
Honestly.
But this works. Now's my chance.
MIKAN
Soak away the daily fatigue
in our four seasons bath.
Takanashi, what are you doing?
I am in deep concentration
to prepare for the inevitable.
The inevitable?
That I cannot say.
Do you mean...
The Superior Contract?
You're so obvious!
Nibutani, are you reading my thoughts?!
It's a Morisummer miracle!
Don't call me that!
Danger! Break away!
I'm surprised.
Ooh, dynamite!
I will join this battle!
Itty bitty.
Uh... Pretty!
You shut up!
Want some, Mjolnir Hammer?
You want to kill me?!
He said that?
Yes. When the Dark Flame Dragon
was brought back to life,
my part of the Contract
became more solidified.
Yet nothing has changed.
Stay!
He restricts my activities.
Solve this correctly, and you can have this.
And he believes that I will obey
if he rewards me with something black.
Wake up!
And he is heavy-handed with me
in spite of my contractual status.
He probably thinks that saying
"dark" will please me!
Ooh, Master has gone wild!
That's why you want to enter
a Superior Contract?
Yes. Otherwise it will never change.
Now the Dark Flame Dragon has been revived,
the Contract must be revised accordingly.
But...
The more I think about it,
the more I feel I might dissolve away.
That is why I have a favor to ask.
A favor?
I want you to watch me
to make sure I don't run.
Rikka.
Master.
Understood, Wicked Lord Shingan.
Stop that.
Someone is in love with you?!
Yeah. Remember how
I had a lifeguard job at the pool?
That's when it happened.
It's someone named Chihiro.
That's great!
So your time has come!
You're wrong! I'm not bragging about it.
I'm devoted to Kumin-senpai all the way!
That's why I worked
all through summer vacation.
So I could buy her a present. But for what?!
Makoto?
Chihiro...
"Chihiro"?
WHAT?!
Makoto, I've missed you.
You mean, Chihiro is a...?
Chihiro.
Chihiro?!
Makoto, we must be joined by
the Red Thread of Fate
to run into each other in a place like this.
Ah, just stop. I am... I am...
Isshiki!
MEN
Isshiki, I wish you happiness.
You didn't find out anything?
That's right. This one time,
Takanashi was very tight lipped.
She said she'd tell you herself.
Herself?
Yeah. She wants you to
come here after school.
BASE
COME HERE
Be sure to go. She looked serious.
Sure.
Bye.
Rikka.
How'd it go?
That was nothing for me.
It was almost too easy.
What?
Nothing. I was just thinking how much
you really love us, Morisummer.
Don't call me that.
You're supposed to respect me.
Master, that's crooked.
Mjolnir Hammer, it's almost time.
We have to hide.
I know that!
It is time, Master. Godspeed!
Wait! I can't go through with it!
Master.
Y-you traitors!
Wicked Lord Shingan, you asked us
to make sure you didn't run.
I changed my mind!
There are many other
higher contract categories
in Wicked Lord Shingan's
selection of Lover's Contracts!
There is a diverse variety...
Wicked Lord Shingan is all-powerful!
You can't run away now.
That's what you've always done, right?
You conquered your fear...
Met Hero...
Dove into his arms...
And entered into a binding contract with him.
You did all this because
Wicked Lord Shingan is all-powerful.
You made it this far because of
Wicked Lord Shingan.
So you have to believe in him.
Believe in your own strength.
Sophia.
Wicked Lord Shingan really is all-powerful.
The emotions have such power.
I will give you all the power I've got.
Deko.
Stop taking so long!
Togashi will arrive soon.
I am fully aware of that
without your information!
Wicked Lord Shingan, it is
all the natural logic of the world.
He's here!
Quick, hide.
Hey, what's up? Did you make a new discovery?
Y-Yuta Togashi!
Or should I say, Dark Flame Master.
Or should I say, Ghelzonianses!
Pick one and stick with it.
I command you to enter into a
Superior Lover's Contract with
myself and Wicked Lord Shingan.
Superior Contract?
If you cannot determine its significance,
then you are a fool!
Surely you don't mean... But why?
My demands have been stated.
The hows and whys of the world
mean nothing to the Wicked Lord!
But...
Will you or will you not? Choose!
Just kidding. I didn't mean to do that!
Yuta.
Perfect defense.
Shall we go?
No!
Hold my shoulders so I can't escape.
Got you!
Look.
No! I was momentarily possessed
by something dark, that's all.
I'm all right now.
You're sure?
I'm sure.
I don't get it.
I want to get closer to you.
I want to be with you,
but it's so embarrassing.
It makes me feel so scared and embarrassed.
I'm too scared. Why am I so scared?
Rikka.
We already talked about this.
There's no need to force ourselves to change.
It's not healthy.
But I am bound to you for eternity.
I am bound to you by contract.
That is why Sophia entrusted
everything to me.
Wicked Lord Shingan.
I must consummate the emotion
she entrusted to me!
That is my mission.
I'm sorry. I thought I
knew how hopeless I was...
...but I'm worse at it than I thought.
You really thought it through.
Yuta.
Rikka, remember how you told me?
We would spend fun time together...
...and go home together.
You said that nothing could make you happier.
Yeah.
I feel the same.
We live in the same apartment,
go to school together...
...go home together, eat together....
...play video games together,
get mad, and laugh.
It could feel like such a drag,
and then feel like such a relief.
Every one of those things is happiness.
It's better than any hugs and kisses
or other things that lovers do.
It makes me happy, and it makes me
feel very close to you.
Rikka, you will always
be the only one for me.
Yuta...
Yuta, Yuta, Yuta!
Besides, it is gradually changing.
We couldn't do stuff like this a year ago.
Yeah.
In the beginning it was pinkies.
Next we held hands.
It's happening slowly, but it is changing.
HOME
Oh, that's me.
Deko.
I knew this would happen.
What?! Chimera did what?
Yeah!
She had babies!
Say what?!
Come home quick, Big Brother!
Got it! I'll be right there!
Babies?
Yeah, our family is growing.
Ooh! Chimera Two!
"Two," nothing. There are six of 'em.
Six! A chimaeric beast army!
Yeah!
Hold it.
You're not going to let it
end like this, are you?!
Why are you mad at me? Why are you here?
Do it! I practically raised you two!
The least you could do
is to let us watch you do it!
"Watch you do it?"
Do not make it sound so vulgar!
Yuta, escape!
Right!
She's getting away! Hold it right there, you!
Master!
What will happen next?
What will become of Rikka's chunibyo?
What will become of our love?
Who knows?
But Rikka and I have always
held on to one thought.
This one thought from the very beginning.
This one thought we will always hold on to!
"EVEN THOUGH I'M IN CHUNIBYO,
I STILL WANT LOVE!"
THE END