As I wait...
We touched it at the same time!
But it was on my side, so I get it!
All right!
Trit-Trot
That was mine...
It was mine.
I was faster.
Trit-Trot
I could tell.
What?  But...
Megumu...
I was slightly faster!
...is contesting a card!
Don't be ridiculous, Yu-chan.
The leader of this team is me.
The person who can make
everyone happy is me.
The one who will challenge the Queen
is me!
I gave up the card she contested,
but that makes up for the earlier one.
It's fine, Ayase.
Just be your usual self.
Okay...
Time to attack!
Mizusawa!
Yeah!
Okay, one card!
One card!
One card at a time!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 14
People
would
always ask
if I was
pining for
someone
"The emotions," "All," "May my lonely," "My fear is not," "As my,"
"So spring ends," "Feel love," "Long," "While the," "I feel that,"
"My fear is that," "May it," "The fall wind," "The hazed...light,"
"Rain," "Feel sorrow," "As I," "So spring nights," "A night," "Nobody," "I feel as,"
"No more," "While it brings," "Impassioned vows," "My only...the," "Note that,"
"My life," "The hazed...mist," "A house," "I hear," "No matter," "Silent,"
"The sound of birds," "When I," "Nothing," "When the," "Look," "As this,"
"As friends," "While autumn," "May I live," "Swift," "While it may," "In order to,"
"When winds blow," "Since I," "Would this," "A mountain stream," "While I,"
"Said bed," "May the time we," "The night," "For the," "My own home,"
"A mountain village," "The tail," "After many," "May my sighs," "Since the,"
Sh-Sho-chan, she hasn't
taken a breath.
She isn't breathing...
"The sky is," "Though I," "So the flower petals," "Impassioned was," "The storm will," "I wish"...
Arata, this is no simple
letter of remorse!
It's a work of literature!
It deserves to be published!
Stop reading it.
This is better than Kawabata
Yasunari and Natsume Soseki!
You're exaggerating.
Aren't you leaving, Arata?
I'm staying here as
part of my punishment.
I won't leave until the
tournament's over.
You ooze integrity.
Brings tears to my eyes.
Once my uniform is dry, I'll be leaving.
Oh, sorry I'm late!
Coach!  Tajiri!  You're late!
Way too late!
Sorry about that.
The engine stalled just when we got
close, and we had to call JAF.
Since we knew we were disqualified,
we stopped for gyudon on the way.
What?!
Wait, is that Queen Wakamiya?
It's really her!
Why are you skinny now?
What diet did you use?
Tajiri!
I saw the results downstairs.
It looks like Shoyo from Kyoto is out.
They lost to Mizusawa from Tokyo.
Oh, that's too bad.
I should have been
there for their match.
Mizusawa?!
Mizusawa won?!
Are they still in?!
Mizusawa beat Shoyo to
make the top four,
and now they're playing First Akashi Girls'
from Hyogo in the semi-finals.
An impressive run for an unknown school.
They're winning.
They're playing hard.
Taichi...  Chihaya...
Team matches are so nice.
Like a fun type of recreation.
It's fun to do things together,
karuta or otherwise.
I find it relaxing to watch.
How can she relax?!
"All," "As this," "Like the," "I feel that," "Impassionate," "Since the,"
"May my lonely," "Impassioned vows," "Like a," "The emotions,"
"The hazed...light," "I know," "As the first," "As my,"
"When I," "The fall paddy," "Silent," "My fear is that,"
"After I heard," "When winds blow," "No more," "Would the,"
"Long," "The sound of birds," "The sight of Mount,"
"Though my," "As the years," "While I," "When the,"
Team tournament?
That's for players who don't love karuta.
"While the," "My life," "Would this,"
"A mountain village," "Said night," "My only...I"...
Arata, I might not present
much of a challenge,
but why don't we play a match now?
We can kill some time.
She's looking to kill more than time!
I can't play.
Why not?
Today is a day for teams.
Forgive me then.
Shinobu-chan considers matches
a way to kill time.
Because she's too strong...
Wh-Why?
Everybody's watching this match.
Is the other match too one-sided?
Hokuo already dropped three games?!
What's that?!
They're good...
This year's Fujisaki team is
better than their reputation!
Still, I didn't expect the First
Akashi Girls' vs. Mizusawa match
to be more exciting than the
Hokuo vs. Fujisaki match.
Mizusawa came out of nowhere.
They don't have any
experienced supervision,
yet those kids are able
to play this well.
I came here to cheer for
my friends from Tokyo.
If Wataya Arata-kun came
here to watch Mizusawa...
It's too late.  Their match is almost over.
She's good...
More strong than good, actually.
When I try to contest cards, she gives
me a scary look, so I back down.
I don't like to argue with girls in the first place...
Excuse me.
Megumu made these headbands for us.
But if I want to become Queen,
Megumu's my rival now!
Sorry about that.
Forget it.
I'm treating you like a boy!
You're weaker than Megumu!
Okay, I won!
One win for First Akashi Girls'!
N-Not again...
Not in such an important match!
What are you doing, Nishida-senpai?!
I'm calling you Porky-senpai
from now on!
It's settled!
Yes!
Yuube-senpai got us a win!
Yuu-chan took the first win from me!
Swoon!
Akashi is the first team on the board.
Can they pull out the win,
or will Mizusawa hold them off?
Only seven cards remain...
I can look up and see the
snowy cap of Mt. Fuji
Rain takes longer...
No way!
Megumu even lost her "Rain" card?!
Who is this girl, to do that
to the West representative?!
Ousaka Megumu...
That name is perfect for a karuta player.
What are you talking about, Yu-chan?
All the syllables in both Ousaka and Megumu
correspond to single-syllable words.
"Long," "Rain," and "Silent."
Why "Silent waves"?
Because the "mu" in Megumu is for
dream, like in the second verse.
Because the "mu"
means dream
In that case, those are cards
I can't lose, not even to the Queen.
Megumu...
One win for Pizusawa!
Pizusawa?
She slipped up!
But...
Kana-chan!
That's one win!
Oe-senpai held on to win!  Amazing!
A win immediately after
losing the first game...
That was perfect timing.
That's big...
It eases the pressure
from the first loss.
Mizusawa is a good team.
Six cards...
That's the number of cards
remaining on the field,
but there are more to worry about.
Does she know that?
"Though my," "Like a," "After I determined,"
"Impassioned vows," "For the,"
"So the flower petals," "A house," "A mountain
village," "Said world grants no escape,"
"When winds send," "I wish,"
"I feel as," "Nothing," "As the first,"
"My fear is that," "While I,"
"The sound of people," "The fall paddy."
There are still 18 dead cards!
The fall paddy...
Ah, a fault!
Good!
A dead card.
Six cards remain on the field.
The match could go either way now.
The West representative,
Ousaka-san, could even lose!
I never knew there was such
a strong player out there.
I lost "Silent" and "Rain."
Her speed is real.
This girl...
Ayase Chihaya...
as my sleeves are wet with dew
Impassioned gods...
Got it!
Two wins for Mizusawa!
Yes!  Our best card!
Did Chihaya
lose "Impassioned"?
the red that is the Tatsuta River
This is payback for "Silent" and "Rain."
Megumu-tan held a grudge!
Amazing!
"Impassioned vows" and "Impassioned
was" haven't been read yet,
so even Bellatrix was playing it safe!
This time, the girl in
glasses went aggressive.
This is a match between two
girls seeking to become Queen!
Mizusawa now leads 2-1.
If they win one more game,
they'll advance to the finals.
Hokuo lost 1-4...
That's pathetic!
Mori!  Is that a video?!
Have you forgotten you're
in the photography club?!
You can't capture her speed,
even with continuous shots.
Th-They're so fast.
She barely beat her opponent.
Megumu-tan is getting faster.
Because of her opponent.
We want to watch
as you battle with strong friends,
encounter strong enemies,
and realize your true potential!
I feel as though I am like
the Izumi river split,
Megumu-chan...
Let's work hard...
Let's work hard!
We can't let
Shinobu-chan be alone forever!
What is it?
people would always ask if I was pining for someone
I thought I heard
"Since I could" being read.
Chihaya-chan...
No matter how much it may hurt,
you must show your respect.
Thank you very much.
She won!
She lost.
First Akashi Girls' has 2 wins...
Mizusawa has 2 wins...
Desktomu-kun!
His opponent has "The sight of Mount,"
while Komano has "May my lonely"
in a luck of the draw.
There are four more dead cards...
Everyone's watching!
people would always ask if
I was pining for someone
I can't stand this!
I can't bear the fact that our
team's fate is on the line!
I can't bear to watch!
Though my hatred has waned...
So the flower petals...
I wish I could show the
people how my sleeves
It's not over yet?!
Excuse me.
Karuta is hard and scary.
I got nervous when
Porky called me out...
It's scary.
This is the last game...
to decide the match!
Said world grants no escape
Komano, have you noticed?
There aren't any more dead cards!
The next card will decide
the game!
It's scary...
But...
I hide in the mountains, only to
hear the haunting cry of a deer
I'll always have...
The sight of Mount Arima...
Thank you very much.
Desktomu-kun...
Desktomu-kun!
Mizusawa High School defeats
First Akashi Girls' 3-2.
Thank you very much.
The final will be between Fujisaki
High School and Mizusawa High School.
Please return to your
seats in 15 minutes.
That was incredible.
The second-years really gave it their all.
Megumu-tan...  Will we get it?
Will we get it?
Will we finally get a rare
shot of Megumu-tan's tears?!
Here it comes!
Memory wipe time!
She was quick today
Can you give me this data?
You were taking pictures during
the whole match, right?
Give them all to me.
Let me see them.
Megumu-tan...
Wait!  Those are the battery
packs, not the SD cards!
That was my last time
playing karuta on this team.
Megumu?
It's all over.
I always thought that I
would stop playing karuta
once I could no longer play with all of them.
We'll help, so let's practice until
you're invested enough to get upset.
Good Luck Megumu
I'm so stupid.
I'm upset after winning.
I can't stop...
Okay, it's finally time to face Fujisaki!
Pay attention to the following points.
Desktomu-kun...
You're incredible, Desktomu-kun!
Incredible!
Why did you go after "The sight
of Mount" in that luck of the draw?
Did you hear it?
Of course not.
I was gambling.
Going from the data from
the matches I've watched,
there's a slightly higher chance of a "The" card
being read in a luck of the draw.
That's all it was.
Anyway, for the final lineup,
I think we should stick
with the second-years.
Statistically, he had a 50%
chance of guessing right,
but I've heard people say...
I've heard Master mention that before...
There are all kinds of superstitions
when it comes to luck of the draw.
Some only go for three-syllable cards
that have become one-syllable cards.
Or they believe that a
"The" card will be read.
Superstitions...
Desktomu-kun has only been playing
karuta for 15 months,
but he's already formed
his own superstitions.
Desktomu-kun is learning...
I'll always have my data to help me,
and I'm sure it'll help everyone else.
The grand final...
Our team won, but I lost...
Why?
When the score was 2-2,
Megumu-chan took "May my sighs,"
then sent "Since I."
It's one of my better cards,
but I lost it at the very end.
What could I have done better?
I was able to identify
Megumu-chan's weaknesses.
I was able to conquer my own.
What could I have done better?
Nail marks...
I was using that much strength?
Relax...
This is the final.
A voice mail from Mr. Matoba?
The Mizusawa concert band?!
They lost their competition
in the regional preliminary.
No boost for us this time.
What is it, Tsukuba-kun?
I have a request, Ms. Miyauchi.
Order them to replace
Oe-senpai with me.
Use your authority as the advisor!
There you go again.
If you just want attention, stop it.
That's not it!
I'm not doing this for attention!
But I'm here!
I'm scared about going up
against Fujisaki in the final,
but I'm still a member of the team!
Please, Tsukuba-kun...
Do I look that tired?
Huh?
I'm just fine.
I can play another match.
That was a lie.
Tsukuba-kun, please win for me.