The Third Plate
Four
The 92nd
Moon Festival
Welcome!
Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup!
Kuga Restaurant
Wow, the rumors weren't wrong.
The Chinese Cuisine RS packs quite a punch.
How about some black pepper buns?
Totsuki Culinary Teahouse Academy
Famous Taiwanese
Black Pepper Buns
We also have sorta-danzi noodles!
Yuki-chan, Ryoko-chan!
What's going on?
What about the taro stew booth?
We're taking turns going on break.
More importantly, are you
guys turning a profit?!
Um, our sales improved thanks to our
new sorta-danzi noodles on the item,
but we still have a lot to make
up for from the first day.
Day 4
Final Day
Day 1
Day 2
Day 3
Seriously?
Yukihira-chin...
Oh, Kuga-senpai.
Would you like a black pepper bun?
Nope!
I hear you've been scurrying around at night.
You've broadened your offerings, too,
but this is day three, you know?
It's not exactly pleasant to have
you in front of my establishment
with your poor sales performance.
Why won't you close up shop
for us, say, right now?
Close up, close up, close up!
I'll never forget that you were here, so!
Let's close up, stat, yeah?
Just do it, okay?
Just go. Leave now!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Close up, close up!
What the hell? What an asshole.
Wow, what's this line for? Whose booth is it?
It's Sichuan cuisine!
Want to try it?
Oh?
Here, here!
Sorry, please go to the end of the line!
Kuga Restaurant is eager to serve you!
Why'd Yukihira pick such a hopeless battle?
He's too reckless.
It's nothing new, but...
You know, Soma-kun was
saying something yesterday.
About Chinese Cuisine RS...
Do you think their booth's getting
everything right from A to Z as a restaurant?
So, yeah.
Huh? But...
They're doing so well, though.
Yes, but...
Soma-kun hasn't given up yet.
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Main Tournament
Finalist
(Winner)
Main Tournament
Finalist
Prelims
Top 8
Prelims Top 8
Main Tournament
Finalist
Lost
Money
Hup! Hup! Hup!
Pride of Young Lions
Seriously?
Wow, that's super helpful.
Yeah. Thanks, Tomita-san!
Okay, he's going to get it for us.
I also really want lots of what
we talked about around our booth,
but I'm not sure I have anyone
I can hit up for that.
I might be able to help with that.
Just focus on recipe testing, Soma-kun.
Okay.
Oh, captain, hello?
Um, I have a favor to ask...
It's done...
Soma-kun, this is amazing!
With this on the menu...
Yup, let's roll.
Tomorrow's Saturday, so there will
be even more visitors than before.
It'll be a bull's-eye.
Moon Festival  Day 4
Kuga Restaurant
Good morning, all!
Our Chinese Cuisine RS scored yet another
victory in top sales in the Central Area!
I only have high praise for you all!
Let's keep up the same pace today!
Yes, sir!
Only two more days left, Tsukasa-san.
I am the monster Xiao Long Bao Man!
Fresh Fish
I am the monster Ground Chicken Skewer Man!
I am the monster
Fresh Assorted Sashimi Platter Man!
We're the Totsuki Squad, Gastron!
You evil food monsters shall perish!
Gastron! Good luck!
Wow!
It's the legendary cooking manga,
Knife-kun Ajiro!
It's a complete first printing set!
That's super rare!
It smells so good!
I can't stand it!
So good.
Wow!
One, please.
Me, too!
Piping hot!
It's so fragrant.
So good!
So spicy!
Spicy!
But so good!
Hup! Hup! Hup!
Um, Captain Kuga!
Look...
Huh?
Wow...
Yeah!
Hey, thanks for this, Tomita-san!
I can't say no to you, Soma-chan.
Besides, they were just gathering dust
in the shopping district's warehouse.
Still...
That other place is so out of this world.
Are you sure these benches will work?
Yeah, I'm super grateful for them.
Oh, Tomita-san, please have a bite
before you go as a sign of our thanks.
Oh, really?
I haven't had your food in a while.
I can enjoy Yukihira Diner's taste again.
You're not very smart,
are you, Yukihira-chin?
This is what you finally came up
with after wracking your brains?
You think you can just up your customer
numbers by increasing seat numbers?
That's pretty simplistic, isn't it,
even if you know you can
never beat my flavors?
It's true that this is my first Moon Festival,
and I'm a newcomer to the scene who
only transferred here six months ago.
But as far as my experience in the service
industry with actual restaurants goes...
I've got about ten years on you, Senpai.
Besides...
What?!
What's he making?!
It's mapo tofu!
He's going to face Kuga Terunori
head-on with mapo tofu?!
Here, Soma-kun!
Thanks!
He's adding noodles to the mapo tofu.
I see. It's mapo noodles.
He's put a bit of a twist on it,
but that doesn't mean it's anything novel!
It's laughable that he's trying to go
up against Chinese Cuisine RS
with so little impact!
What?!
What's that?!
What's with that giant meatball?!
Besides, I told you, didn't I?
I told you I'm going to win with my cooking.
Let's get back.
Meatballs are nothing unusual.
They're just for show!
Indeed!
That meatball...
Dig in, Tomita-san.
Thanks!
Huh?
Soma-chan, what's this?
Never mind that.
Please start by trying it without
touching the meatball, if you can.
Hmm...
This is the Yukihira taste!
This is the mapo tofu I've eaten before!
The stable umami that almost makes
you keep wanting to eat it every day!
The pairing with the noodles is spot-on, too!
Well done, Soma-chan!
But...
Thank you for waiting!
Here's Kuga Restaurant's
Specially-Made Authentic Mapo Tofu!
So spicy!
Spicy!
I can't stop!
This is hardly enough to beat
their far more dominating food.
That opponent has no weaknesses.
Is that really true, though?
Huh?
It's difficult for even a veteran
professional with decades of experience
to completely please every
single one of their customers.
How much longer?
I'm tired of waiting.
I'm hungry.
I wonder when I can get in.
Excuse me, sir.
During peak times,
we're asking everyone to leave their
tables within 20 minutes of being served.
What?
But we just finished eating!
I really wanted to try authentic
Sichuan cuisine, but the line is huge.
I'm hungry!
How much longer?
I'm tired of waiting.
I'm starving.
I can't wait anymore!
I want to eat!
I'm at my limit.
Hm...
I've been watching them all this time.
It just took me a while to realize what the
drawbacks of Kuga Restaurant's set-up were.
Okay, Tomita-san.
Plunge that meatball right into
the mapo tofu and split it open!
Huh?
O-Okay.
Plunge the meatball in...
Th... The moon...
The moon came out?!
And this fragrance...
There's no mistaking it!
It's curry!
Curry, the dish that brings
a smile to everyone's face!
What's that dish?!
Curry in mapo tofu?!
I've never eaten anything like that!
The moon's slowly melting and
mingling with the mapo tofu!
Oh, nice.
Now's the best time to dig in.
Have at it!
What are these marvelous flavors?!
Herbs! Spices!
Sharp, yet gentle and mild!
The flavors gently wrap around you
and sink into your very bones!
So this is the new Chinese
cuisine Soma-chan has created!
With beef bone stock as the base,
I added select spices used in curries
along with garlic and ginger to
create this special curry broth.
That's what the "moon" is.
I added gelatin to the
curry broth to solidify it,
then wrapped it in pork filling from
the black pepper buns before cooking it.
When the meatball eventually breaks,
the umami of curry spreads
throughout the mapo dish!
This my second revised Yukihira dish!
Countdown Mapo Curry Noodles!
Hey, that kind of looks awesome!
Just smell that! I can't take it!
H-Hey...
Yeah!
Our line!
He took more than half of it!
Calm down.
There's no way that small stall
can handle that much workload.
They'll implode in no time!
Welcome!
Please enjoy.
Those meatballs...
The ingredients and preparation method
have been tweaked quite a bit,
but they're very similar to a hot pot served
in Taiwan and one of China's regions
called Lion's Head Stew!
The dish likens the brawny
meatball to the head of a lion.
I thought he was a weak housecat,
but in just two nights since
his major defeat on day one...
He's become a ferocious lion!
But don't think you've won, Yukihira-chin.
We are legion, while you are only two.
There's no way you can win, is there?
The 92nd
Moon Festival
Main Avenue
Don RS
Six Ultra Premium Dons!
Nikumi!
At this rate, today we might...
Yup, we might even get first place.
Two servings of Trippa alla Fiorentina, up!
Thank you for waiting!
Central Area
Three mapo curry noodles!
Two of that for us, please.
Sure!
I want the mapo curry noodles.
Two black pepper buns and the
sorta-danzi noodles, too.
Oh, one black pepper bun here, too
Kuga Restaurant
One mapo curry noodles, please.
Can I have the danzi noodle dish?
You must be reaching your limit
right about now, Yukihira-chin.
We're starting to fall behind
in filling the orders!
It's about the time for him to show up.
Huh? What?
So I need more help on the day
I'm gonna make a break for it.
I don't think you're doing a booth.
Can you help?
I'll need to train and visualize
how this is supposed to work.
That'll help me speed things up.
It'll be best to give me access
to the same environment as my
profiling target if at all possible.
Let me use your diner's kitchen.
That's just like you, Mimasaka. Sure.
Thanks.
Okay, here.
Diner
Yukihira
Y-Yukihira-kun?
Dig in!
Thanks!
The mapo set, right?
Hang on!
My name is Yukihira Soma!
I'm doing my best to beat Kuga-senpai!
I've got about ten years on you, Senpai.
Never mind all that.
Just hurry up.
That guy was in the
Autumn Elections' prelim semifinals!
It's Mimasaka Subaru!
Heh, not like adding one more
pair of hands will do much.
Did you learn the recipe
I gave you yesterday?
Don't underestimate my perfect profiling.
I'll show you the results of all
the training I did until today.
Great!
All right, then!
Let's rip Kuga Restaurant a new one!
Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup!
Ten mapo curry noodles, please.
Got it!
Wow!
That rugged-looking boy is matching
Soma-chan's speed perfectly!
Here you go!
Impossible!
It's as if there's another Yukihira Soma!
Delicious!
It smells so good!
There's curry inside!
This is good.
Man, you're a huge help.
I'm serious.
Thanks for agreeing to
do this without a fuss.
I owe you a big one.
Huh? What'd you say?
Nothing.
We don't have time to chit-chat.
We're gonna get even more customers now!
The black pepper buns look good, too.
Totsuki Culinary Teahouse Academy
Famous Taiwanese
Black Pepper Buns
Danzi Noodles
Also Available
1 Plum Ticket
Mapo Curry
Noodles
Mom, I want that!
Give me three.
Tadokoro, I'm counting on you!
Got it!
Please sit here while waiting.
Oh, thank you.
Would you prefer to use a spoon?
Oh, that'd be great.
Since you have a stroller,
would you prefer to sit here?
Oh, thank you!
What steady customer service!
She's a formidable fighter in her own right!
Thanks, Miss!
Oh, that looks delicious.
Categorize the customers' needs
and wants by relative importance
before acting on them.
Make sure you draw on everything
you learned at the Stagiaire!
A'ight!
I have an idea!
Right, that's it!
What idea?
I need to make preparations!
Ryo-kun, come with me!
'Kay.
Hey, what the hell—
Hayama-kun, make curry!
Something with great spices
that would go with cacao!
Huh? Cacao?
Hey, Nakiri!
Hurry up, Ryo-kun.
'Kay.
It's about to get dark.
Yeah.
I think they'll come soon.
Tadokoro-kun!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Captain!
Let's get this all set up!
The Regional Cuisine RS's prized collection
of lanterns from across the nation!
Yeah!
So pretty.
Amazing.
Hey, it kind of reminds me of
that Jiufen place in Taiwan.
I kind of want to eat black pepper buns now!
Thank you! It's so bright and beautiful now.
It's so nice of you after I'd turned
down Regional Cuisine RS's offer, too.
It's true that we were surprised
you wouldn't be joining us,
but we knew you must've
had a reason for that.
You're not the kind of person
to turn away for no reason.
Captain...
Thank you!
Hey, what's with all those lanterns?
They're so pretty!
Let's check that place out!
What's that?
I smell something good.
Want to take a look?
Is a plum ticket good enough?
Yes.
Please wait a while longer
for the black pepper buns.
One sorta-danzi noodles, please.
O-Okay, coming right up!
Five mapo noodles, please.
Three of those black pepper buns, please.
Two danzi noodles, please.
Okay. Please wait in line, sorry.
It's getting pretty hard to keep
this going with just three people.
Yeah, but if we don't stand our ground now,
we'll never be able to catch
up to Chinese Cuisine RS.
Hey, hey, hey.
Are you doing okay, Yukihira-chin?
Even if you get a ton of customers,
you won't be able to beat us
if you can't up your throughput.
Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup!
Sorry, can you clear the table?
Oh, yes, coming!
Two mapo curry noodles, please!
When will the black pepper buns be ready?
S-Sorry, please wait a while longer!
Tadokoro's starting to crumble.
I'll have to handle the black pepper buns!
Mimasaka, hold it together for a sec!
Idiot!
If you step away from the burners,
you're gonna lose your shot at victory!
Let Megumi focus on customer service.
I'll handle the black pepper buns.
Mito-san!
Nikumi! But what about Don RS?!
I'm having the junior members handle it!
I had a hand in the creation of
these black pepper buns, after all.
You don't need to teach
me the recipe or anything.
When gauging whether the buns are done....
Don't miss the moment when the
buns become slightly burnt.
That's the ideal cooking point, when the
filling's juiciness begins to shine.
I can do this with my eyes shut.
Have some piping hot black pepper buns!
Thanks, Nikumi.
Thank you, Mito-san!
Whoa!
Here's the team who helped
save our shopping district!
Bento Shop
Tomitaya
Talk about a powerful and dependable
reinforcement rushing in to join the battle!
You seem to be struggling, Yukihira.
I can't stand to watch.
I suppose that if you insist,
I wouldn't mind lending a hand!
Oh, I'll boil the noodles.
Awesome, thanks.
Hey, wait a minute, Isami!
Listen, Yukihira.
You challenged Kuga Terunori.
I won't allow you to lose
without accomplishing anything!
This is the moment of truth, Takumi.
Can you keep up?
Why bother asking?
Aldini...
You easily managed to reach the
speeds I only finally achieved
after my perfect profiling!
What's the matter, Mimasaka Subaru?
You're slow!
Shut up! I'm just getting started!
I'll beat you!
I wouldn't be so sure about that!
It's finally becoming a good restaurant.
I see...
That man... Yukihira Soma...
spent four days completing his restaurant.
We have one more hour until
the day's sales are tallied.
This is our dash to the finish line!
Let's put our backs to it!
Yeah!
I'm touched by what I'm seeing.
You're tugging at my heartstrings!
Bento Shop
Tomitaya
Don RS
You don't feel like a stranger
to me for some reason.
We will now report the sales
rankings for the Central Area.
Third place goes to El Fuego
by Spanish Cuisine RS.
Second place goes to
Kuga Restaurant by Chinese Cuisine RS.
Second place...
Yukihira-chin!
And first place goes to
Totsuki Culinary Teahouse Academy
Famous Taiwanese
Black Pepper Buns
Yukihira Soma's Chinese Cuisine Stall!
Yeah!
We did it!
Soma-kun, you're amazing!
This should mean you're
no longer in the red, too!
You have good skills, Mimasaka.
You too, Aldini.
Thank you for eating!
Wow, so pretty!
Is that really chocolate on this curry?
That chocolate comes from
this food 3D printer.
Wow! You printed food?!
Yes.
I added spices to chocolate
with 80 percent cacao content
and used this machine to print it.
With this topping on the curry,
the gradually melting chocolate
adds flair to the curry flavors
and transforms the dish!
The curry itself smells really good, too!
Dad! Please get me one!
Give me one!
I want to eat one for sure, too!
Two orders here!
Three, please!
The dish is proving popular to
a broad range of customers...
This menu item has let us
make a complete comeback.
Our ranking improved tremendously.
This should let us turn an overall profit.
Yes. But above all, I'm glad
we made our customers happy.
Here you go.
Where's our order?
Yes, coming right up!
I'm sorry to make you wait!
Color me impressed.
Oh, a pine ticket?
Hayama-kun's smiling.
I'm so glad you're making friends!
Yamanote Area
Hisako.
Our guests have all arrived, have they not?
They have, Erina-sama.
Er, by the way...
You've left one table open today, too.
And such a good table at that.
Yes.
It's just in case.
Totsuki
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Next Episode: The Darkening Dinner Table
I hope you savor the next episode!