Mode/ Combat
Shiroe
Race: Half-Alv
Enchanter, Level 90
Electrical Fuzz!
I see them.
Confirming seven briar weasels!
Careful! To your right!
I know.
Bring it.
Th-These things are tough...
I'll have to use a Shield Smash... What the...
These controls suck!
Naotsugu!
Two from the left!
Th-They stink... Get off me!
It's hard to grasp a situation
when the field of vision is reality.
Akatsuki?
Same here, my lord.
It's all I can do to hold them off.
Akatsuki
Race/ Human
Assassin Lv. 90
Naotsugu
Race/ Human
Guardian, Lv. 90
Naotsugu! Akatsuki!
Shiroe
Race: Half-Alv
Enchanter, Level 90
Fall back for now!
Roger!
This isn't like a game at all...
It isn't a game.
This is
our new reality.
They're coming...
My lord!
Wait...
I'll use a Nightmare Sphere.
A triffid?
Oh, no... Where did it come from?
Shiro!
My lord!
Enchanter, Lv. 90
All of a sudden, there I was.
The Apocalypse
The Apocalypse.
Where am I?
The smell of moisture in the air,
and the bright sunlight...
The Silverleaf Tree...
Could this be...
Akihabara?
What's going on?!
Is this Akihabara?
This can't be happening...
Why am I dressed like this?
What's going on?
Get me the GM!
Are you listening?!
I-I don't...
Ow...
Skills
Quest
Equipment
Items
Wh-What?
Wait, this is
a status screen, isn't it?
Does that mean...
Items
Dezanegg's Magic Bag
I can control it...
Log Out
No good... It won't work.
What's this?
Friend List
My friend list!
Let's see...
If their names are lit up,
does that mean they're here?
Even Tohya and Minori are here?
Naotsugu...
No Guild
Naotsugu
I know, voice chat!
If I can talk to him via telepathy...
Shiro? Is that you, Shiro?
Naotsugu!
Hey, Shiro!
Naotsugu...
Naotsugu
Race/ Human
Guardian, Lv. 90
Hmm?
What?
Oh, it's just, you look the way I pictured you...
So do you.
An intelligent man, with glasses
and nasty, beady eyes.
My race is supposed to be Half-Alv...
So, I log in for the first time in two years...
And what the hell's going on?
Tell me anything you know, nasty-glasses.
I don't know, either.
But...
It appears we're in the world of Elder Tale.
Wasn't today the day they planned
to add the new expansion?
Yeah, The Novasphere Pioneers.
Up until the second they executed the
update, I can remember everything.
And the next thing I knew, I was here.
Same with me.
This is definitely Akihabara.
I've seen it hundreds of times in the game.
But...
The sky stretches so much further.
Yeah.
And it feels like I'm really touching it.
Which means...
I guess this isn't a dream.
Then we're in the game, huh?
I thought that only happened in fantasy novels.
You think we can get home?
I don't know.
How did we get here, in the first place?
Yeah.
I know... We may not be
able to return quickly.
Which means...
We should be ready.
What do we do?
Let's gather information.
We have to know more about this world.
That's true.
Good to see you as calm
and analytical as ever.
I'm counting on you, Strategist.
Calm isn't the word I'd choose.
I know this isn't what you expected,
but welcome back to Elder Tale, Naotsugu.
Yeah!
The buildings and roads
were just as I remembered.
In other words, just like the game.
Looks like I can use my items...
Quest Items
Food         Potions
As well as my magic and skills.
But it looks like we can't log out...
I checked, too.
Want to have a look at the outside zone?
No,
not yet.
Right.
I'm sure monsters are out there!
No way!
You go check it out!
Hell, no... You go.
What's going to happen to us?
Shut up!
Help me! Someone, help me!
If you're back in the game,
you work must have calmed down.
Yeah.
What really sucks is there
aren't any cute girls at work.
Who cares?
What was that?
You're just a closet pervert!
I'm not a closet anything!
There are two types of men in this world.
Open perverts who admit it,
and closet perverts who won't.
I am the former!
And I love panties!
You are the latter.
Yeah, yeah.
And I know you love them, too!
What's wrong?
How tall are you, Naotsugu?
In real life.
183 cm,
just like in Elder Tale.
My character is taller than I really am.
So this body doesn't feel quite right...
That's what you get for showing off.
Anyway...
To some degree, your game character
reflects your real self.
What are you doing?
That's dangerous!
You're...
Akatsuki!
Akatsuki
Race/ Human
Assassin Lv. 90
What? You know him?
We were in a party together.
Not much of a talker, but a good assassin.
So you're also here, Akatsuki.
I'm Naotsugu, a guardian.
Whether you're an open
pervert or not, let's get along.
You say that to someone you just met?
Yup!
Shiroe, I've been looking for you.
I want you to sell me a potion...
An appearance-changing potion.
That voice...
Akatsuki, you're a girl?
No wonder you never spoke much.
Appearance-changing potions...
Those are rare.
They only distributed them once.
I remembered Shiroe had one.
L-Let me go...
I thought you wouldn't use voice chat
because you were playing as an assassin.
Are you okay?
It's all right now.
She's hot!
The real deal!
Akatsuki
Race/ Human
Assassin Lv. 90
Female
You saved me.
I really appreciate it.
I-It's fine...
I retract my earlier statement.
You can't be either an open pervert
or a closet one, because...
You aren't a man!
Shiroe, is there something wrong with him?
There are many things wrong with him.
Why is that?
In any case, he's messed up.
So, Akatsuki,
did you adjust your character
to be closer to your real size?
Yes.
You should have done that in the first place.
Games are fun because you can do things
you couldn't in real life, right?
But once I was stuck here,
it was very inconvenient.
Inconvenient?
Ah! You mean like the bathroom!
Shiroe, is it all right if I knee
this strange man in the face?
Ask before you do it, shrimp!
Don't call me a shrimp!
Anyway, how much do I owe you?
Oh, don't worry about it.
I can't do that.
I don't want anyone saying
I wouldn't repay a favor.
But...
If it's that big a deal, you can...
Shiroe, is it all right if I knee
this strange man in the face?
I said to ask before you do it!
And I didn't even finish!
You were about to say something bad.
I was, but...
Anyhow, why don't you stay with us for a while?
Strategist! Explain.
That's true... We can't leave her by herself.
Akatsuki...
Didn't you refuse to join a guild?
Assassins are lone wolves.
We aren't in one, either.
But right now, I think it's better to
stay in a group than go alone.
Are you all right with that, Shiroe?
We'd be happy to have you.
I see...
Then, as a ninja, I shall revere you as my lord.
Ninja? Lord?
Wasn't she an assassin?
You have saved me from the dire fate
of being transformed into a man.
Thus, I must work to repay you.
That is what requiting a debt means.
From now on, as your ninja, I shall protect you.
Well, um... Thanks.
Then we're a team!
Aren't more People of the
Land around than before?
Albel/ People of the Land
The NPCs that inhabit the world of Elder Tale
call themselves People of the Land.
And we players are called adventurers.
Want to buy something, guys?
You mean we can eat these?
No time to waste thinking about it!
I'll take rice dumplings and green tea.
Sure thing.
What is this?
They all taste the same.
This...
It feels like a soggy cracker, without salt.
And all the drinks taste like water.
What's up?
Incoming Call
Someone's calling me.
Who is it?
Marielle
Crescent Moon Alliance
Welcome!
From Marielle?
Guild Building
Japan Server
Akihabara
City/ No Monsters
No PVP
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
Yeah, she leads the guild known
as the Crescent Moon Alliance.
It's weird how the guild building
is nothing but doors, though.
Each Guild Hall is its own zone.
Only the really weird stuff is still like a game.
Guild Hall 236
Guild Master: Marielle
Guild Name: Crescent Moon Alliance
Entry Restrictions: Yes
ID: Shiroe    No Guild
How cute.
This is the guild master's room?
Shiro!
Marie!
Are you okay? You must be hungry!
Eat something... Not that it has any flavor!
Calm down, Marie...
Marielle
Race/ Elf
Cleric
Guild Master:
Crescent Moon Alliance
What's this?
Do you have a girlfriend now, Shiro?
No!
You're so adorable!
Want a lollipop?
Shiro, where were you hiding this hot chick?
I haven't been hiding her.
Who's this?
Naotsugu!
Nice to meet you!
Naotsugu, huh?
Wh-Wha—
You're pretty buff!
You play sports?
No, um...
I mean, this is armor...
What is her problem?
She's scaring me.
Marie, stop it.
Another one!
Hot girls everywhere!
Henrietta
Race/ Human
Bard
Crescent Moon Alliance
Henrietta!
Oh, dear...
I apologize for summoning you here, Shiroe.
Given what's happening, I'd like
to exchange information...
She's so cute!
There they go again...
Um...
Save me!
Do you want to share information?
Then what about the Crescent
Moon Alliance members?
Including myself, nineteen are online.
Eighteen are in Akihabara.
Eighteen of nineteen?
I'm told that, along with Akihabara, the other
four major cities on the Japanese server,
Shibuya, Minami, Susukino, and Nakasu
are all in the same shape.
And the inter-city transport gates are offline.
In other words, teleporting elsewhere is impossible.
The Akihabara adventurers are all meeting
with their guilds, just like we are.
Some guilds are also looking to recruit.
At a time like this, the more people
on your side, the better.
But even if this isn't our world,
we're all very familiar with Elder Tale.
Not necessarily.
You remember the new expansion, right?
The Novasphere Pioneers.
I get it.
If they've added that new expansion,
then monsters, items, and quests
may all be different.
This world may not be the Elder Tale we know.
H-Hey, Shiro...
I know you aren't a big fan of guilds.
But...
Would you like to join ours?
Marie?
Debauchery Tea Party is gone, right?
And right now...
I'm sorry, Marie.
But I can't yet.
That's a great guild master.
It's all she can do to stay under control,
but she's still acting so friendly.
Wasn't Debauchery Tea Party a
legendary guild that disbanded?
No, no...
The Tea Party wasn't a guild.
It was a small group that
never formed a guild,
but managed to complete several
large-scale battles called raids.
And Shiroe was their strategist.
How long are we going to be stuck here?
How long will they just sit around there?
Die and you can escape.
In stories like this, that's pretty common.
And sometimes, if you die in
the game, you die in real life.
When it was just a game,
you'd revive at the Cathedral.
But we can't very well experiment.
But even if you do revive,
what about your penalty?
What's wrong, my lord?
Let's try it.
The Archive Tower Forests?
We're level 90.
That's the level cap.
Normally, low-level monsters
would just ignore us.
But in this area, the monsters will aggro on sight.
So it's the perfect place to try it, my lord.
Oh! You can't use your
mini-map in the outside zones.
Briar Weasels.
Level 28...
Briar Weasel
Rank/ Normal
These guys are nothing!
W-Wait...
Naotsugu...
It's hard to enter commands while
monsters are running at you!
There's a difference between
"using" and "mastering"...
Get into formation, as discussed!
It doesn't hurt as much as I expected.
But unlike when you play the game,
trying to fight monsters in front,
while keeping an eye on your
party and overall situation...
This won't be easy.
To survive in this world, we must
hurry and learn its rules and how to fight.
But what do we do?
Akatsuki?
How did you do that?
I don't know...
My body just moved on its own.
Naotsugu!
Don't use your commands.
Try to use your body to feel the motion!
What are you talking about?
Just do it!
I don't get it, but fine...
Shield Swing!
My lord, this is...
Elder Tale.
An MMORPG with over twenty
million worldwide players.
Without warning, an estimated thirty
thousand Japanese alone...
And several hundred thousand worldwide...
Were trapped in a world just like the game.
Nightmare Sphere!
Cross Slash!
Assassinate!
Later, they would come to call this day...
The Apocalypse.
Serara, what's wrong?
Serara
Crescent Moon Alliance
Susukino
Japan Server
Edge Zone/ Susukino
City/ No Monsters
No PVP
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
Serara...
Say something!
Marielle, I...
We found her!
Over here!
Serara!
One day, we found ourselves
trapped in another world.
There, we fought and hurt one another.
But it was only a game,
to keep our minds off the fact
that we weren't even allowed to die.
When a young girl in the
Crescent Moon Alliance, Serara,
runs into danger in a distant northern
land, Shiroe sets out on a journey.
Next time: The Battle Of Loka.
The Battle of Loka
This is our reality.