Saito, hurry up!
Come on!
What's the big hurry?
Aquileia's bazaar is really popular,
so the good stuff gets snapped up fast!
If you can't move faster,
I'll just go on without you.
Don't come crying to me if you get lost!
As a Void Mage, I am
responsible for this world.
Louise... She has to contend
with so much pressure...
...with that little body of hers.
It's so pretty!
You didn't have to buy it for me.
I do get my pay as a knight.
I can afford it.
Not that I could get you a real mansion.
A real mansion?
Living in a mansion, alone with Saito!
It's nothing, okay?!
She's not always honest, she gets jealous,
and can be rather annoying.
But I'm going to protect her,
no matter what.
Aquileia's Shrine Maiden
Ladies and gentlemen!
Tomorrow, during the
third anniversary celebration
of His Holiness'
ascent here in Aquileia,
it will be our duty,
as the Order of the Undine Knights,
to ensure the safety of the streets.
Without further details,
that sounds somewhat important.
But in reality it's nothing
more than crowd control.
Forward, Undine!
This city is so romantic.
It's like being on a honeymoon.
It's pretty rude of Miss
Vallière to cut out on us.
It's too bad.
Louise and Tiffania have both...
...accepted the role of shrine maiden
at His Holiness' celebration.
Your Grace, please ensure their safety.
Certainly.
Something like yesterday
will not happen again.
Is that not so, Julio?
Yes.
For the entire two weeks of ceremonies,
we have 300 holy knights
securing this area.
And yet, just yesterday,
the Founder's Round Mirror was stolen
by mercenaries who call themselves
the "Elemental Siblings."
What about the possibility that those
who hired them are plotting a conspiracy?
We can't rule it out.
However, we have prepared magic
detection spells throughout the city.
Anyone who tries to use magic
will be detected immediately.
There is no need for concern.
What do you think, Agnès?
I don't like it.
I believe we are being too careless towards
an enemy we can't read.
What concerns me the most
is that I could sense
that His Grace was not
shaken by yesterday's event.
Are you saying he expected it?
I hope I'm just making too much of it.
Isn't it possible that it was
Saito who was summoned back then?
It's happened again!
Just looking at him was enough
to make my heart race.
This isn't normal!
I'm back!
Saito.
Welcome back.
L-Louise...
This is my shrine maiden
outfit for tomorrow.
I wanted to show it to you first.
A holy maiden...
I'm in the presence of a holy maiden!
Louise!
L-Louise!
S-Saito, you mustn't!
I can't do that in the clothes
I'm going to wear before God!
It's fine. You look so cute.
I'm not cute...
You are!
You're like a... like a...
...little lemon!
A lemon?
Your skin is smooth,
your scent is soft...
You're a little lemon!
Stop!
I don't like you when you
get like this, Saito!
Yup, you're a lemon!
I can't help myself against
this little lemon.
I don't understand what you're talking
about, but am I really a lemon?
Yes.
Try saying, "I'm a shy lemon."
I-I'm a shy lemon...
What a cute lemon!
She really is so cute!
I'm so happy!
This little lemon is happy, too!
I have a message from the wind sprite.
Malicorne?
The walls of this abode
are unexpectedly thin.
Please consider your neighbors.
Yes.
And seriously, little lemon?
I... I didn't...
Saito, he...
He made me say it!
Flame.
Flame under my contract.
Flow to the place that I indicate.
That makes it three.
Good work, Lord Bidalsha.
The Fire Stone.
You used the power of the sprites
to seal the power of fire
into this crystal?
To put it simply, yes.
But it is actually much more
complex and profound than that.
Then I have a question
for you, Lord Bidalsha.
How much land can a stone
this size conflagrate?
Excuse me?
I'm asking about its potential
as a weapon of mass destruction.
A weapon of destruction?
I was not told it would be used for that!
I'm merely proposing that we
discover new uses for this stone.
Why don't you come and observe?
I must decline.
I do not wish to take part in crimes.
You have the nerve to say
that after you locked your
innocent daughter away on my orders,
and used secret elven magic
on Jörmungandr's armor?
You've already done more than take part!
But do as you please.
And what about my muse, Sheffield?
How are your preparations?
King Joseph, by tomorrow
everything will be ready.
The Founder's Round Mirror and
the other key ingredient...
Honored Founder Brimir...
May you protect the peace of Halkeginia.
May you keep this land pure for all time.
Everyone, please calm down!
I just want to have one
moment with His Holiness!
If I did that, I could die in peace.
I'm sorry, but it's impossible!
Commoners can only get a glimpse
of him through the window!
If you will be watching,
please move to the right.
No, you can't go this way!
Malicorne!
I hate this job!
Wow, look at all those people!
The knights must have their hands full.
Hm?
This way, Mademoiselle.
Please, watch your step.
That idiot.
Today's ceremony is finally over.
I guess there are a lot
of fervent believers,
even amongst the commoners!
Your standing does not matter
when it comes to faith.
But commoners only pray to
God when they need something.
Maybe that's true.
Still...
Louise!
Let's go!
I'll be right there!
Just wait for me in the common room.
Isn't that proof, though, that their
need for God is even greater?
My goodness.
Nice job today, Tiffa.
Thank you, Saito! You, too!
All I did was stand there.
I can't believe this will
go on for two weeks.
I have to know.
I have to know if Saito
is my familiar or not.
D-Do I have something on my face?
Saito, may I ask you for a favor?
Sure, you know I'd do anything for you.
Then, I'd like you to kiss me.
Oh, so that's what this is about...
Wait...
What?!
T-Tiffa!
If he really is my familiar,
once we kiss, a rune should appear.
T-Tiffa, we can't!
Which is not to say it
doesn't make me happy
that you want to kiss me, but you know,
it's all so complicated...
Please.
If we don't, I'll keep burning here...
Saito...
T-Tiffa...
You're sure we can just take a break?
Of course we can!
Let Guiche do some real work for once.
S-Saito and Tiffa?!
Actually, this isn't...
I-I'm so sorry!
Tiffa!
So, first you got a lemon,
and then you want a melon, huh?
Uh, well....
Seriously, why are all guys idiots?
Huh?
Tiffa, what's wrong?
Tiffa?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, but commoners
are not allowed in here.
You're Miss Louise of House
Vallière, am I right?
Yes, but...
I work as a farmer on the land
that Lord Vallière controls.
You're part of our fiefdom?
Yes.
Please, won't you have mercy on me?
I see.
You came with your mother
to see the ceremony!
That's wonderful!
Unfortunately, my mother collapsed
when we entered the city,
maybe from exhaustion.
I'm sure if you visited her
as a holy shrine maiden,
she would feel better.
Louise left the holy halls?
Yes.
This common girl asked her for a favor
and I guess she couldn't refuse...
Thank you.
I'll go find her.
Why does she always have
to do these random things?
Louise!
Where are you?
Hey, pal!
You!
Thanks for the other day.
How dare you do that to Jacques?
Get out of my way!
Hey!
What are you doing there?
Easy as pie.
What is he doing here?
I hope he hasn't done
anything with Louise!
I'm not done repaying you
for my brother...
She's over there.
Mother!
Miss Louise has come to see you!
You've traveled a long way from
Vallière's lands to get here.
Raise your head.
I do hate these common clothes.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm Jeanette.
That was my older brother you
defeated a few days back.
I can't move!
This knife is poisoned.
But don't worry.
It paralyzes the body only temporarily.
Wh-What do you mean?
Wow.
You've got quite the power.
I guess that's why they want you.
Stop getting involved,
you child of the elements.
I'll take over from here.
You can go now.
Are you sure?
Even if I leave now,
you'll have to pay in full.
Your employer is telling you to go.
Well, then I leave it to you.
We might have become good friends
had we met under different circumstances.
Goodbye.
Shall we go and pay a
visit to our great master?
Doudou?
Damn.
And it was just getting interesting...
What did you guys do to Louise?!
Oh, that girl?
She's really cute and nice and innocent...
If anything, I'd say she's a little too nice.
Where's Louise?!
A really scary lady took her away.
They've probably left the city by now.
Jeanette, stop talking so much!
Damian will blame me for it!
It's fine.
Our work is finished.
Louise!
Damn it!
It's all my fault!
All because I was so careless...
Louise... Louise...
Louise!
I found this in an alley not
far from the holy halls.
I am certain it belongs to Miss Vallière.
I see...
My deepest apologies.
That such a vile act would
occur in broad daylight...
And without using magic...
This is Gallia's work.
Tabitha!
I called her.
She has a history with
the Elemental Siblings.
Please help us, Tabitha.
They belong to the Knights of the
North Parterre of Gallia, as I once did.
I've heard that there is a special order
of knights in Gallia just for dirty work.
That means the true mastermind is...
The king of Gallia, Joseph.
So Joseph has kidnapped Louise?!
But if that is true...
Gallia's borders are very close to ours.
Louise might have crossed the border...
My liege!
I don't care if I have to enter Gallia,
I'm going to rescue Louise!
But you can't, Saito!
If you do, you'll also get...
My deepest apologies for this disturbance,
but there is something I must
divulge to His Holiness at once!
Come forward.
I think it would be best if
everyone here hears this as well.
There has been a message sent by our
troops patrolling the Gallian border.
The Gallian fleet is
encroaching on our borders...
What?
But Your Holiness... Then, that means...
It means they may invade our lands.
Is the young miss finally awake?
Let me go!
Come, come!
Do you think I take orders
from just anybody?
What are you planning to do with me?
If it's something horrible,
I'll just bite my tongue off
and make myself bleed to
death before you get me!
Calm yourself, young lady.
You're...
I am Joseph, the king of Gallia,
but I know they call me
"The Incompetent King" in public.
Don't worry.
I am not going to mistreat a school
friend of my niece Charlotte.
Like I can believe you after
what you did to Tabitha!
Locking up a niece still reeks
of something a human would do.
What I'm going to do next
is something that only demons,
without a shred of humanity, would do.
But to do that, you'll have
to lend me your powers.
Whether you wish to or not,
you will witness it...
The hell that will be born
once the elven spells
and Void magic are combined.
Saito... Saito.... Help!
King Joseph of Gallia... What is he plotting?
Oh, stop!
Don't use my powers for
something that horrid!
Next episode:
The Incompetent King Gone Mad.
The Incompetent King Gone Mad
Please, Saito, come save me quickly.