Hm?
Just one more time...
At the very moment Hinata is at
the highest point of his jump,
to set the ball at the
optimum spiking level...
Then I will take aim...
...and swing!
Haikyu!!
Episode 13: Rival
The toss was a little too high.
Captain.
Nice save, Daichi-san.
It's in.
Front, front.
Nice, Inuoka.
Bring it.
Tora.
Let's do this, Hinata. One, two...
All right.
Kai-san, nice cover.
Wow, the supporting players
on both teams are doing a good job.
They're not flashy, but they
keep the ball in play.
There wouldn't be a match
without them.
Kenma.
One more!
Even if I'm only average on offense,
I'm still Nekoma's ace!
All right.
Damn.
Taketora-san is more fired up than usual.
Karasuno's team has a a similar kind of guy. Maybe that's why.
Or maybe he got inspired by the
battle between Inuoka and #10.
Hinata-kun and Kageyama-kun's
quick sets haven't been syncing...
That's because they're
trying to do normal quick sets,
instead of the freak quick sets
where Kageyama matches Hinata perfectly.
But Hinata needs to develop his skills.
You're still straining.
Your timing's slower than usual.
His body has to learn,
and the only way is through repetition.
He'll have to keep training,
but once he has a unique set of skills...
...that duo will cease being
an oni and his iron club.
They'll become a pair of oni.
Karasuno      Nekoma
Nice serve.
Which way should I receive?
Over or under?
Cover, cover.
Ryu.
All right! Asahi-san's not the only one
who can score in a pinch.
Wow.
He blew away the block.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
I won't just keep
getting blocked by you.
I'll block you, too.
Hinata.
Like Kageyama says, don't strain too much.
Maintain a broad perspective.
Y-Yes.
Fukunaga.
The guy with thick crewcut
dashed forward...
Maintain a broad perspective.
And now #7, from behind #2?
Nice one touch.
Chance ball.
Fast!
Nekoma's #7 reacts fast, too.
They influence each other
in a tight battle.
At times, they push each other's abilities
to new heights.
They are indeed rivals.
He got it through.
It landed in.
All right.
Still a little too high...
One more.
All right.
Damn.
Karasuno      Nekoma
We can't let them
reach 20 points we do.
Inuoka, serve.
Yes.
The lanky guy rotates to rear guard,
and comb-head becomes vanguard...
It's fun playing against Lanky, but...
This guy is scary.
Inuoka's 20 cm taller than you,
and yet you've played an even match.
That's amazing, shrimpy.
You can call me a shrimp,
but you're the real shrimp.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Let's do our usual quick set this time.
The zoomy one, not the floaty one?
That's right.
But I was starting to get
the hang of the floaty one.
Not this time.
Not while that guy is vanguard.
But why?
Just because.
Huh?
It's my intuition.
Inuoka, nice serve.
Yes.
That always feels so good.
I think that was a good decision.
What?
Sorry, sorry. I didn't react at all.
I think the freak quick set is more effective
against that third year middle blocker.
Kuro-san, don't worry.
It's because the normal quick set
would be an easy target
for that skilled middle blocker.
Okay, it's my serve next.
That sure was amazing.
Get it over the net, okay?
Those guys are what you call superhuman.
I know that.
Okay, then...
Let's get that point back.
Hinata, nice serve.
Nice receive.
Wow, they got jumbled...
Who's getting this one?
It's gotta be that strong-looking guy...
#4!
Back row attack...
The three in front were decoys!
Our block's been completely thwarted.
Chance ball.
Who's next?
An A quick.
Wow.
In a split second.
That was quite a solid quick.
Maybe it's because he's keeping a
close eye on our unpredictable Hinata.
All right, my serve.
Karasuno      Nekoma
Yamamoto, nice serve.
Crap.
Sorry, cover!
Open.
Asahi-san.
Who's attacking next?
Another A quick?
He didn't jump!
What was that?
One guy changes the timing.
He fakes doing a quick,
then spikes after messing up
the blockers' timing.
You don't see it used much these days.
But he took the initiative immediately
after that perfect A quick.
Nice toss.
That was impressive.
Nice kill, Kuro-san.
Karasuno      Nekoma
Nekoma's reached 20 points.
It's over if they score five more points.
We're in trouble.
And I've already used up the two timeouts.
Damn. He's smirking at me!
I don't know about that,
but ever since their #1
took the vanguard position,
I can really tell that their team
has an experienced offense.
I agree.
Half our starting players are first-years.
They've just
started playing together.
If our team is Level 1,
their team is Level is 10 or 20.
Yamamoto, nice serve.
Nice serve.
They're a fully mature cat,
and we're a newborn raven.
Yeah, something like that.
In terms of defense and offense,
we're no match for them.
At least for now.
In which case...
We have no choice but to fight.
Pound them with your power and speed!
In other words, force them to surrender?
That's kind of villainous.
Villainous, huh? That's fine.
Ravens are sort of villainous, aren't they?
Ukai-kun, you look really scary!
We'll make up for our lousy quicks
and receives with sheer brute force.
You guys are rough around
the edges and awkward,
so use that as your weapon!
Wield your weapons with all your might.
Attack,
attack,
and keep on attacking!
Yes. Nice block, Tsukishima.
Tsukki, nice.
Karasuno      Nekoma
Don't mind, Inuoka.
Sorry.
Karasuno's reached 20 points.
Karasuno's totally gone on the offensive.
Don't rush things. Understood?
Yes.
Good.
Keep your connections solid.
Yes.
Karasuno      Nekoma
Okay, one more point and we're even.
D-D-Do your best.
Calm down. We'll stop this one.
Yes.
Just when we thought we were out of danger,
Karasuno      Nekoma
it's Nekoma's match point.
One more point to go.
Yeah.
Damn.
Does that guy ever get excited?
I guess he really is
a mature cat, after all.
Don't worry.
Everyone is still fired up.
All right...
We'll even the score.
You won't get past me.
Karasuno      Nekoma
That #3 is vanguard now.
We can fake out their blockers' cornerstore,
the middle blocker.
Tanaka, nice serve.
On top of that, Hinata is capable
of thwarting him and scoring.
And then there's Azumane, who
is our most powerful attacker.
Now that those two are vanguard,
Karasuno has its best chance
of turning the tables.
One more point and it's deuce.
Yes. If we can reach a deuce,
we'll have a chance
to turn the tables on them.
This is the moment of truth!
Nice receive.
Hinata's quick is too uncertain right now.
Go.
He saved it.
But...
It's coming back. It's our chance ball.
Damn it. I'm sorry.
Azumane, direct spike!
Crap.
Slam it, Asahi!
Saved again!
Their chance ball again.
That's how it is.
Huh?
Even if we lose our bearings, and we
can't get in a position to attack...
As long as the ball is still
in play, we haven't lost.
Chance ball!
Hinata's aura...
It's what I felt the first time
I first played against him.
His overwhelming presence
at the most crucial moment...
As if he's saying,
"I'm here. Give me the ball."
He's calling me!
We did it!
The team with strong spikes doesn't win...
The team that drops the ball loses.
And...
...that's what it means to "connect."
Karasuno      Nekoma
All right.
We didn't make many mistakes.
Our best weapons were
working as they should.
Yet, we still couldn't win.
Kenma, nice.
They're a real team,
not a group of individuals.
They totally defeated us.
Once more.
Let's do it.
Yeah, I'd like that.
That's what a practice match is for,
so we can do it "once more."
Nice course.
Nice serve.
One more.
May 6 / Good weather
8:50 Karasuno assembles at the sports park for practice match
9:10 warmups
10:00 practice match
Karasuno Nekoma
We've been defeated fair and square.
Everybody's...
...exhausted.
Once more.
Hey! You've been moving around like crazy.
Is your stamina limitless?
Hey now, we can't.
We have to catch the bullet train.
Huddle.
His granddad and I are old acquaintances.
Your receives were particularly amazing.
I learned a lot watching you guys.
We did a lot of practice matches together.
You thoroughly defeated us.
They were good matches, every time.
However...
You're retiring?
I'm getting too old for it.
Sorry.
I see...
Well, even if you're not around,
we can practice with other teams.
But a good rival is hard to find.
Old Man Ukai made a comeback,
but collapsed soon thereafter...
I was afraid Karasuno would be
done for after that.
But frankly, your abilities
exceeded my expectations.
Especially #9 and #10's quicks on offense.
You guys are pretty much unstoppable.
And you two on the left,
you're both powerful weapons.
Practice maintaining connection.
Yes.
As a team, you're rough-hewn
and lack training,
but you have overwhelming potential.
The more you train,
the stronger you'll become.
You guys make me happy.
We finally have a good rival again.
Let's meet again at nationals.
In front of a huge audience,
in an arena swirling with emotions,
in that shining, glistening,
enormous gymnasium.
The Battle at the Garbage Dump.
Let's have the best match ever.
Yes.
All right. Let's start cleaning up.
Yeah.
You piece of crap.
You turd.
Equipment Room
Come on, let's hurry up.
Hey.
Huh?
What's up? Still wanna fight?
City boy. Come on.
Um... well... your...
L-Lady... ma...
What's your manager's name?
You!
You plan on bothering our precious manager?
I'm gonna rub your fuzzy head so hard...
No.
I do not have the courage to speak to her.
Fukunaga, mop over there for me.
Okay.
Yaku, get me that mop.
Kiyoko-san.
She's Shimizu Kiyoko-san.
Really?
She's the very embodiment of that name.
Indeed, indeed.
It took me a long time before
I could speak to her,
so I know how you feel.
However...
When you talk to her and she ignores you,
it's still pretty good.
That hurdle's too high for me.
You're a pretty good guy.
You, too.
I'm Yamamoto Taketora.
I'm Tanaka Ryunosuke.
How long have you been playing volleyball?
Who taught you?
How long have you been setter?
How do you train?
Do you get along with your team members?
Have you ever hit a wall?
Our setter is a little more... intense.
He was talking about him.
You were amazing, Shoyo.
You're like... Zoom! Bam!
Oh, I'm Inuoka, a first-year.
You, too. You're big, but
you're like... Wham! Kaboom!
I especially like how you "argh!"
And I like how you "boom!"
And your smack hit me like "bang!"
It's not quite "bang!"
It's more like...
What the heck are they talking about?
They don't sound like high schoolers.
But you on the other hand, maybe you
should go a little crazy,
like a high schooler.
I'm not good at that sort of thing.
Ah, youth.
I'm sorry I'm so slow.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
No, I was wrong. Please forgive me.
Stubbley over there is scaring
that first-year half to death.
They look like a kid and his dad.
He looks more like a kidnapper to me.
Um... That guy's really staring at me.
I'm sorry. You'll be fine if
you don't look back at him.
#3, your receives were amazing.
I've never seen anyone able to receive
so many of our ace's spikes.
Your entire team is high-caliber,
and you're their libero.
I think you have amazing talent.
I'm going to do my best, too.
Goodbye.
Hey, don't just say that and leave.
I'm sorry about that.
He's kinda dangerous.
Huh?
He's a high-caliber libero, too,
but he's not arrogant about it, at all.
On the contrary, he only seeks to improve.
That's scary.
Nekomata-sensei.
Thank you for coming all
this way for the match.
No, no, thank you.
Since you have no connections,
it must be hard for you
to get games together.
All those calls you made to me...
You even threatened
to come see me personally.
I'm sorry.
However, your enthusiasm
stoked my enthusiasm.
Even if you're awkward, your students
will follow you just the same.
Do your best.
Thank you very much.
Keishin. Do your best.
We played three matches
and you didn't win a single one.
I'll win them all the next time.
Just you wait and see.
Let's hope you're not all talk.
Sensei, you're too confrontational.
It's his fault.
He looks too much like that geezer.
That's an immature remark.
Ukai-kun.
What you were saying about coaching
only until the match with Nekoma...
Did you hear what he said to me?
I can't bow out now.
I'll have my revenge for sure,
and on a huge stage.
'Til we meet again, my friend.
What's with them?
Dunno. It's quite unusual.
We won't lose the next time.
We won't lose the next time, either.
Terrifying! They're terrifying!
The next time around,
things won't go your way like they did today.
Fine. Otherwise, it wouldn't be good practice.
And them, too!
They're so immature.
Kenma.
Shoyo.
When we talked on the road the other day,
you said you didn't
particularly like volleyball.
Oh. Yeah.
How did it feel to win today?
Sort of... normal.
The next time,
we'll make you guys desperate.
We'll win, and...
...we'll make you say,
"I'm mad," or "That was fun,"
instead of just, "Sort of."
Okay.
I look forward to it.
If today's was an official match...
It would have been all over
after we lost the first match.
All over.
Boy's Volleyball Prefectural Tournament
Kitagawa Daiichi
Loses by a Hair
Yukigaoka    Kitagawa Daiichi
I know.
I'm glad you know.
And the official matches,
the Inter-High preliminaries,
are right around the corner.
When we get back,
we'll think about and analyze
today's practice match.
Then we'll train.
Yeah.
Next Episode Preview
By the way, Kageyama,
did you ask that setter about
that feint and his other tricks?
No.
For crying out loud Kageyama-kun!
Are you shy?
Shut up, moron.
Ouch! Not the iron claw!
Episode 14: Formidable Opponents
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Formidable Opponents"
Inter-High