I can't believe you're a spy.
There was no other way to get across the Wall.
Of course.
But those clothes really suit you.
Is that a compliment?
Or...
It's both.
Anyway, now we've fooled Control.
Let's run away together.
I have the route planned out.
There's a white house waiting for us
in Casablanca. We can...
I can't.
I told you.
I need your help
to make me Queen.
You don't mean...
That old promise?
With the Wall gone, we can be together
and it won't matter who knows it.
That's true, but...
But...
I understand.
I know it won't be easy.
No, you don't understand!
Morgan MP was killed on the way to hospital.
Why?
The people at the top were afraid he would talk.
So they silenced him.
That's the world I live in.
That's why I...
Even so...
Even so.
I want to be Queen
and eliminate the things that come between us.
All right. I'll do it.
Ange!
I will deceive them all.
I'll deceive you,
the world...
and...
even myself.
It is the turn of the 20th century.
The Kingdom of Albion's new royal air force,
commonly known as the Air Fleet,
has created a dramatic shift
in the balance of global power.
With its monopoly on Cavorite,
and the Air Fleet at its command,
the Kingdom of Albion became
the greatest world power since the Roman Empire.
However,
revolution split the kingdom into East and West,
with the London Wall separating the Kingdom of Albion
from the Commonwealth of Albion.
Ten years later, London became the front-line
of a secret war fought between the nations' spies.
How did you like this morning's tea, Your Highness?
I was just in the mood for some Nuwara Eliya.
You know me so well, Beatrice.
Today, you're expected to attend
the send-off for the Crown Prince at 10.
Then you will be participating in the
inaugural meeting of the Life Improvement Society,
and reading a message on behalf of
Her Majesty the Queen.
Thank you, Beatrice.
And...
I'm sorry.
For making that decision about Ange
without talking to you.
I'm against it.
Those people are spies!
Their job is to trick and deceive people.
We can't trust them!
But they do say,
"The enemy of my enemy is my friend."
Anyway, Your Highness, I will protect you,
just like I always have...
Princess, you in there?
Wow, I didn't think your room would be so plain.
Wh-where are your manners?!
You don't have an appointment!
I'm visiting a friend. Don't be so uptight.
A friend?!
We're all fellow students here, aren't we?
Maybe on the surface, but...!
If we're going to be friends, we'll need a reason.
What should our story be?
We grew up together on the Black Lizard Planet.
No!
What about cross-dressing?
We know the Princess' unspeakable secret!
Certainly not!
Why would Her Highness do something so indecent?!
Then back to the Black Lizard Planet idea...
No!
Absolutely not!
Welcome to our club room.
Club room?
If we tell everyone it's for our club,
we can get away with all kinds of things.
We'll figure out exactly what club it is later.
Oof!
Are they all... real?
You did all this yourself, Dorothy?
Are you impressed with me now?
Yes, I'll come to you next time
I'm making an anteater hutch.
Nice work getting the safety off.
Your Highness!
And you lot!
Bringing Her Highness into such a dangerous place...!
What are you thinking?!
The truth is, we have orders from Control.
You mean from the director of the Commonwealth spies
who are infiltrating the Kingdom?
Our orders are to board HMS Gloucester
and recover the printing plates
for the Commonwealth Pound.
Why would the Royal Air Force have plates
for Commonwealth currency?
They were stolen.
The Duke of Normandy plans to mass-produce pound
notes in the colonies to create financial instability.
That's where Princess comes in.
We need you to board the Gloucester
and create an opening for us to stow away.
So this is my first mission.
No! I won't let her do anything so dangerous!
Don't worry.
If the worst should happen...
I'll take her place.
In that case, our beginner has nothing to worry about.
It's true. It's like I'm looking in a mirror.
Your Highness!
How can you be so calm?!
These people are-
Beatrice!
Excuse me!
What was THAT all about?
There was a mechanism in her throat.
Beatrice's father is known for
being fanatical about machines.
Possessed by machines himself,
he eventually began to experiment
on his own daughter.
It's the mechanical girl!
Go on, say something!
Yuck, she smells like oil!
...ness!
Your Highness!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Come on, Beatrice.
Let's you and I be friends.
Your Highness, I don't think those people
are just any spies.
They mean to replace you.
I know. I know God won't do anything for us.
The police work for the Duke of Normandy,
and the Duke of Anquitaine, Lord High Admiral...
he can hardly be considered an ally.
I'm the only one...
...who can protect you.
I'm terribly sorry for dropping in unannounced.
This is where we held the send-off
for His Royal Highness Prince Abyssinian.
We are deeply honored to have you, Princess.
This will certainly improve our sailors' morale.
Our ship will be preparing for departure soon.
We don't have much to offer,
but perhaps some Kalinga tea...
My, that sounds lovely.
I can't let you go any farther, Miss.
Oh, that's hardly friendly.
Classified material's in there.
If you like, you could wait in the Officers' Mess...
Actually...
There's somewhere else I'd really like to go.
A-as long as it's somewhere I can authorize.
I can't hold it in any longer.
Why did you come along?
You hate us, don't you?
I-I'm here for Her Highness!
I'm keeping an eye on you,
to make sure you don't try anything funny!
Don't bother.
You're an amateur. You'll never hit me.
I'd be so embarrassed if you heard me.
Could you step away, please?
I-I beg your pardon!
Answer me! Why do you
look so much like Her Highness?
Because Princess and I
are sisters from the Black Lizard Planet.
Don't joke with me!
You're planning to replace her.
That's why you look like her!
Isn't it?!
Almost time to go.
What? But-!
Save the chat for teatime.
Wait!
I said wait!
No! I have to protect Her Highness!
You're awake, then?
Y-you'll get no thanks from me!
I don't want any.
Anyway, hurry.
Once we get the plates,
we're parachuting out of here.
You want me to help a spy? I would rather die!
Then die.
For your princess.
If you got caught, they would have no trouble
cracking an amateur like you.
Then they'll know that Princess
made a deal with the Commonwealth.
I... I would never do anything
to sell out Her Highness!
Then get caught and see.
A professional interrogation
is more than just a chat.
Is somebody in there?
What's up?
Oh, nothing. I thought I heard voices.
Voices?
A telephone switchboard?
This is Corporal Henry, Royal Marines 2nd Company,
I've just completed my guard shift.
This is engine watch.
Distillation amounts are normal.
I've just completed my guard shift.
Naval command, copy that.
No effect on the ship's internal gravity.
Now you go dream about that fiancee of yours.
The Cavorite jammer has activated.
Jennifer, was it?
When we get there, you're paying me back.
No... are you listening to all of them at once?
Get me Number One.
Not at all. The world of economics
makes a fine battlefield.
About that missing special delivery...
This is the Chief Gunner. Prepare for arms inspection.
You need money to feed your troops
and pay for weapons and ammunition.
And to add troublesome cargo to your warship's load.
I appreciate your cooperation, Captain.
I will put in a good word for you
with the Duke of Normandy.
Yes, I hope you will.
What was that?
The captain and one of the Duke of Normandy's men.
The one responsible for transporting the plates.
The gun room.
Here.
It's so far away.
And we have to go past the sailors' cabins?
Wh-what?
It does seem difficult.
We'll take a different route.
Change into this.
You're still wet. It will be cold outside.
"Outside"?
Do you see that turret?
The plates are under that.
I'll go first.
"First"?
When I pull the wire three times, come after me.
No! I couldn't possibly...!
Think of Her Highness.
Is that...?
Miss Ange!
Someone's out there!
This is the underboard quarter crow's nest!
A suspicious person has appeared
below the fourth port hatch!
An intruder?
What's this about, then?
Sir!
There appears to be an intruder
on the ship's exterior.
Don't give me that nonsense!
We're in the middle of the sky!
Dammit! Shut off that siren!
How in the...?
She's coming this way.
Dash it all, she IS after the plates!
Miss Ange...
The door's locked!
Bring a cannon!
Confound it!
What IS she?
She's an intruder! Kill her!
S-stop shooting!
Fire!
There should be another one in here! Find them!
Oww... Miss Ange...
Miss Ange!
Are you all right?
The plates.
Take them... and get out of here.
When you reach the ground... call Dorothy.
I-I told you I refuse to help a spy!
Give it to her yourself-!
Just... go!
But there are plenty of other para...
No...
Major!
Major, are you all right?
Hurry.
Oscar! Norman!
Save yourself.
Answer me! Dammit!
Take the plates.
Honestly! What is it about you spies?!
Is the mission that important to you?!
I don't know how much they pay you,
but is patriotism and principle
really worth risking your life over?!
When you're dead, it's all over!
Beatrice.
If I die here, I'm just a spy.
But if YOU get caught, they'll suspect Princess.
And I will not let that happen!
Major! We're going to blow the door down!
If you can hear me, please step back!
We'll charge as soon as we fire!
All hands, prepare for impact!
Ready and...
Don't fire!
I'm fine. I dealt with the intruder!
The door was warped in the fight
and won't open, that's all.
I have everything under control here,
so you make sure there aren't any others!
Yes, Sir!
Major!
Wh-what is it?
This is Sergeant Stewart.
How did everything go the other day?
"The other day"?
The other day...
Beatrice.
Enough of your jokes.
I know that voice, Corporal Henry.
You're going to propose to Jennifer, aren't you?
Go win yourself some glory.
Yes, Sir! Excuse me, Sir!
How did you know?
I heard his voice back at the switchboard.
It's all or nothing. If the Cavorite breaks
before we land, we might both die!
I don't care!
Here goes!
I love Her Highness!
I love her kindness, her elegance,
her intelligence... all of it!
So I'm going to protect her!
I'll keep her safe from everything,
and be someone worthy to stand beside her!
And I...!
I hate that stupid Princess!
I knew it.
You are a liar, Miss Ange.
So how about we say we became friends
because of our common fondness for whiskey?
Couldn't you at least make it wine?
Dorothy just wants to drink.
What if we're all sea turtle egg-laying enthusiasts?
What? What does that even mean?
Exactly what it sounds like.
Etiquette dictates that at teatime,
we all enjoy it together.
I like salt in my tea.
Salt from the Black Lizard Planet.
Please, take your time.
Thanks.
This salt is awfully sweet.
Because it's high quality.
You girls...