Did you wait long, Takeo-kun?
No, I just got here!
Sunakawa-kun, why not come
see a movie with us?
Huh?
You like books and movies, right?
I don't really have any cash on me.
That's perfect!
Huh?
No, nothing...
Today is on me!
I got my paycheck.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Then, I guess I'll borrow money...
My name is Gouda Takeo.
I'm a first-year in high school.
It's almost fall, but right now,
it's the middle of springtime for me!
Today Is on Me
Did you really see the killer?
Yes! I'm telling the truth.
That's strange...
All the streetlights in that area were
out because a bolt of lightning
caused a power outage.
Takeo-kun...
Suna!
How was the movie?
Was it good?
The ending was different than the book,
but in a good way.
Was it fun?
Was it?
Huh?
Yeah, it was.
Great!
What's with you guys?
Anyway, when did the killer die?
While you were sleeping, Takeo-kun.
And he wasn't the killer.
Yeah!
Look, Sunakawa-kun... Mountains!
Yeah, mountains.
Well, Suna? They're mountains!
Sunakawa-kun, do you find mountains fun?
So, Suna, do you find mountains fun?
Well... I don't really go mountain climbing.
I guess.
Is this fun?
Is it?
Yeah, it's fun...
Yeah!
Oh, good timing.
We'll take a break there!
Sure, whatever.
I'm not that tired, though
Suna!
Sunakawa-kun
Happy...
...Birthday!
What?
It's your birthday, right?
September 13th, right?
Yeah, September 13th.
9/13 (Sunday)
It's the right date, yep. It's my birthday...
I totally forgot...
Sunakawa-kun
I was just taken aback.
I'd no idea this was about that.
You're perceptive, so we did a pretty good job
to keep it under wraps.
Well... Yeah.
I didn't expect this at all,
so I'm not sure how to react.
Just be happy.
You're right.
I'll be happy.
Thanks.
Success!
This is your present.
What is it?
A blanket.
You get cold easily, don't you?
You're always burrowed under
the covers until morning.
You always throw them off.
I get hot easily!
Sometimes, I can't sleep because
my feet are too hot,
so I put them up on the windows
to cool them down.
Oh, I see...
You have a high body temperature!
Yeah.
Well, I'll use this.
Thanks.
You're welcome!
You look good in it!
Thanks.
Bro Café
Machos
Welcome!
Today is on me,
so order anything you want.
You look great in that uniform.
Aw...
I love her!
Here's the menu.
Wow, there's protein tea.
I wonder if it'd bulk me up if I drank it.
If I bulked up,
I wonder if I'd be able to beat
egg whites in a single minute.
You might be able to.
If I bulked up, would you still like me?
I would, even if you bulked up.
Orange juice for me.
Oh, milk tea. Iced, please.
Got it.
We have an order!
One orange juice and one iced milk tea.
Aw...
Takeo-kun's working.
It's so cool!
What should I do?
The tray looks like a plate with him.
Yeah, it's so cool!
The manager asked that part-timer not to quit,
so he only works when he has time.
I hear he has a lot of fans.
Are you Gouda Takeo-kun?
And who might you be?
Hmm, I understand.
You are good-looking...
I guess I can understand.
But... I win.
I am Gouda Takeo!
Huh?
What?!
That's my friend, Sunakawa.
Oh, Suna.
Huh?! Sunakawa?
Eh? You're Gouda?
Yeah.
Takeo-kun?
The high-schooler?
That's right.
Gouda Takeo-kun?!
That's right, I'm Gouda Takeo.
What do you want?
Oh, um...
I don't mean any harm.
Here, this is my ID.
Ousaki University
Student ID
Oda Hayato
Ousaki University?
Oda Hayato?
That's my sis's university.
Huh? Sis?
Oh, hello!
Hi!
Oh, hello...
Sorry, Takeo...
I didn't mean to interrupt you at work.
Bye.
Oh, so it's one of her friends.
Then she's visiting?
Come to think of it,
she said she was coming home
for the long weekend.
What the hell do you think
you're doing to Takeo?!
What do you mean, "what"?
I told you I have feelings for you.
That's why I'm here.
I wanted to see for myself the
man you have feelings for.
This Gouda Takeo
that you like...
Wait, that's the one, right?
What the...
He was super
intimidating!!
It isn't that there's another
with the same name?
That's him!
That's Takeo!
Do you have a problem with that?
I mean,
I just didn't expect him to be that kind of guy.
I made a mistake and talked
to your brother first.
So he's the one who told you that
you look like a beautiful flower?
And the girl with him is his
girlfriend, Yamato-san?
That's right...
My heart's already been broken, okay?
Have you had enough?
Just go back to Nagoya already!
No, I won't.
I want to have a proper talk with Takeo-kun.
I need to know exactly what kind of man he is.
I want to know what kind of
man you fell in love with.
Oh, come on!
Let me have that much, okay?
Takeo-kun's the reason why
you turned me down.
No!
You'll just make things more complicated...
Just stay out of this!
Those two are happy.
Yamato-san's a really nice girl.
I'm happy for them!
I've got closure.
So just leave me alone!
Let me be!
Got it?
Just go home!
I'll take you to the station.
Come on! Hurry up!
Sunakawa-san, how did you
know that's where I'd be?
You're the one who sent me a text that
said you were going to see Takeo!
I'm glad I got to see his sister.
The last time she came was for Suna's dad.
She really helped me out last time...
What?
Um, she gave me advice about you and stuff.
I'd like to thank her somehow...
Maybe I can bake her something.
I'm sure she'd like that!
Okay.
Now that I think about it,
I wonder who that guy was.
Seemed like he was a friend of hers.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Oh, I'll have some of that coffee.
How long are you staying this time?
Until Sunday evening.
Did that guy go back?
Yeah, I took him to the station just now.
Did Takeo say anything?
No, nothing, really.
By the way, how long has
Takeo been working there?
Since summer.
His girlfriend's fine with it?
She seemed excited enough.
Oh, I guess.
That back... It was a pretty big turn-on.
I see nothing's changed
Where can I take Yamato with my paycheck?
Oh!
Welcome to MM Land
Special Halloween Event
10/1-11/1
MM Land?
It's a great place!
I love it!
It's kind of expensive, though.
I see.
Want to go sometime?
Huh?
Oh!
Oh...
I think I'll pass.
Oh, okay.
"Huh?"
Sunakawa
"Oh!"
"Oh..."
What does that mean, Suna?!
Oops, that's right.
His sister's visiting.
Sorry!
One time in junior high, I came over,
and she was in just her jammies.
Oh, morning, Takeo.
That was bad of me.
Makoto's still asleep.
She didn't seem to mind,
Have some milk while you wait.
but when she's here, I shouldn't
storm over whenever I want.
Takeo, I'm sorry for earlier.
Huh?
At your workplace.
Oh, you mean your friend.
Well, it's more like we're in the same seminar...
Then you're friends.
I'm sorry he bothered you.
No, I acted poorly toward him, too,
because I thought he was hassling Suna. Sorry.
So, what's the problem, Takeo?
Huh?
You wanted to talk to Makoto
about something, right?
Right...
Well, I asked Yamato to go to MM Land,
but she just sounded awfully half-hearted...
Half-hearted?
Like, she wanted to go,
but at the same time, she didn't want to.
Again?
You said something
similar last time, too
I think something's going on.
I'll ask her.
Let's have tea tomorrow with her.
I'll casually check in with her.
You'd do that?!
Leave it to me.
Gouda!!
Thanks!
See you tomorrow!
He needs a lot of help, doesn't he?
Hey! Don't you go worrying about me!
It's not like that anymore.
I want to help them, you know.
They're a really good match.
I want them to be happy.
Dream
Encounter
Takeo-kun!
It's been a while.
Hello.
Do you prefer tea over coffee?
I drink coffee, too.
I like both.
What about you, Yamato-san?
I prefer tea.
Yeah, I can see that!
I drink water.
And juice.
You're such a kid, Takeo.
Yamato-san...
Have you ever been to MM Land?
She went straight for it.
Oh, yes.
It's a fun place!
I really like it.
Right, it'd be weird to fish around,
instead of just asking.
She knows what she's doing.
I love MM Land, too.
What?!
She loves it? Then...
Then why not go with Takeo?
Huh?
She complicated things.
Um, I won't go with Takeo-kun.
Why not?
Are you holding back because it's expensive?
Guess you're ending up
asking her yourself,
anyway...
That isn't it.
But I just don't want to go there with you.
Why?!
I love MM Land, too.
Oda!
You didn't go back?
After we parted ways at the station,
I went up on the Skytree.
I'm sorry for being rude to you yesterday.
I didn't know you were a friend
of hers. I apologize!
So close...
Oh...
I see.
Sunakawa-san said I'm a friend of hers.
How cold...
I've told her I love her.
Oh, is that why you came from
Nagoya? To pursue her?
She turned me down, though.
Huh?
I see.
So this man likes her.
Suddenly, I'm starting to like him.
Sunakawa-san has someone else in her heart.
Hey!
Oh! She likes someone!
Sunakawa-san's love is unrequited, too.
What? Unrequited?!
Who'd do that to her?
Unforgivable!
It can't be helped.
The guy has a girlfriend.
Oh.
I guess that sort of thing can happen.
If you spill any more beans,
consider yourself dead.
Whoa, you're so scary...
Hey, so is the reason you don't want
to go to MM Land that jinx
that says if you go there on
a date, you'll break up?
Yes...
That's the reason, actually.
Oh, really?
Well, that sort of jinx is common.
I didn't even know about that...
I don't pay any attention to stuff like that,
but there are athletes and others who do.
When I hear about things like that,
I just can't go.
If there's even a slim chance,
I really don't want that to ever happen.
We can all just go together.
If it isn't just you two,
it wouldn't be a date.
So the jinx won't kick in.
I'll go, too, okay?
Really?
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Sure.
Wow, then we can go!
Yeah!
Thank you.
Thanks!
Takeo-kun, do you know they have a parade?
It's really sparkly!
What? Sparkly?
It's really pretty!
Really?
I really wanted to see it with you...
I see.
Well, now we can.
Yeah.
Great!
Maybe we can go tomorrow?
Is everyone free?
Yes!
Sunakawa-san's brother, how about you?
Uh, me?
Of course you'll go, too,
right? Sunakawa-san?
Hey!
Okay, that's all decided, then!
I'll be the organizer...
Give me your contact info, everyone.
You're trying way too hard.
That was fast!!
I'm so excited about tomorrow.
I have to think about what to wear.
Oh, did you know?
There's a ride that's super fast.
She's really girly, isn't she?
Takeo's girlfriend, I mean.
She's cute.
She really loves Takeo, too.
She's a good girl.
I can see that.
But...
I like you, Sunakawa-san.
See you tomorrow, then.
I'll send out a text about when
and where we're meeting.
Why did you tell him about Takeo?
I didn't...
I mean, I did.
It was an accident...
Huh?
It was a social event for my seminar,
and someone said he could do hypnosis.
I somehow went under, and...
You should be wary of hypnosis, too.
Sounds like it.
Evenin'.
Oh, Takeo-kun...
You really took me by surprise.
That's bad for my heart.
Oh, I texted everyone about tomorrow.
Okay, thanks!
What're you doing?
Oh, I'm trying to figure out
where I'll be staying tonight.
I only had my hotel booked till yesterday.
He came here for Ai, huh?
I guess a net café or a manga café.
You can just stay with me.
That's close
Huh?
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Mom, this is Oda-san.
He'll be staying over tonight.
Good evening...
I'm sorry to bother you so suddenly.
Oh, okay. Sure.
Wow!
I love salmon!
It's nice to have so many side
dishes all out at once.
I'm living on my own, so I miss home cooking.
I'm back.
Oh, you must be Takeo's father.
Thank you for having me!
I'm Oda, a friend of Takeo's.
Oh, hello.
Make yourself at home.
Does stuff like this happen often?
Your parents didn't seem to care at all.
No, not really.
Takeo-kun...
Didn't you find Sunakawa-san scary at first?
Not at all.
I see, I see...
You wouldn't, I guess.
I did, just a little.
I'm kind of loose and laid-back,
You have poor
attendance.
so I just laugh things off,
I'll be your errand-boy
if you'll pass me!
Oh, I'll carry that!
even with profs.
I guess I had it coming...
I lost really important documents for my seminar,
and ticked off the prof.
He was so mad, he said he
wouldn't let me graduate.
Oh, my god! Are you okay?
When stuff like that happens,
The prof went too far.
girls usually act nice and sympathize, but...
I'm sorry, Odacchi.
Sunakawa-san got mad.
You idiot!
That's why I told you not to weasel
your way out of everything.
First, apologize!
Don't make excuses.
Don't try to pass it off!
I'm sorry                  I'm deeply sorry
For whatever reason, she came
to apologize with me,
Oda!
I found them!
and she even found the documents.
Here!
They were in the cafeteria.
You didn't look hard enough.
Men...
She's awesome.
Right?
I thought she was older,
Maybe I'll call her "Sis."
but she was in the same year.
I couldn't stop using honorifics, though.
That's so like her.
When did I first meet her?
As far back as I can remember,
she was always around.
Takeo!
Wait, why are you wearing
your undershirt on top?
Without her,
I bet I would've gone through elementary school
wearing stuff wrong every day.
I'm fine if she loves someone else...
I just want to embrace her, feelings and all.
But...
But she won't fall into my hands...
He's a man, all right.
Goodnight.
Yeah.
Morning, Takeo.
Mornin'.
Mornin'!
Why are you at Takeo's place?
He let me stay with him.
But why?
Takeo-kun goes to sleep
real early, doesn't he?
Why do you have that with you?
I know!
If you told Takeo anything...
I didn't!
Sunakawa-san, when we go to MM Land today,
I'm going to separate Takeo and Yamato-san.
I'll make sure you two can be alone,
so you should tell him how you feel.
You said you're fine, but that's a lie.
You can't move on because you never told him.
Please tell him and get some closure.
My Jinx
Next time: My Jinx.