I love you, Haru.
I-I can't believe I just said that...
Wh-What now?
I kind of got carried
away by the moment...
What does Haru think?
Oh.
Heh...
Hmm...
I-I was lying.
Why are you blushing?
You're such a child.
He's acting mature?!
Uh...
So...
Wanna go out?
G-Go...?
N-No...  I was lying.
Wait, you were seriously lying?
That's brutal.
Oh, well.
That makes me feel better.
I feel much, much better.
What?
What?!
Nuisance
Sorry, I can't keep him at my place.
We have a pet cat.
Oh, that would be dangerous.
The cat will eat the rooster.
Actually, my cat's too scared
to come down from the dresser now.
You brought it back, Yoshida-kun!
You never stop, Saeko.
Hey, can we keep him at school?
We had chicken coops at my grade
school and middle school.
I think we had one at
our middle school.
Really?
I never noticed anything.
So Sensei, can you ask for permission?
What?!
No way!
You kids have no idea how much
of a pain those geezers are!
They gave permission...
Hooray!  Hooray!
What?  What?
Why?
A-Anyway!  You better take
good care of it, Yoshida-kun!
I'm counting on you, Mizutani-san!
I knew it...
Don't worry.  I'll help.
I can lend a hand,
since it's kind of my fault.
You're a nice person, Sasahara-kun.
You can call me Sasayan.
Sasayan-kun.
Library
Okay...
That should cover everything.
We just need to figure out what
Kick-off Meeting
Name: Nagoya
Clothing: Feathers
Food: Chicken feed
Shelter: Chicken coop
we're doing about the chicken coop.
Mizutani Shizuku-san,
please participate.
Gulp.
How do you build a chicken coop?
Oh, I can look that up.
You can find anything on the Internet.
There's a hardware store near my home.
I could go buy the materials.
L-Let's go together!
We can all go over the weekend!
The School Rooster Committee
Kick-off Meeting
Name: Nagoya
Clothing: Feathers
Food: Chicken feed
Shelter: Chicken coop
Sure, I guess...
Mind if we go after my practice?
Spending the weekend with classmates...
That's perfectly okay!
Now that that's set,
it's time for the next step!
Next step?
Choosing a meeting place!
You know, a location and time!
So...
Wanna go out?
N-No...  I was lying.
I feel much, much better.
Should I have accepted?
But that was a spur-of-the-moment
confession on my part.
What's wrong with me?
In any case, it's clear that
he wasn't happy about my feelings.
Misawa
Batting Center
Ah.
You're early.
Oh, yeah.
We got out of practice early.
W-Want to wait inside?
Sure.
Right, I don't like being
alone with boys.
Huh?
And don't come back.
Did you see that?
He was pretty handsome.
Yo.
'Sup, baseballer.
Huh?  Do you know him, Sasahara-kun?
Yep, I come here all the time.
What?  Are you also one
of Haru's friends?
We're in the same class.
I'll go take a few swings.
Sure.
Hmm?  What is it?
You shouldn't lend
strange people money.
Huh?
Yo, Natsume.
You're supposed to hold
the bat like this.
Huh?  What?
S-Sorry!
My brother broke my alarm clock...
Granny clothes.
Hardware
Absolutely not!
Why not?!
It's so cool!
There isn't enough money
in the federal budget!
Borrow money!  Take out a mortgage!
No!  Roosters can't find work!
I've had enough.
Let's leave them here and
go look for materials.
Sounds good.
Gold...  Gold... Gold...
Brown...  Black...
Excuse me.
Hey!  Aren't you...
I-It's them!
Perfect timing.
We need to talk to you.
Mizutani-san, how big should the...
Sasayan-kun.
A-Am I interrupting something?
Who's the twerp?
What do you jerks think you're doing?!
Run, Mizutani-san!
That was scary.
I thought you were going to fight them.
That's crazy talk.
I've never been in a fight in my life.
Let's get out of this place.
Hey!  Wait up!
Whoa, you're so slow!
Yoshida!
Behind you!
Mizutani-san's in trouble!
Haru!
Hey, Haru!  Wait!
No way...
Oh, it's you guys.
Crap.
Just run, Haru!
You're so slow, Shizuku.
Uh-huh, yeah.
Sorry, but can you buy what
we need, Natsume-san?
They might still be around.
Thanks.
I'll go help her carry everything.
Yoshida, look after Mizutani-san.
Sure.
Drink this.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
Yeah...
The surprises never end with you.
You sent him flying with one arm...
What am I supposed to say
to the guy I just rejected?
You're acting weird.
Huh?
Normally, you would refuse
to look after the rooster.
You would refuse to go
out over the weekend.
It's weird.
Did something happen?
He's right...
This guy is weirdly perceptive.
Nothing happened.
Don't lie to me.
I-I'm not lying.
Are you sure?
If you say so.
They're taking forever.
Was he worried about me?
Hey!
We bring goodies!
Misawa Batting Center
Parking Lot
Cutting wood is a pain in the ass.
I told you to ask the
store to cut it for us.
It doesn't seem realistic
for the four of us
to build this coop by ourselves.
I went with the simplest
instructions I could find...
I told you we should have
bought that cool one.
Oh?  What's this?
You're already giving up?
Sawing wood?
That's grueling work.
Oh, I have a chainsaw you can use.
Why didn't you mention that sooner?!
Man...  I'll go grab it.
Then I'll go buy ice cream.
What do you want?
Get me a soda flavored
Garigari-kun popsicle.
I'll have a Choco Monaca Jumbo.
You've got it!
Are we going to finish this today?
Found ya.
Whoa, they're back.
Don't be too hasty.
We want to talk.
Anyway, we kinda feel bad,
but he's been ignoring us.
Oh.
Why don't you apologize then?
Right, Mizutani-san?
I think it's selfish to expect him to
listen after you hurt his feelings,
but you're welcome to offer an apology.
As long as you don't
interfere with our work.
This girl is cold...
Can't you see that we're
asking you to help us out?
Not my problem.
Oh, I see how it is.
You're in love with Haru.
Wow, for real?
I-I'm not!
Oh, really?
I said that I'm not!
Hey!  It's you guys!
Haru!
Now, now.  Calm down, Haru.
I'm outta here!
We're only here to talk.
Right, Mizutani-san?
Don't touch Shizuku.
That hurt!  Listen to me!
Get that dirty look off
your face, Yamaken.
You're always resorting to
violence like a little brat!
So, why are they here?
Don't touch her like that.
Beats me...
Oh...
Hey, Haru.
They want to make peace.
As proof,
they're going to help us
build the chicken coop.
What?!  That's bullshit!
Why would we waste our time on that?!
If you want to make peace,
you need to show that you mean it.
Make peace.
She's right.
Oh, I see.
You should have said something sooner.
That's great.  Come join us.
Too easy...
I-I've seen this happen on TV before!
We're going to become
friends now, right?
Hey, you're actually attracted to this?
You're in love with this?
You guys aren't so bad.
I bought ice cream!
I got sidetracked, so
it's a little melted.
There's more people!
Whoa!  She's super cute!
Next, assemble these.
You're right.  She's super cute!
Hey, don't let go!
M-Mitty...
What's your name?
Who are these people?
I can build something without
doing any work myself...
Beautiful.
What?!
Nagoya
And so, we were able to
complete the chicken coop.
It's not cute!
It's so cool...
Yeah, we did a good job.
I brought Nagoya.
He went inside!
Ain't it great?
Congrats, Mizutani-san.
You didn't do any work.
Why would I?
I told you not to touch her.
That hurt!
Cut it out!
You ticked me off.
I can't wait to take it
to school next week.
Yeah.
I have a feeling we're
going to get yelled at.
Just put it in a grassy spot and it'll be fine.
Your friends are a little scary,
but they're nice people.
Oh...
Yeah.
Hmm?  Why did he look at me?
I'm going this direction.
Ditto.
I'll walk with you.
See you on Monday!
Good job, everyone.
Bye.
By the way, why did
you name him Nagoya?
Now you ask?
Nagoya Cochin chickens are famous.
This is far enough, Haru.
Don't be shy.
Huh?
I want to stay with you a little longer.
There he goes again...
What now?
I can't bring myself to look up at him.
Did you know?
God decides when people get
to be lucky or unlucky
so everything balances out in the end.
It nets to zero?
Well, I don't believe any of that.
It's a bunch of smoke and mirrors.
Still, I've been thinking lately.
If meeting you was my lucky moment,
it balances out everything
else that's happened.
Only good things have happened
since I met you.
I—
I give up!
You win!
I love you, Haru.
It's impossible to guess
how someone else feels.
In that case, I should let it all out.
You said that you felt much better
after I said that I didn't love you.
You meant what you said, right?
I understand that you
don't want my affection,
but I've fallen in love with you.
What am I supposed to do?
You're pretty blunt.
Only because you keep playing dumb.
Sorry.
It's not that I don't
want your affection.
I love you, too.
I've had some dirty thoughts about you.
I didn't need to know that.
But my love is probably
different from yours.
I thought you would leave
me if you realized that.
I was scared.
I see.
In that case, let's start all over.
I'll wait for you to fall in love
with me before I say it again.
Yes, this is right.
The answer was very simple.
Well, we should go home, Haru.
Y-Yeah...
After all, Haru said that
he wants to be with me.
That's all I need right now.
Mi-chan
Yuzan's on his way
Shizuku, don't go home yet.
Let's find a place to spend the night.
My simple answer
was immediately shot down.
What?
What?!
Seriously...
He's so much trouble!
I'm home.
I'm Yoshida.  Thanks for having me.
Nice to meet you, Pops.
Uh, Shizuku-san?  This is...
He doesn't want to go home tonight.
What?!  What's that supposed to mean?
Takaya, have you eaten dinner?
Yes.
Nice place you got here.
N-No, it's just a normal house...
Isn't your mom around?
She's working.
You can stay in the guest room...
Let's find a place to spend the night.
For a moment there, I was
picturing something else.
Here.
What's this?
It's just fried rice.
Did you make this?!
Weren't you watching me?
There's also pickled vegetables.
You're amazing!
Like one of those countryside grandmas!
Thanks.
Man...
I told you not to come back here.
Are you listening to me, Yuzan?
Hey, there's a spirit in this house.
H-How can you walk around
my house naked like that?!
Wait, you study at home, too?
Wh-What do I do?
I can't look at him...
I'm bored.  Let's play a word game.
No, thanks!
Actually, Dad always walks
around in his underwear.
I-Is this normal?
I-I guess I could sneak a peek...
Use the futon if you're going to sleep.
Where is he?
He's not coming home tonight.
What?!
Sweet
But I brought him a present!
Whatever.  Make me
some tea, Mitsuyoshi.
Yeah, yeah.
Haru's such a coward.
He can't run away forever.
He was acting a little strange,
but maybe it was my imagination.
Oh, why were you guys in
the spray paint section?
Duh.
For graffiti, of course!
It's a crime to deface public property.
It's not against the law to spray
the statues in my own home.
His yard is full of sculptures!
Why do punks like to draw on walls?
Because the wall's
asking to be drawn on!
And because walls are a
big draw for punks!
My point is...
Hmm?
Yard is full of sculptures...
He's rich and an art buff?!
Hey, don't be too...
Do you want to know why
I named you Nagoya?
It's because...
No, forget it.
Something happened with
Nagoya Cochin in my past...
No, I can't tell you.
It's a secret.
Next Episode
Summer Break
Sorry!  I can't tell you!
Cut me some slack!