Is that...
Could that be...
The Skytree?!
No, that's just a transmission tower.
Samurai
of the East
Nekoma
Metropolitan
High School
Here we are, Tokyo!
The scenery's not that different from Miyagi.
Well, we're in the suburbs.
Walk faster!
Actually, hey...
Aren't we missing some people?
Actually...
This is how awesome...
...your senpais are!
You both barely got over 40 points...
What? Hinata, you failed English?
But you were so confident...
Apparently, he figured out
right before time was up
that he'd filled in all his
answers off by one.
Seriously?
Sadly, the English teacher, Ono-sensei,
won't let things like that slide.
Yeah, Yachi-san was really shocked.
They're right... They're right!
And Kageyama failed modern lit...
Apparently, there were a lot of reading
comprehension questions this time around.
But he'd concentrated on
memorization when he studied.
Wow, he got a perfect score on kanji. Dang...
Well, don't be too discouraged.
This won't be the only
time we have away games...
How are we gonna get to Tokyo?
Should we run?
Nah, we need bikes.
They're totally planning on going.
Hey, you two.
Huh?
So the power duo's taking some
supplementary exams right now?
Yeah... But, well...
Th...
There're two girls now!
Now they've got a pretty one and a cute one!
A mohawk... Tokyo's intense.
Do you see, Tora?
Samurai
of the East
This is what Karasuno's
true ability looks like.
So bright!
Let's go.
R-Right...
All right. When you're all
ready, come to the gym.
The other guys are already there.
Yeah.
Haikyu!!
Episode 4: "Center Ace"
Well, well...
You two look unusually serious.
You guys only failed one test, right?
Then you should be able to finish your
supplementary exam in the morning.
After that, I'll call your savior.
Do your best!
Hey, failure boys.
Karasuno Cafeteria
Get in.
A-Are you Tanaka-san's older sister?
Call me Saeko-nesan.
I'll get you two to Tokyo in no time.
Saeko-nesan!
Karasuno Cafeteria
All right, here we go!
Yeah!
However, the safety and comfort of the
ride absolutely cannot be guaranteed.
Thank you for your understanding.
It's been a long time,
Nekomata-sensei.
Glad you could come all this way.
Thank you so much for letting us
participate in the group practices.
Not a problem. I'm looking forward to seeing
just how much stronger they've grown.
Let's play!
Yeah!
Huh? Where's Shoyo?
Apparently, he had a supplementary exam.
Oh...
Ubugawa High Volleyball Club
All right!
Fukurodani
Once we're done with our warm ups,
we'll regroup and the teams will
play each other in rotation.
Right.
The team who loses their set will do a penalty
lap of diving drills around the court.
a lap of diving drills around the court.
Diving?
They're going to act like they're
diving to receive a ball.
They'll slide across the floor on their chests,
with their arms stretched out in front of them.
Take a look at the match line-up over there.
Hey, was that guy with Nekoma the last time
You should be up against Shinzen first.
we had a practice match with them?
Got it.
The one who's staring hard at us?
Yeah.
No... I don't think so.
Hey, stop sulking.
I can understand that
you're in a hurry, but...
There are some flowers you only
see when you take detours.
I don't really get it, but that's awesome!
It means you should be thankful
for your failing grade,
because now you get to ride with me.
Whoops.
So you like volleyball so much that
you're that concerned about it.
Yes!
Why did you start playing volleyball, Shoyo?
When I was in grade school,
I saw the spring tournament on TV!
It was right when Karasuno
was playing, and...
I saw the Little Giant!
You saw the Little Giant,
or something?
Ha, so I was right?
Saeko-nesan, you know the Little Giant?
I think I actually went to school with him.
What?!
But I never spoke to him.
I might have known him better if he
was the mischievous type and stood out.
Were you like the sort of person who's friends
with all the bad guys, Ne-san?
Pretty much, yeah.
But...
I happened to catch one of their
practice matches one time,
than any of the scary-looking people I knew.
But more than scary, he was intense.
You mean the way he'd spike the ball?
No...
Maybe he wasn't feeling his best at the time,
but he was being switched out.
Karasuno                  Yugama
He's what you guys call an ace, right?
The absolute pride and
confidence of being the ace...
You could see that rising up from his body.
Actually, I almost fell for the guy.
So when the ace is in action,
everyone around him acts
like they aren't gonna
let him do all the work.
Ne-san, you know a lot
about the Little Giant.
Not really! I just happened
to see some of his matches.
You were awake, huh?
Well, I was hungry.
So you just follow your instincts.
Yes.
...we won't get weaker
just because you watched us.
The absolute pride and
confidence of being the ace...
All right, it's just a little farther.
I'm flooring it!
#7!
Karasuno       Fukurodani
One!
Nishinoya, nice receive!
Left! Left!
Damn it!
Karasuno       Fukurodani
As we suspected, they're very strong.
Yeah.
One lap of diving drills!
Right!
It's not that we're not on top of it.
This is just what it means to be a team
that competes in the nationals.
Nice serve!
Damn it, Tarako!
Their arms are gonna snap off!
Everyone on that team is
very strong server.
The manager from Ubugawa mentioned that.
They put their all into their serves.
Yeah...
I think it's a bit harsh how to have to do a
hundred serves at the end of their practices.
One more! Nice serve!
Ubugawa High School's serves
are their ultimate attacks.
Ubugawa High School
(Kanagawa)
But once we're able to return that serve...
Bring it!
Whoa! They're all moving at once?!
Too bad, I'm actually over here!
That was an amazing combo.
Th-There are people
jumping up everywhere.
I can't tell who's going to hit it.
Yeah!
They are indeed the masters
of using combos.
Shinzen High School
(Saitama)
Shinzen High School.
And then we have our destined rivals...
Yaku-san!
Those are some excellent receives, as usual.
The school that's known to
pick up the ball, connect,
and wait for the perfect
chance to counterattack:
Nekoma High School
(Tokyo)
Nekoma High School.
Two blockers!
And...
Sorry, cover me!
Got it!
Akaashi!
Just like Ushiwaka,
Bokuto-san!
he's one of the top five aces
heading to nationals.
Tsukki!
Damn it, Kenma! Don't run away!
But my arms are gonna break off...
They won't!
We're very thankful...
All right! I'm so awesome!
Hey, hey, hey!
school whose powerful team is lead by
a powerful ace to compete in nationals:
Fukurodani Academy
(Tokyo)
Fukurodani Academy.
To be able to take on such amazing teams...
Yeah.
However, this is no time to be scared
of how strong our opponents are.
We have to be on the same
level as these guys.
Karasuno        Ubugawa
All right!
One lap of diving drills!
Right!
How many times have they lost already?
They're not exactly weak,
just sorta... mediocre.
Who are the first-years that
Nekoma had such a hard time with?
Maybe Nekoma was exaggerating.
Calm down, Hitoka-chan. There, there.
It's okay.
If what Tanaka said was true,
it shouldn't be much longer...
Hey, they're still at it.
We totally made it.
Not bad at all.
Ne-san!
Wait, that's your sister?
No, she's Ryu's sister.
Now that you mention it, they do look alike.
Glad they made it in one piece.
So the stars are showing up fashionably late?
How annoying.
Haikyu!!
Nice serve!
Nice receive!
Hey, what was that?
All right!
So fast...
I've never seen a quick attack like that.
We're stopping the next one!
Right!
Nice serve!
Sorry! Cover me!
Eikichi, I'm counting on you!
Wow, nice serve! Not bad!
Nice, Hinata!
Eikichi! Stop their #10!
Shinzen       Karasuno
Damn it!
I managed to tap it,
but I couldn't control it.
What the hell is up with their
#9 and #10's quick attack?!
Don't act all cool, you tardy test flunkers.
One lap of diving drills!
Right!
So in our ninth set, we finally got a win.
We finally don't have
to do the diving drills.
I'm starving!
Nice serve!
Looks like it's Ubugawa High
versus Nekoma over there.
Yaku-san, nice receive!
Given the time, that might be
the last game today.
Yeah.
In the second half, they were able
to keep up with that quick attack.
Date Tech,
Seijoh,
and Inuoka from Nekoma.
Apparently that quick attack won't keep
working on strong opponents after all.
Yaku-san! Nice receive!
Huh?
Inuoka's on the sideline?
One blocker!
Go, Lev!
All right!
A swing like a whip?
Wow...
That #11...
At first glance, it's hard to tell
because he's slouching,
but he's pretty big.
He might be over 190 cm.
His arms and legs are so long.
Who the heck is he?
Nekoma          Ubugawa
All right!
Seriously, who the hell are
that shrimpy middle blocker
and setter from Karasuno?
They were completely toying with you.
Shut up! Take a look at
their quick attack up close!
You wouldn't know what the heck was going on!
Man, this year looks like
it's gonna be interesting.
Good job!
Your quick was as amazing as ever, Shoyo.
But at this rate, nothing's going to change.
Nothing's changed since then.
I came here to get stronger.
Hey! Who the heck is that middle blocker?
Oh...
That's the first-year, Haiba Lev.
He's half Russian and half Japanese.
H-Half?! So cool!
L-Le...
Lev. What does it mean
in Russian again? Tiger?
It means lion! Yup, lion!
He wasn't there last time, right?
Yeah. Lev started volleyball in high school.
When we went to Karasuno around Golden Week,
he still hadn't played very much,
and only the regular members went.
He just started and he can play like that?!
Yeah. And when we were paired
together, it was really difficult.
No matter how hard I tried,
our timing was off.
I'm used to it now, though.
Huh...
Kenma-san couldn't stop sighing.
I guess there are times when even
you can't read people, Kenma.
Lev is just too special.
Right now, he's mostly working with his
innate physical abilities and instincts,
and his height.
Yeah, his height totally isn't fair!
I want some!
He's been blessed with too much!
But I'm not gonna lose!
Well, he's a powerful asset,
honest, and not a bad guy.
Though he's too honest at times.
Oh, but his passing basics
are still completely bad.
He's worse than you, Shoyo.
His serves are worse than yours, too, Shoyo.
Am I the the guideline of
what's bad or not, Kenma?
Kenma's actually talking
without being shy.
But you are bad.
Yeah.
Haiba... Haiba Lev, huh...
Western-style names are so cool!
R-Russian! A Russian greeting! Russian!
Karasuno's #10.
Japanese?!
Oh, sorry. I can't speak Russian.
I was born and raised in Japan.
I see! Hey, how tall are you?
I'm Hinata Shoyo, a first-year.
It was 194 centimeters
the last time I checked.
I'm Haiba Lev, a first-year.
194! So cool!
You're even smaller up close, Hinata.
What'd you say?! Huh?!
Men's Bathroom
S-Sorry! I didn't mean anything bad by it.
But you have no problem
jumping this high, do you?
I saw that earlier in the match.
But I can jump even higher than that.
Men's Bathroom
Ow...
Then I'll jump even higher!
Past that, to the very top!
Your spikes were really cool,
since you didn't seem to care
if there were blockers there or not.
Yeah, well...
I'm Nekoma's ace.
But if I actually said that, Taketora-san
would get really mad at me.
Wha? You don't call a guy
who can barely guard an ace!
But you're a middle blocker like me, right?
Center, right?
Aces are usually like the mohawk guy
on your team, the wing spikers, right?
Do position names have
anything to do with it?
The one who's able to score the
most points is the ace, right?
Simple as that.
Well, see you tomorrow.
I'll be the first one to stop
your quick tomorrow, Hinata.
"The one who's able to score
the most points is the ace."
With their own hands...
Ubugawa         Karasuno
Bring it!
All right!
Karasuno looks a lot calmer than
they were during Golden Week.
Not to mention, they've got
their #10's usual quick attack.
Yeah. It does seem that they're
much more stable overall.
But are you content with that, Karasuno?
You lost with the power you
have right now, didn't you?
That's why you came here.
To become stronger, right?
All right! Our opponents still aren't able
to counter you weird quick attack,
so keep on using it!
Right.
Right...
Need a towel?
Oh, yeah.
#4!
It went up! Kenma, cover!
Left! Left!
Give it to me!
All right!
Nice kill, Lev!
Sorry for being rude.
I overstepped my bounds.
And I keep telling you not to worry about it.
But if you're asking for a slide hit
out of nowhere, I can't always keep up.
So that's called a "slide hit"?!
That's so cool!
So that was an unplanned slide hit?!
Well, I was still able to do it.
I'm Nekoma's ace.
Center ace...
Kenma! It's your turn to serve!
We lost in the IH prelims.
What do we need to choose to move forward?
I'm not sure if it's the proper path,
Kenma-san! One more! Nice serve!
but we've got new blood
flowing through our veins.
Does Karasuno want stability
in order to achieve more power?
Or is it...
evolution?
Lev's finally blending in with the team.
Yeah, even though it's little by little.
That's not true!
Oh? Do you feel like you're
not quite there yet?
I'm already an indispensable
part of the team! The ace.
You're an ace at not understanding
the position you play, maybe.
Episode 5: Greed
Next time on Haikyu!!
"Greed."