5 Days Until Christmas
Isn't Christmas great?
It's so exciting.
Why don't we all have a party on Christmas Eve?
That sounds like fun!
Christmas means chicken and cakes, doesn't it?
Sou, is there anything else you want to eat?
Let me see...
Christmas means salmon to me, I guess.
Salmon?
Why salmon for Christmas?
There's nothing wrong with salmon.
Right? Isn't salmon great?
Watermaple House
Japan Server
Akihabara
City/ No Monsters
No PVP
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
Um, isn't this a little too short?
My legs are completely visible.
That's not true.
It's a perfect fit, Sia.
Fifteen centimeters above the knee for justice!
It's so cute!
I don't really know a lot about Christmas,
but I believe that Santa Claus
was a man, was he not?
That's right.
Aww, Akatsuki's betraying us.
She'll have to be punished.
Shattered Wings
Shattered Wings.
You're both so cute!
I could eat a hundred chickens!
That'd be a snack after dessert!
Yes... Right.
They're wearing miniskirt-Santa and reindeer outfits.
It's super-duper cute.
Miss Liese, who are you talking to?
I'm reporting to my lord.
I'm just joking.
I'm not actually on the phone.
Thank goodness...
If that monster found out,
who knows what he would say?
I'm sorry.
That was a bit mean of me.
My lord is so dedicated to the princess,
I couldn't help myself.
Everyone!
Mikakage
Race/ Human
Druid, Lv. 78
Roderic Merchant Guild
It's snack time!
Let's eat.
At first, it was only Akatsuki...
It's delicious.
This fruitcake looks like jewelry, doesn't it?
It does!
You're so good at desserts and cooking, Mikakage!
To me, sweets are an art,
and all other food is just for fun.
Nyanta's food is also good, though.
I can't believe I get to eat delicious cake
while I'm protecting the princess.
This is a great job.
When are the D.D.D. members coming back?
I've been told that the attack on
the goblins is going very well,
but at earliest, not till after New Year's.
They won't be back for Christmas, huh?
But we had a big event planned...
Everyone's really busy.
I haven't seen Shiroe at all lately, either.
Is he locked in his room again?
He...
Well, Shiroe isn't really the type
that enjoys events like Christmas.
And I'm sure there's a lot of work
to do for the new year.
You're right.
It's really tough, isn't it?
See you later, Princess.
Farewell.
Akatsuki!
Thanks for today.
For dressing up like that with me...
That was...
They forced me to do it.
But you come every day.
I've been meaning to thank you.
Thanks.
Well, it's my job...
See you tomorrow.
Okay.
When did I get so weak?
Guarding the princess...
I should be happy that my lord is relying on me.
But when I realize that he's thinking about her,
it hurts.
If I were like her, would things have
been different between me and him?
But if I were like the princess...
I couldn't have been by my
lord's side as an assassin.
Amenoma
Um...
May I ask a question?
What happened to the katana that was here?
We sold it.
Really?
Yeah, really.
They very boldly paid in cash.
Akatsuki seems like she's suffering.
Does she seem that way to you, too?
She does.
Normally, she isn't the type to let her
feelings show, so it's really obvious.
I see...
Akatsuki has been coming to observe the D.D.D. training sessions.
I only noticed her there once...
5 Days Until Christmas
But it looks like she's been there many times.
You know, we work hard to provide
the best raiding environment in Akihabara.
But it didn't seem like she wanted to join.
I reported it to my lord,
and he said to allow her to
watch as much as she liked.
I guess he owes Shiroe something.
He said to help Akatsuki if anything came up.
Is that so...
It's possible she's observing other guilds, as well.
Is she dissatisfied with her level or skills?
It may be something even more basic.
I think what Akatsuki wants is confidence.
I suppose all we can do is to stay by her side.
You're right.
Duvarcher's Bird Land
Japan Server
Mihama Area
Field/ Monsters Present
PVP Permitted
Skill Use Permitted
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
The Teachings...
Shiroe said they're real.
Shiroe did?
Yeah, he says they exist.
If my lord says they exist, then they must.
Major combat guilds like D.D.D.
and the Black Sword Knights
should have the world's best assassins.
If they're using the Teachings,
I want to see those techniques
and their power for myself.
Get closer!
That was pathetic.
Move faster!
If I can learn the Teachings, then I, too...
Akatsuki, welcome back.
We're having bouillabaisse today.
It'll be done soon.
Have a seat and wait.
I'm fine...
But it turned out really good.
And Rudy and the others will be back soon.
I'm not hungry.
What's wrong with her?
Lately, she's been really down.
Yeah.
That stupid, too-perfect middle school girl.
She's a brat, a child, and a show-off...
I'm embarrassed.
Whenever I see Minori, all I can
think about is how jealous I am.
I'm so ugly.
It isn't Minori's fault.
She's working so hard.
I'll work at least as hard as you.
I'll do my best, so I don't cause you problems.
Shiroe...
Minori helped my lord.
But I was so busy with my own
problems, I couldn't help him.
I've always been by his side...
Yet I can't be useful to him.
I've never been in a raid, so I'm
only a second-rate assassin.
I can't even buy a first-rate weapon.
That's why my lord didn't take me with him.
All I can do is fight, but I'm weak...
I wish I were strong.
It sure has been lively around here lately.
Will they all be back again tomorrow?
Yes, we're going into town.
I see.
If the adventurers are protecting you,
that must make you feel secure.
They say we'll have a delicious
cream stew for dinner.
That's wonderful.
Adventurer-style?
Seems so.
Recently, everything's been adventurer-style.
I even had to wear a costume of
someone called "Santa Claus" today.
Ah, I asked them to bring some things.
So that was among them, eh?
Huh?
I don't know anything about adventurer clothes,
so I wanted them to teach me.
So that's it...
But wearing clothes you aren't
used to is kind of tiring.
Well, I don't know if I should say this,
but you seem to be having a good time.
I'm glad you've made friends.
They aren't my friends.
What? But you look like
you're having so much fun...
I'm sure you sometimes feel
uncertain or troubled, but...
I wasn't having fun talking to them.
They aren't like us People of the Land.
They're adventurers.
But you...
The etiquette I've learned doesn't work with them.
If you're having fun, you say you're having fun.
If you're sad, you say you're sad.
If you're happy, you say you're happy.
Otherwise, they won't know what
you're feeling, so that's what I'm doing.
Normally, I'm lazy, cowardly, and irresponsible.
I don't care about high society or nobility.
That's just my job.
Maybe she can't be honest with herself
because she's been expected to
be a perfect lady since she was little.
But he's the one exception, isn't he?
Our march on the goblins is steadily
raising the participants' levels.
If we keep fighting like this until spring,
they'll be a powerful force when
they return to Akihabara.
My lord?
Hm? Oh, yes.
Are you bored?
Do you want a new toy or something?
Of course not.
If there's any change, let me know.
He's so easy to read.
Roderic Labs
Japan Server
Akihabara
Separate Zone/ No Monsters
PVP Permitted
Entry Restrictions/ Yes
Exit Restrictions/ Yes
What shall we do about the ambrosia?
Keep it going.
Roderic...
It's already night.
What?
That's strange.
I thought it wasn't even noon yet.
Even if you skip lunch, night will still come.
I have several matters to discuss with you.
How about joining me for lunch?
I told you, it's night now.
Then let's get some ramen.
Oh, all right.
Here you go!
Ramen
How's progress with the list I asked you for?
You need high-end phantasm-
and treasure-class items...
And quite a lot of them.
But why include the flavor text?
There's some reason, I assume.
Well, I understand that we're
the right people to come to.
We can work out a way to
finance the research funds,
where other, smaller guilds couldn't.
I'm very grateful.
It's none other than Shiroe's request.
I'll do my best.
I'm sure we'll need this research eventually.
I'm counting on you.
Chief Nyanta, do you have a moment?
Perfect timing.
I just came from the Roderic Merchant Guild.
Thank you.
I know I should've been the one to go.
Don't worry about it.
I got some tasty ramen out of the deal.
How's everyone doing?
The city's excited for Christmas,
but nothing's really changed.
It's that time already?
Um... What about Akatsuki?
She's visiting Princess Lenessia daily.
All right.
I'll contact you if there's anything else.
What did the chief say?
Nothing's really changed.
Oh, but he said everyone's excited for Christmas.
There's no way we'll get this
done in time for Christmas.
Enough!
Ow...
Thank you!
You really are strong, Kyouko.
I'm level 90, after all.
Please tell us the secret to your strength!
Akatsuki...
This is nice!
Let's take it to the palace.
It'll brighten the place up.
You're right.
Sia will be so happy.
You shouldn't call the princess "Sia," should you?
She laughed and looked happy, so it's fine.
Is that for Naotsugu?
Um, well, when he gets back,
I wanted to give him at least
a little Christmas to enjoy...
A maiden in love!
I-It's not like that at all.
What about you, Henrietta?
Do you have anyone to give a present to?
Me?
I don't.
Really?
Come on... If you're going to buy it, buy it.
Just wait a second.
Excuse me!
An unrequited love, from a safe distance.
This feeling is just a sweet ache I can live with.
Of course there are wishes that can't come true.
I've gotten used to that pain.
Marie's bottomless cheer casts its
glow on everyone around her.
It may be her self-confidence.
But Akatsuki...
Akatsuki is so bright!
She hasn't lost the easily injured vulnerability
that grows numb as adulthood sets in.
That vulnerability may be her weak point,
but it's also a great treasure.
Not that she's realized that.
She's so precious, I just want to
squeeze her tight right now!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Princess Lenessia, you look so cute and fluffy.
Really?
I chose it from her wardrobe.
Well, let's go!
Before we get that stew, let's look around town.
I want Sia to learn more about Christmas.
Right.
Get too excited, and you'll trip.
Ow...
The adventurers
are so different from us,
I don't understand them at all.
Many People of the Land ask me various
things about the adventurers,
but I don't know, either.
I deal with them every day,
but the number of things I don't
understand keeps rising.
Even so, there's one thing I've learned.
The adventurers are only adventurers.
Even if I don't know the right answers,
it's a mistake to lump them all into a group,
and merely view them by their jobs or roles.
Even I know that.
The adventurers are jewels.
Each one of them is different,
and shines brightly.
They're special.
So I can't call myself their friend.
We're here.
Restaurant
Milky Margaret
The stew here is fantastic!
I heard it's super-duper good.
Let's hurry inside!
I'll be leaving you all here.
What's wrong?
I have something to do.
All right.
We'll take care of the rest.
Restaurant
Milky Margaret
Is she going to watch someone train again?
Akatsuki's suffering, too.
She's like a dagger...
She's like an obsidian dagger,
strong and beautiful.
I know I can't get stronger simply
by watching people train.
I don't have the power needed to do anything...
I miss my lord.
I want to talk to him, just for a bit.
To get close to him, to tug on his coat.
To sit on the same sofa, and look out the window.
To eat red bean buns.
I want to be near him always.
Even if I'm just in the background.
But that's just me lying to myself.
If I can't fly anymore, I can't be by my lord's side.
Right now,
I still can't be with him.
I got three salted salmons at Shopping Street 8.
I'm sure Sou will be happy!
Santa?
Enheart Nelreth/ Samurai
No, it's not!
A PKer?
But there's no fighting allowed inside towns!
The Royal Guard isn't coming.
It's okay.
I'm the West Wind Brigade's
second captain for a reason!
There's no way I can lose!
When his dear friend is wounded,
Soujirou's rage silently rises.
Lenessia is forced to make an important decision.
Akatsuki runs through the city, lost in thought.
As the snow falls, the battle with
the murderer finally begins.
What secret of the Teachings does
Soujirou share with Akatsuki?
Next time: Christmas Eve.
Christmas Eve
Rise up once more.