Okay, engine repairs are complete.
Restarting all systems.
Alektra.
Hurry, get the stretcher.
It's no use.
Just...
Give me a smoke.
Embryo...
I tried to destroy his Ragna-mail,
but he got away.
He's not anywhere I can reach.
I'm sorry, Alektra.
I did something so stupid...
You really are just like me.
You're like my sister.
You're so serious, and such a crybaby...
And so presumptuous.
Right down to your taste in men.
That's why
I didn't want you mixed up in this.
I'm sorry I took it out on you.
Alektra.
I'm glad in the end I—
Alektra!
What the?
Merging at 98.5%.
Don't give up!
The tremors stopped.
Between time and space...
At the end of non-gauge space,
in a sea of imaginary spaces.
That's where Embryo is.
Who are you?
Aura...
To the End of Time
No.
This can't be...
Yes. This is Arzenal.
The original one.
The two Earths and the two humanities.
The world of Mana, and the Tuner.
Everything began here.
And soon, everything ends.
Come, Ange.
Let's watch the birth of the
new world from premium box seats!
To hell with that!
Don't bother trying to run.
This isn't the Arzenal that you know.
Let's tell an old story.
This island used to be the world's top
elementary particle research facility.
Here I discovered and created many things.
Unification theory.
Supersymmetric particles.
And multiverses.
Our foray into a new world
began a new age of discovery...
Using manned dimensional
probes called Ragna-mail.
The plan was to use them
to open doors to new worlds.
But due to the sudden emergence of a
localized inflation, the system went haywire,
and this island was caught in a
rift between various space-times.
But that was the beginning of everything.
Time had stopped here.
Huh?
I had infinite time.
It became my personal garden.
It was the safest of all spaces.
From here, I began using the
Ragna-mails to influence the world.
I ended wars, created a new world,
and recreated humans.
As the Tuner, I would guide humanity.
Unfortunately the advanced
information technology
society based on Mana failed.
But you alone were different.
You are a strong,
intelligent woman, fit for me.
An angel born among misfits.
Let's create the next thousand
years for humanity together.
I'll pass!
We're going to be alone together now.
Forever. Here.
L-Like hell!
A rift between space-times?
Yes, a place isolated from all universes,
inaccessible even from a singularity.
How are we supposed to get there, then?
The Villkiss.
That machine has an activated
space-time jump system.
There isn't time.
Hurry, while I'm holding
back the space-time merger.
But Ange is the only one
that can use the Villkiss.
No.
Ragna-mails were created to
shed light on humanity's future.
It will respond to a strong will,
to a person's wishes.
It will.
A strong will.
Tusk, you do it.
Huh?
I hate to admit it,
but Ange is most strongly connected to you.
Villkiss! Villkiss!
It's no use.
I left the ring behind.
You!
Beautiful.
But...
But you've been sullied!
By that wretched monkey!
I'll have to purify you...
With my love.
Please, Villkiss.
Lend me your strength.
Villkiss!
You violent piece of shit!
After all your big talk,
you're just a horny bastard!
You shouldn't speak that
way to your beloved husband.
Look.
It's the climax.
The space-time merger is coming.
Maintain control!
Why?
Why won't you move?
Villkiss!
You protected Ange all this time, didn't you?
Do you really want her to
be taken by that bastard?
Sing, sing, the two wishes are now,
Strongly, strongly shining in heavenly gold,
Wake up, Villkiss!
Lend me your strength!
It speaks of eternity.
Tusk.
I heard her.
What?
I heard Ange's voice.
The Villkiss.
Wow.
We must follow.
All right.
Tusk-san.
Please take care of Angelise-sama.
Hilda.
Take my Ragna-mail.
Okay.
Don't you dare die.
I'll be waiting, Hilda.
Salia-chan.
You better come back.
Fly, Villkiss!
Godspeed everyone.
I pray for good fortune.
Good luck!
It's... the rift between space-times!
The wind flies, El Ragna,
making promises with destiny.
The wind goes, El Ragna, with roaring wings.
The light of the beginning, Kirali, kirali.
The light of the end, Lulala lila.
The returning El Ragna...
The time flows,
Through the hour glass.
Lulala lila...
The flames of countless lives,
That's...!
Ange?
Fall through and become stars.
That's Ange!
They fly beautifully...
Ange!
Tusk!
Sorry.
You must have been scared.
Thank you for coming.
Everyone gave me a hand.
And I promised to give this back to you.
You idiot.
You.
How did you get in here?
Take the Villkiss.
The suit is in the bucket.
Get away from Ange!
Tusk-dono, here.
Thanks, Salamandinay-san.
You brought them all here for me, didn't you?
Here we go, Villkiss.
Everyone, it's that Ragna-mail
that's manipulating time.
And Embryo is controlling it.
We have to take down both...
Or we can't save the world, correct?
You still speak of defeating me, Ange?
It seems I'll have to make you to understand...
Even if it's by force!
Try it!
Ange, take those two!
We'll wreck these ones.
Welcome home, Salia.
I won't forgive you.
Not you!
That's my line!
He's not switching with
his body in undefined space.
You're the real Embryo!
For the crime of tarnishing my wife...
I'll kill you endlessly!
I believed you'd come back, Salia.
Yes.
To kill you!
This...
...is for Alektra!
My adorable Salia.
You just need to follow my orders...
Dodge!
What the?
What's happened to this thing?
Why?
Why did you have Ange?
There are plenty of women in the real world.
You could have chosen any of them!
But I waited a thousand years!
I only have Ange!
Ange, you're human, too.
You can't find happiness without my guidance.
So you abducted her and tried
to control her with violence.
What an embarrassing man, Tuner.
Salako.
Ange's not slutty enough to
fall for a coward like you!
Hilda!
That's exactly right.
I won't let myself be controlled by anyone!
Yeah, me neither.
Aura said the Ragna-mails
respond to people's wills.
I'm me.
I won't let anyone control me!
Me, too.
I won't let some shithead guy
have his way with me!
What?
Why, Ange?
My infinite time and infinite love...
Why won't you let me control you?
Because I'm human!
Anti-authoritarian, aggressive,
rebellious misfits...
That's what humans are.
I understand now why Normas were born!
Judgment!
Human genes will not be
controlled by the likes of you.
Why are Normas all women?
So they can bear children to those
they love, and so reject your world!
That's why Mother handed down
the song and the ring to me.
So I could destroy this rotten world,
made by a rotten creator.
I waited a thousand years to choose you!
I don't need a woman that
won't understand my love!
Love, my ass!
Always grinning behind your creepy hair,
with no sense of style, and always being cynical!
You shameless narcissist!
You don't even know how to treat a woman!
I really don't want the
genes of a dirty old man
who hid himself away
for a thousand years!
Return to dust!
I-Impossible!
This is for the sorrow of my father,
my mother, and my friends!
Take it!
Ange!
It's ten million years too soon
for you to even try to hold me!
Ange!
Tusk.
Ange.
Quiz time!
Where are we?
It looks really familiar.
Welcome to our world,
the true earth.
Hey, hey, why is Arzenal so huge?
Space-time was released,
and everything was
returned to its proper place.
The space-time merger has stopped,
and the world has been freed.
The world has returned...
And is now in your hands.
Libertus is over.
Yeah.
What are you going to do now?
There's no more reason for you to fight,
nor for us to continue killing each other.
I'll found a nation here.
A nation just for us.
No matter whether were
Norma, human, or DRAGON.
A nation where we live by our own will,
and where rough going is a given.
I'll follow you.
Anywhere.
And that is my duty.
Angelise-sama,
what's going to become of the other Earth?
Not my problem.
Embryo's dead.
No one will guide them anymore.
Fight, unless you want to die.
They'll starve to death if they
don't learn how to live on their own.
I suppose so.
Now, let's go.
Down our own path, with our own legs.
Yes, ma'am.