Thank you.
Her name is Fukahori Yurika.
2nd year, class six, seat number 22.
So she's a year ahead of us.
She moved here from Tokyo during
her first year of middle school.
Her hobbies are oil painting
and fencing with naginata.
Her birthday is February 10th.
That's all. Just for your information...
W-What are you talkin' about?!
Don't play dumb.
This has gotten as hard as a rock.
When you think about her,
you get a lump in your throat,
so you can't get the food down, right?
Poor thing...
You're completely lovesick.
L-Love?! This is what love is...?
Don't tell me you've never
fallen in love before?!
Nope.
You've got to be kidding me...
Wait. If he really falls for that girl,
then he won't get between Ri-chan and me.
Alright, we'll skip jazz after school today
and meet up to formulate a plan, instead.
Mikanomachi
End of Summer Sale
Hah? At my house?
We ain't goin' to Ri'ko's basement?
You'll be able to relax more at home, right?
I don't mind, but...
If we went to that basement, it's possible
Ri-chan would overhear us talking...
Here it is.
This is Ri-chan's shop...
We live in a row house, so Ri'ko's
place is connected to ours...
Hey, Ma!
Bro!
Welcome home, Bro! You're
back early today, huh?
Play with us!
Hold on, hold on. Where's Ma?
Ma, Bro's home!
Richie!
What are you doin'? Come on in!
Ma, this is Richie.
Oh, hello there.
I appreciate you always
looking out for Sentaro.
Oh... You're too kind...
Don't be shy. Dig in, Richie.
I thought you didn't have an appetite today.
I can always eat watermelon.
Sentaro loves his watermelon...
He told me he wasn't feeling
hungry, which is unusual for him,
but I had a hunch he'd be able to
eat watermelon, so I iced one up.
Hmph...
Bro! Bro!
What is it, Taichi?
We found a weird bug!
A bug?
Is it a big one?
It's over here!
Bro, if you plant a watermelon
seed, will it grow?
Let's plant one an' see.
Look, there!
Oh, there it is!
It flew!
Yeesh, don't cry about it!
A group date?
Yeah. The four of us will go,
including Ri-chan and me.
If you started with just the
two of you, she'd be on guard.
Huh... I get it...
Of course, you'll be the
one to invite Miss Yurika.
What's the point if you're
not the one who does it?
I can't! I just don't have it in me!
Look...
What's that sound?
Sarah.
Sarah?
My girlfriend.
Hah?
What's wrong, Sarah?
You're in a bad mood...
Cute, ain't she? Her full
name is Sarah Vaughan.
A pigeon, huh?
What is it, Sarah?
You're really agitated today.
She's probably jealous.
Since you keep talking about another girl...
Huh? What's wrong with me?
I'm suddenly enjoying myself?
That was so funny!
I know!
Oh...
U-Um...
I-Idiot! Who goes up to the
girl and then runs away?!
I can't do it, man!
Remember the note!
Y-Yeah...
He's coming back...
I'm sorry...
...for suddenly interrupting you.
Are you free this weekend?
I would like to take this
opportunity to cult... cult...
"Cultivate".
...cultivate... our friendship!
That idiot...
Richie! Richie!
She agreed! She says she'll go!
We're going to Rendezvous Rock, right?
Shall I pack us a lunch?
Um, that'd be great. Just something
light, like onigiri, would be good.
Okay, leave it to me.
By the way, just so I know...
Which of the two of you is inviting me?
Oh, that would be...
This guy! He insisted on inviting you!
Hah?
Oh.
I see.
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
You said okay to a date?!
Really?!
You really are a fool!
It was going as smooth as
can be and then you blew it!
Yeah, I dunno why I said that...
Wind back time for me, Richie!
As if I can?!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
There's Kaoru-san!
Hey, what happened to your face?
Oh, just another one of Sentaro's fights...
Let's go, Kaoru-san.
Wait a minute, Ri-chan. Actually, one
more person is joining us today...
I'm sorry!
I'm late!
Making lunch took longer
than I thought it would...
You're the girl those hooligans
were propositioning at the beach...
Th-That's right!
You remember her, huh? Actually, today...
Hey! Get a hold of yourself!
The one with the glasses invited me...
Are you alright?! Hey!
Kaoru-san invited you?
Yes.
What the heck are you doing?! Hey?!
Is it okay for a newcomer
like me to intrude...?
Get up already!
O-Oh, of course... The more the merrier!
What's wrong with you today?!
Really? Good.
Oh, so it was Kaoru-san that asked her...
She's beautiful...
Kaoru-san must have a
weakness for pretty faces...
What is it?
Nothing. I was just thinking
that your hat is really stylish.
Oh, this?
Even if I wore it, I would
still look like a yokel...
Oh, that's not true.
Pardon me...
Ri-chan, when did you change your hairstyle?
Yurika-san did it for me. What do you think?
It looks super. Really cute!
Oh, that's right. I'm told your family
owns a record shop, Ritsuko-chan.
Yes... Do you like jazz, Yurika-san?
These two practice playing jazz
music together just about every day.
They play jazz?
Uh-huh. Kaoru-san plays piano
and Sentaro is on drums.
That's really something! I know
some people who listen to jazz,
but this is my first time meeting
anyone who actually plays it!
My two big brothers like jazz,
so I listen too, once in a while.
My brothers frown and get a wrinkle
between the eyebrows while they listen,
but I prefer music that really
hits you with a bang, you know?
Y-Yeah! That's it!
I'd like to hear you play the drums.
Y-Y-You can't! I still, uh... stink at it!
Oh, but you know you can't get better
at music unless you have an audience.
Come on, let me hear you play.
This... is an unexpected development.
Ow!
Oh, no! I think I got scratched by a branch.
Well, what do you know?
Looks like he's got moves...
Say, I heard a rumor that
couples who climb together
to the top of that rock will get married.
No girl's gonna get up that!
Richie, you up for it?
Why me?!
Oh, I'm not letting you
get away with saying that.
I can climb that far!
Would anyone like to go with me?
Go on, already!
N-No!
I mean, the sign says it's off
limits... and it's dangerous.
Oh, that's too bad. I really wanted
to see the view from up there.
You shouldn't have wolfed it down!
Those two seem to be getting on well.
Kaoru-san... You can have this.
Where are you going?
I'm just going to pick some flowers!
Probably the bathroom...
Boy, this onigiri is huge...
It's my fault...
I hurt Ri-chan...
In the cruelest of ways...
...I made the girl who's
most important to me cry.
Those shoulders look so
sad, but I have no right...
...to try and comfort her.
Good morning, Kaoru-san.
Good morning.
Richie!
C-Come with me a sec!
This! This handkerchief!
Yurika-san gave it to me as an
apology for my towel yesterday!
It smells kind of nice...
Or is it my imagination?
What the hell was that for?!
Kaoru-san?!
I couldn't let you pick up this handkerchief!
I couldn't bear seeing that!
If you're here about the handkerchief,
you can have it back.
I was in the wrong.
It's all my fault.
What are you talkin' about?! Spill it!
Shut up!
You're satisfied as long as you
have this handkerchief, right?!
Go home and sniff on it all you want!
That's enough.
You lookin' to start a fight?
Stop it!
Sentaro, let go of Kaoru-san!
This is stupid...
Don't get rough with him! You
owe Kaoru-san an apology!
Hmph.
I don't owe that guy nothin'.
Wait, Sentaro!
You can't forget this.
This handkerchief is
important to you, isn't it?
Kaoru-san...
I bet Sentaro is drumming away
like a madman right about now.
Richie, you stupid idiot!
...and like that.
It's easier to make up if you do it early on.
Come with me to practice.
No...
Kaoru-san, before you moved here,
Sentaro always practiced alone.
Shutting himself up in the basement,
not letting anyone near him...
Even I didn't feel welcome in the basement.
But ever since you came, Kaoru-san,
that feeling's been gone.
I'm positive he was happy to find
a friend he could play jazz with.
Kaoru-san, shall I guess what you
two were fighting about today?
You like Yurika-san, don't you?
So you got mad at Sentaro for
showing off that handkerchief...
She is really pretty.
I wish I'd been born looking like that...
Wha...?! What are you talking about?!
Ri-chan, you're plenty...
...a-attractive.
Thanks for trying to cheer me up, Kaoru-san.
I'm not... I wasn't...
I wasn't trying to cheer you up. I...
Here we are!
Well, good luck!
Hey! Ri-chan! Open up!
Let me out, Ri-chan!
What's the ruckus, Ritsuko?
Drastic measures.
I-I didn't come here to see you.
What?
N-Nothing...
He has the same feelings
for the girl he likes.
Hey, don't just join in!
Hah?
I wasn't joinin' in anything.
He's following along again...
What the heck is this?!
It's jazz with a festival dance beat!
Cut it out! I can't play if I'm laughing!
Next time, maybe I'll play
something just for Ri-chan...
And then... maybe I'll try
letting her know how I feel.
Sentaro-kun...
I'm coming in.
Oh, don't be so stiff.
What the...
...hell is he doing?!
I'm sure Ri-chan is thinking about him...
Meanwhile, he's...
Um, Ri-chan...
There's a song that I'd like to play for you.
Actually, I wanted to practice
the song a little more first...
...but I feel like I have to
play it for her right now,
this piece I've secretly been
practicing my heart out...
Play through me, Bill Evans.
"Someday My Prince Will Come".
That's the title of the song.
So are you the prince, Kaoru-san?
I'm right, aren't I?
You've been practicing for Yurika-san, right?
And this is your "dress rehearsal"!
No.
This is the real performance.
You're the one that I like...
You don't have to give
me an answer right away.
I just wanted to let you know...
...that there's somebody
here who's in love with you.
Ri-chan's eyes are on him.
She's always thinking of him.
Still, that doesn't bother me right now...
You taught me that it was possible
to fall in love like this.