Can you see them?
Sir.
I can't see them yet...
...but I feel their presence.
It could happen at any time.
Why are all the Octobrists
so fearful of them?
Those northern freaks came many times...
but they have never breached this wall.
We've been driving them to the
other side for hundreds of years.
We are the people of Carneades,
the protectors of this wall.
What can those freaks do?!
Those soldiers are useless.
They won't even last two days.
You're in charge here. I'm going
to Kafet to check on the situation.
Are you talking about those two old men?
Yes. If they don't lead the army,
this country will be destroyed.
We can't win a battle like this.
The power of Drifters alone
can't bring us a victory!
"Act 3
Army of Ours--Sortie at Dawn"
Don't be a fool!
Are you telling me to give up my command...
...to those bizarre Drifters?!
Don't mess with me, magicians!
But if we don't let them lead, we'll lose.
Are you mocking me?!
What do you know?!
You are just a magician organization!
Besides, what can those two Drifters--
those scruffy old men--do?!
What? What? What are you two arguing about?
Well... umm... we're trying to have him
give up command of his troops to you two.
Huh?! All of a sudden! That's impossible!
I know it's unreasonable, but...
...if you don't command them, we'll all die.
Hmph. Why on earth do
we have to do such a thing?!
Nasty Drifters!
--Bastards!
--Shut up, Drifters!
--What the hell are you talking about?!
I don't understand their language,
but I could tell we were insulted.
H-Hey!
Huh?!
I'm about to pee my pants.
"Shiver shiver shiver"
--Huh?!
--You idiot! Hold it! You old fool!
No, I can't. Aging causes me to
have sudden urges to urinate.
Wh-Wh-What should I do?
I'm fed up with this lightning of Carthage.
I-I hate getting old...
He is just a stupid old man!
There's no way I will give
command to such an old wretch!
W-What the...
That man is...
...someone even millions of you can't defeat!
That man... That man...
That man is Hannibal--Hannibal Barca!
My Roman Empire did not fear
Yet, facing that man alone,
Hannibal, did Rome tremble!
any enemy, even if there
were millions of them.
Wh-What are you saying?
Damn you!
You two, that's far enough.
Even if he gave in now,
it's already pointless.
Please get ready to escape.
Soon, this place will descend into carnage.
The Octobrists will also withdraw.
Before the battle against
the Black King's army begins,
we must allow the Drifters to escape...
...no matter what it takes
or whom we sacrifice.
Scipio...
...thank you.
W-Well, that's the assurance of the victor.
Besides, I am stronger than you.
What did you say, you beardless idiot?!
You wanna fight, old man?!
This is Semu. This is Semu.
What should we do?
Wh... is... the... con... dition... ther...
Ca... yo... hea... me, Gr... Mas...
It's magic disruption.
Shoot! They are coming!
There is no response from
four reconnaissance units.
Damn!
What are those noises?
What's goin' on?
You got a cigarette?
Don't be an idiot. Course not.
You're lying! You're hiding the
last two cigarettes, aren't ya?!
Whose fault was it that we
ended up in a place like this?!
Who would give ya cigarettes, ya fool?!
I want a cigarette so bad.
Wherever we go, there's no tomorrow...
We, the Wild Bunch, only got today.
I should at least be able
to smoke as I please.
The Black King...
...is here.
Crusade, crusade.
Crusade of his Majesty, the Black King.
The time has finally come.
Crusade, crusade.
Those who have ears, listen.
Those who have eyes, watch.
Those who have mouths, shout.
Let them know everything.
Crusade, crusade, crusade.
It's the beginning of
the eradication of mankind.
Gather together. Join us.
All your power to the Black King!
The Black King... The king of the "Ends."
It's too late!
He's already here!
Do you hate us that much, Black King?
The "Drifters," this world...
...and everything else?!
They are coming! They're closing in!
Archers! Take aim!
Bring death.
Sh-Shoot!
Hijikata.
Joan of Arc.
Anastasia Nikolaevna Romanova.
You may go.
At last, you've made your move.
Are you really going to eradicate this world?
You do as you please.
Yeah. That's how I live my life.
So, allow me to continue on.
Kurou Hougan Yoshitsune.
Which side are you on...
...the Drifters or the Ends?
Let's see... Whichever interests me.
Shoot! Shoot! Fire at will!
Don't let them close in! Shoot!
From Air Command to Dragon Cavalry.
Engage in aerial support.
Deploy mobile aerial forces!
Damn it! They're coming one
after another. There is no end!
Descend! Begin Operation Draborne!
Descent successful. Minimum damage.
2nd platoon, ready up!
Go! Go! Go!
From Agnela 1 of Air Command
to Dragon Cavalry.
Backup requested by the Goblin 7th battalion.
Coordinates, 42-7-12-73-42-8.
It's too late. We can't save them!
But if a way for the Drifters
to escape exists...
Which one...?! Which one?!
Which one...?!
Which one?!
What the hell?! Damn it!
Shit! Shit! What the hell has just happened?!
"August 1, 1945, Kanno
Destroyer Naoshi Captain"
Hey! Who told you to stop?!
Run! You piece of shit! Damn it!
All right! Here we go!
Hey, hey, hey!
What the hell?! Is this fuckin' Uzumasa?!
Where the fuck am I?!
What the...?! You moron!
What the shit?! Why the hell are
you riding on a dragon, you idiot?!
Where the shit am I?!
Don't mess with me, you jackass!
Wh-Which one is he?!
No clue! For now, the Drifters'
evacuation must be...
The Northern Wall was torn down!
What?! Bring more troops here now!
B-But it's too...
It's hot... So hot.
I feel like my body is on fire...
Burn them all.
Everything... Burn them all to ash.
Drift in the air. Float
on the water's surface!
Burn! Burn!
Everything in this world
should be burned to ash!
Wh-What?!
What on earth?!
Sleep, everyone.
Run!
You... bastards!
You fuckin' jackass!
Open up! Open the gate!
We can't get it open. It's frozen.
May I defrost it for you?
K-Kill them!
They still ain't here.
Hey, it isn't looking good, is it?
Not good. Not at all.
Why don't we leave without 'em?
This way. Hurry.
--They're here.
--Please get on quickly!
We'll catch up with you later.
Get going, please!
Are those two old men going to be our cargo?
Thank you, thank you.
Why are ya dressed like that?!
What did you say, punk?!
There's nothing more that can be done here.
"The Northern Wall,"
the Kingdom of Carneades, has fallen!
Scipio! Hannibal!
You must be disturbed by our sudden
request to fight so soon after your arrival.
But... But please help us.
How can we... How can
we defeat that Black King?
Or do we even have a chance?
I am not sure.
Hey, what do you think?
There is a non-zero chance.
It's non-zero!
And if they join up with
those guys, we still have hope.
Together with the warriors
of the deserted castle...
...we still have a chance!
Let's go!
Wait!
Get them!
Do it! Get 'em, Kid!
Damn! Not many bullets left!
What on earth?! It's amazing!
Give me that. I'm going to destroy Rome.
We'll see about that, old man!
Hold on!
Do ya have a cigarette?
If not, die!
We're almost at the West Gate. Hurry!
Reporting! Bogie down!
Engaging!
Target "Dragon"! Target is "Dragon"!
Kanno Naoshi, the commander of
the 301st "Shinsengumi" squadron!
Who do you think you are?!
You disgust me, damn it!
I don't know what the hell
is going on here, but...
...crash, you damn scum!
A Drifter!
He was a Drifter!
I'll never let you get away with this.
Never! Black King!
I will be sure to fix your mess!
You're not supposed to exist here!
It's too late. You humans
are fruit to be cast off.
Chase them. Seek them.
Find them. Kill them.
The Drifters won't be allowed to live.
They must be brought to extinction.
By the mandate of the Inexorable Tribulation.
I lost contact with Grand Master.
W-What should I do?
No way the Northern Wall
was breached, was it?
Furthermore, that crazy
trio has been acting up.
What... should I do?
I knew we were being watched.
Who the hell are you?!
No! I'll get killed!
It's a "Leave your head here" ghost!
Who you calling "ghost"?!
Perhaps... a spy?
She looks too stupid for that... or maybe...
Hey, Toyohisa.
Yeah?
This girl is speaking Japanese.
You're right.
Hey, you! Tell me! Tell me everything!
No! Help me! Please don't take my head!
If you don't confess,
I'll let him take care of you.
Hey! I'm Demon King of the Sixth Heaven.
My hobby is scorched earth and slaughter.
Let's make a toast with the skull
of a person I killed! Cheers!
No!
I-I'm a magician with the
Octobrist Organization, Olminu.
I was just keeping an eye
on you Drifters under Grand
Master's orders. Help me!
What the hell's she saying?!
Did you hear what the idiot just said?
Explain in a way that even
the fool can understand.
That's unreasonable.
Who're you calling fool?!
Do you want me to take your head?
You heard what I said.
So, you are, as she said,
a "leave your head here" ghost, huh?
Umm... well... it is...
Here, those like you who
are transported from the
other world are called the "Drifters."
Our mission as the
"Octobrist Organization" is...
...to monitor their activities
and to bring them together.
And you were brought here to fight
against the people called the "Ends."
Who cares?!
What the hell?! Don't make up stories.
Nuh-uh.
"Buddhist Monk"
"Miracle"
"Demon King of the Sixth Heaven"
"Act 4
Active Heart"