Once upon a time,
a kind-hearted red ogre lived all by himself
in the mountains.
Home to a kind-hearted ogre.
All are welcome.
Delicious sweets and tea available.
Becoming friends with humans
was his constant desire.
But...
They were afraid of the ogre and stayed far away.
The red ogre's friend, the blue ogre,
came to him and said,
"Say, Red...
How about I stir things up in the village?
You can defeat me.
Then the humans should rethink who you are,
and you can become friends."
My name is Gouda Takeo.
I'm a third-year in junior high.
30th Graduation Ceremony
Shuuei Junior High School
Today is my last day in junior high,
the graduation ceremony.
And now, it's time for farewell.
It's time to say goodbye.
My Story
Takeo!
It's too bad we won't be in the same high school!
Yeah.
I wish we could've gone to the same school!
Keep in touch, okay?
We'll come see you.
Okay!
Takeo-senpai!
Osu!
Right.
Thank you for being with the club for three years.
Please come by sometime!
Okay.
Thank you for everything
—Shinonara Ippon!
Thank you! —Nomura
You're the man!!
You're my role model
To Takeo-senpai
Congratulations on your graduation
This is from all of us.
Okay, thanks.
Make it to nationals this year, okay?
Bye!
Oh, Senpai!
Senpai!
Takeo-senpai!
Wait a minute!
Senpai!
Takeo!
Hey, Takeo! Where are you going?
I've been working with Satou-san
in the student council.
She's kind and has a great smile.
Gouda-kun...
Before I graduate, I want to tell her how I feel.
Where are you, Satou-san?
Satou-san!
Um, I...
I've always liked you, Sunakawa-kun!
I don't have any feelings for you.
Oh, Takeo...
You going home?
Uh, yeah.
Okay, let's go.
Let's get out of here.
This guy is my friend, Sunakawa Makoto.
Why are we friends, you ask?
I'm not really sure myself.
When is the high school entrance ceremony again?
April 7th, I think?
No, the 6th...
Around there.
You lazy bum.
Suna's super popular with the girls.
Sunakawa-kun's so cool.
I've never seen him laugh.
Wouldn't that be great?
I bet he only laughs for girls he likes.
That's so cool.
Isn't it?
When we graduated from kindergarten,
the girl I liked, Yuzuha-chan...
I like you a lot, Sunakawa-kun.
I don't like you.
With that, he made her cry.
Don't make girls cry!
Sorry.
It's okay.
See? I apologized.
It was the same story in elementary school
with the girl I liked, Misaki-chan.
I like you.
I don't.
And for Kayomi-chan.
No.
And Eriha-chan.
Nope.
And Mao-chan.
Dislike.
All of them fall for Suna.
People often ask why I'm friends with him...
We live in the same apartment complex.
We're neighbors, and our moms are friends.
As kids, we played together a lot.
We're here!
Come in! Sorry for the mess!
Yeah!
Real men should fight!
It's time for a face-off, man!
How do you wanna do this?
Sumo?
Sword fight?
Card game?
Yeah!
Achooo!
Even though our moms got along,
Wa-chaaa!
that isn't to say that we did.
Kick!
Video game, then.
Laser Beam!
Def not on the same wavelength...      Laser Beam
However...
Crap!
I can't see
Why?
Why can I not win?
Because you suck?
Damn it!
I'm always losing!
This sucks!
Damn it!
I can't see
We never fought, either.
Man, another loss!
I lost again!
And so on and so forth.
Till the present day. I guess.
Look, it's Sunakawa-kun.
I guess he comes through here!
Oh, Sunakawa-senpai...
Hey, wasn't that guy super hot?
Hey, Suna...
Yeah?
Did you hear that there's been
a prowler around here lately?
I guess.
Shisuda Municipal Elementary School
What? Seriously?
Is he after kids?
How dare he?!
I got kind of hung up over it, so yesterday...
Shisuda Municipal
Elementary School
Huh? What?
He makes me nervous
Sir?
We got a call that there's a scary guy
standing at the school gates...
So yesterday, I got reported to the cops.
Girls, this is how he looks when he laughs.
You don't have to laugh so hard!
Oh, sorry.
Not that it's a big deal...
Hang on, we're almost there.
Whoa!
That was smooth...
Thank you...
Nice job!
He's a real pro.
Ignored?
Here, please.
Th-Th-Thank you...
I'm just not a smooth customer like Suna.
Hey.
That guy... Isn't he kinda sketchy?
I wonder if he's up to something.
Get off this train at the next station!
Hey! Why are you—
Ow!
Thank you.
Where do you take losers like him?
Do we just leave him with
someone who works here?
We'll take things from here, so you can—
I'll come, too!
A groper?
You again...
You're the one who caught him?
Yes, sir!
Oh, you can let go of him now.
I'll see what he has to say.
Yes, sir!
I didn't do nothin'!
Give it up already.
I have no idea what you're talking about!
Officer, this guy hurt me!
Can you believe that?
He grabbed my arm, like this.
Then he did a number on my neck, like this!
Can you believe that?
He groped me!
This man helped me!
Huh?
Look who's talking, with your skirt up to there.
You were really asking for it!
Like hell she was, you scumbag!
Oops.
I got suspended.
I'm bored.
Door was open, but just in case...
Takeo, here are the notes from today.
Not that you'd study anyway, of course...
Cut it out, Suna!
Gouda!!
Who is it?
I didn't think you'd go after him.
Well, I guess I kinda thought you might...
Then cut me some slack!
I totally didn't think you'd slug
him in front of a cop, though.
Well, he pissed me off.
Oh, my.
Hang on a second.
Well, I guess so.
Take!
A girl's here to see you! A girl!
She says she's Yamato-san.
Can she come up?
Sure.
Who's Yamato?
No idea.
Anyone from our junior high?
Actually,
you sure you're okay with a girl in this room?
Ask her to wait one sec!
Um, I'm already here...
Thank you for helping me yesterday.
I like her!
I'll get going.
Huh?
You're leaving?!
Oh...
This again.
No surprise there, I guess.
Oh, um, here...
I brought this to thank you.
I thought it might be better to
share it with more people.
Oh, maybe you don't like this.
Actually, maybe you think I'm creepy
because I came over without asking!
Sorry, I asked at the train station yesterday, and...
No, I love it!
I'm glad.
What is this deliciousness?
What kind of cake is this?
It's cheesecake.
You've never had one before?
No!
But now that you mention it, I taste the cheese!
Huh? What are you saying?
Thanks for the cake.
Then, I'll really get going.
Oh, I guess I should get going, too...
I'm the one who helped you out, you know.
Thank you so much.
But I guess I kind of went
off the rails at the end.
Goodbye.
Well, I got a cake out of it.
And it was good, so it's all good.
I helped a girl who turned out to be a nice girl.
That gives me the strength to go on.
End of story!
What's with this pink cell phone?
Incoming Call
Public Phone
Is it Suna's?
Hello?
Oh!
Oh, I thought so!
Sorry, I forgot my cell phone.
Ah, I'm Yamato from earlier...
Oh, it's with me, at home.
I'm so sorry!
I'll come get it...
When would be a good day for you?
Oh, I can just bring it to you, if you tell me where.
Then how about we pick a time and place?
I go to Koizumi Girls Academy,
so how about we meet in front of
the fountain in Shisuda Park?
Sure.
Um, how about tomorrow?
After school, around three o'clock?
Guess it isn't "end of story" yet.
What's with the smartphone?
You buy it?
The girl from yesterday forgot it at my place.
I'm going to return it to her now.
Oh...
Good luck
That girl, Yamato-san...
I bet she's expecting Suna to show up, too.
After all, she saw him with me both times.
Let's go!
Why me?
Just come!
No worries...
I'll bring him with me.
That's what real men do!
I'm so sorry for the trouble.
Thank you so much.
There's no need to be so polite.
We're the same year, aren't we?
Both high school first-years?
Right.
Th-Thanks.
You're the one being polite.
Um, here!
It's to thank you this time.
I wanted to thank you for taking the
trouble to bring me my phone...
If you'd like, we can find a seat and eat here.
What's this amazing deliciousness?
What kind of food is this?!
Macaroons.
Macaroons are delicious!
I'm glad.
Actually, I baked these.
The cake last time, too.
What?!
They're home-baked?!
You mean "homemade."
Pretty sure that's wrong
Munch, Munch
Wow
I'm good at baking, I guess.
Good at baking...
Baking...
Is it true you need stamina to make sweets?
Yeah!
You have to mix a lot!
Mix a lot...
A lot... A lot...
Why...
Why are you blushing and nervous all the time?
Are you in love?
Do you like Suna that much?
Stop staring.
You're invading her personal space.
Off to the toilet!
Okay...
Why won't human emotions,
not even my own,
work out the way we want?
Am I just naïve?
No point in developing feelings for her.
It'll just make things awkward for her.
I don't think it's a good idea, but...
Your head's soaking wet!
I have a towel!
Over here, too.
Dude, do it yourself.
If this girl...
If Yamato-san gets heartbroken and cries,
It'll be really sad.
If I can, I want to help her.
I...
I'd like to eat cake again...
Would it be possible for you to bake another?
Dude, that came outta nowhere.
You'd let me?
Yeah.
The next one I'm good at
would be a sachertorte.
What do you think?
Do you like sachertorte?
serious face
Sure, I love sacherotote.
Dude, you totally faked knowing what it even is.
Okay, next time, sachertorte!
See you later!
I'll help you in any way I can!
She told me that when she bakes,
she doesn't use a hand mixer.
Huh.
She likes going through the extra trouble
and seeing it all come together.
I see...
That's unusual.
She's...
kind of nice.
This is the first time I've heard Suna
say something nice about a girl!
This is...
Thank god...
I made it back in... time...
Yo...
What?
What's wrong?!
Yo...
Your e-mail...
I don't know your e-mail.
I need it to contact you, so...
Please tell me your e-mail!
She sprinted back
as fast as she could.
She's totally sweaty...
Am I that sweaty?
It's okay!
I'll dry off!
Use it.
You can keep it.
Here's my e-mail.
Dude, just use infrared.
Thank you.
You really like Suna, huh?
Student Planner
All right, my mind's made up!
I'm gonna be your cheerleader.
I'll help you out.
Don't worry!
What's with the old-school washcloth?
My mom likes 'em.
My Love
Next time: My Love.