You are what
you eat!
Home Delivery Vegetables
Tanaka Farms Fresh Vegetables Set
Veggies Good Enough to Be the Main Dish!
We Support Your New Life Campaign
Super Special Price
Original Model
Washing Machine
in Hachioji
Eco-Friendly Home
New
Building
Private Viewing of Site
Episode 11   Umaru's Days
Hey, Onii-chan! Let's get pizza for lunch!
What? We just had pizza the other day.
You need to eat more veg—
Who could that be?
H-Hello, Onii-san.
Hello.
Umaru                                      un
Hi, Ebina-chan.
Oh, Umaru-chan. Hi.
You came to visit?
No... I, uh...
A-Actually, my parents sent
me some Akita Komachi...
Please have some!
What? Rice?
Thanks! That'll help out a lot.
N-No problem.
I-I'm so sorry! My tummy just...
Why don't you stay for lunch?
Huh?
You did give us rice from Akita, after all.
Akita
Akita Komachi
What a great opportunity.
Since junk food is all Umaru ever eats,
I'll show her how delicious Japanese food can be.
All right. I'm gonna go all-out
and use an earthenware pot.
S-So your brother cooks, too.
Yeah, sorry about that.
He's all hyped up now.
No, it's no problem at all.
Since you're with us, we
should have gone out to eat.
Like pizza...
Oh, but I'm always by myself,
so it makes me happy to be able to eat
a home-cooked meal with others like this.
Ebina-chan...
It's finished!
I cooked some white rice in the earthenware pot.
And I chose side dishes that
should go well with white rice.
Wow!
Too many vegetables.
All right, lunch time! Let's eat!
Yes, let's eat.
But I wanted pizza...
It's delicious!
I guess rice from Akita really is different!
Delish.
I'm sorry! My dialect slipped out!
Oh, no, it's fine.
That means you like it, right?
Ah, ayup.
"Ayup"?
Thank you for the meal.
The rice from Akita was great.
Um... Thanks for inviting me for lunch.
No problem. Come by anytime.
Okay!
Didn't have enough?
N-No, th-that's not it!
Oh, I guess she's posing like that
to try to keep her tummy quiet.
Why don't we order some
pizza, then, Onii-chan?
Pizza? But pizza would be kind of...
Um... Then maybe we can order a half-size.
We're ordering one?
Another meeting? What a pain.
No proposal from our team has ever
passed one of these meetings.
Proposal Meeting
The best way for an organization to
convey its ideals is through meetings.
Therefore, we have all of our employees in
attendance when we present any proposals.
This is because it is impossible to reach the
best solution with the power of one alone.
Now, then... What snacks should I buy?
Should I prioritize sweetness...
No, maybe salty?
Then again, the breads are appealing, too.
Ugh! This is taking too long!
Nothing says snacks like potato chips!
This is a staple, and the most obvious choice!
This is why you can't rely on old people.
What?
We should throw out such antiquated ideas.
Did we always have an Umaru like that?
Yeah, you know, when the personality
that's sort of fake-like comes out?
Then what do you think we should get, Umaru?
From now on, we should expand
our horizons when choosing snacks.
Cucumber
Crackers
Intense Cucumber Flavor
This is a new product.
Cucumber-flavored crackers.
I'm sure you're curious as
to what they taste like.
This Taste is a
New Discovery!
If that's the case, I prefer chocolate.
I know, right? I want
Chocolate Mushroom Fields!
What?! When did you convert
to mushrooms, Umaru?!
Chocolate Bamboo Shoot
Mountains are best!
I've always liked chocolate
mushrooms better!
Hey! Stop fighting over something so trivial!
You know nothing beats Suginoko's Town!
Everyone, how about some cake?
Nah, cake is out.
Yeah, totally.
Yep.
B-But, I mean, you never know...
If we choose cake, there'll be a lot of trouble.
Argh! How many times must I tell you
we have to go with Tontacos?!
Nay! We must go with beef jerky!
Who is that Umaru?!
I-It's no use! We can't decide this alone!
Oh, whatever, already.
Hey, you. The Umaru with
no hood. What do you think?
Huh? Oh, well... Um...
I think I want something that gives you energy.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Onii-chan.
What is it?
Here, Onii-chan.
Good job at your meeting.
Thanks!
But I'm surprised you knew, Umaru.
Huh?
See? It passed the meeting.
You knew it'd pass, so you got me
something to celebrate, right?
Huh?
Huh?!
Meeting to Decide What Snack to
Cheer Onii-chan Up With When
His Proposal Fails at His Meeting
Man, I can't believe it actually passed.
Maybe I should have gone with the cake...
What? Onii-san is?
Yeah. His proposal passed,
so he's been all hyper since yesterday.
But I'm sure a proposal Onii-san
came up with must be amazing.
So, Ebina-chan, about this Sunday...
All right. Let's go.
Um, are you sure it's okay
for me to come along?
Of course! Celebrations like this get
you psyched up for the next project.
R-Right...
I-I need to make sure not
to eat too much today...
My tummy kept rumbling last time,
and I even ate that pizza...
Spring Strawberry Parfait
Cherry Blossoms and Chocolate Parfait
Hearty Bitter Chocolate and
Banana Sundae
It's been so long since I've had parfaits!
Pa...
This is to thank you for the snack.
No need to hold back.
P-Parf...
Which one are you getting, Ebina-chan?
Huh?!
If I eat a lot in front of Umaru-chan,
she might think I'm weird.
U-Um...
I'll have what you're having, Umaru-chan!
Parfai                              in
Those are pretty big...
Will you be able to finish those?
What are you talking about, Onii-chan?
Girls slurp up parfaits like they're nothing.
Like when they say there's
always room for dessert?
We might even get seconds.
That's fine, but I kind of doubt you can.
Come on, let's eat, Ebina-chan.
S-Sure.
Delish!
So good!
Huh? Ebina-chan, you haven't eaten at all.
Huh? Ah...
No need to hold back.
Okay, I'll eat.
Let's eat.
That was so good.
We actually finished them.
I don't think it was quite enough, though.
You thought so, too?
Yep. Then...
Seconds, please!
I-Is that okay?
Rainy Season
It's really coming down...
There's always so much rain
this time of year... What a pain.
Uma—
What's wrong?
My potato chips are soggy.
It keeps raining every day, and it's all humid.
Well, we are in the middle
of the rainy season.
I don't feel like doing anything.
That's no different from usual.
Is she actually using the rainy season
as an excuse to laze around?
Oh, hello, Onii-san.
H-Hello...
She was here?
Er, what's the matter, Kirie-chan?
Huh? W-Well...
Actually, I'm always like this when it rains.
I get really down.
H-Her smile is scary.
I'm scared!
It's dark! I'm scared!
Trauma Switch ON
Did she just remember something horrible?
Hey! You can't do this, you two!
It's times like these that you
need to hype yourself up!
That's not happening with this rain.
There are good things about
the rainy season, too.
For example, the sound of the rain.
Listen to this sound that soothes the heart.
Don't you think it has a certain charm?
Huh...
Maybe this sort of elegance
is beyond high schoolers...
I guess the rain doesn't
have a very good image.
Maybe I should give them
something to look forward to.
Hey! When the rainy season
ends, summer will be here!
Why don't we go to the ocean?
Th-The ocean?!
Huh? Uh, yeah.
How are we going to get to the ocean?
Trains are tiring. I don't wanna.
Well...
I guess we could ask Bomber to drive.
B-Bomber? Is that a human?
Oh, yeah. I guess you haven't
met him, Kirie-chan.
He's a friend of mine.
I-It's a guy?
I'm sure he'll be fine if he's
a friend of yours, Onii-san...
But it's so hot in summer.
But when it's summer,
doesn't ice cream taste even better?
Ice cream!
Summer is amazing, isn't it, Master?!
They're so simple-minded...
Yes! How could I forget?
Summer has the best snack of all: ice cream!
Welcome, summer! Welcome, summer!
Well, one way or another,
I guess it's good they cheered up.
Hey, wake up, Umaru.
What is it? It's so early...
Take a look outside.
Huh?
The weather cleared.
It's summer, Onii-chan!
My younger sister, Umaru, is hot and popular.
Umaru                                    un
She's kind, smart, and gifted
with many talents.
She's the perfect high school
student, without any flaws.
At least, that's what everyone seems to think...
Wasn't shopping fun, Umaru-chan?
Yeah. I got some really great stuff.
It's so hot again today.
I want something cold to eat.
New Sweets with Mixed Ingredients!
Ah, Ebina-chan, you got the
red bean wafer sandwich.
The one in the box.
Yeah, I really like these.
You got the soda one, Umaru-chan?
Yep.
It's so good.
Yeah.
Nothing says summer like ice cream.
Yep.
Now, UMR-san!
Wait...
The way it's facing, and that angle...
We can do this! I'm going for double!
You're going for two?
There we go!
How do you achieve such balance?!
You did it!
Nothing less from you, UMR-san!
You like matcha, TSF-san?
I love all things Japanese,
so I drink matcha all the time.
It's delicious.
Ah, I see.
Still, you've got a lot to learn if you're
eating ice cream in a cup like that.
Really?
When you eat ice cream in a cup...
You first lick the lid.
The lid?
Emperor penguins live in a very cold region,
and stand very still,
even when warming their eggs.
Nothing is better in summer
than watching a DVD on emperor
penguins while eating ice cream.
Indeed, Master!
Have some ice cream, too, Kirie-chan.
N-No, Master! That's your
ice cream, so I could never...
It's fine! I bought plenty!
Oh, my goodness! You even
have a cooler just for them!
It's a must-have item for summer!
Th-Then is it okay if I have
this mint chocolate chip?
Yep.
Mint chocolate chip: a staple of summer.
Kirie-chan has definitely leveled up.
What's the matter, Master?!
I won! Look!
Winner
Well done, Master!
This is because of all my hard work every day.
Nothing less from you, Master!
There. All done.
Umaru, dessert's ready.
Huh? Dessert?
Look! Shaved ice!
Doesn't it look like the
parfait you had the other day?
What the heck is this?!
Let's eat!
Uh, you should've seen that coming...
So good!
This is my little sister.
She's lazy,
selfish...
I'm off.
...and completely different when she's outside.
That's my one and only little sister, Umaru.
Umaru! You've been eating tons of
ice cream every day, haven't you?!
When did you buy a cooler?!
You were hiding it, weren't you?!
Busted...
Next Time
Episode 12      Umaru and Everyone
Everyone! The next episode is the last one!
I'll do my best to the very end!
I'll follow you to the ends of the earth!
We shall battle, even in the last episode!
I'm just gonna laze around, even in the last episode.
What?