Sorry about that.
There's a pickled plum in it.
Why are you crying?
Because of the sun.
Because you're the sun, Tsumugu-kun...
Even though it's night?
That might be why.
You're even brighter.
When I was little,
I was told I couldn't go up
to the surface by myself yet.
Despite that, I always
looked up to the sky.
I admired it.
Beyond the sea, beyond the sky...
The sun that was so far, far away.
It was so bright.
It shined down on me.
It made me warm.
It made me excited.
But...
But?
Episode Thirteen:
Unreachable Fingertips
It's really quiet.
Was it always this quiet at night?
I always thought there
was a lot more noise.
Is it because it's right
before the hibernation?
Is it because the saltflake
snow has piled up?
I see...
I was the one that was noisy.
When it was decided that
Nami Junior High was going
to be closed, and we started
going to school on the surface.
That's when it happened...
I can't let anyone see
this no matter what!
"Anyone"?
You're already showing me.
You're allowed, Hii-kun!
Manaka had said that...
but towards Tsumugu...
At that time, there were
ripples making noise in my heart...
It got stormy...
And when I realized it,
it felt like it was a ship caught in
the middle of the stormy sea.
But it wasn't just me.
Everyone cared for someone, and...
Some of us didn't realize
those feelings ourselves...
or know what to do with them...
And even though someone had cared
about us, we couldn't realize it...
Or couldn't respond...
We were shaken, crumpled...
Everyone is desperately taking control
of the wheel and crossing.
And yet...
No, that's why...
Manaka.
Hii-kun.
Sorry for showing up so suddenly.
I'm sort of glad you were outside.
Were you out on a walk?
Um... Something like that.
I see.
The moon's really pretty.
Yeah, it is...
So, uh...
Um...
About earlier...
So—
Go ahead!
R-Right.
About earlier, I'm sorry
I said that so suddenly.
I was sort of going with the momentum...
The blood had rushed to my
head and I just blurted it out.
I guess I haven't really
matured, or something...
So I wanted to say it properly.
Properly?
I... really do love you, Manaka.
I love you, and you're precious to me.
That's for sure.
But Chisaki, Kaname, and Tsumugu...
Akari, Miuna, and Sayu... even Dad.
All of you are precious to me.
Whether you like me or not,
the fact that you're precious to
me won't change, no matter what.
So... What were you trying
to say a second ago?
The Ofunehiki...
After it's done, I'll tell you.
Huh?
Hii-kun, wave the flag.
Wave it a lot.
That way, no one will get lost.
Yeah.
I'm heading out, Dad. Mom.
So you're going up there?
Yeah.
Do you understand?
Today's the day of the hibernation.
But...
Just don't stay out too late.
We'll do our best to stay
awake until you get back.
I thought you'd try to stop me.
You were secretly eating while
you were up there, weren't you?
Did you think we wouldn't notice?
Dad...
Go on.
I hope the festival goes well.
Mom...
All right. I'll be going.
Morning, Chisaki.
Kaname...
So they properly sent you off.
Yeah. They said to do my
best in the Ofunehiki.
Thank goodness. I was worried.
What about you, Kaname?
Did everything go okay?
It's the first time we
ever had a huge fight.
Somewhat worked things
out in the end, though.
I see.
But I'm glad.
You were working really hard
preparing for the Ofunehiki.
I was just doing whatever I could
so I'd have more opportunities
to be together with you.
Huh?
You know, Chisaki...
You might have had your hands full
with your feelings for Hikari.
But I did actually confess to you, too.
O-Of course I didn't forget.
I am really thinking about it.
Even if we do end up asleep and
wake up at different times,
the fact that I love you won't change.
Just don't forget that.
Kaname...
Hey!
Morning, Hikari.
Morning.
Where's Manaka?
She's not here yet.
And we were taking our
time getting up here, too.
W-Wait!
To be late today of all days...
You really are amazing, Manaka.
Huh?
Seriously. She really may
be the greatest of us all.
Um...
You guys aren't
complimenting me... right?
Duh.
Jeez...
But Grandma was falling
out of her futon.
Well, well...
You're all quite lively considering
we're all about to sleep.
Uroko-sama...
We came to say our greetings.
We're about to go do the Ofunehiki.
You said it'd be pointless,
but we're going to do it anyway.
Do as you wish.
I will not be able to change anything.
However, all of you may actually
be able to change something.
Yes.
Apparently you've grown before
I even realized it, as well.
Dad...
Go.
I have nothing more to say to you.
Only... Since this started
because of what you said...
Make sure you don't run away,
no matter what happens.
You don't have to tell me that.
Tell Akari... to be happy.
<Ofunehiki Festival>
It's finally happening.
A lot happened, but who
knew it'd get this big.
It's all thanks to you guys.
Seriously, thank you.
What are you being all serious for?
You're embarrassing us! Jeez...
More importantly, Hikari,
are you planning to be the guide of
the Ofunehiki dressed like that?
Why not?
It's just my school uniform.
Nope.
You're a man of the sea, now.
And the uniform for a
man of the sea is...
That!
What's up?
Uh, I am a person from the sea,
but I'm not a man of the sea...
Shut up. We're taking you in.
Hey, Pops. Could you turn him into
a proper man of the sea, too?
Huh? What?!
Mo-Mom... M-Mo-Mom...
M-M-Mom!
I'm sure that'll make
Akari-san really happy.
You... think so?
Yeah!
Miuna, there's trouble!
Akari transformed!
Miuna, it's amazing! Look!
I am...
Miuna, Itaru-san, thank you so much
for listening to my selfish wish.
It's fine.
We're going to be together forever
now anyway, right, Aka-cha—
M-Mo—
I can't!
If I look at you now,
even though this is just for show,
I won't be able to let
you go marry the Sea God.
So I can't look! I'll never look!
D-Daddy?!
Aka-chan!
Once this is over, I have
something I want to tell you.
So...
All right.
I'll see you later, then, Miuna.
Uroko-sama.
Let us begin.
Let's go!
Fishery Cooperative
Akari, accept this.
It is our gift to you.
The sea...
Dad...
Wow.
They're being led by sacred fire.
Akari...
Can you see, Sea God?
In this wide ocean, we may be
small, insignificant beings.
But the people of the sea and
the people of the surface
are all doing their best to live.
We all want to be together forever...
With the people who are
precious to us, forever.
So, Sea God, if you're really out there...
Please, Sea God.
Please...
Hear... Our wish!
Wh-What is that?
Could it be...
The Sea God really...
...has come to take Akari-san?!
Akari!
Akari-san!
Mukaido!
Tsumugu-kun!
Akari-san!
It's no use...
It's like my body won't listen to me...
Ah...
It's so pretty...
Uroko-sama! What's going on?!
Forgive me.
In the end, I am the
scale of the Sea God.
Hurry!
If we don't get up to the surface soon,
Tsumugu-kun will...
Kaname?
One, and...
Tsumugu-kun!
Look! The bridge pier!
No!
Please stop!
Akari-san has people waiting for her!
Please!
Don't take her away.
Everyone...
Is someone precious to someone!
Please don't try to forcefully rip
apart those who love each other!
If you insist on taking someone...
...take me instead!
Manaka!
Hii-kun.
Look over there!
Someone's floating!
Get the boat out!
Hurry!
Mom!
Akari!
Even now, I look from here...
To the sea where Hikari
and the others are.
Episode Fourteen:
The Promised Day