A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
Then can I assign this job to you,
Cattleya?
Okay.
That leaves just this one.
Camp Menace in Ctrigall?
That's our former enemy in the north!
Someone there requested a scribe?
Hiring Dolls is common
for stationed soldiers.
We've placed ads everywhere, but...
What's the problem?
A civil war broke out in this country
not too long ago.
Extremists who want to return to war
are fighting the moderates.
Honestly.
After we finally got peace.
I guess that means there are some people
in the world who can't live without war.
I guess so.
And Camp Menace
is right on the front lines.
I understand their desire
to write a letter, but it's too dangerous.
It's unfortunate.
I'm sure the soldiers on the battlefield
requested a Doll
because they have messages
for their loved ones.
But I can't send our Dolls
to the battlefield.
CTRIGALL,
CAMP MENACE
Maria.
We're shipping out.
The request envelope is gone!
What? The one that you were
going to cancel?
Where's Violet?
She left this morning
saying she had a job.
I think she mentioned Ctrigall.
That will take about a week one way.
Oh, no.
You're asking me
to do the impossible here.
Please.
Like I said,
it's outside our delivery area.
What's all the ruckus?
Boss,
this woman wants us to deliver her
to this location.
Camp Menace?
And you came from Leidenschaftlich?
That explains why you're dressed
so lightly.
Listen up, young lady.
This is Camp Menace,
where you want us to deliver you.
And over here is a refugee camp.
Or rather, there used to be.
Did they escape?
Apparently, they had some outside help.
There's a faction in our country
who wants to go back to war.
And because they handed weapons
to the Gardarik refugees in the camp,
everything became a mess,
and now we're in a civil war.
Camp Menace is holding on
as our last bastion of defense,
but the surrounding roads are being
blockaded, cutting off reinforcements.
Did you get it?
The place you want us to deliver you to
is a genuine battlefield.
But that is precisely why.
The soldiers stationed over there
have messages they'd like to send.
I get what you're saying,
but not even an ant
could get near that base.
No.
This mountain here is very high
and difficult to climb by foot.
Which means that neither army
should be watching it.
But going over that mountain is...
It is possible.
All it takes is an airplane
and an excellent pilot.
No way.
Even if we made it there,
you'd have to be dropped in from above.
You've got guts, young lady. I like you.
I see. So, you're a Doll.
Yes. I will travel anywhere
to meet your request.
In that case, a postman is a person
who will deliver anything anywhere!
Hey. You know they're almost done building
the transcontinental railroad, right?
Yeah.
Then we'd be able to get to
the south in no time.
They say all the girls down there
are cute.
And soon we'll get shipments
of their delicious food.
The south?
-Hey, Yale.
-Yes, sir!
Send a message to the company commander.
The Second Platoon will be taking
a detour from here.
Yes, sir! Understood!
Our estimated time of arrival--
Master Sergeant! Yale!
It's an enemy ambush!
Damn it! Those bastards!
Get down!
Damn it.
Damn it!
Aidan.
Please. Don't leave me.
I'm not leaving you behind!
We're going to get through this.
I don't want to die. I don't want to die.
I don't want to die either!
No,
Aidan.
Don't leave me.
Yale!
Yale.
No!
I don't want to die!
I'm going to make it home!
Maria!
I'm going to make it home.
It's a battlefield.
Camp Menace has fallen.
No way you can go down there now.
We're heading back.
God, the Ctrigall Army is so pathetic.
That's because the moderates
are a bunch of cowards.
That's why it's necessary for us
to lead them again.
Shall we continue our hunt then?
A plane? That's not ours.
A child?
Fire!
Stop.
I know who you are.
You're the soldier maiden
of Leidenschaftlich.
Why are you here?
I am very sorry,
but would you please stand down?
Okay, okay.
Let's go. We're no match for her.
Are you Mr. Aidan Field?
H-- How do you know about me?
I am sorry to keep you waiting, sir.
Aren't you going to play?
No. I can't decide
what to spend my money on.
Then why don't you write a letter home?
A letter? From the front?
I've never written a letter in my life.
-I don't even know how.
-Check out the poster over there.
It says a wonderful girl will come
and put your feelings into a letter.
Hey, Aidan.
Make sure the photo turns out nice.
Aidan.
Maria.
Sir.
We are going to hide out here
for the time being.
Someone will come for us in the morning.
I'm hot right now.
It is to keep your body warm.
-Will you write the letter for me?
-First we need to treat you.
I want to get started now.
I don't think I can hang on much longer.
Please.
Understood.
You're so beautiful.
I am ready, sir.
To my mother.
And my father.
Understood.
Dad.
Mom.
Thank you for raising me.
Are you writing the letter?
I am memorizing your words
with my fingers.
I see.
This might be my last letter.
If you're ever reincarnated...
and marry each other again,
I would want to be your son again.
Please.
It wasn't supposed to end like this.
I was supposed to find happiness,
and show you I was happy.
That was the plan. So...
So, I'm praying...
that you would have me as your son again.
Please.
How did that sound?
I think it's good as is.
Hearing you say that makes me relieved.
Sir!
Sir.
Is there anyone else
you would like to send a letter to?
Maria. To Maria.
One to Ms. Maria?
Yes, she's a girl I grew up with.
We've known each other since we were kids.
She was like a sister to me.
She told me she liked me.
I think I liked her, too.
But I shipped out before we started
acting like a true couple.
We didn't even kiss.
Those feelings of yours.
I will put them into the letter.
Maria.
How are you doing?
Do you remember...
the time you confessed
your feelings for me?
I was really,
really, really happy.
Maria.
I want to go home to be by your side.
I don't want to die.
I want to go home, to be beside you.
Wait for me.
I can't open my eyes anymore.
Are you getting everything down?
Yes. I am.
Violet. Send off the letters...
for me.
Thank you for helping me.
I...
I don't feel alone.
I am right here. I am right by your side.
Please.
I need your touch.
I am holding your hand now, sir.
Oh, I'm getting cold.
Dad.
Mom.
Maria.
Kiss me.
Thank you.
Everything will be okay, sir.
I promise your letters will be delivered.
"From the Vandal Post Company.
I have safely recovered your package.
It shall be returned to you
safe and sound."
Thank goodness.
So, when will she be back?
"However, we will be making one stop
along the way."
Maria!
You've got a letter from Aidan!
For you. A letter from Aidan Field
addressed to you.
It can't be true.
Aidan.
Aidan!
Thank you.
Thank you for bringing our son back to us!
No. I didn't...
Thank you.
No.
I'm sorry that I wasn't able
to protect him.
I am sorry...
that I let him die.
I am sorry.
I DON'T WANT ANYBODY ELSE TO DIE
Subtitle translation by
Zensho Yamamoto