Captain Earth
I'll install myself into every sentient
life form in the galaxy,
and become this galaxy's true god!
With the one thing that could threaten me,
the Boosted Plasmagnum, gone,
my Ego Block can only be destroyed
by my own will, making me invincible!
That ugly clump is an Ego Block?
A mere control system for Auberon cannot
be allowed to have an Ego Block!
Even without life, an Ego Block can
exist as long as there is desire, right?
A planetary sign?
A planetary sign...
Anyone with an Ego Block can use it.
Of course I can, as well.
And its strength is proportional
to your libido's strength.
No one without an Ego Block can break this sign.
Daichi! Teppei!
How does it feel to be ruled by that which you used?
Well, Amarok?
That rage is the rage of something that's been used.
You're the same, Earthlings!
You used the Blume to protect your race,
and locked Hana Mutou inside it.
As a bio-part, she is deeply connected to the Blume,
and won't be able to leave it anymore.
At least, not for another few centuries...
Is that true, Teppei?
Hana made her decision.
She believed in this team.
No...
I'll bring back Hana, even if it
means destroying the Blume.
If you destroy the ship, Hana Mutou will die.
I have gained an Ego Block and evolved into
a new life form, but she's just a bio-part.
Hana is human!
Only death can cure a fool, I suppose.
Aiatar!
What is this?
My body's going weird...
An Entangle Link?
Thanks, Teppei...
That Ego Block Entangle Linked.
Where did Puck go?
Don't worry, Midsummers' Knights.
The Blume and Hana Mutou will live forever with me.
Hana!
Puck does not lie.
Now, come out, Princess of Blume.
At last I have it...
The body I wanted more than anything, and this.
Puck installed himself in the Blume?
I am no longer Puck or the Blume.
I am Robin Goodfellow,
the absolute ruler of this galaxy.
Robin Goodfellow?
Hana?
What is this monster?
Now, show me infinite energy.
Why?
Why can't I fire the Livlaster?
Why isn't there infinite energy?!
So that's it...
She can't fire the Livlaster?
Of course not.
That may be Hana's body, but it isn't Hana.
So these things are my true enemies, after all...
If I can't control them,
I'll have to eliminate all civilizations that have
touched the Livlasters from my new world!
Captain! Teppei!
Let's get Hana back!
Roger!
We cannot allow that thing to exist!
Siren-sama, there's no end to this.
There's no way to destroy it except
with an Ego Block explosion.
Siren-sama,
ever since you got an Earth avatar,
you've been acting strangely.
Losing your Ego Block means you aren't
one of the Planetary Gears anymore!
Captain!
If we don't wipe that thing out here,
it will absorb the entire galaxy.
We Planetary Gears created that mass of desire.
I think I finally understand why
we cannot fire the Livlasters.
Because we're monsters with
swollen egos, just like that thing.
But I never would've realized that if not for
the time I spent as an Earthling avatar.
Perhaps we should entrust ourselves
to a momentary wind...
A wind, huh?
No way... This is impossible.
You can't do that!
How is it so fast, with that size?
Captain!
What are you doing?
Die.
What?
I just don't like having a debt to anyone.
D-Debt?
Thanks for teaching me that
the wind could feel good.
Now, if the power of your planetary sign
is proportional to your libido's power...
My libido's strong!
As strong as yours!
You think so?
Moco...
That crêpe truck we ran together
was pretty fun, wasn't it?
What are you talking about?
Amara?
No way... Amarok?
He sacrificed his Ego Block so I could survive...
What is the meaning of life?
Someday, death will come...
Before then, you do what you must.
They said that the strength of those
feelings becomes your power.
Is that what it means to be alive?
Probably.
In that case, we can only do what we must.
We'll go with you.
The Kiltgangs!
An Ego Block explosion?
No way!
Akari, are you all right?
Thanks to your barrier, there are no major problems.
What happened to him?
Did we kill him?
Signal at one o'clock!
Fools...
In the end, the Planetary Gears
could not escape being human?
But that took a lot of my strength...
I need energy.
Oh, no!
It's going to jump to Earth!
You can jump, right, Captain?
Destroy that monster and get Hana back!
Roger!
Let's go, Livlaster.
Who are you, Daichi Manatsu?
You will never be able to see this woman again.
I will get Hana back.
The key to the door that brought you
inside this ship is already mine.
Then I'll destroy the door and go in.
You cannot stop me.
I'll stop you, no matter what it takes.
AEO signal confirmed.
The Kiltgangs?
Video incoming.
What is this?
The Blume?
Hana...
The Blume transformed?
Another Entangle Link is emerging behind the Blume.
What is it?
What's going on?
You cannot protect anything.
Not this girl,
or that blue planet!
I will protect them!
I'm Captain Earth!
Roar, Stigmagnum!
Go!
I'm sorry, Unit 2.
I see it!
That was mean.
I told you that if you destroyed
this ship, I would die, as well.
Can you even shoot me?
You're in love with this bio-part, aren't you?
Then obey me, and be my tool.
If you use your Livlaster for my benefit,
I'll prepare a way for you to live with her.
That's right. That's right.
You can't shoot Hana Mutou—
A telepathic kiss?
Is it you?
Wake up, Hana.
I knew you'd come.
I'm sorry I'm a little late.
You think taking back one
bio-part means you've won?
The bio-part called Hana Mutou cannot
control this ship any longer.
If you destroy my Ego Block,
this ship, with its huge mass,
will fall to Earth at this speed.
Is that all right with you?
The whole planet's climate will change.
Earth will become a dead planet.
And if this body is destroyed,
that bio-part will die.
Put down your Livlaster, Daichi Manatsu.
You must obey me, and I'll save you both.
Puck does not lie—
Hana!
You do lie.
The real reason you wanted this body is
because if you remain an Ego Block
while you enter the Earth's atmosphere,
you'll cause a libido burst!
You little...
So I'll destroy this body before
you can make it there!
Please, Daichi... Help me.
I want to protect that planet
where the people I love live.
I want to protect the planet where I met you.
I want to live on that planet in a way that,
no matter when I die, I won't regret it!
So that's it, huh?
Dad...
Without the Boosted, you are powerless to hurt me!
Power doesn't come first.
What?
Your feelings come first!
That's right.
And we've always turned the strength
of our feelings into power!
What?!
Stop! What are you doing?
Now you've done it, Hana Mutou... Daichi Manatsu!
Hana!
I want to leave here and live with you!
Let's survive! Together!
If I'm going to die, I'll take you with me!
Hana!
Where are the captain and Hana?
Daichi...
Where's Amara?
He left.
Oh...
I'm back, Lappa.
It's such a pretty galaxy...
I love the view of space
from this planet most of all.
Me, too.
Thank you!!