Weather conditions clear.
Visibility good.
No anomalies in exercise programs.
Eight nosedives...
Eight pivots, total four sets each.
Then, we'll work on a new formation
for attacking Frigate-class foes.
That will be today's training.
Questions?
Nope.
After Salia Squad launches,
get ready for the transport craft landing.
Group Three,
and Group Four,
prepare for turnaround.
Help me, Onee-sama.
Angelise-oneesama!
Sylvia...
Arresting gear connected.
Launch systems complete.
All units ready for liftoff.
Salia squad, lifting off.
Ange, you are clear for liftoff.
Ange, what are you doing?
We're stuck back here behind you.
Hurry up and go, you constipation bitch!
Seriously. Who's the burden here?
Right, Hilda?
Hilda...
What are you doing?
The fleet is right there.
Emergency launch, hurry!
Mei, do it.
Ange, emergency launch.
All stand clear.
Engaging emergency launch system.
What was that for?
You were just sitting there.
The fleet is coming in for landing.
Again, don't be rude to them.
Here it comes, the Festa.
Festa?
You didn't know, Ange-chan?
The Festa is—
They fight the DRAGON in those?
That's correct, Misty-sama.
Bikini Escape
It's the Festa!
This is the Festa?
Every year, the humans give
us just this one day off.
We're relieved of all
training until tomorrow.
It's a one-day festival for us Norma.
It's a day of hope for us so
we can endure our cruel tomorrow.
Pero, pero!
Every good girl gets a
present from Perolina!
Thank you, Perolina.
A chance for the slaves to vent steam, huh?
Fine.
But what's with this?
It's a tradition.
The uniforms and rider suits are too stuffy.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Being in a bathing suit, I mean.
Thank you for coming so far,
Princess Misty Rosenblum.
Arzenal administration is
the Rosenblum family's duty.
You have finished your
baptism ritual, haven't you?
Yes.
Congratulations.
You're now a full member of the royal family.
May I ask one thing?
Yes, anything.
I've heard that Angelise-sama is here.
The Empire of Misurugi's
First Princess, Angelise-sama.
Th-There is no such person here.
Then please find her.
I want to see her.
No matter what.
That's it, beat them!
Pork Bone Impact!
Yeah, there! Go!
What's wrong with Hilda?
You idiot!
I feel like she's been avoiding me lately.
Go! Go for the last spurt!
You're the only one that can
multiply my cash 307.2 times!
Rosalie.
Wh-What?
About Hilda.
What?
She's not at the Festa.
What's wrong with her?
It's probably her period or something.
Shouldn't we go get her?
Leave her.
She's not here, so she doesn't
want to be with anyone.
But—
Have we ever been able to figure
out what Hilda's thinking?
Leave her, she'll be back
to normal eventually.
How can you get sniped?
Pork Bone Impact!
Tu m'aime?
Je t'aime.
It sure is lively.
It's almost like a school festi—
I'm sorry.
Angelise-sama.
Sylvia-sama, right?
There's no point worrying about it.
There isn't anything I
can do right now anyway.
But... I have a call.
Sylvia?
No.
Emma-san.
It's from the Officer.
Oh. I see.
Yes, Momoka here.
Yes.
What?
Angelise-sama.
What's wrong?
There's someone that would like to meet you.
Me?
Who?
Misty-sama.
Misty?
Misty Rosenblum?
I'm told she's the fleet's representative.
She'd like to meet you.
What'd be the point?
Does she want to mock me?
W-Well—
Um... Angelise-sama?
I don't want to bother. I'm disappearing.
Go away.
You'll blow my cover if you're near.
B-But Angelise-sama!
My name is Perolina, pero.
Perolina-sama.
Barbecue squid is so good.
You eat so much, Vivian.
The sports festival's coming up.
I need to be ready!
Ugh, squid stink.
For Angelise-sama.
Momoka-san.
Where's Ange?
I, um, lost her.
Misty-sama's waiting.
Commander, call Ange, immediately.
To hell with these people.
It's so hot.
It's so stuffy.
It's salty.
Are you okay, pero?
Yes, thank you, Perolina.
Stop it.
It's fine.
No one comes here during the Festa.
I'll stay here, then, pero.
Pero?
Wh-What's wrong with you?
That's better.
Leave me.
What's wrong with her?
Don't. This Perolina is insane.
It's breezy.
Sylvia.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Sylvia.
It's my fault.
It's not your fault.
Please take me afar again, Onee-sama.
Perolina-sama.
Where are you?
I hope she isn't dehydrated.
You're finally alone.
Fight for one million in cash!
Sports Festival!
It's the grand opening of the
annual Festa Sports Festival.
Everyone, go for the cash prize.
I'll make up for that pig in the water.
And now, the first contest.
The horror! Bun-eating
in melting swimsuits contest!
Group one, you're up.
Ready—
Wh-What the?
Who are you?
I'm here to see you, Misty.
It's me.
It can't be.
Angelise-sama.
It's been a long time, Misty.
Did you need something from me?
I've been wanting to see you, Angelise-sama.
Yeah?
I saw you at the Baptism Ritual.
I couldn't believe it.
The well-composed, wise,
beautiful Angelise-sama.
My eternal admiration, Angelise-sama.
It must be some mistake
that you were a Norma.
I must find out the truth.
That's why I came with the fleet.
Is this going to take a while?
I'm a Norma.
That's the truth, and that's all there is.
Are you happy?
E-Er, uh...
Yes.
Good.
Now, can you hear my request?
Yes.
Help me escape.
And now the fifth contest!
Hold the eggs between your
boobs and carry them across!
Who will be the winner?
Ready...
Start!
Damn it.
I got this.
Executed?
Yes, for deceiving the people,
the Misurugi royal family will someday...
Then Sylvia, too?
We have to hurry.
Help me.
What's this?
It's a Kingdom of Rosenblum transport ship.
You can use Mana, so I'm sure you can fly it.
I could, but what for?
Isn't it obvious?
To escape.
I refuse.
I only respond to Angelise-sama.
Want to die, then?
Are you okay with not being able to help
your beloved Angelise-sama anymore?
Momoka.
Angelise-sama and Misty-sama.
My, oh, my.
The Burn Princess.
Momoka, why are you with Hilda?
This woman wants me to fly
this plane so she can escape.
Escape?
Why?
What does it matter to you?
I won't let you.
Yeah? You're going to stop me?
I'm using this ship.
What?
For Sylvia-sama?
I took that girl's freedom.
So I have to protect her.
I have to.
Will you come with me, Momoka?
Gladly.
So we both want the same thing.
How about we cooperate, then?
No, thanks. I can't trust you.
Yeah?
Then how are you going to
remove the locks on this ship?
Locks?
This transport ship is
locked down with arresting
gear for maintenance checks.
Force it open, and the alarms will sound.
Force it to fly, and it'll be damaged.
Do you think you can release it?
I can.
I've been preparing for this the whole time.
So?
Want to team up?
Misty-sama.
Fight for one million in cash!
Sports Festival!
The winner this year is—
Who would have thought?
The darkest of dark horses!
Chris of Salia Squad!
To think she'd had such a
grand and intricate plan.
That was an amazing comeback.
Fly like a butterfly, sting like a butterfly!
Amazing, Chris.
Let's go eat something good.
Me, you and Hilda.
Chris, you—
That's the end of this year's Festa.
Hurry, the Festa's ending.
Emergency launch system standing by.
Understood.
Now!
All right!
It's an emergency!
Momoka, lift off.
What? But she's still—
Just do it.
What are you doing? Wait up.
I haven't forgotten about the bra.
I went through hell because of it.
That was a long time ago.
That's not all.
You shoot me from behind.
You use your minions to harass me.
The Perolina costume smells.
What's that last one?
Anyway, I can't trust you.
Live well with your friends.
Momoka, close the rear hatch.
Bullshit!
I waited years for this.
I let myself be Zola's
plaything so I could survive.
I made friends with those pests.
I did everything.
I've been waiting for this day.
I'm going back home to Mom.
Mom?
Momoka, we're taking one.
R-Right!
Oh, no! Misty-sama's been abducted by Norma...
You let yourself be bought out cheap.
Some guard dog you are.
Jasmine.
Call the boy.
Got it.
Shit, they got away.
Where's Misty-sama?
This is where we part ways.
Ange.
You better not die.
You, too, Hilda.
Preview
It's the long-awaited
swimsuit episode, pero.
But there were only a few slurpy scenes, pero.
Running pigs, stinky outfits,
and a great escape, pero!
Do they really know what a
swimsuit episode is, pero?
The Hometown of Betrayal
You're just making me make funny
noises, aren't you? Pero!