There's so much I need to talk about.
About her.
Him.
Her.
Hey!
And him.
But it wouldn't make
sense to start here.
Let's go back to the beginning.
Sitting Next To
Yoshida-kun
My name is Mizutani Shizuku.
I'm a first-year at Syoyo High School.
I sit next to Yoshida-kun,
who hasn't come to class once
after spilling blood on
the first day of school.
I heard he was covered
in blood and laughing.
Now, Yoshida Haru
They say he hangs out with scary people.
He can shatter concrete with
a sideways karate chop.
is the hot topic of the school
as "the phantom first-year."
A month ago, he put several
upperclassmen in the hospital,
and you can still find
lingering evidence of
the carnage at the crime scene.
However, none of that mattered to me.
I could use a new study guide...
10,000,000 Yen Annual Income
1st Grade Class 1, Mizutani Shizuku
I have a dream.
In order to achieve that dream,
I am completely focused on
calculus for the time being.
I don't have time to pay
attention to other people.
Mizutani-san.
Little Nines
Excuse me.  My name is Mizutani.
Is Yoshida-kun here?
Haru?  He's...
It's your fault that Marco died!
Haru!
I told you to control yourself in here!
But Mi-chan!
He...
You can't blame Marco's
death on anyone else.
You just suck.
Anyway, here.
You have a guest.
Huh?
Oh, here you go.
I was asked to drop these off.
Misawa GAME
Batting Center
Thanks for coming out here.
Hey!  Are you a spy for the school?
Huh?
Don't play dumb!
Ow!
That hurts!
I was just dropping off some handouts!
Handouts?
You better not be lying to me.
I thought you were going to tell me
to go to school like
that one teacher lady.
Hey.
What's your name?
Mi-Mizutani Shizuku.
Shizuku?
Hmm?
S-So this is like when someone gets sick
and a friend brings him handouts?
Oh, you can call me Haru!
S-Since we're friends!
See you later, Shizuku!
Incomprehensible.
Disturbing.
That was my first impression.
Receipt
Ninomiya Saeko
For study guide
Purchased on May 10th
Pay up, Saeko-sensei.
You promised to buy me a study
guide if I ran an errand for you.
Thank you, Mizutani-san!
I didn't know what to do because
he refused to see me.
How did it go?
He called me a friend.
What?  That's amazing!
In that case, can you persuade
him to come to school?
Persuade?
You see, Yoshida-kun's suspension
has already been lifted.
He did get a bit carried away,
but the upperclassmen were at fault.
When it happened, he was
suspended without any discussion,
so he doesn't trust the school anymore.
I'd have trouble sleeping at night
if he quits school as a result.
So persuade him to come back.
Okay, Mizutani-san?
I refuse.
Wh-Why?!
I really need your help!
Are you telling me to go persuade him?!
Are you a blizzard?!
Out of the question.
A raging blizzard!
Blizzard!
Never again.
I'm staying clear of that guy.
No funny moves.
Make one peep and I rape you.
Good.
Follow me.
Um...
Why did you bring me out here?
I found a stray dog on the way over.
So I hid it here.
A dog?!
What?
You see...
I'm not too
fond of dogs...
Actually, I'm not fond
of animals in general.
Sensei!
She died!
Yes, Mimi lived a happy life,
since she had so many friends.
What's wrong, Mizutani?
I need to do my homework,
so can I go home now?
After that, my classmates
began calling me Dry Ice.
What was I supposed to do?
I didn't feel sad at all.
Oh, there it is!
Were you sick of waiting?
Your breath really stinks!
That's probably not a stray!
I managed to return
the dog to its owner.
Why am I here?
And wait...
Who are these guys?
Yo, Haru.
What's up, Yamaken?
Who's that?
My friend Shizuku.
Friend?
Heh...
So Haru, could you lend me some money?
Again?
I screwed up and my allowance was cut.
Come on, aren't we friends?
This guy is an idiot.
So, what's it like?
Huh?
Don't play dumb!
I know you went to school today!
Wh-What's your point?!
W-Was school fun?
Huh?
S-So, this is kinda like
hanging out with a
friend after school, huh?
Yoshida-kun, are you saying that
you want to go to school?
If you want to know what
it's like, just go.
I'm scared.
Everyone is always afraid
of me for some reason.
It doesn't take long before
they all start avoiding me.
That's why I don't want to go to school.
But you're the first person
who came to my home,
and those guys were
the first people to hang out with
me without acting scared,
so I don't need to go to school now.
You're the only one
who sees it that way.
Huh?
Real friends wouldn't use you for money.
I don't have any friends,
so I'm no expert,
but I'd rather have no friends
than have friends like them.
You're a bad person.
What's his problem?
I was just stating the facts.
Why was he so mad?
Mizutani-san.
Did you ask him to come to school?
No.
I see...
He's refusing to take my calls...
The way things are looking,
he'll probably be expelled.
Welcome.
Haru isn't here.
Oh.
No, um...
Can you tell Yoshida-kun
he'll be expelled
if he keeps skipping school?
Bye.
Hold on.
Want a go at it?
Left Hit
Right Hit
I can't hit the ball...
Why am I doing this?
I shouldn't have come here.
Man, what's up with Haru?
He stopped giving me money.
Really?
Does it matter?
It's not like you're broke or anything.
But it's lame.
No point in bothering with him anymore.
See?  Told you so.
Idiot!
Oh...
So he actually has feelings.
Not that I care.
The dog was kidnapped!
Seriously?
Something's wrong with me today...
The collar should have told
him that it wasn't a stray.
Yes, really.
What do you want?
Why am I doing this?
Oh, isn't she...
the girl who was with Haru?
But...
After seeing that look on his face...
Yo-Yoshida-kun thinks you
guys are his friends.
So, if you consider him a friend,
you should be honest with him!
What's her problem?
Ha-Haru?!
You guys should leave.
Afterwards,
Yoshida-kun walked me home
without saying a word.
Y-You don't need to cry!
No...
I was so happy.
I don't understand...
I didn't shed a single
tear when that happened,
but now, I'm about to break down...
It's okay.
It won't be long before you're
surrounded by lots of people.
If you're there,
I'll try going to school.
I'm glad to hear that.
My heart is beating really fast.
Huh?
I think I like you.
Y-You mean in a friend kind of way?
In a sexual way!
W-Wait a second!
I-It's probably just something
like an imprinted sentiment.
You're misunderstanding
your own feelings
because you've never
had any friends before.
Huh?
So once I make more friends,
you'll believe me?
I-I guess...
Fine,
but my feelings won't change.
I'll always love you.
It was a beautiful spring day
when I received my first
confession of love in my life.
The next day, Yoshida-kun
showed up at school.
Shi-Shizuku!
I'm so nervous that
I can't move my legs!
What are you doing here?!
One Month Later
Shizuku!
Help!
I'm being robbed!
They told me to give them money!
Huh?
3. Modern Japanese
4. Gym (Co-ed)
5. Math
Where are you going, Shizuku?
Gym.
O-Oh...
It's finally come...
But this is normal...
There!
What are you doing?!
What?!  But Mi-chan said that...
Over the past month,
I've come to realize that there's
no end to the wacky behavior
that arises from
Haru's misguided notions about school.
But...
None of it mattered to me.
The problem was that...
May - Monja Special
20 monja places you must visit
Take me here.
No.
Why not?!
We're talking monja!  Monja!
Like I already explained,
I want to study after school!
Monja!  Monja!  Monja!  Monja!
Yes, ever since returning to school,
he's been following me around,
and I'm having trouble studying.
Oh, Mizutani-san.
Eh?
What are you looking at?
Okay, no need to intimidate her.
I don't like you!
Get lost!
You should join her.
Wait!
Stop!  Stop!
Yo-Yoshida-kun, you're supposed
to treat girls with care!
I'll lend you one of my favorite books!
Okay?
Get along now!
"That was when he placed
his arms around me in a gentle embrace,
and my heart began to pound..."
My feelings won't change.
I'll always love you.
After thinking, thinking,
and thinking some more
about what he meant...
Sensei!
What does it mean to treat
someone with care?!
You need to be considerate.
What do you do to be considerate?
You should do nice things.
For the first time in my life,
I gave up on a question
I couldn't solve.
They look like they're having fun.
I bet they get to eat dinner
or play dodgeball together.
I wish I got to do something...
Come on, Shizuku...
I already said that I'm not going!
Midterms are coming up.
It's not just about monja.
Friends are supposed to
hang out together, right?
I want to go with you.
Nobody else is willing
to look me in the eye.
That's because you're either
glaring at them, threatening them,
or beating them up.
There was a speech during
the opening ceremony
that was given by the first-year
with the highest score.
I've always had the highest grades.
I worked very hard
to make that happen.
Next, we have a speech
from the first year class.
But this time...
it wasn't me.
So...
I have to redeem myself during midterms.
I don't have time to waste on monja.
Oh.
First, you find the coordinates
for the intersection.
And this answer is wrong.
It should be b=4, not b=8.
I remember now...
The first-year speaker...
Please step forward.
...never showed up.
First-year speaker, Yoshida Haru!
Hmm?
Oh!  Shizuku!
Why did you go home without
telling me yesterday?!
What?!
Sorry, but until midterms
are over, you're my enemy.
I need you to stop distracting
me from my studies.
What's so special about studying?
Every problem has an answer.
How hard can it be?
You must really hate me.
Man, seriously!
Why am I so upset?!
I should study.
Right.  Other people don't matter.
That's the philosophy
I've always followed.
Hey.
Yes?
Where's Shizuku?
I-I don't know...
Oh, I saw her a second ago.
Man, why did you bring her here?
Aren't you mad about that
first-year beating us up?
Pumpkin
Pudding
Cookies
How adorable.
Are you a first-year?
Want something to eat?
You always act without thinking.
They're the ones Haru beat
up for robbing him.
Excuse me.
Do you mind if I study?
Huh?
Er, go ahead.
Right.
Everything has gone wrong
since he came into the picture.
I just want
some peace and quiet
to study.
Where is Shizuku?!
Shizuku!
Bastards!
What did you do to her?!
Forget it.  Let's go.
I can't let this slide!
I'm going to kill them!
It's okay.
Stop it...
Shut up!
W-Wait!
Are you okay?
I've...
had enough.
We're finished.
I'm sick of your friendship games.
Just disappear.
Maybe you thought
I could provide you with the
connection you always wanted,
but I can't give you that,
because I think it's a waste of time.
So that's how it is...
Midterms
1st Period - Modern Japanese
2nd Period - English
3rd Period - Math
Midterm Grades - First Year
1st Mizutani Shizuku
2nd Sawada Riku
3rd Kasano Masamune
Yes!
Yes.
I don't understand...
I came in first.
I should be happy.
Man...
If you're not being victimized,
you're picking fights.
Just look at what happened
with those kids.
You should be honest with him!
Oh, welcome.
First.
Huh?  What's your point?
You hate me so much that you
wanted to rub it in my face?
I don't hate you.
I don't hate you, Haru.
Y-You don't need to cry!
No.
I was so happy.
In that moment,
I could feel my heart move.
I forgot to tell you:
Thank you for coming to save me.
You made me happy.
After that...
The general consensus
is that Yoshida Haru
has calmed down.
You're quiet today.
Yep, you bet.
Because you care
about studying a lot,
for some reason, right?
If it's something you care about,
it's something I care about.
I see.
So that's what it means to
treat someone with care.
Which means...
I'm being cared about right now?
What is it?  Are you done?
A-Are you hungry?
Monja!  Monja!  Monja!
You must be really hungry
if you stopped studying.
Oh.  Well...
I wasn't getting any studying done.
Hmm?
Plus, you look happy.
What?
Huh?
My heart isn't pounding.
Why not?
So I've noticed that
you don't make my heart flutter.
Huh?
I wonder why.
My heart was jumping out
of my chest before.
But I still love you.
Hey.  Let's hurry up, Shizuku.
Huh?
Ooh, a rooster.
Wait, are you a stray?
Well, you'll catch a cold if
you stay out in the rain.
Come in here.
You don't want to?
I took a bath yesterday...
Next Episode
Weird
Ow!  Ow!
Watch the claws!
That's a sensitive area!