This is justice!
In response to the cowardly act of the Terrans
who turned on Princess Asseylum,
who came down to Earth in order to
make herself a bridge of peace,
we Orbital Knights must
deal them a crushing blow!
The Terrans' spilled blood will be
our tribute to Her Highness!
Okay, keep it coming!
I was a nervous wreck! I thought I was
going to step on you, Matsuribi-senpai!
If you had, you'd get hit with a
lot worse than point deductions.
That ain't even funny,
right, Yutaro-chan?
I wish you'd stop
calling me that...
Can you climb down?
Yes.
Thank you for your concern.
What's going on?
The landing craft's radar has picked up
multiple massive bodies above Shinawara.
A meteor bombardment...
Freaking Martians!
We made it out just in time.
You're safe!
Yes. Thank you, Eddelrittuo.
How go things here?
No change, Milady.
I see. Thank goodness.
Good work out there, Nao.
Yuki...
I mean it, good job.
It's due entirely to the guidance of your
good-natured, beautiful instructor, I'm sure.
You did good.
You, too.
Nina!
Inko!
You came to rescue us!
Yeah. When I didn't see your names on
the ferries' passenger manifests, I...
It's a relief, huh?
Yeah.
She's my favorite.
The city is gone, isn't it?
Yeah...
It's only a matter of time
before we...
No way. We're gonna survive this,
mark my words.
If that's your plan,
then maybe you should start
by dodging that?
Right? Right? Left?
Quick exhaust.
Sheesh, what's the helmsman doing?
Um...
Sure.
Thank you for earlier, er...
Inaho. Inaho Kaizuka.
Thank you so much, Inaho. I am-
Please, call me Seylum.
I'll do that, Seylum.
If it is not too much trouble, perhaps
you could show me around the ship?
Inaho?
But Milady, you-
It's all right.
Let us try that again. I am
Asseylum Vers Allusia.
Emperor Vers' granddaughter.
That's the real you?
My earlier appearance is the
result of what I am told
is a form of optical camouflage
that employs holography.
The princess was assassinated on the day
of the parade. I saw the whole thing.
She was-
A double.
Her Highness was not
feeling well that day.
For that reason, the skeptical security detail
leader insisted that a double be used.
So that wasn't a hypothesis.
When my grandfather the emperor
learns that I am alive and well,
this war will come to
an end immediately.
I wish to get in touch with
Vers as soon as possible.
How?
At the very least, it would be
difficult to do from here.
Their jamming makes long-range
communications impossible.
And our telecommunications bases have been
destroyed, so we can't use the Net, either.
But we can take you to a facility that
can contact the Vers government.
I'll talk to my sister Yuki
and the others about it.
You mustn't do that!
There is a Vers spy hidden
amongst the Terrans!
In league with those assassins, no doubt!
The spy wishes to see
Her Highness dead!
I do apologize for dragging you
into our problems.
I beg you, keep this
matter between us.
I'm really glad that we
have you here, Dr. Yagarai.
I haven't used exoskeleton
therapy in a long time.
Please refrain from doing anything crazy.
This is only temporary.
It'll do, it'll do!
Just because you aren't in pain doesn't mean
there isn't any strain on your system.
When that anesthetic wears off,
it's going to be unpleasant.
I've got it, don't worry. I'll come in
for fine-tuning later, okay?
Or maybe I should have you make a few
more adjustments while you're here...
Oh, so Okisuke was...
Man, he was a moron
up to the very end...
A moron and a perv
and a slacker.
Poor bastard, dying and then
getting chewed out like this...
He shouldn't have
gotten himself killed, then.
Inko...
They started a war
and destroyed the Moon.
Heaven's Fall wrecked the Earth.
They've been up there in the Satellite Belt
looking down on us ever since!
I'll make them pay! For Okojo and
every other Terran who was killed!
Martian sons of bitches...
About earlier...
What will you do?
Keep her secret?
In an extreme situation where there's
no telling when an enemy will come,
human beings aren't known for
remaining calm and rational.
If they found out that she's a Martian, there's
no telling what might happen to her.
You're a real softie, aren't you?
Showing concern for the enemy?
She isn't the enemy.
The enemy is the people who
tried to assassinate her.
If what she says is true, we need to deliver
her... Seylum, safely to United Earth HQ.
And you?
Rayet.
My name.
It's Rayet Areash.
What about you, Rayet?
I'll make no guarantees.
If I think we're in danger,
I'll spill everything.
Martians are all the enemy.
Sir Trillram... is dead, you say?
Yes, Milord. He was caught
in the meteor bombardment.
Swine... To think one of us would target my
occupied territory under the cover of the battle!
Have they no honor as a fellow
Orbital Knight with a common goal?
Very well. Sooner or later, I shall uncover
his identity and mete out his punishment.
Summon Vlad!
Hunt down the remnant Terrans
and burn this place to ashes!
We shall avenge
Her Highness!
Milord Count.
About Princess Asseylum...
That's why I'm going to kill her
and make certain this time!
What?
Nothing, Milord. Inflicting further devastation
upon a previously conquered area...
Given Princess Asseylum's sentiments,
might that not be...
Oh. You imply that you wish to
have some say in avenging her?
Know your place, Terran!
You think yourself worthy of
doing battle at Vers' side?
For 15 long years, we Orbital Knights
ingloriously looked out at the Earth
from the shattered Moon, yearning for the
day we would reach out and take it!
With her death, the Princess has made
that cherished dream a reality!
This battle belongs to the Orbital Knights.
It is no concern of yours!
He's trying to exploit
the Princess' death, too.
Trillram was an invited guest
at Castle Cruhteo...
If we let her live, my entire clan and its
followers will be branded as traitors!
"We"... This assassination
conspiracy has a ringleader.
Count Cruhteo?
No, it couldn't be...
What should I do?
Power down engines!
Captain Magbaredge!
I'm glad you're safe!
We've been waiting for you!
Commander Nakabayashi. Good work.
Where's everyone else?
The amphibious assault craft Wadatsumi is
currently taking a longer, safer route.
The seas are a mess thanks
to that meteor bombardment.
On XO Mizusaki's orders, we went ahead
in Craft #1 with Appaloosa Platoon.
We are here to support you and defend the
refugees until the Wadatsumi arrives.
That's a big help.
Still... this place was
abandoned, wasn't it?
Even though there's been no
damage to this area yet.
Yes, ma'am.
It's a wise decision.
Digging in only makes the damage worse.
The best thing is to bug out.
Exactly the opinion I'd expect from someone
who lived through the war 15 years ago.
We'll wait for the Wadatsumi to arrive.
Have anyone who isn't busy help with
resupplying the landing craft.
Understood.
We'll leave your rations here!
Thanks.
It's unusual for you
to offer to help out, Calm.
Yeah, you always played hooky
from military drills.
That was then.
Now, I'll do anything if it means
wiping out the Martians.
I've set up a three-shift
perimeter watch.
Any word from
the Wadatsumi?
No, the jamming's too intense.
I can't believe a signal can't
cross a few dozen miles.
We'll continue scanning.
Appaloosa Leader,
this is Appaloosa 33.
Have located friendly unit.
Appears to be damaged.
What's the matter,
Appaloosa 33?
What's that?
We're under attack!
What the hell?
All hands to battle stations.
Yes, ma'am.
Prep Craft #1 for liftoff ASAP!
Get inside, everyone!
Appaloosa 33, sitrep!
Enemy Kataphrakts, 1.
Hiding behind building.
Currently engaging.
Surround it and fire at will.
All units, spread out.
Projectile weapons?
How crude.
Witness the power of my
customized Kataphrakt, the Argyre!
Aldnoah output climbing.
Connecting to energy joints.
Deploying blade field.
Aldnoah drive output at maximum.
Plasma generator startup preparations complete.
Sword drawn.
Open fire!
Some kind of laser weapon?
No... It's a katana?
Appaloosa 33!
Message from Craft #1.
Put it on speaker.
Captain Magbaredge!
Status?
Not good, ma'am.
How about on your end?
Fueling complete!
Refugee boarding complete!
We'll lift off, too.
We'll get some distance and
finish this with SSMs.
Let's regroup out at sea!
A Mars Knight...
Sitrep!
Damage to hull! Negligible!
Will not affect seaworthiness!
APU shutting down!
Unable to power up engines!
I'll go look.
I'll go, too!
What the hell?!
Hey! Calm!
The main engine looks okay.
Make temporary repairs!
That isn't the same type
as the one this afternoon.
That thing in its hand...
Is that a beam katana?
Like I care.
I shall speak with
that knight.
Mila-
It's too dangerous! What if he is
in league with the assassins?
I am aware of the risk. But that is
the only way to keep everyone safe.
No! You were lucky
this afternoon, nothing more!
You must never do something
so reckless again!
Please stay here.
Stay here.
Inaho?!
I'll buy us some time.
You two get inside.
We're your friends, aren't we?
We'll help!
Thanks.
Hey, you two!
Inko, I need you up there.
Up where?
Trainers?
Inaho?
Engine room!
We're patching straight
into the pressure tank!
No luck with HE rounds, huh?
Then let's try AP rounds.
Clever. Rounds that contain no
explosives won't detonate in midair.
Nevertheless!
The tips are evaporating and throwing
off the bullets' trajectory...
The Leidenfrost effect, huh?
The heat it's putting out is incredible...
A pincer attack, eh?
What?!
How amusing. But how long can
you last in that Kataphrakt?
Damn it!
This is the end.
Maybe a little more
to the right...
Bingo.
My main monitor!
Calm.
Finally!
One more time!
Don't underestimate me!
I guess not!
Who do you insects
think you are?!
Sorry we're late,
Captain Magbaredge.
It took a long time to
find a safe route.
Mizusaki, would you like to know
why you can't get a date?
I thought you were supposed to
arrive fashionably late, ma'am.
That's a tactic that you use
after you've landed a date.
The smoke's cleared!
Now able to target!
Disable fuses on rounds.
Kataphrakt Platoon, take aim!
Fire!
Come on!
We have pressure!
Turbine RPMs climbing!
Ignition!
Let's withdraw.
Roger!
You think you can get away?!
You're not worth my time!
Exactly as planned, huh?
What plan?! That was really
close back there!
It's not like you to be
so reckless, Inaho.
I suppose it isn't.
Maybe you're right.
What is it, Slaine?
Please allow me to avenge
Princess Asseylum!
As I recall, I told you
that you are not worthy.
Begone, Terran.
Let me...
...go into battle!