I got called over by my crush.
Confession
It must be a confession.
I'm ecstatic.
It's been ten minutes.
Have you still not worked up the courage?
H-Hey...
Wait!
D-Do you have a crush on
anyone or anything, Takase?
What's the correct answer in this situation?
Should I just say, "you"?
But then I'd be stealing her confession.
But it's not like I don't have a crush...
Oh, you do?
No, I didn't mean that.
What? You aren't making sense.
Just say so if you do.
F-Fine, then, I don't.
What do you mean, "Fine, then"?
I mean I don't.
Really?
Wasn't there something you
wanted to talk to me about?
L-Like I said, I wanted to know
if you had a crush on anyone.
So?
I'll tell you, and then what?
Fshh
Fshhh
Are you done? I'm leaving.
It's not that I'm done.
But I kind of missed my chance today.
All right, I'm leaving, then.
W-Wait.
H-Hey...
W-Would you...
All right, bring it!
Would you meet up with me tomorrow, too?
I guess I should do it.
I-I'll tell you tomorrow.
Nah, it's fine.
But first, there's something I...
Really?
You'll meet up with me?
S-Sorry about today.
I forgot what I was going to say.
No.
About that...
Huh?
I-I'll tell you tomorrow that I like you.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Minagawa-san, the class rep,
doesn't do her job.
She's a slacker
Could you help me out a
little, Minagawa-san?
But I'm too lazy.
Then why did you become the class rep?
Because I like you, Furuya-kun.
Could you please not mess with me?
Oh? Are you angry?
Sorry.
That wasn't my intent.
I-I'm not angry, really.
It's true that I like you, though.
Is that supposed to be a confession?
Of course.
Will you go out with me?
But there are rumors that you
hang out with lots of guys.
I'm a virgin, though.
Besides, I have guy friends,
but it's not like that.
Y-Yeah?
Do you think I'm lying?
Not really.
You think I'd sleep with anyone, don't you?
N-Not really.
You're getting horny just
imagining me having sex.
No, I'm not!
I knew it, you're just toying with me!
Sorry.
But these things are always really awkward.
That's why I can't tell
if you're serious or not.
Then will you give me an answer
if I told you properly?
A-Answer?
I don't know you that well.
Besides, why me?
You could get with anyone.
I like you.
And what about you?
I-I don't know anything about dating yet.
But...
Teehee
Shudder
What are you grinning about?
You're too adorable, Furuya-kun.
No more, we're done talking about this!
You haven't given me an answer.
You're going to laugh at me again
if I try to answer, aren't you?
Yup.
Did I make you hate me?
Yeah, specifically how flippant you are.
So reject me, then.
Seriously, can we not talk about this?
So you don't totally hate me.
I seriously hate you!
The student council president saw me smoking.
Dammit.
The Student President's Woes
That's no good, Kaji-san.
Akagi! You aren't going
to rat me out, are you?
Nope, I'm not a monster.
I'll let you off the hook just this once.
You're pretty cool.
If you give me a kiss, that is.
Are you messing with me?
I'm being serious.
There's something that's
been on my mind, actually.
I've never been in love with a woman.
What are you, gay?
Nope, I tested that.
Huh? Tested what?
I just have a hard time
finding interest in women.
I can't figure out what's
so fun about dating.
So you want to kiss someone to find out?
Sure, that sounds fun.
I'll teach you how to kiss.
No, I know how to kiss.
Oh, sorry.
You're surprisingly cooperative.
Well, it's not like this is my first time.
I'll kiss anyone for money.
Really?
Then how much would you sell your body for?
Say, 100,000 yen?
That's perfect.
Why do you have that much?!
Are you scared?
What?
I'm not scared.
Shudder
Zzzzzip
You've never actually prostituted
yourself, have you?
What?
Who do you think you're talking to?
No one asks for 100,000.
That proves you've never
actually sold yourself before.
But 100,000 is actually too little.
I want you to value yourself more.
Akagi...
I'm still asking for that kiss, though.
You are?!
Of course.
Don't forget our agreement
about your smoking.
Are you scared?
N-No, I'm not scared.
All right, here we go.
You reek of tar.
You reek, Kaji-san.
Shut up! What'd you expect?!
You should quit smoking.
Bite me!
What are you, my boyfriend?
That doesn't sound bad.
I think I can fall in love with you.
As long as you quit smoking.
Piss off!
Astronomy Club
Yukawa-senpai is a third-year.
He's graduating tomorrow.
Senpai, show me the stars again tonight.
No way. You're too annoying, Sasahara.
You suck.
I was going to confess to you, too.
How many hundreds of times has it been?
Shucks, you got me.
I'm sick of it.
This is a bad habit of mine.
I make a joke of my feelings for him.
Spica
I want to tell him how I
feel, for real this time.
First, I think it's important
to set the mood.
Senpai, it's cold. Is it all
right if I huddle up with you?
Yeah, stay out of my way.
Also, is it okay if I push you down?
What?
Sorry.
This is our last time seeing
the stars from here.
It is.
This is the last time seeing
the stars with you, too.
It is.
ba-dump
I mean, we could see the stars
together if we really tried, though.
Blush             Blush
Shut up, already.
Have you learned any of the stars yet?
No, well, uhh...
Spica, I guess?
That's the first one I taught you.
I'd never forget a star
that you taught me, Senpai.
Point out Spica, then.
U-Um...
Get it together.
You're the only member
in this club next year.
That's your fault, Senpai.
You always look so grouchy.
Then why did you join?
For love, of course.
Sure, sure.
I'm glad my juniors love me.
Would you be glad if I really liked you?
I did it!
I told him I like him
without joking about it!
I wonder if Yukawa-senpai
will appreciate it.
Maybe he won't.
Huh? What's with this vibe?
Am I making a mistake?
Did I blow it?
No, no, no...
Sasahara.
Just kidding!
Did you think I was being serious?
I blew it.
I can't tell him I like him anymore.
He wouldn't believe me.
I told Senpai I like him so many times over
the past two years we spent together.
I could never tell him I was serious.
Senpai's graduating.
I'll never get to tell him I like him.
I'm going to cry.
No, no.
I don't want to cry in front of Senpai.
I don't want to worry him.
I don't want to make it awkward.
I want him to smile like he did before.
Don't cry, don't cry, don't cry...
Please don't cry.
I'm tired of hearing you say you like me.
You're awful.
But that ends tonight.
I want to hear it one more time before I go.
I'll say it, if you won't.
Senpai...
I seriously love you.
Stop crying, idiot.
Next episode: "Spring."
Spring