Episode 5   Umaru and Summer Vacation
Midterms
1: Doma Umaru
2: Tachibana Sylphynford
Umaru-chan, you're number one again?
That's amazing. You're so perfect.
Th-That's not true.
298: Ebina Nana
What's this?
Shupaaan
Umaru-san, I won't lose next time.
Self-flower petals?
Sylphyn kept it pretty simple today.
Maybe she's plotting something.
Well, what's more important is summer
vacation, which starts tomorrow.
I'm so psyched for it.
Yeah. Now that our tests are over,
I'm totally gonna let loose.
What will you do, Umaru-chan?
The same as usual, I guess.
The Next Day
Summer vacation: the time
when I can stay at the arcade
all morning long without being bothered,
while the masses are busy working.
I will take full advantage
of this right as a student.
All I do is sit here dropping tokens.
Currency
Exchange
But that's why it's so great.
Shupapapaa
Winner
Shipaan
I'd recognize that back anywhere, UMR-san!
I've found you!
0.2 Seconds
Well, hello, TSF-san.
Yes, I am TSF. Tachibana Sylphynford!
Oh? Do you wear your mask
in private, as well?
W-Well, I have my reasons.
Well, that matters not.
I have some unfinished business
with you, UMR-san.
You see, I have a classmate
named Doma Umaru-san.
Umaru-san and I are rivals.
Shupaan
My mission in life is to defeat Umaru-san.
However...
Shupaa
Before that, I will win against you, UMR-san,
since you defeated me recently.
Wha...
Come. We shall play some Supe IV.
No, er, uh... I didn't bring
my personal controller today.
Oh? Is that so?
Well, then...
I shall defeat you in this
game you were just playing.
Why am I playing a coin
game with Sylphyn-san?
Here I go.
Chance
Wh-What is all this racket?
Jackpot!
Er, it's a chance for you to get more coins.
Whoa, you got 5,000 coins!
That's amazing, TSF-san!
I've never seen that happen before!
What? Does that mean I win?
Uh, I wouldn't exactly call it winning...
I shall give this to you.
Now, let's play another game.
This is a blessing from God!
Now that I look at this game more
carefully, it's all just about luck!
No, this game is about probability,
where there's an expected value...
We will settle things with another game!
What?
Here you go.
Authorized
Personnel
Only
My goodness...
We've played so many games
and still haven't settled anything.
Well, they're all games that I'm good at. But...
Um, I'm not sure why
you want to win so badly,
but I think an arcade is a
place for enjoying games.
So, in that case, here.
Winner
You win, TSF-san.
I have won!
Shubuwaa
She looks so happy...
Shubatuurn
UMR-san.
Rivals become friends after a victory.
UMR-san. You will join forces with me,
and we shall defeat Umaru-san.
Wh-Why and how am I supposed to help?
I haven't the slightest,
but you're going to help me!
" Y o u ' r e  g o i n g  t o  h e l p  m e ! "
.
U . M . R  h a s  j o i n e d  T . S . F !
Tokyo
Sunny
38 degrees Celsius...
It's hot.
Man, it's summer, all right.
Wouldn't you say there's nothing
better in summer than sitting
in a well-air-conditioned
room and playing My Summer?
Indeed.
Master, I shall make more Calpis.
Ah, I'd like mine with a ratio of 7:3.
Yes, Master.
Kirie-chan's so good at taking care of me,
I'm becoming a worse person.
Here you go, Master.
Ah, thank you.
Heck, I'm fine with becoming worse.
Auto
Air Con.
Wind
Strength
Temp
All right, Kirie-chan.
Let's enjoy summer even more.
Yes.
It is overwhelmingly summer.
I wonder what people living in the
outside world are doing right now.
I heard that it's hotter than
35 degrees Celsius outside.
But I am in my nice, cool room, drinking Calpis.
Huh? Master?
She's so comfortable, she fell asleep.
So cute!
What is this adorable creature?!
Menacing
I just can't!
I-I want to keep the memory of
this adorableness in my hands.
I know. I'll use my cellphone camera...
I-I'm sorry, Master.
I just couldn't help myself...
Huh? Master?
Are you awake?
Sh-She's climbing me!
M-Master, what's wrong?
Is this a new pasttime?
So this is happiness...
Master!
Cola
Master! It's a dolphin!
Master, isn't this the best summer?
Stop
It's hot!
Good morning.
Preference      Heat       Temp
Your bath is ready.
How do you all take your baths?
Long baths.
Milk baths.
Quick baths.
There are many kinds,
but what I'm about to show you
is how I usually take my baths.
Ice cups, potato chips, a manga magazine,
and a waterproofed gaming console.
Shonen Jumpu
Umaru's castle is complete!
Because I am so busy,
I bring my games to the bath.
As a gamer, I can't let
even a second go to waste.
Also, it may seem like an odd match
to eat potato chips in the bath,
but I can eat them without worrying
about my hands getting messy.
While my game is loading,
I can read my Jumpu.
And... Ice eaten while bathing is just...
If you don't do your homework,
no potato chips and cola for you.
-Taihei
I can feel all of the stress
of the day draining away.
Aw, the bubbles stopped.
I want to put a lot more in,
but the last time I used a lot, I got yelled at.
I'm going to keep an eye on
this so you won't waste it.
Bobu
Just a little more...
The bubbles envelop my whole body!
When I'm in the bath, time
goes by slower and slower.
It gets hot, I can't breathe,
and I get thirsty...
And that's when...
I have my post-bath cola!
Drinking cola after waiting until
my utmost limit is the best!
Don't drink too much.
Oh, yeah! I've gotta drink my coffee
milk right after my bath, too.
My cola! O-Onii-chan!
What a mighty fine bath.
The amount of laundry is ridiculous
since I can only do it on my day off.
Man, it takes forever to get a lot of gold
in social network games these days.
Umaru.
Huh? What?
10,000 yen?!
Wait, what's this for?
Bribes won't work on me.
But you just took it...
You don't have a lot of clothes
to wear outside, do you?
It's summer vacation,
so why don't you invite Ebina-chan
and Kirie-chan and go shopping?
If I had this much in gold, I'd be invincible...
Don't buy anything other than clothes.
I'm so happy you invited me
to go shopping with you.
I invited Kirie-chan too, but...
Kirie-chan, you're already here.
Y-Yes.
Thank you very much for inviting me out toda—
Your clothes are so frilly and cute, Kirie-chan!
Looks like Kirie-chan still
doesn't like Ebina-chan...
What kind of clothes do
you guys want to look at?
I want to look at cute clothes.
What about you, Kirie-chan?
A-Anywhere is fine...
Man, there're so many shops in heah...
In here.
Which shop should we look at?
I know. Let's take a look around,
and buy whatever we like most last.
Good idea.
So expensive!
I could buy 60 colas for the
price of this piece of cloth.
Can I help you find anything?
Oh, we're just looking around...
Wow, you're so cute!
Are you a model or something?
What brands do you usually wear?
Solid colors are pretty popular right now.
Menacing
W-Welcome...
Is actually just looking at Umaru
Shubaa
Hey, I think this would look
good on you, Umaru-chan.
Ebina-chan is always so meek,
and yet she's so sharp right now.
Ah. Um... K-Kirie-chan,
did you find anything?
They're still a bit rigid with each other...
I know.
Ebina-chan, Kirie-chan,
since you're both here, you two
should try on some clothes, too.
'Kay?
S-Sure.
Y-Y-Y-Y-Yes.
That was so much fun!
Yeah.
Okay, let's go buy the things we liked,
and meet back up here in an hour.
Okay.
Now, I'll go get that dress
I saw at the first shop.
On Sale Today!!
Limit 1 Copy
per Customer
Yen (Tax In.)
Don't buy anything other than clothes.
Don't do it!
Don't you do it!
Don't buy anything other than clothes...
Don't do it! Don't you do it!
Sunday
You do have more clothes now,
but they all seem kind of dull.
Huh? Onii-chan, solid colors
are really popular right now.
What's that about?
Hey, wake up, Umaru!
It's only eight...
How long are you going to
act like it's summer vacation?
Your new semester starts today.
I guess it's true that you only realize how
precious something is once you've lost it.
My summer vacation... and Onii-chan, too.
Stop saying depressing things
and eat your breakfast.
Where's my steak?
There isn't one. Could you even
eat that right after waking up?
For crying out loud...
It's already the usual time that
Ebina-chan's waiting for you.
Meow.
If you understand, hurry up and eat...
Don't fall asleep!
Well, be careful, you two.
Bye, Onii-chan.
U-Um, uh... Have a good day.
I'm sorry!
System Support Section
Bomber, we just got to the office.
Yeah, I usually get a boost in the afternoon.
Taihei-senpai, my PC froze.
Could I ask for your assistance?
Huh? Sure...
I'm in my panties,
but I'm not
embarrassed!
2-D Love
Channel
Do it over.
How ya doin', Taihei?
Say, Taihei.
Hm?
You always bring homemade stuff.
Do you make it yourself?
Or is it your girlfriend?
Ah...
No, it's my little sister...
Huh... Is your sister cute?
Umaruun
Onii-chan, buy it!
Nah. Normal.
Huh...
Settled                     Not Settled
Sorry.
No, it's okay.
Want to get some drinks? My treat.
Don't worry about it.
I love you.
No, seriously, don't worry about it.
Imported Steak
Super Cheap!
I'm home.
Wake up, Umaru!
Wha?! What?!
An earthquake?!
It's time for dinner. Wake up.
O-Onii-chan? Welcome ho—
Why are you smirking?
I'm not...
By the way, Umaru. What do you
think is for dinner tonight?
Hm, sushi?
Wait, steak?!
Yeah, actually...
Can you eat that right after waking up?
Heck yeah!
Next Time
Episode 6       Umaru's Birthday
Oh, no!
I have to do the preview by myself this time!
We did finish using all the
main characters last week.
What will we do after this week?
Just get the director or Sankaku Head-sensei.
That's it!