Here.
Why did she have to glare at us like that?
Just because we're going on a trip doesn't
mean we've done something wrong.
I think that's just her job.
Yeah, yeah! It was crazy!
So? So? What happened?
A plane!
Is this the plane we're taking?
I think so.
Will it really fly?
I always dreamed about being a plane!
Being a plane?
Yes, being a plane!
A Place Further Than the Universe
#ExtraLargeHelping #SexyPinUp #24Hours
Welcome to the Durian Show
4 Likes
3 Comments
Dear Mom
What?
It means the plane has stabilized
and you can walk around.
Yes!
I'm so nervous...
I didn't realize this was your
first time on a plane, Shirase!
I watched my mother fly
out a number of times,
but I've never been on one myself.
I bet you've flown lots of
times, right, Yuzu-chan?
For work, certainly...
How do I use this?
Same question! Same question!
It says "Games"...
Um, you press this...
Is this soba?
Can I trade my celery for your sweet egg?
No.
Green tea.
Right! Go right!
Hey, stay on your side!
Why? Why am I the only
one who didn't get any?
Because you were asleep.
Um, turn off this "data roaming" thing...
Wake her up.
Kimari-san!
I can't believe you slept through all that.
We're here?
Wow! So much English!
Of course there is.
Which way do we go?
We're taking the subway,
so we'll follow the MRT signs.
What do you mean, you forgot
to change your money?
And to change all your money...
we're leaving in two days, you know.
You need to tell me this stuff in advance!
It's hot...
It's summer!
Well, we're right by the equator, after all.
Last time I came, I could
have just died right then.
Where's the merlion? The merlion!
It's not here, clearly.
What a strange building...
Shirase-san!
Discount please!
Please!
We can shop later!
Darn it. It took us forever
just to get to the hotel...
Did it?
Because you bought all that stuff!
We only have one day before we have
to get on a plane to Fremantle.
We need to be efficient...
A double bed!
One, two!
First comes rock! Rock-paper-scissors!
Yes!
What's going on?
We're betting on who has to
sleep next to you, Kimari.
Kimari-san, why don't you
just start out on the floor?
You'll probably fall
sooner or later anyway...
Why?
Because that's what you did during training!
So cold...
So warm...
I don't remember at all.
That's why it's a problem!
Hey, let's put our valuables
in here before we head out!
Japanese yen, plane ticket, and...
Huh?
What's wrong?
N-Nothing!
We'll get ready in our rooms and
meet in the lobby in 30 minutes.
I've seen that! It's a pool, right?
Yes, it is!
What's that?
There it is!
It's so...
It's not as disappointing as I expected.
Yeah! I'd heard it was more disappointing!
Were you hoping for disappointment?
Line up.
We gotta pose! We gotta pose!
Then...
What, exactly, is this?
Is this really oolong tea?
That's what it says.
Miso ramen?
I told you, they won't have any.
But it's ramen!
Because of the miso.
It's so...
There must be some mistake...
Stuffed to bursting.
Shirase-san, your mouth's hanging open.
Look what I bought!
Durian ice cream!
How do you even have room?
It's dessert!
Join me, Hinata-chan!
You want me to eat that?
Oh? Shirase-chan, then!
What?
Huh?
I warned you...
Hey, Yuzu?
Yes?
You took out your passport when
we went through customs, right?
Well... yes.
You still have yours, right?
Of course. It's right here.
Of course it is.
Wow, cool!
Where's the pool?
It's over there, but you can't
go in unless you're a guest.
What? Really?
It's just an ordinary pool.
Though it does have a nice view...
No way! You've been in it?
Once, for a shoot...
Hey, w-was it a sexy bikini pin-up?!
Are you making fun of me?
Was it?!
No!
It's a bit like the crossroads
of the sea, isn't it?
Is it?
Then people leave here to
go all over the world, huh?
Probably.
It's kind of amazing, isn't it?
What is?
In two days, we're leaving here.
But this view will remain the same, right?
Of course it will.
We'll go to Antarctica,
and come back to Japan,
but boats will still come here every day,
and the city will be full of people...
Going to school, working their jobs,
hanging out with their friends...
They'll all keep living their lives...
It's the same in Japan.
School's still being held.
They're probably having
dinner right about now.
In places we've never seen,
locations we've never been...
So many people are living
so many kinds of lives.
Every day, without stopping.
That's amazing!
Even though it's common sense.
But I know what you're getting at.
Hinata-san?
What?
You're hiding something, aren't you?
You can't find it anywhere?
Well... I'm sure it'll turn up.
It's so important, after all.
But then it would have come up
after all this searching, right?
That's true...
Without a passport, not only
can you not leave the country,
you can't go back to Japan, either.
Really?
Then, if it doesn't turn up...
Oh! Long ago, I did live in Japan!
Oh, the good old days!
...is how it'll be.
Why would I still work in a
convenience store over here?
Our flight's in two days!
Don't worry, don't worry!
We'll work it out somehow. Somehow!
How?
Somehow!
I mean, there're lots of options...
What options?
Options... like...
Right back atcha!
Huh?
Anyway, let's look it up.
If you lose your passport,
you can get a new one printed at the embassy.
The shortest time is... half a day.
Then if we go tomorrow,
we'll make it in time!
But the embassy takes
Sundays and holidays off.
And tomorrow is...
Sunday.
What the heck?
We convenience store clerks
work 24 hours a day,
365 days a year, without rest!
The government is stupid!
We'll just have to wait for a
plane two or three days later.
We'll arrive later, but we'll
make it before the boat leaves.
Good idea!
Tomorrow, let's stop by the airport counter.
Are we going... to change our arrival date?
It may be the only option.
Will that be okay?
I mean... the members of the expedition
are awfully strict about rules.
They might say "maybe you shouldn't come."
It'll be okay.
Extenuating circumstances and all that...
Yes!
But...
Why don't we email Kanae-san about it?
You mean, to tell her we'll be late?
It seems like the best thing...
Hey... look, we depart in the
morning in two days, right?
So we have a whole day to go.
Let's talk again tomorrow.
After all, it might still turn up.
That's right!
Please, turn up!
Merlion...
I will murder you.
Either way, you three should
head for Australia in two days.
I think I can work this out on my own.
So if I make it in time, I'll come after you.
And if you don't make it in time?
I just go back to Japan, right?
I can pay my own fare.
I'll tell Kimari and the others myself.
I'm sorry.
It's because I didn't want
to change flights, right?
I'm well aware...
that when things don't go the way
I plan, I tend to get very annoyed.
Hey, you don't have to apologize, Shirase.
I'm the one who lost my passport.
I'm the one who should apologize.
Sorry.
That's not what this is!
Sure it is.
I don't want to be a drag on you guys.
What if you're right, and you don't get
to go to Antarctica because of this?
You'd never recover.
But...
I never said I wasn't going.
You three go first. I'll catch up.
Okay?
Now it's settled!
Let's all go together!
I just have to email Kanae-san
and explain the situation...
I would like to take a shower!
Do you mind?
I'm sorry.
Shirase, I know you were
trying to be considerate.
I just really hate that kind of thing.
I know that's how relationships work, but...
when people try to be considerate of me...
it's disconcerting, I guess...
Like I can't tell how they
really feel anymore...
That's why I couldn't handle high school,
and wanted to be alone as much as possible.
At the end of the day,
when I'm with someone else,
things usually end up like this.
So, no need to worry.
The problem's all on me...
That's not true.
I have problems, too.
Ever since I came to high school, I've had
this "keep away" aura running full blast.
I've never been good around people—
This is what I'm talking about.
I told you, I don't like people
being considerate of me.
I'm not.
Sure, you are.
Shirase, you want to go to Antarctica
more than anyone, right?
Yeah...
You've wanted to go forever, right?
So what?
It's okay to make that your priority!
That's what would make me feel best.
Okay?
Good night.
My alarm clock!
She's here!
Hinata-chan, over here!
Why did you leave without me?
I thought you were sleeping in
because you were under the weather!
Yuzuki-chan's asking if we can
change our tickets right now!
Oh, you don't have to worry about that now.
We decided that you three
would go without me.
We did?
That never happened.
Yes, it did! Later on.
Don't make things up.
Why are you so stubborn?
You're the one being stubborn!
We can't do it.
There's not another opening for
these tickets for another month.
Really?
It's because we bought the cheapest tickets.
See? It can't be done.
So you three should go tomorrow.
I'll get my passport reprinted myself, and—
Shirase-chan?
Change! Late two days! Air!
No.
Shirase-san!
The mwillion yen...
Please change! Four person!
Wait! Why are you being so stubborn?
Shut up!
What's wrong with being stubborn?
That's how I've always lived my life!
I'm stubborn, people make fun of me,
and I've had awful experiences.
But I remain stubborn...
because I'm right!
If you don't want me to be
considerate, I'll say it outright.
I don't want to be the kind of idiot
who doesn't worry about something
just because you say "don't worry about it!"
I don't want the kind of shallow
relationship where I go without you
because you say "just go without me!"
I don't want to be the kind of
coward who gives up without trying,
even though we said we'd all go together!
We're going, the four of us!
All four of us! That's my priority!
What the heck...
What the heck?
What happened?
Dunno...
But it seems like a good thing.
Is this... business class?
You didn't have to go that far!
There weren't any other openings.
I didn't have a choice.
Now I don't want you losing
them, so hand them over.
That's one million yen!
Why are you acting so smug?
I'm not acting smug.
Well... maybe I am.
What the heck?
You hate it when people act
considerate of you, right?
So let's pretend I'm not.
Oh, come on...
Anyway, we're all going together now.
So tomorrow, we'll go to the embassy and...
Huh?
No way...
My shoelace came untied.
Hold this a minute.
It's dangerous to just carry it around.
Hainanese chicken rice!
Shirase-chan, I brought Hainanese
chicken rice and kaya toast!
R-Really?
Something wrong?
N-Nothing!
Oh! Oh! Looks delicious!
Shirase-san.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
Now, let's get eating!
Shirase-chan and Hinata-chan's durian show!
For serious?
W-We really have to do it?
Be glad that's all we're making you do.
Yeah! Don't you realize how worried we were?
But we were able to cancel the tickets...
And we still get to fly out the same day.
It's neatly divided into four, but...
Why don't we play
rock-paper-scissors to decide...
Let's eat!
Who the hell called this the king of fruits?!
But I might like it once I get used to it...
Are you serious?!