Abyssal Shaft — Entrance
Japan Server
Beneath Tearstone Mountains
Dungeon/ No Monsters
No PVP
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
It's finally time for our full raid.
And we're the first adventurers to ever come here.
I love this tension.
I-I'll do my best, too.
Don't worry!
It'll work out.
Okay, guys...
Everyone ready?
We're going to plant our flag in this raid zone!
We let two of them through.
Get them back here!
Go around!
A raid zone on the lowest level
of the Depths of Palm...
Abyssal Shaft — Zone A
Japan Server
Beneath Tearstone Mountains
Dungeon/ Monsters Present
PVP Permitted
Skill Use Permitted
Entry Restrictions/ Yes
Full Raids Supported
Exit Restrictions/ None
The Abyssal Shaft.
This is a familiar raid dungeon
from the original game.
It's an expanded, strengthened version
of a normal dungeon,
with more corridors and rooms,
and more traps and puzzles.
And it's composed of multiple large zones.
You search these zones for your goal,
for treasure, and for the exit.
The Abyssal Shaft
The Abyssal Shaft.
Enemy encounter!
Get ready quick!
Orks' Jelly x 3.
Naotsugu!
Yeah!
Full Raid
A full raid is carried out by twenty-four
members, in four parties of six.
This is our formation for this raid.
Party 1
Party 1 consists of the tanks.
Their job is to attract the enemy from
the front and endure their attacks.
If they go down, so does our whole plan.
Three enemies coming from the southwest exit.
Leave 'em to me!
Anchor Howl!
Wyvern Kick!
Party 2 is the seek-and-destroy team.
They're in charge of handling
any enemies Party 1 missed,
or dealing with unexpected reinforcements.
Party 2
Depending on the situation,
they have to think fast and react fast.
Party 2              Party 1              Party 3
Enemy reinforcements. Requesting support.
Party Chat
Party 1        Party 2        Party 3        Party 4
East exit, in the direction Party 4 is traveling.
Orks' Jelly x 6!
Rapid Shot!
The primary job of Parties 3 and 4 is attacking.
They're comprised of members
whose emphasis is on attack.
But their defense is weak.
When the situation calls for it,
Get back!
Right!
Party 3 becomes our main offensive force,
Party 1                                              Party 3
Party 2
Party 4
while Party 4 guards the surrounding area.
That's our formation for this raid team,
and the basis of our strategy.
Standard monsters in a raid zone
are far more powerful than normal monsters.
Shiroe
Race/ Human
Enchanter, Lv. 92
Log Horizon
After the Apocalypse, the level cap
was raised from 90 to 100.
Even so, if we aren't careful, we'll be wiped out.
Dead adventurers revive at
the raid zone's entrance.
I screwed that up.
Wyvern Kick!
Demikas!
You're too far ahead!
Our healers can't reach you!
I don't care!
This is too easy!
What's this?
Physical Damage Increased
Brigandia
If you defeat a raid monster,
it'll drop special materials.
It's possible to use these to create powerful items.
Here! Heal!
Thanks!
Oh, dear!
Are you doing okay, Naotsugu?
I can handle these slimes anytime!
Hey, you're using me as a shield, aren't you?
I'll heal you, so just keep
sacrificing yourself for me.
And...
That's...
Raid zones have anywhere from five to ten
special monsters called "raid bosses."
It looks just like Vendémiaire of the First Prison.
"The Nine Great Prisons of Heilos"?
I remember that.
Vendémiaire of the First Prison, Lv. 91
Rank/ Raid
It's the raid boss from that dungeon, right?
Data gets reused all the time.
Everyone, it's coming!
Split up and get ready!
Party 1, get in front of its right leg.
Party 2, flank its left leg.
Party 3, take the left rear.
Party 4, take the right rear.
Anchor Howl!
All right!
We'll start by knocking its HP down the usual way!
Roger.
Offensive classes are given attack
boosts and extra damage buffs,
and the rear forces use ranged
attacks from a safe location.
Warrior tanks are given
heavy healing, plus defense boosts
and reduced-damage buffs.
And their most important task is controlling aggro.
In other words, keeping the enemy's attention.
What's wrong?
Look over here, ostrich monster!
What?
It's going to fly?
No, it's some other motion.
Shiroe!
An area-of-effect attack that ignores aggro?
Shiroe, damage report.
Five rooted. Four petrified.
One instant kill.
We need healers.
Get them a revive!
You're kidding me...
He didn't have that skill during Heilos!
Hurry up with those debuffs!
Hey, Demikas!
I'm not waiting for your slow healers!
Tiger Echo Fist!
Cross Slash!
Vendémiaire of the First Prison, Lv. 91
Rank/ Raid
Hey, look.
We finally chipped off ten percent, huh?
That knocked off a few of us!
One's on the platform below.
Two have vanished from the zone!
The damned thing's moving up.
Follow it.
Right!
Be careful!
He has a fire knockback, right?
A raid boss uses more powerful
attacks each time its HP drops.
Its timing and attributes are
different than the last time!
It's gotten a lot nastier...
To deal with it, you need different
tactics than for normal battles.
Naotsugu! Tetra!
Strong party members alone
aren't enough to win.
Dinkuron's petrified!
That's bad...
All our tanks are down.
Any healers left?
No! They're lost!
William, we need to...
I guess we'll have to.
Retreat!
Everyone, fall back!
And so, through repeated defeats and retreats,
you discover the enemy's abilities
and break through them.
We continued to fight Vendémiaire
of the First Prison again and again.
We were never completely wiped out,
but several times, we came very close.
Damn it...
I screwed up again.
You learn the patterns until they're
instinctive, analyze them,
and try many different ways of winning.
Raids are long fights. Some can
take more than a month.
And...
It's the blink...
After that, it disregards aggro,
and uses that attack that inflicts
negative status effects or insta-kill
on ten people at random.
We'll measure the intervals in the next fight.
Sixty seconds.
It's a sixty-second interval.
Start counting!
One, two, three, four...
Go around!
Debuffs! Now!
Five... Six...
Hurry and get into positions!
Seven...
Some raid boss attacks have a cool down.
If you can figure them out, avoid them,
and minimize the damage...
Sixty!
William!
Right!
Take this!
There's no flash this time!
Okay!
The attack was canceled!
This is our chance!
Shave down its HP!
Up the DPS!
If you can memorize every one of the
enemy's strengths and weaknesses,
and get the team to work together well,
it's just a matter of time.
If you defeat a raid boss, you can
get a phantasm-level item.
Then, we found the second raid boss,
El Raida of the Fifth Prison.
Though she was a tough opponent,
with aggro resets and guardian beast summons...
After a dozen or so tries, we beat her.
You defeat each raid boss, one by one,
and attempt to clear the dungeon.
That is what a full raid is.
It's been three weeks since we started the raid.
Demikas!
Sheesh...
Die, monsters!
Hey!
I told you to wait for my next taunt!
Demi-Demi's aggro is...
Shut up, blabbermouth.
I'm—
Demi-Demi! Behind you!
Wyvern Kick!
His teamwork is a mess.
We'll just have to back him up.
As we get deeper in,
we've really begun to understand
how hard the dungeon is.
The monsters have leveled up,
and the fights are more difficult.
We don't even know how big the zone is,
let alone how close we are to clearing it.
Here I go! Here I go!
Sorry if you fall in love with me!
Just shut up and do it!
Here I go, then!
What everyone's been asking for...
Aurora Heal!
We're saved.
Concentrate your attacks!
Avoid close-range attacks!
Right!
Ever since we defeated the first two,
we haven't encountered any raid bosses.
And searching the dungeon
is getting us nowhere.
The battle had entered a stalemate.
How much do you think is left?
How many raid bosses?
Abyssal Shaft — Safe Zone
Japan Server
Beneath Tearstone Mountains
Dungeon/ No Monsters
PVP Permitted
Skill Use Permitted
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
Three or four, probably.
This isn't good...
We can't last for ten days.
We're currently facing supply problems.
During repeated battles,
equipment gets damaged.
To keep it in good shape, you need someone
with crafter skills to do maintenance.
William only has a limited
supply of crystal comets.
A high-level crafter had to use
phantasm-level materials to make them.
Supplies, huh?
Who knows how long our food will last?
To attempt a full raid, you need good equipment.
And the only real way to get it is during a raid.
Same with crafting materials.
Other raid guilds will do low-level
raids simply for materials.
Since the Apocalypse, it's been
harder to visit a lot of raid zones.
But we can't go through easy raids just for supplies.
We aren't a weak guild like that.
Our guild master doesn't like
anything done halfway.
Indeed.
Isn't that why we followed him here?
I have some materials I prepared.
How long will they last?
I'd guess twenty days total.
Twenty days?
That isn't much, is it?
Y-Yeah...
You're right.
Yeah.
Seriously?
Log Horizon is a small guild,
with only eight members.
How did he get all those materials?
He's obviously no ordinary guy.
After I left the Round Table and
wandered to a bunch of raid zones,
I ended up in Susukino.
I don't regret my actions.
I don't, but...
We're tired.
Bye.
It was fun, guild master.
What are they planning to do?
Weaklings.
And this time, I came to a place
like this without even asking
what Shiroe was after.
And they believe in me.
I don't know what's right.
Or what I should say to them.
I'm no more than a gamer.
Games are the only thing I've ever
taken seriously in my life.
But...
What do you think, Shiroe?
No Goofing Off!
It's convenient that we can go underground.
But they aren't people we can keep
fooling forever with tricks like that.
Maybe Minami, but not them.
That bastard!
Shiroe...
I can take the cat-head and the guardian.
They fought with their own power.
But he...
He just lurked in the back and issued orders,
and even worse, he...
Which of you is Brigandia's Demi-glace?
Mister, uh... Delicious?
It was an enchanter skill
that gave me that buff.
Physical Damage Increased
Brigandia
He used Keen Edge to buff me,
and Mind Shock to stun the enemy for a moment.
That bastard saved me?
Saved me?!
Maybe he discovered I gave him extra veggies?
I don't think that's it.
What a problem he is...
You said it.
But...
Yeah. If nothing else, he's no coward.
Check out this stew!
Let's eat!
Chomp!
Isn't this great, Naotsugu?
What's wrong?
It seems like Shiro isn't doing so well.
Does it?
He's always busy, and he always looks upset.
But he's actually enjoying
himself, and taking it easy.
But since he's always that way,
he can't tell when he's really suffering.
And is he really suffering now?
Yeah.
Then he needs an idol.
I think he's got one.
Should I show him my panties?
Listen, pan—
A-Akatsuki's curse again!
I don't think he needs that, either.
But if he's suffering that much,
what's he doing in a hole like this?
Why, indeed...
This is just a guess,
but it might be to protect his home.
His home?
Not like an actual building.
By his home, I mean... His guild? His town?
No, the world?
The world?
A human needs a home,
and a place to eat, right?
And companions.
In our old world, that would be family.
In this world, that'd be our guild, right?
And something like that needs a place to belong.
His home's home would be...
Akihabara, in other words.
If the town isn't happy, the many
guilds there can't be happy.
And the people in those guilds
would have to be sad.
Shiro would fight a whole town, or a
whole world, to protect his home.
His home?
Akihabara, huh?
It's about time to talk to Marie...
No, I guess it isn't quite time yet.
No, but I can't...
What's wrong, Naotsugu?
N-Nothing!
Nothing at all!
Absolutely nothing whatsoever!
Is "Christmas" different from "Snowfell"?
Isn't that the People of the Land's winter festival?
That's right.
Do you think Shiroe will make
it back in time for Christmas?
Christmas, huh?
Right about now, the old world must be...
What's wrong, Katsuo?
I-I've never spent Christmas with
anyone except my family.
I... I...
Don't say anymore.
This year, we're all together.
Santa Claus?
During Snowfell, people exchange presents.
Christmas is when Santa hands out presents.
Yeah.
He rides a reindeer.
No, he rides a sleigh, actually.
Presents, huh?
I wonder what he'll give us.
I want the Teachings.
If there were a scroll of the Teachings,
I would definitely want it.
What's that about the Teachings?
Akatsuki?
When did you get here?
That's our mysterious ninja!
Welcome back, Akatsuki!
Y-Yeah.
Thanks for the hard work.
How about some tea and snacks?
Thank you.
Hey, what are the Teachings?
You don't know?
The whole town's been talking about it.
I've heard of them, too.
Basically, it's a new rank for skills.
The same skill can be more or less powerful,
depending on who's using it, yes?
Because their rank is different, right?
Correct. The same skill can have four ranks—
Fatal Flash/Assassinate
Adept
Basic
Basic, Adept, Hidden, and Secret—
Secret
Hidden
with each more powerful than the last.
For "Adept," you need a scroll made by
an adventurer in the same job class.
For "Hidden," you need a scroll made
with rare materials, right?
Both can be purchased, though at a high price.
But "Secret" requires one to clear a special quest.
You have to participate in a raid.
A raid...
And the "Teachings" are a level above that.
But isn't it just a rumor?
It seems very few people have
actually acquired or seen one.
Shiroe said they're real.
Shiroe did?
Yeah, he says they exist.
We'd also like to earn them, right?
A special rank for skills, one that
didn't exist when this was a game...
The Teachings.
Come on in!
How about it?
Let's Eat Bird!
6 Days Until Christmas!
Bird Is Yummy
Six days until Christmas!
It's almost Christmas!
What frivolous, weak fools...
We are not your dogs.
Don't get cocky, lowly adventurers.
"I want to become strong."
In Akihabara, Akatsuki is uncertain
and alone without Shiroe.
Why did Shiroe leave her?
Why is she weak?
And Lenessia has given up, as well.
She believes adventurers and People of the
Land cannot understand each other.
Shattered Wings
Next time: Shattered Wings.
Rise up once more.