Abe no Seimei.
An onmyoji from the Heian era.
He was skilled in both
astronomy and astrology,
using many different types of familiars.
He was the one who gave
Kohaku his name, supposedly.
So, our research indicates
that it's a safe assumption that the Miyako
family is descended from Abe no Seimei.
I saw that coming.
#8 "Old Coyote and the Garden of Falling Stars"
We also believe that the genealogy chart
the Miyako family possesses is accurate.
September 12th
Nocturnal Community Relations Section
Kamata Sachiko
Administrative Scrivener
But then, where did the
name "Miyako" come from?
To keep people from finding out, right?
That happens a lot in this business.
You're absolutely sure about this?
Don't worry.
Coincidentally, I happened to meet
someone who's a direct descendant.
They happened to invite me to their library,
where they happened to leave
the relevant documents on a desk,
and I happened to get a chance to see them.
You're terrifying.
Which means...
Your knack for languages hasn't changed a bit,
Abe no Seimei.
What he said was...
True, probably.
You may happen to have inherited an
especially strong version of Seimei's power.
Do you think so?
Kamata-san, this is my sister's paperwork.
Thanks!
Your sister's paperwork?
Yeah.
The way she has to return
to society is a bit unusual.
We decide if we use official channels,
and get a family court to retract
the missing persons' report,
or do something else.
Sakaki-kun's sister isn't the first person
to go missing thanks to an Another.
So the question is whether she stays
her own age, but looks like she's 17,
or becomes a different person who's 17.
And for things like that, you need
people like us who can help you.
Both options have their
upsides and downsides.
So think carefully on it.
Got it.
September 13th
That looks great on you, Shiori-san.
Do you think?
Right?
Yeah. It looks great.
Okay, I guess I'll get this.
Okay!
Sorry to drag you out
here on your day off.
It's fine.
Honestly, I'm glad Izumi-chan was able to help.
Me and my sister have no idea
what teenage girls wear these days.
You look happy, Sakaki-san.
I sure am.
When I was a kid, I caused my
sister a lot of trouble.
And you...
You and Theo helped me out a lot.
Sakaki-san?
And thanks to you, I finally have her back.
I don't know what I do from now on.
But for now, I'm just happy to
be able to do something for her.
Next we'll need to get some
winter clothes for her.
I hope you can come then, too.
Thanks for coming today, Izumi.
It's fine! You bought
me a bunch of stuff, too.
How's your arm?
It's fine now.
What about you? Are you okay?
Is what you're doing dangerous?
Izumi...
I know you can't tell me all about your job.
But...
Are you getting involved
in things like that a lot?
I'm a little worried.
Don't worry.
I have co-workers I can trust.
I'll be fine.
Yeah, they seem good.
Right?
Arata, what's wrong?
She's worried, huh?
I guess that's natural...
What's got you down in the dumps?
Whose fault do you think it is?!
Whose?
I haven't forgotten that
you put Izumi in danger!
It was for a friend.
Will you do anything for a friend?
Well, yeah, because they're a friend.
Kohaku?
Yes...
A friend?
Could we see them today?
Let's go.
Go where?
Just come on!
H-Hey!
September 13th
Bunkyo Ward, Koraku
You're not taking me someplace weird, are you?
I haven't been on a walk with Arata in forever.
You're nice to cats, aren't you?
Since you invited me.
Bastet's scary when she gets mad.
Bastet?
An important cat!
She gets mad really easy,
but she's a good musician.
Wow, it feels so alive!
Kohaku?
I love this place.
The stage is big! The music's loud!
And everybody's so excited!
You've been here before?
Yeah, I come by here a lot!
You pay for tickets, right—
No point in saying that
to an Another, is there?
You're still here?
I keep telling you not to live here.
It's a mid-autumn harvest moon tonight, right?
I was thinking of harvesting a mandragora.
Don't let the general affairs
department find you.
If they find you using the office on
a day we're closed, they'll get mad again.
What about you?
Bunkyo Ward got in touch with me.
Bunkyo Ward?
Yeah. It's a day off and
they're still mad at me.
I'm too old for this.
And why'd they get mad?
Well, you see...
There's that Another following
Miyako-kun around, right?
Huehuecóyotl, right?
The one Arata calls Kohaku?
Yeah.
And supposedly, he's wandering
around Bunkyo Ward.
He's got the local Anothers
in an uproar, they say.
Of course he does!
He's an Aztec god!
He's on a whole other
level than most Anothers.
Yeah...
And supposedly, Miyako-kun's with him.
He seems to just be going for a walk, though.
What's that idiot thinking?
Stop him somehow!
Anyone would be surprised if the god of
disaster just showed up at your doorstep!
Sheesh!
Let's let it play out for a while more.
It's not right to lecture
a young man on his day off.
Yes. This is Senda with the Shinjuku
Nocturnal Community Relations Division.
Oh, good talking to you the other day.
September 13th
Taito Ward, Ueno
Huehuecóyotl is in Taito Ward?
Yes. Yes.
Jeez, those guys...
Join in, Arata! It's fun!
No! Come down from there!
September 13th
Taito Ward, Zoo
Taito Ward, Asakusa
September 13th
Sumida Ward, Oshiage
Arata... I'm hungry.
It got really dark.
How far are we going?
It's to the east...
But... how far?
Things are so different now, I can't tell.
If we go up there, we might be able to see!
Up there?
Come with me, Arata!
Come with you where?
Just come on!
A-Again?!
Don't worry about it. Come on!
Just come with me!
Arata, look!
So you've finally come this far, foreign god?!
The land past this point belongs to my master.
You will not be allowed to proceed!
Proceed? He just dragged us with him.
No excuses! Begone, fatty cat!
F-Fatty?!
Who are you calling fat?!
Sure, maybe I haven't been
exercising much lately,
and Arata's place is comfy,
and so is his work,
and the food is good.
But...
I won't let you call me fat!
You want to fight? Very well.
I feel like I've seen this before.
Yeah, you see it a lot in the mornings.
No!
I'm not a normal crow!
I am Yatagarasu! The famous
Abe no Seimei had me guide him
through the land of Musashino!
Look at these beautiful inky-black wings!
Seimei-sama gave me a special name
because he loved their beautiful color!
Now clean out your ears and listen carefully!
My name, given to me in honor
of my nobility and dignity is...
Kuro.
Sound about right.
Yeah. Pretty standard.
That name was a gift from Seimei-sama!
Wait, you understand me, human?
Yeah, I do.
S-S-Seimei-sama?!
I'm so sorry!
My eyesight's bad at night, and
I had no idea that you'd returned.
If I'd known, I would've...
I'm not Seimei. I'm Arata.
Miyako Arata.
Seimei and I are that similar?
U-Uh, my bird eyes can barely see.
My cat eyes can see fine!
A crow who was a friend of Seimei's, huh?
Perfect.
Take us to Seimei's garden.
Seimei's garden?
Yes... Yes. Sounds great. Thanks.
Did you write down what
they said on the phone?
Yeah, it's fine.
He's so weird.
He has sympathy for a devil,
sides with Anothers,
takes gods of disaster for walks...
Sympathy for a devil, huh?
The disappearances were actually kidnappings
committed by the devil named Azazel.
So now the case of the missing
high school girls is solved, right?
I hope so.
Sorry for making you deal with such
a big case while I was gone.
It's fine.
I'm glad your sister's back, though.
It's because you recruited me
to Nocturnal Relations.
You, too.
Miyako-kun, thanks to your Ears of Sand...
What's wrong?
I couldn't bear to listen...
The girl's maddened screams.
Azazel's disappointed sobs.
I can't get them out of my head.
I... I feel so bad for Azazel.
Even though he kidnapped your friend?
If you saw... If you saw that...
anybody would feel sympathy.
Ears of Sand, huh?
I thought they were a double-edged
sword, and I was right.
Understanding them means he can
sympathize with them easily.
I hope he doesn't end up dead someday.
We'll take a right up ahead.
You're excited, crow.
Shut up, fatty cat. You need to leave.
I've waited for Seimei-sama for so long...
You have no idea how happy
I am to guide him once more!
Well, I protected the treasure
of Arata's ancestors for years!
Seimei's here?
That's right.
It's been 1,020 years!
Huh? Twenty-one?
It doesn't matter.
Is this where you wanted to take me?
Hey, what were you doing?
In the long time since Seimei died...
Where were you?
What were you...
We're here.
This is Seimei-sama's garden.
Seimei's garden?
It's beautiful!
I didn't exist.
You asked where I was when you—
when Seimei—went away.
I didn't exist.
Kohaku...
It was the name you gave me,
a name that only you knew.
Without someone to call me that
name, Kohaku did not exist.
Until you called me by that name again...
If... If you were to give me a name, Arata,
what would you call me?
A name you gave me,
a name that only you knew...
A name I gave you?
The thing is...
You'd still be Kohaku, I think.
The deep yellow in your eyes...
It's like "kohaku," amber.
Yeah. That's right!
Okay, I'm going home!
Wait, Kohaku!
Wait! Hey!
He's gone.
He left me here?
What will you do, Arata?
Let's go home, too.
Look at the time.
It's past midnight.
Um, the closest station is...
The closest station is Aoto Station.
On weekends, the last train is at 11:57.
I can tell you're a guide!
Guiding Seimei-sama is my job!
The last train left!
How much would a taxi to Kagurazaka be?
About 6,000 yen including late night fees.
I can tell you're a guide!
Guiding Seimei-sama is my job!
Six thousand yen...
Storage #1
September 14th
Nocturnal Community Relations Section
Good morning.
Morning.
Six thousand yen...
What's that?
Reports.
Reports?
The rokurokubi at Yushima
in Bunkyo Ward went missing?
Damage caused by the kappas at Shinobazu Lake.
Tanuki rummaging through
trash bags at Ueno Park.
In Katsushika Ward, okurijochin were
lighting up the streetlamps at night.
All these are because you took
Huehuecóyotl around the city.
The Anothers get spooked when you
take the god of disaster around with you.
The phone was ringing the whole night.
Okay, Miyako-kun. Take care of those today.
I'm going to bed.
Huh? U-Um...
I was dragged all around the city,
Good morning!
paid 6,000 yen out of pocket,
and now have to write reports.
What's wrong, Miyako?
It's all the fault
of the god of disaster!
What?
#9 "The Dream Demon of
the Haunted Apartment Block"