I've had this image in my
head since I was a child.
An image of a landscape
you could find anywhere.
A scene from a dream that
I have all the time.
But I've never been there.
I've been told it's because I've
undergone In-Grove's Anti-Feminus.
But it didn't really matter why.
I just wanted to search for something.
That's why I went on this trip.
Huh? An emergency?
I'm hitting debris? Why?
There aren't any cleaners this far out...
Please...
Rinon!
Take control of the ship!
Make a short jump as soon
as the ship is stable!
Please!
Take me to that place!
Just... a little farther...
There's a life-sign in the crash zone?
I'd likely...
...been searching for that place.
Nanami-san!
Kanna-chan?
Oh, man. I had this weird dream.
This naked girl was holding Kai-kun
while they were surrounded by light.
The girl was really adorable.
No, she was very beautiful.
Yeah, she looked exactly like
that girl sitting over...
...there?
Na—
Nanami-san!
Could you explain exactly what's going on?
Just let me say this:
Don't get the wrong idea.
What idea would that be?
What you're thinking right now.
Anyway, she's—
Ichika Takatsuki-senpai.
She transferred into the third year
class at our school today.
That's right...
So your name's Ichika Takatsuki-san?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kai-kun's older sister, Nanami.
Thank you for having me in your home.
Indeed...
So? Why is she at your house, Kai-kun,
when you've only just met today?
I, uh...
W-Well...
Th-There was a malfunction
in the quan linkage,
and my altalite was seriously damaged,
so I couldn't go anywhere,
and the damage to the
incrobe was extensive...
That's all too hard for
Onee-chan to understand...
Basically, she has nowhere to
live due to some problems,
and it seems she has no money, either.
I just happened to run into her
on the way home from school,
and she told me the story.
So I told her she could
stay here for a night...
I mean, you couldn't just walk
away after hearing that.
You can't have a girl camping
out somewhere by herself.
So that's what happened.
Question.
Why were you two
embracing by the front door?
We weren't!
That was...
We were?!
Ka-Kaito-kun's altalite...
I-I mean, he wasn't feeling well,
so I was just taking care of him!
Oh, that's right...
I started to feel sick and
lost consciousness...
Kai-kun, are you sick?
Huh?
I'm not sure, but I'm fine now.
Taking care of him...
That's what you were doing?
Holding him close to you
so he gets better...
That's "taking care of him," all right.
Did you think he'd get better
if you embraced him?
That's what we do on my planet!
Your planet?
I-I mean, where I come from.
Where are you from, Takatsuki-san?
Ple—
No, I mean...
North of here.
Like, Hokkaido?
No, farther away than that.
Are you studying abroad?
Y-Yeah, something like that.
Wow, so you came from so far
away to study abroad by yourself!
That's impressive!
Your Japanese is really good, too!
Th-Thanks...
I see.
Well, I understand what's going on now.
That's good.
But if something happened,
why not contact your parents back home?
Well, I...
Senpai?
Did something happen to your...?
I think I know how you feel!
Are you an esper?!
Takatsuki-san...
No, Ichika-chan.
I'm sorry we brought up such sad memories.
Kai-kun and I lost our parents, too,
so I know...
I really know how you feel!
Wai— Nanami-san?!
A-Anyway, so that's what's going on.
So there shouldn't be a problem with
letting her stay here a night, right?
A night?
How about just letting her live here?
Nanami-san?!
I mean, I'll be leaving for a pretty
long business trip tomorrow.
Someone'll need to take care of Kai-kun.
Since she's a senpai from his school,
I won't have to worry.
And since she's a girl, she'll be
able to cook and do the laundry.
I-I'll do my best!
Sounds great.
Nanami-san, you're being too lax!
You can't let a girl and guy live
under the same roof like this!
People have to help each other
out when they're on hard times.
And Kai-kun is nice,
so he wouldn't try anything funny...
...just because he's living
with a really cute girl.
He wouldn't, would he?
O-Of course not.
You paused!
You thought about it for a second!
No, I didn't!
Your eyes are lying!
What eyes?!
Your eyes right now!
Okay, so it's settled.
I'm not at all worthy of such favor,
but I thank you, Onee-san.
Call me Onee-chan.
Okay, Onee-chan-san!
They sound like they're
going to get married...
I'm going to walk Tanigawa home.
You seem like you're mad.
I'm not.
So, Tanigawa...
Senpai, she's...
You're just helping her out, right?
She was in a bad spot and you
just helped her out, right?
Yeah, that's it.
That's all there was to it.
Then I'll trust you.
Huh...
You don't have to walk me any farther.
See you tomorrow!
Tomorrow, huh?
Really?
So that pretty girl is going to
stay at Kirishima-kun's house?
How did that happen, Kanna?
I don't really know.
It just kind of kept building up to that.
But Kirishima-kun lives
there with his sister.
His sister is leaving tomorrow
on a long business trip.
What? Seriously?
That happened pretty fast.
What should we do, Tetsuro-kun?
I've got it.
Got what?
I know where we're going
tomorrow for our meeting.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Dinner's ready.
Is something wrong?
N-No, it's nothing.
U-Uh...
Where's my sister?
She said she still had to do some packing.
She ate dinner already and is in her room.
Oh, I see.
Pasta and miso soup?
Pretty normal, right?
Besides the pairing.
Did I get something wrong?
No, it's fine.
I'll have some.
How is it?
A-Are you okay?!
Is it bad?
No, it's not that...
It tastes kind of sour...
Is this a cold noodle dish?
Yeah...
It was hot today, so I thought
something cold would be good.
I just wasn't expecting the
flavor, so I was surprised.
Yeah, this cold pasta will be fine.
Could I ask you a question?
What is it?
Why did you come to study abroad here?
Hm...
There's a place I wanted to visit.
Where's that?
Is it around here?
I could take you there, if you'd like.
Well, I don't know where it is...
You don't know...
There's a tree there, and a lake.
It doesn't really have anything
special to identify it.
That'd make it hard to find.
Yeah.
But I'd still like to go there.
That was one hectic day.
And I have to have a meeting
with everyone tomorrow...
How am I going to explain this to them?
Actually...
What is this?
It's spreading?
Oh, yeah, not too long ago, I...
Did you think he'd get better
if you embraced him?
Embraced...
Oh, my.
I need to give you medical
attention right away.
Pain, pain, go away.
Kiss.
Yeah, right.
That'd never happen.
This isn't working.
It doesn't look like I can repair it.
Rinon, how is the quan linkage looking?
It's bugging out pretty badly.
But I don't regret what's happened.
I was able to make it to this planet.
Maybe I was too tired
from everything going on,
but as soon as I hit my bed,
I fell right asleep.
I didn't even have any dreams.
Episode 2
Together with Senpai...
Kaito-kun.
Wake up, Kaito-kun.
Onee-chan-san said she's
going to leave soon.
I didn't know it was so late...
Wh-What's wrong?
You're wearing...
Oh, I borrowed it from Onee-chan-san.
Sleepwear from this area
is a little embarrassing.
I-It really is!
Kai-kun!
Your sister is leaving!
If you don't say goodbye, I'm going to cry!
I'll be right down!
Kaito-kun, make sure you don't get sick.
Try not to use too much
out of your living expenses.
Make sure you study,
get along with your friends,
and don't stay up too late.
I'm getting sad, so goodbye and take care.
Ichika-chan, take care of Kai-kun for me...
It's time to go.
She finally left.
Kaito-kun.
You lonely?
A little, I guess.
Oh, yeah, Senpai.
There's a place I want to
stop by before we head back.
A place you want to stop by?
Nee-san asked me to.
Onee-chan-san did?
Yeah, you need to get
some everyday clothes.
She's...
...a little strange sometimes,
But...
She's cute.
Total due
This should be enough.
Thank you.
That was a lot of fun.
Shopping really is a girl's greatest pleasure.
I have to tell Onee-chan-san
thank you, too.
You can wait until she calls us.
I will.
Huh? It's open.
Why?
Huh?
Oh, you're late.
I almost couldn't wait any longer.
Yo.
Welcome back.
Wh-Why?
We said yesterday we were going...
...to have a kick-off meeting
for the movie, right?
Sorry, but we all decided on your
house as the place to do it.
That's not the problem!
Oh?
Close enough to go shopping
together already, huh?
Th-That's not it...
How did you get in the house, anyway?
You should use a better lock.
Don't just unlock it without asking.
That's really illegal!
But I have to do my due diligence.
On where my good friend is staying.
How did you know that?
Tanigawa!
Now that we're all here,
we can begin our first
meeting regarding Director...
...Kaito Kirishima's work that we
volunteers will put together.
It will begin now.
Hey, Director.
Do you have to call me that?
Actually, why is she in charge?
Why not? She's an upperclassman, anyway.
So what type of movie are we making?
We'll be using this script
I wrote for the film.
By the way, the idea was
developed over twenty years.
The writing took five.
Hey!
What's the story like?
In the 23rd century, mobile weapons
are used across the world.
It'll be a huge flick that's far beyond what Hollywood could pull off.
That's not happening.
We'll do it all in CG, so it'll be okay.
We might not need a camera, then.
Shouldn't we do something
we know we can do?
How about a story related to school?
I'm sure the school will
let us film there, too.
Well, that's one way to play it safe.
What would we do for the story?
How about this?
Zombies appear at the
school out of nowhere,
and the main characters,
the only people left alive—
That's not happening.
Do you have any requests, Ichika-senpai?
Kirishima-kun, you're quite the brave one.
Me?
You're the lead, so you should
tell us what you'd like to do.
Huh? Wa-Wai—
Hm... It doesn't have anything
to do with the story,
but I'd like to see some pretty scenery.
I just got here, so I'd like to go...
...all over the place and
see different things.
There's a place I wanted to visit.
Oh, s-sorry for being so abstract.
It sounds good to me.
Let's go around to different places.
It's almost summer break anyway.
Sounds good.
We can film the movie and
have fun at the same time.
I think we'd end up just messing around.
That wouldn't be so bad.
It's not like we have to put
together a movie no matter what.
Let's go all over the place.
Huh?
You might find that place you want to go.
Thank you, Kaito-kun.
We'll think about the content of the movie.
But let's all toast for
the success of the film.
R-Right...
Well then, cheers.
Cheers!
What is this, anyway?
It tastes pretty strange.
But it has a bit of
sweetness that's kind of good.
Do you have any more?
Yes, I brought a lot with me,
so have as much as you'd like.
Revolution! And I'm out this round!
Smirk.
Hey, Remon-senpai.
What's this drink called?
Dynamite Drink.
I see!
That works!
Dynamite!
Senpai, are you okay?
I kinda feel hot...
Hot?
Yeah, my body feels warm.
Your body...
Yes.
I-I see...
Th-That sounds like a problem.
Hey!
What are you guys doing
out there by yourselves?!
Come here!
What is it, Tanigawa?
You think I'm disturbing you two, don't you?
Don't you?!
That's not true.
What about you, Senpai?
I wasn't thinking that.
You're going to be staying here, right?
Yeah...
You guys are going to live together.
Yeah, I guess so.
It's almost summer break.
You two will be alone together all day...
Alone!
Well...
Ichika-senpai!
Y-Yes!
I'll get straight to the point!
How do you feel about Kaito-kun?
I-I...
Well, Kaito-kun helped me when
I was in a time of need...
Not that!
I'm asking what you think of him!
I...
Wh-Why?
What is that?
A biological entity...
I mean...
It's my p-pet.
Its name is Rinon.
Is there even an animal like that?
It's really weird.
But it's kinda cute.
It's dancing, too!
Now that things are really getting started,
we'll play my special version
of the "King" game.
That sounds good!
King game?
You'll understand when we play.
Who's the king?
King
It's me.
Now, to start off easy,
number three, flick number one in
the forehead, as hard as you can.
Ow!
Number four, hit number one.
Stupid Kai-kun!
Why is this all happening to me?
Number five, kiss number four.
What the hell is with this drawing?
Kiss.
Number three, take off your pants.
Okay!
Why are you taking off your boxers, too?!
Pervert!
Number four, make a pose
like a female panther.
And number two...
Me?
You and number one...
...must have sex.
Not happening!
That was wonderful, everyone.
This movie is shaping up very well.
Kaito-kun.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I guess so.
How about you?
I'm fine now.
I see.
I wonder what that drink was.
My head hurts all of a sudden...
Huh? Kaito-kun!
S-Sorry, Senpai.
Close your eyes for a second.
Rinon!
How is it now?
Huh?
It doesn't hurt.
I'm glad.
Stupid...
Stupid Kai-kun.
I'm the stupid one.
Senpai...
Senpai, I...
I...
You can't.
You can't say it.
Please.
Don't say it.
Episode 3
Senpai says...
Kanna, Kirishima-kun's out today.
This is bad! We have to go visit him!
It's our top priority!
That was the one thing you
shouldn't have said.