Just now joining us, Julius?
Thanks for gracing us with your presence.
Please... You will ruin my reputation.
But I am not the man called "Julius."
Let's see...
Perhaps I shall go by "Juli."
Even if it is temporary,
a man with a knight's status
must never lower himself
to the rank of mercenary.
The man you see here is not
Julius Euclius, the knight,
but a simple wanderer called Juli.
A proper household's code of
chivalry is a real pain, huh?
Bull...
It seems you're doing better than I expected.
How are you feeling?
Well, there were only some scratches!
A little spit fixed them right up!
What about you?
Been busy writing apologies
for fighting so seriously with an amateur?
I didn't mean that...
I was talking about the damage to your
honor by the mabeast subjugation.
But I'm glad your wounds from
before seem to have healed.
Thanks to all of you, we succeeded
in defeating the White Whale.
But it's not over yet.
I have to settle a score with the Witch's
Cult guys that picked a fight with me.
Once that's done,
the White Whale subjugation will be complete.
The Witch's Cult is next?!
Can we trust allegations that the White Whale
and the Witch's Cult are connected?
We only came as reinforcements for
the White Whale's subjugation—
What was that for?
If you can't believe him,
then you just need to believe me!
I'd prefer it if you believed me, though.
I don't like to recall it,
but I've run up against
the Witch's Cult before.
I learned it then.
Didn't you look into that, Old Man Wil?
I would not term it definitive evidence,
but the distributions of Whale
appearances and Cult activities
coincided in several respects.
That makes it doubly credible!
On that note,
we're going to head
for the Mathers domain.
The Witch's Cult is hiding in the forest there.
The way we defeat them
is as simple as it gets.
Raid them before they can
read our movements,
and crush them!
Is there a way to protect the villagers?
I asked Anastasia-san and Russell-san
to talk to the merchants along the highway.
Under the condition that Margrave Mathers
buys their cargo at asking prices,
they'll ask the merchants
to evacuate the Arlam
villagers and Roswaal mansion residents.
And a messenger from Crusch-san's household
is headed for the mansion
with a handwritten letter.
There will be chaos
if we don't notify Emilia and the rest
about the alliance and such.
Sounds like we're all ready.
Yeah!
We have never enjoyed such an advantage
in a battle with the Witch's Cult.
Yeah.
With Julius and his crew, we don't have
to worry about being outnumbered.
I would like to offer one correction.
My name is Juli.
Please take care to use it.
That'll just be a hassle in casual settings!
The battle with the White Whale
was so tough, I thought I'd die.
Some of us did die.
Some others vanished, never to return.
Let's win the war without losing anyone here.
Let's all return home alive!
You really managed to win?
Huh?
The subjugation of the White Whale
was a long-standing wish
of the Imperial Knights.
It seems I owe you my thanks.
You don't have to force it.
For putting an end to a calamity that
all nations ignored for far too long,
I thank you.
I'm...
grateful to you, too.
For coming to back us up.
Even after what happened.
About that, I was...
Oh, damn it! Crap!
I know, okay? I know it now!
It was my fault.
Sorry. I... I apologize.
I apologize, as well.
I cannot take back my words and actions,
but I apologize, from the bottom
of my heart, for belittling you.
I'm sorry, but...
I hate your guts.
I feel bad for what happened,
and I'm grateful you're here.
But I hate your guts.
Seriously, I hate you from
the bottom of my heart!
That is fine.
I have no intention
of befriending you, either.
All right, as I say every time,
let's get this fight started.
Fate, bring it on!
You must be exhausted, Lia.
You should rest a bit.
No.
I don't think I'll be able to fall asleep.
What about you? Aren't you tired?
I'm fine.
The forest barrier is all fixed up, too.
You don't have to worry about anything!
Yeah.
But...
This feels like the time
I found a cockroach in the
corner of a quiet room.
You were drawn to the smell, huh?
Perfect cockroach bait...
Do I really smell that bad?
Thanks for coming to meet me.
Sorry to say it when you just arrived,
but I'll leave you to work the
details out for yourselves.
So don't get in my way.
If they'd stuck around long enough
for me to order them
to gather their stuff and go home,
this would've been easier...
I have been waiting for you, believer in love.
In the Witch's Cult, I am a Sin Archbishop,
representing sloth,
Betelgeuse Romanée-Conti.
I welcome you,
beloved child, blessed with love.
Wonderful!
Hey.
I really appreciate the unexpected welcome.
But I'm not sure I really feel this
"love" you keep bringing up.
It always begins suddenly.
Everyone, on a certain day,
realizes that they are loved.
They feel the love!
The love! The love! The love! The love!
The love! The love! The love!
Um, and what am I supposed to do now?
Ah, the witch's generous love...
You wouldn't happen to be Pride, would you?
Of the six Sin Archbishops,
only Pride's seat remains vacant...
You have
received the Gospel, haven't you?
The Gospel?
My brain
trembles!
Presentation of the Gospel,
proof of love...
Proof! Proof! Proof! Proof!
Huh?
My Gospel has no account of you.
That book is the Gospel?
Then why did you appear here?
Why visit here?
What fortune are you here to deliver?!
Oh! So that's the Gospel!
I see, I see...
I understand, I understand.
You should have just said so.
Aw, darn it! I'm sorry!
What?
My Gospel is, well, you know...
I used it as a coaster, and it got messy.
So I threw it out.
Proof of love!
Authority of Sloth...
Unseen Hand!
What?
It's an "unseen hand," right?
So if I can see it, I can evade it!
You can see my Unseen Hand?!
Okay, I'm just about done buying time!
Prepare to be buried alive!
Suffer, as you regret the things you've done!
How... How could this be?
My fingers, so cruelly, so mercilessly,
so chaotically, so arbitrarily,
so artlessly, so meaninglessly...
My brain... My brain trembles!
Yikes, that guy's kinda scary.
I think all the Witch's Cult
members are like that.
Yes, of course...
Fine... Fine.
I understand. Let's do this.
I'm ready to do this.
The time has come to learn which
of us is worthy of her love!
Her love! Yes, her love!
Sorry to interrupt your fun, but...
—ove?
I have someone else lined up to take you on!
I-It's over... Right?
He's very much dead!
The capital's most powerful
healer guarantees it.
I see...
Wilhelm-san, I'm sorry to ask
such an unreasonable favor.
Was it unreasonable?
Isn't cutting someone down
without warning, from behind,
the worst thing a knight can do?
Chivalry is long dead.
You need not concern yourself with that.
Hmm... Doesn't look like he's
carrying anything useful.
You mini guys are ransacking his corpse
like it's the obvious thing to do...
I'm not mini. I'm Tivey.
I think it's our right to search
out the spoils of battle.
What is this?
I think it's the book that Betelgeuse
called a "Gospel."
Eep! This is a Gospel?!
Oh, no! I touched it!
I can't read it...
Felis, can you read this?
Whoa, nyo way! Don't point that thing at me!
And don't do something as stupid
as trying to read a Gospel!
Is it that dangerous?
The Gospel is the proof that one
belongs to the Witch's Cult.
They're basically their sacred texts.
Sacred texts?
Rumors say one is delivered to anyone
with the potential to join the cult.
And once a person gets it... Imagine that.
They're nyow a devout member
of the Witch's Cult.
How shady can you get?
Well, I guess I'll take this with me.
If I can decipher it,
maybe I can figure out what
the Witch's Cult really is.
Hey, hey, we've killed the enemy here,
so shouldn't we go make sure the
other enemies are dead, too?
You know, as adorable as you look,
you say some pretty disturbing things...
Aw, I'm adorable? You're makin' me blush!
Then the subordinates that Betelgeuse
called "fingers" number ten, in total?
I think one of them is pinned under there.
Ten minus one is nine!
So nine are left!
Then, shall we go?
But they really are dead, right?
They won't come back the second
we look away, right?
Fine... If you're that
worried, we'll make sure.
We crushed two fingers here.
A few of the cultists were skilled,
but they posed no threat.
Driving them off, we made no error.
I'm glad it went well for you guys, too...
Given your demeanor,
evidently, I can assume your
news is good, as well?
Yep, we took out Betelgeuse!
And since this guy is such a worrywart,
we blasted him to bits with one more
"kaboom" after we killed him!
All to bits!
Then, that leaves the simple task of
mopping up the remnants, huh?
We'd better hurry
and take care of 'em before
my lady turns into an old granny...
Oh, that was my best joke, y'know!
We rendezvous soon with the dragon-drawn
carriages you arranged.
Let us eliminate the remaining fingers
and greet our victory together.
Okay, Subaru-kyun, time for the bait.
Put out that smell!
Breathe in...
And out...
And out... And out... And out...
Hey, hang on! Don't be crazy!
So I guess...
Once this is all done,
we'll go back to being friend and foe.
How confident of you to worry
about what is yet to come.
Hey, sue me.
It's going almost too well, so I
may have lowered my guard.
Get down!
What is this?
What's goin' on?!
The Unseen Hand...
Betelgeuse should be dead!
So who's—
Subaru-dono!
Damn it!
Ah!
My brain... trembles...
Who are you?
Wh-Who the hell are you?
Are you Betelgeuse's...
Finger, yes!
Let me go...
I am a finger,
one who reciprocates love.
A faithful, diligent
disciple who will carry out
the Ordeal, following the guidance of love!
A copy?
A replica of... the original Betelgeuse?
If so, this couldn't...
possibly get any worse.
Sniff, sniff.
The love that hangs from you does not
compare to that of a mere follower.
It is equal to that of a Sin Archbishop.
It is exceedingly
displeasing, dissatisfying, disagreeable,
discomforting, disproportionate, discordant!
But that is the proof that you are Pride!
Don't make me keep saying it...
I'm not even close to Pride.
I've never gotten a free book,
even as a membership perk!
My! Are you being stubborn?
Still, soon enough, you will quite readily...
The Gospel...
The guidance of my love!
The Gospel that allows me,
though inexperienced, to return love!
It isn't with me now!
Was it you?
You? You? You? You? You? You? You? You?!
Did you steal it?!
Wha...
A spirit?
A spirit!
Spirit! Spirit! Spirit!
Damn it.
Is that all you can do?
If so...
Be dismayed. Disappointed. Dejected.
Are you two slothful?!
My life is spilling out...
My blood is running dry.
My diligent pulse, my life's support,
is stopping... disappearing.
Ah, my brain... trembl—
The first Sloth we defeated was a double,
and this was the real one?
No,
this may not be a matter of which is real.
You mean that there may be more
than one Sin Archbishop of Sloth?
Either that...
Or all hundred followers,
including the fingers,
are the Sin Archbishop of Sloth.
I dragged you all into this.
If I'd realized it sooner, I could
have avoided this.
I knew what kind of power it was, so I...
Subaru-dono...
I am sure that many thoughts are running
through your mind right now.
And I am certain none are superficial.
But while this may be inelegant
of me, I must say this.
Fight!
Even if you have regrets,
even if you have remorse, you must fight.
If you have made the decision for
yourself to fight, to struggle,
then fight with all you have.
Do not give up for one second,
one moment, or one instant.
Cling greedily to the victory
you have within your sight.
If you can still stand,
if your fingers still move,
if all your teeth have not broken.
Stand and fight.
You must fight.
You're telling me to get stronger?
No.
I am telling you to be strong.
Ready to go?
Yeah, let's go.
Lend me your wisdom and strength!
We're gonna start evacuating
the mansion and village!
Don't waste a single second!
Right now,
the Witch's Cult hasn't noticed yet
that the plain is wide open.
We can get Emilia and the others in carriages,
and get them to safety in plain sight.
With Emilia-sama and the others safe,
we won't have to worry about them.
So we can focus on
subjugating the Witch's Cult.
Fighting isn't easy when you know
you have a weak point!
You're making my ears hurt...
But that's exactly right.
While I'm at it, let me say one more thing.
Subaru-kyun, you should really
make up with Julius soon.
Soon? We already reconciled after our fight.
You didn't see?
That was just for starters, wasn't it?
You still subconsciously harbor resentment.
You can rely on Julius.
But I admit he is a bit unapproachable
and incomprehensible.
Go on, hurry up.
Okay, fine!
Uh...
So, hey, there's something
I wanted to say to you...
A Flash of Sloth