Here I am again.
Really? Are you sure?
Fwap
How many days of food expenses
will we save from this?
This is wonderful! Thank you!
We got extravagant for New Year's,
so she told us to be frugal for a while.
But now we can have delicious food
from tomorrow!
Warm
We were already done eating.
Those are the leftovers, so I hope that's okay.
D-Delicious!
Th-The egg rice is delicious!
Hey, Rei. Can you sleep with Momo tonight?
That's a good idea!
Let's do that! After all, tomorrow's Saturday.
I have to go home tonight.
Why? Let's stay here together!
Why? Why, why, why?
Momo.
I've got a match coming up
that I just can't lose.
So I have to go home and study.
Study? Do you have a test?
Yes. That's right.
It's a test where I show my opponent
and myself how hard I've been trying.
Momo.
Then you have something to tell Rei.
Tell him what?
Um, Rei says he has a test.
Right. So what do you say at a time like this?
You say, "Do your best."
Rei, do your best!
I will.
I'll do my best.
Black River (Part 2)
All right...
...time to go?
After that, I spotted Kiriyama
just once at the Shogi Hall.
He was looking at shogi game records
and making copies of them.
I was going to talk to him, but...
I saw that stern look on his face,
and stopped.
Kiriyama had been gathering the game records
for Shimada 8th-Dan, and Gotou 9th-Dan.
Just those two.
Sheesh. The little punk.
Man, that pisses me off. What a jerk.
He's totally ignoring the possibility
that I could win?
And he expects to crush Mr. Shimada,
then move right on to Gotou?
Who does he think he is?
I don't have it. A vision of me beating Gotou
and then facing off against Mr. Shimada.
But I understand.
That's right.
That's what the problem is.
The vision Kiriyama sees isn't just
a selfish figment of his imagination.
We're professionals.
Whether I accept it or look away,
deep down I measure my own ability
with cruel precision.
Measuring that is what it means
to be a professional.
There are some people who think, "I may win"
and there is a possibility that they will win.
I don't have it.
A vision of me beating Gotou
and then facing off against Mr. Shimada.
And that's how it is.
But going from there, trudging on
and sidling up to victory
is also part of a professional's job.
Gotou often uses the forms of Static Rook
and Bear in the Castle.
In response, I'll use the Windmill.
If Gotou is "heavy" and "stiff"
I'll be "light" and "expansive".
All right, please begin.
Let's have a good game.
This is my second time playing against Gotou.
Last time, to prepare for a drawn-out battle
from Gotou's heavy defensive position,
I also strengthened the defense
around my king,
but the "nimbleness" I always put my faith in
was weakened by the armor it wasn't used to
and the result was a crushing defeat.
Based on that, I've come up
with a number of countermeasures.
This time, I've decided to face him
with what I excel at.
I won't shield my king much,
but I'll move the pieces around quickly,
making countless small wounds,
and stealing his vitality.
Against that...
Gotou will make a firm, measured defense,
and attack me with a single massive strike.
If that strike hits me, it's over.
I can't let my concentration slip one millimeter.
But I'm ready to do this.
A match in which victory and defeat
is decided 100% beforehand
doesn't exist between professionals.
Such unpleasant clouds, like it'll rain.
Actually, on the news
they were saying it'll snow tonight.
No wonder.
I thought it was especially cold out.
Just how much vitality does he have?
I keep wounding him, but he won't crumble.
There are no openings to attack.
I've drawn a lot of blood,
but he hasn't flinched.
Conversely, my moves
aren't getting very far right now.
And then...
...that one strike came.
Sacrificing his Rook for my Silver?
What the hell is he doing?
What is...
...this man seeing?
He's attacking me with tremendous force.
He'll pry me open!
Pitch black water is rushing in.
I can't breathe...
Just like that, I'm getting dragged down...
...to the bottom.
There's nothing I can do.
I lost.
You were light.
But still a little heavy.
After I moved 2-f-Bishop,
you defended with 5-b-Gold from the left.
You should've gone up to 6-c-Gold instead.
The way you did it, the "heaviness" came out.
Lightness is your creed, right?
If so...
...don't hesitate.
That was pathetic.
Not only was it a helpless, complete defeat,
but my delusions were shattered as well.
A full course, huh?
Don't hesitate.
What's the deal with that heavy manliness?
How old is he? 41?
Will I be able to project
that kind of punch in ten years?
I bet he's popular with the ladies.
Now I'm getting pissed off.
All right. For the rest of the night...
Course A. If it goes in, I drink my cares away
at the usual hostess pub.
Course B. If I miss, I go home,
get under the covers, and sob.
Rustle Rustle Rustle
Gasp!
Shiver
Could it be?
Perhaps a Course C?
Shrink
Course C:
Bring a stray cat
home and
take care of it.
Mew...
What should I do?
Okay, already! I get it!
Okay, okay. Stop crying.
We'll start again.
You and me both, from square one.
Black River (Part 2)
Hey.
You look well.
Too bad.
I see.
If we keep going like this,
you and I will go head to head.
Well, I'm looking forward to that.
It should be a little more interesting
than beating you with my bare hands.
That's right.
I want you to pass on a message
to your old man, Kouda.
It's about that stalker woman.
Tell him to get her off my back.
She's really annoying.
You know?
Beyond the Door
He was provoking me.
I know that.
But...
I have to do it.
First, I have to deal with today.
Nothing will start unless I win today.
Kai Shimada, 8th dan. Five years in Rank A.
I've been looking at a lot of his game records,
but it's strange.
I can't find any distinctive features.
Tactics he's good at, his weaknesses...
There's nothing I can pinpoint.
I haven't played against him before.
But, wait...
When I was in grade school,
he was a guest speaker
at a children's shogi tournament I attended.
He was awfully thin and tall,
and I remember he spoke quietly.
I'd had a winning streak,
so I just watched from afar.
He didn't really make an impression on me.
Instead of "playing to win,"
he's someone who "plays not to lose" shogi.
Matches against people like that
are usually drawn-out battles.
It's not my favorite.
But...
I can't get irritated.
That's where he'll eat me alive.
Stay calm.
Gotou recently gave it to me.
I can not lose here.
No matter what.
I went first for this match.
It's a Double Fortress.
It's been standard moves up to now.
All right, time to start the battle.
Here I go.
5-b-Rook?
Does he intend to block everything?
In that case...
He moved his Gold back.
Does he mean to move the Rook around?
Then so will I.
Somehow...
...it's hard for me to move.
At a time like this,
it's a good idea...
to surround the king.
Surround...
Wait a second.
Something's wrong.
I was supposed to be attacking.
And yet...
...somewhere along the way, I started defending?
What is this?
When did the situation get this bad?
I didn't... make any mistakes.
No mistake, and yet...
And yet, what is this?
This...
This intensity?
I can't...
...attack anymore?
Crap!
Gold General
Knight
Geez. You finally look this way.
Shogi Hall
Big Brother!
What did you come here for, kiddo?
You don't have a match today.
Sorry, Big Brother.
How's your fever?
You still have one.
You need to take care.
Your promotion is on the line.
You promised you wouldn't overdo it,
remember? To both your teacher and me.
In exchange, we promised
we wouldn't tell anyone.
Yes. I'll head home and lie down.
Sorry.
Well, me too.
Sorry for getting on your case like that.
I was just surprised to see you here.
So why are you here, kiddo?
Is there something you wanted to tell me?
Yes. Actually, Big Brother...
I want you to...
I want you to split Kiriyama's head in half.
Dang it, kiddo...
I was wondering what you were going to say.
Such a troublesome thing...
Well, then...
Let's continue, shall we?
Beyond the Door
Next Episode Preview
Episode 14
You can't be eating cold food
when you're depressed.
You'll lose half of your hit points.
Is that how it is?
What should I do?
I can't understand it anymore.
Well, let's try advancing it from here.
"March Comes in Like a Lion"!
At long last, my Big Brother appears!
You'll watch our brotherly love, right?
Big Brother!