The Second Plate
Episode 10
You don't look very happy, Eizan-kun.
What are you talking about?
The arena's really pumped.
This year's Autumn Elections
are a major success.
As the organizers, there's
nothing to be unhappy about.
But it looks very different from how
you imagined it to be, doesn't it?
Hmph.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
You're the one who directed Mimasaka Subaru
to target Soma-kun, aren't you?
If he used Takumi-kun,
Soma-kun would no doubt
agree to the Shokugeki.
If he were defeated before such a large crowd
without being able to avenge his friend,
there would be no greater humiliation.
You kept your own hands clean,
and manipulated everything
from behind the scenes.
It's very much your style, Eizan-kun.
But your schemes didn't work.
You used your wits to set up a trap
for him the best you knew how,
but maybe you're the one who
got caught and drowned instead.
What did you just say?!
I'd like you to have seconds, too.
Does no one want more?
It's the end of the line.
With this, we conclude the evaluation—
If it means you'd have seconds,
I'd like you to pour this
over the rice and dig in.
Hmm!
Well, to be more precise,
it wasn't only you.
Everyone at Totsuki felt the same way.
My Pacific saury dish is not yet complete.
That's...
...a white soup?
A New Genius
Let's have seconds.
Yukihira-kun, you're free to
struggle on till the very end,
but isn't this just a remake of the idea
you used in your match against me?!
No, it's not, Alice.
It's—
There, honored judges.
This is my Pacific saury dish:
Porridge-Style Pacific Saury Rice.
Enjoy!
The slightly viscous soup
has soaked into the dish,
and gently melded with the rice.
There he goes!
Bare-chested!
Mild and creamy...
This white soup is soy milk!
That's right!
I gradually added miso and just a touch
of Parmesan cheese to the soy milk,
then slowly simmered it
until the soup became warm!
Soy milk?
You noticed, Alice.
The critical component
of porridge is the broth.
He used soy milk as the broth,
and built this dish on that foundation.
I see.
Broth is essentially umami itself.
Like kelp, soy milk contains
large quantities of glutamic acid.
It is more than qualified to serve
as the base for the porridge's flavor.
Further, umami components
have a synergistic effect.
When two are present,
the resultant umami is far more
than the sum of its parts.
The inosinic acid from Pacific saury
and the glutamic acid from soy milk...
Combining the two makes total sense.
A soy milk porridge...
How interesting.
There are ingredients that have suddenly
become prominent by
adding the soup, as well.
What's mixed into the rice?
Crunchy pickled plums.
What?!
Crunchy pickled plums?
Not common snacks again?!
These plums serve as important accents.
The crunchy mouthfeel is fun,
and it adds vivid visual impact!
For the taste buds, the plums help
cut through the fattiness of the Pacific saury,
and provide a refreshing aftertaste.
The dish makes full use of the acidity's
ability to increase appetite.
The plums were pickled in salt.
They are the perfect choice to
complement the aged Pacific saury!
Another item of note is the
Parmesan cheese in the soup!
This Western ingredient is combined
with Japanese ingredients
such as the salted rice bran Pacific saury,
pickled plums, and miso,
to create a brand new flavor!
It reminds me of when I met my beloved...
This way.
Oh!
An encounter made possible
by two that have developed
in different countries and cultures...
A most unique encounter.
You've got to be kidding.
That's high praise right there.
Who knew that the transfer student would...
Did you see this Totsuki Sports issue?
According to the journalism club,
News Flash
Totsuki Sports
Autumn Election Finals
they can distribute more copies
when they write an article bashing Soma-kun.
Of course they would.
He publicly said that this academy's
just a stepping stone for him.
You can tell from the
audience's reaction, too.
The transfer student is disliked
not just in name, but in actuality.
Is that really true?
I don't think that's the only reason.
He had a very close spice match
with Hayama-kun in the prelims.
Hayama Akira
Yukihira Soma
Kurokiba Ryo
In the main tournament,
he defeated Alice-kun,
a relative of the Devil of Food.
Furthermore, he defeated Mimasaka-kun,
a monster who'd been
undefeated in 99 Shokugekis.
Yet many students don't want
to acknowledge Soma-kun.
Why is that?
You see, I've asked Soma-kun's father before.
Yukihira Diner
Dad!
I'm gonna become a chef
who can beat you, Dad!
Oh, yeah?
Well, good luck.
Okay!
Let's do a cooking match right now!
In my eyes, Soma didn't have
any special cooking skill.
Kids say that sort of thing,
so I thought he'd have enough
once I beat him a couple of times.
But Soma never let himself get down.
Every time, he gets one step closer.
One day, I realized something.
Soma lacks something
any normal person would have.
What do you mean by that?
See, everyone wants to believe
that it's obvious for someone
to lose to someone more talented.
They want to lower their expectations
to protect their pride, self-respect,
and similar sorts of things.
But Soma doesn't have that defense mechanism.
He has the strength to face
his inadequacies head-on.
That's an incredible strength
that even I don't have.
Soma-kun's cooking inspirations
aren't from natural genius
or anything like that.
He just thinks things through.
He keeps testing and retesting his recipes.
Everyone can do that,
but not everyone actually does.
I bet it won't work.
He's up against Hayama Akira,
who has a superhuman sense of smell.
Kurokiba Ryo is an elite who was
handpicked by the Nakiri family, too.
A way to win against them?
I wouldn't even bother thinking one up.
It's impossible.
Of course the genius will win.
Why did they want to think less of Soma-kun?
Because if they acknowledged him,
it'd mean acknowledging
their own lack of effort.
But the tide's about to turn.
He's amazing!
Yeah.
He's playing at their level—
against those two monsters!
He might be able to do this.
Yeah, I kind of have to respect him now.
Yukihira...
Yukihira.
Yukihira!
Yukihira Soma is...
...amazing!
Glad you liked it!
With this, we conclude the evaluation!
We'll now enter the final assessment!
Oh, c'mon.
Well? What is it?
I'm sure it'll be okay!
He can do it!
He can!
Soma-kun...
Yukihira...
After closing the gap in ingredient quality,
you even managed to make
a dish of that caliber.
Interesting.
You're really interesting, Yukihira.
Good or bad, this is the final result.
This is it!
First, well done.
You presented each of your
unique strengths well
in a clash befitting the finals!
First, regarding your cooking techniques,
all three of you are on par.
Next, regarding your ability
to judge ingredient quality,
Kurokiba and Hayama are clearly exceptional.
They made the perfect choices
when selecting their Pacific saury.
However, Yukihira has closed the gap
through his creativity.
His inventiveness is
exceptional among the three!
Great!
Even more surprisingly,
all three dishes had flavors
that were nearly equal.
However, the deciding factor
was to what degree the dish was
a reflection of the chef as an individual.
The chef as an individual?
That's right, Yukihira-kun.
A dish brimming with true originality
allows you to picture the chef in
your mind just by tasting the dish.
Put differently,
it's a dish with such originality
that only that specific chef
could've created it.
We call such a dish the chef's specialty,
as a sign of respect.
The one who deserves victory
is the chef who best pursued his own cooking!
The chef who truly sought
what his cooking should look like!
And that person's name is...
8 Years Ago
I don't know what my parents
look like, or my real name.
All I know
is that I was abandoned as a newborn
in the outskirts of the slum.
You deserve better than this.
Your sense of smell
may remake the world itself!
It was Shiomi Jun who
pulled me out of the slums.
Professor Hayama, who was
Jun's advisor at the time,
agreed to become my legal guardian.
Raising
a Child
for the
First Time
They chose my name to indicate
someone who would bring
a new world of cooking to light.
Hayama Akira
I was named Akira.
Jun was always by my side.
Akira-kun is a very good boy.
He's so earnest in helping with my research.
He helps compensate for what I lack.
I can't thank him enough, really.
But...
I'm scared.
I'm scared that I'm making
Akira-kun do something he doesn't
really want to do for my own sake.
No.
That's not true, Jun.
You saw something in me...
My true worth.
You deserve better than this.
You gave me a reason to live!
You're the one who brought me into the light.
I have to win for Jun.
This isn't good enough!
My cooking's meaningless
unless I can win using a method
that no one else can copy.
I will change the world of taste
through the power of fragrance.
That's my cooking.
I'll give everything I have
to offer to this one dish!
The 43rd Autumn Elections Main Tournament Finals
Victor
The victor...
...is Hayama Akira!
The 43rd Autumn Elections Main Tournament Finals
Victor
Hayama Akira
Hayama!
It's Hayama!
Seared Pacific Saury Carpaccio.
The dish was worthy
of being called a specialty.
Congratulations, Hayama-kun!
Congratulations...
Congratu...
You did it, Hayama-kun!
I'm so happy for you! So happy...
Ugh, you always keep your cool.
You should act a little happy!
For winnin—
Huh?
Huh?!
Akira-kun, wh-what's wrong?
N-Nothing!
Akira-kun, the smell of cinnamon
is said to cheer you up.
I see...
His expression during the semi-finals...
I'm the one who'll climb to the top!
I won't let anyone else get close!
That wasn't a smile of confidence.
It was to rouse himself.
It was almost as though
he was threatening himself.
How fragile.
What?
Hayama-kun, that was a wonderful dish.
Thank you, Chef Dojima.
But too great a talent
will turn against itself in the end.
I hope that you will be able to maintain
a good relationship with your talent.
Ryo-kun!
Jeez! Jeez, jeez, jeez, jeez, jeez!
I can't believe you lost
right in front of me!
Jeez, jeez, jeez, jeez, jeez!
Hey, that hurts.
What's that for, bitch?!
Oh?!
How dare you call your master a bitch?
We're through!
You can apologize to me once you feel sorry!
I'm gonna become a chef who can beat you.
Hm?
Hey, Soma.
That sardine is no good.
Huh?
Don't lose to anyone else
before you lose to me next time.
Hayama.
Can you still make that carpaccio?
I have the ingredients, I guess.
Let me have a taste.
Huh?
Why?
Let me have some.
Uh, but it takes some work—
Let me try it too, bastard!
Why're you acting like you're
trying to start a fight?
What's with you two?
I would've been able to make it better.
Huh? A poor loser, huh.
Listen.
Tonight decided the first-years'
preliminary rankings.
Among us here, I'm the top seat.
You should show me respect from now on.
Want to have a rematch right now?!
Sure.
The results still won't change.
Now, now.
Hayama, you made a pretty good dish.
Why're you talking down to me, third place?
You don't know that!
Don't make things up!
You're saying I ranked below you?!
Don't yell while eating!
But yours was good too, Hayama.
Maybe there's nothing
to worry about with Hayama.
Those three look to become
an interesting trio.
Right.
The diamonds in the rough will polish
each other by crashing into each other.
That is the basic principle of Totsuki.
Indeed. Tonight, yet another
new genius was born!
Tch.
The 43rd
Autumn Elections
(92nd Class)
Victor
Hayama Akira
Soma-kun, that was really good work!
Okay, tonight, we celebrate
Yukihira finishing second!
Let's party!
Yeah, in Marui's room!
Why is it always my room?
Because it's big, okay?
Crap!
Sorry, can you guys go ahead?
What do you want, Dad?
Hey, Soma.
Been a while.
Well?
How'd the main tournament go?
Oh, well...
So...
Aw! You lost, huh?!
Who won?
Hayama.
Oh, Shiomi's disciple, huh.
Get it together, yeah?
It's like I lost to Shiomi.
Shit.
He's so upbeat when he's making fun of me.
What kind of parent feels happy
when their son loses?
Well, but to be fair,
if you can perfect fragrance,
it's amazing.
No, that wasn't all there was to it.
In his dish...
...I sensed something like an obsession.
Dad, I'm glad I left Yukihira.
If I hadn't, I wouldn't have
noticed all these things.
So, I'm going to explore
the kind of cooking only I can do.
If I don't do that,
there's no point in my carrying
on the family business.
Huh?
Now that I've said it,
that doesn't sound that different
from what I've been doing already.
Well...
Why not? Be that way.
Was that a yawn?
Bye.
He's finally met someone his age
who can blow who he is now
out of the water, huh?
That's right, Soma.
Meet them.
Only through these encounters
can a chef move forward.
If you face a dish on your own,
you'll only see the same self as before.
My own cooking, huh...
A Few Days Later
Hiya!
Nikumi-cchi!
Welcome!
Thanks for the text.
You got a shipment of good game meat?
Nice!
Looks tasty!
Here.
It's one of mine, but it looks good on you!
Oh, thanks, Megumi.
All right, let's start!
Yeah!
How nice.
Lovely girls in a kitchen
together in harmony.
It doesn't look so lovely when
you actually look at it, though.
By the way, where's Yukihira?
Oh, he's back there today.
So, the mellow soy milk flavor
enhances the gentle saltiness of the
Pacific saury in a good way.
Still, crunchy pickled plums feel too cheap
for me to want to eat them.
But you're shoveling it in like you like it!
Seconds.
And you want another serving?
The cartoccio I made for you
yesterday was better, though.
Huh?!
Then try making it again!
Let's compare!
Whatever, but why are you guys
taste-testing at our place?
I made tea!
What?!
You don't have to play hostess, Jun!
And why're you offering
such high-quality cookies?
They'll be fine with cheap snacks!
Hey, we can hear you.
You're a skinflint, and a nagger, too.
The specialty... a dish that shows
the chef's character.
That's because you're such a pig.
What Hayama's cooking has, but mine doesn't.
Hey!
Don't cram them all into your mouth!
Hayama!
I want to compare dishes.
One Seared Pacific Saury Carpaccio, thanks.
Make that two.
Shut up. Go home.
Two on the double, yeah?
You guys!
Yukihira's crazy,
spending all that time
with someone he lost to.
Yeah.
Isn't he frustrated by the results?
I'm sure Soma-kun feels more
frustrated than we'll ever know.
That's why he's there all the time.
But to know who you really are,
you must step outside the world you know.
Even if that means facing
the one who got the better of you.
I'm sure the same goes for the girls, too.
They're trying their best to
glean something from others,
just like Soma-kun.
Damn, we can't be left behind.
Let's do a taste-testing festival!
You guys come, too!
Sure!
Let's do this!
Not my room again!
You too, Ibusaki!
You're not going to go
with them, Ibusaki-kun?
Oh, maybe you want to join the girls?
You're a closet perv, I see.
Well, there's no huge rush, but...
Either way, first-years in our high school
division can only relax for a short while.
Why's that?
What do you mean?
Soon, you'll be tossed outside the academy.
It's going to start.
The practical training program, The Stagiaire.
The Stagiaire?
Food
Wars
The Second Plate
Next Episode: The Stagiaire
Next time, "The Stagiaire."