We're here?
No, we aren't...
This isn't Uranus.
I've got it.
What we're seeing is the seventh moon, Hyperion.
We're in orbit around Saturn.
We're still a bit away...
Hana, can we Entangle Link again?
Yeah.
I think so.
I'll start getting ready now.
Thanks.
But why did we fail?
You and I might be the cause, Captain.
Us?
Our minds weren't used to the Entangle Link.
That could've caused interference.
The minds of the crew can interfere
with the hyperspace jump.
And there are signs we're being affected
by external interference, also.
Come to think of it, I had a weird dream.
It was like they were locking me inside my dream,
and trying to keep me there.
Same here.
We should assume that was a
psychological attack by the enemy.
Kiltgang in sector 79.
Distance: .03 AU.
Captain, they're coming!
I'll stop it!
Bugbear?
The captain will be in danger alone!
I'll go, too.
Teppei, use the Boosted.
Take care of the captain!
Roger.
This overwhelming force...
The champion?
Daichi Manatsu...
I thought you didn't want to be the captain.
He's infiltrated our communications...
That isn't all.
They...
They really were inside my dream.
Daichi Manatsu, are you really awake?
This might still be your nightmare!
Don't let him fool you, Captain!
I'll scramble our communications.
The backdoor I used on them last time...
I guess I can't use it anymore.
Your lives don't even last a century.
They're no different than dreams!
They end quickly, and you lose everything!
What is something like that worth?
Why are you the one to decide if our
lives are worth anything or not?!
This is the extent of your power.
Those without power can't protect anything.
I know you are a special person.
Live in a way that lets you see the true light...
Like me.
Earthlings are meaningless creatures.
I'll kill them all!
Can you hear me, Captain?
I'll use the Boosted.
Get away from Bugbear,
or you'll be caught in the blast!
Roger.
It doesn't matter what you try to do, Daichi Manatsu!
Captain!
You are helpless.
Against overwhelming power,
your desire to protect something is meaningless.
Feelings are powerless.
No...
Power doesn't come first.
Your feelings come first.
The strength of your feelings
becomes your power.
Captain...
That's why he'll be fine.
Is that what you mean by strength?
But...
Once you're dead, everything is over!
Give me the power to protect my friends, too...
God!
What?
The captain is correct, Bugbear.
We've always turned the strength
of our emotions into power!
Albion?!
The Nebula Engine Entangle Linked?
Yeah, that's how it looked to me.
Are you okay?
You look really beat.
I didn't realize it.
But I guess I really did jump.
Your Ego Block is gone now, isn't it?
Yeah.
But even without our Ego Blocks
or spaceships like Blume,
it was said that a Neoteny
could also Entangle Link, depending
on how they used the Livlaster.
Then it was you that jumped, not the Nebula?
The Livlasters are devices capable
of Entangle Links, too?
When the Nebula Engine was hit by the
Boosted Plasmagnum, the reason it survived
must be because it phase shifted, via Entangle Link.
Well, anyway...
When you tried to protect the
captain, you powered up.
You two boys really are in love.
For a second, I was praying to God.
I think, for the first time,
I found a God I want to believe in.
Thanks to you.
If you did that, can I do it, too?
I love the way you can't stand to lose.
Hey, you said they were inside your dream, right?
Yeah, during the Entangle Link, they were
trying to shake me up inside my dream.
Is that really possible?
They have Ego Blocks, so I don't think it's impossible.
If they've prioritized Operation Summer
over attacking the Earth,
then why?
They've realized that with our power now,
we can destroy the cocoon inside Auberon.
The cocoon at Auberon's center
contains the safeguard systems
for the Ego Blocks, and the core of the
mechanical intelligence controlling Auberon.
But there's another reason they
wouldn't want it destroyed.
That's right.
On their own, the Kiltgangs can't Entangle
Link through interstellar distances, right?
Yeah.
If they lose the cocoon, even if
their Ego Blocks are intact,
they wouldn't be able to leave the Solar System.
That explosion was really huge, wasn't it?
Yeah.
If you hadn't been there, it would've been bad.
We destroyed Bugbear's Ego Block.
With the Boosted Plasmagnum,
destroying Ego Blocks is possible.
Yeah.
We'll destroy all the Kiltgangs and the cocoon.
Captain...
I'm ready.
Roger.
You gonna be okay this time, Captain?
They may attack again.
What about you, Akari?
I'm a magical girl, after all.
I'll be fine, too.
No matter what happens,
I'll do the best I can right now.
That's all.
We're jumping to Auberon!
Auberon
We're here.
Earth Engine!
Nebula Engine!
Scramble!
That's Auberon?
It's bigger than I'd imagined.
Okay...
I'll take over the Kivotos!
Let's go with it.
We're doing it?
We're doing it.
Okay, Captain?
Roger.
You're ready, aren't you, partner?
Let's go.
Okay, guys!
Pirate formation! Go!
Captain!
They're still coming.
Roger!
We're going in!
Captain, we're heading into the core.
This is their cocoon?
I'm ending this.
Above?
It's them!
They ambushed us!
Akari!
I'm fine!
Concentrate!
Welcome back, Albion.
And Earthlings, you've done well to come this far.
To be honest, I'm surprised.
I can't believe you Earthlings can
perform an Entangle Link.
What is this voice?
It isn't coming in via communicator.
It's resonating throughout the Auberon.
I have a proposal for you.
You were able to withstand an Entangle Link,
and your growth as Neoteny has been impressive.
You're becoming very similar to us.
So I'd like to have you join us.
Siren-sama can do that.
Bugbear, awaken.
Welcome back, Bugbear.
I thank you, Siren-sama.
His Ego Block regenerated?
You understand, don't you, Albion?
An Ego Block can only be recreated
as long as the avatar is alive.
Of course, not just you.
We can give Ego Blocks to the Princess
of Blume or to the Earthlings.
We can welcome you into the Planetary Gears.
But abandon your Livlasters!
They are life forms that cannot be held
by someone with an Ego Block.
I'm serious.
I can make you, and only you, true humans.
Your energy's mine, and now I'm invincible!
Akari! Hana!
Then negotiations have failed?
They wouldn't listen to a plan like that.
They're already being controlled by the
extradimensional creatures called Livlasters.
First, you should destroy the Earthling
weapons that pose a threat to me.
What do you mean by "a threat to me"?
I mean this, ancient princess...
Siren-sama!
What is this light?
Liban?
Siren-sama, I'm so glad you're safe.
Something's wrong...
I can't move!
Liban!
What?
Teppei!
I'm fine!
But the Boosted was destroyed.
Liban's Ego Block exploded?
What's going on?
Did you do that, Puck?
What did you do?
The part of a Planetary Gear's
Kiltgang body capable of
generating the most destructive
energy is the Ego Block.
So I used it for my own purposes.
A very logical decision.
You're a tool of the Planetary Gears...
And you used us as tools?
I already have a system that can install
my own ego into a Planetary
Gear's Kiltgang at any time.
Now you are no more than my tools.
So that's it.
The sudden change in Masaki Kube was
because you installed your ego in him?
That's right.
What the hell are you doing?
Stop!
I can install my ego into an Earthling or
a Planetary Gear whenever I want.
Even the cocoon you're protecting
is a part of me now.
Then...
What are you doing, Daichi Manatsu?
I'll just destroy it, as well!
Can you do that?
I will!
What?
The cocoon...
Did I get him?
Earthlings are so emotional.
They're so easy to manipulate.
Now every threat to me has been eliminated.
What is that?
I'll install myself into every sentient
life form in the galaxy,
and become this galaxy's true god!
The mechanical intelligence Puck
installs himself into Blume,
transforming into a massive weapon
of destruction, Robin Goodfellow.
Its power overwhelms the Midsummer's Knights,
and attacks their home, Earth.
But the boy who chose his fate
does not give up the fight.
Next time, Captain Earth, final episode:
Captain Earth.
Captain Earth
Captain, thank you.