Nervous?
Don't worry.
All our customers are nice.
A lot of them are perverts, though.
Masochists, too.
Occasionally, you'll get one that freaks you out.
Cut it out.
New girl, you've got a client.
See you later.
Good luck!
Relax. It's Room 304, down below.
So you're Tilarna?
Yes, I am Tilarna Elnebara.
Do you speak Earth language?
A little.
Come here.
Your socks...
Leave your socks on.
I prefer it that way.
You're new, I heard?
Yes.
Don't worry.
There's nothing to be nervous about.
What?
Christ.
This is the police. You're under arrest!
Wait! This is some kind of mistake.
I just...
You just happened to find yourself
in the room of a high-priced brothel?
Yeah, right.
You sure as hell don't look like the pizza guy.
You must've gotten the wrong room!
Listen to me.
Sure, we'll listen to you.
Once we get down to the station,
you can talk all you like.
It's closing time.
Get ready to go home, miss.
I didn't lay a finger on her! It's true!
Take him in, boys.
--This way!
--Hey, get off me!
Now then...
Oww! What do you want?
You're late! He touched my hair!
--Idiot! Dummy! Rakebye!
--Knock it off!
We got the info on the club, so who cares?
I care! If you were five seconds later,
I would've killed him!
Don't let the judge hear that, okay?
Hey, his stuff's still here.
Let me see...
Cole Mozeleemay.
I'm pretty sure I've seen him somewhere...
You finally noticed?
Mayoral candidate... A politician?
You sometimes see him on the news.
Well, what do you know?
Mr. Mozeleemay, is it true that
you were using a dating club?
Some of the staff there
were reported to be minors...
Will you be dropping out of the mayoral race?
I'll be putting the date of my official
press conference on my blog shortly.
I've spent years dealing with issues
involving Semanians and poverty.
And I'm sure that many
of you are confused by
the baseless allegations that
have been levied against me.
But I'll do everything I can
to stand up to this abuse of power.
That is all!
Marla, I...
It's okay, honey.
I know you're innocent.
It must've been some mistake
that you ended up there.
Some evil person who didn't
want you to be mayor set you up.
I'm sorry.
Let's fight this together, okay?
Don't touch me.
...many of you are confused by
the baseless allegations that
have been levied against me.
But I'll do everything I can
to stand up to this abuse of power.
--I can't believe it!
--Yeah.
Listen to the crap he's spewing.
I bet even your sword couldn't
cut through that bullshit.
After what he almost did to me...
Shameless!
It just shows you that the
legal battle's already begun.
It's gonna be hilarious
when you're on the stand.
Um... "Leave your socks on,"
was that it?
It's not funny! It's not funny!
All powerful people are like that.
If you get mad at each and every one of them,
you'll waste your whole life.
You should be getting more upset!
Should I?
I don't want to see his face.
I'll wait for you in the car.
Hey, Tilarna.
It's me, Zoey. Did you forget me?
No, you just seemed different...
This is how I am, usually.
You got arrested too, right?
Did they let you go?
I guess...
I had somebody post bail for me.
Well, whatever.
Look what they gave me.
A tracker?
If you wear this, they give you
a discount on your bail.
Anyway, are you free?
I guess...
I didn't think you were going
to ask me to help you move.
This is a huge help!
They kicked me out and I didn't know what to do.
A lot of the movers around here
can't be trusted...
It's gonna fall! You're gonna hit something!
I'm sorry I just disappeared.
Something came up.
No! I'm not mad at you!
I'm hanging up.
Who was that?
My mom... or something like that.
Here, this is your thank-you.
Just this?
You want this too?
No.
Anyway, did you find a place to stay?
Yup.
Let's go.
You can see the ocean!
You can give me the review later.
Help me move this stuff!
That can wait! Take a look!
This is your move!
What do you mean it can wait?
You're so serious, Tilarna.
What is that thing?
It's a camera. Haven't you heard of it?
I've heard of it.
Did you take these?
Yes. They're my work.
Beautiful...
Thank you.
--Even if you're just being nice, I appreciate it.
--No.
I don't understand the technology, but...
The people of this town... I don't know.
They feel like they're alive.
Inside this square frame...
You're making me blush!
Is your real job a photographer?
No way! It's just a hobby!
I'm hoping I can open
an exhibition someday, though.
If you do, I'm going to come see it, okay?
Oh, you want one?
Really?
As a thank-you.
I need to give you something
more than a burrito.
But I can't choose...
Not one of these. I'll take one for you.
It'll take some time, but I promise I'll do it!
--Just 100 dollars!
--What?
I was just kidding!
Assistant Prosecutor Gardner!
Sergeant Matoba.
Where's Exedilica?
Oh, she's on patrol.
Patrol?
Want me to call her?
No, this is nothing interesting.
Just brief her later.
It's about Mozeleemay.
His lawyer's pitching a fit to the media.
The police roughed him up. Set him up.
That always happens. What's the problem?
There isn't one. We just need to tell him
we've got the recording from his arrest,
and he'll shut up.
The conversation your partner recorded,
with the, uh...
--The socks?
--That's right.
Video alone isn't enough proof these days.
What about the date club's
customer list and their financials?
Unfortunately,
they've been really careful with their
use of encoding and cryptocurrencies.
We don't have enough to convince a judge yet.
Mozeleemay doesn't know
that yet, though, does he?
Bluff.
That's the plan.
We push hard and he'll give in.
We may be able to get information
on some of his connections.
Sounds good.
We're the only ones with
the data from the date club.
You're sure, right?
Yeah, that should be right.
Okay, I'll keep that in mind
when I'm going forward.
Perfect timing.
Who was that?
Zoey. From the date club.
The sex worker, huh?
She's quitting, she says.
So we became friends.
Friends? We're cops.
Don't worry.
She thinks I'm some rich girl
who ran away from home.
Fine. Don't meet with her again.
What?
I told you not to see her again.
Mozeleemay's trial's coming up.
That Zoey girl might end up
on the stand, you know?
What's the problem?
She'll think you betrayed her.
She may get mad and refuse to testify.
That's... I'm a Knight of Mirvor.
If I tell her about my desire for justice,
I'm sure she'll understand.
Ridiculous. You think she'll be so
impressed she'll drop to her knees?
Listen to me, Tilarna. Don't get involved
with the people you're investigating.
--But...
--You can't be friends with them.
You live in different worlds.
Different worlds?
Then what about you and me?
That's... something different.
It's not different! It's not different at all!
I can't accept that.
Isn't it expensive?
The rent here.
It's got a great view.
I guess.
Are you going back to your old job?
What about you?
I...
You should quit for good.
Your parents are rich,
and you ran away from home, right?
I'm not blaming you.
I know you want to have your adventures.
I like adventuring too, you know.
Not getting enough sleep?
No, I...
You're hanging out with Zoey, right?
You're coming home late every night.
--Knock it off...
--Are you my mom?
--Huh?
--It's what you always say.
I don't want lectures.
Listen...
Gardner?
We've got a problem.
The San-Teresa police
responded to the leak by...
What the hell is going on?
No way to know yet.
Most of the names on the list
that's going around are fake.
But some of them aren't.
That's why it's bad.
So Mozeleemay becomes one
of the supposedly fake victims?
The preliminary hearing is coming up.
And the judge isn't going to like this at all.
We may not be able to prosecute at all!
So he won't face punishment at all?
Relax.
All we need to do is find
where the list came from.
But...
So we keep working, then?
Yes. Let's find them.
Nobody's following you, right?
No idea. You're the one who
wanted to meet in person, right?
Your information was good.
Then give me the rest of the money.
What?
I want the rest of the information.
That customer list is incomplete.
That's going cost you another 20,000.
It's right here. Look for yourself.
You're all ready, huh?
There seems to be more than there should be.
You know why.
Why?
You came because you wanted it, right?
Stop it, Mr. Mozeleemay.
If you just wanted to make a deal,
you could've done it online.
Let me guess. You couldn't forget me, could you?
That was business. And I quit.
Then why not get back into it?
I can satisfy you. I was a good customer.
Right? Right?
Look.
You're far too careless.
Give me that!
Go ahead and delete it. This one's on the house.
You bitch... How dare you?
I'm being nice, actually.
Why not be a little more careful?
--Get out!
--Sure.
Oh, I'll send you the data you want.
Get out!
Pleasure doing business!
Got it.
Take care of that too, then.
Another dead end.
I'm starting to think that
Mozeleemay's side may not
have access to our info at all.
Kei...
Could it be one of the workers at that club?
One of the sex workers had
a copy of the customer list?
I don't know. If they were that smart,
they'd probably be at another job.
About that. Can I say something?
What's up?
I was looking at the drives
of the PCs we confiscated.
Oh, copies of them, specifically.
I know that. So?
I was able to restore the logs off the webcams.
It shows photos of everybody who accessed
the customer list before we got it.
Most of the time it's the owner
and her suits, but...
Looks like one of the girls
accessed it several times.
Her.
Zoey!
We won't be able to prosecute at this rate.
We need to convince a judge
as to what's real and what's fake.
At a minimum, we need to convince
them that it's not a leak from the police
or the prosecutor's office.
I have an idea. Buy me time.
You okay?
With what?
I can talk to her if you want.
No. I should talk to her, I think.
Okay.
Zoey?
Wow! Don't move a muscle!
What are you doing?
That's my line!
What's that krehg for?
Anyway... remember what
I promised you? It's ready.
Zoey, we need to talk.
I wasn't sure which to give you.
In the end, I just gave you
the most obvious choice.
Zoey!
What?
The customer data from the dating club.
You sold it to Mozeleemay, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
Don't lie to me. I already know the answer.
You a cop?
You are, aren't you?
I didn't mean to lie to you.
You disgust me.
It was a coincidence.
I...
I'll go after them.
You stay with her!
But...
Just stay with her!
Stop! This is the police!
I thought you were a friend!
So did I!
You said you were quitting!
What would a rich girl like you know?
Do you have any idea how hard it is
to go straight in this town?
Zoey!
I've got nothing to be ashamed of.
Zoey, hang in there...
I didn't do anything...
Zoey!
Who hired you?
Tell me!
Shit!
It's me.
I see.
Got it.
Our informant was shot. She's badly injured.
I see...
If she dies, I may be able to get away with it.
They won't be able--
Don't tell me... It was you?
What are you talking about?
Don't think about a thing.
That's for the best.
That look on your face scares me.
You look like you're about to go beat
the shit out of Mozeleemay right now.
He sent an assassin after her.
Got evidence?
No. But it has to be him.
If that was good enough, we never would have--
Is that your people's "justice"?
I can't just let him get away with this!
Zoey... Zoey...
She was my friend!
"Next Time"
Next time on COP CRAFT: