Used Bookstore Hitotose
And hup... and hup...
There we go!
Hina-chan, thanks for helping me
even though it's summer break.
No, I'm doing this because it's summer break.
I was actually able to speak in front
of people at the culture festival.
Right now, I bet I could
wait on customers, too!
So, what should I do?
Well, I'd like you to help me
set out and restock merchandise.
Sure. Leave it to me!
Trying Too Hard
Used Bookstore Hitotose
Hina-chan, do you want to
practice waiting on customers?
Yeah, I do!
Okay, try doing what you'd do
if a customer came in.
Right!
W-Welcome!
We have old books,
rare books... lots of books!
Please take your time looking around!
That was very good!
Really? I did it right?
Yeah!
I'm so glad!
Um, excuse me.
There's a book I'm looking for...
Welcome. We'll be right with you.
Hina-cha—
U-Um, w-we'll be right with you...
I need to do something with these...
There we go.
S-Sorry for the wait!
S-Sure...
Thank you for coming!
I was so nervous...
I couldn't help the customer at all.
Hey, that was only the first one.
You'll get used to it eventually.
I'm back.
Hina-chan, that's just Mayu-chan!
Oh, you're right...
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing...
Anyway, where's Aki-chan?
The landlady?
She came back, then headed right out again.
What? Where'd she go?
I'm not sure.
It seemed like she was going to
hang out with some theater buddies.
Did you need her for something?
No, nothing in particular...
It's just that the two of us
haven't hung out lately.
You're lonely because she
hasn't paid attention to you?
Eh? O-Of course not! I'm not a child!
There's no need to bluff.
I'm not bluffing!
I don't know about that.
There, there.
Darn it! You're ganging up on me!
Used Bookstore Hitotose
Anyway, are you guys hungry?
Why don't we take a break and have some tea?
We'd love some!
You're back to your usual look.
Seeing you dressed
like a maid just feels right.
You like frilly clothes, right?
I'd love to see you in a dress.
I bet you'd look good in lolita fashion, too.
A dress...
Lolita...
I couldn't do that! No way!
How would it be any different
from what she's wearing now?
Hey, Hinako! Are you here?
Yua-sama is here to see you!
You'd better thank...
Welcome!
Hinako, what's with you?
Hina-chan, that's Yua-chan.
Oh, it's just you, Yua-chan!
Are you trying to pick a fight?
So you really do run a café, too.
Go on, Yua-chan, help yourself.
So everyone living in the apartments
here also works in the shop?
Do you work, too, Hinako?
Yep!
I can't imagine you handling
the work of a waitress, though.
She can do it!
But I bet she spills tea all the time, right?
No, she doesn't!
Right, Hina-chan?
Huh?
Well, if that's what you say,
then let's see you do it.
Huh?!
Go on, Hina-chan!
Show her what a great job you can do!
Huh?!
Safe!
The tea is, maybe.
Milk
I'm sorry!
O-Oh, no!
Yua-chan, you're so cute!
Sorry this was all I had.
We'll have your outfit cleaned,
so could you wear this for now?
Jeez... I can't let people
see me dressed like this...
That's not true at all!
You look really cute!
Yeah, you do!
I'm back.
Oh, Aki-chan. Welcome back.
Where'd you go?
Oh...
I went to see some people
from my old theater troupe,
and I lost track of time
while talking to them.
That's fine,
but you could have sent me
a message before you left.
Yeah... Sorry.
I'll do that next time.
Ch-Chiaki-senpai looks so beautiful today...
There, there.
It's so rare to see her in a skirt!
She's my idol!
Oh, Yua-chan, you're here?
Wow...
Yua-chan's regular clothes are
a lot more unique than I expected...
So cute...
So beautiful...
Are you two okay?
By the way,
what brings you here, Yua-chan?
Oh, right, I came to lend you some DVDs.
Performances by my favorite
small theater troupes,
and acting lessons on DVD!
Watch these and study them carefully.
Huh? I can borrow those?
Aren't they important to you?
I-It's no big deal!
If you don't get better,
I'll have no competition.
And as a fellow actress
in the Hitotose Troupe...
Thanks, Yua-chan!
D-Don't get the wrong idea, okay?!
It's not for you—
You really are nice, Yua-chan!
I told you not to get the wrong idea!
They're more like a mother and child
than fellow actresses.
Thanks!
Like I said, I'm not doing this for you!
Yeah.
I'll be sure to watch them.
Today was a lot of fun. I even
got to spend time with Yua-chan.
I can't believe she came to see me,
even though it's summer break.
And as a fellow actress
in the Hitotose Troupe...
I'm so happy to be part of a group
of friends who help each other.
It's too early to go to bed,
so I'll watch just a little bit
of the DVDs Yua-chan lent me.
Huh...
I'll watch this and do my best
to aim for the Suzuran stage!
Help me, Yua-chan!
You can't even play a DVD?!
Just how deep in the
countryside did you live?!
Coffee Shop
Oh, w-welcome!
Help yourself to an open seat.
Maybe I'll be able to manage today.
I have to do my best
to help out after this, too.
Hina-chan!
Yes!
Would you go and take the customer's order?
Okay.
H-Have you decided
wh-what you'd like to order?
Yes, thank you.
You can do it, Hina-chan!
W-Will that be all?
Yes.
Th-Then please wait a... a... moment...
H-Hina-chan!
A-Are you okay?!
37.5 degrees...
Looks like Hina-chan caught a cold.
Do you think we should take her to a clinic?
Maybe we should contact her parents, too!
Calm down. It's just a mild fever.
Let's just keep an eye on her.
You can go on and get back to work.
I'll take care of her.
O-Okay. Sorry I lost my cool.
Is it true that Hina-chan passed out?!
Sh-Should I call an ambulance?!
Or should I carry her myself?!
You need to calm down, too, Kuu-chan.
Thank goodness! You're awake!
Kuu-chan... What did I...
You came down with a fever and
passed out while waiting on a customer.
What? Who's working the coffee shop?
Mayu-chan is handling it on her own for now.
I'll be going to help her later.
I-I'm sorry.
It's all because of me.
It's okay. Don't worry about a thing.
Hina-chan, is there anything
we can get for you?
I feel a little cold,
so something warm might be nice.
In that case, I'll warm you
with my own body right now!
I'm warm-blooded!
How's that, Hina-chan?
Are you warm now?
Yeah, v-very warm...
You know you can't do that.
We need to let her rest.
H-Hina-chan, I'll be back later!
Just hang tight!
That surprised me.
Can I take your order?
I'll clean that up right away!
Ta-da! You here, Hinako?
Yua-sama brought more DVDs to lend you...
Oh, Yua-chan.
What? Hinako caught a cold and passed out?
Yes, so I'm looking up things
that help with colds.
To cure a cold...
Dictionary of Medicines
Of course! She needs medicine, right?
We can cure Hina-chan with this!
Here we go...
You're doing it wrong.
Hina-chan, I brought something
that'll help your cold!
Ta-da! Say goodbye to your cold with this!
Huh? A green onion?
Yeah. Apparently you
wrap it around your neck.
I saw it in a book.
So let's wrap it around your neck right now!
Something just doesn't seem right...
Yeah. It's bound to take at least that much.
I-Isn't that too many?
The more, the better! Everyone knows that!
Even if she gets hungry and eats some,
there's plenty to spare!
Well, I guess you do have a point there...
What else can we do?
Oh, I know!
They say that when you have a cold,
you should sweat it out!
What is all this?
Really, you two should know better.
You made Hina-chan feel even worse.
We're sorry.
I feel alive again.
Really? I'm glad.
Since you got sweaty,
I'll wipe you down.
O-Okay...
Sorry. Is it too cold?
N-No, it's fine...
There, all done.
Th-Thank you.
Okay, we'll be downstairs.
If you need anything,
call us with your cell phone.
Okay.
Hina-chan, you don't have to worry anymore.
I found a surefire method used all around
the world to cure sickness instantly.
There...
Hiss!
What are you doing?
A bite from the Great White Snake
cures any illness—
If it's the real one.
Gods, hear my prayer...
I was just, um... I mean...
Don't make so much noise.
Okay.
Rawr!
A bite from a dragon cures any illness—
Again, only if it's a real one.
Elohim essaim... Elohim essaim...
I implore you...
This is just, um...
What good will it do to summon a demon?
Oops, wrong chant!
You two aren't allowed to go
into Hina-chan's room anymore.
B-But...
I'm worried about Hinako...
I understand,
but the best thing we can do
for her now is to let her rest quietly.
You're right.
Hey, you guys!
Could you help me with something?
It's so quiet...
I think this is the first time
I've been sick since I came to Tokyo.
How many years has it been
since I caught a cold, anyway?
Hey, Hina-chan! Good work again.
After I started working as a scarecrow,
Thanks for helping out every day.
I spent all my time in
the field with no breaks.
Here are your vegetables for today.
Has it been since first grade?
Mom spent the whole day looking after me,
and she made rice gruel for me...
I wonder if Mom is at home right now...
Mom
I wonder if she'll answer the phone...
I miss you, Mom...
I want to eat your rice gruel...
No, Hinako!
If I show her any weakness,
she'll tell me to come home!
I decided I wouldn't go home
until I started acting in Tokyo
and got over my scarecrow problem!
But for today...
Just for today...
Hina-chan?
How are you feeling?
Eh? Ah...
You're not sleeping! Are you okay?
U-Uh... This is just, um... I...
Hina-chan, do you feel hungry?
Huh?
We all made some rice gruel.
Do you think you can eat?
Yeah! I'll have some!
I was the one who cut up the
pickled plum so it'd be easier to eat!
And I cut up the seaweed.
Thanks, both of you!
Here. Say, "Ahh."
It's delicious!
Oh, good.
Strange...
It tastes just like my mom's.
Why is that?
Well... I wonder...
Yeah, I wonder why.
Maybe it's because we made it
with the same feelings your mom did?
The same feelings?
We all made it with the wish
that your cold would get better soon.
You guys...
Thank you!
Can you eat more?
Yeah! I'll have more!
I'll eat all of it!
As long as you don't
get sick to your stomach.
Oh, I'll feed you next.
Say, "Ahh."
It's my turn next!
S-Say, "Ahh."
D-Do you like it?
Yeah! It tastes delicious!
Okay, I'll go next.
Wait! I want another turn!
No fair going twice in a row.
Why not?!
Mom...
I felt a little homesick today
because of my cold,
but thanks to everyone here,
I didn't feel lonely.
Meeting such wonderful new friends
makes me glad I moved to Tokyo.
Okay!
Good morning, everyone!
Thanks to you guys, I'm all bet— huh?
Th-This is awful!
What should I do?
No! This time, I'm the one
who needs to work hard!
Towel, towel, towel...
Fresh clothes, fresh clothes,
fresh clothes...
And water... Water...
Oral Medicine
Nakajima Yua
Directions
Take 3 per day for 7 days.
I wonder if Hinako feels better...
We'll Have a Training Camp
Hina-chan's mom is going to come visit soon!
And the Hitotose Troupe will finally
hold its first performance!
All we can do to make it successful
is practice, practice, practice!
Next time, "We'll Have a Training Camp."