It's the last painting Mashiro
did before she came to Japan.
Has this helped you understand...
Mashiro a little better?
Shiina should...
return to the world of fine arts.
#10 Hate Hate, Love
You're not making any progress, Sorata.
It has nothing to do with you.
Anyway, I thought you
moved into Shiina's room.
Mashiro's working, so I
came in here to play.
I'm working too, you know...
What are you doing?
I'm drawing storyboards for Nyapollon.
I'm diagramming the camera blocking.
Are you visualizing the final
product while you're drawing?
No, I'm just guessing really...
Let me see that.
You have your reference right
in front of you, so look at it.
You have to look at it
while you're drawing.
Rita-san!
Just watch.
You're really good...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You must have it rough.
What do you mean?
Both Mashiro's and Misaki's
work are incredible.
Working alongside people who are bursting...
at the seams with talent
must be quite a burden.
Have you made up your mind...
about Mashiro returning to England yet?
If you're telling me to talk
to her, it's no good.
She won't listen to me.
Either way, I think you'd be more effective...
in persuading her than I would be.
I want to ask you something.
What is it?
What did you mean...
when you said Shiina would destroy me?
Does it have anything to do with
why you stopped painting?
Rita's in here.
Yes. I was deepening my
friendship with Sorata.
Don't say it like that!
You're finished?
What did Misaki-senpai say?
She hugged me.
I love you!
...is what she said.
Must be perfect, then.
Is it okay?
Yeah, I think it's perfect, too.
Good evening.
Don't expect to have
everything your way, freeloader.
What are you trying to say?
I'm saying that Kanda still has
that which you've forgotten.
You seem to have me all figured out.
You've already given up on art.
That's all I needed to
know to figure you out.
You were listening?
A gentleman doesn't eavesdrop.
Kanda-kun, have you been working too hard?
No, I just haven't slept very well recently.
Rita came to bother me again last night.
I don't like that girl.
Just looking at her fake
smile makes me angry.
Her fake smile?
What's on today's agenda?
We've actually run into
a bit of a problem.
If we want to participate
in the culture festival,
the Student Council is
insisting that a representative...
makes a presentation.
A presentation?
Yeah.
We have to explain what we're going to do,
not just to the Student Council,
but to the festival committee...
and the student union, as well.
This is a job for the director, Sorata.
What?!
I have something to report, as well.
The art for the dramatic sequences
is two days behind schedule.
At this rate, we won't make
it in time for the festival.
I'll do my best.
You're already producing work...
with astounding speed and quality.
It would be unrealistic for you...
to shoulder more work alone.
Looks like it's my time to shine!
I'm going to help you, Mashiron!
Kamiigusa-senpai, your modeling work...
is all that you have room for.
Then, we'll increase our numbers!
We'll invite more people
to join our merry band!
I don't think anyone at school
will associate with Sakura Hall.
It's all because the storyboards
are falling behind schedule.
Don't sweat it, kouhai-kun!
That's right.
Slow and steady wins the race.
But if we can't meet our deadlines,
it won't matter how
polished our work is.
Student Council President.
Hau-hau's here, too!
Hey, everyone! This is the girl who's...
providing the music for Nyapollon!
Please don't call me that.
My name is Himemiya Saori.
Are you eating lunch together?
You two sure are close.
Did you get our message, Mitaka?
About the presentation?
Isn't it a little unfair that
we're the only group...
that has to do one?
Suimei High's culture festival...
is a major event for the neighborhood,
spanning an entire week.
We get a lot of outside interest.
Instead of complaining,
try reflecting on the way
you conduct yourself.
Don't be such a stuffed shirt.
We've known each other a long time.
Yes, involuntarily.
Class is starting. Let's go.
Okay.
See you later.
That was the Student Council President?
That's Tatebayashi Soichiro-senpai.
Jin-san, you don't get along with him?
It's not intentional on my part.
At any rate, this'll be a
difficult obstacle to overcome.
Maybe me being the director
wasn't such a good idea...
If that's what you think, just quit.
I don't need someone...
who's afraid of a little
work ordering me around.
Akasaka-kun, don't you
think you should...
choose your words a
little more carefully?
On top of that, can you kindly refrain
from eating tomatoes during class?
Don't bring up such irrelevant topics.
Just so you know,
I have greater faith in tomatoes
than in anything else in the world.
We have to increase our numbers.
Let's look for people who
can rival Shiina's talent.
Easier said than done. Not many people...
can produce work of the same quality.
There is one.
Rita.
Do you think she'll help us?
She told me she gave up on art.
Rita would never give up on art.
Why not?
Rita loves art.
She's certainly talented.
This is...
She's already a professional artist?
You didn't see them?
See what?
Rita's paintings were at the exhibition.
What?
You're kidding!
What were you two looking at?
Rita.
Rita!
Oh, welcome home.
Rita, I have a favor to ask you.
Do you want me to take
you back to England?
Draw Nyapollon with me.
We don't have enough people,
and nobody else can match
the quality of Shiina's work.
Shiina said you'd be able to do it.
I'd appreciate your help, too.
I'll have to decline.
I'm not as good as Mashiro.
That's not true.
You're a good artist.
Please stop.
I've already decided never to draw again.
Why?
You're a great artist.
Rita?
Don't be ridiculous.
I don't want to hear those
words from you of all people.
Why not?
Whose fault do you think it
is that I gave up on art?
It's all your fault.
Do you remember the other children...
who came to my grandfather's studio?
Did you notice how they
disappeared, one by one?
You probably don't even remember
their names or their faces.
You only ever looked
at your own paintings.
Why?
They all grew to hate the art
they'd so loved because of you.
They couldn't even stand to look at...
a canvas or a pencil anymore.
It's my fault?
That's right.
No matter how hard I tried,
I couldn't measure up to you.
It makes me realize what
it means to have true talent.
After ten years, I was the only one left.
You'd swept them all away.
Unaware and apathetic,
you didn't care that
everyone had left.
I couldn't forgive you
for being that way.
I wished you'd just disappear...
that you'd go somewhere far away...
so I helped you become a manga artist.
I figured you deserved a life
of drawing boring manga,
and ruining your own reputation,
so you could understand
a little of what we felt.
But...
But why did you have
to make your debut?
Rita?
I want you to become the
world's most famous painter.
You could have at least
let me brag someday...
that I once studied at
the same studio with you.
I want to think I'm a part of you.
I want to believe I exist
inside your talent.
I'm sure Sorata doesn't
understand how I feel.
Did you get everything
off your chest, freeloader?
If you're done, budge.
You're in the way.
Thanks to you, we've lost
precious work time.
You could have just walked past me.
I hate women.
I avoid being near them
as much as humanly possible.
You recluse types with computerized
friends sure do think differently.
I trust computers,
and I am objectively aware
that I am a recluse.
If that was meant as an insult,
your mind is further gone
than I can possibly fathom.
Don't mock me!
I'm not mocking you.
I just think you're a coward.
Smiling those stupid fake smiles.
Imagine how we must feel...
looking at your depressing face.
How do you think I feel when I smile?
Creating art was my world!
Ever since I can remember,
I've always been told that
I would be a fantastic artist!
But my grandfather told
me to stop trying.
I could never outdo Mashiro
so I should just stop...
There was no point in
continuing to paint!
I know it's cowardly to cling to Mashiro...
even after being told that!
It's all Mashiro's fault.
It's her fault for existing!
I have one question.
Where was your will in that story?
What?
I understand that people around you...
had high expectations,
and you failed to meet them.
But you don't seem to have
explained what you want.
Why are you taking such
enjoyment from analyzing people?
You're a jerk!
Rita!
Rita-san!
Akasaka, let's go after her!
You go after her.
It'll be more effective.
You really shouldn't do that.
I'm sure I don't know what you mean.
Spouting your mouth off...
when you don't actually care...
what happens to other people!
Where did she go?
I don't know. We just have to look...
Rita hates me.
Shiina?
I didn't understand anything she said.
Sorata, do you understand?
Shiina, have you ever envied anyone?
Envied?
Have you ever thought
someone was great,
or someone was amazing,
or looked up to someone?
I don't know.
I see.
Kanda-kun!
I...
had a vague feeling
that Shiina was alone.
That no one could enter her world.
The other art students are
all curious about her,
but they keep their distance.
Shiina probably doesn't
have any close friends.
But you're different.
You reach Shiina.
Your words, your heart,
your very existence.
There's a lot she doesn't understand,
but I'm certain that you're
very important to her.
You really think so?
I think it's amazing you were
with her for ten years.
Any normal person would have run away.
A normal person looks away from
what they don't want to see.
Even if they know there are things...
they can only acquire if they
face the things they hate.
I want to become someone
who can do that.
Someone like you.
Did you come to console me?
At first, that was my intent, but...
What type of smile is that?
Probably still a fake one.
It looks like that boy knew
from the very beginning.
He's right, you know.
I've forgotten what I want to do.
I see.
I still think his personality stinks, though.
Making something with talented people...
like Shiina and Misaki-senpai is difficult.
It's difficult, but it's
also really exciting.
I learn things just watching them,
and watching an amazing
product take shape...
before my eyes is
an astonishing experience.
That's how you see things?
Don't you?
I didn't know.
You didn't know what?
I didn't know what you were thinking.
How about now?
I don't know.
I expected that.
That's just who you are.
I didn't notice at all.
That's what I don't like about you.
Because I had so much fun...
drawing next to you.
I felt like I wasn't alone
when I was with you.
I only needed you.
But I was the only one having fun...
That's... That's not true!
I had fun, as well!
Rita?
It wasn't just you. I had fun.
I kept creating art to this very day...
because I really enjoyed
painting with you.
Really?
It's true.
I wanted to keep creating
art with you forever.
But I always thought
you didn't even notice me.
When it crossed my mind
that it was only me...
who considered us
friends, I was afraid...
I couldn't help it!
Rita, thank you.
Mashiro... Mashiro...
Thank you for everything.
I want to keep creating art.
I want to take everything...
I did with you and make art.
The moments I spent with you...
are my most treasured.
Yes, I understand.
Mashiro, I'm sorry.
Rita, you should make your own art.
That's right.
Making something with
someone else is fun.
Sometimes it'll bring you down,
but that's only natural.
After all, I don't have
any skills or experience.
Rita and Shiina spent
ten years together.
She was overwhelmed by Shiina's talent,
but she kept trying hard.
Compared to her,
I've only known Shiina for half a year.
Getting depressed and
losing my confidence...
when nothing has happened
would be shameful of me.
It's okay. We can do it.
If the residents of Sakura
Hall work together,
we can create something amazing.
Shiina's not alone anymore.
We're all friends working
towards a common goal.
I'll do everything I possibly can.
So I can get just a little
closer to reaching Shiina...
Welcoming Rittan and Presenting Nyapollon
at the Culture Festival Celebration
After some minor delays,
let the "Welcoming Rittan...
and Presenting Nyapollon at the...
Culture Festival Celebration" begin!
Yeah! We did it, Rittan!
Thank you very much.
We did it, Nyapollon!
We should be thanking you.
With your help,
we won't have any reason...
to worry about our schedule.
I can't wait to see the final product.
I'll work hard on learning my lines.
Sorata, good job.
Look forward to it, Nanamin!
Th-Thanks. Why the mushroom?
I've prepared an ultra-cute cat suit!
A cat suit?
It's a gift.
You just didn't want it, did you?
I don't think I really
need to be here...
Ryunosuke.{
I'm sorry about the other day.
I spoke too rashly.
Acknowledging your
mistakes is a virtue.
I finally understand what
you were trying to say.
Sorata really does have
what I had forgotten.
Don't stand so close to me!
It's giving me the willies.
You really do hate girls, don't you?
I want to know what
kind of person you are.
K-Kanda! Change seats with me!
What's your problem?
Thanks for Coming!!
Sorata.
Huh?
I still haven't changed my mind.
I think Mashiro should paint
instead of drawing manga.
But I'll behave myself until
the culture festival.
I want to see Nyapollon
completed, as well.
Rita...
I love making art.
Thank you, Sorata.
Thank you, Mashiro.
The culture festival...
What a lively event.
#11 Milky Way Cat, Nyapollon
Girls from other schools come
and play with Suimei girls.
But this year's culture festival
will be difficult and energetic.