It's summer!
In preparation for the big event,
everyone's taking a
breather and kicking back.
The young people of Biscotti
got together for a summer training camp.
I really would've liked to go,
since Sink and Noir were there, too.
Meanwhile, what did we do in Galette
after welcoming our Hero, Nanami-chan?
Galette is a territory blessed
by the bounty of the sea.
Galette Sword Style Record!
The town today is peaceful as usual.
Noir is still in Biscotti, but...
Sorry I'm late.
All right, let's go eat!
Our Hero, Nanami-chan,
spends so much time with us.
Ugh, having all these meetings
back-to-back is exhausting.
Yeah, huh.
I really wish we could just
swing our swords and let loose.
Seriously.
Oh, Leo-sama. Gaul-sama.
What's up, Violet?
Is something wrong?
Yes.
A strange rumor has spread
here from the town.
Thank you.
Welcome.
A highwayman?
That's right.
That's what they've been saying.
By "highwayman," you mean...
people who rob you of everything,
even your clothes?
Yes. It's not really happening
around here, though,
but deeper in the
continent, around Ayase.
All the guests coming from Ayase
have been talking about it.
It's making a lot of people uneasy.
I see.
So the rumor is spreading
in town, as well...
Yes.
That's all everybody was talking
about at the Sea Dragon Inn.
I just confirmed it with Ayase's mayor.
Because the town has a
lot of protective power,
there were no fatalities
or serious injuries.
This is still armed robbery!
We can't just let this go.
I don't really like that
Noir isn't back yet,
but do you three
want to go check it
out with me, tonight?
Yes!
I'll go!
In that case...
Leo-sama. And you too, Gaul-sama!
You mustn't!
This whole thing will
blow out of proportion
if either of you two go out there.
Plus, Princess Millihiore is scheduled
to dine with us tonight!
I suppose you're right.
But we can't possibly let
them go on their own.
Then I'll lead the operation.
I guess, with that group,
we have nothing to worry about.
Still, I haven't been to
the Ayase region in a while.
Going out there wouldn't have been bad.
Yeah, huh.
So, Millihi and the others
should be here soon, right?
Yes.
I believe they are arriving right now.
Ayase is a town in the
eastern part of Galette.
The city was built by people
who were originally from the
various eastern countries,
and reflects the style
of their homelands.
I'll go visit the mayor.
Why don't you guys go talk
to the townspeople?
Sister, wait!
These are from Leo-sama.
What do you mean?
This is so Leo-sama!
When in Rome, dress
as the Romans dress!
Now we totally blend in with the locals!
It's perfect!
Why do I have to wear one, too?
Well then, let's start our investigation!
They say that if you walk
the roads at night,
a suspicious shadow will
come up behind you.
Then it'll say, "What a
beautiful kimono you have!"
And when you try to turn...
It goes, "Bam!"
Really?!
Yeah, they say that he'll take
your goods and your clothes.
It's horrible.
You can't walk the streets at night.
The highwayman got Yuuta's sister,
when she was coming home from an errand.
The red kimono they had just
made for her was stolen.
They don't let us play outside much anymore.
I see.
Pops, I left the money here.
Got it! Thanks!
He's not only a highwayman,
but a pervert who targets
kids and girls!
We've got to stop him.
I really want to find him!
Hey, I've got a good idea
for catching the perp.
That's good!
Nanami-chan?
What was your idea?
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I'll tell you after we've
met up with Violet-san.
That sounds good.
But first, let's have some
of those sweet dumplings.
Absolutely not!
I can't allow the Hero of our land
to become the bait for the investigation.
I know, but we're kind of famous,
and our ears and tails
are pretty flashy...
Nanami-chan doesn't
have that problem!
I said, "no."
Violet-san, please!
Everybody is scared, and the
kids can't play outside...
I just can't stand that!
I want to catch the perp
as soon as possible!
I'll be fine.
I have the Ex Machina and
Vert and Jau will be close by.
You won't give up, will you?
Fine.
I will respect our Hero's opinion.
Yay! Thank you, Violet-san!
You're so kind!
You're so wonderful!
See you tomorrow!
Bye-bye!
Thank you for your hard work.
Be careful on the streets at night.
It's not been too safe, lately.
Yes, thank you.
Nanami-chan's disguise is great.
Good. Let's scout the area
while we protect Nanami.
Yeah!
I guess it's almost
time for shift change.
Yeah.
A kid?
Pardon me,
young lady.
You mean me?
That's a nice kimono.
So it really was him?!
Wearing something like
that, at this hour,
is basically asking to be assaulted.
We found the perp! Vert!
Roger!
Huh?
Oops...
No, wait a second.
You're the thief who
keeps terrorizing Ayase!
Too bad you were not able
to see through my disguise!
Exactly!
We, the Lion Army's Investigation Unit,
have clearly seen your face!
Now, let us arrest you!
Sorry, we'll have to continue
this game another time.
Oh no!
We let him get away!
We have to chase him!
Just as I thought,
the real one has come out.
I wonder if I can handle this by myself.
Let's split up.
I'll go this way.
I'll go that way.
Then, I'll go this way!
No, it's not here.
Big sister...
That's a nice kimono.
Please give it to me.
Jau?!
Don't stop! It's behind you!
Seriously?!
Heavenly Draw...
Flying Heaven Wolf Fang Attack!
Do you get it now?
These are the real perps.
Little monsters who are
disguised as people.
Monster? These cute things?
There are probably more out there.
It's dangerous, so you
should go back to your inn.
Wh-Who are you?
Got it?
Take your friends and go home quickly!
Oh yeah, Jau and Vert!
Well, I'm sure those two
won't be defeated or...
They actually were.
We underestimated them.
I can sense them more clearly now.
There must be quite a
few out there, still.
Hey!
Excuse me!
We're sorry about before.
You are...
We're a Hero and bodyguard
team from Vannette.
We came here to investigate.
Oh, you're from the castle...
A Hero?
We want to assist you!
Our captain of the Imperial Guard
is also strengthening security
by directing the guards.
We will help you fight the monsters!
Okay. If that's the case,
let's work together.
These monsters, the Highwayman
Rabbits, move in packs.
They have a habit of gathering
the things their boss likes.
This time, it's girls' clothes!
They have a strong sense of camaraderie.
If one of them gets captured...
They'll come to rescue them!
Here they come!
Four of them!
Allow me to get you back
for what you did before!
Flak Arrows!
Jau, let's go!
I'm ready, Nanami!
One, two...
Tiger King Fist!
Boom.
That's four down.
That sound...
It's a huge monster!
It's headed towards
the city's main gate.
Understood. I will chase it.
I guess he saw no chance
and decided to run.
Violet-neesama is chasing it right now!
There it is.
Someone's there?!
You there! It's dangerous!
Please run!
There's no need to run, is there?
No, there isn't.
First, you invaded these people's city!
Second, you performed filthy thefts!
Third!
Bad kids who bother everybody face...
This Lion King Samurai and...
Me, the Dog Princess Samurai...
and will be vanquished!
Here we go, Dog Princess Samurai!
Yes, Lion King Samurai!
Run free, Blade of Judgment!
Illuminate the sky, Sword of Banishment!
Ex Grandia Finale!
Justice is served!
Th-They totally stole the show.
Leo-sama, Princess, that's not fair.
Oh jeez, those two...
Oh, you guys, it's fine now.
Okay.
Thank you, guys.
I captured all the heroic footage
of the Lion King Samurai
and the Dog Princess Samurai in here.
Perfect.
I guess they're done over there.
Looks like it.
Noir!
Well, I'll be on my way, then...
Huh?
No, no, please wait.
At least tell us your name.
Oh, I'm not really...
Isuka-sama!
I knew it, it's you!
Yuki-pup!
Yes, Isuka-sama.
It's been a long time!
Yeah.
I rushed over here when I sensed
that some monsters might be loose here,
but I guess you guys are all okay?
Yeah.
Yuki, who's that?
Jeez.
I was wondering who caused this ruckus.
Should have known it was you, brother.
Bro...
...ther?
Hina! Oh, you came, too?
I-I told you not to call me that!
Oh, let me introduce you.
This is Isuka-sama.
Hello.
He's actually milady's older brother.
He's a foolish brother...
A counter-monster swordsman,
just like Brioche,
and a world famous swordsmith...
Isuka Makishima-san really
is an amazing person!
He's already crafted
many wonderful swords
and blades that are on par
with the Treasure Swords.
No no, I am just a simple
wandering swordsmith.
It's fine that you're wandering,
but what were you thinking,
never sending a note?
I thought you had died
in some random ditch.
You're so silly, Hina.
Like I would die so easily.
Actually, I hope you're not
ruining your body
by drinking too much.
You're one to talk.
You drink way more than I do.
We solved this case,
so I don't think anyone could
object to some booze at the
rare reunion of these two.
Nanami-san, you guys must be hungry, right?
Let's have some food, then!
Yay!
Hey, Sink.
The monsters we catch...
you release them in the mountains, right?
Yes, in a location far
from the settlements.
Well, those are really
more like wild animals,
rather than monsters.
If coexisting is possible,
that's the best solution.
I see; that's good.
Apparently, they were able to reclaim
all the stolen clothes
from the monsters' nests.
Yes.
All is well, then.
I feel like I wasn't able to do
anything heroic at all, this time...
Oh well, it was a nice Monster Riot.
And thus...
Case closed.
Yes, yes, yes!
Perfect!
The welcoming plan is perfect, now!
Yeah! Let's surprise the
Princess and Leo-sama!
Of course!
We are ready to welcome both sides!
For the pride of Pastillage!
Together we are...
The Princess Samurais!
Don't you think I got
too little screen time?
Don't worry about it!
Pastillage's Hero King Legend
You've got fun company, Hina.
I told you to stop!