Tsuritama Episode 5
Discouraged Jerking
Summer vacation started.
I see.
I figured you'd want one.
Yeah.
Just looking at them
made me want my own.
You're gonna buy your own pole, Yuki?
Besides, I figured we shouldn't be
borrowing poles
from Misaki-san forever.
It's okay. Misaki's nice!
I don't think she's bothered by that,
but I guess you would want your own.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll get one, too.
I understand. I was like that once, too.
I didn't really get into fishing
until I bought my own gear.
But they're pretty expensive.
There's actually a wide range,
but if you're going to buy one,
you might as well get something good.
Good point.
But I don't have any money.
We're waiting for your
smile
}Help Wanted!!
Yeah.
Yup.
Thank you very much.
Let's just go see what they have.
Where's the captain today?
He's not here yet.
I see.
We'll start with rods.
If you're looking for a rod, I'd
recommend one of these over here.
How about this one?
There's no paint coating,
so it's pretty light.
They call it unsanded.
This one.
That one, huh?
Lunamis S900ML.
Not a bad choice for an amateur.
The Lunamis is made primarily
for catching sea bass.
It's a middle-grade rod.
The amazing thing about this rod is,
Try swinging it.
Okay.
compared to a top-grade rod,
it performs almost exactly the same way.
It's so light. This thing's great.
With the surprising power
and feel of a Spiral X
and Hyperpower X along with
Shinoma's unique construction,
Isn't it?
Yuki, hold the rod like that.
it's got a light and tangle-proof chitin frame K-guide,
You should be able to tell
the difference in rigidity
and flexibility compared to
the rod you've been using.
as well as a lightweight yet strong
Sea Eye Four-based reel seat.
You're right. This is different!
At 37,500 yen, I think it's a steal.
And if you're buying that
rod, I recommend this reel.
Twin Power C3000HG.
Well, I prefer a Stella.
This reel's got a reasonable price
considering its high specs.
If the Stella is every fisherman's
true love or princess,
this would be the schoolyard's Madonna.
In other words, high school
kids like you can afford it.
I want it!
Yuki, you seem happy.
What are you looking at?
A hundred thousand?!
Yeah. A Rod and reel,
plus lures, fishing wear,
and everything else comes
out to around that price.
Well, if you're really serious about it,
you'll end up spending about that much.
I don't have that much money.
It's hot out.
Hot, hot.
Welcome.
Hello.
Hey, Natsuki. It's so hot
you could melt, isn't it?
I'm melting.
Haru, is it hot on your planet, too?
No, it's super cool.
He knows about Haru?
I'm jealous, you jerk.
Did you hear that, Misaki-san?
Doesn't it sound great?
I bet it's the perfect place
for a summer vacation.
And you, Indian.
Take off your turban when
you're in the store.
It's making me hot just looking at it.
Who is he?
Hey, boy, catch anything?
Misaki-san, the usual.
Okay. Hot tea, coming right up.
That's the captain.
Captain?
He's like my older brother.
He's a good guy.
Yeah. Ayumi-chan's a great guy.
Even if you can't work in a
store, you could probably fish.
Fish?
Natsuki, we don't make
any money by fishing.
But you can.
Captain.
What?
Could you let the three
of us work this year?
Huh? What'd you say?
This summer vacation, I was hoping
you'd let the three of us
work on your fishing boat.
Work on a fishing boat? You can do that?
He's staring me down!
What is this, an interview?
What am I gonna do? Should I smile?
Please, Captain.
He's serious about fishing and
desperately wants his own gear.
I can't do it!
Okay, you pass!
What?
We pass!
That's great.
Thanks, Captain.
You start tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Thank you.
Thanks!
You'll be all right.
Three days on my boat and you'll
be a real man of the sea.
A man of the sea? Me?
Way to go, Ayumi-chan.
We knew we could count on you.
Excuse me.
All right!
The god of love must
be smiling down on me!
This is great, Yuki.
Thank you, Benten-sama!
A job?
Yeah, you do work and get paid.
I know that, but will it
make him better at fishing?
It's a boat. He'll fish
all day, every day.
Well, as long as Yuki
gets better at fishing.
Enoshima bowl!
Sorry, Koko.
I was just feeling a little
dried out, so it's fine.
But don't go too far out, Nii-chan
If he's out there, you'll be in trouble.
He?
Who are they talking about?
I thought they just wanted to fish.
Top Secret
Bermuda Syndrome refers
to the strange events
occurring in the triangular
region of the ocean
between Florida, Puerto Rico, and the
I have no choice.
Bermuda Islands known
as the Bermuda Triangle.
I must go with them.
Marine vessels and aircrafts
disappear without a trace.
In the moments before they disappear,
No. This is my job.
their compasses and other
instruments behave strangely...
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Look at that summer sun.
It's a perfect day for mahi-mahi.
"Seishunmaru"
I wanna catch some mahi-mahi!
Yuki.
Mahi-mahi are huge.
Some of them are almost two meters long.
That big?
Catching them isn't that hard,
but they're well known for their violent strength.
I see.
They're pretty, too.
When they get excited,
their colors change.
Really? I hope I catch one.
What are you doing here?
Fishing, of course.
I look forward to fishing with you.
Look, Yuki. The ocean's beautiful!
It really is. I'm glad I came.
Do boats always rock this much?
Yuki, Haru, get the nets!
What?
Why is Natsuki so calm?
Nets, nets, nets, nets, nets!
I should go, too.
Watch out!
Ten out of ten!
No problem!
There's no way I can do this!
Natsuki, no fair. You're fishing.
No, I'm instructing.
Instructing?
On how to catch mahi-mahi.
It's my job to catch the first one.
Once you get one, the rest
of them will follow.
Then all the customers will
be able to catch one.
I see.
Natsuki, those glasses are weird.
These are polarized glasses.
With them, I can see the
fish under the water.
Those sound great! Let me use them!
Later.
If one of the customers catches one,
get the net out right away.
What do you do when you
catch something big?
Perpendicular.
That's right. If you pull
parallel, it'll break.
You too, Yuki.
Got one!
It's beautiful!
He's right!
Cast away!
Kid, the net!
Okay.
Kid, over here!
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Yuki!
It's so heavy!
Crap!
What are you doing?
S-So...
Why are you so angry?
You're the one who screwed up!
Why are you making that face?
I'm so-
I'm sorry.
We'll get the next one.
Make sure you get the next one, kid.
But look at this guy's face.
What are you, a stone fish?
Stone fish.
Stone fish. Stone fish!
Yuki, you're a stone fish!
That was an old one.
Don't worry about it.
Fish!
Fish, fish, fish!
Fish, fish!
You're...
surprisingly into this.
Good job on your first day.
Good work.
Now it's time for the paychecks
you've been waiting for!
Happy!
What's wrong, Yuki?
Yuki, why?
If you don't have money,
you can't buy a pole.
It's okay, Yuki.
It was just the first day.
But...
Just take it.
What are you doing?
Don't worry about it.
We need to get going.
But Yuki's not...
Haru, why didn't he come with you?
Yuki told me to go on ahead.
Isn't it time to go?
You're here again?
Yuki's still not here.
There's no reason to wait.
You don't understand, do you?
There's no way he could
come after embarrassing
himself in front of everyone.
You're the one who doesn't understand.
Yuki will be here.
He won't let something
like that get him down.
We'll see.
You don't have any friends, do you?
He's here.
Sorry.
You were fixing that?
Yeah.
Let's go!
Mahi-mahi gather in currents
with driftwood and jetsam.
Aim for those areas when you cast.
Then bait them to you by jerking
your lure back and forth.
Got one!
Once you've got him,
raise your pole and reel in.
If tries to run, wait him out.
When he stops, reel him in.
Keep doing that and wait for
him to tire himself out.
Come on!
Amazing!
Cast away!
Natsuki's so cool.
I want to fish, too!
Yuki!
You're standing!
Huh? What?
Kid, could I get a net?
Yes.
Yuki, perpendicular!
Perpendicular, perpendicular,
perpendicular!
I did it!
Good work.
Hey, Yuki.
Why were you suddenly
able to stand today?
I don't know.
I was just watching Natsuki
catch a mahi-mahi,
and before I knew it...
That's amazing!
Did you hear that, Keito?
What? Yes, yes, yes.
Of course.
She says you were probably able
to stand because you love fishing.
I see you smiling, Yuki!
Just eat your food!
Drinks, drinks.
Yuki.
I can't do this!
You said you'd do it.
Yeah, but...
Yuki, I can see them.
Fish, fish.
I can see them! There's tons of them!
Mahi-mahi.
Enoshima bowl!
Don't be scared!
Even if you cast too far,
you can always reel it in!
Okay.
Is that kid okay?
He's fine.
Well, Yuki? Fun, isn't it?
Then smile.
The mahi-mahi are smiling, too.
Enoshima bowl!
All right!
Bait them by jerking the
lure back and forth.
Come on, come on.
Got one!
Raise the pole and reel in.
Wait him out when he runs.
Reel him in when he stops running.
He's huge!
Amazing, amazing, amazing!
Amazing, amazing, amazing,
amazing, amazing!
Got it!
Cast away.
What'd you say?
Say it louder.
Cast away!
Catch as many as you can!
Good work!
Here.
Thank you very much!
See? You're a man of the sea, now.
Ow, ow. That hurts.
Tapioca, let's go.
No, I'm fine.
I don't need friends now.
That summer...
Good morning, Tamocchan!
Hey.
I changed.
Good morning!
Yeah!
I finally found something
I was really interested in.
They're already practicing.
What?
The Enoshima dance.
I always had friends by my side.
And I even surprised myself...
Enoshima bowl!
They took it!
by how loudly...
Cast away!
I learned to laugh.
Continued in #6