Serara, the girl we saved in Susukino,
belongs to Marielle's guild,
the Crescent Moon Alliance.
A guild is a team comprised of many players.
Guilds offer many advantages that parties,
which are more provisional, don't have.
For example, a shared vault in the game's bank,
and a dedicated communication system.
And most important, potential use of a guild hall,
located here, at the Guild Building.
These halls can be purchased or rented,
and are divided into several ranks.
Normally, you select a hall
based on your guild's size.
The Crescent Moon Alliance uses what's known
as a rank-B hall, consisting of seven rooms.
Welcome home, Serara!
For them, the size is exactly right.
Making the food without using
commands is more difficult,
but it's worth it.
This smell... This perfectly charred color...
I remember this!
It's food!
You're going to make it too salty.
I still can't do it!
To make difficult foods,
you need a high cooking skill.
And even if two people with the same
level use the same ingredients,
their dishes can still taste different.
It's no different than in our old world.
Serara's working hard.
Even though this party is for her...
Resolve
Resolve.
Listen, kid.
Your level isn't what's important.
It's what comes after that.
What comes after my level?
Secret techniques?!
I mean panties.
Pa—
What are you talking about?
Nothing much, just p—
Powerful monsters! About powerful monsters...
Marielle?
Coming!
Don't tell anyone?
We shouldn't let our rivals learn
about this food for a while.
Why? It's a big deal!
It's too big a deal.
If people suddenly find out,
it could cause problems.
That's what Shiroe said.
Thank you for your help.
I-It was nothing...
Everyone's grateful!
Let's have a toast!
I'm so happy!
Not just Ashlin, but Akatsuki, too!
Wh-What are you going to do?
Ashlin...
Right!
Today, we have three types
of summer dress for you.
I am my lord's personal ninja!
I couldn't wear such frivolous things!
Shiroe's given his permission.
Now, just give up...
Y-You sold me out, my lord!
You sold me out!
Marie, I...
We'll have a lot of cleaning tomorrow.
Are you going to sleep, too?
I'm not that tired.
Then shall I make some tea?
You really helped us this time.
Thank you.
It's fine, really.
I didn't do anything too big.
If it wasn't big, then what would be?
While I was away, what's happened here?
Here? You mean in Akihabara?
I think it's better than it was.
There is far less PKing, and it's a little safer.
But...
I couldn't say exactly why, but there's
something unpleasant in the air.
It's like, well... Like everyone
has fallen into ranks.
Ranks?
We're a small guild, with fewer
than thirty members, right?
We have four level 90s,
while most are under 50.
But the biggest guilds...
For example, have you heard
of D.D.D., Crusty's guild?
The raid guild that beat Oracle's Tower, right?
The Legion Raid that they said the
Japanese couldn't have beaten...
Yeah.
A raid like that can have hundred-player fights.
Supposedly, they have over 1,500 members,
including plenty of level 90s.
Then, by "rank," you meant the guilds?
It feels as though
the bigger guilds are determining
the town's feel and its rules.
For example, who has priority using the market.
I had no idea.
It's the same way with the hunting grounds.
Since the strong and weak guilds were divided,
the weak guilds will no longer approach
the stronger guilds' territories.
Then the larger guilds have
taken all the good hunting spots?
You can't fight in the town, of course.
But that doesn't mean you can
clash in the hunting areas.
Well, it means there's less PKing, which is good.
But that's still...
Somehow, I don't like it...
I understand what you mean.
It isn't just the hunting grounds.
Invisible barriers are being erected everywhere.
I think that's what they mean
by the guilds falling into ranks.
No one's to blame.
And I'm sure the large guilds
have their own problems.
No laws or ethics prohibit people from
using whatever strategy they can
to give themselves an edge in this world.
But still...
It isn't a good thing.
Though perhaps it's a matter of preference.
That's true.
A few days ago...
But even if we try to oppose the bigger guilds...
That's why we're trying to think of a way.
For example, we could share the
hunting grounds among ourselves.
...many small guilds that know each other well
discussed the possibility of
creating a joint council.
But each of the small guilds has its own opinions.
We ended up quarreling over minor
differences of opinion and selfish requests...
W-Wait...
Why don't we talk about this a bit more?
It's a waste of time.
Bye!
I'm sorry.
I wanted to help, but...
I knew this wouldn't work.
Further,
the Black Sword Knights and the
Silver Sword are aiming for 91.
91?
The old level cap was 90,
but with the expansion...
Yeah.
With The Novasphere Pioneers expansion,
the level cap was raised to 100,
wasn't it?
And since no new players have
entered since the Apocalypse...
Oh, I see...
Because of the limit on how
many you can allow to join...
The Black Sword Knights have always
had a thing about being the best.
Their guild master, Isaac, is proud...
Or maybe just enjoys excluding others...
He won't allow anyone below 85 to join.
So he isn't in the position D.D.D. was,
where he can just start absorbing
a bunch of smaller guilds.
He's trying to fight quantity with quality, then?
But...
At a bare minimum, they'd need
to hunt for level-85 monsters.
But this isn't the same as the game...
Isn't that pretty dangerous?
It would be if they did it the normal way.
They're using EXP pots.
EXP pots?
Do you mean they're leveling up by cheating?
EXP pots...
Items that slightly increase attack
power and health regeneration.
And they double experience earned from combat.
Death
One of these potions
was freely distributed to every
player below level 30 once a day,
so new players could level up and
start enjoying the game more quickly.
After the Apocalypse,
a guild called Hamelin gathered new players,
claiming they wanted to help them.
But they're selling their EXP pots
to large guilds that want to raise their levels.
It's all starting to go wrong.
This town... This world...
Who's at fault?
No, to a greater or lesser degree, everyone is.
Including me, since I'm not doing anything.
That's right...
I only went to Susukino
to vent some of my frustration
at the way things are going.
Thinking again?
There's nothing wrong with thinking.
But you're smart enough, so why
not just solve the problem?
But what can I do?
I don't even have a guild...
I don't have a guild...
is it?
Tohya
Hamelin
Minori
Shigeru
Honesty
Crusty
D.D.D.
That's just an excuse to run away...
Can't sleep?
No.
Yeah, I'm too tired to sleep...
Your brother helped me out yesterday.
Tohya did?
He's a good guy.
Kind, cheerful, and hard-working.
He's just empty-headed.
You two seem to really get along.
When this world was still a game,
you two would form a party and
adventure together, right?
Yeah.
Tohya...
Tohya wanted to play.
All the old guilds that invited me
just wanted to take advantage of
my status as a veteran player.
I hated it, and that's why...
No, that isn't it.
It wasn't all bad, having people rely on me.
I wish our guild master had
a better grasp of things.
Our guild's done for...
But when a lot of people get together,
lip service isn't enough to get
by anymore. And I hated that.
No...
I knew all that going in...
A guild... A guild?
Do you still not like guilds, Shiroe?
Chief...
Meow.
To be honest, I don't really know anymore.
The more I think about why I didn't like guilds,
the more haughty and childish I seem.
It's true that the system itself
makes it easy for guilds to go rotten.
So I can understand why you'd want
to keep your distance from that.
But if there were a thing that never went
bad, I don't know that I'd trust it.
Any kind of life can go wrong, or sicken, or suffer.
Lives get old, decay, and finally die.
Disliking that fact because it hurts isn't
any different than disliking life itself.
I know you realize this.
For example, our old place,
the Tea Party, was a wonderful place...
But the reason was because everyone
worked to make it that way.
Any treasure you attain without anyone
ever working is no treasure at all.
He's right.
The Tea Party and the Crescent Moon Alliance...
In both, there was someone hard
at work behind the scenes...
Chief, what should I do?
The most amazing thing that you can.
Amazing?
You hold back too often.
I don't think you need to feel
so bound by duty all the time.
I mean, there's no need to hold back!
I've kept you waiting?
That's right.
Both of you were waiting for me?
Instead of going elsewhere,
you stayed with me.
That's right.
Oh, a message...
Shiroe
Um, hello.
Do you remember me?
It's Shiroe.
This is Minori, right?
Yes.
Listen carefully, Minori...
Cough softly once for yes.
Twice for no.
Three times if you want to say something.
Got it?
Shiroe knows what's happening to us now...
Cough once if you understand.
You're both in Hamelin, right?
And you're giving your EXP pots to Hamelin?
Are you okay?
Really?
You want to say something?
I did tell you to cough three times
if you had something to say.
All right, I'll hurry, so I can hear it.
For now, I'll believe you're okay.
So believe in me, too, all right?
I'll come to rescue you.
Got it?
Hey! Shiro!
My lord, don't worry me.
If you're leaving, say something.
That's right.
What...
Those two have been waiting
for my words.
This time, I'd like your help with something.
Our help?
Anything you need, Shiroe!
That's right.
The Crescent Moon Alliance owes you much.
Well?
Some twins I know are being held captive...
Or rather, being forced to stay in a nasty guild.
I'd like to save them.
I see...
So you just need them to quit the guild, right?
We could draw them off...
Um...
This guild you're talking about...
This guild supposedly gathers new
players and takes their EXP pots.
Hamelin...
I think it's time they left.
W-Wait a second...
Do you mean you'll destroy them?
No, I mean exactly what I said.
I'm going to have them leave Akihabara.
Shiro, I understand how you feel...
But we...
I'm sorry, but please let me finish.
This is only the first part.
Hamelin's just a small portion of this.
To be honest, I don't really like the
way Akihabara feels right now.
It's petty, pathetic, and cheap.
That's why
I'm going to clean the place up.
Akihabara is our hometown.
It's the largest city on the Japanese server.
And it's sad, unpleasant, frail...
Everyone walks with their heads down...
It's as if our only purpose in
life were to be pathetic.
We number thirty thousand.
But that also means there are
only thirty thousand of us.
I think everyone's been underestimating
this world far too much.
We aren't nearly desperate enough.
I...
Please help me.
Shiro...
Guild master...
Could we at least hear him out?
For a long time, I've been feeling the same way.
Shouryuu...
How would you do it?
It depends on your plan.
Tell us.
And we'll decide if it's something
we can help you with.
I need money.
For now,
five million gold.
F-Five million...
M-Money?
That's insane!
Our treasury only has sixty thousand.
Even if we included all our members' belongings...
What would you use all that money for?
The money isn't that important.
It's only the start.
The real problem comes after.
I need everyone's hope and goodwill.
I believe that more people
like this town than hate it.
The more people who want to
save it, the more likely it is
that we can win.
So I'll say it again.
Lend your assistance to me.
To me... And to my guild.
Shiro, did you just say "guild"?
"My guild"?
Yes.
Then you made one?
I'm sorry, since you've invited me.
No, it's nothing to apologize for...
I see.
Congratulations, Shiro.
So you managed to make one...
You made a home...
What's it called, Shiroe?
What's the guild's name?
Ah, right...
Its name is...
Log Horizon.
Fragrant scents are in the air...
Juicy meat... Crisp, fresh lettuce.
And tomato with a touch of sourness.
The sweetness of lightly toasted
bread and smooth butter.
Topped off with spicy mustard.
This is called the Crescent Burger.
On sale today, for just 50 gold.
Next time: Crescent Moon.
Crescent Moon
This is our reality.