"Act 5
Bring Back Love"
--Damn it!
--Search thoroughly!
They are not here.
There is nobody here either.
The place is completely empty!
What the hell is going on?!
Commander, please come and look.
What is it?!
The well...
Wh-What is this smell?!
It's shit.
It looks like the Elves threw shit into the well.
There's also something strange...
What?!
Sir. The soil underneath the toilet's
subfloor was dug up and it's gone.
How the hell did that happen?!
Is this Elven magic?
What is going on?!
Where did they disappear to?!
What is happening?!
I am going to kill all of them tonight.
I will take everyone's head.
Altogether, we took twenty blades
and sets of armor from the dead.
We also took two horses from them,
but the Elves don't know how to ride.
We'll utilize the horses according to my plan.
The armor is not our primary concern.
More importantly, only a few of them
know how to wield a sword.
On the other hand, they are strangely
infatuated with making bows.
I have Yoichi helping them
create bows as we speak.
In a way... they look happy
making bows and arrows.
They are as quick and efficient
as skilled craftsmen.
More pressing than the sword issue is...
...our need for spears. The length of spears
would relieve some of their fears.
Even peasants could kill samurai
with a twenty-foot-long spear.
You probably don't know about this,
but Akechi Mitsuhide was killed while hunting
down the routed peasant militia in Fushimi.
Huh? Seriously?!
All right! Good for Kumquat Head.
Well done, peasants of Fushimi!
I exempt them from tax for a million years.
By the way, you look like you're
having a great time conspiring.
A battle is only the consequence
of matters built up in the past.
I believe that the true contest lies in choosing
our actions well before the dawn of battle.
Nobody besides Hideyoshi could
understand this essence of battle.
No wonder we didn't see any
corpses of soldiers in the village.
They've been bringing them here!
Pick whichever you like, though there
are still some blood stains on them.
Eh?
You, the chosen ones,
may wash them yourselves.
Ugh! They are covered with blood.
--How many are they?
--What are we going to do?
It'd probably be best not to tell them
what we did to the corpses.
Toyohisa cut off all the soldiers'
heads and buried them, but...
...as for their bodies, Nobunaga...
You paid your respects to the dead heads
and made offerings, didn't you?
We shall gratefully use their bodies.
Smells horrible.
Is this a saltpeter mound?
I mixed corpses with
grass, soil, feces, and urine.
It will be another two years
before saltpeter can be collected.
This was the trick the Ikko sect
followers used to employ.
The villagers should be prohibited
from entering this hill...
...to prevent an epidemic.
What should we do with
the soil from the toilets?
We have charcoal, but not sulfur.
Just leave it as it is for now.
It's terrible... to do that to their corpses!
What's wrong with it? The outcome would
be the same even if we buried them.
They would rot, get eaten by bugs,
and eventually break down into soil.
We're just speeding up the process.
It's the same thing.
We don't want to be wasteful.
I cleaned up those heads, put them
back together, and buried them.
I made offerings to them as human beings.
If you want to pay respect to them,
that mound is good enough.
You may think shit and urine are nasty.
But if you and I cut open our bellies,
the inside would just be flesh filled with shit.
Could the soul dwell within
a body filled with shit...
...instead of in a head to which we pay respect?
That wouldn't be logical, would it?
I see. The clear differences
between these men and us lie...
...not in knowledge, technology, or culture...
...but in their views on life and death.
Hey, Olmi-Boobs.
Why do you always get the last
part of my name mixed up?
I can't be bothered to get
upset about this anymore.
"Mutter, mutter, mutter"
There is this stinky yellow stuff
found near a volcano.
It is almost like a powdery form of fart...
called sulfur. Are you able to get a hold of it?
Eh? Sulfur? Well, I think I can manage that,
but what are you going to do with it?
Don't worry about that.
Just bring me a lot of it.
Ask your something organization...
Whatever you call it.
--What?!
--Boobienu Organization or something!
It's called Octobrist.
Well, I'm afraid it will cost you.
Do you have money?
Shut up, you damn Boobienu Organization!
After we claim five or six states, I'll pay you.
Just shut up and bring it to me, you fool!
Soil from toilets, corpses, sulfur...
What is he going to do with them?!
I don't get it at all!
Wow, that's excellent!
Look! Almost a bull's-eye.
All right! I want to try it, too.
Amazing! They are learning too quickly.
We are natural-born archers,
but we'd been prohibited from making
or even touching bows for a long time.
We used to practice shooting
as children before the war.
I can't let them beat me.
Ha.
Wow!
Okay. Okay. We get it.
I don't know what's going on, but...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I apologize.
We totally get it. You are
number one! You are the best!
You're wasting arrows. Please stop!
We are now going to invade the village.
Don't let anyone leave alive.
Taking back the village is
not the end of this mission.
From there, we'll march
into the lord's castle, and...
...take his head.
Wh-What?!
These two told me the reason...
...why there are no women left in the village.
We Elves can reproduce only once a year.
During that time, all the young women
were taken by the lord and his men.
I see. That's the reason.
Their intention is to drive
your race... to extinction.
Take back your wives and children.
Stop living like animals.
Go take the heads of the men who
reduce you to nothing more than livestock.
If right and wrong exists
in this world, this is right.
Even if you are killed, you can face your
forefathers in the next world and say...
"We died fighting."
"We died protecting our family."
Take back your wives.
Take back your children.
Reclaim your state!
Reclaim yourselves!
This man is a natural-born warrior.
He has the abilities required
of a warlord, not a ruler.
What he has is the power
to impel people to fight.
A zealous determination.
Where did the Elves disappear to?
I don't know.
I've been told we're going to the surrounding
villages to search for them tomorrow.
If any village harbors them,
are we supposed to destroy it, too?
Maybe...
I'm thirsty.
Bear with it. We can't get water from the well.
They threw shit into it. Damn Long Ears.
We should just slaughter all those bastards...!
What the...?! What the hell is happening?!
"Toyohisa Assults Orte's Troops"
--What the hell is going on?!
--It's the east side of the village!
Dr-Drifters...
Ready? Come at me!
D-Don't let him get away. After him!
As I suspected, the Drifters are behind this.
No matter what it takes, capture him!
--Get him!
--Don't let him get away!
Let's do this. It has begun.
Everyone ready?
"Battle Plan"
In battle, it's speed... that matters most.
Move as I told you.
Don't worry so much.
Even if you mess up, you'll only die.
Run!
I used to lead an army composed of over
200,000 soldiers, and this is how I ended up.
This existence is intriguing...
I can't get enough of it.
After him!
What are you doing?!
We're going against only one man.
Close in on him and attack him!
Yes, sir!
What the...?! What the hell is he?!
He is smiling.
What the...?!
Unleash the horses!
Begin working!
Get it as tight as possible!
Hurry up!
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry up! Get a move on!
You will die!
Everyone will die! Hurry up!
Ready the fire arrows!
This is it. Say goodbye to your village.
Steel yourselves!
This is your farewell to the
village that restrained you,
and a goodbye to your lives as serfs.
Release!
What the...?! What is happening?!
The Owari soldiers in
my hometown were weak...
...which became problematic.
I constantly tried to
come up with measures...
...that would make up for their weakness.
I've never even thought about
copying that monkey, Hideyoshi.
This is my Sunomata Castle.
Draw!
All right! Now, release!
Orte is currently engaged in war, isn't it?
That means these soldiers here
are only third-class crap.
That explains their poor skills and low morale.
There's no way they will fight till they break.
No need to crush the entire army.
If we destroy 10 or 20 percent--
30 to 40 soldiers--they will fall apart.
They will scatter.
They won't gain any glory
fighting against serfs.
If they are defeated, they die in vain.
What a pity.
Furthermore, all we need to do is to
graze them. It is a good opening gambit.
It's an easy fight.
What the hell are you doing?
Reorganize the formations!
If you charge all at once, that crappy
barricade should drop like nothing.
Sh-Shit! They coated the arrows with shit.
What the...?! Water! Wash yourself
with water. Or else you could get tetanus.
Water... There is no water!
They threw shit into the well.
Our water ration is almost gone...
Th-They planned this from the beginning...
It was for this reason that
they threw shit into the well.
The entire village was a trap!
It was a trap.
The village... The village
was not really abandoned!
Take aim!
Shoot!
What the hell?!
Don't panic! We overwhelmingly
outnumber them.
If we can close in on them...
What a cry! It sounds just
like a monkey's yelling.
That's no human battle cry.
I'm going to take the commander's head.
You wouldn't mind if your head
became my trophy...
...would you?
Wh-What?! What the...?!
Got it!
This man... Toyohisa...
He found the perfect time to attack, take the
commander's head, and destroy the army.
It seems he is a natural-born fighter.
W-We... won!
We won!
We did it! We won!
We did it...
Not so fast!
It's not over yet!
I told you we would
take down the lord's castle.
You kept saying, "take down,"
but do you have a plan for that?
--Nope.
--Ahh... As I thought.
When you attack an enemy, you need to keep
after them till you crush the root of their power.
I was taught to attack them
until we destroy them all.
That was the teaching of my father,
my uncle, my other uncles,
my grandfather, and my great-grandfather.
Your entire clan is moronic.
As I thought, you were a bunch of freaks.
What did you say?!
Calm down. I have an idea.
Besides, the soldiers who ran...
...should be experiencing hell by now.
Damn it! We've been scattered.
Shit! They did it again! It's a trap!
They coated it with shit again...
Damn bastards!
--Run!
--Shit!
This is just like him. Such... Such tactics...
Such conduct is against
warrior code. It's unfair, isn't it?!
Unfair? Warrior code?
What is unfairness?
There is no injustice or code
of honor on the battlefield.
You are naïve, Yoichi.
The Taira clan, the Minamoto clan, and my
stupid brothers in Kamakura are all credulous.
Don't ask anything else. Just do as I say.
Forget it!
Forget about him!
Forget about that monster!
All right. Is everyone here?!
Where are they?!
Not even a single soldier has been back yet!
They haven't even checked in.
As I suspected, the Elves didn't just flee
the village! It wasn't simple civil unrest.
Even so, we've sent out most
of the soldiers stationed here.
Do you think that was the right move?
The status of the mainland war
continues to deteriorate.
We've been oppressing demihumans
in all our occupied territories.
It is only a matter of time before not only
the Elves but also the others explode in anger!
We'll get bogged down if
we keep sending small forces.
We must crush them all at once
through shock and awe.
Before rebellion spreads among
the Elves throughout the territories,
we must destroy one or two of their
villages just to teach them a lesson.
If necessary, we may have to
hang our female Elf hostages.
Lord...
The soldiers... The soldiers have just returned.
Ohh... Perfect! They're finally back!
Open the gate! Open the gate!
Reporting on the ongoing status of our troops!
The main subjugation force is currently
on patrol, continuing their assignment!
Request to open the gate!
Ready? Smile.
Keep walking. Keep smiling. Don't run.
Slowly... Slowly.
Report. Report to me.
How was it? Was it a rebellion, as we thought?!
Uh-huh... Therefore...
Drifters... Elves...!
We will be taking over.
Wh...
It's hot!
It was too bulky!
Where are those women confined?
The tower. They are inside the tower.
Let's go.
What happened to the soldiers?!
My... My soldiers?!
Ahh, them? Well...
I'm sorry, but most of them are dead.
And as for the rest, Yoichi is
hunting them down in the forest.
But don't worry.
In the end, you'll be with them,
mixed with soil and shit,
and I'll make sure you
reincarnate into black powder.
What the hell?!
I surrender!
I surrender to you!
This...
Wh-Why?
He already laid down his sword.
Whether you kill your enemy
should depend on their actions.
It would be a shame to take
the head of one who surrendered!
Even so... But we--
It would be a disgrace!
Saving the women is our priority right now.
Ready?
Let's go.
Yeah.
Wh-What the hell?!
I was wrong.
These pieces of shit in this castle are a blight!
I will carve them up...
...tear them out by the roots...
...and slaughter them all.
"Purge"
"Virgin"
"Black Powder"
"Act 6
Men of Destiny"