Hopes and dreams are the
power that moves humanity,
and keep the Earth turning!
Tomorrow doesn't come because
the sun rises in the morning!
The sun rises in the morning
because people keep their
hopes close to their hearts!
We keep the Earth turning!
We are the passionate heroes,
the Gambaraijers!
Thank you.
Why...
Coffee?
Sure.
So bitter...
How did Mom write songs?
Huh?
How?
The normal way?
She'd sing, and then sing...
Was the melody already in her head?
Or did it come as she went along?
I mean, a cat could
put a song together
if all the parts were already
floating around in its head.
But is that really all there is to it?
There must be more!
Sorry, I'm only an expert at listening...
But I don't think you
need to force it.
Take your time.
You're probably right.
Maybe I should talk to Shiho-san.
They went to school together, after all.
Oh, right.
That's a good idea.
Episode 9
Turning White and Turning Red
There are other jobs out
there that involve horses.
Like?
Training.
There's no weight limit for that?
You're so insensitive.
Ow.
My weight's not an issue.
I just can't picture
myself being happy with
other people riding
the horses I raised.
That's understandable.
Sorry I'm late, folks.
I have an announcement!
For the upcoming White Festival,
our very own choir club...
And sometimes badminton club.
Musical Drama
...will perform a musical drama!
A musical drama?
That's right.
Obviously, singing is our top priority,
but I want to include a solid story, dancing,
great costumes, and a real stage!
Who'll do what?
And how?
I'll be the scriptwriter.
And Wakana's already
writing a song, right?
We can use that
as our featured piece!
What?
You're writing a song?
That's amazing!
I haven't written anything!
I don't even know if I can do it.
Sawa, you'll handle choreography.
Choreography?!
Sure. You've got the best moves.
Tanaka and Wien can take care
of the stage and props,
and we'll all pitch
in to make costumes!
You sound pretty serious...
Of course!
Almost too serious.
This'll cost a ton.
Definitely. At least 10,000-20,000 yen.
Does the White Festival
even give budgets that high?
I doubt it.
So then, you have
other sources lined up?
That's what we're here to brainstorm!
Figures.
Work these things out in advance.
I don't mind singing,
but I'm not going to do any "my love,
my heart, I'll die without you" stuff.
You asking for a kissing scene?
As if!
Wien, say something!
Like what?
Anything but that!
Haven't you been listening
and taking notes, like usual?
No, I don't need notes anymore.
Hey, Sawa, how busy
is Shiho-san these days?
My mom?
No busier than usual.
Please take a look at the
documents in front of you.
Western Shopping District Event Planning
Let's make this summer a hot one!
A comparison of the district's revenue
between this summer and last
indicates we're having
a rather rough year.
Basically, we're in quite a tight spot.
Sure, but that's just
a sign of the times.
It's tough out there.
And we're not getting any younger.
Sakazaki-san's in the hospital...
He went for a full check-up.
Well, he does eat an awful lot.
Could you please refrain
from personal conversations?
It's fine.
We don't need an explanation,
we can just read it here.
But I thought I should give you a
rundown, before we started strategizing...
No need.
If we all put in a little elbow
grease, it'll all work out.
Nothing beats honest effort.
By the way, have you heard
about Eikodo's girl?
Word is, she's wonderful.
How about local superheroes?
Local superheroes?
Oh, I understand.
You mean mascots?
We need more than
just people in costumes.
We need superheroes!
Like the ones in groups of red,
white, yellow, and green.
Can you please clarify
what you're suggesting?
They could do "So-and-So Superhero!
So-and-So Ranger!" moves,
and hand out store flyers.
Like a sandwich board campaign?
That's a pretty good idea, Shiho-san!
Yes, yes.
I've already got an
idea for the costumes,
so all that's left is to
choose our heroes.
Boy, am I exhausted these days...
I can't shake these headaches...
I need at least three volunteers,
My back...
though I'd prefer five.
Who'd like to give
our shopping district a—
Oh, excuse me.
Hi, Mom.
Are you free soon?
Yeah.
What's up?
Wakana has some questions for you.
Wakana-chan?
Are you guys heading home
from your club meeting?
Do you have five people there?
Yeah, why?
That's perfect! Bring them all over.
I'll treat you all
to some delicious cake.
Okay. I'll ask them.
Make sure they come. I'll meet you there.
Someone get some delicious
cake over here, on the double.
Well, we're not gonna turn down cake.
Right?
Right.
Then Tanaka can come with us.
You think Shiho-san can help you?
Wein could take the train with Konatsu...
I'm not sure.
I'm just trying to figure out what my mom thought
about when she wrote songs...
Like if she ever felt scared...
Scared? What do you mean?
Like, if she ever doubted herself,
or worried if the finished
product was any good.
I just... I need to
know more about my mom
if I'm going to write a song with her.
That's deep.
Here you are!
Welcome, everyone! Dig in.
Why are you smiling like that?
Thank you!
Thank you.
Say, would you like
to make some money?
We sure would!
Konatsu.
I was taught never to get roped in
by slick talk or fast roller coasters...
Just hear me out.
Wouldn't you like to be superheroes?
What do you mean?
Want the details?
Yes.
Yes!
Careful.
Sure.
Suits and masks?
What is that?
Oh, here we are.
These are...
Superhero outfits!
Red, pink, yellow, white...
Thank goodness.
They look perfectly usable.
There's green, too. Just like the Gambaraijers!
Mom, what is this all about?
These were used for a lunch box contest
Aren't these a bit small?
They're soft, so you can stretch them out.
in the shopping
district a while back.
Oh, hey. There're boots, too.
You wore those?
They're pretty old, but the sizes should be okay.
For a lunch box contest?
Yeah, but we overstuffed it and failed.
Wow, they really do stretch.
I can't believe these were hidden here.
Our ambitions didn't fit in the box!
You can stop talking now.
The association's hoping
you'll wear them this weekend.
How does 30,000 yen sound?
For all five of us?
When would we start?
How many hours would we work?
If we could use all five
of you, it'd be ideal.
We'd like you to do ten-minute shifts,
five times each day.
30,000 yen for a weekend's
work is fair, don't you think?
We'd also need time to rehearse...
What do you think?
Why do I have to decide?
You're in for sure, daughter of mine.
Wakana wants to ask
you about her mother.
Then if you scratch my back, I'll scratch yours.
Traitor.
Please!
You're the only ones I can
ask to be superheroes!
This is a worthy mission.
It's worthy,
because it inspires hopes and dreams.
Hopes and dreams are the
power that moves humanity
and keep the Earth turning.
Wien?
Tomorrow doesn't come because
the sun rises in the morning!
The sun rises in the morning
because people keep their
hopes close to their hearts!
We keep the Earth turning!
I'd forgotten something important.
How could I allow myself to lose hope?
Can you please repeat our job description?
Sure... We'd like you to work over
the weekend, for ten minutes at a...
Wien sure is passionate.
Was he always like this?
That was Gamba Red's speech.
"The passionate heroes, the Gambaraijers."
We saw them in his room, remember?
Oh, yeah.
So this flipped his superhero switch.
So, you guys are in, right?
Yup!
We can rehearse tomorrow at my house!
Not wasting any time, huh.
The battle is upon us!
You want to know how
Mahiru wrote her songs?
Well, I was only ever a singer...
She was easy to talk to,
but I don't think
that subject ever came up.
Oh, I see.
I never saw her worry
much about that, though.
I'm pretty sure she was the
type to let inspiration strike.
Oh.
I wish I had talked to her
more about these things.
Well, if you want to know
more about composition,
you should talk to the vice principal.
The song on that cassette tape
was co-written by her and your mom.
Mahiru told us she wanted
us to write our own song.
At first, we all thought she was joking.
But Takakura has
always been quite serious,
so she got swept up
in the whole affair.
We were surprised
when they actually
finished a real song.
It's a sweet song, don't you think?
Yes.
Takakura could be hard
to approach at times,
but I think she was someone
we could look up to.
Probably.
Is that so?
Thank you for telling me all this.
I'm going to head home now.
Good luck!
What is a song, anyway?
Hey!
I came up with a concept
for the superheroes.
Concept?
Western Shopping District Heroes...
WestStoprangers?
I think that's a "sh."
ShopRangers!
Since we represent the
Western Shopping District,
it makes sense.
So, no twist?
The WestShopRangers are here
to protect the peace of the galaxy
and of our valued customers.
These heroes of justice will
ensure you enjoy your visit.
Meat Red? Fruit Pink? Whitebait White?
Actually, I was thinking...
Are we really wearing these?
Who's doing which color?
I like red.
Sawa, red is for the leader.
Favorite colors don't come into play.
Huh?
Of course, if you think
you're ready to be Red,
I will do the right thing and step aside.
I can do that... I think...
But first,
I have to ask if you truly
are ready to be Red.
Red's qualifications are a sense of justice—
No, no, no, I've got no
qualifications at all.
Are you okay with Pink, Wakana?
You can be Red.
I want to be Yellow.
Okay, then Miyamoto's Curry Yellow.
There's no curry place
in the shopping district.
I don't like curry.
I was thinking of asking you to
make us a theme song, Wakana,
but since you're busy writing
our song for the White Festival,
we can just use the
Gambaraijers theme.
The most important thing
is their trademark phrase.
Full Power!
Energy Charge!
Meat Red!
Taichi, you're up!
Me? Uh, well...
Straight from the source!
Bursting with flavor! Whitebait White!
You need to sound cooler!
The kids are never gonna buy that!
Sawa, your turn.
Uh...
Vitamins, minerals, and nutrients.
Veggie Green supports good health!
Put more feeling into it!
And do a pose with each word!
Wakana, go.
You first, Konatsu.
Curry Yellow loves curry! Try it!
Try what, some roux?
You sound like a commercial.
Be serious, you guys!
This might just be a small
show in a small town,
but being superheroes for little kids
is an important mission!
Serious?
It's just to draw crowds.
We'll be fine.
Did something happen?
Air mail?
From who?
I'd mailed them to a friend in
Wien, but they were sent back.
A girl?
Konatsu!
It says there's
no person named "Jan"
living there anymore,
so I should stop sending letters.
Have you tried calling their
phone or texting them?
Jan's just a kid. He'll
turn seven this year.
We'd watch the Gambaraijers video
my grandpa sent, on repeat.
Gamba Red was our hero.
But then I had to move back to Japan...
Are you really going?
I'll miss you.
Don't worry.
Gamba Red will protect you.
Right.
Will you write to me,
once you're back home?
I'd like to know more about Japan.
You bet I will!
So that's it.
Did you write about cultivating
excellence and saying "to arms"?
And the white rhino
in the school's basement?
Yes, all of it.
Too bad it all came back.
You know, Wien...
It's okay.
I get the feeling I'll
see Jan again, someday.
Until then, all I can do is trust Jan is doing his best.
And I'll do my best, too.
As a West Shopping District Hero. As Red!
All right!
I just thought of a new pose.
Straight from the source!
Bursting with flavor, Whitebait White!
That's way better!
Yeah, huh?
You see the whitebait, right?
If you move like this,
it'll look even more natural.
Like this?
Hey, this doesn't come with a skirt.
It'll show everything!
I guess these characters
were supposed to be boys.
Jeez.
Don't worry! You have a great figure.
Yep.
And you can't actually see
underwear through this,
so we don't need skirts.
This smells like the main hall at my house.
Like the temple?!
Can you guys hurry up?
Are you done?
Open that door and I'll kill you.
Oh crap, it ripped!
It did? Where?
What the hell are they doing?
Hey...
Red.
Red!
It's gonna be a long day.
What is the meaning of this?
I was against it, of course.
But even as principal,
I'm also an employee.
If my superiors—
This is outrageous.
It's just too sudden.
It's irresponsible!
Can you honestly accept this?
Have you forgotten
all the feelings and
hard work from the days
when you were the choir club's advisor?
I'm sorry.
Shirohamazaka High School Rule 18:
Except in special circumstances,
students are prohibited from
having after-school jobs.
Doesn't this qualify
as a special circumstance?
Wow, you're raising money
for the White Festival?
I'm so proud!
The vice principal?
You're dreaming.
Ain't happening.
Nope.
Well, worrying won't solve the problem!
Let's try!
Excuse us.
Madam Vice Principal,
we've come to ask permission
to have an after-school job.
If we're to perform at the White Festival,
the choir club needs to raise funds.
It would be different if we were given
an ample budget, like the main choir,
but our club is poorer
than a church mouse!
Jobs are allowed if there is
a special circumstance, right?
This is exactly that kind
of special circumstance.
Huh?
Um, we'd like your stamp of approval...
Oh, I see.
Thank you very much.
We did it, we did it!
That was easy!
Don't you think the vice principal
was acting kind of weird?
I told you!
Yeah.
It was too easy.
Great job, Konatsu.
You came in that?
Beta Carotene Shower!
Curry Punch!
Episode 10 - Crushing and Burning
Mango Beam!
Your tempo and timing are horrible!