Send?
Yes
No
Sending
Kagerou of the Spring
What is this?
I apologize for making you wait.
Please take your time.
I couldn't do anything yesterday.
Thank you.
He says he likes me for me.
He's trying to understand me.
I want to reciprocate, but...
I-It's that racing heartbeat again.
What's wrong, Miss Ririchiyo?
I-I'm fine.
You damn fox!
Don't think that because of yesterday,
everything is settled.
It's still anyone's game, because I am...
Sou! Chiyo! Morning!
Good morning, Watanuki.
Natsume.
Listen to me!
That uniform...
So, you're in my class.
Hey, Ririchiyo.
This is the first time I've seen you at school.
Sorinozuka.
Are you going home now?
Yeah.
That's quite a boring ringtone
for a high school girl.
That's because it's an unknown number.
It's him again.
Again?
We'll meet soon.
This morning, I also got a
message from this address.
I'm by your side.
Is it a stalker?
Is everything okay?
Sadly, I'm pretty used to stalkers
and kidnappers.
I guess so...
You've always been pretty and rich,
plus there's your attitude.
That always earned you a lot
of warped attention.
Maybe you should tell Miketsukami about it.
That's not necessary.
Look, I know you're stronger
than normal human men, but...
No need to bother him with this.
You're being pretty considerate.
I just don't want to overreact!
Well, if it turns out to be nothing,
just write an apology letter.
A letter?
You wrote plenty of them
when you were a kid.
You were so polite and honest in them.
I keep telling you,
I only wrote those to practice my handwriting!
Yeah, yeah.
Welcome back.
Miketsukami...
Look at that guy!
Who is he?
He's sparkling.
Waiting for you was like a living death.
Your return is like receiving
a new lease on life...
That sounds quite inconvenient.
It's also nice to see you again, Big Brother.
You actually noticed me.
You're my Miss Ririchiyo's
precious older brother.
What's up with calling me
"big brother," anyway?
I'm not her brother.
You told him to call you that!
Then I shall see you later.
Please do not hesitate to call,
should you require anything.
How can I ever repay him?
At the very least, I'd like
to tell him I'm grateful.
You wrote plenty of them
when you were a kid.
You were so polite and honest in them.
Maybe writing a letter out of
the blue is over the top.
Then again...
I'm simply expressing my gratitude formally!
That's not over the top at all.
This is where we display
our original designs.
I must say, they're not half bad.
Thank you.
I'll take this one.
It's gotten late.
But...
Again?
It's dangerous
to walk alone.
He must be close.
The dark is
dangerous for
people like us.
"People like us"...
Does that mean he's also descended
from the supernatural?
Do you have some business
with Miss Ririchiyo?
Oh, you have a boyfriend?
Huh?
I wish you guys happiness!
What are you doing here?
What are you doing,
walking home all alone?
Did you not think it dangerous?
If you're talking about that drunk,
I knew he was there.
Don't underestimate me.
I'm not talking about him.
Your big brother told me about it...
The text messages.
Why am I here?
Why didn't you tell me?
That notwithstanding,
you know it's dangerous for us
to walk around at night.
Be it shopping or anything else,
you know I'd do anything for you,
if only you'd ask me.
If something were to happen to you...
If I cannot protect you,
my life has no meaning.
It does have meaning...
You...
He said he likes me for me.
Is that how you've felt?
To think that, all along, you've been
carrying this burden alone.
Why don't we try it, then?
Pardon me.
It's just that
you've angered me.
Miss Ririchiyo may not always be
the most socially adept of people.
But she is honest, conscientious, and loyal.
She is also very, very delicate.
He noticed.
That's right...
And that's why, I also...
I also want to notice more about you.
Miketsukami...
Miss Ririchiyo.
Please stand back.
So you're the one
who's been sending me
those silly messages.
That's right.
But as you didn't scare at all, I grew bored.
I guess that level
of play wasn't enough for you!
It's been too long, my human toilets!
Human?
As always, you take your jokes too far.
You know this person?
What?
Don't tell me you've forgotten me.
You are too cruel.
My name is Kagerou Shoukiin.
Am I not Soushi's old master and your fiancé?
It's been too long,
you pigs!
I have returned in fine health!
Kage!
You're back.
Sata Andagi
I am.
Who is that? And wait a minute...
What is he making Karuta wear?
Lick, lick... Lick, lick...
I love it!
My charge lives in room two.
He gets cabin fever though,
so he's rarely in.
He's one of the childhood friends
I was telling you about.
It's been a long time, my masochistic slave.
Yeah!
So that's the nature of your relationship?
You...
You're here, too?
Good to see ya, cow.
Chacha bun chacha bun chacha bun chacha.
What are those times I'm thinking of?
Can you remember?
We did this...
And we did that...
Trims
Do you remember?
I still love hearing you cry...
It's so good.
It's nice to get the gang back together.
Right, Sou?
You're right.
Welcome back, Mr. Kagerou.
I'm happy to see you again.
You showed me quite the
entertaining welcome back there.
I just remembered!
I have a gift for you all.
Where did you go?
To Okinawa!
Sata andagi.
For you, Banri,
I got an iron maiden!
For you, I got a straw rope.
Thank you very much.
A whip for you.
That has nothing to do with Okinawa.
This is the first time I've seen you two...
As a token of our new acquaintance,
I give you a Spanish donkey!
And for you, a ball-gag.
Come any closer, and I'll freeze you!
You're into ice-play, huh?
That's good, that's good...
You're a man, a pervert,
and you haven't introduced yourself.
But you want to get to know me?
I guess you have a point, sow.
Uh, Nobara, it's really cold in here.
My name is Kagerou Shoukiin.
I live in room two,
and I am Karuta's master!
Additionally, I am Soushi's old master.
And I am Ririchiyo Shirakiin's fiancé!
Huh?
H-Her fiancé?!
Oh, yeah. You had one of those...
Didn't you write him a letter every day?
You liked him, didn't you?
I didn't!
This is so stupid...
This was something decided on
by both our families,
and it has no meaning.
Besides, I haven't seen him
since I was a kid.
The issue is basically dead.
But you were sad when he
stopped writing to you.
I was sad that I was missing an opportunity
to practice my handwriting.
Could I get a new one?
I actually like you quite a bit.
It's more fun to break in
someone with fight.
I love that expression! Yes, that one!
At first glance, you'd think she's a sadist,
but I see the makings of a true
masochist in that expression.
Who are you calling a masochist?!
And I'm a sadist, so that makes us
perfect for each other.
And further...
You're a sadist, too!
And one even worse than me,
because you don't show it.
Stop fitting people into your little world!
It is not only my world.
The world is divided into
sadists and masochists.
And I have the ability to see what
someone is with one glance.
You're a masochist!
Wh-What the hell?!
I'm not a masochist!
I'm a—
You're a sadist.
You really think so?
That's a secret.
Shut up!
And why am I a masochist?!
Do you want to eat?
Or do you want to be eaten?
I want to eat.
Then you're a sadist!
I-Is that how this works?
You're a sadist!
I told you to stay away from me.
Now, let us go, my fiancée.
What are you doing?
I shall guide you
to the dazzling world of S&M myself.
B-But I don't...
Let's go!
That boy's a sadist.
That man's a masochist.
Next!
Sadist.
She wants you to think she's
a masochist. She's a sadist.
Masochist.
Looks like a sadist, but he's a masochist.
This elevator sure is making us wait...
It's a sadist!
So hot, it's a sadist...
But once you're used to it, it feels good.
So it's a masochist.
I love that noise. A sadist!
Gimme some of that.
It's sticky. Sadist.
But it tastes good. Masochist!
This aquarium is hard. Sadist.
Masochist.
Sadist.
Sadist! Sadist!
Masochist!
This carpet is so soft,
it feels quite good to step upon.
It's a masochist.
You want to be stepped on that badly?
Then I'll step on you.
How's that? How's that?
The rooftop is high.
Sadist!
Enough...
The night is dark...
Sadist!
I said enough!
Whoops.
It's time.
I have to get going, or I'll miss my plane.
Why did you even come here?
I heard that my fiancée moved
into Ayakashi Kan,
so I stopped off during my trip.
Aren't you happy?
Also,
I had something important to tell you,
but we've run out of time.
I'll tell you next time.
I'm sure it's nothing that
important anyway.
I hope you have a safe trip.
Take care.
Then farewell, my sex toys!
I'll come back to discipline you.
Be sure to await it!
I'm impressed you managed to
exchange letters with that guy...
I love him.
I told you. I was just
practicing my handwriting.
Besides...
Miss Ririchiyo...
You'll catch a chill out here.
Let us return to your room.
You're right.
It isn't like there was anything
I wanted to tell him back then.
Just...
He said that Miketsukami
used to serve him.
So,
does that mean he knew I had a fiancé?
Don't underestimate me just
because I'm a tanuki.
I am bad!
Treat me like a pet, and you'll get hurt.
Watanuki's great...
You're so cute.
I-I'm not cute!
But I like the cute Watanuki...
Is that wrong?
Next time, on Inu X Boku Secret Service:
Don't Think.
I-It's not wrong!
It's fine!
Don't Think
For watching until the end, without changing
the channel, you're a masochist!
For reading text this small, you're a sadist!!