...to reveal moonlight, clear and bright.
So the flower has...
Feel love, nobody, feel sorrow...
...years in this world.
Let's start a competitive karuta club!
Please come see Ayase Chihaya in class 2-9!
Impassionate gods have never seen...
Hey.
I don't think we should hold
a karuta demo tomorrow.
What?  Why not?
We'll scare away all the first-years.
Huh?
True.
Kana-chan's right.
Huh?
They'll run for the hills.
But...
Don't worry!
Let me handle this!
Okay...
Taichi.
Will any new students come?
It's hard to say.
I hope they fall in love with karuta.
Yeah.
The way we did...
to set the Tatsuta River ablaze
Chihaya Furu
Verse 1
So
The
Flower
Has
Wilted
Good morning.
Have you heard?
The younger sister of the model
Ayase Chitose is in
the class above ours!
No way!  I'm a fan!
Let's go check her out!
From: Kazuki
Subject: (none)
First day of school for us both.
I'm so tired.  Feel lousy.
Time for a new start, though,
so why don't we both
look for new partners?
What I mean is, let's break up.
Impossible...
I was dumped...
I need to find a new boyfriend!
The hottest guy in this school!
Available Clubs for New Students
That's a cute strap!
The tennis team's goal this
year is to win Nationals.
Where'd you get it?
These pink student IDs are so cute!
Our badges are cute, too!
We love everything cute.
Um... Hanano-san, right?
I'm Hinako.
What's your first name?
That's a lot of mascara.
We love how cute we are.
Hanano Sumire.
We search for someone who
loves how cute we are.
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm searching!
Oh!  There's a nice one in class 1!
I'm going to make him regret dumping me
Next, we have the competitive
Hundred Poets Karuta Club.
because we went to
different high schools
by finding a super hot guy!
I'm the president, Mashima Taichi.
I-I'm the captain, Ayase Chihaya.
Dude!
He's gorgeous!
They're wearing kimonos!
She's so cute!
We have their attention now!
Recruitment Strategist
Kana-chan
"Karuta club?  What's that?"
"Sounds minor."
"Not interested."
Before the typical
reactions can kick in,
Was told
to keep
quiet
The karuta club plays a competitive
one-on-one card game
we send out Chihaya-chan
and the president in hakamas
to make our club look important
based on the Ogura Hundred Poets.
and grab the hearts of the
first-years like an eagle's talons!
Hey, Hanano-san!
While the game is meant to be
competitive, there is also a cultural aspect...
Isn't he hot?!
Hana—
Eagle?
Please drop by, if you're interested.
Finally, our captain would
like to say a few words.
Huh?
Um...  Er...
I-I don't...
...have many ordinary friends,
but my goal is to become friends
with all one hundred cards,
so I want one hundred junior members!
A hundred members?!
You're too greedy!
She wants to be friends with cards!
Cute and clueless?
Annoying.
She's so cute!
But...
I found my man!
Are any new members going to come?!
Notice:
If the karuta club does not recruit five new members
next year, you will have to return the clubroom. Good luck.
I was able to increase the club's budget to 30,000 yen.
-Miyauchi
We'll be in trouble if no one comes.
The reaction to our
introduction was promising.
Really?!
Yes.
But we don't want too many.
Well, if we get some
first-years to join,
we'll have to figure out
who's going to teach them.
What?!
Why?!
Me!  Me!  Me!
Why are you volunteering when you're
the worst possible candidate?!
Don't you need to practice?!
Me!  Me!  Me!  Me!  Me!
How many first-years are going to come?
We were able to buy new cards
with the extra budget.
I hope they learn to love karuta.
And then...
Hello!
What's wrong, Senpai?
Are you okay?
I-I'm okay...
This is my application.
Here's mine.
I can't wait to get started!
Really?  You're all going to join?
I can't wait!
Thank you!  Thank you!
Glad to be here.
Ni-Nira?
Nira-chan?
Nira-chan
She can't even read my name right?!
Stupid!  Chihaya, it's Sumire!
Sumire!
Su-Sumire-chan!
She's definitely an enemy.
Pretty, clueless, and dumb.
She's every girl's enemy!
I couldn't tell when she
was wearing a hakama,
but she's got an amazing figure.
They look good together.
Um, let's start by introducing
the second-years.
From the far end...
Excuse me, can I ask a question?
Does President Mashima
have a girlfriend?
Excellent question!
Way to go, Hanano-san!
Your upperclassman is talking!
It's not your turn to speak!
Small figure with huge boobs!
Enemy!
I need to take care of the tennis team.
I'm counting on you.
Um, have any of you played
competitive karuta before?
Who's memorized all of the
Hundred Poets poems?
It's okay!
We were all beginners at one point!
I made printouts of the poems with
their unique syllables and meanings.
Please start by memorizing
all one hundred.
What?  Memorize?
Why?
How many pages are there?
This looks hard.
I can't do this.
Just skim it.
There will be a test in one week.
If you haven't memorized
all of the poems, you fail.
There will be a retest offered.
What?  A test?
Kana-chan, a week isn't long enough.
We have to memorize all of them?
They're in high school now!
They can do this.
But...
We have to make them do this!
Um, we'll explain the rules next.
Me?
Matches are played between two people.
You take 50 of the Hundred Poets cards
and put the remainder back in the box.
Each person places 25 cards, with
a 3 centimeter gap in between.
Here's your 3 centimeters.
This is the basic layout.
You win if you reduce the 25 cards
on your side to zero first.
First, you have 15 minutes to
memorize the positioning of
the 50 cards on the field.
This is just a tutorial, so we'll
only use three minutes.
One minute's enough.
The first poem read
is the opening poem,
which isn't part of the Hundred Poets.
The poem of Naniwa Bay, said to be known
universally during the Heian period,
was chosen as...
Kana-chan.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
I feel that my love...
As my love first came...
Huh?
What?
What are they doing?
Um, so there you go.
Once you learn the poems,
the unique syllables,
and how to position, you'll be
able to quickly take cards.
Let's work together to make it
to the National Championship.
Um...
We're not interested in
this complicated stuff.
Can we play bozu mekuri
with the cards in a corner?
You're too frank, Hanano-san.
No kidding.
But I like the idea of
playing bozu mekuri.
I don't know how to play that, either.
We'll start by learning
the Hundred Poets poems.
See you again next week.
Let's start a competitive karuta club!
Please come see Ayase Chihaya in class 2-9!
You're a riot, Hanano-san.
W-Well, that's how it goes at first.
Since we have twenty
people who want to join,
we should do what we can to
help them understand karuta.
Right?
Huh?
Chihaya.
You don't have time to teach first-years
who aren't particularly interested.
If you're serious about playing
in the Master and Queen match,
shouldn't you skip club practice and go
to the Shiranami Society instead?
What are you talking about, Mashima?
The high school tournament comes first.
It's been a year since we
last played as a team!
Are you saying that the individual
tournament is more important?
Sure, you're probably worried because
you still haven't made Class A...
Porky!
I'll take responsibility
for teaching them.
We don't need twenty new members.
I'll only let the ones who can keep up remain.
What?  You can't do that, Kana-chan!
I think it's a good idea.
The five of us will be playing
in the high school tournament.
The first-years aren't important.
They can play bozu mekuri
in the corner if they want.
Wh-Why would you all say that?
We need to train new members!
Or else the karuta club
won't last very long!
Ayase, what are you expecting
from the first-years?
We're the ones who will
be winning matches.
I never knew, until
the first-years came,
that we all cared about
different things.
From: Nami
Subject: Heya
Sumire!
Heard the news!
You broke up with Kazuki?
And in spring! Too sad!
That's not true!
I've already found my
next potential boyfriend!
He's a second-year and
he's handsome and tall!
...and tall and the class prodigy!
I joined his club too,
so I'm totally gonna date him.
Want his picture?
I took it when he wasn't looking!
From: Nami
Subject: Re: Re: Heya
Whoa!
He's out of your league.
Good luck!
I don't see you landing that hunk.
She doesn't get it.
My slightly above average looks
make me your typical shojo
manga main character!
I want to be popular!
Plus, there's a beautiful
rival for me to defeat!
Literature
Class 2-9
Fukasaku Tokiji
On page 12, you'll find...
We're the ones who will
be winning matches.
Akutagawa Ryunosuke's Rashomon.
One of Akutagawa Ryunosuke's...
There might be a first-year who
loves karuta and is really good!
...more touching stories is...
We only have two months until
the high school tournament prelims.
There's no time to train them now.
We can wait two months.
...about a lesson he taught his
young child who was at play...
If we wait two months,
they'll all leave!!
I don't see a problem?
Never step over a book.
Wait, that's it?!
We're all so different...
Science
Class 2-1
Miyauchi Taeko
There will be a quiz at the
beginning of every class.
As second-years, you need to begin
counting down to college exams.
Prepare by identifying the
schools you wish to attend...
I'll teach them.
She doesn't understand how
precious time is right now.
She's the one dreaming
about becoming Queen.
She's the one who cries
when she loses.
Didn't we say that we would
have a meeting during lunch?
But I ate my lunch during class, so
I need to go buy some melon bread.
I'll give you half of mine.
That's not enough.
Oh, Kana-chan!
You're early.
Class 5 is the closest to this room.
Oh, everyone's here.
Class 1's too far away.
So, on the topic of the first-years...
Me!
Chihaya...
What do you care the most about?!
Priority:
Master and Queen Match
You're not going to defeat
Wakamiya Shinobu like this!
Priority:
Proper Etiquette
I'll teach the first-years!
Some may quit, but we need
to teach them how to behave!
Priority:
The Practice Environment
If we can just keep this room
and have some fun with the
first-years, we're in good shape.
We can't focus on practicing
with 20 kids babbling!
Priority:
High School Championship
The preliminaries are in June!
Chihaya?
Right now, I care the most
about Taichi making Class A.
Wait... Chihaya?
I'm the most important...
My goal is
to win the team High
School Championship,
as well as the individual High School
Championships in each class,
while training the first-years,
so we can become a strong karuta
school like Hokuo Academy!
Huh?  Wait, what's wrong?
Sh—
She's so greedy!
I've never seen anyone
this greedy before!
Are you okay?
Chihaya...
Ignoring your other goals for now,
how are we going to become a
strong karuta school like Hokuo?
We need a proper coach
for that to work.
Well...
If we recruit enough new members,
I'll come back to teach them
karuta after I graduate.
I've never seen anyone so greedy.
Or anyone who loves karuta so much.
Huh?  Mashima-senpai isn't
going to be teaching us?
The other second-years are practicing
for the tournament in June.
Once you've learned the basics,
you'll be able to practice with us.
Don't you need to
practice, Ayase-senpai?
Are you teaching us because
you won't be playing?
Benched?
Is that how it works?
I'm the ace!
Ace... Ace... Ace... Ace...
We'll use the tape today.
Yes.
Are we starting now?
Uh, I'll play Kana-chan
while Mashima plays Porky.
Say...
Can I go practice at
the Shiranami Society?
Just on Tuesdays and Thursdays?
Why are you bothering to ask?
Get going!
You can practice with
Dr. Harada and Tsuboguchi-san!
Right now, I care the most
about Taichi making Class A.
I think that Ayase's changed a bit.
She's changed?
It's hard to say...
But I mean, Ayase's words
inspired Mashima to think
about himself, for once.
I'm tired...
You can memorize poems
in their entirety,
Memorization? Is this a
classical literature class?
or you can use shortcuts.
Huh?  I don't remember any boys.
Whatever.
09 So the flower has wilted during the long spring rains,
just as my beauty has faded
during my forlorn years in this world
For "Though I prayed,"
the second verse begins
with "I never asked,"
so think "pray, never ask."
Hmm?
Sumire-chan!
What's wrong?!
Did you see something?!
A ghost?!  A bug?
This poem is absolutely correct...
Youth and beauty...
...soon fade.
So I must live for love!
Senpai, I'm so sad
that I need to go home!
Huh?
She's so sensitive!
Mashima-senpai!
Huh?  Aren't you...
What a pleasant surprise.
I have a headache, so I left early.
Um...  Sumire-chan, right?
He called me Sumire-chan!
What's your last name?
Hanano.
Do you think you can handle
the karuta club, Hanano-san?
Of course!
Really? That's good!
Call me Sumire...
Even his voice is perfect!
I'm so lucky that we take
the same train to school!
This is working out pretty well, right?
I think my chances are looking good!
There's an open seat.
Why don't you sit down?
No, I can't sit down
while you're standing.
There might be other
people who need to sit more,
so I would rather leave the seats open.
I just have to play the
sweet little girl.
Don't worry about it.
You're not feeling well, right?
Look at him.
Isn't he handsome?
Y-You must be popular, Mashima-senpai.
I wouldn't know.
You must be.
I bet girls ask you out all the time.
You don't have to worry about
looking for a girlfriend.
I'm not really sure about that lately.
It doesn't seem right to
let a girl choose me.
I would rather choose the
girl I devote myself to.
Bubaigawara.  Bubaigawara.
You're pretty cute, so I bet a
lot of boys would choose you.
Bye.
That really stung...
Mashima-senpai will never choose me.
I won't accept it!
I want to have a choice, too!
I...
...don't want to write
poems about regret!
While the story is taking a
romantic twist for some members,
during my forlorn years in this world
our captain is bullying the new members
by taking all 100 cards
in a Genpei match.