Invade the Empire of Misurugi?!
Embryo is in charge of all of
the human world's defenses.
Their air defenses aren't great,
so the invasion itself should be easy.
I-I see.
The problem is Embryo, Salia, and their gang.
All right. Here's the plan.
Rosalie and I will lead the
invasion of the Empire of Misurugi.
We'll draw away Salia's people.
R-Right.
Meanwhile, Vivian will storm
the empire's headquarters.
Find Ange and the Villkiss.
Roger!
How are we going to find them?
Like this: sniff sniff, sniff sniff...
Seriously?
It beats using radar.
Once we find Ange,
Tusk, you'll go in from very
low altitude and meet Ange.
Get her on the Villkiss and escape.
Got it.
The new troops will stand by at the border.
They'll help Ange and the Villkiss escape.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
What's wrong? Are you nervous?
B-But Onee-sama...
I've never flown in the human world before.
Don't worry. It's my first time, too.
What?!
It'll be all right. I think.
All right, Hilda Squad, move out!
Yes, ma'am!
The One Left Behind
Salako...
Is it you?
Is she an acquaintance?
You're looking pretty ragged,
compared to the last time I saw you.
And I can smell you from downwind.
How about you go take a bath?
I'll take care of this.
All right, then. Thanks.
Are you ready, you two?
Yes, Salamandinay-sama.
Let me through, please.
To Aura!
What is that?
Help me!
Embryo-ojisama!
Salamandinay-sama.
Hilda, something's not right.
They're already fighting.
What?
Sniff sniff, sniff sniff...
Hilda, Ange is that way.
What?
That way!
Shit, what's going on?
Tusk, we have a change of plans.
Ange isn't at the palace anymore.
We'll be following her.
Got it.
Momoka, any followers?
Not for now.
There's Ange!
Damn, she really found her.
We're here to help you, Ange.
Guys...
Ange!
Move.
Ange, I'm taking you back.
I'm taking Ange.
Piss off.
Oh? You're here to help her.
Even though...
...you abandoned me!
W-Wait, Chris!
I told you to piss off!
Do you really think you can beat me?
You haven't changed, have you?
You still think I'm your
worthless old puppet, don't you?
What?
I'm not the same person I was before.
Get in my way, and I'll kill you.
Chris...
Try it.
Tusk, the Villkiss is down.
I have my hands full.
Take care of Ange.
Got it.
Princess.
Momoka.
The Villkiss.
Let's go, Momoka.
Where to?
Hilda and the others are here.
That must mean the Aurora is nearby.
We should be able to meet them at sea.
Okay.
Everyone, hang in there until
Mommy Ersha gets back, okay?
I'll go find a car.
Please wait here.
Sorry to burden you, Momoka.
I, Momoka Oginome, am your top maid.
Momoka.
You must be tired, Ange.
Embryo.
Now, come home.
Angelise-sama, the car.
Go, Momoka.
What? Yes!
Ange!
Wait, please, Chris!
Why?
Why do we have to kill each other?
You left me for dead.
We wanted to help you, but we couldn't.
Because I wasn't worth saving, right?
That's what you people are like.
You haven't changed.
Hey, do you remember this?
At the Festa, seven years ago.
One, two...
That's the one I bought.
Oh? You have good taste.
I chose it.
That's so you.
It's cute.
But what should I do? I only have one.
Why not get rid of one of your pigtails?
I already have two.
That sounds good.
Right?
S-Sure...
How could you?
I liked my hair that way.
What of it now, after all this time?
That's not all.
I've always been holding it in.
I tried to accept everything.
All your self-indulgence.
My own place among you.
I thought we were friends.
Ah, forget it.
You wouldn't get it, would you?
One woman who can't
understand other people's feelings,
and an idiot who never thinks at all.
But Embryo-kun is different.
Poor Chris.
Betrayed and walked all over.
To think, only you really
believed that you were friends.
You have a mind that can keep
peace between others,
even at your own expense.
How beautiful and noble.
Would you be my friend, Chris?
This is—
This is the proof of our eternal friendship!
You were never my friends!
Please, Chris, listen to me!
Rosalie-oneesama!
we should go, too.
Wait, Marika.
Our orders were to stand by.
But Onee-sama's in trouble.
That girl was Embryo-san?
What's going on?
I don't know.
But she looked like she
was being manipulated.
Have you forgotten?
Have you forgotten who created these humans?
Momoka!
What did I just—
Momoka, ahead!
Momoka, are you all right?
Are you hurt, Ange?
Come home, Ange.
This way.
We aren't strong enough right now.
We're retreating, Kaname, Naga.
What?!
We can't rescue Aura with our current forces.
We're going to retreat and regroup.
Riza, I trust you can hear me.
You shall rendezvous with us, too.
I won't ask what happened to you right now.
But if you regret having let
so many of your friends die,
you'll fight along with us now to save
as many of your friends as you can.
Salamandinay-sama...
Go back to the dungeon peacefully.
Otherwise, I'll have
Embryo-ojisama punish you.
What a sad child.
It was Julio that
killed your father, and yet...
What? What are you...
Wait!
Shit, you're not getting away!
Don't chase them too far.
What?
Um...
Princess, what was I just...
I don't know.
You can't escape, Ange.
You're smart.
You must have realized.
I can control everyone who uses Mana.
So long as that maid is with you...
I said I don't know!
My, my.
What a stubborn bride.
Do you need to be punished again?
Ange!
Tusk!
Sorry I'm late.
Get on and run.
What about you?
I have business with him.
Hurry!
Momoka, let's go.
Yes.
You'd dare separate us?
Prepare yourself, maggot.
I am Tusk, the son of Villkiss Knight
Istvan and Mail Rider Vanessa!
As the last of the Ancient
People and Ange's Knight...!
So you...
Oh?
Chris is strong!
Shit.
Hilda!
I found Ange.
Protect her.
What about the Villkiss?
It's in the water.
We can't get it back now.
Tusk!
Damn it!
All units, retreat!
Rendezvous with Ange
and return to the Aurora.
Understood.
You won't escape.
Onee-sama!
Marika.
Why are you here?
To give you backup!
Piss off!
Marika.
Marika!
Chris!
You!
That machine.
It's Salasala-san!
It's Salamandinay, Vivian.
Damn.
Chris, wait, dammit!
Rosalie, calm down.
Dammit!
Ange's knight, you say?
You're just an Old World monkey!
You terrorist remnant!
It's no use.
No it isn't, demon of Heiselberg,
resident of a nondeterministic world!
But if I can slow you down,
even just a little...
Oh?
So the monkey has grown a little smarter.
But he's still just a monkey, after all.
Shit!
Momoka, it's the ocean.
Momoka.
Ange...
You're beautiful when you're angry, too.
Why do you reject me so much?
Is it that man?
Let go of Ange.
Momoka!
I've increased her physical ability
to the limit of her body's capabilities.
Behold, the end of a foolish man.
Stop, please.
Stop, Momoka!
It's useless.
She can't go against her creator's commands.
No.
Momoka is my top maid.
Wake up, Momoka!
Angelise-sama.
Tusk-san.
Please take care of the princess.
Run, Princess!
Oh?
Momoka!
Mana!
Light of Mana!
What?!
Momoka.
Momoka!
Wait.
Tusk, please.
Momoka!
My, my, I'm impressed.
To think, a homunculus rejected me.
Embryo.
How could you...
Momoka...
You're going to live on.
I'll be back by your side, I promise.
No.
No, Tusk.
Tusk.
Tusk!
You slave.
No one likes persistent men!
No way.
Right?
Right? Momoka? Tusk?
Don't leave me...
Next Episode
I can't believe it! Tusk and Momoka?!
We'll have to take over for them.
I'm Tusk, then!
I'm the maid?!
Ch-Cheer up, Angelise-sama!
That's too much.
Look who's talking.