What is it, Akatsuki?
N-Nothing, just...
Aren't you going to the party, my lord?
No, I don't care for those flashy events.
I'll let Crusty handle it.
Oh...
Oh, I hear you did a fantastic job!
I'm told you easily defeated the Goblin General.
I believe that victory was only possible
because People of the Land and
adventurers worked together.
Please. You don't really think that.
He's so strong.
He's wonderful!
The Two of Us Shall Waltz
The Two of Us Shall Waltz.
The food here is great!
Shiroe and his buddies ate this stuff
every day during the conferences?
Wherever you eat it,
the food you enjoy with friends
is the most delicious.
Where's the hide-and-seek genius?
Where is she?
Isn't she here today?
What's wrong?
You aren't eating.
We haven't wiped out the goblins,
so how can we celebrate victory?
It's been a month since we pinned the
goblin army on the Zantleaf Peninsula.
The Goblin King is still at their
headquarters in Seventh Fall.
Why can't we go destroy him right now?
It's more important to build our
relationships with the People of the Land.
That was Shiroe's decision.
Over the past month,
the Round Table has signed basic
trade and peace treaties
with Eastal's League of Freedom Cities.
The Round Table has issued many goblin-fighting
quests to adventures in Akihabara,
which has kept the goblins in Zantleaf.
Then this is
reminding everyone that adventurers
are accepting quests again.
And if we defeat their king first,
the goblins will go out of control without a leader.
All of this is part of Shiroe's plan
to take out Seventh Fall.
I understand...
He's thinking several steps ahead.
Are you certain?
I can really join Log Horizon?
Yes, that's fine.
I'll let Shiro know.
Th-Thank you!
After all you've done, and
all the help you've given me...
Friends should stay together, right?
Leave Miss Isuzu to me.
With the strength of the adventurer
Rundel Haus Code, Akihabara is—
Thank you! Thank you!
I'm happy for Isuzu.
Shiroe?
Why are you looking there?
Is something wrong?
Come to think of it, I haven't seen him.
Shiroe is the Akihabara army's strategist.
He should be one of the guests of honor.
But he isn't even here to say hello?
I see...
That sounds like him.
Sounding like him doesn't excuse this behavior!
Meow...
My lord...
Um...
Shiroe!
Oh, no.
Akatsuki, take care of this.
My lord!
Akatsuki!
Let's get you changed!
Oh, do you know where Shiroe is?
Oh, you smell so good!
Akatsuki?
That was close.
Ooshima
The Little Birdies
Ooshima?
How's it going since then?
What? In the west?
The Demon Festival of Suzaku Gate?
I see.
So that's it.
So we were just ripping up goblins,
tossing them aside...
You could hear the Phoenix's roar
echo through the whole valley!
Boom!
They don't know that they'll lose some
of their memories if they die.
We've only told the Round Table's
major members about that.
Well, knowing Shiro, I'm sure he'll handle it.
I'd love it if you'd visit my territory sometime.
I'd love for you to tell my troops
some tales of your victories!
No, no, please visit me, as well!
My daughter is seeking a husband,
and I think you'd get along well.
Grandfather, is that...
And then? And then?
What happened?
And then, heroes from a
different world came to ours.
They were immortal, strong, and wise.
I know that!
The Precursors, right?
The Izumo Knights, right?
No, they were far more
powerful than the Precursors.
Oh, my!
One day, the king of monsters
appeared with his army,
burning villages, destroying castles,
and ruining fields.
The heroes came quickly, and defeated
the monsters, one after the next.
The monsters that had covered the beaches,
those that blackened the forest...
But during the battle,
one of them lost his life.
That's strange...
Weren't they immortal?
The boy who died was merely one
of the People of the Land,
one who longed to be one of those heroes.
Oh, my!
The heroes begged their wizard to save him.
But not even their wizard
knew how to restore one of
the People of the Land.
And then?
What happened next?
So the wizard thought, and then, of all things,
he created a new form of magic
that hadn't existed in this world.
And so, the young boy of the
People of the Land became a hero.
But after that, the wizard...
What? What?
That's all for today.
We'll continue the story next time.
Aww!
No, there's no way...
Oh, hello there.
I am honored by your visit.
And congratulations, Shiroe.
For what?
The creation of a new type of magic.
What? You noticed?
A month ago,
I sensed a magic unknown to me in the
east, and I saw its light fill the sky.
It was world-class magic,
that which can alter the laws, fate,
and very existence of the world.
You are every bit the man I thought you were.
If I hadn't met you, I never would've had the idea.
You honor me.
Incidentally,
I also felt a powerful magic in
the western sky, just recently.
The western sky?
It seems that one besides yourself
has created a new form of magic.
One of the adventurers, I assume.
The western sky... Adventurers...
That means
it would have to be in Minami, right?
Akihabara, Shibuya, Minami, Susukino, Nakasu...
Just as Akihabara has changed
since our arrival in this world,
the other cities have changed, as well.
Almost all the Shibuya adventurers
have gone to Akihabara.
Susukino never recovered from the
deterioration it suffered after the Apocalypse.
Ever since we saved Serara,
we've sent several armies up to evacuate
anyone who wanted to leave.
But there are still
over two hundred adventurers who continue
ruling over the People of the Land.
And Minami...
Yamato was once united as
a single kingdom, right?
Yes...
After we last spoke, I studied up.
As I recall, the Unified Westelande Empire...
was swallowed up in the history of battles with
demi-humans and the Luquenje, and died out.
But the Cowen family is distantly related.
Yes.
As is the Holy Empire Westelande,
which rules the country's western portion.
Within the territory is a city
of adventurers, Minami.
And I'm told that a certain guild rules Minami.
Are you aware that the Demon Festival
of Suzaku Gate occurred in the west?
I am.
Though the eastern nobles don't
seem to have noticed yet.
The Demon Festival of Suzaku Gate is similar
to the Return of the Goblin King.
It's an event that occurs at set intervals.
It appears the Izumo Knights
were involved with it, as well.
The Demon Festival of Suzaku Gate...
Hints of magic...
Something is happening in Minami.
I found you, Shiroe.
Hide-and-seek is over.
And so,
you'll be doing your share of the cleaning.
Sounds good to me.
Now you'll have the chance
to see why they call me
the "Dish-washing Fox of High Society."
Dish-washing Fox?
You couldn't make less sense if you tried.
Rudy, stop eating only meat,
and have some vegetables.
No, there's no need for that...
Just eat it! Come on!
No! Anything but that!
Eat it!
No!
Huh?
This song...
This was Elder Tale's theme song
when it was a game.
It really is a nice song...
But nobody's dancing.
Both the People of the Land
and the adventurers are too afraid
of each other to dance.
For the sake of both,
someone should take the lead.
I think you and I have that responsibility.
Responsibility...
Lenessia,
it was not Eastal that asked the
adventurers for help with the goblins.
It was you yourself, Lenessia.
Grandfather, that's...
Eastal expresses its deepest thanks
to the adventurers of Akihabara,
but we have no obligation to do more.
In other words,
you have no intention of offering them
reward money, or compensation money?
I must take responsibility myself?
My city, Maihama, will be establishing
an embassy in Akihabara,
and will be sending an ambassador.
You can't mean...
You spoke of showing respect.
Thus, it is your responsibility
to stay with them,
and to thank them whenever
the opportunity arises.
No, it's simple courtesy, is it not?
It comes with three meals and a nap.
I believe you witnessed this yesterday,
but adventurers aren't as concerned
with formalities as nobles are.
There are few tea parties or balls.
That's the kind of town you'll be coming to.
It should allow you to enjoy a
life with three meals and a nap,
never having to leave the house.
Then...
My old dream of enjoying three
days of such laziness
that I don't even take a bath?
Well, as long as it doesn't
go much past three days.
He read my mind again!
No, no...
I must not let my guard down.
He is a monster that can read minds.
Yes!
He's a mind-reading monster!
He's so wonderful!
Now I can finally return to
my life of self-indulgence.
Right, Crusty?
I don't know...
You seem to have a habit
of ruining it for yourself.
Ruining—
U-Um...
What's wrong, Serara?
I... I'm...
Meow?
I'm really grateful to you for
saving me in Susukino.
But...
The Crescent Moon Alliance
has done a lot for me,
and I need to look after the new players, so...
Um...
So I...
I...
I want to be with Nyanta, but...
can't stay in Log Horizon...
Serara,
you're such a good girl.
Would you dance with me,
Serara?
Y-Yes!
I'll go get something to drink.
Okay.
Where is Shiroe?
Did you hear about how that
Shiroe guy tricked the princess?
I did...
He dragged her out to the battlefield,
and used her in negotiations
with the People of the Land.
You know, they call him a villain.
Who is he, anyway? What's he
doing in the Round Table?
I know guys like that.
They skulk around the shadows,
taking advantage of people's weaknesses.
You aren't going, my lord?
I think I'll pass.
Tonight, the star is Crusty.
I'd just make things awkward and tire everyone.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Nothing?
Why are you smirking, my lord?
I'm not smirking.
No, you were smirking!
That isn't true.
You were... You were smirking!
You're acting kind of strange.
This time, I hardly did anything.
Outside of battle, I think
I only slowed you down.
That's not true.
You stayed with me the whole time, right?
Ever since we came here,
you've been my bodyguard,
and got me information.
You heard what Regan said, and you shared
the secret about our memories with me.
Even when I went to save Rundel Haus,
you were with me.
I've only made it this far because of you.
It's true.
It's hard to express gratitude to someone...
Naotsugu!
Let's dance, too.
No, I don't really...
Marie...
There, there...
Shall we dance, Miss Isuzu?
S-Sure...
You're very good, Serara.
Th-Thank you.
Would you like to dance?
I'd be honored.
Want to dance?
No, my lord...
I'm not good at dancing...
You were practicing, right?
No, that was, well...
My lord...
Don't laugh at me.
I'm a beginner, too.
I won't laugh.
Oh, my...
That is quite the dance, as well.
My lord, is this a dance?
Don't laugh.
Welcome, Princess Lenessia!!
Love Lenessia
Several days later, Lenessia came to Akihabara.
Rather than making a big deal of it,
I spread the news about the
lost memories as a rumor.
But naturally, many were scared.
But you only lose part of them, right?
They say people who've died
ten times have no problems.
Original Fishing Rods
All Kinds
of Lures!!
But it didn't cause chaos.
They say the Round Table knew, but hid it.
Seriously?
Nah... I could see them doing it.
Especially that Shiroe guy.
Shiroe Memo #6
Builds, Skills, and Subclasses
Minori?
Is there still something you don't understand?
No, I'm fine...
I see.
U-Um...
I... I like...
I'd like to ask you about my skills.
And then,
autumn came.
A festival?
Yes. The Committee for Crafting Guilds
has mentioned displaying and
selling their new products...
And Marie said...
It's October, right?
And October is autumn, right?
Ya-hoo! Ya-hoo! Ya-hoo!
So festivals, right?
I want to have a festival!
That's what she said.
Come on, let's have on! It'll be so much fun!
Um, Marie...
Didn't you say the same thing in summer?
So, when are we gonna do it?
Two weeks.
So soon?!
That's almost no time at all!
It'll be fine.
Leave it to your strategist, Marie.
Air glasses?
I've got it all planned out.
I call it...
Ta-da!
Scale Festival Plan
The Scale Festival?
Two forks are offered to you...
Two bites of cake on them.
Which will you eat, and which won't you?
Jealous glares and a demon's spell.
Say, "Ahh."
An all-you-can-eat cake buffet
is the young girls' battlefield,
where Shiroe's reality suddenly explodes.
Swallow and Young Starling
Next time: Swallow and Young Starling.
We will change the world...