How's life out here?
Morning.
It's not as bad as I thought.
No bug bites?
Nope.
I've caused you a lot of grief.
Where did that come from?
Well, we're going to be living together now.
I figured we should get some of the
serious talk out of the way first.
It's pretty good.
Right?
Thinly-sliced ham.
Tastes great lightly fried with olive oil.
Normally, parents dragging a child around
for their own personal reasons is...
We have dependents.
We have to expect it to some extent.
That makes me feel better.
But that's only when the child
is small and can't live on his own yet.
Let's go together.
Maybe that's not it.
Do you always listen to this?
It's a little embarrassing when
you're around, but I guess.
Out of all Mom's performances,
this is one I like quite a bit, too.
Yeah?
Episode 4:
"Steep Road"
Sacchan
Sacchan? How are you?
Feeling okay?
It's been two days since we went hiking,
and my legs still hurt.
Yeah, my legs are fine, but—
Are you being hospitalized?
What? You already knew?
Yanagi-chan should be fine.
It's not bad enough that she needs to stay.
Yana-chan?!
Yeah.
I got a call from Yukinari-kun.
Yanagi-chan hurt her leg during a lesson.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
It's just a sprain.
You didn't have to come.
Of course I did. We're family.
What's with the face?
Nothing.
What do you mean "nothing"?
Sorry, thanks.
What? We aren't strangers.
Don't run.
Hurry!
Fine, fine.
Whoa, Yana-chan?
Yukinari-kun.
Never mind. You're heavy.
Yuki.
Oh? I'm jealous.
Like this?
Friendship punch!
Yeah, I'm a lot better.
Okay, see you.
Wind, Sand, and Stars
Antoine de Saint-Exupéry
Hello.
Morning.
I'm here to return that book.
You read it already?
Y-Yeah.
It was good.
That fly in the bus, in the desert—
Do you want to come in?
To think that this was the future.
Knowing that, it makes me curious.
But I don't want a bad future.
I want to see a future that I'm happy with.
I wonder what's going to happen
with Yana-chan and Yuki-kun.
And with me.
Hey,
focus.
You'll get hurt.
Okay.
Ow.
Full of Fruits
White Panda
Today's special.
Sure. I'll be fine.
I want to walk to do some rehab anyway.
See ya.
Up we go.
Sorry.
No.
Honestly, I don't even know
what you're apologizing for.
Yeah.
Sure, it was a shock,
but what could I expect?
It's not your fault at all.
That's not it!
My heart was racing.
So—
Of course.
That would happen to any girl,
if a guy said that he liked her.
Yeah. You're right.
Of course.
David.
Okikura-kun.
Kakeru Okikura.
He's kind of hot, isn't he?
Really? I think he's a bit stuck-up.
True.
He seems a bit self-centered.
Pretty self-centered.
I lied to you.
I never intended to confess to Yuki.
No! You just
hadn't made up your mind.
I mean, you were still unsure.
That's not lying.
Of course you couldn't make up your mind.
You're a girl. You'd get nervous!
I guess.
Thanks, Touko.
Again, I don't even know what for.
I'm glad I came outside.
I'll be fine on my way home. Don't worry.
I'll be doing this at the school yard.
Show me your sketches next time.
I don't know.
It's been a while.
Roger, was it?
Oh, and that's—
Hi, Jonathan!
Okikura-kun?
Hey.
Yuki-kun.
What are you doing at school?
Can I sit beside you?
Sure, of course.
We aren't strangers, Yuki-kun.
I guess.
I guess it'll be a bit awkward
after what I said.
Sorry.
I thought you were Okikura-kun.
I like that about you.
What are you—
Wait, what do you like about me?
You're just a little bit rude.
Just sit down.
They made a movie.
See,
there's a banner ad.
Exile and the Kingdom
The classic reborn
In theaters now
Exile and the Kingdom.
Um, wanna go see, maybe?
Sure.
Wait, I'll check the times.
Are you free the day after tomorrow?
Sure.
Then—
Pins and needles!
Maybe it's still too early.
Hey, what are you doing at school today?
Uh...
Huh? What?
I saw you walking through the gate.
You mean you—
Just sit down.
Are you happy with that?
Not really.
You want me to grab them for you?
I figured this would happen, so...
Ta–da! Here.
Rice grains?
Thanks.
But don't you kind of think
ground-baiting is cheap?
You know what...
Looks like it's going to rain.
Shoot.
I'll be done in a second, sorry.
There should be some conté
crayons left here...
Um... Found it!
What's wrong?
I can't.
I can't be in a room alone with you.
Touko, are you thinking
about that Kakeru guy?
What now?
Do you like him?
I see. You do.
No, that's not it.
You thought I was Kakeru earlier.
You're waiting for him.
Deep down, you were waiting for him.
I said too much. I'm leaving.
I like...
Okikura-kun?
This way.
Thanks.
I might have been screwed if I were alone.
I'm—
Davi—
Kakeru Okikura.
You're one of Touko's friends.
Yanagi Takayama.
Your leg looks painful.
It's just a sprain.
I'm not impressed that
you'd walk around on that.
Kakeru is such a weird name.
Yanagi is a nice name.
Hiragana?
The kanji looks ghastly, so hiragana.
Flexible but tough.
Modest and strong.
What—
Kakeru is—
"Horse" and "section."
To make horses run, or to chase
them down—something like that.
They may have intended to imply
I was lacking in some way.
I don't think anyone's parents
would mean something like that.
You think?
Of course.
You... think?
Come on, get inside.
It's starting to rain over there.
You're lucky you have
nothing to worry about.
It's really coming down!
The rain's stopping.
Thanks for—
So now my doctor
is this fresh new lady.
Yeah?
She listens to my lungs
with her stethoscope.
She keeps going,
"And breathe in. Breathe out."
Four times in front, four times in the back.
And she looks all disappointed
and says, "Your lungs sound nice."
Like, are you really that
into the sound of my lungs?
Hmm.
You didn't like my story?
Dad, you should probably stop there.
Should I?
Peak
Dinner
Shopping
Rendezvous
Dinner: Family restaurant?
Washroom: 5 times
*Don't panic
Date Schedule
So nice!                     I've got this
Score!
Thanks for waiting.
Hey, where's Hiro-kun today?
I think he's on a date.
A date?!
Dance School
So many surprises today.
I wanted to talk to you.
I can't tell you yet.
Want to come over right now?
Episode 5:
"Hinode Bridge"