Ayase Chihaya
Wakamiya Shinobu
Chihaya Furu
Episode 22
Long
Last
We
Meet
We will now begin the third round
of the individual tournament.
Please place your cards.
Thank you very much.
The quarterfinals of the Class
A individual tournament.
Of the eight remaining
players, three are ours.
Emuro-kun is up against
Amakasu-kun from Hokuo.
He has good game sense,
and his reflexes allow him
to take cards quickly.
In terms of mental strength
and overall balance,
Emuro-kun has the advantage.
Suzuki Manata must be upset about
being taken out of the lineup yesterday,
since he's playing better than usual today.
His opponent is Wataya-kun from Fukui.
I've been asking around
the other societies,
and I was only able
to learn that he's the
grandson of the Eternal Master Wataya.
What kind of karuta does he play?
Yamai-kun is up against Ousaka-san
from First Akashi Girls'.
While Yamai-kun relies on his power,
Ousaka-san's weapons are
her speed and grace.
She's also been playing better
than in the team tournament.
This will be a battle of willpower.
And there's the Queen,
Wakamiya Shinobu.
Her opponent is Ayase-san
from Mizusawa.
Her game sense was
enough to defeat Rion,
but how far will it take
her against the Queen?
Coach...
She's been using her left
hand this whole time?
Ayase-san removed the bandages.
Is she going to use her right hand?
I don't know how much I can do against
Shinobu-chan with this hand,
but I don't want any regrets.
Huh?
Lame T-shirt.
The super rare Mommy Bear tanktop!
It appears that you've
injured your favored hand.
Shall I play with my right hand?
That's not something
you should joke about!
Since I played Shinobu-chan last year,
not a day has gone by
that I haven't remembered
her speed, her strength...
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
My only goal has been to beat Shinobu-chan.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Show me your true strength.
The strength of the number one
player in Japan, in the world.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Wow!
How is she so fast?
So fast...
The Queen's play is steady today.
Hey, Chihaya!  Enough already!
The drama I was briefly
in is about to start!
This again?
Haven't you gotten sick of
watching that chubby girl yet?
I watched the Queen match so many times
that my sister was disgusted with me.
when I should have
gone to sleep instead
As my love first came...
I knew it.
It looks like she waits until
the unique syllable to move,
but that's not the case.
She doesn't move her hand,
but her body is moving in
response to what's being read.
She's saving it up.
word had already spread
So she can take the card as soon
as the unique syllable is read,
without any mistakes.
So...
she can stab the border of the card
at the shortest distance.
is that I have no way
to tell you in person
I feel as though I am...
The storm blasts autumn leaves...
In order for us...
Sh-She's strong.
How can she be this accurate?
And so fast, too!
It's like there's something connecting
her fingers to the cards.
Not a sound...
That's how light and sharp
her movements are.
She is truly the Queen.
I'll let the people watching talk
about how strong and fast she is.
the plum blossoms still smell the same
For you, I would have given up my life
I-I got it!
She usually struggles with them,
but she defended a multi-syllable card!
I only had 10 minutes to
practice, but it worked.
It was a gamble,
but I moved "For you, I would"
from my usual position on
the inside lower right
to the inside lower left.
This was something I didn't realize
until I tried playing with my left hand.
There's a position for
multi-syllable cards that's
difficult for left-handed players to reach.
Forget about it.
If I hold back at all,
I won't be able to take a
single card against her.
There's only one thing for me to focus on.
How can I win?
now together, I guard it dear
How?!
Ayase-san appears to be reacting quickly,
but the Queen is taking all of the cards?
How?!
In
the sleepy spring sunlight,
I'm losing by a hair.
Shinobu-chan is beating
me with her accuracy.
That was one of my best cards!
The gauze and tape are too heavy.
I've worked hard on my accuracy.
Why?
Aren't you the ace of the team that
won the tournament yesterday?
You and your friends accomplished
your goal, right?
So why?
Why are you so focused on
me when you're injured?
So focused on karuta?
...I could not hide my love,
"Since I could not hide"?!
She took the Queen's best card!
Is something wrong?
I-I'm fine.
I lost "Since I could not hide."
I'm sending a card.
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Please wait!
people would always ask if
I was pining for someone
Wow!
No mercy on an injured opponent.
Ayase-san...
as helpless autumn leaves
are caught against the flow
So many cute pictures!
If you like karuta, we can visit
the nearby karuta society.
I understand.
Nice to meet you, Shinobu-chan.
Oh, there's a girl your age who just joined.
You can practice with her.
She's over there.
now bloom inside the nine-fold palace
Long last we meet...
The same time.
A card touched at the same time
goes to the side it was on.
That goes to Shinobu-chan.
Better luck next time.
That's a poem written by Lady Murasaki
about a reunion with an old friend.
Another close win for me!
Shinobu-chan, we're rivals!
Shinobu-chan, why don't you
play Ryuusei-kun next?
He's much older than you are.
Give it your best shot.
Impassionate gods
have never seen
Thank you very much.
Oh, Wakamiya-san.  What was the score?
I won by 23 cards.
Impressive as always.
23 cards...
Ayase Chihaya
Honestly, you shouldn't
push yourself like this.
Look at the swelling.
You even took off the taping.
It must have hurt.
I'll go find an ice pack, so wait here.
How many cards should
I have let her take?
We should keep Shinobu-chan
away from children her age.
She'll learn to go easy on her opponents.
He's right.
The more isolated she is, the
stronger she will become.
Coach Ise is always right.
Th-Thank you!
For not going easy on me!
Let's play karuta again!
When?
When will we play?
The Queen match!
What was her name?
Satoko-chan!
In any case, the Queen
is as strong as ever.
It appears that there's no one
her age who can challenge her.
I'm worried about her motivation.
If she stops participating in
tournaments like Master Suo...
That was a sorry performance.
What's wrong with me?
I only won by 23 cards.
I lost two. And she was injured.
I even lost "Since I could not hide."
Next time, I won't let
her take a single card.
My match with Shinobu-chan is over.
It's over...
My summer is over.
Nobody wishes to see...
Over here!
Thank you very much.
I did it!
I won!
I made it to the third round!
Full power!
It was hard to tell since I'm always
surrounded by karuta freaks,
but I'm actually pretty good.
I might be able to win
the Class D tournament?!
That's amazing, Hanano-san.
I'm impressed.
Yes!  On to the semifinals!
Eliminated in the third round...
Eliminated in the third round
Hanano!  Hanano!
I made it to the semifinals!
Take a picture so I can
send it to my brothers!
What?
I have an e-mail from Ms. Miyauchi.
Oh, Mashima-senpai and...
Mashima-senpai is still in it!
I'm going to go cheer for him!
What?
I'm still in it, too...
Mashima-senpai!
What's this atmosphere?
I can't lose...  I can't lose...
I will win...  I will win...
I'll beat Mashima
and make Class A!