It's another peaceful day, Fi.
The Little Prince and
the Legendary Hero
It's another peaceful autumn day in fall.
The arranged marriage game
Leo-sama held was very popular!
Prince Leaf of the Kingdom
of Halver, who showed great
skill in the games, has become very popular—
Well? Did you rest well?
Yes, thank you.
You came all the way from Halver.
Before you go home,
you should have a look at Galette
and the rest of the continent.
Yes, I hope to learn a lot from it.
I'll meet up with you at night.
See you later.
Thank you.
And so...
I'll be here a little longer.
Okay!
Come by the barracks later.
I'm sure our men will be happy to
see a strong warrior like you.
Okay!
You're not coming with us, Gaul?
I've got work to do, so I can't.
And you know, even if he's
little, he's still a prince.
Don't be too friendly with him.
Oh, yeah.
No, I'm still very young,
and I'm not performing
my official duties now,
so feel free to think of me
as one of Vert's relatives.
Really?
That would be a lot more relaxed.
We really are relatives, too.
Jeez...
Just keep an eye on them and make
sure things don't get too crazy.
Okay, Gaul-sama.
And so...
First we eat!
A favorite of Galettian warriors...
Enjoy the lunch menu of
the Sea Dragon Tavern!
It's fresh fish from the sea.
It's a popular spot for fishermen to go, too.
Yup!
Here you are, special hero-brand soup.
And this is a popular menu item from Earth
that Nanami taught us how to make.
It's based off of bouillabaisse,
a popular dish from Earth.
Worldwide!
Come on, let's eat before it gets cold.
Let's eat!
Boys need to eat a lot and
grow up big and strong.
That's right.
Yeah.
It's hot, so be careful.
Thank you.
It's good!
Isn't it?
And this is Vannette City.
I bought the presents
I gave you here.
I see.
And if you head into a back alley...
Some places sell things
a little cheaper and less fancy.
Amazing!
The place seems so alive.
Oh my, it's Nanami-chan
and the Genoise girls.
Want to see what I've got? I got
some good dried fish today.
That's great.
We're showing Vert's relative around now,
so we'll come by later.
Okay!
I hope your cute relative enjoys his stay.
Y-Yes!
And this is where the knights work.
Um... is it okay for someone
from another country to be here?
It's fine. We're with you.
And Shinku and the others
have already come here.
Both Halver and Galette have
meeting rooms like this, right?
Yes. We discuss the war games or
hold meetings on national policy,
and make announcements.
Leo-sama and Gaul come here all the time.
Jaune, too, lately.
I've been working hard.
I've heard you're going to
be the next general, Jaune.
We don't know yet.
But if I can help Galette,
that would make me really happy.
I know how you feel!
Company 2, fire!
Fire!
They seem really fierce.
It's pretty serious for a
training exercise, isn't it?
That's the army that Gaul-sama is leading.
The people from Biscotti are
participating today, too.
Shinku and Eclair-chan are at the front.
And that's the army General
Godwin is leading.
So where's the old man?
Over there!
Old man!
Hey, old man.
What brings the four of you here?
And who's that kid?
You didn't see the marriage games?
I got back late from an expedition last
night, and I've been here all day.
You haven't seen today's news?
The marriage games were another big success,
but nobody won.
Was there anything else?
There was one other bit of news.
One other bit of news?
Oh, I heard that one of the losers was
a young man who fought very hard.
He must be pretty tough
to stand up to Lady Leo.
I'd like to see him.
Okay, here's your chance.
Huh?
Hello, General.
I'm Leaf Lang du Sha Halver,
from the kingdom of Halver!
He's the warrior who almost beat Lady Leo.
He's a relative of mine
and a prince of Halver.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Even if I didn't know,
that was very rude of me.
Please don't worry.
I'm being shown around the country.
I'm not here on official business.
I see.
You're so stiff, old man.
I hope you can be friends.
You guys are too relaxed!
General, can Prince Leaf and I
borrow the training grounds for a bit?
That's perfectly fine.
It's afternoon break just now.
Please show our soldiers the skills of
their Hero and Prince Leaf.
I'll tell Prince Gaul and the Hero Shinku.
Hey!
Right!
Prince, let's show the people
of Galette how cool you are!
I'll do my best!
Listen, everyone!
Did you see the games held
yesterday by our leader,
Lady Leonmitchelli?
Yeah!
Prince Leaf, who performed
splendidly in the games,
is here with us now.
And he and our Hero are
going to have a practice match.
Yes!
Watch carefully and use this
as inspiration for your own training.
This is a pretty great way to
entertain us on our lunch break, isn't it?
Yup!
Okay! I'm ready!
Give us a second.
Vert, I'm okay now.
Wanna bet? I'm betting on our Hero.
Then I'll bet on Prince Leaf.
What about you?
I don't bet.
You're so stiff, Eclair.
But well...
I'm interested to see who'll win.
Okay!
Here I come!
Begin the game!
Ready...
Water God's Fist!
Nice!
Nanami's amazing.
I can't believe she survived that.
She knows how to dodge.
Yeah.
I'm just a Hero who comes
here once in a while,
but I hope I can be friends with you.
Me, too, Hero Nanami!
Just call me Nanami!
Okay, Nanami-san.
Call me by my name, too.
Okay, Leaf!
I'll support you in
your love of Leo-sama.
I don't know if I love
her, it's more like...
I'm Leo-sama's Hero,
so I want to be with her always.
Is that okay? Does that bother you?
Not at all!
I don't really know
all that much about Leo-sama yet,
but since you came,
her smile's been even more wonderful.
That's what I think!
That's my answer right now.
Thanks, Leaf.
But this fight is something different!
Yes!
Here I go, Leaf!
Special move!
Their special moves exploded!
Who will be the victor?
This might be no good...
It's a tie!
Nice fanservice from Prince
Leaf to the Galette Knights.
It kind of bugs me that
I lost, but this was fun!
I won't lose next time!
Nice job, Leaf.
This is exciting!
Gaul, want to join in?
Sounds good!
Prince Leaf, want to have
another match with me?
Want to make the second round a team fight?
Then we'll play, too.
That sounds great.
You, too, old man.
Me, too?
I'm sorry.
This has turned into a pretty big deal.
No. It's fun!
Once we've played a little more
here, we're going to Biscotti.
Is there any place you want to go
or anyone you want to see?
Yes, actually...
A visitor.
Hina-sama! It's been so long!
Miss Nanami.
And the Genoise.
And who's this?
Hello there.
This is Prince Leaf from
the Kingdom of Halver.
When we told him about you,
he said he'd love to meet you.
I see.
It's not a big place, but enjoy yourselves.
Thank you.
Halver is far to the north,
so we don't know a lot about
the central continent.
I've been granted permission by Lady
Leonmitchelli, Princess Millihiore,
and Duchess Couver to visit
the capitals of their nations.
I was told that you, Lady d'Arquien,
are a free knight of the Biscotti Knights,
the continent's "strongest swordmaster,"
and more than anything,
a member of the Hero King's party.
I'm honored to meet you.
They're not that serious when
they say I'm the strongest.
There are lots of strong
swordsmen everywhere.
N-No, I mean...
More importantly, it must
be tiring to be so formal.
Relax. Relax.
Okay.
Okay!
Tea's ready!
Thanks!
That's great!
Thank you!
Jaune-chan, Noir-chan, you join in, too.
Okay!
Snacktime!
Now then, would you like to hear some
old stories about the Hero King's era?
I'd love to hear them!
It'd end up being a pretty long story.
You're all going to Pastillage
this evening, right?
Yes!
We're all going!
Then it would be good
to ask Adel afterwards.
I'll ask her to tell you.
R-Really?
Sure.
It's always good to have a young person
listen to your old stories.
Thank you!
Come on, enjoy the Fuugetsuan's special buns
while they're still hot!
Okay!
I heard we're going to Pastillage.
Are they doing something there?
I see, so you haven't heard.
They have a fun event going on!
Featuring the princess!
Because I know my wish will come true!
Let's hold each other passionately!
Like those days when we used to run...
The promise we made, hand in hand,
I know it will always come true!
I'm waiting here.
Thank you!
Please enjoy my concert here
in the Pastillage national hall!
Princess Millihiore is so amazing.
It's about to get even more amazing.
Yeah!
I'll never forget...
You taught me...
Thank you all for waiting, everyone.
Princess Millihiore will
be arriving shortly!
Everybody, thanks for
coming today!
With your help, today's concert
was a success.
It's thanks to all of you.
Thank you all!
We've prepared some
simple food and drink for you!
The princess will give a speech later,
so until then, enjoy yourselves.
Halver has singing competitions,
but this is much more exciting!
The princess's concerts are a
little special, aren't they?
Prince Leaf!
Princess Millihiore!
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you.
You were amazing.
The prince was waving his
shine stick the whole time.
Thank you.
That makes me happy.
It was fun!
I'd love to go to
Halver someday for a tour.
Yes! I'm sure my people would love it!
Excuse me, Hero Shinku.
The people from Dragée and Orange
both said they'd love to see you.
Really?
Would you come with the princess?
Sure.
Okay, Prince Leaf.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
Yes.
That's so great.
Leo-sama!
I heard from d'Arquien that
you're going to see Adel-sama after this?
Yes, that's right.
Couver and I may go, as well.
I'm interested to hear stories
from the Hero King, as well.
Yes!
I'm surprised you're interested
in old stories, though.
The stories of the Hero King
are famous in Halver, too!
And so you see, ancestor, I'd like you to
tell some old stories to our guests!
That's fine!
It'd be good to have Valerie
there, too, wouldn't it?
Yup!
Then I'll take you to the
perfect spot for telling stories!
Valerie, you listening?
Couver's friends want to hear stories.
I'd like you to tell them, too.
I'm in the middle of some research I haven't
been able to get to for a long time.
Oh, don't say that.
Hina will be coming, too.
Please!
Oh, fine.
I'll take everybody there, okay?
I'll bring you the
hot black tea you love!
Thanks!
Old stories, huh?
This way!
The Hero King Adel-sama, and
the Demon King Valerie...
It's kind of making me nervous.
Don't worry.
They're my ancestors.
Ancestor!
Welcome to our library.
Are you the ones who want
to hear old stories?
Yes!
Oh my. Sit down.
Yup!
Maids, get tea ready!
Yes.
It's quite the atmosphere you've got here.
I just happened to be here.
Telling old stories to the young people
is part of the fun of being old.
Right, Hina?
Well, that's true...
Oh?
It seems like the two Heroes and your
princess are missing, Hina-san.
They've got work to do.
They'll come later.
Yeah.
Okay, it looks like we're ready.
I'll tell you the story then.
It was a long time ago,
when the five of us traveled together.
Me, and Valerie,
and the swordmaster Hina,
and Isuka the swordsmith,
who's probably off drinking sake somewhere.
And one more.
The last princess of the
Kingdom of Pastillage,
and its last ruler.
The person who summoned
me as a hero to Flognarde.
Clarifier Einz Pastillage.
We called her Fi.
The Sea Dragon Tavern seafood restaurant!
Check out the cute waitress uniforms, too!
Why am I wearing one?
Next time—
Recollection: The Story of the
Hero and the Princess
Hot!
Huh?