Polishing my body and soul...
I want you...
Hey, Mr. Jiro,
I need you to clean the backyard
once you're done with that.
Roger that, young master.
Morning!
Right! A new trimester starts today!
The uniform looks well on you, Ohana.
I agree.
School uniforms really bring
out the purity of a girl...
Mr. Jiro.
I'm off to clean the backyard!
He's good at cleaning the
bathhouse for some reason.
It probably combines fun
and profit for him.
Minko, we should get going soon!
Minko!
That uniform's too big for you.
You look like you're dressing up
as an elementary school student.
Wha-
Hey, Tohru.
Where's the new dish you
said you thought of?
You don't mind giving it a taste?!
What are you doing?
I'm so nervous...
You'll be fine.
I'm sure you'll make friends in no time.
I wish you had said that
in front of Tohru.
Huh?
Nothing.
I hope I'm placed in the
same class as you two!
Being in the same class with
you would be so balut.
Isn't that word hard to
use in everyday life?
Tough to tell whether you're
referring to me or the situation.
Shut up, you balut-
Wow.
It came from over there.
Oh!
Fukuya is a famous hot
spring inn, right?
Fukuya
Yeah. It's also listed
on many guidebooks.
A powerful rival has appeared!
"Appeared"?
They've been around longer than our inn.
Wow!
So pretty!
You look like you're having
so much fun, Ohana.
Look!
Usually, when it's in this much bloom,
there's so many people
crowding around it-
Wait for me, Ko!
My bag got stuck!
Don't leave my side!
This is a little embarrassing...
Then how about this?
I was always being protected by Ko.
Ohana?
Something wrong?
N-No.
What should I do about
my reply to his text...?
Faculty Room
You can handle the rest, right?
Thanks, Nako.
No problem. Bye.
Please let me be in the
same class as them...
For crying out loud!
Please let me be in the
same class as them...
Are you Matsumae?
Y-Yes.
Umm...
Matsumae... Ohana!
Ohana!
It's the first day of a new trimester.
Get your butts in your seats already!
Good news for you all: a new student.
Attention!
Introduce yourself, new kid!
U-Umm...
I'm Matsumae Ohana.
I came from Tokyo.
Awesome! Tokyo!
I've seen that hairpin
in a magazine before!
I bought it in a 300 yen shop.
Her perm is like that of
a young foreigner boy!
So fashionable!
I just have naturally wavy hair.
Her skirt's height is also adjusted!
Thank Tohru for that.
Minko-
Matsumae!
Where in Tokyo are you from?!
Shinjuku? Harajuku? Shibuya? Odaiba?!
People don't live in those places.
No, they do.
Do you have a boyfriend?!
B-Boyfriend?
K-Ko isn't really a...
Tsurugi works at the
same inn as you, right?
Minko?
Yeah.
Yup.
We live in the same room-
Seriously?!
You gotta tell me how
Princess Minko she looks
outside of school!
P-Princess Minko?
Yeah!
How do I explain it...
She looks like a plateau girl
who would look well in a white dress!
The fact that she seems a
little stern and unshakeable
makes me think of an expensive flower!
She's usually just
wearing a jersey and is
kind of awkward in expressing herself.
Do me a favor and take a picture
of her outside of school!
I'll pay you 3000 yen!
What?!
If it's one of her right
out of the shower,
I'll pay you 3500 yen!
How dare you look at the
princess with dirty eyes!
We'll settle this on the rooftop!
E-Excuse me...
Cut it out!
Y-Yuina!
Geez, people!
You're troubling Ohana!
Right!
Ohana, our next class is Home Ec!
We're going to be practicing!
Let's go together, okay?
See you all later!
I can't believe I'm in the same class
at the two most popular
girls in our grade!
I'm probably using up my
lifetime's worth of good luck.
Umm...
Sorry to drag you all this way.
They're a noisy bunch, aren't they?
But they're all nice.
Please let it slide.
So she was saving me from them...
Th-Thank you.
You're also not from around here?
Huh?
Oh, my dialect?
It's just that I felt like speaking
in a fake Kansai dialect today!
Isn't that a little... no.
Isn't that really odd?
You're the granddaughter of the
manager of Kissuiso, right?
I know what it's like
to be in your shoes.
Huh?
Wakura Yuina.
I'm the successor to the
Fukuya hot spring inn!
That big inn?
It's just old.
Do you study every day
to prepare yourself
for succeeding the inn?
Not really.
Though my grandmother is pretty bossy.
So you don't plan on
becoming the next manager?
It really doesn't matter either way.
Huh?
As long as I'm having fun,
I don't mind either way!
You're so cool, Yuina.
What?
Oh, there's also someone
cool at Kissuiso.
There is?
But who? Jiroumaru?
But he's pretty perverted.
Seriously?!
Minchi is really popular
amongst the boys.
She always finds many love
letters in her shoe box.
Yeah?
Well, she *is* pretty.
So, what did you need?
Speak of the devil.
Min-
Listen,
I've always liked you, Tsurugi.
So...
But I don't like you.
Harsh...
Hang on!
He's not backing down!
Th-Then, what kind of guy do you like?
Why should I answer that?
I'm pretty serious about all this.
I can't just give up on you,
and I want to become more
like your ideal man.
So...!
Someone with a sharp tongue,
but is actually kind.
Someone who always takes the initiative
and is serious about work.
Someone with this much hair,
and eyes that are slanted upward.
Someone with long eyelashes.
She sure is being concrete.
Is the person Minchi likes...
He must be someone substantial,
unlike people like Tohru.
U-Umm...
What the heck is a "plateau girl"?!
Being asked out behind the
school building?! What?!
What's with this
bittersweet situation?!
I'm sorry!
Look at me. My life consists
only of work and no men.
That's it.
I'm going to take a picture of Minko
with her hair done up tight,
and ruin the imaginations
of the boys at her school.
What?
N-Nothing...
What are you doing, you moron?
When you're skewering,
you need to add a twist motion.
Like this.
All in one push.
Miss Tomoe, please!
You seem pretty relaxed, Ohana.
Don't tell me you have a boyfriend!
K-Ko isn't really...
Ko?
Is that a boy?!
I-It is, but...
You've got it all wrong!
You traitor!!
From: Ko
I'm sorry I didn't see you off.
Good luck with everything, Ohana!!
To: Ko
I'm doing fine.
How are you, Ko?
I feel like I'm cheating him if I reply,
pretending as though he
never told me he likes me.
Delete.
I appreciate what you
told me the other day.
I'm doing fine!
Delete!
What do I do?!
Ohana?
Bending, stretching,
hopping exercise.
I'm surprised.
Even you have trouble getting
things across to people.
I'm just dumb.
That's not true.
I'm a bit envious because
you always speak your mind.
Whoa!
W-What's...!
W-What?
It lives around here.
It's a grey heron.
I-Is it okay for it to be around here?
Aren't they usually at the zoo?
This is the place, Ohana.
Oh, is this about the
neighborhood association?
Yes, thank you.
What a huge lobby.
Are you girls from Kissuiso?
Y-Yes!
She's... kinda scary.
I'm glad you came with me...
N-Nako?
I'm too scared to come here alone.
Doesn't this scare you?
Want to stop by somewhere
on the way back?
S-Sure, I don't-
I've always been withdrawn
since I was a kid.
I began working at the
inn in order to change.
Wow, you've got dynamism.
But I always come here
to pray to this goddess.
A goddess?
It's a little girl who tamed a fox.
So she keeps getting lost.
A goddess getting lost?
Yeah.
That's why the Bonbori Festival
takes places in October.
Bonbori Festival...?
October.
On the day when all of the gods
in Japan return to Izumo,
everyone holds a bonbori
up high to make a path.
Wow...
In order to prevent the gods
from straying from their paths.
A path...!
So pretty...
That must be a really
pretty festival, Nakochi!
"Nakochi"?
Minko is Minchi, so I figured
you can be Nakochi.
Is it going to bother you?
No!
I'm really happy to
be given a nickname.
Y-Yeah?
I've always wanted
to have friends I can
use nicknames with.
Tsurugi Minko | Minmi
Minmin | Mimoh | Minpo
But I could never come
up with anything good.
Minko-chan.
Minchan.
Minmin...
Minchan
Okay.
M-Minchi-
I-I couldn't finish it!
"Minchi" just doesn't sound right!
It just doesn't!
What is it, Nako?
Well,
about the Mist Room's
breakfast tomorrow,
Wow, that's interesting!
It's not...
I wonder if people around here
tend to write down their thoughts.
Minko did the same with "balut," too.
Thoughtful people...
Huh?
Nothing.
Nakochi, think of a
nickname for me, too!
I-I'll try.
Looking forward to it!
I enjoy the scent of the
cherry blossom in here.
Yes, Tohru made it.
That kiddo has really improved.
Okay...
The table is set.
Okay, then...
Hello?
Oh...
I'll be right back, Ohana.
Okay.
Hey! What are you doing?!
Of all people...
That's not where you put the fish!
Sorry.
It makes the food look
bad, don't you think?
Oh yeah, how was school?
Huh?
Bet you didn't make any friends.
Miss Inconsiderate.
The successor to the Fukuya inn
goes to your school, right?
Who, Yuina?
I can't believe you
two are the same age.
Wouldn't be able to tell
with your body development.
Are you referring to my upper arm?
Minko!
I'll do it.
She has other things to do.
Go on.
Here, Minko.
Okay.
She saved me...
She's actually a nice girl...
I wish I could become friends with her.
I need to start by
calling her "Minchi."
I-I need to say something.
Let's see...
Oh!
Girl talk expands when we
talk about a common enemy.
Hey, Minko?
Thanks for earlier.
Tohru is alawys complaining
about something.
His villainy is apparent in his eyes!
She reacted!
This is where I use her nickname...
Don't you agree, Minchi?
Huh?!
You're such a balut!
I am?
Tohru never "complains."
He may be sharp-tongued,
but that's only because
he's always thinking about others!
He's more determined
than anyone, and...
He's kinder than anyone I know!
"Someone with a sharp tongue,
but is actually kind and determined."
Where have I heard this before...
Minchi, don't tell me the
person you like is...!
Minchi!
Oh dear.
Good night!
Good morning!
Minko!
Hang on! I'm sorry!
I said something stupid again.
About Tohru...
Balut!
Why don't you understand
that what you're saying
*right now* is stupid?!
I'm sorry!
Tohru?
Yuina?!
~Let's party~
"Let's party"?
M-Minko!
Episode 4
Grey Heron Rhapsody
Falling in love with
someone is incredible.
He won't be coming.
What do you--
I saw it last night.
Kitchen hand.
Please let me work here!
Episode 5
A Tearful Chef Romance