My name is Motoyama Tomomichi.
I'm ugly.
My friend wants to meet
behind the school building.
What could he want?
Yamane-dono!
Motoyama-kun.
She would be Kurihara-dono.
Leave Behind My Corpse
The kind lady who has shown affection
to as gross a man as Yamane-dono.
Why would you bring me here
when you're alone together?
Well, Kurihara-san called me here.
It's the first time a girl's asked me
to meet behind the school.
I was afraid of coming alone,
so I wanted you to come along.
S-So what did you want, Kurihara-san?
I made too much pudding,
so I thought I'd share it.
What a clumsy excuse.
I-I don't deserve that.
Yamane-dono appears to be
so fixed on his ugliness,
he can't understand what
the lady is trying to do.
Accept it with the greatest of gratefulness.
She made it with you in mind.
No way, no way! Absolutely no way!
You're insulting her.
If Yamane isn't going to budge...
Kurihara-dono, was it?
I apologize for interrupting.
I shall leave you two alone—
No, please stay here.
You, too?!
You're a wuss, too?!
You're accepting the pudding, Yamane-dono!
I don't think I should be
the only one, though...
I actually brought two.
Really?
That's great, huh? Motoyama-kun?
She made that pudding for you, Yamane-dono!
Wh-What are you talking about?!
Kuriyama-san's sharing them out of courtesy!
No.
She called you behind the school.
It's not out of courtesy!
You've noticed, have you not?
About how Kurihara-dono feels about you?
S-Stop it!
Rumors would start flying
if she gave me pudding in public!
If let for while...
You're far too self-deprecating, Yamane-dono.
Just accept the gesture.
How could you, Motoyama-kun?
Y-You got me.
Huh?
What? I didn't push you that hard.
It seems that Kurihara-dono
is more important to you
than me, your best friend.
Then I shall be on my way.
Have the pudding amongst yourselves.
M-Motoyama-kun!
U-Um...
W-Would you please take a hint?
I'm embarrassed with my terrible acting.
I want to get out of here!
Next time, I'll make some for you, too, okay?
She's a better woman than I'd imagined.
Best of luck, you two.
Okay, I'll be going.
O-Okay.
Thanks.
The End
I think my girlfriend's been on edge lately.
Goda-kun, could you open this lid for me?
Here.
Oh man, thanks!
Jealousy
What's wrong?
Kamine, have I done something recently?
Huh? Wh-Why?
I get the sense that you're angry at me.
N-Not really.
You haven't done anything.
Oh.
Takeru, let's arm wrestle.
Ready, and...
I'm pretty sure
Kamine's angry about something.
Goda!
I need to apologize to Kamine.
I need to go to our usual meeting spot.
She's not here.
Is she not here yet?
Kamine Ayaka
Out of service area
Redial      Cancel
I-Is she blocking me?
She's that angry?
Guess who.
K-Kamine.
You're here.
Yeah.
Did you think I went home?
Went home?
I thought you were done with me.
Ah, no.
Sorry.
I wanted you to worry about me,
so I was being a bit mean.
You were so angry at me
that you had to be mean?
S-Sorry.
Let's go home.
Aren't you going to hold hands with me?
I mean, you held hands with Patricia-chan.
Are you upset that
I arm wrestled with Patricia?
Oh.
You could have told me.
I would have arm wrestled with you.
No!
It's not that I want to arm wrestle with you.
In fact, I don't want you to.
What does that mean?
Nah, you'll just hate me if I told you.
Sorry for troubling you.
Why would I ever hate you, Kamine?
I'm your boyfriend, aren't I?
I'll hear anything you need to say.
R-Really?
You won't hate me?
I won't.
Then...
Don't get too close to other girls.
Call me by my first name from now on.
I can't blame Patricia-chan,
but I'm the only one who can call you Takeru.
And don't hold hands with other girls,
not even arm wrestling.
I'm the only one who can hold hands with you.
You can help them open plastic bottles,
but if you're nice to someone,
you have to be even nicer to me!
So that's what it was.
I'm so needy, aren't I?
No, but you did surprise me.
It's fine!
I know I'm being stupid, too!
No, I don't mind.
Call me Ayaka, then.
Uh...
The End
It's been a while since
my girlfriend and I started dating,
but we haven't even kissed yet.
How can I get to kiss her?
Hey, Chiaki...
What's up, Kana?
Gotta poop?
No, you idiot!
Look!
Lovers
Isn't that Goda and Kamine-san?
They don't mess around in class.
They've been doing it here.
T-Takeru-kun...
Yeah, Kamine?
Aren't you going to call me by my first name?
Was Kamine-san always like that?!
R-Right.
Ayaka-san.
That's it.
So?
It's nothing.
I just wanted you to say my name.
I'll say your name
as much as you want, Ayaka.
Was Goda-san always that manly?!
I guess people do change
when they're in love.
We haven't changed, though...
Kami— Ayaka, you've changed
since we started going out.
Sorry, am I annoying?
No, you've gotten cuter.
You've gotten cuter, too, Kana-san.
I'll destroy you.
Let's get going.
This hurts to watch.
Y-Yeah.
Can I be more needy, then?
What is it?
So... I want to kiss.
Now?
No?
Of course not!
You're in broad daylight!
Right, Kana-san?
No kidding!
All right.
D-Does it really work like that?
How much is Goda kissing all the time?
No, Goda-kun's right!
It's that sense of initiative
that you don't have, Chiaki!
N-No way!
Wait, Goda-kun, I wasn't ready for that!
You weren't?
Goda— Takeru-kun, you're always so sudden.
Sorry.
Take this.
No way!
You see that?!
The Kamine-san!
Doing that!
Huh?!
You expect me to do that?!
There's nothing wrong with the girl
making the first move.
Jeez, and you call yourself a guy?
Let's do it properly next time.
Yeah.
There's no sense fighting.
Okay, I'll kiss you, then.
I-It's fine.
I'll start.
On the count of three, then?
Fine.
One, two, three...
Hey, it's Chiaki-kun and Kana-san.
It's Goda and Kamine-san!
What are you guys doing here?
N-Nothing, really.
What were you guys doing?
Huh? Um...
Nothing, really.
The End
What a coincidence!
I invited my girlfriend over.
Thanks for having me.
No one's home today.
I'm gonna kiss my girlfriend today!
Bubbles
E-Everyone's on vacation right now.
Oh, what time do you have to be home today?
No, I'll take it even further.
I have to be home by eight.
Oh, okay.
Damn Chiaki.
I mean, we haven't even kissed yet,
so I kind of expected that much, but...
Huh?
Am I wearing good undies today?
I have 'til eight. I have 'til eight.
Good.
Okay...
Why don't we study for exams?
G-Good idea.
Uh... Is the air conditioner setting okay?
I-I guess it's a bit hot.
Why am I avoiding this?
I decided I'd make a move today!
Kana!
Y-Yes?
Ki...
Was kinematics on the exam?
Huh? Yeah.
Ki...
What about kinetic energy?
That is too, yes.
Shit.
W-Want to take a break?
I'll get something to drink.
O-Okay.
I'm going to strike out again.
Why can't I just go for it?
We're running out of time.
I have to leave before seven.
I want the mood to be right
for our first kiss, though.
There's no point rushing it.
What's wrong, Chiaki?
Nothing.
Where are the drinks?
And why are you so red?
Kana, want to kiss?
This kid...
There we go.
Kana...
Wait a second!
Did you drink something weird?
I don't want to do it like this!
You keep telling me to take the initiative!
That doesn't mean anything goes!
Besides, our first kiss
is going to be a precious memory.
Kana!
Listen to me!
I do want to kiss you, too,
but I want to kiss the normal Chiaki.
I don't need a special mood or anything.
I just want to kiss you normally.
I can't believe you'd rely on that stuff.
You're right.
This is wrong.
Chiaki...
Psyche! I'm just acting!
Yes!
I've finally kissed you!
You're so low.
Why so serious?
You gotta play along.
Next time, why not start one pretending
that you're getting attacked by an alien?
Or how about a soccer PK goal into one?
Ow!
I'm going home.
Are you actually upset?
That was just another one of our skits.
I'm done with our duo!
Wait, say what?
How am I supposed to react to that?
Kana-chan?
Next episode: Tuning.
Tuning