Kawagoe City Daisan Middle School
Opening Ceremony
Were you on it?
Hey, I'm in Class 3.
I'm Class 2.
There's me!
Nakajima
Kotono
Ninomiya
Hina
Mizuno
Akane
Miyamoto
Aira
Ryuuzaki
Shiho
Class 1.
None of us are together.
Are you with anyone?
No one in the track club.
Aww...
Hey, at least we can see
each other in the club.
That's true.
You think we'll get some first-years?
I hope we get lots!
Shoot, I forgot about the poster!
What?
Hira asked me to do it.
The lawyer one?
Yeah, that one.
Want me to help?
Thanks.
Cool, let's make this happen.
Time to get serious!
Right, Akane?
Oh, yeah.
Starting today, I'll be a
third-year in middle school.
Good morning, everyone.
It's April.
The cherry trees are blooming,
and it's the start of a new year.
To the first-years,
Kawagoe City Daisan Middle School
Term 1 Opening Ceremony
I hope that you will hold on to the
fresh state of mind that you're in now,
and that you'll live your coming years
at this school to their fullest.
To the new second and
third-years, your classes...
Man, I'm beat.
I can't wait to get home.
I'm so nervous.
Stay calm.
Stay calm!
Okay.
Even in middle school, there's inequality.
The upper and lower class.
The cool clubs and the lame ones.
Attractiveness and grades.
We use every weapon at our disposal
to establish a pecking order.
Yay!
Wow, you're popular.
Damn, Roman.
What?
Player.
You bastard!
Get off me.
Check this out.
What?
This doesn't hurt.
Your shoulder blades. See?
Dude, ow!
Yeah, right.
Ow! Seriously!
Really?
Want me to try it on you?
Sure.
Doesn't hurt.
Um...
Nope.
You guys...
Akanecchi.
It's me, Aira. Remember me?
We were in the same third grade class.
Oh, yeah.
You're in the track club, aren't you?
Yeah. Nice to meet you.
Do you know her?
No.
Ryouko-chan's here.
All right, take your seats, please.
Track and Field Club
Members Souper Wanted
I hope we get lots of first-years.
I know.
Can you believe we're third-years now?
Okay, let's do this!
Let's do this!
Hey, look!
Members Souper Wanted
It says "souper" wanted.
Souper!
Who wrote that?
Soup wanted!
Stop it, you're killing me!
Kota!
Kotarou.
See you tomorrow.
You'd better show me that novel.
I'm not showing you.
I'm taking the key.
Open
Feel free to talk to me.
Librarian
I'm at the desk up front.
Ready?
Go!
Akane, your arms!
Keep going, Mizuno!
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Apparently we're eating out today.
What? Really?
Want to take a shower?
I'll be quick.
Dear, turn the TV off.
Fine, fine.
I'm so hungry.
Cafe Restaurant
Guest
Table for four.
You're always on LINE.
What do you care?
That kid from before?
I'll have the mixed grill and mini-ramen.
I brought us water.
Thanks.
You'll get fat.
You don't want any, Kotarou?
I run. Can I have dessert, too?
I'll get the drink bar.
You should stick with tea.
You're ordering too much.
Eat well. You're working hard for your club.
What about you, Onee-chan?
Pasta salad and the drink bar.
That's it?
The seasonal veggie meal
is bamboo shoot rice.
You're ordering beer and
the drink bar, dear?
Come on, what's wrong with that?
That sounds good.
Isn't that wasteful?
I want both.
That, and a beer.
Please don't get drunk.
I thought I had it in here.
Man, my daughter's so cold. At least let me
have a beer while we're out, would you?
I told you to check before we left.
Found it.
I think I'll have this one.
Okay.
Maybe I'll have this one.
Gratin and lasagna both sound good, too.
Want me to choose for you?
Or maybe pasta?
Dad, be quiet.
It'll make me fat.
Okay.
Want to order a drink, Kotarou?
You're ordering from the
drink bar, right, Kotarou?
Would you mind pressing
the buzzer for me, honey?
Okay.
Are you listening, Kotarou?
I'll have the drink bar.
Dazai said...
"How excruciatingly arduous and
unbearable it is to live."
Want to order sautéed spinach, Akane?
Iron is good for you.
You're ordering too much.
Akane will eat it.
Right?
You have a tournament soon, right?
You have to eat lots of healthy food.
Stop it.
Oh? What's wrong?
Hey, chubby!
I'm going to get something to drink.
Tasty
Water
Iced Coffee
Akane, can you get some for the rest of us?
The usual, please.
I think I'll have melon soda.
Akane, can you carry all that?
Do you know him?
He's in my class.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Hey, Mom, get this.
What? Really?
Wait, what?
Kawagoe Daisan
Track and Field Club
My daughter, Akane, is in his class.
Oh, my.
Kotarou didn't mention a thing.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Azumi Kotarou's mother.
Oh, hi.
Nice to meet you.
Hello there.
Will that be all for your order?
Wow, look at all this food!
Hilarious!
What's wrong with it?
Eat up.
Hey, she's cute.
Don't do this to them, dear.
Kotarou's a teenager now, you know.
Are you okay, Kotarou?
It's bitter...
Delivery
now available
Reserve now!
Thank you.
Bye for now.
I'm so nervous.
I want my squeezie.
H-Hey...
Don't tell anyone at school about today.
It's embarrassing.
Okay.
Th-Thanks.
Kawagoe Daisan
Track and Field Club
But that doesn't embarrass you?
We haven't spoken since then,
even though we've both noticed each other.
All right, now that we've
finished assigning tasks...
There's going to be a
briefing after school today
Referee Group
Nakajima Kotono
Tabata Kousuke
Recorder Group
Sasano Hana
Yasumoto Keigo
Equipment Group
Yoshioka
Mizuno
Toudou
Azumi
Marking Group
Kasukabe
for each of the Sports Festival task groups.
After the announcements,
we're going to have each task group
meet up in separate classrooms, and...
Equipment Group
Now that we're all here, I'd like to begin.
I'm Hira of the track club.
The track club will be taking on
the equipment group's work.
I'd like to ask you all to help with that.
As I'm sure you're aware if
you were involved last year,
we'll be doing things like preparing
the equipment for each event.
It's curling up...
Huh? LINE?
We made a group with the task
members in our class last year.
It made things really easy.
You should ask them, Akane.
Okay...
Hey, can you guys come here for a second?
What's up?
Yo!
Don't you have club?
I'm not going today.
Skipping?
No.
I'm writing at home today.
Let me read it when you're done.
No way.
Come on, what's there to lose?
That's not what it's about.
Yeah, it is!
LINE...
Miyamoto Aira
Do you know the guys' LINE IDs?
I have Toudou and Yoshioka's.
Don't worry.
Thank you!
Got it.
There we go.
Equipment Group
Now I just need Curly-kun's.
Here are the contacts for the group.
All Equipment Group members,
please meet up at the gym storage
room at lunchtime on April 14th.
Thank you!
Hey, Nagahara, did you check LINE yesterday?
You never responded.
Sorry. Arcade.
Unbelievable!
Jeez.
I said I'm sorry.
You're awful.
Sorry, Setsuko.
You ignored me last time, too.
I got "Perfect" on the taiko game.
Really? Wow!
I'm a drum god.
Taiko?
You don't know it?
Taiko no Tetsujin.
I heard Nagahara's really good at it.
He's so damn cool!
Yup, I am.
Yeah, I want to see.
Akanecchi, wanna go to
the bathroom with me?
Okay.
Hey.
Hello.
We're going to be practicing
for the festival next week.
Okay.
Schoolgirl
Dazai
Osamu
Sensei doesn't even know that there is
a rose embroidered on my underwear.
That's a good short story.
Dazai writes a woman's inner
thoughts in first-person.
No way a normal guy would know
how a girl feels, though, right?
Schoolgirl
Dazai Osamu
I guess.
Here you go.
The one we were talking about before.
Happy End
Yudemen
Yudemen?
It's the first album by a folk rock
supergroup called Happy End.
All the members ended up becoming
huge in the music industry.
They're an amazing group.
Wow...
Hold on to it for as long as you want.
Thank you.
Any books you want?
I'll take this one.
This one's on me.
You should read all kinds of books.
Azumi, you weren't there for
the equipment group meeting.
I'm sorry.
Everyone else is doing their part.
I'm going to have you help, too.
Okay.
The scoreboard is in the gym storage.
LINE!
Bring it out.
Yes, sir.
U-Um...
You scared me!
I'm sorry, I forgot to contact you.
There's a contact list
for the equipment group.
Oh...
Can you give me your LINE ID?
I made a group for the task members.
Oh.
Yeah.
I don't have my phone on me right now.
Then, uh...
Here's mine.
Got it.
I'll help.
It's okay.
I feel bad, though.
But what about your club?
I LINE'd them.
It won't take long if we do it together.
You got dust on you.
Seriously?
Your back.
Uh-oh.
All better.
R-Right.
I'm really sorry.
It's fine.
Bye.
Yeah.
Mizuno Akane
Azumi-kun has joined
Looking forward to working with you.
Kotarou has joined.
Looking forward to it
Dazai once said that the feeling of
joy is perhaps like a speck of gold,
glimmering faintly at the
bottom of a river of grief.
Your boyfriend?
No way!
I'm going to mess with her.
Spring and Hard Times