They're late.
Relax a little, Kei.
These people would be late
for their own mother's funeral.
I know. But I've got somewhere to be.
Meeting a lady?
Yeah, she's gorgeous.
A lovely blue-eyed brunette.
Every night she digs her nails into my skin.
Oh, you mean Kuroi.
Finally. There they are.
Let's get to work, then.
You got the cash, mister?
You shitheads are late.
The cops could be by at any minute.
The cash. Do you have it? Or not?
What about you? You got the stuff?
It's supposed to be good quality stuff, right?
Shipped straight from the source.
Show us the money. Money first.
You piece of shit...
Calm down.
Look, here it is.
Fifty grand in cold, hard cash.
Now show us the stuff.
What do you think, mister?
A real fairy.
Yeah, that's good quality, all right.
Right, Kei?
A higher race, huh?
You could make some
really good drugs with this.
Where'd you get it?
Afraid that's a trade secret, mister.
Whatever. We'll take it.
--Rick.
--Right.
Thanks for the business, mister. Thanks.
Pleasure working with you guys.
Glad it worked out.
I'm happy too.
Now we can finally get to the point.
This is the San-Teresa Metropolitan Police.
You're under arrest.
You bastards are cops?
You're under arrest for
kidnapping and human trafficking.
This fairy is a Semanian citizen.
On your knees, hands above your heads.
Get to it.
Damn it! You shithead cops set us up!
You've got quite the potty mouth, don't you?
Rick, read 'em their rights.
You can do the honors, Kei.
Alrighty, here we go.
Listen carefully.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything that comes out
of that foul mouth of yours
may be used against you in a court of law.
You have the right to a lawyer.
If you can't afford to pay
one of those meddling shitheads,
you will be provided a public defender.
So grateful you could cry, right?
Go to hell, pigs!
Hey...
Rick!
"You pathetically weak barbarians..."
"I'm taking the girl."
That's no Earth language... Farbani?
"The fairy was always meant to come to me."
Shut your damn mouth, alien...
Rick...
Rick!
Damn it all!
Fifteen years ago, a hyperspace gate
appeared in the middle of the Pacific.
Beyond the gate lay a strange world
filled with fairies and monsters.
Kariaena Island. The city of San-Teresa.
This city is Earth's "front door."
Over two million citizens
from this other world live here.
A mixture of different races and
diverse cultures, haves and have-nots...
The world's newest "city of dreams."
But in the shadows of all this
chaos lurked countless crimes.
Drugs. Prostitution. Weapons smuggling.
The San-Teresa Metropolitan Police maintained
a special unit to deal with these crimes.
Matoba, they found the perp's body.
--No entry!
--It was lying on the road in Apple Hills.
Apple Hills? That's two miles away.
Chief Roth, I got three clean hits with a 9mm.
No way in hell he made it that far.
If he was a normal criminal, no.
It was one of those goddamn aliens.
So he was being controlled by
a Semanian wizard, you think?
The perp was speaking in Farbani.
Using vocab from their intellectual class.
He said that fairy was special.
I'll get things in order.
Matoba, you get some rest.
Not happening.
My partner of four years was just killed.
I'm gonna find him and make him pay.
That's an order, Sergeant Matoba.
I'm sorry about what happened to Rick.
But that's why you need
to get some rest. Got it?
What the hell am I supposed to tell his wife?
I'll talk to her.
No, I'll do it.
I want your report on my desk
by 9:00 AM tomorrow.
Roger.
Shit!
Mister, I'll wash your car for you.
It doesn't need washing.
Don't say that.
See?
Three hundred dollars. If you don't pay it,
your car might get banged up.
Money. Now.
Scared, doreany?
Fine, fine. Calm down.
Hurry up!
Now, where'd I put it?
There we go.
Here.
Pick it up. And appreciate it.
You bastard...
You're Semanians, right?
Earth may be weak, but there are
scary people here. Remember that.
Whatever...
"Yes, sir," you mean.
Y-Yes, sir...
Get lost.
Pathetic...
Okay, go! Go!
Oh, Kei! Rick's not home yet.
Did something happen?
No... This can't be.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
About tomorrow...
There's been a change of plans.
I need you to go meet a noble for me.
What?
Go meet a noble.
A VIP from the Farbani Kingdom
is arriving early tomorrow morning.
You want me to go meet some alien noble?
That's a diplomat's job.
We don't have enough detectives
who can speak their language.
No thanks. Let me hunt down
the guy who killed Rick.
The VIP might be involved in this.
What?
Go get them.
I've already talked to the coast guard.
Bossy bastard...
Hey.
We're almost to the gate.
You ever been to their world?
Yup. I was in the military.
In the war, huh?
I was stuffed inside a transport plane,
so I didn't get to see the gate itself.
Nobody can see the Mirage Gate.
We need to rely on information
from our observation satellites.
But those damn aliens
can tell where the gate is
just by looking at the wind and tides.
And do a damn sight better job than we can.
And that's why the coast guard's always busy?
Yeah. If we wanted to catch all
the smugglers and illegal immigrants,
we'd need twice the funding and manpower.
There they are.
It's some important noble, right?
I'll let you deal with them.
A child? A servant, maybe?
Where's the VIP?
Hey.
I am Exedilica, of the Knights of Mirvor.
Do Earth sailors not even
have the ritual of welcoming?
Do you not know how to talk?
Um... no.
Then answer me. Well?
I didn't notice you.
I see.
My name is
Tilarna Barsh Mirvor Imsedalya Iyeh
Tebreina Devol Nelano Seiya Nel Exedilica!
In your Earth language, that means
"Tilarna, eldest daughter of Seiya,
of the House of Exedilica,
heir to the bloodline of Duke Devol,
of the glorious Knights of Mirvor."
Now. What is your name?
Kei Matoba.
What?
It's Kei Matoba.
It's short.
No, people of low birth often have short names.
I won't let it bother me.
I usually go by Tilarna Exedilica.
Now, carry my things, Kay Imatuba.
Kei Matoba.
I don't care. Start carrying.
What?
Did you not hear me, Sergeant Matoba?
You'll be working with her from now on.
You'll be doing your investigations with her.
She'll take Sergeant Fury's place.
You want me to work with this alien?
That's racist, Sergeant Matoba!
I'm sorry. He doesn't understand
the circumstances.
She came here to find that fairy.
She's a fiel.
Fiel queze badeley. It means "most noble fairy."
That fairy is the equivalent
of a VIP in the Semani world.
It was kidnapped there
and brought here by smugglers.
She's a Farbanian knight
sent here to recover the fairy.
That's correct, yes?
Correct.
In accordance with our treaty with
the country called "The United Nations,"
the Knights of Mirvor are given
the right to dispense justice on Earth.
I, Tilarna Exedilica, request your help
in the name of the Farbani Kingdom.
This is bullshit! Rick was my partner
for four years, and now he's dead!
And now I'm supposed to babysit some kid?
This is an order.
Your order can go eat shit!
Chief Roth, don't you want
to avenge Rick? This is just--
I've known Rick for 20 years.
I'm telling you to do this
because it's necessary.
Do you need any more explanation than that?
But...
It appears that my own will is being ignored.
I want to work with the best "boliceman"
your city has to offer.
I can't imagine a rude boor
like this acting as my guard.
Oh, I'm sorry. We can find another...
No, he'll be your partner.
Or do you want a man
whose etiquette is perfect,
but who's otherwise completely useless?
Inspector Roth...
If so, I don't think you'll
be getting your fairy back.
Don't touch it.
I said don't touch it.
What've we got, Tony?
He talked. He was too scared
to say much, though.
That fairy was stolen, supposedly.
From a gang of Mexicans in a Ridgeline.
Sounds like he doesn't know their names.
Thanks.
What?
Nothing. Let's go.
So? Where are we going?
We're going to find the fairy's original owners.
There can't be that many Mexican gangs
in Ridgelines running around.
What's a Ridgeline?
A car.
What's a Mexican?
A person from Mexico.
What's a gang?
Enough. Just shut up and sit there.
What's this?
No!
Rakebye! Are you trying to get me killed?
Please, just don't do anything!
Don't touch anything!
Wait here.
I'm not taking orders from you.
I'm going with you, Kay Imatuba.
Fine, whatever.
Just try to walk as far away
from me as possible.
I don't want anyone thinking we're friends.
What a coincidence. Neither do I.
Hey, we don't open until seven.
Oh, Mr. Matoba.
Kenny, is O'Neill in?
He's in the other room on the phone.
Hey, that's an alien!
I hate those guys!
Have a good time with her, then.
I'm going in.
Hold it, missy.
What?
He can go in, but you're not welcome.
Hey, did you not hear me? Turn around and...
Turn around and what?
Go on in, miss.
Very good.
Did you think I'd get scared and beg for help?
Yes, this should be a good deal for us both.
This gift of 50 51-inch TVs
brought to us by these sinful
young children is truly a blessing from God.
For the Lord sayeth...
There are no TVs.
It's a theological analogy for God's grace.
Oh, I've got visitors.
Blessings of God be with you!
Sergeant Matoba!
Feeling the breath of God today?
And who's the beautiful lady with you?
Welcome to my house of faith!
Want something to drink?
O'Neill, I'm looking for a Mexican gang.
They drive a Ridgeline.
Probably transporters. Know anything?
They're a violent bunch, and I'd rather
not anger them if possible...
So you do know something.
It's impossible to say!
But perhaps a sufficiently large
donation could make God
whisper something to me...
A donation of around
300 dollars, specifically.
If you don't know anything,
you'll have to deal with
the goddess of the courtroom
and her sword and scales.
You're on probation, aren't you?
That's an illegal threat, Sergeant Matoba!
Someday Satan will get his claws into your soul!
Satan can suck my dick.
Now, what's this about 51-inch TVs?
Maybe I should go ask the guys
in the burglary division?
You're willing to believe the words of a thief?
He's an informant.
But he's a thief.
O'Neill may be a criminal,
but he doesn't like drugs or murder.
He can be trusted... to a degree.
He's a guy you just can't hate, I guess.
I don't understand. Aren't you supposed
to be enforcers of justice?
Well...
I was told that there were warriors on Earth
who fought for the cause of justice.
That they helped the needy and fought evil.
That's what you "bolicemen" are, right?
I honestly had some hopes for you.
But I can't believe you're
making deals with a thief.
Do you have no pride?
It's complicated.
What is?
A lot of stuff.
In the old days, you'd be right, but now...
It's really complicated.
I don't understand.
Nobody does.
581 Mason Street. Room 603.
Antonio Alvarez. You need backup?
Nope. If there's no word from me in 30 minutes,
then you can worry about me.
Roger. Be careful.
Thanks.
You stay here...
Yeah, I should've known you wouldn't listen.
Of course not.
Don't touch anything.
No, it's the smell.
The smell?
The smell of latena.
Someone controlled by
an evil wizard was just here...
What are you talking about?
The enemy's close!
"Shield of law, protection of the war god."
Follow me!
Hey, wait!
Don't move! This is the police!
Get down!
Crap!
"Next time"
Next time on COP CRAFT.