This is Code Papillon!
Midsummer's Knights, do you copy?
This is Code Papillon.
Do you copy?
This is Manatsu.
Do you copy? Over.
Yes!
We've got communication back.
Is everyone safe, Captain?
An unknown group attacked us,
and the Nebula was immobilized.
But Teppei and Hana are safe.
We're heading for Australia Central Command...
Were you ambushed by Globe
unmanned weapons or something?
In Australia, Salty Dog has a lot of power.
Central Command will be dangerous.
So we have a new plan.
I'm sending the data now.
To your north is the Carpentaria base.
It's relatively undefended,
but it has a newly deployed heavy transport craft.
The ekranoplan Bravnik.
If you're familiar with it, we can skip
the instruction manual, Teppei.
That's fine.
Leave the activation codes to me and my magic.
Hold it!
If you do something like that inside a base,
it'll give them a reason to shoot you down.
The risk is too great!
I'm saying...
I've hacked Central Command's main
computer, and knocked it offline.
Wh-What?!
I wish I hadn't heard that.
I'm going to pretend I didn't.
Impressive.
Don't think I'm finished yet!
If they want a fight, they'll get one!
I'll help you out in every way I can.
Make sure you come back!
Got it.
Commander, the Midsummer's Knights
will now return to Tanegashima.
Roger.
Be careful.
Thanks, Akari.
It's my job.
There's no need to thank me.
Listen, Akari...
Governor Yomatsuri told me—
Stop!
You can tell me when you come back.
Okay.
Lately, she's really begun to smile a lot more.
What?
So it's you, huh?
Just be careful.
I'll be fine.
Everyone is with me.
It's thanks to Daichi and the others
that she can smile like that now, huh?
The commander will be heading over there—
It was easy to get in with their systems down.
Akari's amazing!
That's a magical girl for you.
What?
Why is the Bravnik leaving its hangar?
Let's go.
Australia Central Command and
its peripheral bases have had
their main systems hacked,
and have been down for nearly an hour.
The computers are just now coming back online.
They took advantage of the chaos
to steal the ekranoplan Bravnik,
and are already heading to Tanegashima.
It will take about ninety minutes to
get the Sarama Engine online.
Once it is,
we'll be able to stop them before
they reach Tanegashima.
Pillaging and running...
I feel kind of like a pirate.
Pirate Captain Earth, huh?
Cut it out.
This is fun.
Your Smile Means Everything
Sorry, I have something to do today.
Leave tomorrow night open.
Sorry, I'm busy tomorrow.
Then, the day after?
I'm sorry...
The day after won't work, either.
So it's true.
I've been dumped.
What are you doing?
I'm done playing games.
I'll have Puck find us an area
where we can have Siren-sama collect
high-density libido for an all-out attack.
Hey...
Aren't you interested in this avatar's body?
No.
You have no libido...
This is bad.
They're going to pursue the three
of them with the Sarama Engine.
The Sarama Engine?
This is it.
An unmanned Impacter developed
primarily by the Ark Faction,
just like Cerberus.
It's much more mobile than its size would suggest.
And it's equipped with smaller attack units.
These specs look tough.
But once the Bravnik enters
Japan's air defense zone,
the enemy won't be able to touch it, right?
I don't know.
I don't think it'll be that easy.
We were right to send Salty Dog's observer back.
I didn't do anything.
She probably thought that if she stayed,
she'd be arrested for her attempt
to kidnap Hana Mutou.
You're using the Sarama Engine?
Won't that bring in the JSDF Air Force?
Over.
You don't need to worry about that.
More importantly, tell me what's
going on at the Tanegashima base.
Over.
They're a tough nut to crack.
Organizations run by older people
tend to be experienced, knowledgeable, and careful,
but too cautious to make any serious moves.
And organizations composed of
the young have a lot of energy,
but tend to lose control and destroy themselves.
But when the young and old work
together with mutual respect,
they make a strong team.
Tanegashima has that.
Over.
Understood.
I guess we can't underestimate them.
But we need Hana Mutou, no matter what.
Over.
But even if we do acquire Hana Mutou,
I can't imagine she'll do what we ask.
Over.
Once we have her, we'll make it work.
She has a teenage girl's mentality.
They're willing to do anything it takes now.
They need Hana that badly.
They need her power to operate the Blume.
Science Chief, thanks to your efforts,
we learned where that spaceship came from,
and about the dangers our planet faces.
No, our technology couldn't
even get inside that ship.
But fortunately, the entrainment analysis
technology I developed allowed us
to successfully communicate with
the intelligent life form inside.
That's all.
Science Chief,
is that young girl the intelligent life
you've been communicating with?
She looks like a girl... Is it her?
From my communications with her,
I was certain that she was some kind of
biological part of that spaceship.
Since I've been speaking to her,
it seems natural to me
that I've been speaking to
something that looks like a girl...
No, that is a girl.
And she's terribly afraid of going
back inside that spaceship.
Apparently, she can't leave the ship on her own.
But, Science Chief, why was Daichi Manatsu alone
able to bring her out of the ship?
I've calculated the time when the
Sarama will reach the Bravnik.
20:25 JST.
Make sure you come home!
For the sake of this planet's future!
Now that I have a body,
I'm finding there are many things I didn't know.
Peter Westvillage, Science Chief
of Globe's Tanegashima base,
has sent an e-mail to Masaki Kube.
Peter Westvillage...
For a short time, he was our
company's science advisor.
Is he sounding us out about
the Machine Goodfellows?
After the Kanda incident,
our company ostensibly has nothing
to do with the Machine Goodfellows.
He won't find out about that.
No,
he is asking for Masaki Kube's opinion
about a scientific matter.
What does he want to ask me about?
Eternal life, apparently.
Oh, isn't that interesting?
"If you had eternal life, how would
it change the way you thought?"
But why me?
Macbeth currently possesses the world's
most advanced machine intelligence.
That is, me.
And Masaki Kube is the one who
deals with me the most.
Machine intelligence differs
fundamentally from humans.
It has no biological lifespan.
It seems he wants to know
how this machine intelligence regards
its own life, its eternal life.
Of course, if you have eternal life,
the next thing you need is infinite energy.
The theory that the Livlasters were
extradimensional life forms
that took the shape of a gun...
Peter Westvillage was the one
who wrote the report.
If those guns have a will of their own,
Perhaps they are the ones
trying to take over the galaxy...
My true enemies.
They're here.
At this rate, they'll catch up to us.
We're always cutting it close...
There are only two kinds of "close."
"Close, but out" and "close, but safe."
It's okay.
I'm sure we'll get home.
It isn't easy being a pirate, huh?
In the distant past...
I was in a world where everything
was veiled by darkness.
They created me to fire the Livlaster.
But I couldn't do it.
Darkness surrounded me on all sides,
and the only thing they wanted
me to do was to fire that gun.
I wasn't even sure if I wanted to give
them what they desired or not...
But then, I thought I saw a light.
It felt like someone's voice calling to me.
I thought that I needed to meet that person...
That I wanted to meet that person.
So I ran toward the light.
And then...
I found you.
Is it you?
No, that isn't it.
You found me.
Hana?
I'm going to the Flare Engine.
You're going?
I'm going.
I'm counting on you.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Both craft have entered Japan's air defense zone!
Is the Air Force scrambling?
There's no report of that!
It seems Salty Dog is pulling
strings behind the scenes.
Hana...
Commander,
I'm beginning the mission.
Mission?
What mission?
That is the full story behind Operation Summer.
I'll ask you straight out.
Hana Mutou,
do you have the skills to complete this
mission, and the will to do so?
I'm okay now.
I don't know how we do this all this time...
It's too big for us to damage!
It's overwhelming them.
Capture Hana Mutou!
Is this some kind of nasty dog-monster?
Hana!
I'll deploy a team to find Hana Mutou.
Eliminate Daichi Manatsu and Teppei Arashi.
Crush the Intercept Faction's hopes!
High energy readings from
under the nearby sea!
It's surfacing.
Could this be...
Get them, Hana!
The Blume surfaced?
Is Hana Mutou operating it?
Don't!
Why would you damage the Blume?!
It's huge.
That's the Blume?
I'm okay now.
If you go inside the Blume, you won't
be able to leave by your own will.
Right?
It's okay.
The captain will come for me.
I will, no matter what.
So it's okay.
Then only Daichi Manatsu can
bring you out of the Blume.
That's right, isn't it?
In other words...
If anything happens to him,
we'll lose the ability to extricate you from the ship.
Are you aware of this fact?
I am.
And you're all right with that?
Yes.
If I lose the captain,
there'll be no point in leaving the ship anyway.
Hana...
The spaceship Blume goes up
to the orbiting satellite
to rendezvous with the Tenkaidou.
At last, we prepare for the final battle.
But what? Why?
For some reason, the popular idol Ai-chan
is here as "governor for a day."
And Salty Dog is on the move, too.
Next time, on episode 20 of Captain Earth:
Satellitejack.
Satellitejack
Earth Engine, expand!