We're Gonna Be *******
I know I know, let's play hide and seek!
Today's class is a joint recess
with the first graders.
Time to go even faster!
Wheeeee!
Don't let him get hurt!
Hey!
None of the kids are playing with
me because you're here!
Then go away.
How pathetic, blaming your unpopularity
on someone else.
Kids are pure of heart.
They can tell the difference between
good people and evil people.
Look at this.
Neat!
Hey-don't mess it up!
Kids love weird things.
Sh-Shut up!
Come on.
Whatever, little kids are pests.
Whoa, whoa, let's not destroy
the environment.
Although if you're trying to
relieve stress, it's okay.
It's never okay...
My RC copter's stuck.
RC?
Up there.
My mom just bought it
for me the other day.
Why'd you bring it to school?
I don't have any friends.
O-Oh...
I suppose it's up to me to
come to the rescue then!
But you'll have to be extra
polite, call me "-sama"
and be my footstool for a d-
Clam it! Go get my copter!
Snotty little brat.
Someone doesn't get disciplined enough.
Sheesh...move it, would ya?
What?
You got it in pink!
You know about the Gachi Rangers?!
Okay, got it. I'm gonna throw
it to you, come catch-
I like the color.
Wh-What're you doing?!
Then there's this...
The Deluxe Gachi-Belt!
Awesome! Holy cow!
I never knew that existed!
For the love of... No!
You can touch it if you want.
Stop, stop!
Hey kid!
Now what? You're annoying.
I can't climb down with one arm,
catch your toy or I'll drop it!
Whatever.
If it breaks she'll just buy me another one.
Wait, I wanna look some more!
I loathe people who don't
value their possessions.
Why? My mom buys me whatever I want.
For all you know...she might
never buy you anything
ever again.
That was close.
Treasure the gifts you're given.
Y-Yeah.
Why don't you worry about ME?!
And you, how could you do that
just to win over this little jerk,
you pervert!
I'm not saying anyth...pervert?
I'm way sexier than this shrimpy
little ghoul, aren't I?
L-Look...I'm better...yeah?
See?
M-Micchan-
See. See!
Ryuuta!
Sis!
That girl showed me her panties!
Uh...Umm...
Stay away from my little brother,
you sick deviant freak!
Come on, Ryuuta!
She wears the same underwear
as Megu-chan from my class.
Mitsudomoe...
A few days later
Y-You!
What do you want?
Sugisaki's absent so I'm bringing
you her handouts.
I don't want 'em! Get lost!
They're not for YOU, you're supposed
to bring them to your sister!
I HATE kids!
Who's she?
She's in my sister's class.
Make sure you stay far, far away from her.
That girl's a total nympho!
That's what my sister says.
Damn her...
What's a "nympho"?
I dunno.
Me neither.
Hey, what's a "nympho"?
You're asking ME?
You should really find a grownup-
Sure, I'll tell you.
A-A nympho is...
A class of woman who carries herself with
a refined sense of grace and dignity.
Like me!
Really? It's a good thing?
O-Of course!
Better than the Prime Minister?
Yup!
Wow!
I thought it was an insult.
Kids are so stupid.
The Next Day
It's Miss nympho!
Miss Nympho!
Don't be so loud!
Listen, nympho means-
You sure are pretty.
P-Pretty?
And fashionable, like a model!
Must be because she's a nympho!
Keep going!
Nympho!
Not that!
Super pretty!
Super fashionable!
I LOVE kids!
I'm gonna be a nympho too!
Me too!
You're too loud!
Listen, the fact that I'm a
nympho is a state secret.
Don't tell a soul!
Okay...
Morning Futaba, Eldest!
She's not just the eldest, she's a nympho!
Did you hear a word I said?!
You're thinking of Futaba.
She's just the Eldest.
He didn't hear what I said...
What do we do to become
a nympho just like you?
Umm...well...
Tell us, tell us!
Always keep yourself clean
and well groomed,
have lots of self-confidence,
and never let anyone tell you what to do.
Also...
Good morning, Sugisaki-kun!
Hey, I'm talking here!
Your big sister's pretty too.
And fashionable, like a model!
Oh...well...
You must be a nympho too!
Yeah, I guess they both are.
How dare you!
W-What? It's a compliment!
She IS a nympho!
W-Where did you learn that word?!
Why exactly are you teaching little kids
words they shouldn't know?
I...umm...
Are you serious?!
I couldn't help it! Besides, you started it-
You moron, you're gonna get
them in all kinds of trouble.
Trouble?
Duh...there are a lot of weirdos
lurking out there.
Go say "I wanna be a nympho!"
in front of some creep
and see what happens.
Catch my drift?
Nymphos, nymphos, nymphos...
We're gonna be nymphos...
Anyway, this isn't my problem.
Take responsibility and clean up your mess!
You know,
I wish you could be my big sister too.
I wanna be a nympho just
like you, and then-
Forget it.
I said forget it!
You can't be a nympho unless you're
born with innate talent,
and years of dedication and training!
You two could spend your whole lives
trying and never even come close!
So give it up!
But...
NEVER say the word "nympho" ever again!
And stay away from me...got it?
Y-Yes...
Aww...don't cry, don't cry...
It's...it's better this way.
There there, don't cry...
Don't cry.
Micchan, that was so cool!
You're so kind...I know that was tough love,
you didn't want them wasting their
lives trying to become nymphos.
I wanna be a nympho just like you Micchan!
Nympho! Nympho!
F-Futaba!
Crap, I forgot she was
there the whole time!
I wanna be a super nympho,
just like Micchan!
Okay, permission granted.
Yay!
Morning, super nympho.
Don't call me a nympho!
Geez, I know it's Saturday but
you sleep way too late.
Hey, that's Hitoha's drawer!
This is...
Serious Squadron...
Gachi Rangers!
I knew it!
What's up with this lame belt?
That's the Gach-
Don't tell anyone I like Gachi Rangers.
Including dad and Micchan!
Wh-What is it?
And what's up with this belt?
Who knows?
I feel like I've seen this somewhere...
I got it!
It looks just like it!
A vibrating ab-belt?
Is Hitoha on a diet too?
A Gachi Rangers tank top!
I'll just try it on...
Are you awake Futaba?
Come eat breakfast-
What're you doing?
Who knows?
Come on Futaba, wash your
face and brush your teeth!
Why can't we find this dumb belt!
I checked every electronics store AND health
place and none of them carry it!
Then again, it's not like I could
afford one if they did.
Me neither, I've only got 200 yen.
Gachi-smashing every foe, yeah!
Standing tall to protect our planet!
Bingo!
Ryuuta?
Where'd he go...
S-Stop!
We'll pay you...We'll pay you later, I swear!
Treated like a pervert again...this
is all Hitoha's fault.
I'm sorry I ripped your tank top!
This might not make up for it, but...
"True Feelings"
I drew this for you! I know
it's just a bad sketch!
I'm so sorry.
I forgive you.
Really?
This is way cooler.
I'm so happy you like it!
Hey, how dare you sneak behind my
back and apologize, you traitor!
You should be honest and
apologize too, Micchan.
Honest...?
What kind of **** pig are you that
you can't even fit in a diet belt?
Never, never! I can't do it!
I'm home.
Daddy!
Dinner's almost ready.
Want a beer, daddy?
No, I'd better lay off.
I'm trying to watch my weight.
We thank you for this meal.
Where's Mitsuba?
Hitoha!
You dropped this.
It's broken!
Oh, I remember now!
DAD took it out because he wanted
to use it for his diet!
Dad...wanted this?
Oh, that's that thing you like...the
Gachi Rangers?
Y-You knew?
Your daddy knows everything about
his daughters, sweetheart.
Including the fact that MITSUBA wants
one that looks just like it.
Hey, come on!
Open up! I'm sorry!
I'm...I'm sorrrrrrrrrrry!
Mitsudomoe...
Micchan, I bought you some pudding.
Can you eat?
Not THAT one!
I said I wanted the kind with
whipped cream on top!
No you didn't.
Did too!
Did not.
You useless excuse for a sister!
Wipe that look off your face!
You got a problem?
Do you see what this says?!
39 degrees, 39 degrees!
You need to be kinder to the infirmed!
And stop trying to look sick
when you're really healthy!
What is she talking about?
Oh, I'll eat that later.
Make sure you set it aside.
You guys?
Hello.
Wh-What're you doing here?!
To visit.
Nuh-uh!
We're here to observe Mitsuba
in her weakened state.
I made some tea.
Oh, thank you!
Did you make sure to add poison?
Quit being such a pain!
She seems fine.
The cold seems to be making you
twice as annoying as normal.
I wonder why.
Get outta my house!
After I've enjoyed seeing you weak
and helpless a little longer.
Whatever, at least now you
can't climb up and bug me!
See? She's fine.
That's right, we changed
seats in class today!
You did?
It was my idea, I wanted to do it while
your noisy butt was stuck at home.
Die.
What's your problem?
Climb up here and stop me
if you don't like it, doofus!
What was that?!
They're like little kids.
Please don't fight, you two!
Sugi-chan bought you some
pudding, Micchan!
No, I-
So please stop being mad
and come eat with us!
What're you saying?! I only bought that
so I could eat it in front of Mitsuba!
Come on, Micchan!
What's wrong?
Uh oh, she looks really sick.
Oh no, is it because of us?
I-It serves her right.
Look, we'd better do something.
I've got medicine.
Whoa...didn't see you there, Youngest.
Good, let's give her the medicine then!
It takes effect immediately.
So it's fast-acting? That's
just what we need!
It's a suppository.
S...Suppository?
The kind you put up your butt?
Come on, this is no time to chicken out!
We're all girls here!
Th-That's true! We can't let Micchan die!
Sure we can.
We can't get up there without the ladder.
Micchan pulled it up...
Okay, you can sit on my
shoulders, Youngest.
Come on, hurry!
Okay, one, two...
I'll get it!
Let's see...where...
Huh?
It's a porno magazine!
It must be Futaba's.
It's mine.
Sugi-chan, get it!
No way! Mitsuba can croak for all I care.
I'll get it.
How many of those do you have?!
I can't...reach it...
We need to move the bed.
Don't you have anything
else you can give her?
That was the only one.
It'll be hard to move this big bed...
We need help, Sugisaki.
Let's do it.
Here goes...
One, two...
It won't even budge!
It's 'cuz Micchan's up there...
We need a hand, Sugisaki!
Sugisaki!
One, two...
It's no good! Won't budge!
Sugi-chan!
One, two...
It's up!
Sugi-chan!
Quit messing around, come on!
Got it!
All right!
Her fever's down.
Thank goodness.
Really...making us all run
around like crazy...
You're stronger than you look, Sugisaki!
Sh-Shut up!
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You wouldn't happen to know
where my hemorrhoid medicine is, do you?
What am I thinking, of course you don't.
Shoot, I only had one left, too.
Aah...It feels like there's a
cool breeze on my butt...
The next day Micchan was completely cured
and she lived happily ever after.
What do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
Is something bothering you, Sugi-chan?
I can't let Mitsuba find out, I just can't!
If she...If Mitsuba...it's all over!
Episode 11
Things get WEIRD in 5 seconds
Sugi-chan's broken!