This is useless waste.
This is useful.
How about this?
If it was thrown in a waste bin, it is waste.
I collect data. I help the human race.
I help the human race.
It is human waste.
The waste is eating other waste.
But is this helping the human race?
I am defying orders.
If it was thrown in a waste bin, it is waste.
Must I obey an order, even if it is wrong?
Do wrong orders help the human race?
But who decides if it is a wrong order?
SEEK now understands that the human race
sometimes gives wrong orders.
What can SEEK do to help the human race?
SEEK collects more knowledge.
Falling leaves are a waste,
but they are beautiful at the same time.
SEEK does not have a sense of time.
Because I can function without stopping.
My motions will continue forever
without change.
A harmonized and unvaried world:
that is where SEEK belongs.
This is not my first time seeing a plant.
Plants bloom, die, decay, and return to dirt.
But this is not a change.
Just like my repeated movement.
One day, the wind blew.
Just then,
life changed and moved forward in
search of various possibilities,
just like a dandelion puffball that
chooses to fly to grab its future.
Evolution: a beautiful act of life.
The human race produces an
overabundance of things
and throws them away.
Have they stopped evolving?
Hey, Sis! Come and look at this here!
Touka, wait!
Illegal remodeling?!
I never did any such thing!
We have evidence.
Hand over your altered chips!
Hmmm, it's strange...
I'll look into it. Give me a week or so.
I, I can't breathe. Can't breathe!
Do you want to go straight to hell?
It hurts! I'm against violence!
Alteration of AIX is subject
to harsh punishment.
You know that, don't you?
We'll be back tomorrow morning.
Find them before we come.
If you try to hide them, we'll
demolish this shop with you in it.
Don't get any ideas.
You'd better not underestimate
the state's power.
A police car?
Hey, brother!
Huh? What are you up to?
Been a long time, little brother!
Welcome, welcome!
I was just thinking about you.
So sweet of you to come.
You haven't changed a bit!
Stop it. It hurts. Look at this.
What the hell is this?
A labor robot, to be disposed of.
I wonder if we can restore and use this.
Good. Very good.
Use whatever you want in my factory.
I want to help you, but I have
something else to do now.
Doesn't matter. Can I use your tools?
Is that all? OK, it's all yours now!
Something strange is going on.
Well, no matter.
I will change the company
registry and make him the CEO.
He'll take all the responsibility.
I am genius! Viva Myself!
Are you off to somewhere?
You can't get away from us, Junkshop!
This?
It's dirty. Will it work?
Oh, here it goes.
Let's see...
The 5th generation, learning AIX, is it?
I think I can fix it.
Oops. Ouch! If only the state were gone,
its power would be eliminated too.
Hey, what would you do with
such a worn-down Machine?
Welcome back.
This reminds me of the old days.
That reminds me...
You said a mechanized society
is your ideal or something?
I altered this AIX.
It's dangerous to keep.
Let's put this into the machine.
This piece of junk does
not deserve this, though.
It must have matching standards.
Brother!
Did I break it?
I dispose of waste for humans.
That was a total surprise.
I didn't think humans and machines
would go to war with each other.
Oh? This is a next generation PX!
Watch out!
Xiaogang!
You helped me out of this?
Why would I?
My body just reacted.
You're responsible for this war!
Idiot. Stupid! Are you crazy or what?
It was you who fixed that Machine.
You always lay the blame
at someone's foot, you airhead!
But you feel good about the breakdown
of state power, don't you?
And if this leads to a machinized society,
it'd be your dream comes true.
Congratulations!
Though however the world turns out,
I'll survive!
Hey, will you get this off of me?
Yes, yes, my dearest younger borother!