Union Fest is over now,
but I would like to create more events
with you all that are
as fun as this one was!
Union Fest's final stage.
The passion that connected
the three countries
never waned...
That night, the party continued
with great enthusiasm
until the end.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll return to our usual,
calm and peaceful days.
And then...
Yes?
Hero, you're going out with the
Princess and the others, right?
Yes, they're making
our lunches right now.
Yeah, I took a peek earlier.
This is for you.
Are these clothes?
I had them made at a shop I frequent.
Try it on. I'm sure it'll suit you.
Wow, this is nice!
It's not bad to wear something other
than your Hero outfit, right?
Yeah! But is it really
okay for me to have these?
I don't want to take them back.
Please wear them.
Now, Hero, this will be your
last mission this summer.
Okay!
Relax and enjoy your day today
with the Princess and your friends.
Have fun with the Princess,
Rebecca, and the others.
Can you do it?
I will do my best,
I swear on my Hero title!
Right, then go!
Hey, Sink!
Your Highness, Nanami!
Sink, where'd you get those clothes?
Ecle gave them to me.
Oh really?
Looks good.
Everybody's here.
Sorry for the wait.
Then, shall we?
The highland picnic tour for
the rulers and the Heroes!
Off we go!
This is amazing!
It's nice, isn't it?
This is our favorite summer spot.
The water is really nice
and there are even fish.
You're right, there are so many!
And so many local gods...
The protection of the sprites
is especially strong here.
That's why nature's bounty
is so plentiful here,
but you shouldn't be so
impressed quite yet.
We have much more to show you.
Let's take a picture!
A picture with everybody!
Shall we take turns?
First, Nanami and you guys...
Oh, don't worry about that.
Leo-sama, it's okay, right?
Yes. Noir!
Yes, ma'am!
Secret Escort Troop.
At your service!
Okay, Noir, can you
take the picture then?
Sure.
All right, there's still plenty
of places I want to show you!
Adel-sama, Isuka-dono?
The Hero Crystals I gave
to Sink and Gaul...
we never gave you one, Nanami.
Oh, yeah...
You also have the proper
qualifications to be a Hero.
We'll make sure to have created one
for you by next time.
Really?! Thank you!
Well, kid, we had quite
some experiences,
but it was you and our little
shrimp that woke me,
so I'll say thanks.
I'd like to express
my gratitude as well.
You've inherited the Demon Crystal!
Make sure to keep training
on the other side, as well!
Yes, I'll do my best!
Sorry that I didn't find
a better time to secretly
hand this over...
Oh, no.
Really, thank you for
making the trip out here.
So anyway, here's what
you asked for.
Everyone!
Our rulers and Heroes
are about to return!
The surprise Hero farewell party
organized by us young knights...
...will have to be really huge!
This has indeed become quite huge.
Yes, Prince Gaul's
holding the reins.
The princesses and Heroes are arriving!
Everybody, get ready!
I bet you didn't expect that, did you?!
You were probably thinking
of having a light meal,
but we won't allow that!
A surprise party organized by us
young knights to thank our rulers
and Heroes for their hard work.
I bet you never suspected that
we had planned this all along!
We didn't!
You got us!
Now rulers and Heroes, please...
...take each others' hands
and get up on stage!
Hey, Hina. I'm back.
Welcome back.
I got this from the princesses.
Shall we?
Sounds good. I'll have some.
So how was the farewell party?
The young ones all seemed to have fun.
They liked the swords
I made, too.
What did you make them?
Small blades for use at home.
An all-around knife
great for cutting fruit or for camping.
Since Rebecca likes cooking,
I made her a cooking knife.
You made household blades, eh?
That brings back memories.
You're telling me.
But I got to make nice blades
and see nice smiles.
That alone made it worth coming back.
I see.
Welcome back, everybody.
Captain Riselle!
We're back!
Princess, sorry for the wait.
Don't worry.
Oh, where's Cou-sama?
We both left after getting
ready, but she said
she remembered some urgent business.
Oh.
Sink, you're late!
Wha... Cou-sama?!
I wanted to give
those two "girl talk" fans
as much time alone as possible.
So why don't we two inheritors of
the Hero King take a bath together?
That reminds me, Rebecca-san.
Do you think you'll get
anywhere with that thing?
Oh, you mean that Sink
always calls me Becky?
Yes.
Not at all.
I think I'll always be Becky to him.
To him, I'll always be the girl
that was his little childhood friend.
I don't think that's necessarily true.
Well, it's okay.
Nothing's changed anyway.
Anyway, I think your work
will be really hard,
so if you ever need
my help, let me know.
I'm Pastillage's Hero, but
I am also your best friend.
Yes, thank you.
The same goes for you,
any time you need me!
Yes, thank you, Princess.
Sink, you're so good.
Really? Thank you.
All right. Rinsing it out now.
Okay.
Oh yeah, I wanted to
ask you something.
Yes, what is it?
Do you have any plans to get together
with Rebecca or Millihi-nee,
or maybe both?
What?!
You know, if a ruler
and Hero get married,
it has some influence on the
country ruling business, so...
Uhh.. let's wash your tail first!
Please do!
Well, I'm still just a fledgling
Hero, and I haven't
reached my goal yet.
Goal?
Winning against Nanami.
We've had quite a few fights,
but I've never beat her in a serious match
or public event.
Victory!
Oh yeah, you did lose in the
one-on-one during the Fest.
Yes...
It's my goal to win
against Nanami during
a public event on earth.
Until that's done,
I'll always be just a kid.
That's why I think it's too
early for things like that.
I see.
Don't forget that you
have to take care of those
who stay by your side while
you march towards your goal.
You're right.
Thank you, Cou-sama.
I'll make sure to remember that.
Okay.
Rebecca!
Cou-sama!
Was your bath okay?
Sink washed me, so I'm all good.
Ah, a freshly washed Cou-sama.
You smell good.
Indeed.
You two, please feel free
to move onto the bed.
Okay!
Sink, you, too.
Wait, I don't think that's okay.
Let's sleep together!
Come on, Sink.
If you say so...
Sink, come here!
Those two are already asleep.
They got up early today.
I'll turn off the lights.
So, Sink...
Yes?
Do you remember how I said
that I loved you when
we parted last time?
Of course. I said the same thing.
It's kind of like a dream
that I'm holding the hand
I let go of back then.
Though we do have to part again soon.
The next time I can come
will be after my exams in fall.
It'll be really soon.
Yes, I'll be waiting.
Tonight I want to hug you tightly
so I won't forget your
smell and warmth.
Is that okay?
Of course, as much as you want.
Then hug!
So warm... and happy...
Now, Leo-sama,
Nanami-san, it's morning!
Gau-sama and Genoise,
get up, get up, get up!
Come on, get up, please!
Violet-san, you're sticking
to the routine too much...
Can't you think of a more gentle way
to wake us on the day we have to part?
This has nothing to do with that.
After completing many tasks,
the Heroes will return to
their homeland for now.
Biscotti's Hero, Sink,
and Pastillage's Hero, Rebecca,
shall have some time to recover.
Now, please return the divine
swords to your summoners.
The return ritual is now finished.
Thank you!
Rebecca, I want you to have this.
It's my treasure; my mother
gave it to me before she left.
So the other day, you
went to go get this?
That's right.
I want you to have it...
and, if possible, wear it often.
But this is too precious...
The summoner and the Hero.
An article of promise to
connect the two worlds.
For that, an item that both
have deep ties to is best.
That's one of the requirements
of Rico's new summoning technique.
I'm sure that this will definitely
create a path for us.
Then I'll keep it safe for you.
I'll make sure that I can return it
any time you want to wear it.
Thank you.
I love you, Cou-sama!
I love you, too, Rebecca!
Sink, I have this for you.
It's a Biscotti-made Earth clock.
Rico designed it,
and Eclair, Yukikaze, and
I helped with the assembly.
Thank you. I will treasure this.
Okay!
This is from me.
The Galette army's MVP
prize for the Union Fest.
Awesome! Thank you!
I'll probably be back here in no time!
So please wait for me, Leo-sama!
Yes, I'm counting on you, Hero Nanami.
All right, Princess, Cou-sama.
Bye you two!
See you soon!
Yes!
Earth / Great Britain, City of London
Oh?
Welcome back, Nanami.
Mom...
When did you get back?
I would have come to pick
you up, if you had called.
I'm home...
What?  Are you still jet-lagged?
Make sure to put out
your laundry and trash.
Okay.
Same Day - Earth / Japan Kinokawa City, Tokino
Is this your room?
Yes?!
Hey, Sink.
Nanami? You got home safely?
Yeah, how about you?
We're fine, too.
Want to talk to Becky?
Yeah!
Yes. I'm fine, too.
Where did you go back to?
So our summer of
adventures came to a close.
Our memories stayed with us,
and we have solid proof we were there, too.
It's nice to be home,
but since I slept with
Cou-sama every night,
I can't settle down...
That's something every
Hero has to deal with.
Hang in there!
I really understand how you felt
at the beginning of spring now.
See!
Oh, did you write your letter?
Yes, I did.
We're doing our homework at
the library tomorrow, right?
Will you look over it to make sure I
didn't mess up the Flonyard letters?
Roger that.
Sink, come eat.
Okay!
See you tomorrow.
Mom, this way!
Sink, sorry for the wait.
Hey...
Is something wrong?
No, it's just that I haven't
seen you outside with your hair down often.
I kind of did it so that it would
work with Cou-sama's pendant.
I look a bit older, don't I?
I was surprised because you
look quite a bit older.
Becky, you're really pretty!
Thanks.
That reminds me,
you saved me during the
pendant episode, too.
We both did it. The two Heroes.
Since you're a Hero and
totally look grown up,
I think calling you by your childhood
name "Becky" might be rude.
I guess then it's "Rebecca"?
Well, I did think that I might like it
if you called me that...
Rebecca.
It's way more embarrassing
than I imagined
to have you
actually call me that!
Why does it feel so weird?!
Rebecca, it's just because
you're not used to it.
Rebecca?
Stop. Stop, I can't!
Really?
I'm sorry. I'll be fine
with Becky for now.
I'll change my hair back, too.
Well if you say so, Becky.
Sink, you're so nice, even though
I'm being totally crazy.
No, no.
Thank you, Sink. I love you!
Yes! I love you, too!
Let's go!
Yeah!
The second summer vacation
of middle school...
It was the second time for
Sink, and the first time
for Nanami and myself to
live the Hero experience.
The place where fun and hot days
and people we love are waiting for us...
We'll definitely be
going back there again.
This summer was truly great, again.
Yes, and we'll be back
together in no time, right?
Yes, so everybody...
See you soon!