hence the name fall leaves
Impassionate gods...
She did it!
Chihaya went from being helpless against
the queen to taking two cards in a row.
She's staying on the attack.
Hitting her groove...
She converted on the card she just sent.
That was sheer willpower.
But look at the score.
The Queen has 7 cards left.
Her opponent has 23 cards left.
That barely changed anything.
The Queen is just a first year high schooler.
She must have a breaking point.
What's big is that her opponent
still hasn't given up.
Hasn't given up?
She's playing to win!
Chihaya...
Why are you always so obvious?
It's too late.
She's down 16 cards.
The Queen just has to play
normally and she'll easily win.
With that trademark smile on her face.
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Chihaya Furu
Verse 15
As Though
Pearls
Have
Been
Strung
Across
the
Autumn
Plain
the red that is the Tatsuta River
For you, I head out to the fields to pick spring greens
The hazy early morning light
comes not from the moon
Another multi-syllable card!
Her smile's back...
Scary.
No luck...
She finally got into a groove,
but, since then, it's been
multi-syllable cards: her weakness.
but from the crystal white snow of Yoshino
Still, there are less than thirty cards left!
Go!
Chihaya!
Since the dew...
Chihaya can't handle fifty cards,
but when only thirty are left,
it's easier for her to
pinpoint the card she wants.
Since that reduces the number
of syllables before a unique one,
there are more one-syllable and two-syllable
cards where Chihaya shines!
My third card...
Here is #20!
#77 "Since the"!
Oh!
Okay...
The Queen was taking every card,
so I never had a chance to
stand up and retrieve cards.
My body's starting to loosen up again...
I want to become faster...
To become freer...
During a match...
So when I'm playing an opponent
who's so strong that I'm scared stiff,
I can move freely.
Move freely!
Free!
I still don't understand,
but is that what it means
to be a strong player?
Thank you very much.
May I see you never forget
your promise to always love me
I was only able to take five cards.
The Queen is still...
...twenty cards better.
I can look up and see the
snowy cap of Mt. Fuji
Since I could not hide my love,
Oh, Wakamiya-san.
You're already done?
Wakamiya Shinobu
Mizusawa High School
Ayase Chihaya
Tokyo's Mizusawa High School...
Ayase Chihaya.
Impressive.  What was the final score?
Mizusawa High School, Ayase Chihaya...
Ayase Chihaya...
Chihaya.  Chihaya!
Next time, I won't let
you take a single card!
O-Oh, um...
Your Snowmaru T-shirt is really cute.
That snowman actually has a name?
Other people can recognize it?
Chihaya...
have been soaked red with tears of blood
Oops...
As the first frost has fallen,
What's wrong with me?
I'm more upset than she is.
Chihaya lost by twenty cards.
The Queen's that much better than her...
Is Chihaya okay?
Rain takes longer to dry in the autumn time
Nah.  Knowing her, she's probably already asleep.
Yikes, she really is asleep-
A straight line.
Straight...
Straight and swift as an arrow.
My memorization has to be
better for this to work.
Memorize...  Memorize...
Straight! Swift!
Straighter!  Swifter!
Listen hard...
Harder...  Harder...
What do I have to do to beat her?
What will it take?
Today is the day.
The day Chihaya's dream became real.
Next time, we'll meet in a match.
-Arata
Dream...
The Class B third round is about to begin.
Please sit down in your assigned seat,
once you've checked who your opponent is.
I hear the beating of cloth,
as a chilly autumn breeze
It's over!  Wakamiya-san wins!
descends from Mount Yoshino
upon my long-forgotten home
Thank you very much.
High School National Ogura Hundred
Poets Karuta Championship
Thank you very much.
This is my last year,
so I thought you might let me win this.
You're good, so I was scared I might lose.
You beat me by 12 cards...
Man, Wakamiya Shinobu is the champion again?
She's the real deal.
She never joined a karuta society, right?
Seriously?
Straight as a line...
Straighter...  Swifter...
Chihaya-chan.
Chihaya-chan!
Straight as a line...
Kana-chan.  How'd it go?
I lost in the third round.
So did Desktomu-kun.
I see...
That's because you were
watching Class A matches the entire time.
Right!  I haven't had anything to eat!
The Learning Center curry!
Chihaya-chan!
That doesn't matter right now!
Mashima-kun is in the Class B final!
Let's go cheer him on!
Rain takes longer to dry in the autumn time
Taichi is in the final!
leaving a hovering mist
above the trees and grass
While some dodge...
Said night was young...
When winds send waves...
I could spend my entire youth on karuta
without ever becoming better than Arata.
Save that for after you've actually tried.
Dr. Harada...
Can I really do it?
Lose...
Cry...
But continue to advance...
to catch up to Arata.
I recall how my own efforts were in vain
So the flower petals,
Would the,  Feel sorrow,
In the, In order for, I feel
as, I feel though, I know...
Taichi...
Hey, Ayase!
You're late!
Where have you been?
Get over here!  We saved a seat for you!
I recall how my own efforts were in vain
May the time we spend
apart from one another be
A fault.
That never happens.
He went for a completely different card.
He still has the positions from
his previous match in his head.
When you're tired, forgetting
is harder than remembering.
Mashima's on his sixth match.
At that point, you can have perfect
concentration and still make mistakes.
Taichi...
Dammit.
It's okay.
Review the cards again.
Review.
"So the flower has" was read, so I can take
"So the flower petals" on "So the flower."
"Would the" hasn't been read so I
have to be careful on "Would this".
"Feel love" has been read, so I
can take "Feel sorrow" on "Feel."
"In order to" hasn't been read, so I don't
want to fault on "In the" or "In order for."
"I feel as" and "I feel that" are both
in play so I want to attack those.
The "I know" card and the "I wish" card on the
opponent's left side should come soon.
"Said world offers no change" and the like
card "Said world offers no escape" are both left,
so I need to cover mine
and watch the other one.
I can take both of them!
"While it brings" and "While it may" have been read,
so I can attack "While it pains" after "While it"
and hit the "While I" on the opponent's
left side at the same time.
"For the" is now a single-syllable card because
"For you, I head" and "For you, I would" have been read.
I have to take "Swift."
Can't let him defend that one.
"May I see" and "May the time we" have been read,
so I can attack "May it" on the opponent's side
before coming back to "May the time spent" on my side.
My mind's so numb that I can only
see what's in front of me...
That's all I need to see.
as short-lived as the reeds of Naniwa Bay
Feel sorrow wash over me...
I want to move faster,
but my arm can't keep up.
Pick it up!
My mind is doing fine!
Faster!
Move faster!
Victory for Fujisaki
Yes!  He won!
Toda-senpai!
Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
You did it, Senpai!
I was playing a third-year from Fujisaki...
I only lost by three cards.
Second place.
I did good enough.
That's like the textbook
display of disappointment.
I-It hurts...
Huh?
It must hurt...
Second place hurts the most.
I can't cry -
not when I haven't put in the time -
but it still hurts.
High School National Ogura Hundred
Poets Karuta Championship
It's always difficult to accept defeat,
even after you're an adult.
Yet...
they aren't trying to
console each other either.
Omi Learning Center
We'll need to hurry if
we're going to make our train.
Make sure you haven't forgotten anything.
Oh, there are already students here.
Running this early in the morning?
Is it the track team?
Th-The karuta club?!
Are you interested?
No...
Figured as much.
I'm sure everybody identified a few issues
with their play during the tournament,
but the one problem we all
share is a lack of stamina.
You can't focus if you're tired.
We can use summer break to train ourselves
to be able to play ten hours straight.
In terms of actual skill,
I'm not worse than Mashima.
I'm aiming to win Class B!
But...
Don't fall behind!
Step for step!
We're rivals!
Oh, she's awake.
Did I fall asleep?
Yes, for ten minutes.
Oh, it's because Porky chased me down.
I've been dreaming about
Shinobu-chan a lot, daily.
Snowmaru, too...
Is Shinobu-chan the current Queen?
Uh-huh.
I watched the video.
She's so good, it's scary.
That's why I call her Shinobu-chan.
I met Arata at Nationals,
but he doesn't show up in my dreams.
I want to meet him,
and not in my dreams.
Yes, who is it?
Oh, you've finally come.
Mr. Kuriyama, I wish to join
the Fukui Nagumo Society.
Until we meet again.
for I could not recognize you,
like the moon hidden behind the clouds
So spring nights are...
Nobody wishes to see...
As this trip takes me away...
I have only autumn leaves as an offering
for the gods watching over me.
It's the second term:
Fall, the season of karuta...