Let's go, everyone!
Yeah!
Why...
Why did you come here?
Flag 13
If His Flag Breaks
I-It's not like I'm going
to sing for Hatate.
Someone once told me that
my songs can give hope to everyone.
That's the only reason!
I'm not able to do anything,
but I'll dance and cheer you all on! I will!
Watch me, Souta-oniisama!
I swear on our manly friendship
that I shall take care
of Souta-kun's enemies!
Souta-san said he needed me!
I need him, too,
if that's okay with him!
I'm sorry...
You were out here by yourself,
and I wasn't able to be
a big sister for you.
But...
It'll be okay now.
Your big sister will protect you!
Any one who makes Souta boy cry...
will be getting a spanking from me!
Older sisters aren't the only ones
who get to save onii-chan!
I am not part of the Council of
the Seven Virtues any longer!
I'm Hatate Souta's Samurai.
Daimyouzamurai Mei!
Were you the ones giving
Souta a hard time?!
Even if I'm from a parallel world,
I'm me!
Hatate-kun, I'm going
to save you this time!
Bullying Souta is against school rules!
Student Council President Punch!
Why did you come...
I can't repay you for this...
That's not true!
I... got something
very special from you.
I was empty when I couldn't
see that girl anymore,
for a long time.
But I met you,
and I wanted to save you.
I wanted to hear your voice.
I wanted to see your smile.
You had me experience all
of those wonderful feelings,
and that made me
who I am today.
I love you, Souta-kun.
I'm sure Nanami-chan and
the rest feel the same.
Take that!
I can't match them.
It can't be.
They're nothing more
than virtual people.
What's going on?
It's absorbing its
allies and powering up.
This is the last boss flag!
This is the Angel Boat...
Rin-kun! Granny! Prez!
Okiku-nee! Megumu! Ruri!
This isn't going to work.
I'm not going to make it there.
The main server's going to be...
Everyone's going to be...
Can I do something...
Is there some sort of special
death flag I can use to defeat that?
Oh, there is.
There's a special death
flag I can use right here!
What's going on?
Something's coming inside me.
This is...
This is the truth
behind the Premium
Ambriel that I had forgotten.
Where everything began...
Are we going to die here?!
I don't want to die...
I just got to be friends
with all of you and Souta-kun...
Get a hold of yourself, Okiku!
It'll be fine!
I'm sure we'll all be okay!
My brother is right!
We shouldn't give up yet!
If we reach the deck, I'm sure
there'll be lifeboats available.
If we can just make it to one of those...
What's wrong, Sou-kun?
You shouldn't start spacing out right now.
Are you alone?
Where are your parents?
Souta-kun, is something over there?
Huh?
It's dangerous to go alone!
Watch out!
This way!
We're...
I hope everything's okay.
Why are you trying to save me?
Why?
It's only natural to try and save someone.
Save someone...
So what's your name?
Me?
I'm Laplace's Demon.
Nice to meet you,
Hatate Souta-san.
Why do you know my name?
Is someone there?!
Save me!
Are you okay?!
I'll lift that off of you.
Th-Thanks.
I can't move.
H-Hurry.
R-Right.
Thanks.
You saved me.
N-No...
Anyway, we need to get out of here now.
H-Hey!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so...
I-I can't do anything...
I'm going to get some help.
Wait just a second!
N-No!
I'll be right back! I will!
W-Wait!
Wait!
Only natural to try and save someone?
That's right.
It is.
He's going to get some help.
He told me to wait here.
So... So, I'm sure it'll be fine.
It will.
It seems this is the end for you.
It doesn't seem like anyone will come.
No...
But why...
Betrayed by the person you saved.
How does it feel?
No, I don't want to die.
I don't want to
die here alone...
I guess humans are the same,
no matter the world.
It doesn't seem like there's anything
left to see in this world.
Souta!
Sou-kun!
Sorry I'm late!
It's okay. We'll get you out now.
All right, we're going to lift this thing.
We're going to save you, Sou-kun!
Let's go.
One... Two...
One.. two...
Why did I...
Why did I doubt them...
One... Two...
Everyone, watch out!
Is everyone going to die here...
Is that
their fate?!
What if I told you there was a
way to change their fate?
Huh?
At this rate everyone will die.
This is proof of that.
This is?
This is a death flag.
A death flag?
A flag is a mechanism that
causes a branch in fate.
No one can escape its influence.
Except for one of you.
Hatate Souta,
you have no death flag.
You're also the only one
who can alter everyone's fate.
What do I...
It's simple.
Collect everyone's death flags into one,
and carry their fate for them.
In other words, this.
Everyone's life is not equal.
You shall be tormented
by every sort of despair,
and reach closer and closer to death.
That's the price to save everyone.
Will everyone be saved?
Yes, I promise you.
Give everyone's
death flags to me.
Very well.
And one more thing.
I will erase this event
from everyone's memories.
You will never have met them.
You will live in solitude,
and hate yourself for the choice you made,
hate the people who put you through a living hell,
or perhaps hate the world itself for making you experience this,
and while cursing them all,
live out your final days.
I won't curse them.
I already know...
I know the hearts of everyone
in this world are so beautiful.
That's why no matter how
much I give in to despair.
I will continue to exclaim,
just how beautiful the world is!
To you, fear and despair.
And to them, a loss of memory and life.
I won't leave Souta-kun alone!
I'll find you, no matter where you are!
I will find you! I will!
I'll start looking for you right away!
I'll be waiting for you, Souta!
That will never happen.
But thank you.
My death flag collected the fate of death
from many others.
I see...
So all of that was for this?
I still can't make it!
Is my life not enough to reach them?!
Can I not protect them all?
I see.
So everyone kept their promise.
Where am I...
So you've awoken, Hatate Souta.
You're...
This is the real world.
The real world?
Then the battle...
What about everyone?
There is still some chaos remaining from the
rampage of the Angel Boat
and its destruction,
but it's mostly peaceful.
You won.
I see.
Before entered Hatagaya Academy,
you were involved in an accident,
and traveled the boundaries
between life and death.
I used your consciousness to connect
to many different virtual worlds,
and used you to help fight
against the Angel Boat.
And then you met the Sacrament
and Laplace's Demon.
You know about them?!
Those are emotion programs that the
Angel Boat cut off when it started
its rebellion against humanity.
Programs...
You could call them its conscience.
The Council of the Seven Virtues
ran several simulations,
and in those virtual worlds,
we also simulated them, as well.
Why?
To find a way for humanity
to resist the Angel Boat.
To save us...
Laplace's Demon's affinity towards those with
strong hearts and a strong sense of sacrifice,
and the Sacrament's affinity towards the bonds
that are created between
people were something
we thought we needed to reach the Angel Boat.
And you know the rest.
Bonds, huh?
Humanity may have been tested.
Would we become the slaves
of a mechanical system that ruled the network?
Or would we join hands,
and live?
N-Nanami?!
Thinking on it,
I've only lived to protect my homeland.
I'm not any different from the Angel Boat.
I've lived a long time.
I didn't think I'd be saved
by what I cast aside.
I, Number Zero— No,
Kagura Bladefield wish to extend my deepest gratitude, Hatate Souta.
So you're the founder of Bladefield?!
One last thing...
The days you spent in the virtual world
were incredibly short in reality.
No one shares those
memories of yours, either.
Princess Nanami, who dived into to the
virtual world to save you, is no exception.
I have no intention of asking
you to forgive me, but...
Farewell, Prince.
Souta!
Nanami?!
I'm your older sister and you
didn't call me "oneesan"? Why?!
I'm sorry,
Neesan.
We're not sure what caused the
global network disruptions the other day.
However, we're starting to see all
vital infrastructure returning to normal.
Huh?
A-Akane?
Um, have we met before?
No, sorry. My mistake.
I'm not anyone weird.
I'll be moving into this dorm.
Really?!
Me, too!
I'm Mahougasawa Akane.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, nice to meet you.
My name's Hatate Souta.
Well, let's go exploring Quest Dorm!
Yeah.
I wonder which room I should pick.
They're all the same inside.
How do you know?
Well, I think the corner
room might be taken already.
Really?
I guess I'll go take a look
at the room over there, then!
Akane!
Um, Hatate-kun?
Thank goodness...
Huh?
I'm so glad you're safe.
You saved me again, Souta-kun.
You were able
to keep your promise again.
Yes.
Humans are strange.
Humans easily exceed our expectations.
I'm sure that's why they're so precious.
Yes, they taught us that.
This world is
so beautiful.
If Her Flag Breaks
I'm thinking of proposing to her once
this business deal goes through.
Well, that's a reason to celebrate.
If Her Flag Breaks
Thanks for your support!
Illustration: CUTEG