Midterms
Day 1
Science
All right, time's up.
It's not over.
You still have tomorrow.
How did you do?
Terrible.
Come with us, Akanecchi.
Shopping.
The school trip is coming up.
When exams are over.
I have practice today.
Oh, okay.
Is it language arts tomorrow?
Yeah.
What do you think will be on it?
Kota!
Hey, don't ignore me. Kota!
What do you want?
How was the test?
No good.
You're totally out of it.
Yeah.
Want to see my new move?
Do it, do it!
Please don't.
Ogasawara Dynamic!
Stop it!
Ow!
Cut it out, seriously.
Ow...
How's that different from your usual move?
Kumano Shrine
Kadoyama Publishing
Newcomer Awards
Winners
Literature
Kadoyama
Publishing
Kotarou-kun.
You're here early. What about school?
It's exam week.
Oh, yeah?
What are you up to right now?
Cleaning up around the kagura hall.
Huh?
Hey, Kotarou-kun.
You're here early. What about school?
It's exam week.
Is that that one book?
The one you let me read before?
That was my second story.
This one's my first.
Kotarou-kun, I'm counting on
you for the Sunday practice.
Okay!
You've submitted before?
So you got the results?
No time to be thinking about exams, huh?
Kotarou!
You'd better be studying.
I know.
I know that.
Mizuno-san
Thanks
You're welcome
Sorry about today
No problem
See you at school
Yup, see you
I don't feel like studying
Would that be annoying?
Azumi-kun: Are you studying for the exam?
Yup
I'm not bothering you, am I?
Akane, did you take your bath yet?
Oh, yeah, I did.
Okay.
I guess I will too, then.
Not at all
Something crappy happened
before exams
Like what?
Club stuff... I guess?
Literature club?
Yeah
Weird. I can't even manage
to talk to her at school.
I get bummed with club
stuff all the time too
Really?
What do you do when you
can't make things work?
I think you're fine the way you are
Like you said at the sports festival
I was happy you said that to me
I think you're fine as you are too
The secret to good shiatsu
is a mother's touch!
Okay, time's up.
Please pass your answer sheets forward.
Kota!
What are you doing later? Wanna hang out?
I have club.
I have club, too.
Seriously?
But exams are finally over.
Come on, let's hang. Let's hang!
Go ask a girl out or something, Roman.
It's not like that.
Why? What's the matter?
Akanecchi!
Bye-bye!
Come on. The school trip
is coming up, after all.
See you tomorrow.
Let's go buy snacks.
Oh, yeah. Bye-bye!
Snacks?
Yeah.
I guess I can't say no to snacks.
Come on, let's go.
Just skip your club.
I can't skip out on my club!
Come on, just this once!
I can't miss a day right now.
I can finally run.
Right?
Oh, I'm gonna go toss this. Hold on a sec.
Okay.
Hey, Curly-kun!
Hey!
We're friends now.
You told me Curly-kun's cool, so...
We have a week until the meet.
Let's stay focused.
Okay!
Have you noticed?
Everyone's hooking up.
For the school trip, I bet.
What? Is that it?
How dumb.
Why? What's wrong with that?
Off-leash dogs are
causing problems
Please keep your
dog on a leash
I wish I had a boyfriend.
Right?
Not especially.
But what about Hira?
Huh?
What?
Nothing.
Not gonna go out with him?
Why?
I heard someone asked him out, but he said no.
Seriously?
He said there's someone he likes.
Definitely Akane.
That's what I think, too.
The literature club has a superstition.
Pick out a book at random,
and that book will give you the perfect
life advice for your situation.
At the very least, I don't believe
romance comes down to chance.
I believe it comes down to volition.
Really?
He should just ask her out.
Hira?
I doubt Akane would turn him down.
Not before the meet.
After the meet, then,
when emotions are high.
Yeah, I can see that.
Have you decided which
high school you want to go to?
More or less.
Don't they ask after your midterms?
I'm too busy thinking about the track meet.
Oh, that's right.
Dad's gonna come cheer for you this time.
Why don't you go to your sister's school?
My school's nice.
Is it?
They're really focused on clubs,
and everyone's pretty cool.
I think it'd be good for you.
It's so far away, though.
Let's move back to Tokyo.
You're gonna be transferred
again anyway, aren't you, Dad?
That's a harsh thing to say...
Being so close would be convenient for me.
More, please.
Go, go! Let's go, let's go, Akane!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, Akane!
Go, go, Akane!
Man, she's fast.
Ready, and...
Akane!
Good job!
Nishio Chinatsu (3)   Kawagoe, Kawagoe Daisan
Mizuno Akane (3)   Kawagoe, Kawagoe Daisan
Just watch me.
The baby boy koala has been
revealed to the public.
He popped his adorable face out of his
mother's pouch, charming the zoo visitors.
Is your track meet coming up?
You're on LINE a lot these days.
Why do you care?
Is your track meet coming up?
Yup, on Sunday
I have practice on Sunday.
I'm going to the shrine on
Sunday, so I'll pray for you
Please and thank you
Why the shrine?
Neighborhood association stuff
He should just ask her out.
Hira?
I doubt Akane would turn him down.
Hey, is there a guy that you like?
I want to ask, but...
Pray for me lots! I want
to beat my own record
I've got you covered
Thanks
All right.
Let's do this.
Full speed ahead
Shoumei High School
The first-place runner in
the last race ran in lane 6.
Kimura-san of Jounan.
Record: 14.21 seconds, tailwind
of 1.3 meters per second.
You're up soon, right?
Yeah.
I hope you beat your personal best.
I don't know...
You can do it.
I've seen how hard you've worked.
Y-Yeah.
Let's both do our best.
Yeah.
Hey...
Mizuno...
Go, Rie!
Nah, never mind.
See you.
Oh, Hira.
Hey.
I'll be cheering up top.
Kumano Shrine
Akane's nervous.
Go get 'em, Akane!
Go!
Set...
Lane 5 takes the lead.
Mizuno-san of Kawagoe City Daisan.
Go!
I wonder how it went.
What should we get?
I'm starvinging.
Say what?
Large vanilla shake.
Wow, you're loaded.
My parents gave me 1,000 yen.
Lucky.
What about you, Mizuno?
Huh? Oh, um...
Wasn't that girl awesome?
Who?
The one in Tanaka's heat.
Oh! Yeah, yeah!
I made up my mind.
I'm gonna train like mad.
Oh?
Starting tomorrow.
But the school trip's coming up.
Are you going to train in Kyoto?
The meet's over
Good idea!
Seriously?
By the way, did you hear?
Kaneko confessed to Miyamoto-san.
Jeez, really?
Aren't they in your class, Akane?
What? I... I don't know.
What? What?
I wasn't asking you boys.
What's up?
Bathroom.
How did it go?
How did it
How did
How
Thank you very much.
Well done.
Bye.
Later.
Mizuno-san.
Oh, um...
Come over here.
Okay.
Is that...
This is, uh...
For the Kawagoe Festival?
Yeah.
Wow!
Are you in the march?
Awesome!
Nah, it's nothing.
So, um, how was the meet?
I set a new personal best.
Nice!
Congrats.
Thanks.
I was wondering how you did.
My battery died...
I was on my way home,
thinking you might be here...
And I found you.
Yeah.
This is weird.
Who was it that translated "I love you"
as "Isn't the moon beautiful tonight?"
Was it Dazai Osamu or Natsume Souseki?
The moon...
Huh? The moon?
I know. It's so pretty.
Would you go out with me?
Howling at the Moon