Let me think, I suppose she was around 11
when she became humanity's first Kamitsuki.
You stay young when you
turn into a Kamitsuki, don't you?
Only on the outside.
The heart can also age, Highness.
Is that true, Renbo?
It's "Renbokoji."
That's too long!
Your godmother's name
is also Renbokoji.
I just call her Godmother.
Tell me, when did you and
the others receive the Blessing?
Blessing?
At the time, we called it a curse.
This is Gustav-eins.
JIOR dropship located.
Moderate damage to hull.
No sign of Valvraves or passengers.
Repeating, moderate damage to hull.
At present, local army forces
are setting up a dragnet.
A thorough search is being conducted,
but they have not been located yet.
We're dealing with the Valvraves here. They're
too much for regional forces to handle.
But sir, we may be on Earth, but we're the
space navy. We don't have jurisdiction.
I understand that this is their turf.
We'll simply offer helpful suggestions.
But sir...
Is there a problem?
No, sir.
I have to say, they picked an interesting
spot to come down in.
Wow, Dorssia's a barren wasteland.
We came down out in the boonies, that's all.
I'm just glad it's not snowing.
Our entry angle was just 0.2 degrees off,
and we end up way out here...
We're done for. I can't believe we landed
right in the middle of enemy territory.
It's no big deal. We're here to pound
the crap out of Dorssia, anyway.
It sounds like this fool still doesn't understand
what "force reconnaissance" means.
- What did you say?!
- Get it into your head already!
We landed in the enemy's lap. We got
no choice but to fight now, you know?
You've got a one-track mind.
Stop it, guys!
This is no time to be
fighting among ourselves.
Right now, we have to think of
a way to reach JIOR from here.
I wonder just how far away it is.
You got a plan?
Um... L-elf is thinking of one. Probably.
We're turning to him again?
He's one of us now.
He's saved our lives on a bunch
of occasions up until now, right?
Did I imagine it? But...
There was blood splatter, too.
Well, yeah, but...
I have faith in L-elf. We need him.
Here is the plan.
The objective of this operation is
to procure a means of transport.
That's true. We abandoned the shuttle.
So where do we get this
means of transport?
From the Dorssian army.
From the enemy?! Sure, a military transport
would be able to carry the Valvraves, but still...
Yet another tall order.
But compared to a consumer product,
its performance would be a lot better.
You make it sound easy,
but how do we do it?
We send spies into the enemy ranks.
This team will be Saki Rukino
and Akira Renbokoji.
Akira?!
Go outside? Me?
Akira Renbokoji. We need your skills.
I'm against it!
He's right! We can't send Akira-chan in undercover!
It would be cruel!
But not me?
Well, Rukkie, you're... You know.
Yeah, you're... You know.
It's because they don't feel
protective about you.
Why Akira?
In terms of skill set, it would
be difficult for anyone else.
Come out!
Stop it, Akira isn't ready to—
I'll go.
Akira?
I'll tough it out.
Look, I'm happy that you want to do
this for your big brother, Akira,
but don't push yourself.
Shoko-chan.
Do you think this will
fool the Dorssians?
Cobbling together a bunch of spare parts
to look like a Valvrave is crazy.
It'll work. L-elf said it just has
to put doubt in their minds.
The goal is to buy time.
Oh, it is?
Miss Sashinami!
There's a call from the ARUS
Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
From ARUS? Not Dorssia?
Yes. They say that the five Valvraves came
down in Dorssian territory, not JIOR.
No way!
Reply from JIOR.
They want to know where
their friends came down.
As we thought, they don't appear to have
any means of contacting the Valvraves.
Although the dimensions and mass of the
Valvrave spotted at Module 77
match the Figaro Report,
the probability that it is a fake
seems to be quite high.
Let's play along and pretend
to be fooled by it.
Sir?
If there are other Valvraves at Module 77,
it will probably put pressure on Dorssia.
That's true. We'll word it as the government confirming
a civilian news organization scoop.
I'll have a draft prepared right away.
The Council of 101... The Magius...
What plans are they setting in motion?
Sorry for the wait.
Huh? Where is she?
We're really taking her with us?
There isn't much time. We're leaving.
Through here?
I've already confirmed that this
leads to the surface up ahead.
Already confirmed?
You know this place?
Yes. I built this place.
Take a close look a the layout, everyone.
Drill L-elf's plan into your heads.
The bombs go further inside.
It's the real thing...
Don't worry, they don't
go off that easily.
"That easily," he says...
Well, they can be triggered to
go off really easily, though.
Which is it?!
Okay, I see what he's doing.
He's cautious, that one.
Sorry, could you hand me a screwdriver?
Um, I just need a screwdriver...
You know, I didn't expect you
to come with us, Marie.
I asked L-elf about it.
He said that you volunteered
to come to Earth.
That's because I thought that if I came
down to Earth, I might remember.
Remember what?
I heard that you were the one who
proposed this operation, Haruto.
What made you decide to go to Earth?
There's a lot that I want to know.
In addition to the situation in JIOR?
About the Valvraves, about the reason
for this war, and... about myself.
- Haru—
- Tokishima!
Food's ready!
Like they say, an army
marches on its stomach.
People in the past had
some good sayings.
For sure!
There's still some
curry-flavored left.
Are you sure I can have it?
Of course!
I'm amazed that you found
this path, Q-vier.
That's our runt!
Say, X. Can I shoot him?
Cut that out, idiot!
Q-vier, permission granted!
Permission acknowledged!
Damn it, cut it out!
Q-vier.
The sound of a gunshot would carry
a long way here. Use a knife.
Don't encourage him!
Roger! A knife it is!
You actually pulled a knife!
Give me authorization, too.
Hey! Cut it out!
Is this... a village?
Yes. It hasn't changed
at all since then.
Wow, people actually live
in a place like this...
What is that?
The pride of the Dorssian army,
the Ideal Blume mobile base weapon.
It establishes a bridgehead by making
assault landings inside enemy lines.
It's a revolutionary weapon that made
the Third Blitz War possible.
That's what attacked
the JIOR mainland?
That's right.
Um... I forget, how do you say "Hello?"
It really hasn't changed, not one bit.
You must work for the Karlstein Agency.
Two of you? Perfect.
The Karlstein Agency.
It may look like a typical settlement, but it's actually
a top-secret facility that trains Dorssian agents.
We were told to kill
anyone suspicious.
Kill any informants.
Kill any deserters.
Kill any witnesses.
Kill.
I-I'm fine, so don't come out yet...
But... the blood...
Didn't you hear me? I'm fine.
If we didn't kill them,
we would be killed.
I explained it back at the Moon, remember?
We Kamitsuki are indestructible.
Wounds heal up in no time.
Really?
Yep, really.
H-Here.
Thanks.
Can you move?
Almost, give me a minute.
Hurry. We're proceeding to
the next step right away.
Those kids, did you kill them?
No. We have use for them.
Saki Rukino. Akira Renbokoji. Body-jack these
two and infiltrate the Dorssian army.
It's time. I'll go on ahead.
Stick to the plan.
Will do. I'll see you on the surface.
There should be a record of the
monitor feed in the cockpit.
If I look at that, I'll know for sure
if I was imagining things.
It's been a long time!
Marie, right? Right? Right?
How do you know my name?
I know you. Pino and Marie. Friends.
Friends? But you're—
This isn't the real me. What's important is that
you and I are friends. Starting 5 years ago.
Five years!
Yes! Friends! Friends!
Your goal is to lure the
enemy force to this hill.
When they arrive at the hill, we collapse the ground
beneath them using the bombs we planted.
Ah, we'll knock them down
into that cave.
Akira Renbokoji.
Your job is to infiltrate the Dorssian army in all the
confusion and hack the transport ship from the inside.
You aren't alone.
T-Th-Tha...
From oh-three-hundred last night until the present,
did any of you detect anything out of the ordinary?
I observed unusual activity
on the hill to the north.
Two boys, late teens. One girl.
Judging from the language two of them used,
I believe them to be JIORan.
Just what I'd expect
from a Karlstein boy.
You can lead us there, I take it?
We'll head for the north hill at once.
Blitzendegen!
He took the bait!
Wait.
We'll go with you.
Hey, did one of them have silver hair?
These two are L-elf's old squadmates!
Begging your pardon, sirs...
We understand. We'll go strictly
in the capacity of observers.
In the event of an engagement, command
authority rests with you. I understand.
He has silver hair and a
real nasty look in his eyes.
I don't believe he was there.
Too bad! Maybe they're students, then.
Most likely.
Those questions fall under
our purview as well.
Fine, fine.
You remember me from 5 years ago?
You've met me?
It's me! It's Pino!
You forgot? Don't remember?
I don't remember. My only memories
are of the past two years.
Tell me. Do you know
the old me?
Oh, I get it. It's because
I ate Runes.
Ate? Absorbed? Sorry.
My speaking is bad again.
Because they reset system.
What are you talking about?
What are you? You aren't an OS?
Marie...
This body is amazing.
This is Renbokoji. We're in position.
Good. Commence operation.
Unit 3, do you copy?
Yeah!
Your objective is to destroy
the Blume. Get going!
Roger that! I'm gonna
do this with gusto!
Enemy attack!
From the sea?
It's started.
Man, the firepower on that thing!
If I fly, my temperature's gonna spike!
That's the Ideal Blume, the Dorssian army's
most powerful weapon. However...
They had another one hidden, huh?
What the—
The Blume's downward fire offers unparalleled power against
land combat weapons with thin top armor plating,
but Unit 5 can focus all its
defensive capabilities overhead.
It's not stopping?
I can't believe this thing's defenses!
That's your cue, Familiar!
Goodbye, Ideal Blume. With the arrival of the Valvraves,
you're already a weapon of the past.
We did it! Now Haruto is up.
Yeah, since we're going in turns.
Wait, what?
Wasn't Haruto next? Did I get it wrong?
No, Haruto isn't here. L-elf?
Haruto Tokishima. What are you doing?
Marie. You... were talking with the
Valvrave just now, weren't you?
Stop right there.
Haruto, what are you?
What are you talking about? I'm—
I saw it. Your right eye was injured
during reentry, and it healed.
Marie?
I know what I saw. When we got
to Earth, your eye was healed.
Mission complete!
We did it! You and me were
more than enough for the job!
Fighters? I've never seen that type before.
They all look the same
after you shoot 'em down.
Output, 20%. Thermal emission values nominal.
Phase 3, clear. Proceeding to aircraft
operational test phase 4.
I'm going to ask you one more time.
Haruto, what are you?
Tell me.
I'm... not human.
Not human?
That's right.
Tell me everything.
About this Valvrave, too.
When Dorssia came to Module 77, I was...
Marie!
Get into your Valvrave, Haruto Tokishima!
The battle has already begun.
Proceed according to plan.
L-elf!
Kirchbaums, proceeding to
annihilation output.
Kirchbaums, you are cleared to proceed.
Be careful! We don't have any intel on these!
Makes no difference to me!
Yamada!
Why did you shoot Marie?!
If the secret of the Kamitsuki got out, this
combat group would no longer be viable.
Don't give me that! Violence is
your answer for everything!
That's impossible...
Next time, episode 16,
"Marie Set Free."
Valvrave the Liberator... The system
that will expose the truth of the world.