That peddler said
it was just behind that mountain pass.
More like three mountains.
Bro's picked up
a weird habit too.
Dororo, a horse.
Yeah, we should've gotten one
if it was going to be this far.
I'm not walking any further
even if that blacksmith isn't here.
No, I need this.
If not here, we walk more.
I know, I didn't really mean that.
Okay.
I think he said the swordmaker's name
was Munetsuna.
All right, let's go bro.
Betrayed this world
And it simmers within
Rupturing my innards
Swelling a reddish black
Until the sun burnt skin ruptures
There is a light
in the depths of the seething darkness
Confirming each other's voices
in the distance
As if to stroke with wet fingertips
I'd like to touch you one day
There is a light
in the depths of the darkness
Confirming each other's voices
in the distance
As if to stroke with wet fingertips
I'd like to touch you one day
#19 The story of the Amanojaku
Munetsuna? He lives on the outskirts
of the village.
-Really?
-Yeah.
But you're not going to ask him
to forge a sword, are you?
But he's a really skilled craftsman,
right?
Nah, he's nothing of the sort.
Hey, that's not what the peddler told us.
He forged that hatchet for me,
but I'm not impressed at all.
And his daughter, Okowa, is really ugly
and has a bad personality.
I've never liked them too much.
Yes.
Coming. Here to complain
about my papa again?
Who are you?
Hi.
Is this Munetsuna's place?
Yeah, that's my papa.
Then you're Okowa?
Yeah, so what?
We were traveling and heard that
your papa forged great swords.
Oh, a customer. Yeah, my papa's
the best swordmaker in the land.
But you see...
The villagers...
Jeez. The people here
always lie like that.
But they still come to Papa for help.
So he's really good?
Of course he is.
Then can he reforge these for us?
Wow, they've really been through a lot.
Hey, bro!
Okowa.
What are you doing!
Bro, I told you not to do that!
Why?
You just can't.
-Why?
-Because I say so!
I don't get it.
He might get mad if we disturb him.
Wait right here.
First impressions are really important,
you know.
Have your sword out.
Hey, look at that funny thing.
Papa, you have customers.
He wants you to reforge some swords.
He probably wants to marry me, too.
-What are you doing!
-Hey.
Papa, don't get angry.
First impressions are important, okay?
Those swords.
What have you killed with them?
Why are we doing this?
We've never purified a sword before.
You don't need to know.
Bishamon, the guardian god
looks over this temple.
Papa and everyone else at the village
pray to it.
That Hyottoko is another god.
One of forging.
This is a god? It has a funny face.
That's because it's blowing on the embers.
Blowing on embers?
It's been passed down for generations
in our family to keep away misfortune.
The Hyottoko god, blowing on embers huh.
Nobody blows on embers like this.
What's wrong, bro?
Hey.
Put the swords there.
Okay.
What the heck are you doing, bro?
-What...?
-Jeez.
This isn't the time to fool around.
"INN"
I'm pooped.
That Munetsuna guy said he'd bring
the swords here when they're done.
The swords will come here...?
Yeah. So let's get some rest till then.
It's not going to cost us as much
as I thought, so we can just relax here.
Don't need them.
I must be really tired. I thought I heard
you say you didn't need them.
Don't need them...
What the heck do you mean?
You need them to get your body back.
Mr. Hyaku, Dororo. It's me, Okowa.
Come in.
Mr. Hyaku?
I thought you might be hungry,
so I made this.
Thanks, I was getting hungry.
Wow, looks yummy.
No, Dororo. The master of the house
gets to eat first.
Master? And who's that?
Hey, bro and I are on
a really important journey right now.
Once the swords are done, we're leaving.
I'm prepared to go with you.
Are you crazy? It's not some joyride.
I'm the only one who can handle it.
Don't worry. I'm the daughter of
the land's best swordmaker.
Dang it, you tell her bro.
That you can't be with Okowa.
I will be with Okowa.
Mr. Hyaku!
Hey, you shouldn't joke around like that.
Not joking.
-But the journey...
-I quit.
And the rest of your body?
Don't want it. I'm fine like this.
Body?
-Stop joking already, I mean it.
-Not joking.
Then what about me?
Don't have to be together anymore.
Mr. Hyaku, I don't mind, really.
Dororo can stay with us.
Say that again...
I don't need Dororo with me.
Fine, have it your way. I hate you!
You big ole dummy idiot jerk!
Listen here. I'm really glad that
you and Okowa are getting together!
-What did I just...?
-Oh, Dororo.
You two were meant for each other!
Thank you, I'm so happy.
Keep talking. I really think so.
-Oh, Dororo.
-Mumble, grumble, rumble...
That's Mr. Hyaku's sushi!
Little Dororo, crying for us like that.
Dororo looked happy.
Bro, you big ole jerk.
I don't care about you anymore. I mean it.
What's going on?
My condolences. What a great tragedy.
Yes, it truly is.
Only bad things to come now.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I told the villagers that I was going
to marry you, and now look at all this.
Okowa, my dear.
They say wedding attire makes a girl glow.
I'll make one to make you look shabby.
You can count on me.
Okay then.
They're always like this.
Good for you, Okowa.
I'd been hoping you'd hurry up
and get married.
Hope you have a good wedding.
Wow, thanks.
He's honest for once.
What's a wedding?
It means you and I
are going to be husband and wife.
Husband and wife...
I thought the earlier the better,
so I set it for tomorrow.
That's way too fast.
Okay.
Wait a second, you idiot!
Wedding? Hah! I congratulate you
from the bottom of my heart!
Listen here.
No matter what anyone might say,
you're gonna be happy together.
We sure will be, Dororo.
Gosh dang it, what's happened to me?
Hey, don't eat that!
Dororo, it's okay.
I will become Okowa's husband.
Dororo looked happy.
What the heck, bro?
All head over heels for Okowa.
You like her so much, huh?
Fine then. You have it your way,
and I'll have it mine.
Dororo...
My, how ugly you look.
Such a plain girl.
You put this lovely kimono to waste.
Mr. Hyaku, you're not supposed to see yet.
My, my. How ugly.
The swords will come here.
If he doesn't need the swords,
I'll throw them away.
I really am going to do it.
What are you doing here?
-Don't scare me like that.
-Who's scaring who?
This is bro's new sword?
It's not done yet.
I've just been to purify it.
What were you going to do with that one?
So that's why you wanted
to throw them away.
Bro suddenly lost interest in the journey.
And I say things I don't mean.
I don't know what to do now.
Bro doesn't understand how I feel at all.
He's helped me out a whole bunch
ever since we met.
So I'd made up my mind to help him
get through rough times.
I swore that I would.
But now...
How can he quit the journey now?
I came for you.
You just came for me a few days ago.
You jerk.
Did I just fall asleep?
-Don't bother me.
-Sorry.
Aren't you going to Okowa's wedding?
Nothing is more important to a swordmaker
than making swords.
Okowa understands.
You really like swords, huh.
You hate them?
I hate samurai.
So I don't like swords made for killing.
I hate people killing people, too.
My ideal is to make a sword
that makes fighting cease.
A sword that makes the enemy see
that they're no match and give up.
Is that even possible?
It won't be easy,
I might not live to see it happen.
I just know I shouldn't use my powers
for the wrong cause.
I was wrong. I have to stay by bro's side.
Do you really mean that?
Of course I do!
Huh? I've been saying
what I really mean, haven't I?
Why am I okay when I'm here?
Wait, since when have I
been talking in opposites?
Bro... What about him?
Since when has he been weird?
That temple!
-Come on, we have to go to the temple.
-Why?
To get married, come on.
The villagers will hold a celebration
for us afterwards.
The swords will come here.
They can come
when we get back from the temple.
The swords will come here.
Was it you that did all this?
I knew it.
-Dororo?
-Bro!
What's that creature!
That ghoul is probably what made us
act weird.
Get it!
No, that way!
No, not me. Over there!
Mr. Hyaku, what are you doing?
Dororo...
Bro...
You're going to kill Dororo, stop!
Dororo, are you okay?
Dororo.
Bro.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Who'd have thought it was real.
So it was all this ghoul's fault.
Legend has it there was once an Amanojaku
that worked mischief in the village.
It was confined here.
So we really were protected
by the Hyottoko gods.
But when did it get out?
Who knows?
Now then, Mr. Hyaku and Dororo
are back to being friends again.
So let's get on with the wedding...
Wait, if everyone was speaking
in opposites because of the ghoul...
That means...
Dororo and Mr. Hyaku were too, and...
So you see, it's not Mr. Hyaku's fault.
I'm sorry.
Okowa, you don't need to marry him anyway.
I couldn't tell you
how I felt all this time.
But I promise to make you happier
than grouchy face here.
Will you marry me?
Whatever.
Okowa looks happy.
Wow.
I told you,
Papa's the best swordmaker in the land.
The swords are here.
You like them?
Bro looks so happy.
I look happy.
They've been through harsh fates
no normal human could even imagine.
And it's not over for them yet.
There was no place for you by his side
to begin with.
No doubt about that. Dealing with
ghouls like that all the time.
-Don't rub your head on people anymore.
-Why?
Because it'll go pear-shaped!
Pear...?
I'll explain later.
Let's get going then, bro.
You go with me.
Duh. I'm the only one
who can handle this journey with you.
We look happy.
Born into this world
There is no salvation
The distorted shape of the heart
Yet it beats courageously
There is no turning back
Even from the path of evil
Witnessing the withering seasons
We search for the truth
In our ugliness
We don't even recognize the pain
As we peel back the skin
We are forever tormented by our stupidity
But if the dawn never comes
Through the painful night
You who distrusts nothing
You will be able to love
this accursed world
Now that we carry the world
on our shoulders
It's time to take it back
"Amanojaku"