I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Tanaka-san.
Like I said, don't worry about it.
Never mind me. Are you all right?
Yes. I rested a little
on the way here.
I feel better now that
I'm off the bus.
All right, then.
We're counting on you
for today's match.
Do it just like the three-on-three.
Let me spike freely like that.
Tanaka.
Don't pressure him.
What? What's that?
I'll... I'll... I'll do my b...
I'm going to the bathroom.
First the top, then the bottom!
You're a busy guy.
There he goes again. How pathetic.
I'm going to knock some
courage into him.
What are you thinking?
That kind of thing
won't work on Hinata.
But we won't know
'til we try it.
Tanaka! Keep this
simpleton away from him.
Right.
Haikyu!!
Episode 6: An Interesting Team
Hey, that Karasuno team
that's coming today...
isn't that where you-know-who is?
Who?
The King of the Court.
You went to the same junior high
he did, didn't you, Kindaichi?
Oh, you mean Kageyama?
He's no big deal.
Sure, he was head and shoulders
above the rest in skill,
but he's just not cut out
to be a team player, at all.
He's too self-centered.
I see... I guess since
he went to Karasuno,
his strength as a player
must be a thing of the past.
Besides, all I know about Karasuno
is that their manager is a beauty.
Are you serious?
That's right. She's kind of sexy.
Oh yeah, and there's a riffraff
kind of guy there, too.
He's got a shaved head, and an
unpleasant look in his eyes.
He looks real stupid.
Um...
Don't underestimate us too much,
or we'll eat you alive.
You shouldn't say things
like that, Tanaka-san.
Look what you did.
You scared these poor elites.
Now I feel sorry for them.
We're not intimidated.
Who's the guy with the glasses?
Was there a guy that
tall at Karasuno?
Oh, you're right. We should save
our bullying for the match.
You guys.
I can't let you out of my sight.
We apologize.
Oh, it's all right.
Tanaka, stop that look.
It's been a while, King.
Karasuno High School
Volleyball Team
What sort of dictatorship
do you belong to these days?
I'm looking forward to
seeing it in the match.
Yeah.
Why's he pretending to be passive?
Gymnasium No.3
H-Huge.
The gym. The people.
Greeting.
Nice to meet you.
Aoba Johsai is known for each
of its members being highly skilled
equally in offense and defense.
These guys could go to any school
and become the ace.
Here goes.
Their powerful blocks are famous.
What's the matter, you two?
Hinata's here to throw
them for a loop, right?
We know you're lousy, so we'll
cover you. Leave it to us.
But when you hit a serve,
you're on your own.
You'd better not miss.
Just kidding, just kidding.
A missed serve is no big deal.
You don't have to worry about
a thing, just give them your...
Huh? Where did Hinata go?
He went to the toilet.
Again?
This is bad...
What's the matter with
these guys from Karasuno?
All they've got is a big attitude.
That's true.
This guy...
He was next to Kageyama
in the junior high match.
His silhouette is like a turnip.
I remember him.
Hey. You're a first-year
at Karasuno?
Y-Yeah, I am.
Well, then how is Kageyama doing?
Our King seems pompous, as usual.
That's not how he is.
It's not about being pompous.
Under the dictatorship of
the great King Kageyama,
commoners like me are cruelly oppressed,
made to bitterly suffer.
Just because he's a little skilled!
Who does he think he is?
What did I tell you?
He's utterly despised.
There's no doubting his skill at receiving,
blocking, and serving.
That's right. It's aggravating.
But his toss is amazing.
But his toss is the worst.
His toss?
Is amazing.
You've never spiked one of his tosses
in a match before, have you?
They're terrible.
They're too difficult to spike.
Is that so?
Because he's a self-centered king.
He's a setter, and yet he can't do
his most important job.
Letting the spiker spike the ball.
What Kageyama needs are pawns
he can maneuver as he wills.
Anything he doesn't need to win,
he discards.
Let's wait until the match
to see if Kageyama
is still the same as he was
in junior high, turnip-kun.
Huh?
Right, Hinata?
"Anything he doesn't need to win,
he discards."
If I goofed in Kageyama's sight...
Get lost. You're useless.
Players will get switched.
My stomach hurts.
We look forward to it.
Hinata, you don't have
to be so nervous. Relax.
Yes. I will do my best to relax.
Hinata, hurry up and
get in uniform.
Hey manager,
is there anything effective you
could say to that first-year?
Y-Yes...
Hey, there.
I'm counting on you.
And that just dealt the death blow.
I'm sorry, Hinata.
Aoba Johsai              Karasuno
We will now begin the practice
match of Karasuno High School
versus Aoba Johsai High School.
Let's play.
That shrimp is a middle blocker?
That's gotta be some kind of mistake.
That's Kageyama for real.
What's he doing at Karasuno?
Who knows?
Hey, Hinata. Buck up.
Y-Yes.
I will do my best to buck up.
No, I need you to relax.
Hey, Hinata. You know the drill.
The same as in the
three-on-three match.
I-I know that.
Are you sure?
Matsukawa, nice serve.
All right, I got this.
Idiot, that obviously
wasn't your ball.
I'm sorry.
Ennoshita, cover.
Tanaka.
Yeah.
And that's the first point.
Don't mind, don't mind.
Hinata, relax and stay aware
of your surroundings.
I'm sorry.
This guy...
He's completely overwhelmed.
Hinata!
Let's relax, first and foremost.
All right. Lucky, lucky.
Aoba Johsai      Karasuno
Touch-net.
And Karasuno's score
finally changes.
Hey, you! That's enough nervousness!
No! Give me another chance!
They're really not a big deal.
He sure hasn't changed, at all.
All right.
Let's steadily rack up points.
The next serve will be...
This couldn't be timed worse...
Aoba Johsai              Karasuno
It's Hinata's serve.
A serve-miss is an immediate
score for the opponent.
Hinata, relax!
If I miss, the first
set will be finished.
Kageyama. Is he still breathing?
Can he do this?
How am I supposed to know?
Anything he doesn't need to win,
he discards.
Don't blow it.
I'll have to sit out if I blow it.
Relax. It's all right.
It's all right. It's all...
Crap, it didn't hit my hand right.
Aoba Johsai      Karasuno
Crap.
Hey.
Nice headshot, man!
Is your head okay?
Don't razz him.
Stop it, you guys.
Now I've done it.
Hey, Kageyama.
W-W-Wait. Once we talk about this,
you'll understand.
Kageyama.
Stop.
Just wondering...
Yes?
Why are you so intimidated?
Why are you so nervous?
Is it because the
opponents are tall?
Is it because this is your
first practice match?
There's nothing scarier than hitting a serve
into the back of my head...
Is there?
I can't think of anything.
In that case, you have no reason
to be nervous any more.
Because you've already done it...
The scariest thing possible.
So now...
Get back to normal, you jackass.
Was that goof "safe"?
Huh? What are you talking about?
If that was safe, it doesn't
matter what I did here.
Why was I intimidated by
that turnip-head anyway?
But we lost the first set
because of what I just did.
Even if Kageyama is okay with it...
Hey, you. Hinata.
You.
Yes.
Are you thinking you have
to play well, like the others?
As if you have the experience?
If I don't, I'll get switched
with another player.
I want to be in the match to the end.
Hey. Don't underestimate us.
We all know you're a lousy player.
Daichi-san knows it,
and yet he lets you play.
Huh?
As for getting switched
for another player...
Think about it when you get switched!
Huh?
So don't worry about something
that hasn't happened yet.
Shouldn't you jump in?
Oh, yes. But I think
it's all right.
You don't have any brains for that.
Listen to me. In volleyball,
everybody on this side
of the net is your ally.
It doesn't matter if you're lousy.
It doesn't matter if you're a nuisance.
You can slow us down. That's okay.
But to make up for those things...
That's why you have your team
and your senpais.
Oh!
Go on. Call me Tanaka-senpai.
Tanaka-senpai.
Once more.
He just wants to be called "senpai."
Tanaka-senpai.
Yeah, but Tanaka was really
helpful just now.
His speech was totally effective
because he seems to have
no ulterior motive.
Karasuno              Aoba Johsai
What's this?
I hear it's a practice match.
The second set is about to start.
Hey, teach me later how to serve
to the back of the head.
Teach me later, too.
Ennoshita, nice serve.
You'll do the same as in the
three-on-three match.
You go in max speed and jump and
swing where there is no blocker.
Just be careful you don't
bump into other spikers.
Yeah.
Kunimi.
Kageyama, cover.
Yes.
Left, go forward.
Right.
There's no quick...maybe it'll
be open, from left or right...
What?
A quick?
It didn't hit my hand.
They do quick?
Or was that just a bluff?
Either way...
If you can't spike a ball like that,
the King will get mad.
Hinata.
You see?
My bad. That toss was too high.
Kageyama...
...apologized?
I'll try to forgive you.
Ouch! Ouch! Kageyama, I'll go bald.
One point.
Nice serve.
All right.
The right and setter moved.
Bring it.
The left is waiting.
Who will Kageyama use?
Now. Right there.
Oh. Huh?
Yes.
There it is,
the freak toss-and-spike.
Did you see that? That was fast.
Hinata, Kageyama.
One-two...
Yeah!
It's like team spirit!
Huh?
Not like. It's a for real.
Right, right.
Nice toss, Kageyama.
Thanks.
Hey, does that shrimp
do fast attacks?
Let's do another one.
Yup.
He's changed from the first set.
Good, lost your cool?
Lost your cool?
You'd better keep your eyes on Hinata.
Hinata is back in action.
Time for a counterattack.
Karasuno              Aoba Johsai
Chance ball.
All right.
If I know it's coming...
there's nothing to fear.
Oh, yeah?
I was waiting for this.
Damn. The shrimp was just a decoy.
I thought it was coming to me.
How do you like me now, turnip-kun?
I told you we'd get
you in the match.
I thought I was going to
spike it, and said, "Oh, yeah?"
I'm so embarrassed.
That's how it's supposed to be.
You jumped for real, so the
opponents reacted for real.
That's how it is?
That's how it is.
Damn.
Don't sweat it, Kindaichi.
We have our attack strategy.
Don't let them get to you.
Right.
I'm just a bystander and I can
see how the blockers disperse.
I didn't know Karasuno
had such a strong team.
Hinata, you idiot.
But they make a lot of mistakes, too.
Huddle.
Right.
What's the matter, Hinata?
When I entered a tournament
for the first time,
I thought I had to do everything
right all by myself.
But now, there are players who are
way better than me all around me.
So all I can do now is
believe in them, and jump.
I didn't have to overthink anything
in the first place.
You're late.
But it's believing and jumping
that are your powerful weapons.
Hey, Kindaichi.
Kageyama isn't like you said.
I wasn't expecting that, either.
I can't believe there's a spiker
who can synch with
his reckless tosses.
I don't think so.
#5 isn't looking
at the ball at all.
Coach, what do you mean?
I think Kageyama
pinpoint-tossed the ball
directly where he was about to swing.
Is that kind of thing possible?
Kageyama? Matching someone else?
That can only mean
that #5 has the ability
to make that self-centered
and prideful
Wanna drink? Oh, sorry.
Your face is lower than I thought...
Kageyama do what he's been doing.
What's amazing is that he jumps
believing in Kageyama 100%.
He believes that's where
the ball will come.
If they get past your block,
receive solidly.
You're all the best
members of our team.
Show your pride.
Yes.
Kageyama is amazing.
It's a shame we couldn't
have him on our team.
He did get invited, didn't he?
Yeah, but even if Kageyama
had come to our team,
that doesn't mean he
would've played like that.
Huh?
Maybe Kageyama is how he is
now because of Karasuno,
All right. Let's win this set.
Ouch. That hurt, Kageyama.
and because of #5.
A shot in the arm,
a shot in the arm.
All right. It's starting.
Karasuno              Aoba Johsai
Chance ball.
Tsukishima.
All right.
Tsukki, nice!
Nice, Tsukishima.
Your tosses are too accurate.
It gives me the creeps.
What?
I wouldn't have put it that way,
I can just aim at your
glasses, if you like.
but I can sort of understand
what Tsukishima means.
Try it. You'll get banished
from the gym again.
It's like you're wishing the
ball would go somewhere,
and then it just appears there.
I'll do it so no one will notice.
You obviously can't do that.
Are you stupid?
It's totally amazing. But...
We're in a match.
That's about enough.
Tanaka, nice serve.
Nice serve.
I see...
WS Ennoshita    MB Tsukishima   S Kageyama
WS Sawamura   MB Hinata    WS Tanaka
S Sugawara
MB Yamaguchi
WS Kinoshita
MB Narita
The rotation moves every time
we score and we get to serve.
So now it's Kageyama-kun and
Ennoshita-kun in front position.
Yes, it's the exact opposite
positioning from the start of the match.
When Hinata-kun is in front position,
his being a decoy
raises the level of the
entire team's offense.
On the other hand,
if Tsukishima-kun is in front...
we'll have a powerful block
equal to the Seijo team's.
You're good at blocking, too, huh?
But don't get too carried away.
Don't get too full of yourself,
being all gangly like that.
Don't fight, guys. Okay?
Your opponents are on the
other side of the net!
Hey, here it comes.
All right.
Hey. I'm the one that blocked it.
What? It hit my hand, too.
That's enough you two!
Serves those guys right.
What are you grinning at?
Kageyama, stop it.
Damn. Now I'm getting worried.
Karasuno              Aoba Johsai
Hey, that was covered for
you Kunimi, you idiot.
We have to stop #5 somehow.
True, the combo of #5
and Kageyama is formidable.
But then again,
though he has no calm,
that spiker, Tanaka-kun,
is an overwhelming force.
Then there's that somewhat uninspired
but clever blocker, Tsukishima-kun.
And the captain, Sawamura-kun,
who covers all his team's holes.
Bring it on.
There are those who
are inexperienced,
and their defense is full of holes,
but their offense
is freely flexible,
and makes full use of
the inexperienced.
They made a fool of us...
So this is Karasuno.
They are odd.
They are dangerous.
They are an interesting team.
Karasuno              Aoba Johsai
They won the set.
Damn.
Nice toss, Kageyama.
Oh, thanks.
On to winning the final set!
I'm glad they don't have another
serve-hitter like Kageyama.
A comeback victory.
Victory.
Yeah, because I must admit our
team is not good at receiving.
Victory.
Thank you.
We mustn't let our guard down.
I'm thinking that maybe
their setter wasn't
the main setter...
Oikawa, you're back.
Next Episode Preview
What? Seijo's setter wasn't
the main setter?
Who is that sneering dude, anyway?
Kageyama, you know him?
Well, you'll have to wait and see.
What?
Episode 7: Versus the Great King
Next time on Haikyu!!
"Versus the Great King"