That bastard! Where the hell did he go?
If I go into the alley,
I'll only get cornered.
Guess I'll head back out for now, and—
What should I do?
I can't cause a commotion now
and risk getting noticed by the perpetrator.
Hey, you...
Is someone chasing you, by any chance?
Uh...
If you're in trouble, I can help you!
Have we met somewhere before?
I think this is the first time.
But what about your pursuers?
If you don't get going,
they're going to catch up to you.
Gotcha.
The thing is, I'd like to avoid
any trouble if I can.
Okay!
Then come on! This way!
Hey, come back here!
Don't tell me this girl is...
a Strega?
Battle Song
Since we've come this far,
I guess we should be in the clear for now.
Thanks. I really owe you one.
So? Why were they chasing you?
Did they rip you off?
Well, it's complicated.
I see.
Well, you don't have to tell me
if you don't want to.
But if you're planning to head back,
I'd wait a little longer if I were you.
With Rotlicht being
kind of on edge, and all.
It is?
Since there's a Festa
underway right now...
The police have been cracking down
way harder than usual.
So the mafia running Rotlicht
are acting pretty paranoid.
I see...
If that's the case,
maybe I should look elsewhere.
Thanks for everything!
I'd like to thank you properly if I could,
but I just don't have the time right now.
It's all right, it's all right.
Don't worry about it...
Ayato Amagiri.
Look at those speedy reflexes!
No wonder
you're a Phoenix Festa finalist.
But you know, I'm a little devastated
that you'd be so wary of me.
How did you know my name?
Well, aside from the fact
that you're already a celebrity...
I think you should work
on your disguise more.
It's totally obvious that it's you.
Y-You think so?
But it's not like I helped you
because you're famous.
But then why would you...
Who wouldn't help someone
in their time of need?
And besides,
you didn't strike me as a villain.
Sorry. After you saved me...
You really are a nice guy, aren't you?
Right, it's not like I—
For crying out loud...
How about giving
your pursuers a break?
So, was it you?
The bastard who's been
looking for somebody?
My guys would be interested
to hear about that.
You're coming with me now.
Well, whoops!
Who knew you'd actually
chase him all the way here?
What the hell?
There's a woman here, too!
Talk about happy accidents!
I mean, that really motivates me!
Feel free to resist to your heart's content.
Otherwise, it would be such a bore!
Hold up a second!
This girl has nothing to do with this!
You're probably wasting your breath.
I mean, he's the type who puts
his own hobbies over his work.
Right?
Former Jie Long Seventh Institute Rank #7,
Nguyen of the Twin Snakes?
So you know about me?
Well, how awesome is that?
I never thought that a Lindwurs Festa
semifinalist would be reduced
to serving as a runner for the mafia!
Yeah...
That was a long time ago.
H-Hey!
Knock it off!
Outta my way!
Look out!
Is that the best you can do?
Not bad, little girl!
In that case, I'm gonna go for broke!
No...
I've had enough.
If you were still in your prime,
this wouldn't have gone so smoothly.
All right... By the way,
are you looking for someone?
Well, that's what I heard
that guy mention just now.
Well, yeah.
I just might be able to help you out
with that... What do you say?
Help me out? You?
Yes. But first...
Why don't we go somewhere else?
Okay, here we are!
Sorry to take up your time
when you seem to be in a hurry.
No, I'm the one who should be sorry
for dragging you into this.
I see. I think I might be starting
to figure you out.
Figure me out?
Even when you're in trouble yourself,
you're a kind-hearted person
who can be considerate to others.
But you also try to carry
the load by yourself,
and you can't bring yourself
to rely on others.
But during your
semifinal match yesterday,
you did lean on Riessfeld, didn't you?
You two really looked
like a team out there.
You're pretty perceptive, huh?
Well, yes.
All right, then, can you tell me
what kind of person you're looking for?
Oh, but—
Don't worry.
It's not like I'm going to tag along.
The point is, you just need the location
of this person you're looking for, right?
Don't tell me...
you're a Detection-type Strega?
I wouldn't call myself that, but...
Well, I guess I can accomplish
something similar enough.
Anyway, I need some information
to be able to visualize her.
All right. I'm looking
for a girl who's ten years old.
Her name is Flora.
She's not lost, is she?
No. She's been captured by someone.
The perpetrator is...
I can guess, but I'm not sure yet.
Okay, I can do without that, I think.
So what about this girl's
looks and personality?
Um...
NAME
NATIONALITY
DATE OF BIRTH: 5/10        AGE
GENDER: FEMALE        BLOOD TYPE
Let's see.
That's fine.
I think we're good now.
But there's just one thing I want you
to promise me first. All right?
Promise you?
Don't ever tell anyone
about what's about to happen now.
Keep it to yourself.
Gotcha. I promise.
All right, I'm going to get started,
so open up a map.
The bigger the better, probably.
All right. How's this?
You're...
Sylvia Lyyneheym!
Sylvia Lyyneheym...
Queenvail Girls Academy's Rank #1.
A Songstress and a Strega...
Using song as her medium,
she can transform her own image
in all kinds of ways.
Her power is...
omnipotence.
Hmm, hmm...
Looks like it's the northern corner
just outside Rotlicht.
You're saying Flora's there?
Yes, if I had more time to narrow it down,
I could've given you a better idea.
No, no, this is more than enough!
Really...
Thanks!
I'm happy I was able to help!
All right, I'll be on my way now,
or my manager will give me an earful!
Hey, hold up a second!
If you don't mind,
could you give me your number?
I like it!
I don't think anyone's hit on me
so blatantly in a long time!
N-No, I wasn't hitting on you
or anything!
I wanted to thank you properly,
Ms. Lyyneheym.
You can call me Sylvie!
That's my private address,
so contact me anytime.
O-Okay.
To be honest, I've been
a little intrigued by you for a while.
Talking to you in person today,
that intrigue is stronger now.
All right, good luck to you, Ayato.
In my own humble way,
I'll be praying
for little Flora's safe return.
It's great that you got a lead
on Flora's whereabouts.
But how did you
narrow it down to this spot?
Uh... well, you see...
Sorry, I can't say.
Well, whatever.
All right, let's head over there right now!
Both you and Ayato should stay away.
You've got the final.
The final starts at noon.
That gives us some time, doesn't it?
No, this time around,
Sasamiya's in the right.
It would be too reckless
to go into the final like this.
You should rest as much as you can.
Ayato-senpai, Julis, we'll be fine!
We're going to rescue Flora
no matter what!
Fine.
Then let's focus
all our energy on the final.
Right.
We'll go rescue Flora,
and you two will avenge us.
All's well that ends well.
They're counting on us,
as well, aren't they?
Though it's a bit too much.
No problem.
If we can rescue Flora,
you'll be able to use the Ser=Versta.
Well, as long as you get it done
in time, that is.
Do you have to be
such a buzzkill, Yabuki?
- Just sayin', just sayin'...
- I'm gonna kick your butt.
Number 7, what's the situation?
All clear.
And your side?
Compliant, at least outwardly.
Shadow Star doesn't seem
to be on the move, either.
But,
there was a totally suspicious-looking
punk digging around the joint.
Well, as you know, the people
who run the Rotlicht all hate my guts.
So I'm not sure how solid that intel is.
What if someone crashes the party?
Play the hostage card.
I don't give a damn
if it's an expendable one.
Understood.
What's wrong?
Apparently the party-crashers
have just arrived.
This building used to be
a fairly well-known casino,
but recently one of its
customers went berserk
and totally trashed the place, I hear.
Th-That sounds scary.
Well, it's not uncommon, you know.
But I hear they've stopped
construction for the last few days.
Stopped it?
Th-Then it's like
a vacant house right now?
Pretty sketchy, huh?
All right, why don't we
go inside and check it out?
B-But how are we gonna do that?
Hey, hey, just leave it to me.
Keep an eye out for me, will you?
All right!
Okay, now we're in business!
All right, why don't we...
Hey, come on!
This isn't anything hard core!
I just used some tools
I picked up online,
and I've only ever
tried it out a few times.
That was too easy for you.
Now, now...
Come on, let's get going!
The place seems to be deserted, huh?
Upstairs or downstairs?
Either way, I think
we should all stick together.
I heartily second that motion.
Since I'm not a good brawler.
This is the part where you say,
"I'm a man, leave it to me."
But there is such a thing
as "right man, right job"!
Besides, I've done my due diligence.
Due diligence?
Since I won't be of any use myself,
all I have to do is call on someone
who will be, right?
What the hell's that?!
Is that... Is that a human?
There's all this Mana
concentrated around there.
It's probably Setting Magic.
Either way, looks like
we are in the right place!
What the hell?
That wasn't much of a spell.
I'll bet even I can handle...
How many do you think there are?
Don't ask me.
Hey, this must be
autonomous-type power, right?
These guys can only execute
simple commands for the most part!
They must've been ordered
to get rid of any intruders!
I see.
Then there's no reason
for us to deal with them.
Kirin! Sorry!
Can you cover me for a second?
Roger that!
My legs...
39-type Lux Ray Gun, Wolfdora...
Burst.
Strafe.
Are you all right, Saya?
No problem.
I probably only have two
or three more shots left, huh?
Hey! I think it's too soon to relax!
What? Not again!
Th-This could be endless!
Kirin, I know it's a little reckless,
but we're going to charge in.
Yes... I think that's our only choice.
Jeez!
What the hell
do you think you're doing?!
Just the man I've been waiting for!
MacPhail-senpai!
Why are you here?
Damned Yabuki forced me to come!
Hey, now.
What do you mean by "forced"?
All I did was ask you for a favor!
Blackmailing as a negotiating tactic!
Is that how you ask for favors?!
Threatening is more like it!
Okay, MacPhail,
take care of the rest, okay?
Hey!
W-We're so sorry!
We're counting on you
to take care of this!
H-Hey!
Well, then, best of luck, man!
H-Hold up, you guys!
So Kirin... upstairs or downstairs?
Which do you think, Saya?
Down.
Me, too.
I heard what's going down.
But even still...
Why should I have to
take on a role like this?!
COUNTDOWN TO THE FINAL
It's almost time, huh?
Is it?
We never did hear
from Saya and Kirin, did we?
Julis...
Don't give me that look, Ayato.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, Ayato...
It's nice to have friends
you can trust, isn't it?
The thing about me, Ayato...
Flora... Everyone back home...
They mean everything to me.
That's why I swore
I'd do anything for them,
and I always thought
they were all I'd ever need.
But now that I think of it,
by doing that,
I was only closing off the world.
Ayato...
Because I have you as my, uh...
my partner...
that really hit home.
Julis...
I know I'm not done
making more friends I can cherish.
Like Saya and Kirin, you know?
Right now, I can believe
in them whole-heartedly.
So don't worry.
I'll be fine!
I see...
That's good, then.
All right, emerging from the east gate
is Seidoukan Academy's
Amagiri/Riessfeld team!
And from the west gate,
Arlequint Academy's AR-D/RM-C team!
We've seen all kinds of battles
over the last two weeks,
and now the Phoenix Festa
is down to its last battle!
This is the final match!
Oh, wow, I can't wait!
It really is mystifying.
Despite our situation...
Right now, I want to win this match
so badly, I can hardly stand it!
Yeah, same here.
All right, then,
let's go for it all, you and I!
Why don't we take everything
we've ever wanted?
Without missing a single one, right?
So we meet at last, Ayato Amagiri!
I have been looking forward to this day!
As I'm always hearing
about you from my master,
I expect great things of you!
Please trigger more exhilaration
in me than Kirin Toudou did!
Unfortunately,
I can't guarantee that I will.
But this match...
Victory will be ours!
No matter what!
These surging emotions...
I cannot hold them back!
Ayato Amagiri!
I have waited so long to battle you—
Be silent, you good-for-nothing.
Episode 20
The Phoenix Showdown
There isn't sufficient time during this
preview to waste on useless prattle.