Out!
Lucky!
Karasuno                            Aoba Johsai
We won the first set against Seijoh!
We won the first set!
All right!
Take the second set, too!
Sorry.
That idiot! Not only was that
obviously Kindaichi's ball,
but then he steals it only to hit it out?!
And they were at set point!
How can I even start to explain?!
That's dangerous!
Iwaizumi!
Yeah, that's it! That's how to start!
Oh, I'm fine...
I was feeling stressed because
I hadn't been put in the match.
That's not a valid reason!
Who the hell is that?
Why would Seijoh swap in a guy like that?
Aoba Johsai                                Karasuno
Ah, that guy from earlier is there.
He's starting this set.
Since he's replacing Kunimi,
he might be pretty smart.
Be careful.
You're more or less free
to play how you want,
but if you interfere with us,
you'll be back on the bench.
Just don't do any unnecessarily dangerous plays.
Right.
Why did you only reply to Iwa-chan?!
He challenged Iwaizumi-san
a whole bunch of times,
and lost every single time, so he
at least listens to Iwaizumi-san.
Not happening!
What are we, a wolf pack?
Well, the one who'll be
using him is Oikawa-san.
Right.
We're gonna take this
momentum and run with it!
We're gonna win the second set, too!
Yeah!
Haikyu!!
Episode 21: "The Destroyer"
Asahi-san, get one! Nice serve!
Out!
Damn it! Sorry!
So close! You'll get the next one!
Don't mind!
Your face is scary!
What'd you say?!
Oikawa, nice serve!
Aoba Johsai                                Karasuno
Out, out!
Sorry!
Don't mind. We'll get the next one.
I wonder what's wrong with Oikawa-kun.
He messed up another serve.
But that speed is incredible.
Touching that would break off your arms.
I feel like we're getting more in sync.
Tsukishima, nice serve!
Damn you!
Nice cover, Iwa-chan!
There are three attackers on the
front line... Who's it going to be?
Mad Dog-chan.
Open from the right?!
What the heck is "Mad Dog"?!
Is it an alias? That's awesome!
One blocker!
What?
He's sprinting basically parallel to the net?
Three blockers!
That cut shot was insane!
So that's why he was running like that.
Hm?
When you're facing the block,
there are choices you can make,
but chances are you'll get blocked.
Instead, he hit it to cut across the blockers.
He comes in from the right
and hits with his right hand,
pulling off that incredible cut shot.
Mad Dog is amazing!
Aoba Johsai                                Karasuno
Iwaizumi, nice serve!
It's coming back! Chance ball!
Damn it! Sorry!
Oikawa and Iwaizumi can really pressure
us if they make a lot of serves.
Got it!
And now, there's also the Mad Dog...
A double quick?!
All right!
Great, great, Kentaro! Push it,
push it, Kentaro! One more time!
I know he's a mad dog, but
he's not going to keep biting,
so you can come in.
The Shrimp knew you weren't
going to hit it, Kindaichi.
Sorry, I was a bit scared.
Iwa-chan, one more! Nice serve!
Yeah!
Nice receive!
C quick!
Y-You okay?!
Y-Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
It's that #16 again! Three points in a row!
Even though they're getting in,
those attacks seem pretty violent.
Ever since that #16 came in,
their attack rhythm has changed.
Kyotani, nice kill!
Iwaizumi, one more! Nice serve!
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
Sorry!
All right!
We finally get a point back.
Nice, Makki!
Here it comes!
Let's battle, Mad Dog!
After letting #16 go all out on his attacks,
now it's a slide hit from Kindaichi!
All right!
He's angry that he was used as a decoy.
Though that itself makes him
an even better decoy.
I'll make your fangs even sharper.
Let's play carefully! That's a
Seijoh we're not familiar with.
Aoba Johsai                                               Karasuno
Kindaichi, nice serve!
Got it!
Left!
Center!
Is this a strategy where one middle
blocker is always on Hinata?
It's up! Cover!
Got it! Kyotani, get the last!
Sorry! It's close to the net!
Three blockers!
If he hits it, it'll get caught.
Bring it back once!
Nice block!
All right!
That was an intense full swing.
That idiot...
You idiot! There are other
ways to hit or even feint!
If I don't attack in with all I've got,
it doesn't feel good!
Why you...
Now, now, Mizoguchi-kun...
He'll eventually correct
what he has to correct.
Right...
So about him being pretty smart...
I just thought that he might be!
He doesn't know the bliss of
a feint... What a waste.
Aoba Johsai                                  Karasuno
Makki!
Nice, Nishinoya!
Nice, Makki! Mad Dog-chan!
It's the guy who hits from the side again.
I'm going to stop him this time!
All right!
We're saved.
Having three blockers on
you and then trying to hit
as hard as you can on a narrow
course is pretty risky.
That attack that seems to be
powerful, but unreliable...
Since he didn't start in this match,
that #16 just might be a double-edged sword.
That #16's spike...
It's all shwing! Whoosh!
It's so cool!
Right? Right?
Of course, Mad Dog-chan is a strong jumper,
as well as unbelievable dorsal
and abdominal muscles...
He goes in tight and lets loose!
It's intense, right?
If he gets through a block,
the ball won't be easy to pick up.
He finally got one in.
Oikawa used him well.
If it were me, I would have
passed to someone else.
All right!
Tenacity and boldness.
You can't use the mad dog if you're scared.
Kyotani, nice serve!
Out!
All right!
His serve is quite dynamic, too.
Nice call!
Aoba Johsai                                Karasuno
One step forward, one step back.
It's basically a stalemate.
Yeah. That #16 can score a lot,
but makes just as many mistakes.
All right!
Iwaizumi-san, nice serve!
Cover! Cover!
Makki, get the last!
Got it!
One more! One more!
The receive is off!
It's coming to the left!
It's on purpose.
Mad Dog! His timing's even faster now.
Second tempo!
We're well aware that he's
a double-edged sword.
That's why we put him in!
All right!
Great, great, Kentaro! Push it,
push it, Kentaro! One more time!
That's a crazy angle.
Tearing off a block with your own hands
is definitely bliss only a setter knows.
Get on it!
Nice receive!
Center!
Aoba Johsai                 Karasuno
All right!
Shoyo, nice serve!
Hinata, give it all you've got!
Again, I'm rotated to the back
without getting a single spike in...
Got it!
Nice receive!
All right! Here we go!
Hinata's back attack!
My first back attack!
All right!
Did you think now was your
opportunity to use that?
I did, too.
Keep calm, keep calm, keep calm...
My back attack debut...
I thought they could break it, too.
If they don't start catching up,
this'll get ugly.
Ah!
Ah?!
Sugawara got called to the bench?
They're changing setters again?
Kageyama doesn't seem to be doing bad.
What happened now was just due
to Oikawa being intense...
Actually, I don't think they're
switching out Kageyama.
We're not going to let you just take it.
We're going to do everything we can.
Haikyu!!
Is Sugawara-san switching with someone?
It's a strategic player trade.
Don't make it sound so complicated.
Come on, college student.
When someone's not doing
well or someone gets hurt,
there are times where a pinch server
or a one-point blocker goes in, right?
The latter is a strategic player trade.
All right!
Aoba Johsai                                Karasuno
Iwaizumi, nice kill!
In the last Seijoh match,
they were cornered and ended up
being forced to switch, but...
This time, it's most likely
for them to get the win.
#16 is an unknown element, and dealing
with Seijoh has gotten even more difficult.
But we're not going to just
let them take the game.
Yes, but before that...
Oikawa-san, nice serve!
Oh, here it comes.
That's a nice serve toss.
All right!
It's like getting slapped
in the face really hard
and coming back to reality.
Neither of us can let the other win,
and we've both trained to win.
It all makes sense.
It's to be expected, but the reality
is still so terrifying.
Aoba Johsai                                Karasuno
One more, nice serve!
Front!
Damn it! I held back too much!
Nice receive, Nishinoya!
Left!
Tanaka-san!
Three blockers!
All right!
Ryu! Well done!
Ah, here it comes.
The switch.
All right! We're gonna catch up.
Yeah!
Suga, we need that nice serve!
Yup.
Bring it!
Suga-san, nice serve!
Serving right after switching in
sure is nerve wracking.
But there's only one place to aim for.
Kyotani!
That was good!
Now their #16 was late in attacking.
All right!
A break!
Aoba Johsai                               Karasuno
Suga-san! One more, nice serve!
Again...
Kyotani is a wing spiker,
but he's the type who goes after
quicks one after another.
They're getting Kyotani to move on the
serves so he can't go after the spikes.
Karasuno's #2 has hit on an annoying tactic.
Daichi-san, nice receive!
All right!
Yes!
Kageyama pulled back from an attack?
Five Karasuno spikers?!
All right!
N-Nice kill...
Damn it. Kageyama's straight is awesome!
Is this what you call two setters?
Even more jargon...
Then...
Strategic one point two setters!
Right?
That's too long.
All right! One more point!
Aoba Johsai            Karasuno
All right!
Switching players now?
They're in a good spot.
All of the third-years are good at receiving.
I see...
Net
Server
Volleyball has a rotation system, and
the players' positions are always changing.
The front line and backline have different jobs,
so each rotation has a specialty.
And apparently...
Net
Server
The rotation when Tsukishima is serving,
is weak for both defense and offense.
There are only two spikers in front,
and Tsukishima can't block from the back.
Considering their rotation,
it's quite a feat that they were
able to keep getting points.
Aoba Johsai
Well, what's it going to be?
How about we make them miss?
Yeah.
Suga-san! One more! Nice serve!
They're going after Kyotani again!
Got it!
Nice, Makki!
As usual, they figure thinks out quickly.
All right!
Suga-san, nice!
Thanks.
Damn it. I wanted to take it to a tie.
Aoba Johsai                     Karasuno
Tanaka-san!
Yeah!
Kageyama, nice serve!
Iwa-chan!
He picked it up!
Watacchi!
Right!
All right!
How do I put this?
They're forcing #16 to do all their attacks.
Yeah.
Maybe they're trying to get
all the attention on #16
and then hand it off to someone else.
No matter how many balls go to the Mad Dog,
I'm not gonna be tricked anymore!
Tanaka-san!
Got it!
Nice, Makki!
I know why we put Kyotani in...
It's for a little extra punch power.
For a bit more offense.
Mad Dog-chan!
If we don't use him to his
fullest, we're in trouble!
All right!
Damn it...
Here they come, here they come!
Hey, we're in a good spot.
They managed to get into the 20's.
Even if they lose this set,
Karasuno won the first set.
As long as they get the
next one, they'll be fine.
No...
They need to do whatever
they can to win this set.
We're gonna finish this!
If they don't, I have a
bad feeling about the outcome.
Kidaichi! One more! Nice serve!
Front!
S-Sorry!
You're thinking about your aim too much.
Here we go!
Tanaka, nice serve!
Nice receive!
All right!
Trying not to think about something
is the same as thinking about it.
Aoba Johsai                                            Karasuno
Kyotani, nice serve!
Bring it!
All right!
The double-edged sword...
Putting in #16 was sink-or-swim
bet for Seijoh,
but I thought they had
already used him successfully.
Sensei!
Yes!
All right!
Again? So quick!
Now Karasuno's used up
all of their time outs.
With #16 as their new weapon,
they were able to score
point after point in the chaos,
and use #16's abilities to the
fullest during most of this set.
Kyotani is a slow-starter
who requires a lot of support.
But, once he gets started, he's strong.
This isn't good.
When a new set starts, it tends to mimic
the end of the previous set,
and the match as a whole.
At this rate, Seijoh definitely
has the upper hand.
Let's bring it in! Karasuno, fight!
Do whatever you can to just
take this set and win it!
Yeah!
Kyotani, one more! Nice serve!
Let's get this one!
Yeah!
Oh, shut up already. I know.
Please let me go in.
Your engine's starting to get
warmed up, Mad Dog-chan.
Let's finish this!
Kyotani, we're gonna take this set.
Right.
Why do you only answer Iwa-chan?!
I'm not gonna give you any more tosses!
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"The Former Coward's Fight."
Episode 22: "The Former Coward's Fight"