Helpful Advice from
Golubaeser Asako
Helpful Advice from Golubaeser Asako!
Cultural festival!
Cultural Festival
Today was the cultural festival
Our class did grate
It was worth all the practice!
There was a party afterwads!
Zombie House of Terror
Cultural Festival
Today was the cultural festival
Our class did grate
It was worth all the practice!
There was a party afterwads!
But I pickd the wrong song to sing
and looked dumb (lol)
Slaughter!  Kill 'em all!
It was worth all the practice!
There was a party afterwads!
But I pickd the wrong song to sing
and looked dumb (lol)
Ooh, but something wonderful happened today!
My best friend Mitty finally called me her friend. I don't think I'll get any sleep
tonite after everything that happened
Friends are nice...
Good job the other day.
I noticed a lot of typos.
And what does the "Golubaeser"
in your blog title mean?
Mizutani
All or Nothing
I have to face myself.
If these feelings won't go away,
I need to stop running.
Yo.
You're awake, Shizuku?
What are you doing here?
Natsume and Sasayan want
to study together,
so I came here to get you.
You need to buy a cell phone.
No, that's not what I meant...
This would be considered
breaking and entering.
I tried to enter through the front door,
but your dad was surprised 'cause he
didn't know school was off today.
Why would Dad still be home?
He told me not to mention
that he was home,
before chasing me off.
Dad.
Why are you still here?
I let myself in.
Went under?!
Y-You're saying that
the store went under?!
When?!
A-Around two weeks ago...
Why didn't you say something sooner?!
I-I thought it would shock you.
No kidding!
Damn, I was too careless!
I relaxed because everything
seemed fine the past few years.
See?  I knew this would happen.
I should have just apologized.
We won't get anywhere like this.
I need to call Mom.
What?!
Really?
You're going to tell Yoshino-san?
Of course.
Hello?
Oh, Mom?
Looks like you're in the
middle of something, Pops.
Uh-huh, this is Shizuku.
Should I leave?
Uh-huh, Dad's store went...
No, it's okay now.
I would rather have an oblivious
kid like you around right now.
Again?
How long does he intend for me to work?
Uh-huh.  Sorry, Mom.
Okay, I'll let him know.
Bye.
"Die, stubby."
That was her response.
Stop!
Not with the same face, voice,
and expression as your mother!
I'll go get changed.
You probably haven't started
cleaning up the store.
Haru.  Sorry, but can
you leave for today?
Shizuku's incredible.
She's completely unflustered.
Well, this is the sixth time...
Sixth time?!
You're hopeless, Pops.
Yeah, I'm a hopeless father...
My wife works, so we manage to get by,
but Shizuku and Takaya must be lonely.
It would be cruelest to
keep your hopes up
when I already know the answer.
She grew up to be an
emotionless person.
She hasn't made any friends.
Well, she liked math problems more
than dolls when she was little.
She has friends now.
Three, if you include me.
What?!  Really?
Dad, I'm ready.
Shizuku, a girl your age
is supposed to take longer to get ready.
Whatever.  Go put some clothes on.
Yes, ma'am.
What?  I have.
I had a girlfriend in middle school.
What?!
Home Run
Is that true, Sasayan-kun?
Yeah, I heard a rumor that she liked me,
so I asked her out.
Yoshida, do you remember Yamase-san?
I think she was in your
class our first year.
E-Everybody looked the same
to me in middle school...
You went to the same middle school as me?
Wait, you just realized that?
That's cold.
So?
Did you do it?
What are you talking about?!
Just kidding.
She dumped me in a heartbeat.
Honestly...
yrotsiH esenapaJ
If you're going to talk about
that stuff, I'm leaving.
Oh, sorry.
I was just joking around.
So?  What about you, Yoshida?
I'm really leaving!
Anyway, Haru-kun...
Did anything happen with Mitty?
yrotsiH esenapaJ
Huh?  Nothing happened.
It sounds like she's thinking
things through right now.
Huh?
She said that she's going to
think about our relationship.
When did she say that?
During the cultural festival.
A month ago?!
Oh, I think I understand...
why they're not making any progress.
Yoshida, how do I do this one?
Because of him.
Huh?
He's satisfied with the way things are,
Like I said, you just do this and this.
so it's all up to Mitty.
Can you explain it in a
way I can understand?
If he doesn't do something,
Mitty will move on without him!
Here's the answer.
I wish everything was this easy.
Hmm?  What do you mean?
I thought that people in love
were supposed to get together,
but I'm not sure if anything's changed.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
What are couples supposed to do?
Well, I can think of one thing to do.
But we're talking about Mizutani-san.
I don't like where this is going...
Huh?
Welcome, Shizuku-chan.
I-I completely forgot.
I told Haru that I was going to
think about our relationship.
Oh!  Mitty!
You're here!
I just stopped in for a minute.
Dad kept telling me I should come.
This is from him.
Yay!  Sweets!
Were they waiting for me?
Haru, do you have a moment?
I brought him outside, but what now?
Was your dad's place okay?
Oh, you mean his store?
My dad called a friend, so it doesn't
look like it'll take too long.
Your dad said that
you were lonely because
your mom had to work.
Is that true?
Yeah, if that's what he thinks,
he should go find a job...
I want to be like Mom.
I want to become a working woman.
But the pot...
Pot?
For holding water.
There was a large one in our yard.
We were going to keep goldfish in it,
but it didn't work out.
I wasn't that interested
in the goldfish,
but I read books and bought food
and was all ready to have one,
so I was sort of disappointed.
I concluded that I was disappointed
because I built up my expectations.
Huh?
Was I lonely then?
Okay, I have something good for you.
Huh?
Come with me.
Stupid.
You can't feel lonely if
there's no one else around.
Haru.
Stop!  I don't need any crayfish!
What?  But there's a
huge one around here.
I wasn't saying that I wanted
to keep a pet in the pot!
You'll change your
mind once you see it.
Public Library
Excuse me.
I'm looking for this book.
It's on the second floor in the E area,
towards the back on the right side.
Would you like me to show you the way?
No, that won't be necessary.
Thank you.
Um, the stairs are the other way.
Thanks.
That student's asked the
same question five times...
This is a pain.
Why are they assigning reports that
require materials you can't
find in a book store?
Oh?
I found it.  A miracle.
Huh?
Yamaken-kun.
Are you looking for something?
I need a reference on economic policies.
Modern economics?
Do you have to write a report?
I would recommend this book
on economic indicators.
Thanks.
I wanted to see you.
What's wrong with her?
Is she interested in me?
On the last mock exam,
you beat me in English,
but I had the highest overall score.
Like I give a damn!
Now look here, Mizutani-san...
No offense, but I'm not
trying to compete with you.
Is there any point to studying all the time?
No offense, but I think it's stupid.
Considering how I can fool
around and succeed in life.
That's what you call a life that's not boring?
At least in academics, you
can control the outcome,
whether it's good or bad.
Hmm?  Is that why I like to study?
Haru's not with you today?
Haru?
He's been spending a lot
of time by the river.
Huh?
It's November.
He wants to catch a large
crayfish and give it to me.
I'm pretty sure there aren't
any crayfish in November.
He has the mind of a
kid in grade school.
The Japanese Economy and Business Cycles
Damn, why are we
talking about him?
Wait, was I the one who brought him up?
But that's the only conversation
topic I can think of.
And why do I need to think
of a topic of conversation?
After thinking
about what you said to me,
I decided I needed to face everyone.
I don't remember saying
anything about that.
Besides, why are you telling me this?
Hmm?
Why?
I was impressed by the advice you gave
me during the cultural festival.
Oh, hello?
Yoshida?  Where are you?
Is Mizutani-san with you?
Huh?  The river?
Well?
Yoshida's playing around
by the river by himself.
He said that Mizutani-san
probably went to the library.
What?
They're taking it easy, huh?
Geez, Haru-kun is off
doing weird stuff again.
That's why Mitty...
I happened to be someone
who was easily accessible.
...feels that way!
Whatever.
Let's do our best to prepare for finals.
Yep.
I'm telling you, it's true!
No way!
I heard that Kitano from
Class 2 asked Natsume out.
What?  That's the guy Miki likes.
That's too bad.
This seems to happen a lot.
Natsume might as well only
make friends with boys.
Natsume-san?
What are you doing, Natsume-san?
Hey, look.
Yeah, it's her.
Is that her boyfriend then?
Really?  Is he helping her study?
What's their problem?
Sa-Sasayan-kun...
S-Sorry.
Sorry.  Sorry.
Natsume-san?
This is all my fault...
Sorry.
So like I said...
She hasn't changed.
Oh, it's Natsume-chan.
Didn't expect to run into you here.
What are you doing?
L-Let's go.
Hmm?  What's up?
Aren't you getting on?
No, I'll take a taxi.
Okay, bye.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Do you realize who she is?
What am I doing?
If you can't give up one, learn
to balance both at the same time.
Ah, that makes sense.
Priorities                                Stupid -> Haru
Study (Future)
Electronic Organizer              Can't break free
Family Finances                      What is love?
Why does it have to be all or nothing?
Are you a robot?
And why do I have to help
analyze her state of mind?
You're pretty funny.
J-Just to be clear,
I'm only helping you out of courtesy!
I have no other reason for doing this!
I understand.
Thank you.
Damn it!
Why did it have to be Ha—
The girl who's in love with Haru?
Every time I deal with another person,
I'm reminded how little
control I have over my life.
I have an announcement.
Starting today, your mother
will start working because
your father is a failure.
Have a safe trip.
Oh, hello?  Mom?
I got 100 on the last test,
and the test before that.
Why are you a failure?
No mercy, huh?
Oh, Shizuku.  Would you
like a pet goldfish,
since we didn't get to
go to the festival?
No, I don't need one.
I don't need goldfish anymore.
Why does it have to be all or nothing?
Because...
It's a waste of time to bother
with anything uncertain.
Oh?  You didn't go home yet?
Oh, welcome back.
Well, I just got a call.
Yeah, thanks for the heads-up.
Aren't you cold, Haru-kun?
What?  Welcome back, Mitty!
Uh-huh.
Oh, Shizuku!
Haru, you're still here?
Shimoyanagi-kun and his
buddies just left.
We were hanging out together.
Shimoyanagi-kun?
He must have been scared.
Man, you look like you're having
a lot of fun down there!
Really?
Natsume-san, why are you so hyper?
So did you find any crayfish?
Right, crayfish.
I found one, but it was asleep.
Hiding behind a leaf!
He must have forgotten
his original objective.
But I had lots of fun.
That's nice.
I couldn't find any crayfish,
but I'll find something better
for you, so don't worry.
Okay...  Thanks...
Actually, my brother's using
that pot now for storage.
Why does he care so much about
the things I find meaningless?
In the end, I'm still letting
him build up my expectations.
Oh, excuse me.
Could you pull over?
I'm going to return this.
Then I'll never bother
with her again...
Hey!
Are you going home?
Oh.  Yes.
Oh, I left my bag down there.
We'll go on ahead then.
Okay.
Yo.
Haru.
Give that back to Mizutani-san.
Why do you have something
that belongs to Shizuku?
No reason.
I ran into her at the library today.
Yamaken.
Are you in love with Shizuku?
Is that a problem?
Yep, winter break is coming up.
I can't wait.
You have remedial classes first, right?
Yep.
I've been wondering.
How did you get into this school?
A super parlor trick!
Oh.
Oh, the choose-your-own
method of application.
Huh?  Where's Yoshida?
Stare...
It's still warm.
Huh?  Wait, he left a letter behind?
"I went to school. -Yoshida."
Next Episode
Christmas
Homeless?