Karasuno       Aoba Johsai
Up front!
Slam it down!
All right!
Yes! A break!
Yes, yes, yes! They reversed it!
That's amazing... He hit
that before the attack line?
Because he hit it by snapping his wrist,
the spike wasn't as powerful.
But as long as it gets past the block,
they can't pick the ball up from that angle.
Did Kageyama mean to give that to Hinata?
Push through!
Hinata, nice kill!
Or did he make a mistake?
Shut up.
Hey, that was awesome!
That was right below!
Did you aim for that?!
Hinata was close to the net,
so I made the set close, too.
I'm glad it worked out.
Tobio's genius-like qualities
don't lie in his techniques,
but rather how stupid he is.
Where others would probably hold back,
he goes straight for it.
All right! Let's get one more!
Right!
In both a good and bad way.
When he's concentrating,
he can't see around himself
and doesn't even realize that
no one's keeping up with him.
But...
Tsukishima, one more! Nice serve!
Now an idiot that'll walk in front
of Tobio has appeared.
You put a lot of strength into that!
I just went somewhere there wasn't a blocker.
Their #10 finally made a move.
Yeah... Those two never cease to surprise me.
But...
A volleyball team with
six strong players is stronger.
Come on, bring it!
Let's get this one!
Yeah!
If you understand that, then good.
Fly
Rule the Court
We're going to win!
Haikyu!!
Episode 24: "The Absolute Limit Switch"
Tsukishima, nice serve!
Got it!
Nice receive!
That attack...
Left!
It was just luck.
I'm going to crush it before...
...it matures!
All right!
All right! We're tied!
Go for it!
All right!
Tanaka-san, nice kill!
Ryu!
Yeah!
All right!
Matsukawa-senpai, fight!
We're counting on you!
Yeah!
A pinch server, huh?
Yahaba, get one for us.
They're probably strengthening
their defense, too.
Right!
Yahaba, nice serve!
With everything I have...
Asahi!
Sorry!
Cover! Cover!
Tanaka-san!
Two blockers!
Yahaba!
Right!
Kyotani!
Crap! It's short!
All right!
Did he just hit with his left hand?!
He's right-handed, right?
Did he just manage to do that on the spot?
The ability to fully control his body, huh...
Karasuno       Aoba Johsai
A break...
If they get into the 20s first,
it's going to be rough.
Don't let them get a bigger lead!
Yeah!
Nice receive!
All right!
You little brat...
Kyotani...
We're counting on you!
Yeah!
Good, good. We've caught up.
Yeah, that's some concentration...
Tanaka, nice serve!
These guys never cease to surprise me.
Got it!
They're coming on the right! Right!
#16! #16!
Stop them!
All right!
Nice one-touch!
Yes!
Connect! Connect!
It's off! Look out on the left!
Get back!
Nice receive!
Wow...
One more! One more!
Cover!
Left!
Damn it!
All right!
Now we're in the 20s!
Karasuno            Aoba Johsai
They got there first.
We don't have to panic.
It's still just one point.
All right!
We're counting on you!
There he is!
The pinch server who got five points
in a row in the second set.
We're counting on you, Yamaguchi!
Stay calm!
Give it your all!
Right!
Go!
Tadashi!
Nice serve!
Yamaguchi-kun! Do that thing again!
Yamaguchi.
Get a nice serve in.
Yeah.
Karasuno       Aoba Johsai
Nice serve!
Out.
No...
This time it went long?!
Yay!
Yeah!
What?!
He actually connected with it!
Watari, get the last!
Right.
Chance ball!
A synchronized attack!
Yeah!
Damn, his switch is totally turned on.
Nice receive, Iwa-chan.
Iwaizumi-san, nice!
Wow...
Makki!
A feint!
Damn it all!
Yes! We managed to limit #12 to one serve.
All right!
Nice kill!
Yeah!
When I was a kid, I only did
spikes because they were fun,
but now I can truly say...
I'm glad I learned the bliss of
receiving an opponent's perfect hit.
Yamaguchi, don't mind!
But seriously, is that the same
guy from the Inter-High prelims?
Hanamaki, nice serve!
That one couldn't be helped.
The opponent was too good.
Don't mind.
Nice receive, Tanaka-san!
Right.
Yamaguchi!
That was a great serve.
Every hit is really heavy.
Yeah...
They're just gonna have to stay on the ball
and keep stacking up one point at a time...
That's the only path they have.
Karasuno             Aoba Johsai
All right!
Neither side is backing down.
If they get another deuce, do they have to
keep playing until they get two points ahead?
No...
They're not gonna have time
to think about that.
Bring it!
Seriously?
All right!
Great, great, Toru! Push it,
push it, Toru! One more time!
Nice serve!
What is this?
An amazing serve like that right now?
Is he some kind of monster?
One more!
Karasuno                Aoba Johsai
All right!
Seijoh's at match point.
It's that again...
We're just gonna have to pick it up.
Yeah.
Switch it up! Switch it up!
Their mental strength is amazing.
They should be under quite a
bit of pressure right now...
If we manage to touch it,
we can make it work!
We're not gonna lose!
Yeah!
Aoba Johsai
Give it your all!
But of course.
Well, it's time...
You have to get it, no matter what!
Yeah!
All right!
They cut off Oikawa's serves!
Seijoh's still at match point, though.
Karasuno             Aoba Johsai
The wall for this next point is high.
Whoa, Karasuno loses if they
give up another point,
but they're switching out their libero?
Sensei.
Right.
Yeah!
This is the last battle.
Haikyu!!
Yeah!
This is the last battle.
Ooh, now they're going for a
strategic one-point six-two!
Yeah!
If they can't do a break, they're done.
We're counting on you!
Yeah!
Do what you did in the second set!
Suga-san, give us a nice serve!
Yeah!
How is able to concentrate so intensely
towards the end of the match?
Though it's just his concentration!
Huh? Why are you picking
a fight with Hinata?!
We're going to finish it with this one.
Yeah!
Nice serve!
Concentrate on the one!
If I miss this serve, everything is over.
Nice serve!
Go!
Nice serve! Get one!
If we don't stop the opponent's attack,
everything is over.
Here I go!
Is it in or out?
Is it going to be me or Iwaizumi-san?!
Damn, they picked it up!
But the ace is out.
Center!
Yeah!
You stopped it!
Hinata!
Shoyo!
Well, he is the middle blocker.
He's supposed to be able to block.
I feel bad, really!
Great job taking that, Kageyama.
Karasuno               Aoba Johsai
Karasuno caught up!
It's a deuce!
Sorry.
Don't mind!
Next, next!
Rather than going to stop it,
it was more like he went to jump
at the ball, no matter what.
Every time, I'm astonished at
the shrimp's quick response.
Suga-san, one more!
Here I go.
Front, front!
Damn it!
Whoa, that was close!
That barely made it to the front!
He broke it!
This time it's Iwaizumi who was off balance.
He may be Mr. Refreshing,
Center!
but his serves aren't refreshing at all!
Front, front, front!
Fall!
I'll get it!
Yes, yes!
The first touch was Mr. Refreshing...
Now they won't be able
to do that last attack!
Go!
Even if you can't stop it, touch it!
Bring it to me!
You little brats!
Ka...
Kageyama!
I know...
But...
I won't lose!
Karasuno       Aoba Johsai
Just one more point.
You're awesome, Tobio!
Man, when Sugawara got the first touch,
I didn't think Kageyama would attack...
Yeah, but everyone's got the idea
that when Sugawara's in the game,
something's gonna happen.
We just start thinking that way.
Damn, that pisses me off!
That's definitely Oikawa's junior.
He's got a setter's disposition,
staying confident in a situation like that.
Seijoh!
Well, yeah...
I'd love some of that.
Seijoh!
Have you found the
limits of your abilities?
Even though your technique, body,
and mentality aren't complete?
People who are naturally better than you
have been different from you
ever since they were born.
It's impossible to turn that around,
no matter how hard you work,
how well you strategize,
or who your teammates are.
You can complain about that
once you've actually done
everything you possibly can.
Rather than despairing and giving up
because you're not a genius,
believe that your strength
is not limited to this,
and to continue on the path
straight ahead of you...
It may be harsh to say so, but...
Today might be the day to grasp the
chance to let your talent bloom.
Maybe tomorrow, the day after,
or next year...
Maybe even when you're thirty.
I'm not sure if physique
has anything to do with it,
but if you think it'll never come,
it probably never will.
Oikawa-san's seems different
lately, doesn't he?
Rule the Court
Go, go, go, go, go, go, Seijoh!
Push it, push it, push it,
push it, push it, Seijoh!
Push it, push it, Karasuno!
Go, go, Karasuno!
Put everything you've got into it! Do it!
Hey, say it together!
If something like that comes up
front again, I'll get it.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Right!
Don't let your guard down.
They might drop it over here again.
Keep your eye on the ball.
Right!
Make sure you aim for the target!
I know. If I half-ass it,
it'll get hit immediately.
Make sure you at least
touch it when you block.
Yeah!
Let's take this back!
Let's get this one!
Yeah!
Karasuno        Aoba Johsai
Suga-san, nice serve!
The front!
Iwaizumi-san!
All right! He was off balance!
Damn it!
Ryu!
Go!
Finish it now!
Hanamaki-san!
They got it!
But...
It's off!
We're counting on you, Oikawa!
Chance ball!
A super-long
and fast set up from outside the court...
#4's coming in!
Talent is something you make bloom.
Instinct is something you polish!
Right on!
Damn it!
Yeah!
Get the last!
Six who are strong are stronger!
Connect!
Chance ball!
Like hell...
He's gonna hit it from there?!
...you'll get that chance!
Kyotani, nice!
Hit it, Kageyama!
Damn it. How lame.
Give it to me!
Come on.
Come at me with your ultimate weapon,
Tobio!
They read the set up!
All...
...right!
Karasuno             Aoba Johsai
We won! We won!
Shimada... Are you actually crying?
N-No... My contact lens just shifted.
You... wear glasses...
Episode 25 "Declaration of War"
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Declaration of War."