The Second Plate
Episode 4
Regarding the fourth match
in the Autumn Elections
between Candidate Takumi Aldini
and Candidate Mimasaka Subaru,
it will be a Shokugeki.
Shokugeki
A Shokugeki in the middle
of the Autumn Elections?!
Is that even allowed?
There is no question that
the conditions have been met.
The administration has deemed
this an official Shokugeki!
I see.
It knows no restrictions,
be it time or place...
Such is the nature of the Shokugeki!
So far, five judges have made a joint
decision on the outcome in this tournament,
Takumi Aldini     Mimasaka Subaru
but an exception was made for this match,
so each judge will cast one vote.
The match will thus follow
the Shokugeki format.
A Shokugeki.
The candidates will now enter the arena!
Wow.
Bro...
It must be hard, having an
incompetent younger brother.
Pick it up.
Wha?
I'll teach you proper manners,
seeing as you lack any.
If you pick that up, it means you'll
have accepted the challenge.
This is how we conduct duels—the duello.
Italians always seek
vengeance after humiliation.
If I win, I'll have you grovel
and apologize, right here,
to the mezzaluna you've tainted,
and to my brother!
The Pursuer
Hey!
Yukihira!
Megumi!
Where've you been? Jeez!
W-W-Well, we were with Takumi-kun and
Mimasaka-kun until just a short while ago,
but they didn't say anything
about a Shokugeki.
Mimasaka intended to make this into
a Shokugeki from the very start.
That's the kind of guy he is.
He does exhaustive research
on the students he targets,
then uses any means necessary,
be it provocation or intimidation,
to drag them into a face-off.
He has already won ninety-nine
Shokugekis in that manner.
Ninety-nine...
Round 4
Dessert
The theme is dessert!
Let the cooking begin!
Their ingredients...
They're both exactly the same!
I have brought documentation of the ingredients
Mimasaka Subaru has used in previous battles.
It lists ingredients used by both sides.
Mimasaka Subaru Shokugeki History
Date     Candidate & Dish     Candidate & Dish     Victor
Mimasaka Subaru   Sekiguchi Yuga     Mimasaka Subaru
Ma Po Tofu             Ma Po Tofu
Mimasaka Subaru
Duck Steak
Zaitsu Kensuke
Mimasaka Subaru
Tuna Sushi
Hinuma Emi
Mimasaka Subaru
Celery Root Fricassee
Mikami Shunta
What?!
He's always won by serving the
exact same dish as his opponents'!
Semifreddo.
That's what you and I are going to make.
Semifreddo is as cold
in temperature as ice cream,
and as soft in texture as cake.
This semifreddo will have
a topping of scattered pralines,
an "ice cream" layer
with meringue and heavy cream,
and a sponge cake layer.
A triple-layer type.
Did I get that right?
Hmph.
So that's what you got out of stalking me.
You think you can win
if you have the same recipe?
Never underestimate an Aldini!
Mimasaka plays around with
the Shokugeki system as his toy.
He makes his opponents wager the most
important thing to a chef: their tools.
By robbing them of those,
he obliterates their pride.
Does he think of himself as Musashibo Benkei?
Talk about poor taste.
One story has it that he took a
cherished knife that'd belonged
to the opponent's late mother,
and did it while laughing maniacally.
That means Takumi-kun
put his mezzaluna on the line...
Th-There's nothing to worry about!
Just look at him.
He's not showing any hesitation!
Yeah! His movements are meticulous!
If you screw up measurements in any way
when making sweets, the taste is ruined.
That's why you need
a lot of attention to detail.
A hulk like Mimasaka wouldn't—
What?!
H-He's very meticulous.
It's almost as though he is...
...a girl doing embroidery!
Hasta la vista, Aldini.
This is where I'll start adding twists!
Takumi-kun's beating the egg yolks
and egg whites together,
but Mimasaka-kun's beating them
separately when making the batter.
Mimasaka Subaru conducts an
exhaustive investigation of his opponents.
He gathers any and all information
about recipes they are testing
to predict what his opponent
will attempt to make.
He then adjusts his version of the dish to
raise himself one step above his opponent.
A "pâte à génoise" cake, made by
beating the yolk and whites together,
has a moist, delicate crumb.
In comparison, a "pâte à biscuit" cake,
made by beating them separately,
has a very airy crumb,
so it will absorb a lot of syrup,
resulting in great texture.
My version will be able to maximize
the benefits of this divine syrup.
You chose a smooth, gentle texture.
That's the choice you've always made,
even when you were in Italy.
But when these two are compared,
mine will have a stronger flavor.
So by adding such twists in choice areas,
he decreases his probability of losing
until it's close to zero.
So you're making the syrup next, right?
With this liquor?
He even has the limoncello!
It's Italian liquor made from lemons.
Rum and amaretto are
typically used in the syrup,
but he's using the
same ingredient, even here.
He knows about the limoncello panna cotta.
Your family restaurant, Trattoria Aldini,
has a specialty dish
that makes heavy use of this.
That's why I figured
you'd use this in the semifreddo.
Does he really see right through me?
I've added other twists, too.
My custard will have mascarpone in addition
to heavy cream, for added richness.
It's the same thing you did with the
curry pasta you made in the prelims.
How does it feel to be outpaced by
someone using your own special skill?
Director!
Should such a match even be allowed?
In a Shokugeki, the food is everything.
There is no reason to remonstrate
Mimasaka Subaru for his behavior.
Mimasaka Subaru only cares about winning.
That is why he goes
"right down to the last detail."
He profiles his opponents
in order to become them.
Emotional guys like you
make the easiest opponents.
You may look cool and calm on the outside,
but you are passionate about your cooking.
You have much affection
and pride for your homeland,
and that will always show
in your dishes.
I'm glad you're exactly
as I made you out to be.
He continues to observe his opponent,
and exposes who they are.
Mimasaka Subaru is the King of Stalkers!
He's even more dangerous than I thought!
Takumi has to come up with a new twist, too!
But does he even have time for that?
Is he just gonna lose?
Bro has flexibility; he got that
from working in the kitchen.
An Italian wouldn't lose a dolce match!
My intended recipe is
totally known to him...
What should I do?
Make something completely new from scratch?
No, I don't have time for that.
Is there something I can do?
Is there nothing I can do?
Once I put the batter in the oven,
I can't add any twists to it.
Should I add chopped lemons
to improve the fragrance?
No, that would ruin the important texture.
Hey, don't you have to start baking soon
if you want to finish in time?
Takumi put his batter in the oven, too!
Now he can only make alterations
to the toppings and the sauce.
But Takumicchi doesn't have any
ingredients he can use to add a twist!
I have limited time.
I have to proceed with the dish.
I'm being constrained by
the very tracks I laid down!
We now have less than thirty minutes left.
Both of them are done with baking!
Huh?
Is Mimasaka's cake darker than Aldini's?
You're right!
Why?
Biscuit joconde.
Most of the flour has been
replaced by almond flour.
It results in a more fragrant, rich sponge.
Another twist!
Hah. The greater their pride,
the greater their paralysis when
they realize they're in a crisis.
They're afraid to serve a dish
they know will lose.
You're the same way, aren't you, Aldini?
If I lose now...
Why did I even come here to Japan?
Bro!
Don't look like that, Little Brother.
Remember the Aldini kitchen.
The din and clamor...
Have faith in what you learned there!
Let's show them.
With this match, I'll surpass
the person I've been until now...
...and the recipes I've made until now!
All right, it's done.
So beautiful!
Is this the semifreddo that will
surpass Takumi Aldini's dish?
Hmm...
The praline is fragrant with almonds.
The ice cream-like layer
is half-thawed frozen cream.
All very delicate work.
Hmph!
Cobbling together various
surface inspirations!
I doubt the flavors
will form a cohesive whole!
Well, let's give it a taste.
The difference in textures
created by the three layers!
I can tell just by inserting
a spoon into the dish!
The fresh sweetness of the
lemons fills my mouth,
and the fragrant almonds
entertain my sense of smell!
The flavors have been melded together
without any off flavors—impressive!
How sweet and mellow—
my inner girlishness is coming out.
I went with biscuit joconde because it pairs perfectly with praline.
You can detect the fragrance and
richness of almonds in the sponge—
Quiet!
Do you have no principles as a chef?
I struggle to understand what you mean.
"Down to the last detail." That is my creed.
I did not spare any effort in analyzing
my opponent's capabilities
and planning my victory.
What's so wrong about that?
I don't want to acknowledge him.
I don't want to!
But I can't resist the allure.
What a despicable guy...
Despicable... Despicable...
Despicable... Despicable... Despicable...!
Innocence * Contrast
Lyrics: Fuda Yuto
I hate him! He's so cool!
But his smile makes my heart spin.
Still, I have to ask.
Please step on the love accelerator
with your desserts...
Despicable... Despicable...
Despicable...
I turned into a girl without
even thinking about it...
It's the ultimate dessert that feels like
an amplification of Aldini's hotness.
How can he hope to win now?
Oh?
What, you're going to serve them your dish?
Don't underestimate me.
I'm a professional.
No matter what happens,
we serve food to our customers.
That dish...
It's different from the semifreddo
I saw Bro testing.
You're right.
There's a very thin layer between
the cream and sponge layers!
A fourth layer!
Please...
...come!
How vivid!
It's a Mediterranean breeze!
I've eaten many semifreddos.
But this is different from all of them!
Where is this overwhelming
lemon flavor coming from?
What is this golden layer?!
That is lemon curd,
a condiment with roots in England.
Lemon curd!
Some types are procured for use
by the British royal family.
It has a very long history.
This elegant paste is fragrant with
the sweet-sour flavor of lemons.
It melts in your mouth with
the fine génoise sponge.
What a light mouthfeel!
The grainy biscuit joconde
could never be this soft!
Lemon curd is made from eggs, sugar,
lemon juice, lemon zest, and butter.
But you hardly had any butter left!
I used this as a substitute.
Olive oil.
And it's not just any olive oil.
That's a very Italian creativity.
Indeed, the refreshing fragrance of olives
pairs well with the lemons!
I fell behind with regard
to the semifreddo's sponge.
My sponge would not measure up
to biscuit joconde's impact.
I felt I should hedge my bets on
the lemon flavor to win this match.
I thought that if I could strengthen
the lemon's fresh flavor
and mellow depth of flavor
by using lemon curd,
my semifreddo would not
pale in comparison to his!
You had an idea to improvise
using something from England!
And yet you have succeeded in retaining
the dish's Italian roots—your own colors!
In other words,
this is a new condiment
that should be called Lemon Curd Italiano!
He created a new taste
under such adverse circumstances.
Takumi. Isami.
Take this with you when you leave for Japan.
It's our family's homemade olive oil.
It'll protect you, I'm sure of it.
The Aldini name protected him.
When I had the flash of inspiration,
I think I heard a sound...
The sound of changing tracks!
The sound of my previous recipes
being surpassed!
Oizumi-dono.
You seem to have noticed, as well.
Director!
Hey... What's wrong?
What's so funny?
"What's so funny"?
Don't make me sad!
I know everything about you!
Right?
You can tell when you
compare the two, can't you?
You can tell how deep
my semifreddo's flavor is!
I added a secret ingredient, after all!
Preserved lemons.
A traditional Moroccan condiment
made by salting whole lemons
for several weeks!
It is an all-powerful
condiment that strengthens
acidity, saltiness, bitterness,
astringency, and mildness.
I added chopped preserved lemons and their
brine to the sponge, praline, and sauce.
The faint bitterness is enhancing
the semifreddo's sweetness.
See, I "trusted" you.
I believed that you would draw on the
flexibility you'd developed in the kitchen,
refuse to give up,
and add one last twist!
And you always have your good luck charm,
the olive oil, close at hand!
All I had to do was to
trace your thought processes.
The only possible conclusion was that
you'd go for an Italian-style lemon curd!
You're adorable!
Dancing on my palm!
You didn't even know I saw right through you!
It's such a slim margin!
So minor that you wouldn't
notice the difference
unless you were comparing them directly.
And yet...!
You are driven by two things:
your bond with your brother, Isami,
and your rematch with Yukihira Soma.
How does it feel to have both
taken from you at the same time?
Diablo...
Mimasaka Subaru      Mimasaka Subaru
The judges are in unilateral agreement!
This is my memorable 100th win.
I'll be taking this.
Mimasaka Subaru
The victor of Round 4
is Candidate Mimasaka Subaru!
With the conclusion of this round,
Yukihira Soma    Kurokiba Ryo    Hayama Akira    Mimasaka Subaru
the first match of the
Autumn Elections is complete!
The second match will occur a week from now.
Just like the first match,
cards will be drawn to determine
the pairings of the second match,
and you will be notified about
the results by the end of the day.
That is all!
The
43rd
Autumn
Elections
I'm so annoyed!
What's with that stalker?!
I get how you feel,
so don't take it out on me.
Takumi-kun must be in shock...
I want to cheer him up,
but I don't even know what to say.
Oh... Soma-kun?
I'm going back.
Huh?
Hey, Yukihira!
Are you sure you didn't
need to talk to Takumi?
Hey.
Mimasaka?!
Why are you in Yukihira's room?!
A spare key.
What do you want?
Oh, I just had something I wanted to report.
Okay, hang on.
I'll make some tea.
Oh, Mimasaka, did you eat dinner?
I have some leftover beef stew. Want some?
Sure, thanks.
He should just throw a guy like that out!
Yukihira's hosting him
like he's just any other guy.
About the second match's pairing,
it was just finalized.
Oh?
The match will be between
Kurokiba and Hayama,
Yukihira Soma  Mimasaka Subaru  Hayama Akira  Kurokiba Ryo
and you and me, Yukihira.
Huh.
You came all the way here
just to tell me that?
You know where I'm going with this, right?
Let's do a Shokugeki!
The kitchen knife you're always using...
If I win, I'll take that.
In return, if you win, I'll give you this.
Yukihira Soma, I know what
really gets a rise out of you.
You would never forgive an unjust humiliation
of anyone you've come to respect.
That poor Italian... how pathetic.
He suffered such a major defeat
before he could face you!
His pride and future
as a chef are in tatters!
Well?
Come on, get angry!
Your precious friend is being ridiculed.
Well... sure, it's disappointing.
But Takumi isn't the kind of guy
who'd be ruined by something like this.
One more thing.
You're the one who's pathetic, Mimasaka.
What did you say?
I have a pretty high opinion
of your skills, you know?
Recreating a dish by someone like Takumi
would require quite a lot of skill.
But why are you bothering with
a pointless match like that?
Aldini suffered crushing defeat
in a "pointless" match.
As a chef, I completely surpass—
You do not.
You just took advantage of Takumi's efforts.
A dish can shine because of the process
of going through multiple trials and errors.
You're pathetic.
You don't know the true joy of cooking.
That's why you can laugh
about a match like that.
You're robbing people's pride
through a superficial victory.
I can't respect you as a chef for that.
I'll accept your challenge to a Shokugeki.
But what I want isn't just the mezzaluna.
I want the 99 other tools
you've taken until now, too.
Huh?
Don't be ridiculous.
That's way too much!
What can you give me that's worth
my risking a hundred tools?
Fine, I'll quit being a chef if I lose.
I'll quit being a chef.
Food
Wars
The Second Plate
Next Episode: The Secret in the First Bite
Next episode: "The Secret in the First Bite."