Using the power of Lífþrasir is
essentially shaving off
a part of his life.
When he runs out of energy, he will die.
Saito will die?
I've gotten pretty good at this, huh?
Yeah, you're not too bad.
I don't want him to die.
Please, don't let anything
actually threaten the world...
The Awakening of Calamity
Saito, Miss Vallière, I'm coming in.
I know you were up very late
last night, but you should
still get up soon...
Good morning, Siesta.
Miss Vallière, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Something happened, didn't it?
I told you, it's nothing.
I think it's time you realized
that you're a terrible liar.
Well, to be honest, Saito is...
Excuse me.
Is Miss Vallière awake?
I am.
Queen Henrietta has summoned you.
I need Miss Vallière, Miss Westwood,
and Saito to come with me at once.
What's going on?
We'll be right there!
Excuse us.
Thank you for coming, Saito,
Louise, and Tiffania.
Is something wrong?
His Holiness sent a messenger
when he returned
to Romalia after the
coronation ceremony.
The message was that he wishes
the three of you to go to
Romalia as soon as possible.
To Romalia?
But why?
It seems
that a village at the foot
of the Fire Dragon mountains
was destroyed overnight.
What happened?
I'm not certain, only that
something terrible has happened.
If His Holiness thinks your
presence is necessary,
it might mean that...
You don't have to look so worried.
But, Saito...
Let's just go and see for ourselves.
It's not like we can refuse
His Holiness, anyway.
That's true, but...
Then I'm counting on you, Saito.
Julio will come meet you
once you're near Aquileia's border.
Yes, Your Highness.
I asked Queen Charlotte to
aid you with a dragon, so...
Sorry I'm late!
When my sister heard about this,
she was worried, too.
That's why I'm going to do you a favor
and carry you to Romalia!
Really? Thanks!
You should consider yourself
lucky that a proud
rhyme dragon is doing this for you.
Yes, we know.
Please be careful.
We will. Please keep
an eye on things here.
Oh, Miss Vallière.
I don't know what exactly is happening,
but I'm sure everything will be fine.
Once you're back in des Ornières,
we can eat, take baths and
fight over the beds again.
And then we'll all grow old together!
If you believe it, it will happen.
Siesta...
So please, come home quickly.
Saito, Miss Westwood, and you.
Okay. We will.
Good luck!
Take care!
I'm sure they'll be fine.
I wonder where Julio is.
Huh?
Is that the sunset?
No... Hurry, please!
What's going on?
The city, it's...
But that's impossible!
It's Aquileia!
There's someone down there!
We have to help them!
Hey, pal, they're
coming from the right!
Damn you! Go away!
Damn it!
Looks like they're not
in their right minds.
What?
What's that?
Saito, fly up!
Sylphid!
What is going on here?
Saito, stay calm.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Julio!
What's happening?
I'll explain later.
Right now, we've got
to get away from here.
Unfortunately, it's too late...
Julio, what's with those dragons?
All the dragons in this
region went insane.
I've managed to keep this one
under control using my Windalfr powers.
You don't have to worry about Sylphid.
Rhyme dragons are not
like ordinary dragons.
But why on earth did this happen?
The noxious gases coming out
of his body are causing this.
His?
What is that?
It's the legendary dragon of old...
The Ancient Dragon.
As you all know,
the Ancient Dragon has
suddenly appeared and
it has leveled Aquileia.
And now that monster is headed
towards the sacred city of Romalia.
Do not be afraid.
If we use all our strength,
we can certainly defeat it.
Before the Ancient Dragon
reaches our city,
we will strike at the Valley of Oltia.
You holy knights blessed by the
strength of our founder Brimir,
now is the time to
show us your strength.
Do not let this holy city be defiled.
Protect the innocent people!
Long live His Holiness!
Our founder Brimir will protect us!
Let's move out!
Your Holiness,
I have brought them here.
Thank you for coming so quickly.
Your Holiness,
we saw Aquileia burn and there
was nothing we could do...
That monster suddenly appeared
from the Fire Dragon mountains.
We immediately told the
people to evacuate, but...
Your Holiness, could it be
that this is it?
The danger threatening the world
that you were worried about?
I am afraid it might be.
The only thing the
ancient texts say about
the World Crisis is that
it is "a great calamity
that charred the world."
Many scholars, myself included,
have spent much time
studying this subject.
The theory that it is a
giant dragon did exist,
but there was no firm evidence.
However, now there's no doubt.
We must stop that monster at any cost.
This is the time for us Void
Mages to join forces
to prevent more innocent
blood from being spilled.
We have a plan.
Miss Vallière.
Your Explosion spell
is crucial to our plan.
In the end, all will rest on you.
Y-Yes.
However,
according to the reports we have,
the dragon's body is veiled
in a shroud of miasma,
a magic barrier,
that reflects offensive spells.
First we have to negate that.
I can do that with my Dispel spell...
No, I will take care of that part.
We need to preserve your
strength as much as possible.
Miss Westwood,
please cast your Mind Wipe
on the dragon's minions
and protect the holy knights.
Y-Yes! Certainly.
And then, Saito, there is something
I must ask of you as well.
I'd like you utilize...
your Lífþrasir powers.
That's it?
Well, sure!
Wait, Saito!
Think about this first...
What is there to think about?
I want to do everything
in my power to help!
I thank you from the very
bottom of my heart.
Now, let us head to the Oltia Valley.
All right.
Our farsight magic has
revealed that the dragon
is only 30 leagues away!
Don't let your guard down!
But why is the dragon
going for the Holy City?
Who knows, maybe something
is drawing him there.
Your Holiness...
What is it?
Saito isn't going to die
in the battle, right?
I mean by using his Lífþrasir power...
This makes me happy.
When I first met you,
you had nothing but
hatred for the world
and could not love anyone.
That's the kind of boy you were.
Even when you came to live with me,
you still had your
reservations, didn't you?
And now you've become
someone who expresses
concern for a friend.
I truly believe that sending you to the
Magic Academy was a good idea.
You are my pride and joy,
Julio Chesaré.
Your Holiness?
I doubt the power of Lífþrasir
will vanish after
using it once or twice.
However, the more it's used,
the faster his death will approach.
Which is why we must make sure
this plan succeeds on the first try.
Yes, sir.
I guess their plan is to lure
the dragon into the valley
and slow it down by
destroying the cliffs.
Even if it has a magic barrier,
physical attacks might
be able to get through.
Saito...
If only the rocket launcher
I used back then was here.
Listen, Saito!
What?
I don't want you to help His Holiness.
Excuse me?
Do not use your Lífþrasir power.
Don't use it ever again!
But that power can amplify Void magic...
At the expense of your life!
The power of Lífþrasir
can't be replenished.
Once it's used up, the familiar dies!
D-Dies?!
Wh-What are you talking about?
That doesn't make any sense!
His Holiness said so himself,
so I know it must be true!
So I'm really going to die?
I... So that's what Lífþrasir is...
Saito...
Don't worry.
I'll do something about
him with my magic.
I won't let you die!
Tiffa?
What have I done?
This is because I made
Saito into a familiar...
But, Tiffa...
It's all my fault!
I'm so sorry!
Don't falter!
He'll be here soon!
We're ready for you!
We'll show you the power
of the Holy Knights!
Louise, I'm going to do it.
I'm not the only one who
might die in this battle.
I can't allow myself
to cower in fear.
But, Saito...
I am also a knight.
That's why I must protect everyone.
Including you, Louise.
Saito...
Saito, it's almost time. Are you ready?
Yes.
Saito...
Louise, look after Tiffa.
Let's get this over with, all right?
Yeah.
Now!
Keep attacking!
Show no fear! We are holy knights!
It looks like the Mind
Wipe spell worked!
Thank goodness!
Um, Louise, I...
Let's not think about it.
Right now, we just have to believe.
Like Siesta said.
We have to believe we can
all go home together.
Cano Soil Teiwas Isa Unjo
Cebo Ragsjur Dagas!
Wow!
I see. It's Cleansing magic.
Normally it's healing magic,
but for evil beings,
this magic is more
damaging than an attack.
Indeed, this is my Void magic.
Now, Saito, if you would be so kind.
S-Sure.
Even as we watch,
Saito's life is being depleted.
I... I don't want that!
Saito...
Founder Brimir, lend me your strength.
Hey, pal, are you all right?!
This... This is nothing...
Saito...
Fly up! Move!
Something's strange... Sylphid, please!
Use me, pal!
Got it!
I'm sorry, pal...
Looks like this one's a
little too strong for me.
I thought you looked pretty
dopey the first time we met,
but you've shaped up quite nicely,
haven't you?
Wait, Derf!
So long, pal.
Saito!
I don't believe this... Derf...
Saito, hang on!
At this rate...
Julio,
you have to live.
Your Holiness!
You know, Saito, there's something
I haven't been able to
tell you for a long time.
So today, I'm finally going to tell you.
Next time, stay tuned
for "Louise's Choice."
Louise's Choice
Saito, I...