Serial Killer!! in Akihabara?
That serial killer showed up again?
We don't die, so it's kind of hard to understand.
But that makes it even scarier.
How many victims have there been?
I wish they wouldn't do it at a time like this.
It's hurting our sales, and ruining our Christmas.
But why doesn't the Royal Guard show up?
Now that you mention it...
The Royal Guard is a security system
from when this world was a game.
They immediately detect any violent acts
committed within no-combat zones,
and teleport in to neutralize the situation.
They have equipment called "movable armor"
that allows them to use external magic
to greatly increase their physical abilities.
This gives the Royal Guard,
who are People of the Land,
power that exceeds that of adventurers,
allowing them to keep the city safe.
Tomorrow's Christmas Eve, huh?
And look what we're doing.
It can't be helped.
No sign of anything so far.
Moving to the next block.
When you go looking for them,
they don't show up.
This isn't even a quest.
And it's kind of cold.
That's him!
Where did he come from?
Status! Identify him first!
What the hell?
He's—
Christmas Eve
Christmas Eve.
It's Christmas Eve
Wiped out?
Yes. They were some of
my guild's best adventurers.
That puts the death count over ten.
His name is Embert Nelreth.
No guild affiliation, samurai class,
level 94.
That's all the information we have.
No, the bigger problem is that we know
this much and still can't do anything.
Yeah.
And even if he killed us, that wouldn't be the end.
Not for us adventurers.
Part of me thinks we aren't worried enough,
but that's better than panic.
But if we can't solve this soon,
I don't think that will last.
Evacuation is one possibility, I think.
Abandon Akihabara?
Only as an emergency measure.
We could move to Shibuya temporarily.
You're being too dramatic.
And anyway, that's not something those of us
in this room can decide on our own.
Still, maybe we should at least
evacuate the lower-leveled kids?
That's worth discussing.
But still, serial killings in Akihabara?
We need to think of some way to stop it.
Yes.
By the way, what's the villain in glasses doing?
He keeps missing the conferences
that he initiated himself.
Well, he's, um... You know...
He's out and about, trying to deal
with our financial problems.
You know, it's December, and the
Christmas event is tomorrow.
Zantleaf?
Yep.
Anyone below level 50 is being asked
to help take out the goblins.
Isn't that just an excuse to get
us away from the serial killer?
Well, that's at the heart of it, I'd imagine.
I don't want special treatment, Chief!
We can also—
Tohya!
Do you want to defeat the murderer?
Of course!
You might die.
I'm prepared for that.
Because you'll come back to life?
N-No, that's not it...
Tohya?
I...
Is that how a front-line fighter should think?
O-Oh...
That's right.
If I rush in and die, the party
won't be able to function.
Not only that.
Just the fact that you revive
means that, essentially, you're
getting special treatment.
By getting used to that,
thinking of it as normal...
It seems to me that you lose
something in exchange.
Akatsuki didn't come home again today.
It's Christmas Eve. Want to get
something to eat somewhere?
Where are you,
I-I'll pay!
Training on Christmas? You're kidding me.
murderer?
Screw that murderer.
Where the hell is the Royal Guard?
They're interfering.
All these unneeded presences...
Would my lord be angry that I keep doing this?
I want you to protect Princess Lenessia.
What did he want me to protect her from?
It's true that People of the Land are weak.
But I think she has plenty of strength.
Do I have the right to protect her?
Or the right to say anything?
I want to be strong...
The enemy is very skilled.
Keep your guard up at all times.
Assume that his abilities
exceed your own, and even mine.
Make sure you stay with your group,
and report in constantly.
Nazuna will coordinate communications at HQ.
Don't try to be heroes.
Even if you end up in combat with the target,
use formation alpha to delay him.
For this operation, we've put
two healers in every team,
so you won't have enough attack power.
Your job is to delay him and contact us.
Got it?
Got it!
Okay. All right, Souji!
I think you said everything I wanted to say.
Just one thing, then.
The target attacked one of our own.
Murder him.
You can send me out already, you know?
I want revenge on that murderer.
You just died and came back to life.
Rest for a bit.
But Sou's out there fighting for me...
It isn't for you.
No matter which of us had been attacked,
he'd never forgive the murderer.
That's how he is.
I understand that.
He's nice to every girl...
But let me dream, at least.
Anyway, you're amazing, putting
Christmas and pork soup together.
I put in salmon, too.
It's true that Souji's nice.
But not because he's simply a good person.
It's just the kind of boy he is.
That's why, once he gets mad,
there's no telling what he'll do.
There's a fine line between his kindness
and that terrifying side of him.
If those two were here...
The only ones who could talk him
out of it, or affect him at all,
are Kazuhiko and Shiroe.
Really, I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'll be back by New Year's,
I think. Yeah.
I see.
You still can't find the murderer?
Are you continuing patrols?
Yes.
Don't worry about that.
Oh, right...
Akatsuki's working hard, as well.
Yes, that's right.
Yes. You be careful, too, Shiro.
Souji!
Sounds like he's appeared.
I'll order the search team to retreat.
We, in the main unit,
will surround and obliterate him!
It's been a long time, Princess Lenessia.
Kinjou, with the Kunie Clan.
What brings him here unannounced, and so late?
I'm sorry to visit you so suddenly,
at this hour of the night.
A serious matter has come up,
and I've come to explain and apologize.
What is it?
You are familiar with the Defenders, yes?
It seems the adventurers prefer
to call them the Royal Guard.
Yes.
Naturally, I know they're a critical
part of the city's security.
A set of movable armor was stolen
from one of their guardhouses.
We believe one of the Royal Guard stole it,
a member of the Kunie Clan.
A Defender's movable armor
must receive a supply of magic at all times
from a massive magic circle under the city.
Each city's is slightly different.
Doesn't that mean there's no point
in taking it outside the town?
But it also means that, inside the
town, its power is unmatched.
It exceeds that of an adventurer.
Then the murderer...
Yes.
The Kunie Clan is involved in that crime.
It's embarrassing, but I can say this with certainty.
That means one of the People of
the Land killed an adventurer.
This affair is our fault.
I am truly sorry.
Is there...
I mean, is there anything the Kunie Clan can do?
I'm sorry, Princess Lenessia.
Of course, if we shut off the magic supply,
the movable armor would cease to function.
But at the same time, it would
disable the city's magic defenses,
allowing monsters to enter the city.
C-Can't you reboot it?
You can't just turn it back on?
All I can say is that it would take decades.
I wish I hadn't heard that.
But I did.
But what can I do about it?
I want you to protect Princess Lenessia.
It's over...
It's over for sure.
Why now?
Why me?
Why, when I came here, of all times?
Isn't there anything you can do?
Can't you get me out of this?
Can't you go easy on me?
What should I do?
Talk to the Round Table.
But if I do that, won't it mean
fighting the adventurers?
But you can't keep it a secret.
I have to tell them, don't I?
I don't know that.
Why isn't that monster here when I need him?
When I didn't need him, he was always around.
Crusty went to Seventh Fall.
I'm aware.
But even so...
That's not it.
That's not it!
Huh?
Um...
I'm sorry for entering without permission.
Did you... hear all that?
Yes.
Of course you did...
Red Bean Bun
How about it?
It's sweet...
Sweet things make me feel better.
Yes.
But the rest of the world isn't so easy.
Yeah.
The killer is a Person of the Land?
Yes, that's right.
I'm really sorry...
Why?
Why was it stolen?
Who stole it?
They don't know what he wants or where he is.
I think he's hiding in the sewers.
If we assume he won't leave the city
because he'd lose his combat powers,
that limits the places he can hide.
The only place that hasn't been searched,
where people wouldn't see him, is the sewers.
Does that mean we can catch him?
No, the Royal Guard can teleport.
So even if we surrounded him, he could escape.
Oh...
She bears such a heavy burden
on her tiny shoulders.
But she was doing her best
with those tiny shoulders.
This is upsetting you?
It is.
I'll find him.
I'll do my job.
Because I've seen you doing your best.
Tanks, switch!
Naotsugu, draw aggro!
Leave it to me!
Look over here, big guy!
Commander!
Get back, Isami!
Hey, hang in there.
Something about him isn't right.
We hit him a bunch of times,
but his HP hasn't gone down at all.
And his status display looks weird.
Embert Nelreth/ Samurai, Lv. 94
And we've been fighting so boldly,
but the Royal Guard still isn't coming.
Without the commander's support,
we would've been in danger.
We have to help, too!
You can't.
In a narrow alley like this,
you'll just get in the way.
Leave the rest to Souji.
He's like a beast!
Is he really a samurai, like Sou?
Divine Eye...
Souji's Teaching. A defensive ability.
Sou said it allows you to see
the trails that form in the air.
But he isn't getting a chance to use it.
Normally, he'd deflect or dodge,
instead of blocking with his blade.
Master...
Commander!
Master!
Sou!
The barrier I put on Souji is gone...
That should have protected
twenty percent of his HP.
At this rate, he won't last long.
He needs to think about retreating.
But...
If he does, that guy will just turn
around and attack everyone else.
There's no guarantee that
Souji can stop him alone.
What should we do for business after Christmas?
You're changing job classes again?
Wow, it's beautiful! This is for me?
Christmas is that thing the adventurers
are all excited about, right?
Merry Christmas.
What is it, anyway? Does it taste good?
Watch out, Souji!
You're...
From Shiroe's guild...
Axel Fang!
Akatsuki, right?
Stealth Blade!
Quick Assault!
Amazing... She can also...
Gust Step!
Without my barrier, that would've killed me.
He's strong.
And that katana...
Run!
Why?
Because defeating him and solving
the problem are different things.
Assassinate!
Right now, that's the only skill I can use.
I said run!
I can't agree to that.
Withdraw, Nazuna!
Roger!
I'll be waiting at the guild hall.
He was watching his friends?
During a battle like this?
To draw the enemy's attention,
and wait for the right moment for their retreat...
He knows he can't win,
but for his friends...
It's Christmas Eve.
So I have to give some kind
of present to his protégé.
Not that there's much I can say.
Votive Sword Kogarasumaru!
Watch carefully, listen carefully,
wish strongly,
and keep thinking about what you have to do.
Continue to train, without giving up.
It's pathetic how little of an explanation that is.
But this is
the entirety of the Teachings...
Not yet...
I still don't understand anything.
I'm so close!
This can't be real...
Shiro!
I'm told this is what you people say on this day...
Merry Christmas.
What are you doing now, my lord...
I miss you...
My lord...
Akatsuki wanders a town of illusions.
Is what she sees regret,
or an old wound in her heart?
Lost and uncertain, she flees to a moonlit beach.
There, she finds a warmth she remembers,
Shiroe.
What will they find within themselves,
when they meet in the land of the dead?
Next time: A Lost Child at Dawn.
A Lost Child at Dawn
Rise up once more.