Last night, multiple witnesses
observed a mysterious light
along the Pacific coast,
between Shikoku and Kyuushuu.
Some also reported hearing what
sounded like an explosion.
So, they wrote it off as a meteor?
A surprising number of people are posting
that they wish a meteor would fall on them,
and end it all in an instant...
Mysterious Giant Meteor?
The largest solar flare in recorded
history was also observed yesterday.
Experts report that...
A large-scale solar flare?
Anyway, the question now is how
to deal with Hana's absence...
She's the only one we have who can
predict the enemy's movements.
If Hana knows the enemy's about to act,
she'll contact us immediately.
I guarantee it on my name as a magical girl.
But if the enemy captures her, it'll be bad.
That's right.
Hana activated the Blume's weaponry.
Once that information gets out,
more people will come after her.
Captain...
Why didn't you stop Hana?
Because...
Stay back!
Hana!
How much of its stored energy
did the Blume use with that
Orgone beam yesterday?
I'm having Alonzo run the numbers.
I hope it doesn't prove a fatal
impediment to our plans.
It all worked out okay...
Most of the Blume's energy should be
depleted after that attack yesterday.
If they were to use the Livlaster as an
energy source, it would be a problem,
but only the princess's can move it...
Energy is an issue for us, as well.
We need to get Siren-sama here soon.
Yeah.
What about the others?
Are they leaving everything to us?
I don't know...
Everyone has their own thoughts
on the matter, I'm sure.
Perhaps this planet exerts a
strange influence over us...
Hey...
Can you use your singularity to locate Siren-sama?
I can't.
I don't know.
True Self
The royal family of the Planetary Gears
has the special ability to control Orgone energy.
Hana was created using elements
found within the royal family,
so that she could fire the Livlaster.
If Hana could fire the Livlaster she received,
she could've used the Blume as a weapon.
What's important now is where Hana went.
She's turned off her communicator,
so we have to wait to hear from her.
But—
Running around blindly won't help anything.
We're worried, too.
Sorry.
Where did you go, Hana?
Pitz?
Oh, there's another one?
You're right!
They're so cute...
Oh, I remember you.
Hello.
My... Hello, there.
You're a painter?
I'm a wandering traveler now.
I need money.
Pictures of Trumpet sell surprisingly well.
A wandering traveler?
Are you alone today?
There's someone I want to be with forever...
But I suddenly felt afraid to
be with him, so I ran away.
I ran away, too.
When you get deeply involved with others,
you learn that they're scary.
I love to feel the wind.
In this world, there are many wonderful things.
But relationships with people are scary.
If you really try to get close
to another, you'll get hurt.
No.
I can trust Daichi.
His name is Daichi-san?
Sir,
I uploaded the data from
Technology and Research Division 3
to your server, as you requested.
Thank you.
You don't have any plans tonight, do you, sir?
Would you like to have dinner, perhaps?
Sorry.
Tonight, I'm busy with a private matter.
Could we do it some other time?
Very well.
If you need anything, please call me.
Yes.
What is this?
The Machine Goodfellows have been
active during every Kiltgang attack.
What is the relationship between the Orgone
energy capsules and the Kiltgangs?
This is Kube, right?
Kanda-san, yes?
I've been set up.
But not by you.
Be careful.
Who are they?
If they find us, there'll be trouble.
Are they bad?
Yes.
Then, we have to run!
Yeah!
A dead end...
Take care of Pitz.
Um...
I can't get you involved in this.
Hide.
Well, hello.
You seem to be doing well.
We're going through all this
trouble because you ran away.
You understand that, right?
Right, Princess?
What is this thing?
Pitz!
Now!
Blume!
Why do I have more things
to worry about every day?
You're a cold man,
refusing Hitomi-chan's offer like that.
I would never turn her down.
"I"?
Who is this "I" you speak of, I wonder.
I sense a degree of irritation in your voice.
You're the one who told me
to let Amara and Moco handle the
Machine Goodfellow testing.
What is their relationship to the Kiltgangs?
Were you the one who made Legacy fall?
Secrets are a necessary part of life,
but they do make things very difficult...
What are you planning?
What do you want?
Something that will ease all your worries.
That is my wish.
Stupid machine!
The emergency shutdown switch...
Did you really think that would still work?
You were such an easy man to control.
That's Hana's call sign!
This is the Midsummer's Knights.
This is Hana Mutou...
Where are you right now?
I'm sorry. I don't know...
Don't turn off the power again.
I'll trace her signal!
Captain!
You heard him, didn't you?
Please don't turn your communicator off again.
Hana Mutou...
You're a member of a combat unit.
Obey your captain's orders.
I'm sorry.
There is no major Orgone energy movement today.
But...
But what?
Pitz is hurt.
From tomorrow on, we won't be able
to read what the enemy will do.
Th-That's him.
What's wrong, Hana?
Amarok is here...
Earlier, Malkin was with him, also!
It's dangerous for the captain to go alone...
I'll go, too!
Since there's no Orgone energy
activity tonight, I'll go, too!
Wait, you two!
You contact the captain!
Jeez...
I'm the one he's after.
If you stay here, you'll be safe.
Thank you for everything.
Sir, I've brought tea.
Sir?
I can move... I can move.
They aren't following?
Hana!
Where are Amarok and Malkin?
They found me, but they didn't follow.
I'm glad...
I'm sorry.
I...
Daichi?
Who are you?
Trumpet!
This won't take long.
Sir?
She's back!
Huh?
That was so sudden, it took me by surprise...
My biggest worry is gone, and now I feel free.
This is the real me I've been waiting for.
Puck does not lie.
What is this?
Are they filming something?
Then where's the camera?
How does it feel to awaken to the real you?
We are the Planetary Gears.
We reveal the dream of the world.
What?
How are they doing that?
Until a moment ago,
you seemed to be with Blume.
That girl is Blume?
I need to hear more about this.
Understood.
The engine series is probably here.
Then...
We'll meet them in our Machine Goodfellows.
You knew about the real me?
When I heard you were made at
the same time as the Blume,
I had a feeling.
It doesn't bother you?
You know how I feel now, right?
Don't keep your problems to yourself
and get sad anymore, okay?
Yes, Captain.
And...
Thanks for saving Tanegashima.
It's kind of hard to go out there now.
For the time being, there's no
sign of Amarok and Malkin...
Captain! Look out!
Teppei?
They're coming!
Hana, take Pitz and hide!
Okay.
Let's go, Teppei!
Roger.
This is Akari.
The Machine Goodfellows have appeared.
The captain and Teppei are fighting them.
I'm tracking it here.
But there's no MM bus signal.
What's going on?
I don't know...
They may have some other goal.
Anyway, ready the Earth Engine.
The Nebula just arrived.
I'll send it, too.
Roger.
Earth Engine, Nebula Engine... Launch!
There are two Machine Goodfellows on radar.
Be very careful.
Two?
I found the princess.
I can't hit him...
He's too fast!
Once it's tuned, the Neural
Maneuver System isn't so bad.
What?
They're here!
Earth...
Nebula, too!
Two against one isn't fair, but...
Let's go, Teppei!
Roger.
Okay, stop!
Move even a tiny bit, and I'll kill the princess.
I like it...
We look like a really evil bunch now!
Teppei!
I said...
Don't move!
Daichi!
Teppei!
This is seriously bad...
Regret your choice to give up eternal life, Albion!
Teppei!
For my sake... They're both going to...
What?
This light... It can't be...
Orgone energy?
What is that?
Hana?
The Blossom?!
How dare you hurt my friends?!
She's controlling the beam?
That Livlaster is already in ecdysis mode?
This is for Pitz!
Amara!
We can't take any more of those Orgone beams!
Never a boring moment with these guys!
Are you two okay?
I'm okay...
What about you, Teppei?
I'm fine...
What about Pitz?
It's my fault.
I'm sorry, Pitz.
I'm sorry, everyone.
The Planetary Gears use the
awakened Siren's powers
to make new Orgone energy capsules.
The Kiltgang Aiatar attacks Earth.
But the Midsummer's Knights advance
their plans to a new stage, too.
Next time, on episode 16 of Captain Earth:
Her Flare.
Her Flare
Flare Engine, expand!