I hate everything about this.
This sunshine, beating down
on you from morning onward...
These students, who don't have
a thought in their heads...
And having to hike up this steep
slope every day from today,
just to get to school...
It all makes me want to throw up.
Nishimi Kaoru
Joining us from today is Nishimi
Kaoru-kun, all the way from Yokosuka.
It seems he was at the top of his
class at his previous school.
I hope all of you study just as hard as him.
I'm Nishimi. Nice to meet you.
Yokosuka?
Isn't that far?
I'm used to this routine. But...
He looks like a real grind...
Spoiled rich kid...
Their unreserved stares...
Their Kyushu dialect that I can't follow...
This is the most memorable
welcome I've received yet.
Nishimi-kun. Nishimi-kun!
Have you decided what club you're gonna join?
Are you interested in radios?
Look at that loser, Maruo!
Two four-eyed bookworm runts!
They're made for each other!
S-Sorry. Because of me,
they picked on you, too...
Infantile creeps like that can't do
anything unless they're in a pack.
I'm not interested in them.
Nishimi-kun...
Not interested in radios, either...
Nishimi-kun, one thing...
It's not a good idea to antagonize
the guy who sits behind me.
He's a notorious thug that
even the teacher can't manage.
His name is Kawabuchi and if he
zeros in on you, it's all over.
Oh, no. Just thinking about
it makes me feel nauseous...
Nishimi-san...
Nishimi-san?
I'm Mukae Ritsuko, the class representative.
I was instructed to show you around
the school during lunch break.
I'm glad to meet you.
I... don't feel sick anymore.
So the gymnasium is back there.
And the infirmary is in this building...
A-Are you okay, Nishimi-san?!
Whatcha think you're doin'?!
Whoops! It slipped outta my hands!
Sorry 'bout that!
What is it?
Who's that?
Never saw 'im before...
Um... Mukae-san, where's the roof?
I've moved from school to school
ever since first grade...
If something unexpected happened,
I would lose my equilibrium,
and even minor stress would trigger nausea.
But one time, I found a place at school
where I could regain my bearings.
That's right. If I can
just get to the roof...
What's this?
You finally...
...came for me?
Who the hell are you?
Why you holdin' my hand?
You're the one that grabbed my hand!
I get it... You're the key burglar, huh?
In that case, I ain't gonna hold back.
You Sentaro?
This what you're lookin' for?
Then you goons are the thieves, huh?
The roof belongs to us senior smokers!
W-Wait!
I want the key to the roof.
A candyass like you better
get the hell outta here!
You want the key that badly?
I-I want it!
Keep a holda this for me.
H-Hey! Are you all right?!
Hey, come on, wake up!
How reckless can you be, going
up against three seniors?
This is what you wanted, right?
I can really have it?
Yeah, here...
For 100,000.
Don't tell me you thought
I'd give it to you gratis?
I put my ass on the line gettin' it.
100,000 is cheap.
Dammit!
Well, I'm goin' home.
Come to think of it, I didn't even
go to class once today, though...
City boy like that's got no common
ground with us country boys.
I can't believe you, Sentaro!
You got in another fight?!
It's just some scratches...
You... Hey!
Ri'ko, who's this guy?
I'm not gonna answer a guy
who does nothin' but fight.
Maruo! You tell me.
H-He's Nishimi Kaoru-kun, a kid
that just transferred in today,
supposed to be rich and a real brainiac...
Oh?
Later, Maruo!
Hi there, rich boy.
From now on, your name is "Richie".
Let's me and you be pals, huh?
Sentaro's got a new target.
It's curtains for him.
I feel sorry for him.
Oh, no... I feel sick again...
Sorry. I've got a favor to ask...
Huh?
I can't pay 100,000, but could you
lend me the key just this once?
Oh, this?
But right now it's...
Hey! It's raining outside!
There's no problem if I take an umbrella!
It sounds like fun! I'll go, too!
What the hell? This ain't much fun at all.
Of course not. I'm not up here to have fun.
Then why bother comin' up here?
If you're bored, you can always go back.
Nah. Class ain't my style.
D-Don't follow me!
You're giving me the creeps!
This feels good...
Richie, you take a shower, too!
Leave me alone!
What are you scared of, huh?
Nothin' good's ever come of fear.
Let yourself get a little wet!
What happened?!
To the both of you...
I swear...
Cause me no end of trouble...
We're going right to the infirmary
so you can borrow a towel!
Oh, that's right. I'll get your gym clothes!
I'll meet you there!
Is this... jazz?
What, you can tell?
Well, sort of... I play piano,
classical music though...
Classical, huh? What a drag...
Here I am.
Huh? Where's the nurse?
Looks like she's out...
I didn't notice with the glasses on,
but you have a really
pretty face, Nishimi-san.
W-What...?
Oh, is it rude to call a man
"pretty"? I meant "handsome".
N-No, I'm not...
W-What are you doing?!
I'm a human hair dryer, is all!
Sentaro!
There he goes again, bein'
scared. What a fraidy cat!
I'm not scared!
Oh yeah?
How could I be afraid anymore?
After all... that rain felt great,
way better than I imagined...
It's weird.
Even with everyone staring at
me, I can breathe normally...
What kind of magic is this?
That's great, Dad!
Being able to play the
piano, even being a sailor?
Kaoru, I'm going to be away
again for quite a while.
Be a good boy while I'm gone, okay?
When I play the piano, I can
forget all of the bad stuff
and the loneliness from Dad being away.
Don't worry, Kaoru. Your uncle
in Kyushu has a huge grand piano.
Dad... I don't want a grand piano...
What I want is...
Oh, Kaoru-kun. You're up
really early today, huh?
You wanna play the piano? Go on ahead.
Mariko feels like hearing
a tune that'll wake her up.
But playing this early in
the morning would be...
But I wanna hear it right now!
Mariko will take responsibility, so please!
Please-please-please!
All right, fine.
Dad...
Excuse me?! What do you think you're doing?
Playing the piano at this hour...
Don't you have any sense?!
I'm sorry, Aunt. Mariko-chan wanted...
See? This is why I told you to stop it...
Putting the blame on someone else...
I guess it's difficult for a
father to raise a child alone...
Although it's your mother who's responsible,
for abandoning the both of you...
Nishimi-san...
Mukae-san...
Sentaro didn't come today, huh?
Maybe you're lonely without him here?
Sorry. I wasn't able to
comprehend that question.
I'll be quite pleased if he
sees fit to extend his absence.
I-I see... It looked to me like
you two were hitting it off...
Everyone else is afraid of Sentaro,
but you act normally in front of him.
I bet you and Sentaro could
become buddies, Nishimi-san.
Mukae-san... Give me a
break with that smile...
Really, as his childhood
friend, I can guarantee it.
Childhood friend...? So that's why you're
so casual with each other's names.
Oh, you can call me by
my name too, Nishimi-san.
And then maybe I'll call you... "Kaoru-san".
Kaoru-san, Kaoru-san, Kaoru-san...
W-What is this echoing...?
Sorry I said that without
asking. If you don't like it...
No, it's fine! I don't mind it at all...
Oh, that's right... Ri... chan...
Yes?
Do you happen to know of a record shop
in town that sells classical music?
Records? We've got tons
of records at my place!
You should come over!
You know what I really mean by inviting
you over, don't you... Kaoru-san?
I-I think things are moving too fast...
Is this how Kyushu girls behave?
This is our shop...
And this is my father!
Fath...
M-My name is Nishimi Kaoru. Your
daughter has been very kind...
The classical records are over
on that shelf, Kaoru-san.
Right.
What kind of records are you looking for?
Well, like piano music...
I play the piano myself, you see...
You play the piano?!
Oh, it's not a big deal...
Come with me!
Ritsuko! Outsiders aren't allowed in there.
Dad, Kaoru-san is a good
friend of mine and Sentaro.
Sen's friend?
No, I'm not his friend, just a...
Come on, go in.
Go ahead.
What is this?
What the hell are you doin' here?!
Th-That's what I want to ask you!
Ri'ko! We got an intruder!
Listen to this, Sentaro! Kaoru-san
says he can play piano!
Yeah, I know, I know.
But bet you anything it's just rich
kid stuffed shirt classical stuff.
Jazz is the only music for me.
Kaoru-san... Kaoru-san?
Say, Kaoru-san, go on and play the piano!
Oh, I don't...
Ri'ko, only jazz is allowed in here!
If it's the piano you want, I'll play it.
Oh, I know this piece...
I can't hear any more. It's like this.
Wrong! That ain't even close!
What are you talking about?!
I played it exactly right!
There wasn't any swing!
If you play it without feelin' it,
it don't sound like no jazz to me!
Say, I'd love to hear you
two do a session together!
Hah?!
Nah, Ri'ko. That's a no-go.
This guy don't get jazz and
he's got no sense for it.
A little practice and
playing that'll be a cinch!
Hmph!
Thank you for having me over.
Um, Kaoru-san! Come back again, okay?
Ri-chan, do you know the name of the
tune he was playing on the piano?
Um...
The only thing Sen can play on
the piano is the intro to this.
Art Blakey and the Jazz
Messengers' "Moanin'".
I'd like this, please.
Wasn't he here to buy classical music?
Yeah...
I don't know why...
...but his drums just wouldn't
stop thundering in my head.
Kaoru-san?
W-What?
Aren't you walking strange?
Really? This is how I always walk.
Ow!
Ri'ko! Richie! See ya's!
You're running down this slope that
I hate so much like it's nothing...
What can you see beyond the hill?
Is it an outlook that I've never seen?