Inferior Terran scum! Don't think
that you'll get away with this!
The Kataphrakt that defeated Sir Vlad
was orange in color, correct?
Every last Terran
is the enemy!
Your Sky Carrier carried the Argyre.
You saw it happen, correct?
That's right... He was killed by
that devious orange bastard!
Only two Orbital Knights
have been defeated
by Terran units,
Sir Vlad and Sir Trillram.
Also...
...when Sir Trillram was defeated, Princess
Asseylum was with that orange Kataphrakt.
According to this Sky Carrier's data,
the ship that it was aboard
was on a
south-southwesterly course.
I have no hard evidence.
It may merely be a coincidence.
But right now, this is the only lead
that I have to go on.
That battle on Tanegashima...
My big brother fought in it, too.
He was killed in action.
Murdered, rather. By you.
Magbaredge is the name of
the family that adopted me.
My birth name was Humeray.
Your best friend was my brother.
Enemy unit overhead
is in a nosedive!
Three others closing in
from our flanks!
It's on a collision course
with the bridge!
Direct hit! Last!
We won't make it...
Out of ammo?
Captain...
This is the end.
What was that?!
Huh? We're alive?
That's...
Damn him... How long is he going to
continue making me look the fool?
I'm going out in the Tharsis.
Prepare me a Sky Carrier!
Abide a moment, Count Cruhteo,
Milord Saazbaum,
why do you stop me?
Did you not request that
I capture him alive?
I do not wish him to notice your
pursuit and alter his destination.
I wish to know where
he intends to go.
Meaning?
Why do you think that he made
use of the Audience Chamber?
If he is a spy,
surely he has accomplices.
Worry not.
I shall track him
from above.
Enemy reinforcements?
But it stopped
the enemy attack.
There's infighting?
Who knows?
They might just be fighting over
who gets to make the kill.
Either is fine.
Even if the enemy of my enemy isn't
my friend, he might still be useful.
What clan does this
interloper belong to?
This area has already been
laid claim to by Femieanne!
I will not tolerate you
taking liberties here!
Go, my messengers!
Botis' fingers!
He'll pay!
Lt. Marito!
Lt. Marito! Are you all right?!
Humeray!
Grab on, Humeray!
Marito...
Humeray!
I'll get you
out of there, Humeray!
I can't land a shot!
They've put distance between us.
Which means...
Control! Open the well dock!
It's Mustang 22!
Captain...
Kaizuka's brother, huh?
All right, fine.
Cover your ears!
Cover your ears, everyone!
Mommy!
What's that?
A hidden dock?
Engine status?
Still working!
Hull status?
Holding together, barely.
No, taking on water!
Make a break
for the dock up ahead!
A-All ahead full!
H-Hey! Inaho?!
Mustang 11!
We're going, too!
Nao, what do you think you're doing?
Don't run off like that!
I could say the same to you, Yuki.
Who's defending the ship?
Listen here, you...
Machine gun fire.
Target: the rock above the gate!
But, ma'am!
Fire!
Guys...
What does that orange
Kataphrakt have up its sleeve?
All right, now let's deal with
that Ashura over there.
The Landing Castle will soon reach airspace
where we can scan the Japanese archipelago.
As soon as we enter the detection area, scan
for the Sky Carrier stolen by Slaine Troyard.
Princess Asseylum is alive.
I have seen her
with my own two eyes.
Milord Saazbaum.
I have located the
specified craft.
It is above Tanegashima in the
southwestern Japanese archipelago.
It appears to be engaging
Femieanne's Kataphrakt, Hellas.
What?!
Tanegashima, you say?
What is this place?
I've never heard anything about there
being a base like this on Tanegashima.
But whatever it is, let's get
everyone off the ship.
Lieutenant!
Are you okay?! Lt. Marito!
Don't push!
Try not to breathe in
the smoke!
Evacuating the noncombatants
has top priority!
Then the wounded!
Leave no one behind!
Yes, sir!
Matsuribi-senpai!
Where's Mustang Platoon?
Inko and the others
aren't on the deck!
They're still fighting out there.
They're using themselves as decoys
to give us time to escape.
No way...!
Direct hit!
Next, right 3 mil!
Roger.
To attack the assault ship, it has
to break through all that rock.
To increase their impact,
they have to increase their speed.
To accelerate using a rocket,
you have to have distance.
If the distance
is far enough,
throw off the angle just a little,
and it'll miss its mark by a lot.
Enemy unit, 4 o'clock!
Heading this way!
That's not a problem.
That Martian attack craft
will cover us.
You dare?!
What the hell is going on
around here?!
Yuki. Let's attack the
enemy Kat directly.
What are you saying?!
We're no match for that thing!
I'm not so sure.
It might be all bark
and no bite.
Inko. I need to borrow
your handgun.
Okay!
Blocks 11 and 12,
evacuation confirmed.
Evacuation of Block 8
is also complete.
So that's everyone.
Yes, ma'am.
We should get going, too.
Any word from Mustang Platoon?
No, ma'am.
All we can do is pray, I suppose.
Captain Magbaredge!
Mizusaki? Why aren't you leading
the refugees away?
I've had them take shelter in a cargo
room up ahead for the time being.
The thing is...
...there's something that
I want you to see, Captain.
Milady...
Is this my fault?
Did this happen...
because I came to Earth?
Milady!
If I hadn't come, there would
have been no assassination.
If there had been no assassination,
this war never would have...
People would not have been
made to suffer unjustly...
You're right.
Remember that. Because to these people,
all Martians are the enemy.
How is that even possible?!
I haven't the slightest, ma'am.
What kind of installation is this?!
M-Milady!
Where are you going?!
This is... a Martian Kataphrakt!
How did it-
It's a crater.
There wasn't just one meteor
that fell here.
One hit the shore and
formed the bay.
And the other... ended up here.
Then this machine was-
Yeah. The demon we
saw 15 years ago.
I always figured it had been annihilated
in the damage of Heaven's Fall.
Talk about a touching reunion.
Are you telling me
that we seized it?
Then does that mean that
Lt. Marito's Tanegashima Report
was buried so they could
keep this a secret?
But...
...could that be all
there is to it?
Capt. Magbaredge!
Look at that!
What in the world... is that?
Orange...
What are you doing, Nao?
The Ashura over there hasn't
budged from that spot.
All it does is repeat
the same attack.
I'm sure that they're
its only weapons.
All I need now is...
Cover us.
Darn it, Nao!
Inaho!
Are you kidding me?
Opening contact channel.
I'll be quick.
What are you armed with?
I have about 20 howitzer rounds.
And you?
HE rounds, 9.
Then I'm dry.
Don't do it, Nao!
That's a Martian-
Sorry, Yuki.
We'll talk later.
The Hellas' fists increase their hardness
by becoming a single, giant molecule.
No bullet can destroy them.
No, one of the fists
was destroyed.
Their molecular structure probably
reverts when their fingers move.
Patch me into the signal
from your stabilizers.
We use a different standard.
That's all right. I'll convert it.
Here it comes, Bat!
Bat?
I thought so.
Marax!
Why, you...!
Him and his crazy stunts...
We're moving up.
Is that a good idea?
It's okay. His crazy stunts
tend to be the right move.
Pull them closer!
One left!
Get directly behind it!
Their tails have no armor, which means
their engines are also vulnerable.
Two more coming in
from aft!
Course one-seven-five.
Fly parallel to the coast.
Yuki, do you copy?
You only remember you have
teammates when you need help!
Hold that course!
Botis... Marax...
Ronove... Halphas...
Raum... Vine...
How dare you harm
my children?!
We'll attack it simultaneously.
Roger.
You leave me no choice, then!
It flew away!
Crap!
What is that?!
I don't know, either!
It's gained distance!
It's accelerating this way!
Use your rifle to throw off
its trajectory!
It's too big for a rifle!
I'm too heavy with you aboard!
I can't dodge it!
I'm going to crush you
like the bugs you are...
It's almost on us, Bat!
Keep quiet, Orange!
It dodged me?!
He stalled out
to lose altitude?
It's back.
I can't pull out!
The same trick won't
work on me twice!
It's all over.
What just happened?!
What...?
That's...
A flying ship?
No...
A battleship?
I've found you!
Princess Asseylum!
Impossible!
The Terrans have no Aldnoah!
How could they have such a thing?!
Flying enemy craft closing in
from 12 o'clock!
Collision course!
Filthy Terrans!
Brace for impact, everyone!
Damn you... I'm still-
All Martians... will pay
for Father's death.
We did it!
Princess Asseylum,
I've found you at last!
Your princess was dead.
And in spite of that...
...why are you
looking for her?
You knew that the princess
was alive. So why?
What do you mean?
Answer me.
Take me to Her Highness.
Answer my question first.
Wait... Are you intending to
exploit her to your own ends?
If she's exploited,
do you have a problem
with that?
Are you...
Are you my enemy?!
You...
are my enemy.