Kishou... Kishou Yanagihara...
How long do you think
you can remain in Class A?
Would you think about retiring
if you were demoted from Class A?
What do you think
about the up-and-coming youngsters?
I'm scared.
If my work was taken away from me,
what would be left?
I'm scared, Saku.
I hear you, Gan.
I'm always thinking the same thing.
But I still don't have an answer.
However, if you're standing in a burnt field,
I'm still...
...burning.
Well, shall we go?
Winning...
and even losing aren't things
that can ever be decided so easily.
I'll become a human torch again today
and give full rein to my suffering.
Burnt Field (Part 3)
SILVER GENERAL
Silver to 1-2?
What about the bishop?
The bishop isn't going to escape?
I see!
LANCE
That's not it.
Mr. Yanagihara is looking beyond that.
It's Lance to 2-5.
If he drops it there, I can't...
defend!
He's good.
Eldest active player, no way!
There's no way.
He can't be this good.
What should I do?
What should I...
There it is. Lance to 2-5!
Brother, what will you do?
Please!
Bishop to 1-4!
He defended with the Bishop he just captured?
But this is...
Yeah, but...
Certainly...
Was that the right move?
But my only defense against the 2-3 square
was dropping this bishop.
He dropped the bishop right away.
However...
...it was a wise decision.
I'm sure if you leave Shimada alone,
he'll just start winning again.
That's right, Gotou. It's just as you said.
Plainly, simply...
He steadily built himself up
and came back, one layer thicker.
Yes, he must be...
a zelkova tree.
It takes a long time for them to grow big,
but they're resistant to wind and rain,
and eventually become huge, tough trees.
Then what am I?
If I had to compare myself,
what would I have been?
Yeah.
I just don't know.
I don't have a single predecessor left
who would compare me to something.
Huh? Crap.
I can't let my mind drift
in the middle of a match.
Man, my back hurts.
And my vision is starting to blur.
But still, I feel much better than usual.
I felt terrible during our first match.
They called it "aged pneumonia."
I thought I was going to die.
I'm surprised I won that one.
Whoops, he's glaring at me.
How scary. There's no need
to make that kind of face.
You've got the advantage right now.
You're the one who...
I see. So am I going...
to lose?
I thought about it all this time.
If shogi is taken away from me,
what would be left?
Kai Shimada 8th-Dan, has defended against
Kishou Yanagihara's attacks with Lance to 2-5.
Now, the advantage has been reversed.
Will he finally attain his first title?
Meanwhile, Kishou Yanagihara
seems more fatigued
as Shimada 8th-Dan puts pressure on him.
It looks like he's struggling
and can't concentrate.
Kishou Yanagihara is close to the "Eternal Kishou,"
which requires ten Kishou Championship wins,
but is it beyond his reach?
Saku, is this as far as you go?
Just one more! You just need one more win!
No, you did great, Saku.
In fact, you did great making it this far!
I'm going to retire.
Saku, I'm being demoted.
It's frustrating, but I'll look for another path.
Saku, it's over for me.
I've accepted that this is the right time.
Saku, I'm moving back to the countryside.
I'm scared.
I'm scared, Saku.
I feel like I'm in a burnt field.
No!
I don't know why, but...
but I'm not supposed to...
...let go of this!
I'll shoulder this burden and deliver it!
So for the people who tried
with all their might can arrive at a place...
will not be some burnt field!
King to 1-7?
He's bringing up the King?
King to 1-6? I've never heard of King to 1-6!
A climbing king?
What is this?
C-Can he even do that?
Yeah, but...
- Saku!
- Saku, you can do it!
True...
I have no move to rebuke that.
Old man...
You're too old to make that move.
With time, grass will grow again
on a burnt field, whether we like it or not.
It'll become a field of green.
And we'll see it...
together!
Burnt Field (Part 3)
Burnt Field (Part 4)
He had gone far beyond his limits.
Anyone watching could see that.
His body leaned heavily on the armrest,
just staring at the board
as if he were going to fall forward.
But each move those quivering fingers sent out
was like slowly flowing lava, heavy, red...
and glowing brilliantly.
It was a fierce battle.
Any professional shogi player...
would desire from the bottom of their hearts...
that they've always wanted to play...
a match like this.
SHOGI HALL
And then...
after a heated battle that covered 169 moves,
it took all of Mr. Shimada's strength
to utter two words,
and brought it to an end.
After 169 moves,
the winner is Kishou Yanagihara.
By the rules of the Kishou Championship,
since he retained the title ten times,
he receives the official title "Eternal Kishou."
Saku, you did it! Ten wins!
He did it! He's the Eternal Kishou!
Yeah!
Yanagihara-sensei, are you okay?
I'm fine.
My knees just gave way.
Thank you.
Saku!
Kishou Yanagihara...
Wh-What about the post-mortem?
Yanagihara-sensei! Congratulations!
Saku!
That was awesome! That was awesome shogi!
Gan!
H-Huh? Me? What is it, Saku?
Take a photo!
What?
You brought your camera, right?
Take a photo!
With everyone here!
O-Oh, wait a second!
33RD KISHOU CHAMPIONSHIP, FIFTH MATCH
Maybe someone should hold this
to commemorate it.
Good thinking, kiddo. Come on over.
R-Right!
And, there.
Wow, I'm right next to him!
Well, I guess I'll go here.
Since I am the observer.
Should the second row sit here?
Mr. Tanabe! Get behind Saku!
What the hell? I can't fit everyone in
when you're milling about.
Scoot in closer.
Don't you have a wide-angle lens?
What's the difference, as long as you fit?
Hey Gan, you're getting in here too.
Use a timer!
Oh, there he is!
Shimada, you too!
Would you be in the photo too?
A commemorative photo? Me too?
GLEAMING
LIVELY
SHINING
Yanagihara
Merchandise
Didn't you guys come here to support me?
GLOSSY
We can't help it, Kai!
Yanagihara-sensei is a hero to our generation!
He was so cool!
Yanagihara-sensei is still working hard,
so we can't be put out to pasture, either!
That's right!
Maybe I'll plant more plantain lilies
and angelica trees in my greenhouse.
Yeah, maybe I'll grow more garlic chives
and green onions next year!
I can't work away from home anymore,
but I can make some money
from the greenhouse in the winter.
After all, I still want to give
the grandkids some pocket money.
Hold on!
Saku! Get me in the photo too!
Of course, next! To! You!
What the hell? The match is already over!
Bastard. You just came to drink.
No, Saku. Sheesh, you're going senile.
Then what's going on?
You're the one who said, "Toku, I always lose
when you come to watch, so stay away!"
Huh? Did I say that?
That's awful!
Okay, okay! Quit making a fuss!
I'm taking the shot!
All right, all right! Shush, everyone!
Everybody, smile!
Okay, ten seconds!
Ten... Nine...
Life is nothing but goodbyes.
Who said that again?
It's a good, accurate expression.
I know I'm going to lose them one by one.
From shogi and from life.
But I remember.
There were a lot of people I liked,
and people I disliked.
There's no mistake.
Who I am now
is made up of all those fragments.
These sashes are "hope."
I'm bearing hundreds,
even thousands of them now,
and sometimes they're so heavy
that I can't even move.
But because of that weight...
because it's bound so tightly...
it won't let me run away from my fear
of becoming a human torch.
It's ironic.
Then I guess I could also say
that thanks to that "weight,"
I made it this far without running away.
But I won't say thanks!
ANGER
Because I'm serious
and passionate every time!
Every single time, I think, "This time for sure,
I'll seriously die!" Damn it!
Huh? Wh-What?
They foist their dreams on me!
They sit on the sidelines and go,
"Hang in there!"
"Keep your head in the game!"
"Be grateful you can still play!"
I'm doing my best
without being told, every time!
What are you going on about?
And you're even crying.
Still...
Next year would probably be impossible.
Oh, sorry. But it's too early to say that.
What? You just laughed at me!
And of course I can't do it.
I'll die if I play a match like today's!
You're still going to push me?
Geez, I'm almost 60!
Listen.
What you just said?
That's what you told me last year.
Oh, did I?
You sure did. And we're both way over 60.
We've got our 70th coming up.
Burnt Field (Part 4)
Next Episode Preview
Episode 41
Okay, it's ready!
Behold!
Delicious!
It's so chewy!
Good idea! Let's ask him!
This plum syrup was made by Chiho.
There's a nice smell from the plums.
ILLUSTRATION:
RYO IKUEMI
Saku, congratulations!
You really do win
when I'm not there.