Hey.
Good morning, Haru.
Shizuku, this house is haunted.
Huh?
Something woke me up in
the middle of the night.
There was a kid standing by my bed,
just staring down at me.
Oh, that...
That's my brother.
Oh, I like my yolks broken.
You don't look anything
like Shizuku, Pops.
Uh...  How can you be
so casual about this?
Summer Break
Seriously?
You have to take make-ups again?!
Final Exam Scores
Freshmen
1st Yoshida Haru
2nd Mizutani Shizuku
3rd Sawada Riku
Yoshida placed first?
That can't be right.
I'm going to spend summer
break studying hard.
There, there, there.
Cheer up, Mitty.
689 is a super score!
I'm under 300 after adding
up every subject...
I'll be taking make-ups again...
Summer break...
I like bikinis!
You're so bold, Haru-kun!
I don't know what you have in mind,
but I'm not going to the beach.
Hey, guys.
You need to sign up for
a Sports Day event.
Huh?  Where are you going, Mitty?
I have a question about how
this answer was scored.
She should try to enjoy school events.
She's got me as a friend, after all.
Maybe she doesn't
consider you a friend.
Q15. Describe the main character's emotional state using 50 words or less.
She was in despair after losing her chance to marry into money.
Why didn't I get full
credit for this answer?
It's after working hours...
Your teacher can't be
bothered with this now.
School is in session.
Do your job.
Oh, that one.
Your answer wasn't wrong,
but it wasn't right either.
Why...
Because this answer makes no mention
of the pain of a broken heart!
Suffocating anguish with no outlet...
Heartbreak...
Farewell to my love...
I'm guessing you were dumped.
However, that's your interpretation.
I don't agree.
Yes, yes.
I hear you.
You never give up.
Stop screwing around.
You don't yet know what it's like
to have your love crushed.
Right, I was rejected by Haru.
I'll wait for you to fall in love
with me before I say it again.
How do I make him fall in love with me?
Actually, why did I fall in
love with Haru to begin with?
Yo, Shizuku.
Did you get any points back?
Oh, excuse me!
Yoshida Haru!
Than—
Er, cabbage?
Oh, this one?
Th-Thank you...
I'm very sorry!
Are you okay?
He kept glaring at me!
You should stop glaring at people.
Huh?
I don't glare at people.
I'm pretty sure that's
why people avoid you.
When you're scared of other people,
they're scared of you.
I like it when you smile.
Whatever.
Bye.
Chili shrimp!  Chili shrimp!
Yoshida Haru...
I like it when you smile.
Like it.
It.  It.
I-I'm sorry!
It's okay.
Did you watch the special last night?
Hey, you dropped this.
I sure did!
Oh... Th-Thank... you...
You're welcome.
Huh?
Wh-What?
Wait...
Hey, give me that.
Huh?
I'll carry it for you.
He isn't scary?
Actually...
On closer look...
He's pretty handsome?
This is a rooster.
His name is Nagoya.
Well, look who's popular
all of a sudden.
After all, Haru-kun
certainly is handsome.
Plus, he's more social these days.
The girls aren't going to ignore that.
You were right, Shizuku.
I focused on trying not to glare and
people started talking to me.
Is this the power of eye contact?
No.
Haru-kun, Haru-kun.
Huh?
Help me study.
Piss off.
Study by yourself.
It's a little unnerving.
He's acting the same as before,
Scary!
but now that he's popular,
they accept it.
How am I scary?
You're so funny, Haru-kun!
I'm not funny.
Nagoya
Lonely women turn to their pets.
Wh-What are you talking
about, Natsume-san?
Isn't that what you're doing?
It's hard to approach Haru-kun
when he's surrounded by girls.
Send it back, Yoshida!
A direct shot?
Yoshida, that's the wrong goal.
Wrong goal?
Look over here!
Haru-kun!
Yoshida, Yoshida.
Hilarious!
They're acting completely
different now.
It wasn't that long ago that
they all steered clear of him.
We should go practice.
Oh?  What's this?
Mitty, are you jealous?
Oh.
So this is how it feels
to be jealous...
She's so honest.
July 14
Sports Day
Go Class B!
Hey, Mitty!
You haven't touched the ball yet!
Wh-What do you want me to do?
I didn't expect Natsume-san
to be big on sports.
Hey, how did the girls
do in volleyball?
We might have won if Mitty
tried a little harder.
I'm sorry.
Yoshida was a big help on our side...
until he got too excited
and punched the ref.
Where's Haru-kun?
Over there.
Oh, boy.
I hope it works out for
Yoshida this time.
Huh?
I think I mentioned this before,
but Yoshida never came to
class in middle school.
He got in a fight at the
start of our first year,
which caused a big fuss.
Oh, really?
He was pretty vicious back then.
Everyone was scared.
After that, Yoshida stopped
coming to school.
So I hope that doesn't
happen this time.
So he has a record...
Why do you care so much
about Haru, Sasayan-kun?
Huh?
You never talked to him
until recently, right?
Because I owe Yoshida.
Well?  Do you like it?
How does it taste?
E-Excuse me.
The teacher said to help
set up the next event.
What?  Already?
Oh...  I can take care of it.
Huh?  Really?
Uh-huh, I'll go set everything up.
Thank you!
Are you sure about this?
Aren't you friends?
What?  No way.
She's in our class, but we never talk.
Yep.
It's so hot...
You were great out there!
Water...
I know!
Hey, shouldn't we get a teacher?
U-Um...
That hurt.
Why did you drop that on my head?
He has a bump!
You look so dumb!
Shut up!
Let's go already.
Damn, forget it.
You're not wanted.
Get lost.
Yikes.
Poor girl.
Eh?  What do you want?
Oh, I recognize him!
You're the one who came
to Class C, right?
Did you really punch a girl
and make her nose bleed?
Want me to make your nose bleed?
Huh?
Hey.
Don't get too cocky, freshman!
Why do people like you have to tell her
that she isn't wanted?
Hey, there's a fight going down!
Wait a second...
This looks bad.
Are you okay?
Stand up.
H-Hey, isn't this enough?
Just stop.
We're sorry.
Hey.
Haru.
What are you doing?
Hey!  What are you guys doing?!
Honestly...
You ended up making things
worse by intervening.
I never thought I'd have to
run away from a teacher.
Shizuku...
Did I do something wrong?
This happened once before.
I looked up and everyone
was staring at me, stunned.
I have no idea why this happens.
Am I doing something wrong?
It's hard to say.
I can't say that you're going
about things the right way,
but I know that
you're a kind person.
Really...
I know that
you're a kind person.
I'm sure they'll realize that one day.
You were like a hero back there.
A hero that always comes
when I'm in danger.
The upperclassmen were
the ones in danger.
There's something on your forehead.
Yoshida.
The next match is about to start.
Okay!
B-Bye, Shizuku!
Y-Yes?
If we win,
will you go somewhere with
me over summer break?
Sure.
Cool.
Haru.
G-Good luck.
What was that about?
Haru ended up winning
the one-sided bet.
Natsume Asako is diving
from way up here!
Whee!
Next up, Yoshida Haru!
Diving from way, way up here!
Okay.  Since we have
beginners, we'll focus
Summer!
on fish like char and salmon.
Fish look upstream for their food,
so move in a downstream direction.
Makes sense.
I caught a bunch while I was swimming.
Are you Tarzan?
Natsume-chan, can you
wash this pot for us?
Oh, sure.
Wh-What is it?
Yeah...
Gotta love fishing in the mountains.
Oh, so Mi-chan-san and
Haru-kun are cousins.
That's right.
His dad is my mom's older brother.
Since my place is
close to the high school,
I'm looking after him starting this year.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, really...
Did you know that, Mitty?
No, I had no idea.
I thought you were brothers.
Nope, but he has an older brother.
That brother of his is—
Mi-chan.
You're talking too much.
Haru.
Look, we're back.
Help us unload everything.
I woke up Haru!
He was sound asleep.
Shizuku.
We had a lot of fun today.
Yup.
Okay, let me divvy up our haul,
so why don't you wait inside?
Okay.
Oh, I just started a
online community...
That hurts.
Running away the second
he sees my face?
He overreacts to everything.
Sa-Sasayan-kun!
It's that guy!
The one who took money
from Mi-chan-san!
Huh?
Hey!
Haru just came flying out the door...
Oh...
Hey, Mitsuyoshi.
They seem to think that I was
extorting money from you.
Haru-kun's big brother?!
I'm Yoshida Yuzan.
Thanks for putting up with Haru.
Yeah, this is the brother
I was talking about.
I was returning
money that I borrowed.
What?  You cut the watermelon?
I wanted to smash it open.
No.
Anyway, when did Haru
make all these friends?
So tell me.
Is he doing okay?
You bet.
He started going to class
because of Mizutani-san.
I wouldn't say it's because of me.
Oh...  Because of you?
I see.
He can be an idiot,
but don't give up on him.
I was wondering...
Why did Haru-kun run away?
Oh, you mean earlier?
It happens all the time.
He's got a serious brother complex.
Being Yoshida's big brother,
I was wondering what he'd be like.
But he seemed like a nice enough guy.
I need to go shopping.
Bye.
See ya.
Good night.
Shizuku-chan.
Bye-bye.
Keep an eye on Haru for me.
Haru's big brother is a little weird.
Although, the little brother is weirder.
What took you so long?
Why are you always trying
to give me a heart attack?
Did you do it?
Huh?
Did you guys smash the
watermelon together?!
Was he sitting here this whole
time worrying about that?
We didn't.
Oh.
Let go.  You're hurting me.
Y-Your big brother said that
you have a serious brother complex.
I don't!
Why did you run away then?
Because I hate him.
You hate him?  Why?
Just shut up. Stop trying to pry.
Fine.
Dammit.
I thought you got mad and left.
Yeah, I did.
We have watermelons at our place.
Want to smash them?
Hey, I smashed the watermelon, Shizuku.
Next.
Here.
I thought I knew him,
until I realized that I didn't
know anything about him.
Stop trying to pry.
What's behind that scary
look on his face?
Hey, Shizuku.
Sorry about what I said before.
It doesn't matter.
You're always there to save me.
I need to do something for you.
A date.
Huh?
Take me on a date.
Uh...
Okay, I guess...
By the way...
I don't think we're doing this right.
Is this how smashing watermelons works?
Probably.
I may not know the answer
now, but I will eventually.
It's that simple.
Yoshida, you tense up every
time the camera's on you.
It's scary.
A rooster?
That's no fun.
I was hoping to find
fresh eggs for some
homemade pudding topped with meringue.
Now I'm hungry.
Next Episode
Yoshida Family
Matters
Start laying eggs.