Spring...
A warm breeze stirs the cherry
tree branches, and tickles my hair.
It is April...
Wow!
As of today, I'm a first-year
student in high school...
All righty, my wishes came true,
and I got into a co-ed school near my house.
At this moment, my heart is full
of anticipation for my new life!
I wonder what high school's like?
For now, on this first day, with the sky so blue,
and the cherry blossoms in bloom,
I'm somehow getting the feeling that
I'm about to embark on a splendid romance!
"Little Sister"
At least...
That's what I thought...
But it's my first day and I'm already in a bind!
Hey, little girl, you sure are sweet!
You in high school?
Forget about school...
Come have some fun with us!
Wh-Whoa...
wh-what am I gonna do?
I-I'm so scared! S-Somebody!
And since I went to an all-girls' junior high,
I'm not comfortable around guys!
Come on, over here!
Ugh... It's no good...
I'm starting to pass out...
Hey! Knock it off, you guys!
Huh?
Can't you see she doesn't
want to go with you?
Huh!? Who the hell are you!?
Wh-Who...? Saved... me...?
Stand up to us and we'll
make you sorry, damn you!
That's right!
It's too early in the day for this.
Come on, just chill, will you? Big bros...
Oh... but I can't hold on anymore...
I'm passing... out...
Young Master, you forgot this!
Huh? What's up with these guys?
Hey! You guys, I told you not to tag along...
Whoa! Those guys are... R-Run!
Are you all right?
Hey, the kid's passed out.
Who is this kid?
Oh, man, she must've been
scared out of her life.
What should I do?
I can't just leave her like this...
This uniform she's wearing -
it's our school's, right?
Huh? Where am I?
What?
A prince?
You heard me!
These other guys were bugging me,
and he made a dashing entrance!
Yelling, "Knock it off!"
Boy, was he cool! I just know
it was fate that brought us together!
On top of that, he carried me
to the nurse's office when I fainted...
Seriously, how kind and gentle is that?
Oh? Is that why you ditched me this morning?
I was waiting around forever...
Well, I'm glad you're okay.
Sorry, Fu. I never dreamed
anything like that would happen...
But you never saw his face,
and you don't know his name, either, right?
You think you'll ever see him again?
Oh, I'll see him again, I'm sure of it...
I mean, he was wearing our school's uniform.
There's no question he's here at this school...
And it's not like I don't have any clues...
Oh, yeah?
Will we ever meet again? Next time I see him,
I've got to thank him properly...
Hello! I'm going to be sitting here...
so we're neighbors, right?
It's so nice to meet...
Wait, huh? A foreigner?
Not only that, but she's gorgeous!
Wonder if she understands Japanese...
Uh... Um... What is your name...
It's Paula. Paula McCoy.
She speaks Japanese!
Nice to meet you, Paula! My name is...
Oh, no need for you to tell me your name.
Since I'm not gonna bother remembering it.
Huh?
Wh-What kind of attitude is that?
That was just a little too cold...
Pardon me...
Wh-What was that!?
Was that a hand grenade!?
It looked way too heavy to be a toy...
Could it be that she's actually really scary?
Oh! Speaking of scary people!
I almost forgot something important!
It may be important
to search for that prince,
but there's someone else
I've got to hunt down, no matter what!
I've got to find him or else...
All right! All right!
So anyway, just wait till you hear
what happened after, it was awful!
Hey, my bad.
So tell me, what happened after that?
Oh! Really, now!
What's that guy's problem?
This is why I can't stand guys...
Are you all right?
Huh?
Hey, it's her...
I'm so sorry to make you help me like this...
No problem. It's on my way, anyway.
Judging from the color of your tie,
you're a first-year, right?
Uh, yes! Um... And you?
You are an upperclassman, aren't you?
I'm a second-year. If you have
any questions, ask me anything.
You know... I think he looks like
the guy from this morning...
But... No way, right?
The way she's acting, looks like
she doesn't remember me at all.
Oh, well, whatever. No need to make
her feel like she owes me anything.
I'm gonna keep my mouth shut.
But to be honest,
you really saved me!
I'm still not really sure where
the faculty room is and all... And besides...
You've set my mind at ease a little.
See, I went to an all-girls' school for junior high,
so I was a little nervous about going to a co-ed school.
But now I know that there are kind
and gentle guys like you.
Actually, this morning, as well!
A guy from this school came to my rescue...
Oh, really? Well, I'm glad to hear that...
What I'd really like
is to thank him in person,
but the thing is, I don't know
what he looks like or what his name is...
Hey, I know!
You said you were a second-year, right?
Huh? Yeah.
Well, actually, it's both him
and one other person...
There's another second-year student that
I have to find... would you happen to know him?
I've heard rumors that
he's famous at this school...
Famous? Well, what's his name?
Hey, Ichijo! Kyoko's been looking for you!
Thanks! I'll be right there!
So? What was his name?
Ichijo...?
Huh?
Excuse me, but are there any other people
at this school named Ichijo?
No, I'm pretty sure I'm the only one.
Then are you that Raku Ichijo?
That...?
The son of the leader
of the Shuei-gumi yakuzas!
Who, despite having
a drop-dead gorgeous girlfriend,
has a whole entourage
of pretty girls at his beck and call,
and who's rumored to be running the whole school
behind-the-scenes, thanks to his father's authority?
Are you that Raku Ichijo?
Hold up, hold up, hold up!
What kind of rumors are those?
Please don't come near me!
Hey! Then don't tell me that just now...
Just now, the reason you were so nice to me...
That was one of your ploys
to worm yourself into a girl's favor, wasn't it?
How could you!?
I thought you were so nice...
Hang on, hang on!
At least hear a person out...
I have just one thing to say to you!
Don't you dare...
...try to go near my sister again!
Did you see?
N-No...
You'd think you'd have outgrown
bears in high school...
You're so heinous! Heinous, heinous!
You're the enemy of all women!
How was that my fault...?
What's going on, Ichijo?
What was that sound?
Hey, Onodera. Actually...
Sister!
Huh? Haru? What are you doing here?
Sister, don't you worry about a thing!
Now that I'm here,
you're safe, all right? Right? Right?
Huh? Huh?
S-Sister?
My name is Haru Onodera.
I'm Kosaki Onodera's younger sister!
Y-Younger sister?
Yes. So now we're going to be
second-years, huh, Ruri?
I hope I get to be in the same
class as Ichijo again...
Hmm, so the guy she
has a crush on is named Ichijo?
What? Come on... that's really mean, Ruri!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
What were we talking about again?
Huh? Oh, so anyway...
I hear that there's a really scary
upperclassman at your high school, Haru!
They say he's the son of a yakuza...
And his name is Ichijo...
Oh, no, that's terrible!
Wait, what?
Ichijo!? Tell me more about him, will you!?
Now that I've actually met him,
I can see it clearly.
Just as I thought,
this guy is dangerous!
I'll bet he's totally playing my sister...
I've got to protect her!
Hey, that's right. You did mention
having a kid sister the other day...
Please stay away from her!
I'm never going to let you
get your hands on my sister, understand?
Hey! Haru, what are you talking about!?
Sister, open your eyes!
Sister...
You're being deceived!
What's going on?
I've been hearing this commotion...
Huh? Who's this? This girl...
Chitoge...
Wow!
Who is this gorgeous girl?
Is she half-foreign?
Amazing... she looks just like a model!
Hey... could she be
the drop-dead gorgeous girlfriend?
The rumors were all true, after all!
Huh? Kosaki's little sister?
Really? So you have a little sister, Kosaki!
Nice to meet you!
What's your name?
Does he have something on you!?
Huh? Something on me?
Um, what are you talking...
Because otherwise, it doesn't make sense!
A person like you, so drop-dead gorgeous,
so stylish, who seems so likable...
With someone who's
so obviously a loser?
Who looks so shallow
and unpleasant...
It makes no sense at all
that you'd be seeing him!
Hey, hey, hey!
Wh-What...? How could say
such a thing, Haru? Apologize!
I get that you're upset,
but that kind of talk is uncalled for!
Come on, Chitoge, you tell her, too!
I see, so your name is Haru, huh?
You're such a sweet,
good little girl, aren't you, Haru?
My name is Chitoge Kirisaki.
Nice to meet you!
Master Raku!
Would you care to join me
for tea over here?
Whoa! Tachibana!
Wh-What the...?
What's this?
Who might this girl be?
Who is this girl?
And hey, another beauty!
I'm telling you,
stop clinging to me!
Oh, please, where's the harm?
Listen, listen, listen, listen, Master Raku...
Is this girl another one of Ichijo's groupies?
Come now, you don't mind, do you, Master Raku?
Whoa! Cut it out!
No, no... I mean, never mind that...
H-H-How can you just stand
in the middle of the hall
Cut it out!
There's no need to be so bashful!
without a care in the world,
your arms around a guy?
Listen, listen, Master Raku...
Not only that, but he's got a girlfriend!
Doesn't that mean anything to you?
Excuse me?
I see you're still but a mere child.
Love is something that
you must see through to the end.
Even in the face
of such obstacles as girlfriends,
so long as you have love,
there is nothing that you can't overcome!
And so, Master Raku,
now that we're going to be second-years,
isn't it about time you discarded your
outmoded girlfriend, and switched over to me?
I do offer a discount for switching, you know!
Don't talk about me like I'm a used car!
What's going on? Is this person
seriously in love with Ichijo?
Now I'm totally confused...
Haru, Ichijo isn't quite the villain you think he is.
Sister....
I don't know what kind of rumors you've heard,
but rumors are just rumors, okay?
No, you're wrong, Sister.
You're too nice, that's why you see him that way.
After all... after all, I...
After all...
After all, this person got
a look at my underwear!
What kind of underwear
do I have on today again?
Tell me... what does she mean, darling?
It's a misunderstanding!
Save your breath!
What a nightmare. A guy like that
sneaking a peek at my underwear!
And my sister doesn't believe me...
What am I supposed to...
Animal Care – Looking for New Members
Club activities, huh? What should I do
now that I'm in high school?
Hey...
Animal Care – Looking for New Members
There's something called Animal Care!
Animal Care, huh?
Being surrounded by adorable animals
who heal my soul... that might be nice!
Wait.
What's that guy doing here!?
Here you go! Time to eat!
Go on, eat! Hey, good boy, good boy!
This really sucks!
Why do I have to run into him
in a place like this?
Actually, why is he
taking care of animals, anyway?
I'm going home! No way am I
gonna end up in the same club as him...
Oh, man...
I wonder if Onodera's
gonna show up today...
What... what?
It would be just the two of us right now...
And then we could just head home together...
Yeah, right! Well, not that
that would ever happen, but...
You're awful, you know that?
Oh, crap! Did she hear me just now?
Huh? But you're that...
I can't believe you're trying
to make a move on my sister,
when you have such a beautiful girlfriend!
Now there's no doubt in my mind!
You're everything I've heard you are
- a low-life piece of trash!
A person like you...
I will never let you get your hands on my sis–
–ter...
Now that I'm seeing them up close,
those bears are pretty cute.
It's been a while since we took
a bath together, Haru.
Brings back memories, huh?
I guess.
Are you still mad at Ichijo?
Of course I am! He saw my underwear again!
That's twice, you know?
So unbelievable!
I'm never gonna forgive that guy!
I hate myself for even thinking
for a second that he was nice!
You don't have to go that far...
Ichijo is a nice person, you know.
Sure, maybe today
you didn't happen to see it, but...
I don't get it. What makes
you think he's a good person?
Well, I'm not sure
that I can explain what it is...
I guess in a word,
it's how he can be so sweet.
What? What part of that guy is...
Let's see. For example...
He's always thinking about other people, and if
he sees someone in trouble, he can't just stand by.
He stops caring instantly
what's going to happen to him, and...
If it makes that person happy, he can be happy
right along with her from the bottom of his heart...
That's the kind of person he is... Ichijo.
You know, I never asked you,
"what is it that you love about him?"
So anyway! I really think you and Ichijo
could get to be good friends.
Oh, I think I'll pass.
I have no interest in him!
What?
Sister, you're just too nice...
that's why you can't see him for what he is.
Just as I thought, I'll have to protect you...
By the way, what was that you said
on our way home about a prince?
Huh? Oh, right!
You'll never guess, Sister...
Today, I had a fateful encounter, you see!
What?
Welcome home, Young Master.
Jeez. What a fiasco that was today.
Who knew she'd start to hate me
that much... Guess I'm out of luck.
Today I'm just gonna take a bath and crash.
I wonder if I'll see that prince again?
I wonder what grade he's in?
He was tall, so maybe he's a third-year?
I wonder what kind of person he is...
Gentle, and someone you can count on...
Haru!
I just hope I can find him somehow...
Hey, that reminds me!
I almost forgot that I had a precious clue!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
Another bruise there?
Damn that Chitoge, for God's sake... Huh?
Huh?
- Whoa! What is it? Young Master?
- Young Master? What's the matter?
- What's going on, Young Master? Young Master!
My prince... I hope I can find you!
A few days later, Raku found out the truth.
H-Huh? Paula?