Come on, bring it!
It went up!
I'm gonna go show Ushiwaka who's boss!
If you want to beat Wakatoshi-kun,
you're gonna have to beat me, first.
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Karasuno             Shiratorizawa
Episode 03: GUESS-MONSTER
Whoa...
There he is... The Guess Monster.
What do they mean by that?
Is Shiratorizawa's #5 a sleazebag
(gesu), or something?
I-Is he going to try to hit
them in the eyes, or something?
Be careful, Hinata!
That'd be cheating...
Leon-san, nice serve!
Sorry!
Kageyama, get the last!
Stop another one!
Blocking isn't a technique to stop the ball.
Tsutomu, go up straight.
It's a technique to smack down the ball.
Be Courageous Warriors
All right!
When you're able to get a clean block,
it truly is a technique that makes
you feel like the tables have turned.
I'm starting to get into it!
Get the next one!
Don't mind, Kageyama-kun!
Don't, don't mind! Kageyama—
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
Nice receive!
So naïve...
All right!
I'm...
120% today!
How is he able to react like that?
It's not just how he reacts.
In that moment, there
were three possibilities.
Net
First, Kageyama's currently
on the front line,
so it was possible for him to do a dump.
So was he going to dump, or not?
If he wasn't going to dump, he has
Tanaka and Hinata on the front line,
and Azumane and Sawamura on the
back line who he can set to.
And in this case, it went to Hinata,
but there were also various
courses Hinata could have used.
You can see quite a bit when you're up here,
but when you're on the court,
you can get frazzled.
So even if you know which way you want
to go, your body may not move right.
But...
He's able to move.
I guess it's no surprise
that they took a time out.
I totally thought that they were
going to do a back attack just now.
I mean, he totally gave
that other guy a look.
That was a complete fake.
Huh?
Karasuno's setter's pretty good, right?
But that glance was way too
obvious and over the top.
Glances, footwork, and handling...
If Tendo-san figures any of those
things out, you're finished.
Nice block, Satori.
Yup.
Sorry that I'm getting more
attention than you, Wakatoshi-kun.
That's not a problem.
Certain Victory
We're going to cut them off on the next one!
Hinata, we're going to switch
things up! Get this next one!
Right!
Hey, Kageyama, what's wrong with your face?
Nothing's wrong.
You liar!
It's one thing when my spike gets blocked,
but it pisses me off a million times more
when a spike from my set-up gets blocked...
How is their #5
able to continue blocking like that?
Sensei, you remember read blocking, right?
You see where the toss is going
before jumping up to block, right?
Yeah. "Read" in this case doesn't
necessarily mean to read,
but more to understand.
Since you're jumping up
after watching the ball,
there's no danger in the toss tricking you.
Their reaction will be slightly slower,
but if you can cover by using three blockers,
it's the most effective.
We're still in the middle of
practicing this ourselves.
On the other hand, what's
special about their #5's blocks
are his reading and intuition.
He does guess blocking.
"Guess" means to presume something,
and he'll read the attack
before the toss goes up,
and then he'll jump pretty much on intuition.
Guess?!
Of course, there will be times
where his intuition is off,
and he might get in the way of
his team's blocks and receives.
This is definitely a style of blocking
that doesn't work for everyone.
But I think that #5 is so accurate
with his guesses that it's scary.
On top of that, he has a body
that can react to those guesses.
It's better to think that his movements
have no regularity to them.
Don't think too hard and get fooled by them.
Right!
What do we need to do in order
for him not to read our tosses?
Does that mean Kageyama's going to have
to do the crazy feints that Hinata does, too?
That actually sounds pretty
amusing, so why not?
Karasuno           Shiratorizawa
One more, nice serve!
Front!
Sorry, it's short!
It doesn't matter what kind of feints
you try to use against Tendo-san...
So this must be what it means
to have perfect coordination...
Just barely missed me...
Yeah!
I had no idea where the toss was going to go
until he got the spike in.
So you aimed that
to go right over my head
after what I just did.
You must really hate losing.
You guys really are amusing.
Japanese National High School Volleyball Tournament
Chance ball!
I've made a mistake!
One more, one more!
Hup!
Got it!
It's better to think that his movements
have no regularity to them.
Don't think too hard and get fooled by them.
And with opponents like this,
it's best to lead them as far
left or right as possible.
You just don't stop moving, do you?
Karasuno                Shiratorizawa
All right!
All right! We caught up with them!
Hinata, nice kill!
Way to go, Hinata!
There have been setters who I admired for trying
so hard to stop me from reading them...
But that #10's timing sure is fast.
If I'm even one tempo late, I can't reach it.
Were you just expecting us to forget
your "I've made a mistake!" earlier?
Ayup, gesu...
You're talking strangely, Tendo.
Kageyama, one more! Nice serve!
Nice receive!
This is their chance to attack!
One touch!
Got it!
Be Courageous Warriors
Did he just put in a fake?
Or did he just change his mind?
It really seems that conventional logic
doesn't work on Shiratorizawa.
Just what is with #5's blocking?
He's planning on stopping
all of them on his own.
Huh?
Tendo's blocks are basically
blocks used to score points.
He uses his opponent's spikes against them,
and makes them his own points.
But blocking isn't limited
to being done on your own.
The blocking that we're trying to do right now,
blocking in order to connect...
If we can make it work, it'll lead to points.
In any case, depending on the timing,
blocks can actually be
more valuable than spikes.
I see...
Karasuno           Shiratorizawa
Nice receive!
Don't let them get ahead!
Ushijima-san!
If they get their opportunity,
they're not going to stop!
Nice kill, Ushijima!
That was like a blow to
shut up the commoners.
Ushijima! Ushijima! Ushijima!
Ushiwaka's definitely on another level.
In order to stop attacks, blocks evolve.
And in order to break through
blocks, attacks also evolve.
Attacks become diverse by using back attacks,
attacks that get faster, and combinations.
And then by changing how one jumps
and where they're positioned,
blocks shut down attacks.
They think they're at the top,
but they continue to go higher
and higher and keep developing.
Looks like you've learned
a few things, Sensei.
Those are just words.
I'm sure they kept developing
through understanding,
All right!
their fighting spirit,
and unwavering tenacity.
Miraculous super plays will save the team,
but the same can be said
about understanding.
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
Oh?
Hey, it's the normal guy.
All right. Don't let him get to you.
Nice serve!
It's going to fall!
Chance ball! Chance ball!
Damn it... I'm sorry!
A time lag attack?
Huh?
Tsukki!
All right!
Hi. I'm the normal guy.
The time lag attack
may have fooled our wild
beast over there,
but it doesn't work on me.
Pleasure to meet you.
I knew that all the first-years
at Karasuno pissed me off,
but you take the cake.
Thanks.
You piss me off!
Asahi-san, nice serve!
Nice kill, Ushijima!
Please continue thinking.
Be Karasuno's understanding...
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
We'll definitely...
We'll definitely get our chance.
Please put me in. Please put
me in. Please put me in...
Yamaguchi's projecting a tremendous aura.
Huh?
Karasuno           Shiratorizawa
One touch!
Got it!
So annoying...
Chance ball!
Yeah!
That was you, Tsutomu, you idiot!
If you're gonna stare at someone,
at least stare at a girl!
Y-Yes, sir!
Pfft... "Yes."
I don't care if you run into each other!
Go for the damn ball, ya idjits!
And there's the demon coach.
I thought he was pretty quiet today.
Yeah!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
Suga, nice serve!
Leon, up front!
Switch...
...and then...
A synchronized attack!
Yeah!
Nice, Kageyama!
What? What happened just now?
Did the setter hit that?
Those impertinent little...
I guess things haven't changed,
even with the grandson.
That's right. Karasuno's coach
is Ukai-sensei's grandson.
Ukai...
He always did think that
new things meant strength.
I never did like him.
Shiratorizawa             Karasuno
Always relying on the left cannon...
How archaic.
Your team is ridiculous and everyone attacks,
so no one's left to follow up!
There're only a certain
number of things you can do
with these high school teams
that change every year.
Polishing diamonds in the best way possible...
All right!
...is the best possible option.
Washijo-sensei never changes.
Ohira! Ohira
"Simple is best."
He loves height and power,
and is always on the lookout
to gather powerful players.
Leon-kun, nice serve.
Even if they weren't accepted
by the team originally,
if they fit Washijo-sensei's definition of "powerful,"
there won't be a problem.
And then he puts them through hardcore
training to keep them strong.
But you can't call all of them
star players, can you?
Of course not.
Though I'm sure that him getting
someone like Ushijima was a jackpot.
Using a powerful player like
Ushijima as the main attacker,
Ushijima-san!
and making sure that no one gets in his way
probably sums up Shiratorizawa's style.
All right!
Ushiwaka really doesn't stop.
But there are still ways
to turn things around.
Nice receive!
All right!
Karasuno          Shiratorizawa
Nice kill, Tsutomu!
Shirabu-san, nice serve!
Got it!
All right!
Nice, Shoyo!
My heart hurts from all this excitement.
Mine does, too.
As long as I'm here, you're the best!
I could never say something that confident...
But I've gotten to the point
where I can be helpful.
Nice serve.
Their formation broke!
Good!
My chance...
Sorry!
Wakatoshi!
We're gonna stop him!
Yeah!
Good.
I just need
one high toss.
Be Courageous Warriors
Nice kill, Ushijima!
Ushijima! Ushijima!
This is
what it means to be strong.
Keep on breaking them!
What, you say? Their hearts!
Keep on shattering them!
What, you say?
Those blocks?
Nah, their spirits!
I can never read this guy.
He sure is persistent...
That brat with the glasses.
Sensei.
Right.
Apparently, even that serve
isn't enough to stop them.
Yeah.
When they're able to stop ‘em, they can,
and when they can't stop
‘em, they can't! Got it?!
It's true that completely shutting them down,
or breaking through a
three-person block looks cool,
and excites the crowd,
but don't try to finish things.
I'm sure that the rougher things get,
the more you want to finish
things in one shot.
But don't forget to imagine your next plays,
like one touches and rebounds.
All plays are connected.
This doesn't mean you're
supposed to put up your guard.
I know that!
I know I keep saying this,
but even if plays don't lead to points,
they start showing results later.
We're finally doing a five-set match.
It'd be a waste to spend
the whole time dreading
how long you've still got.
Right! Let's do this!
Yeah!
Um...
Would you let me set the timing
for the three-person block?
Shirabu.
Don't forget to pass to Wakatoshi.
Right. Got it.
Why, you little...
Now, now, now...
Nice serve, Tsutomu!
Daichi!
Got it!
Damn it. Their #1, every single time...
Karasuno                 Shiratorizawa
All right!
Daichi-san, nice serve!
Tsutomu!
Right!
Nice receive!
One touch!
Ryu!
He connected it!
Nice timing! Nice one touch!
Keep on connecting!
Ushijima really won't stop.
What's Karasuno's coach so happy about?
They haven't stopped him at all.
Got it!
Chance ball!
Nice kill, Ohira!
Ohira!
Karasuno           Shiratorizawa
Kawanishi, nice serve!
Here I go!
Shirabu-san, nice receive!
He aimed right for the center.
Wakatoshi!
Cage him in!
What's important is the
block's width and timing!
Imagine a wall!
Here we go. Please take it slow.
Ready...
Now!
And the destination
where it breaks through...
is our super libero!
All their plays
are connected!
We're in the final part of this set...
They finally got this important receive up...
It's gotta be... over here!
Seriously?
All right!
Yeah!
They finally got a clean one in.
Total defense.
Now...
Karasuno                 Shiratorizawa
It's finally begun!
Keep on breaking them!
What, you say? Their hearts!
Keep on shattering them! What, you say?
Their spirits, right?
Nah, their will!
They both mean the same thing!
Episode 04: The Halo Around the Moon
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"The Halo Around the Moon."