What was that?
They're after the Aurora!
Wait, that ship...
Get a grip, everyone! We're under attack!
Seal all bulkheads.
Prepare to submerge.
Roger.
Stop!
They've stopped firing.
Ange, Vivian and another unit are
engaging the enemy Para-mails.
Maybe they're trying to protect us.
Do they even know who's fault this is?
For crying out loud...
Hurry, please, Aurora!
Catch!
Get out of my way.
Whoa! Danger!
Go, Bunbunmaru!
Bad girl, Vivi-chan.
Momoka!
Light of Mana!
All bulkheads sealed.
Aurora submerged. Full speed ahead.
That's far enough.
Why are you doing this?
Aren't your friends on that ship?
Why are you attacking them?
Retreat, Chris-chan.
Momoka.
This is attack formation
Stealth Rose Triangle.
Salia...
Ange.
Goodbye.
Tuner of Time
I messed up.
I can't believe I let Salia get me.
They smell like the
roses Mother used to grow.
If this is hell, then
maybe it's not so bad.
Wake up, Angelise-sama.
Good morning.
Where am I?
Your room, Angelise-sama.
My room? Where?
Arzenal?
No.
Your real, true home.
It's well-cleaned and properly maintained.
Just as it was on the day you left.
Then we're in...
Yes.
The Empire of Misurugi.
Embryo...
Real silk!
It's so soft!
I can put my own clothes on.
You mustn't!
You must allow me to take care
of you while we're at the palace.
Then hurry up.
It's getting cold.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm back again...
But why did Salia bring us here?
I don't know.
I was here when I woke up, too.
Goodbye, my ass.
It was just a tranquilizer.
Are Tusk and Vivian safe?
I'm sure they are.
Those two are strong.
You're right.
There you are.
Good.
I would prefer a rifle or a grenade,
but this is better than nothing.
Angelise-sama, what are you...
Planning a raid.
On the man who sent those flowers...
I can't allow that.
You're Embryo-sama's prisoner.
I won't allow you to get out of line.
Embryo-sama, huh?
What happened, exactly?
You loved the commander so much.
Nothing.
I just woke up.
Ange, you fatass!
I got abandoned.
This suits me.
Jill dumped me, and I lost to Ange...
That's not true, Salia.
You simply don't know your own value.
That man saved me.
He made me a new person.
Alektra never needed me in the first place.
No matter how hard I tried,
she never would have vindicated me.
But he...
Your beauty, your strength, your value...
I know them better than anyone.
Would you give me your hand
and help me change this world, Salia?
I found someone I truly needed to protect.
Now, I'm part of Embryo-sama's bodyguard.
I call it the Order of the Diamond Rose.
And I, Salia, am its commander.
Diamond...
Too long.
In other words, you were adrift in the world,
and then a new owner picked you up.
I didn't think you had the courage
to abandon our commander.
Angelise-sama!
I won't let you insult me any more.
Embryo-sama loves me.
Unlike you, who nobody loves at all.
Well, good for you.
Commander!
Ange!
Weak.
You're so weak compared to Salako.
And these names you come up with are abysmal.
And what's with your outfit?
You looked a lot better as Pretty Salian.
Let's go, Momoka.
Yes, ma'am.
Wait!
Where did you go?
Ange!
Sorry, but this is my house.
Mom, let's play hide-and-seek!
No, I want to draw!
Come now, don't fight.
It's Ange-oneesama!
You're right!
Ange-oneesama, when did you get here?
Onee-sama, are you in the Order, too?
Oh my.
Did you all corner Ange-chan?
That's very good.
Ersha.
Embryo Kindergarten?
Yep.
I'm the principal.
I really wanted to bring all
the children from Arzenal here.
Can you believe it?
These children were all dead once.
And then Embryo-san
brought them back to life.
Back to life?
That's not possible,
even with the Light of Mana.
Embryo-san says...
He will make a world where these
children can live free without fear.
I decided to cooperate with him.
I'd do anything to protect these children.
I'd slaughter all the humans.
And I'd kill you, Ange-chan.
Ersha.
Oh no...
Let's go, Momoka.
We need to find Embryo.
Want to come with me?
Chris.
Hey, Chris.
You force yourself to talk to me.
I know you're not interested in me, anyway.
Hilda and the others are angry.
I'm the one that's angry.
They said they'd come help me.
But they abandoned me.
Embryo-kun is different.
He risked his life to save me.
He said he wanted to be my friend.
A true friend.
Um, Angelise-sama...
Who is this Embryo-sama?
Huh? You haven't heard?
Is he a philanthropist? Or a counselor?
God, supposedly.
Huh...
You're useless!
This is Volume Four!
I told you to bring Volume Three!
How could you poison me?
I would never have regained consciousness,
if not for Ojisama!
Don't talk back to me!
Have you forgotten that you're only
alive because Ojisama permitted it?
You lizard bitch!
R-Riza...
Sylvia.
You're here to kill me, aren't you?
You murdered Father, Mother, and Onii-sama!
And now you're here to kill me.
That's right, isn't it?
Go away, you murderer!
Let me talk.
Help me, Ojisama!
Ojisama!
Ojisama?
I found you, Ange!
It's so loud in here.
I'd appreciate if you all could
keep it down while I'm reading.
Embryo...
Truly, books are good.
Contained within is
everything in the universe.
How boring our reality is by comparison.
It's been a while since I've met
someone more entertaining than my books.
Embryo.
Him?
I apologize for being so rough.
I wanted to speak with you.
I asked Salia and the
others to bring you here.
Come.
You must have questions, too.
Angelise-sama...
If you don't mind, I'd like to
be alone with her for a while.
You mustn't.
This woman is dangerous.
Salia...
Ange has been captured.
Vivian and Tusk are missing.
And this happened because
they went out guns blazing...
You just have to laugh, don't you?
If not for those girls protecting us,
this ship would have sunk.
I don't care.
Without the Villkiss, Libertus is impossible.
That's why we couldn't let Ange leave.
I can't believe that boy betrayed us.
I screwed up.
I should have trained Ange to be more loyal.
What's the Burn Princess up to?
She came back only to leave a mess.
She must have had a
reason to escape the ship.
Our ship might be in danger.
What are we going to do now?
We can't do the Libertus thing
without the Villkiss, can we?
Then we'll just have to bring Ange back.
Where are we going?
What is this?
It's Aura.
The sacred first DRAGON.
He's what Riza and
the other DRAGONs seek.
That's Dracunium.
All the Mana in this world is
created by Aura's consumption of Dracunium.
You're using the sacred
DRAGON Aura as a generator?
I couldn't just abandon humanity.
But thanks to Riza's intel,
we successfully ambushed the DRAGONs,
and collected a vast amount of Dracunium.
Now, I can continue with my other plans.
Let Aura go.
Now.
Oh my.
You've sided with the DRAGONs, huh?
I'm your enemy.
You killed my brother.
You tried to kill Tusk.
And you've killed so many DRAGONs.
That's enough to make you my enemy.
What if I refuse?
Oh?
He's big.
I wonder if the Villkiss can carry him...
Do you feel better now?
You ought to stop wasting your time.
You...
What are you?
Alektra must have told you about me.
God...?
I don't care for that crude expression.
I'm the Tuner.
Tuner?
Yes. I tune the sound of the world.
What do you hope to achieve by killing me?
I'm going to destroy this
world and free the Norma.
Why?
Why...?
Do the Norma really want to be freed?
It's true that there isn't a place for
them in this world, as they can't use Mana.
But instead, they're given the
task of fighting the DRAGONs.
All anyone needs for contentment
and peace of mind is a place and a role.
To think for one's self and to live
for one's self is an enormous burden.
What are you...
Oh?
What have you done to me?
Your destructive impulses
arise from your anxiety.
You were robbed, deceived,
and betrayed so many times.
You don't know where to turn.
Sh-Shut up!
That's why you become afraid
and bare your fangs.
I can free you from your anxiety.
Love.
Peace of mind.
Friendship.
Trust.
Belonging.
I can provide everything you want.
So abandon everything and accept me.
Abandon everything you're wearing.
You're strong.
You can trust me.
Good girl.
Golden hair and flaming eyes.
Pale lips and smooth skin.
Firm, ample breasts and pink...
You're beautiful.
Not even Venus or Aphrodite could compare.
Impossible...
Give me anything?
I'm not empty enough to be content
with whatever you decide to give me.
I don't care if you're God
or a Tuner or anything else.
I'll kill you until you die,
and then I'll destroy the world.
So dramatic!
I may have lived just to meet you.
For all these thousands of years...
Commander, it's Hilda.
I'd like to talk to you about
our strategy going forward.
We have to go back.
You can stay here, Alektra.
Forever.
No.
I can't.
I'll be ruined.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Embryo-sama.
Next Episode
It's the preview, Rosalie.
Finally, I can vent!
They feed me laxative, they make me talk
like an old fart, and they treat me like crap!
I almost died.
I want more RosaChri scenes!
ChriRosa, not RosaChri.
Soul of God
What? Oh, right...