"Maki-chan"?
How do you write that?
Ma
The first characters from the words for "truth"
Ki
Name: Maki
Father: Gouda Yutaka
Mother: Yuriko
Eldest Daughter
and "hope."
Wow! That's a great name.
Is her hair still sticking up?
Yeah, she looks like a Saiyan.
I want to see Maki-chan.
Yeah, she's growing really fast,
so you should come soon.
Really?
Is she all chubby?
Yeah, she is.
I'm looking forward to seeing her.
Okay.
Chubby, huh?
She's all chubby.
Name: Maki
Father: Gouda Yutaka
Mother: Yuriko
Eldest Daughter
Maki...
Do you know what month this is?
It's February.
In February, there's something
known as Valentine's Day.
It's the day girls give boys they like chocolate.
The day's almost here!
glare
Yep!
My Chocolate
Red, pink, and brown...
You should watch where you're going.
I wonder what kind of chocolate
Yamato-san will give you.
You think she'll give me chocolate?
Why wouldn't she?
I can't wait!
What's this,
a banzai pose?
I've never gotten real chocolates from a girl.
I've gotten obligation chocolates, but...
Here, have some chocolate.
Neighbor:
Izumi-san
Back in my younger days,
plenty of kids were like you.
You're so generous every year. Thank you.
Kindergarten
Suna gets chocolate every year.
Every year, I think I won't get any,
but I still wonder if I might.
Junior High
And then, I'm always let down.
Gouda
So far, that's how Valentine's Day
has gone for me.
But this year...
I think Yamato-san will give you
something really amazing.
You think so?
Why wouldn't she?
Would she?
Why are you so happy?
Well, I've never gotten chocolate
from a girl who liked me before.
You mean a girl who really likes you.
Really
A girl who really likes me!
Likes
Me
Oops, if I set my expectations too high,
Yamato might feel pressured.
I'll just act like it isn't a big deal.
Good call.
Though, you're doing a banzai pose.
So, this year, I'll actually get chocolate
from a girl who likes me?
I can't wait.
Wait, I was thinking of having
our second kiss on Valentine's.
Get my chocolate, say thank you, then...
The second kiss...
Koizumi Girls' Academy
Rinko...
Please! I'm begging you!
Please teach me how to make chocolate.
It's for Valentine's Day, right?
Yeah!
I've never made anything sweet in my life,
and I don't even have the equipment.
Why not make it together, at my place?
I'm making something for Takeo-kun, anyway.
You're a lifesaver! Thanks!
Having a boyfriend must be nice.
They look like they're having fun.
We don't have anything planned.
We want to make some for ourselves, too.
Okay, let's all make chocolate
at my place, on the 13th.
Really? Let's do that!
Then we'll buy the ingredients.
Takeo-kun...
Hey!
The wind's strong today.
Is it?
Huh?
Just now, you were my shield.
I love her.
I don't really have much cash on me today.
Let's just buy something to drink
at the food court, and chat.
Sure.
Is she low on cash because of Valentine's Day?
Yamato, you don't have to try so hard.
I'm fine, as long as I get something.
Takeo-kun,
on February 14th, are you—
I'm free.
Crap.
She actually, didn't say anything specific.
Oh, I was just about to ask if you were free.
I love her!
I'll go throw these away.
That was close.
I have to be careful not to pressure her.
You totally did.
It's almost Valentine's,
so there are lots of limited-edition
chocolates on sale!
Oh, right, Valentine's is coming up.
You have no shame...
The limited-edition chocolates
are really something.
They come in beautiful colors and shapes.
The packaging is cute, too.
Two-thousand yen?!
It costs that much for this little?
I bet they use really good
cacao beans or something.
They're just so beautiful.
I want them for myself.
I see...
This year, I've seen pistachios a lot.
I don't need anything expensive.
I wonder if that's trendy right now.
You can even give me chocolate
that didn't turn out okay.
I'll be waiting, Yamato.
Please! I'm begging you, Takeo!
Can we hang out with Yamato-san's
friends on February 14th?
February 14th?
That's Valentine's Day.
I know.
I seriously know.
But that's why...
We've never gotten chocolates
on Valentine's Day!
I only remember one, in kindergarten,
when the mom of a girl who rode
the same bus gave me one!
At least you got some once!
Yeah.
I don't want to be sitting at home, alone,
wondering if I'll get some this year!
Nanako's saying she'll give
me some that's handmade.
Man, and I don't like sweet stuff.
I just feel like I'm gonna be all
alone again this year...
Aren't you guys over-relying on Takeo?
He wasn't able to spend Christmas
alone with his girlfriend, either.
You should just let this go.
Ri...
Right...
You're right.
I'm fine.
I'll ask Yamato.
What?
Takeo...
Thanks, though, Suna.
You do-gooder.
Thank you.
I can get chocolate from Yamato.
True Love
That's enough for me.
On Valentine's Day, Takeo-kun's friends
want to have fun with all of us.
Is that okay?
Huh? Sure.
We're fine.
Not like we have a date or someone we're after.
Oh!
Then why not give the chocolates we
make on the 13th to the boys?
Oh, nice idea.
Sounds fun!
Let's do that.
I'll be doing my own thing with Osamu.
Yeah, yeah.
The Hill on the East
Takeo fell out the window!
He was doing back extensions out the window,
and fell out when he tried
to open a new message.
No way! What was he thinking?
Boys are so stupid.
Uh, is he okay?
Yeah, no kidding!
Takeo, I'm glad you're okay!
Sure.
Well, it went like that, and I was fine.
But next time, please grip my legs firmly.
Sorry.
Yeah, sorry.
Man, you're amazing, Takeo.
It's okay.
Your cell phone's amazing, too.
No, I mean we're okay for Valentine's.
Huh?
Yay!
Yamato-san's a really nice person...
I see... They're happy.
Of course they would be.
Yamato Rinko
Subject: It's Okay
Can we decide the location?
Thank you, Yamato.
Gorgeous Valentine
Chocolate Recipes
Cupcake
Gateau Chocolat
Cream Puffs
Cookies
Gateau Chocolat
Valentine Chocolate Sweets to Make Your Loved One
Melt-in-Your-Mouth Chocolate Panna Cotta
Hey, how long do I have to keep stirring this?
My arm's getting tired.
Nanako, maybe you aren't cut out for this.
I can't believe you didn't know
how to separate egg whites.
I'm surprised you'd consider
trying handmade chocolate.
Well, I wanted to show off for Osamu.
Want me to do it?
No, I'll do it.
If others do it for me, there's no point.
You're right.
Rinko, look.
Is this about right?
Yeah, I think that's good.
Let's spread it and cut shapes.
Oven         Preheated
It's pretty fun when you know
you're giving it to a guy.
Do you have anyone in mind?
Oh, I dunno.
Well, do you think they'll like
getting chocolates from us?
Yeah,
I wonder how it feels, getting chocolate
from a girl you don't really like.
Maybe they'll think it's creepy
that it's handmade.
Takeo-kun and I won't let that happen!
Yeah, Rinko will get mad at them!
Valentine's Day, huh?
In kindergarten, there was some
chocolate in Suna's bike basket...
Sunakawa Makoto
Who's it from?
No idea... There's no name.
To: Sunakawa-kun
I don't need chocolates in return,
so please like me.
There was a letter and everything.
I remember thinking, "It must be
from a girl who likes him..."
For this year's Valentine's Day, love is in the air.
It's your turn to give love, Sis.
February 14th!
It's a great day!
It's a good day to get chocolate.
It isn't too cold or too hot,
so the chocolate won't melt. It's perfect!
You're stacking your hopes way too high.
Wow, you never disappoint!
What do you do with all that?
I guess I accept them.
If there are names on any, I just return
the favor on White Day. That's it.
That's it?
Yeah, that's it.
Really?
Well, I can't really imagine a situation
where it'd go any further than that.
I guess some people start dating when they click.
Unlike you, I've never clicked with any girl.
I see.
February 14th
I remember him saying it was a bother before.
He said girls talked behind my back, too.
I see.
This is the place.
I got a text saying they're already here.
Takeo-kun!
Hi.
Been a while!
Please stay where you are.
Hey, since it's Valentine's Day,
we made these yesterday.
They're chocolate cookies.
Here, Takeo-kun.
Thanks.
Here, Sunakawa-kun.
Thank you.
Wai...
Wait!
C-Can you give them out so that it's like
one person's giving them to another?
Yeah, not like you're just distributing...
Huh? What's up with that?
What're they talking about?
Well, I know how they feel.
That's a no-go?
Well, sure, why not?
Oh, then...
Th-Thank you.
Thanks so much!
When I get home, I'm gonna brag to my parents.
I'm so happy.
They're super happy.
I'm glad we made them.
Yeah.
They're even talking about their parents.
It's delicious.
Takeo-kun, you shouldn't eat
that in the restaurant.
Shh.
I love her.
Let's order something!
We ordered drinks already.
Order more. Let us treat you today.
Huh, why?
That'd be bad.
It's to thank you for what you did.
I guess they've given this
a lot of thought, too.
What about you, Takeo-kun?
Sure.
Hot Chocolate
Chocolate...
Chocolate?
No! That isn't what I meant!
I can't let Yamato guess how much I'm
looking forward to the chocolate.
It'd stress her out.
I...
I'll have water!
Huh? Like Perrier?
Just mineral water!
What about you, Sunakawa-kun?
Is the chocolate in her bag?
Is something wrong with my bag?
Choc—
Right, it's chocolate brown.
It's just like yours. Only a different color.
Whew, that was close.
Cho-co-late...
Rock-paper-scissors!
I lost again!
Cho-co...
Wow, Takeo-kun!
You're scooping up all the chocolate!
I'm having so much fun,
it's hard to hide my excitement.
Dude, you aren't hiding it at all.
What do you want to do next?
Where should we go?
It'll be my very first chocolate
from a girl who likes me!
What time is it?
Thanks for everything.
That was super fun!
I was really happy we got chocolate, too!
We had fun, too.
Really?
Um, can we hang out, even if Takeo
and Yamato-san aren't coming?
Huh?
Sure...
Sure, right?
Sure, why not?
Yeah, let's hang out.
Yeah!
You're that happy?
Okay, let's swap contact info, then.
This turned out well.
Great.
Yamato...
I'll walk you home.
Chocolate!!
Oh, I'm in a bit of a hurry today.
You go on ahead, Takeo-kun.
Later!
Today was so much fun!
Bye-bye!
Bye, guys!
Huh? You're going home, Rinko?
Bye!
Later!
We're going this way.
Thanks!
Did I get chocolate?
No, I didn't...
Takeo, you can't go through there.
Takeo, that's the wrong way.
I'm home.
That isn't your home.
Maybe, if you're already dating, you don't
bother giving each other chocolates?
She's always giving me things.
Maybe this time, there isn't anything.
Take,
Izumi-san's granny said this is for
you because it's Valentine's.
When you see her, thank her.
Okay.
I see.
Maki, your brother couldn't get any
chocolate from the girl he likes.
I guess it just might be how things are...
That could be it.
But I wanted some.
I wanted chocolates from Yamato...
Is something wrong with my bag?
Right, it's chocolate brown.
I should have just asked her to give me some.
It's my fault for not telling her I was
really looking forward to it.
Here, Takeo-kun.
Huh?
Wait... Chocolate!
I did get chocolate!
I did!
She was so casual about it,
I didn't realize she was giving me chocolate!
She must have made it the same as the
rest, so no one would feel awkward.
Crap!
My very first chocolate from a girl who
likes me and I didn't savor it!
Idiot!
I didn't savor it!
I just ate it!
Take!
Simmer down!
You'll wake Maki!
Wait...
Try to remember what it tasted like!
Delicious!
I didn't realize she was giving me chocolate,
so I didn't thank her properly!
I bet they use really good
cacao beans or something.
They're just so beautiful.
I want them for myself.
Suna!
I want to get Yamato limited-edition chocolates!
Come with me to the department store!
Oh, you're up there.
I'm coming down right now!
Sure, but it's already closed,
so we should wait till tomorrow.
Shut up, Take!
Guess he isn't listening.
Yamato, thank you.
A box?
Wait, it's Yamato.
Oh, thank goodness you're here, Takeo-kun.
I wasn't sure how I'd get the doorbell.
Here's your Valentine's Day chocolate.
It was so big, I had to figure out the box.
Since it's Valentine's, I wanted to
make something really special.
I got in over my head,
so I made a lot of mistakes.
I was so nervous.
I've never messed up tempering chocolate,
even in elementary school.
I decorated it in a big hurry just now.
I wasn't sure I'd get it done in time today,
but I'm glad I did.
Good for you
But you gave me chocolate earlier.
Earlier?
No, that was just a group thing.
This is special.
Special...
For both you and me.
Oh, hello, Yamato-san.
Oh, good evening.
How's Maki-chan doing?
She's growing every day.
She's taking a bath with her daddy now.
I'll come to hold her soon.
You're welcome anytime.
Okay!
I'm really glad I got to give this to you today.
Okay, I'll get going!
Bye-bye!
O-Okay.
Th-Thanks!
Thank you, Yamato.
overwhelmed
Thank you for giving me chocolate.
Yamato!
Thank you!
I love you.
Wow!
For Takeo-kun.
Thank you for falling in love with me.
I love you.
Rinko.
My very first chocolate from
a girl who likes me!
Thank you.
Delicious!
Sweet!
Take, shut up!
Delicious!
Delicious.
Master, here's my obligation chocolate.
Oh, thanks, Saijou.
Here, you can have one, too, Sunakawa.
Thanks.
Later.
I think she was being considerate
by waiting till the day after.
I see.
She's a nice person.
I think everyone who falls
for you is a nice person.
All the girls who ever asked Suna out
had been talking about me behind my back.
And that's why he turned them all down.
But there must've been someone
who wasn't doing that
Sunakawa Makoto-sama
I don't need chocolates in return,
so please like me.
among the girls who gave him chocolate.
The Letter and Me
Next time: The Letter and Me.