Wonderful, simply wonderful!
Corner her, no matter what!
Yes, sir!
Karen has surpassed the
boundaries of the human race.
Gee, they're so persistent.
Shit!
Take off!
Come out! Great Genie!
Karen's data... under assessment.
Got to move out.
Damn it...
No, no. The Alpha engine.
Dead, they are all dead.
Got it. I'll come tomorrow.
Dead, this one is dead.
This one, too.
Here it is.
Phew, it's done.
I can't fire inside the room.
Be calm.
Calm down.
You're just bothering me too much!
Are you a stalker or something?
Stop following me!
Oh, that's it.
Just stop it!
Oops, it's so hard to keep myself calm.
According to Dr. Shasiem,
the first machine having its own intelligence
was X11, one of Xaxa's products.
X11 was a domestic companion robot designed for parents
who had lost their children.
The machines began their attack on humans
five years ago, on Christmas day.
Human society was destroyed in just five years
and machines with intelligence
began to dominate the world.
Dr. Shasiem urged the world to
destroy the machines,
but nobody agreed.
And town after town was
attacked and destroyed.
Dr. Shasiem organized a resistance group
called "Eleven" to defeat the machines.
Every I hear a gunshot somewhere, and someone dies.
Once we see death every day,
I don't know why, but we no longer fear it.
Instead, I wake up in the morning,
thinking "thank goodness, I'm still alive."
Eating breakfast, taking a shower—
those things have become more important.
Eleven
What is it?
Didn't we have a promise that
robots never gun down
humans in reserve areas.
You are right.
You know, machines fired their
guns at a girl for real...
Your side had begun subversive
acts against the machines.
Give the resistance activities some slack.
So many of us are gunned down every day.
Those humans who attempt
to resist have potential.
It is a program of evolution.
You're right. This is all about evolution.
You are an accomplice.
Right again,
but no destruction in the
reserve areas, okay?
I will convey your message.
In order to restore beautiful oceans and mountains,
we must thin out the humans.
Only then can we create a society
where machines are in control.
Yes, I agreed to that part.
But all that was assuming the
machines evolved correctly.
There are bound to be
errors in any evolution.
Is that not true of both
humans and machines?
Yup, I think so.
You know that.
You wanted to become
human, after all.
And you let the machines
evolve in that direction.
You're becoming bad humans,
aren't you not?
It wasn't my intention
to wipe out the human race and
create a purely machine world.
Understood.
Hey, old man!
Huh?
Gimme that one kilogram beef chuck, will ya?
Thank you for the business.
I love this cut of meat.
Damn, I bet those machines
can't taste anything.
They want to copy whatever we do.
It's been a while. How's everything with you?
Not too bad...
I guess.
Don't push yourself too hard, though I guess
there's no point in telling you that.
Have you received it?
Yes, I have.
Prime Kobe Beef.
Kind of disappointed to think
the machines'd eat these.
Gimme some of them.
I'll wrap them for you later.
Salmon?
No, it's an underwater action-suit.
It inflates with air.
You can shrink it, too.
Take it.
What?
Is this a joke?
They really want you to join Eleven.
You must be Karen.
You must be Xiaogang.
Nice to meet you.