My little sister, Umaru, is renowned for her beauty.
Yeah, that's enough of that.
You're staying there?
Wait, today's Saturday, right?
Yeah. I'll be back tomorrow night.
But it's your day off!
This is why you're a corporate slave
to a wicked company that steals your soul.
Our deadline's right around the corner.
Also, I'll get some time off in exchange.
Summer vacation's over, so even though
I won't be around, you better not stay up too late.
Sure.
Big Brother...
is totally gone!
I'm free, FREE I say!
My night is just getting started!
Big Brother always goes
to sleep before midnight, so...
Go to bed already, or I won't
be able to wake up tomorrow!
But this is the time to burn through all my games!
I just never seem to have enough time!
This is a bulldozer. It will protect you.
Woo-hoo! That's super rare!
Oh, no. I'm going to wake up Big Brother!
He always gets mad, so I just acted out of reflex.
Do you know what time it is?!
Oh, yeah! Big Brother said...
I made you some breakfast.
It's stir-fried bell peppers...
Jeez...
Hey, dammit!
Now THIS is good food!
Stop eating cup noodles so late at night!
Don't drink all the soup!
Late-night potato chips and cola sure hit the spot!
It's late, so keep your voice down!
Quit eating those potato chips!
Stop chugging it!
But now, no one can get mad at me.
I have everything in the palm of my hand!
Today, Umaru shall be held down by NO ONE!
This is a world where nights are long and glorious!
But, I thought it was 1:00 AM!
Sure enough, time flies at this hour.
Time to check what late-night anime are on!
It's morning. Get up, Umaru!
Hng... what? It's morning already?
Huh?
I stayed up late, so I slept in more than usual!
What the heck?!
I've burned through 16 hours!
What are you doing outside?
Huh? I thought if I went out, I could
get back some of what I'd burned through.
"Burned through"?
It's dangerous to be out at night.
Hurry up and get back inside!
I'm not sure what's going on, but... I'm home.
Yup. Welcome back!
Well, let's go, Umaru!
What are you talking about, Big Brother?
It's "attendance optional," right? No one's gonna go!
Plus, it's still September! It'll be hot! You go by yourself.
Oh, really...?
Well, the landlord might find that a little strange.
Like, "Umaru is such a nice girl,
so I thought for sure she'd come."
My, I'm glad to see some youngsters showing up.
As you can see, my back is giving me some problems...
Please, just rest a while.
Okay, Big Brother... let's go home.
Wait up!
Huh?
The heck? There aren't even that many of them.
Hya! Hya!
Hya!
Ebina?
Ah! T-Taihei and Umaru! Good morning.
So you're here too, huh?
I-I only just got started.
Great job, Ebina. You've already pulled all those?
Ah! Well, back home in Akita,
reckon I... I mean, I'm used to this!
You're a world apart from Umaru...
Anyway, I'm glad you're both here.
Honestly, I was a little lonely on my own.
Y-yeah. I bet.
Looks like it's hard for her to go running off now.
Say, why don't we do this together?
O-okay!
Um... so, should I cut these with a sickle?
Ah! I think it'd be best to pull them by hand.
You have to pull them by the roots
or else they'll grow back.
Hya!
Okay, well, here goes...
The heck? This is... kind of fun!
Giant weed spotted dead ahead!
That must be the middle boss!
One, two...
Hey, are you okay?
Big Brother! I quit! I'm going home!
You can if you want.
Sorry for dragging out here in this heat.
You're not hurt, are you?
Hya! Hya!
I can do this a little longer.
Ebina, let me help you.
O-okay!
We finished up pretty fast, huh?
Yes! It feels like we've really done something here.
Ebina, your face is all red.
Are you having a heatstroke?
N-no, I'm not!
Are you really okay?
I-I super really am!
Oh?
Well, how about we all treat ourselves
by getting something cold to eat?
Ooh! Great idea, Big Brother!
O-okay. Thank you very much.
A soccer match?
My school shall be holding it this month.
Huh?
I totally forgot...
This is why I must practice!
What was that move just now?!
Potato Catch!
Stop kicking your food!
It's just something I do at home sometimes,
the Potato Catch...
You're quite good at ball games, yes? Please, teach me!
Sylphyn and I are always battling each other,
but the soccer match will be class vs. class.
This might make it easier to talk to her at school.
You think you can keep up with my training regimen?
Note: Osu! Is commonly used in martial arts circles as a way of not only
agreeing, but to also show determination.
OSU! Yes, Ma'am!
TSF!
Don't watch the ball. Instead,
see the trajectory of where the ball is GOING.
Understood!
Mentality is a big part of sports.
You have to visualize you've already won.
When you take your shot,
the ball should spin like a bullet...
like you're blasting it with a laser!
The ball is your best friend...
The ball is your lover!
Save your stamina for when you'll need it.
Take some breaks during the game. Rest is important.
But if I rest, I will have points detracted.
Soccer is a team sport.
Just take your break and trust in the others!
I...
I wanted to be at the same school,
in the same class as you, UMR.
Th-the people in your class are good at soccer too.
Now take what I've taught you and go WIN!
Yes! Indeed!
So, these are the uniforms we'll all be wearing...
Kirie!
I will protect Umaru... I will protect Umaru...
I WILL protect Umaru!
I'm not feeling very confident.
Ebina!
You'll be fine.
I wish I was on the same team as you.
Huh? Speaking of...
Our uniforms are different.
All right, let's get this match underway!
Everyone, take your places.
Wait, who are these people?
Most of them aren't even in our class!
Uh, well...
They split up our classes
when they were making the teams.
The students were getting too fired up about it
being class vs. class, so they scrapped the idea.
They tried to balance out the teams, and made the
person with the best grades in PE the leader.
The person with the best grades is the leader?
Wait, don't tell me...!
Huh? Your leader hasn't gotten here yet?
Here I am!
Shapaaaaaaan!
She's standing on some balls
and sliding around on them?!
It's like she's water skiing!
Shbwaaa!
I have trained quite extensively!
It is through soccer that I shall defeat Umaru!
Why is this happening?
Okay, it looks like it's almost time for kickoff.
This match will be between Arayada High's Team T...
and their opponent, Team U!
And there's the whistle!
Whoa! Sylphyn has shot forward!
See the trajectory of where the ball is GOING.
Shbwaaa!
Indeed!
Now THAT'S fast!
Her form is all over the place,
but her power is remarkable!
The time is now:
Canzone Sylphyn Bullet Shoot!
Laser Beam!
It's so fast! Is this a done deal?!
Huh?
Kirie?!
This is... a misdirection!
Kirie has changed the ball's trajectory
and sent it straight to Umaru.
That was awesome!
Okay, we're on the offensive!
I wanted to fight alongside Sylphyn,
but still... I'm going to give this all I've got!
The ball...
I can see its trajectory!
Umaru and Sylphyn are locked in a heated battle!
I'm not sure what the caption at the bottom there
means, but is that a universe I see forming?!
Oh, no! I've had to deal with
so many surprises that now I feel weak!
Indeed!
GOAL!
The first point of the game goes to Team T!
Sylphyn pulled it off all on her own, and despite
how far she ran, she's not breathing heavy at all!
I... I pushed myself a bit too far.
That play just now took a lot out of me.
Regardless, I must score another point!
S-Sylphyn! Wait!
Team U has rallied around Umaru
and is holding their own against Team T!
Meanwhile, Sylphyn has turned
Team T into a one-man show!
Kirie! Just do it!
U-Umaru is cheering me on!
Take... Take THAT!
This shot has given the ball a strange gyration!
But will it hit net?!
Later, the judge who witnessed this mysterious
incident explained it as follows:
Yeah, I'd never seen anything like it.
Normally, a ball strikes
and then rebounds like this, right?
But in this case...
The ball hit a sort of soft obstruction,
resulting in a motion nothing short of miraculous.
No one could have predicted
what the ball would do next! Put simply...
It scored a picture-perfect goal against Team T.
It's an OWN GOAL! That's as good as any!
It's not "good" at all!
I shan't allow you to score!
What turn of events is this?
Team U is starting to pick up the pace!
How can the other team keep this up?
D-don't tell me...!
Yes, they're in the zone!
Team U has reached that ultimate
state of focus known as "the zone"!
(For more about this "zone," please see
whichever sports manga is applicable.)
But how? How can there be such
a difference between our teams?
At this rate, defeat is certain!
I practiced so hard, and even
received instruction from... UMR!
Soccer is a team sport.
Tanabe! Take a wide right!
Huh? O-okay.
Daimoji! Cover Sakura a bit so she can rest.
U-understood.
Ebina!
I'm counting on you!
O-okay.
What's going on?
Suddenly, they're moving a lot more coordinated!
U-Umaru?
This fight is ON!
TSF!
And time is up!
Team U came from behind for the win!
Sylphyn...
You were great, Sylphyn!
How did you fire off that "Bullet Shot"?
But, I mean, we lost...
You scored two points against
Umaru's team, and that's amazing!
Plus, your coaching in the second half was fantastic!
You even remembered all our names, right?
Well... yes...
Please teach us soccer sometime!
Yes, indeed!
And so, the soccer match came to a close...
We'll be having a volleyball tournament soon.
I certainly hope we can train together again!
...and the next ball match was already
right around the corner.
Hey! Let's all walk home together!
Y-you're that girl from the class next door, uh...
I'm Haruka! C'mon, let's go!
Hey! I don't even know you,
so stop talking like you're my friend!
C'mon, don't sweat the details!
Jeez... well, fine.
I swear... Haruka is always making friends
with that dazzling smile of hers.
Making friends with a simple greeting
like that sure would make things easier, huh?
But, I mean, it is what it is, right?
Even asking someone to hang out
is way too much pressure!
What if you ask and they say no?
You'll be heartbroken, and you won't even have a friend!
Say, let's walk home together!
You're being WAY too dramatic!
If that sort of thing holds you back,
you'll just regret it later.
Did you have lots of friends?
Kirie, you and Umaru made some
awesome combo plays at the soccer match!
N-no, I wouldn't say that...
Sylphyn, do you understand this question?
Yes, indeed!
It seems like people are talking to Kirie and Sylphyn
a lot more after the soccer match...
Maybe I should try talking to people too.
Huh?!
I-I'm embarrassed for some reason.
Also... what would I do if they're not interested?
Oh. I've always been the one
that other people talk to first...
I wonder if Kirie has club activities...
She wasn't in her class, so I think so.
Maybe if I joined a club,
I could get good at sports like you.
Are you thinking about the soccer match?
Yes. I made so many mistakes...
Still, Sylphyn was kind enough to pass the ball to me.
It was a lot of fun!
I thought about talking to Sylphyn after that,
but she said she had to talk to a friend and just left.
Ebina, you've asked Kirie
to have lunch with you before, right?
Weren't you afraid she'd say "No"?
Yes. I was embarrassed and a little unsure...
But I felt I'd regret it if I didn't try!
Umaru?
I... I'm going to look for Sylphyn, and-
Um! Our tests are coming up, so...!
Ah! Um, they're cleaning the pool today,
so club activities are...!
Say, how about the four of us walk home together?
Y-you certainly are asking a lot.
B-but, fine, I have no objections!
Uh... Yes, YES!
Ah, it's Umaru!
Huh. So those four are friends?
And here we go! Indeed!
Please calm yourself, Sylphyn.
So, where should we go?
What do you say we get some crepes?
Sounds great!
Umaru, this is serious! Our anime has started up again!
Jeez, just relax, Big Brother.
I didn't expect you to be so calm...
I... I CAN HAVE MY OWN THOUGHTS ABOUT STUFF
AND THE STUFF I THINK ABOUT IS MINE AND STUFF!
You're the one who needs to relax.