Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm totally fine.
Hey!
I can hear it... that sound.
Miuna! Don't rush off!
Hikari, look.
What is that?
Miuna! Come back!
Beyond that is...
It was a mysterious sound.
Like grains of sand
scraping against each other...
Like Manaka-san's heart pounding...
Like it was hitting waves.
It's Shioshishio...
Episode Eighteen:
Shioshishio
It's so quiet.
Of course. Everyone's asleep.
Yeah.
If everyone was wandering
around like sleepwalkers,
it'd be creepy.
This is Shioshishio...
Where Hikari, Kaname-san, Chisaki-san...
and Manaka-san lived.
But...
Is this okay?
Yeah, I think so.
The light is on.
Apparently with this,
they can find out all sorts of things,
like the salt density and
the flow of the tide.
Miuna!
It's not really like this.
Huh?
Let's go look for Manaka.
Old man Hayakawa...
I wonder if he was trying
to guard the place.
Even though we were told
that during the hibernation,
we should be relaxing at our own houses.
His back's gonna hurt when he wakes up.
He's just sleeping.
Huh?
Yeah, he's just sleeping.
Once he wakes up,
he'll be back to normal.
Yeah, back to normal.
This was the place I
always dreamed of...
And yet...
What are you so scared of?
Huh?
I told you, they're just hibernating!
It's rude to everyone if you
keep looking so surprised!
Hikari...
Do you think that all of
them are dead or something?!
Hey, Hikari!
Sorry...
Hikari...
Do you mind if I go home for a bit?
Huh?
I'm going to go calm down
before we look for Manaka.
At this rate,
I'll be too worked up and I have
a feeling I'll embarrass myself.
That's possible. I don't have
any faith that I won't.
We'll be back as soon as possible,
so could you wait here?
Okay.
Don't go anywhere.
This is my first time being
in Shioshishio, but...
For Hikari and Kaname,
this is probably a Shioshishio
they don't know either.
She doesn't mean anything by it.
I know.
Hey, they really are
just sleeping, right?
Hikari...
It's just hibernation, right?
Uroko-sama and the adults
weren't lying, were they?
If that's the case, why'd we wake up?
You're right...
I'm just being selfish.
What?
Miuna's birth mother was
from the sea, right?
I wanted her to think it was pretty.
Miuna's mom's...
Our Shioshishio.
I'm home.
The world I always imagined.
The world I didn't know...
With roads I didn't know,
and people I didn't know.
Yesterday was a storm, today is a lull.
What will the sea be like tomorrow?
What do the two sea slugs wonder?
"The light wavers, pepepu."
"The wave draws nearer, pepupu."
"The wavering light is like a net."
"The drawing wave is the song of the sea."
Because the world I had
imagined was so bright...
Because it was shining...
I didn't know... what to do.
Old man Hayakawa was
acting like a guard.
He was always serious
about wanting to do it,
but something was off.
Dad, did you know you have a grandkid?
Not just Miuna, but a little boy.
His name is Akira.
He's almost four now.
But then again, I just found
out the other day, too.
Wait!
Do you know what Akira's
special move is?
It's kancho.
What are we going to do about that kid?
Well, it's not like he's
not cute or anything.
Or rather, he is cute...
Akari says he looks like
me when I was younger,
but I wouldn't know.
I want you to meet him and get
your opinion... or something.
Wait...
Wait, Manaka-san!
Why did I just say Manaka-san's name?
This is...
Oh, and the reason we were
able to come here is Miuna.
She's able to be in the sea now.
It's surprising, isn't it?
And then she heard some weird sound,
and it led us here.
I wanted to show her...
the real Shioshishio.
I mean, we were able to come
back here thanks to her.
Oh yeah, I didn't say it...
"Thanks for bringing us here."
I didn't tell Miuna that.
The Shioshishio that
I always dreamed of.
2nd Year
But the way I acted...
Entrance Ceremony
New Students
I ended up hurting Hikari.
You haven't grown much, Manaka.
Neither have you, Hii-kun!
This is...
It's here.
The place I thought of...
dreamed of... inside the sea.
I'm here.
160 Chisaki
157 Hikari
155 Kaname
154 Chisaki
152 Manaka
149 Manaka
Music Room
Hikari!
Miuna-chan's gone!
I told her not to go anywhere.
Did you actually look?
This isn't the time to argue!
You're right...
Let's look for her.
Oh.
Those weren't there before.
Let's go.
So, you're Miuna.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm just a scale, I suppose.
"Scale"? You mean like a fish's?
Right. That scale.
Was the school inside the sea fun?
Then that was...
Isn't Shioshishio a wonderful place?
Yes.
Did you find what you were looking for?
"Looking for"?
Hm? That's odd.
Did you not come here in search of that?
I...
Um!
What is it?
You're a god... right?
I am nothing more than a scale.
I just told you that.
Manaka-san.
Please tell me where Manaka-san is.
Is that what you were looking for?
If that's what you were
truly looking for,
I don't mind telling you.
It's Manaka-san.
The thing I'm looking for...
is Manaka-san!
That's a lie.
What?
What an audacious child you are,
lying to the face of a servant of a god.
I'm not a child!
I see...
So you're not a child anymore.
Miuna!
Miuna-chan!
We told you to stay right there!
H-Hey, sorry about earlier.
She's here.
Manaka-san is nearby.
What?
How do you know?
I think I just met god.
"God"?
You mean the Sea God?
Maybe she's talking about Uroko-sama.
Uroko-sama?
I wonder if he didn't fall asleep?
He's the protector of this village,
so he probably wouldn't.
What is this place?
I don't know.
This was a play area
for us and we used to
run around here when we
were in grade school,
but I've never seen this place.
What is this?
Are these...
All Ojoshi-samas?
Yeah.
These are probably the Ojoshi-samas that
were sent down over the years...
All of them.
A graveyard of Ojoshi-samas...
What is that?
Hey, Hikari! Wait!
Miuna-chan, wait right here.
Whoa!
Hikari! Are you okay?
Yeah.
Manaka...
Hikari, wait!
Tsumugu told us, remember?
We can't force people who
are sleeping to wake up.
No one knows what kind of
effect that may have on them.
Oh?
So that's what you were looking for...
"I just wanted to come to Shioshishio."
That is nothing more than a child's fib.
It's just like you said...
Once something appears,
something is lost.
Therefore, it all equals out in the end.
Manaka, what are you doing there?
All of us are waiting for you.
You're not an Ojoshi-sama,
so you don't have to be there...
Manaka-san's trying to wake up?
Ena?
This sound!
This is...
Her Ena's coming off.
She's losing her Ena.
Why?
Why is something like this happening?
It's messed up!
If that happens, Manaka's gonna die!
I'll save you right now!
Hikari! What are you doing?
Help me!
We're going to take Manaka to the shore.
At this rate, Manaka's going to die!
All right.
Wait, Hikari.
Turn away for a second.
Let's hurry.
Wait!
Could it be that the Sea God is angry?
About us taking Manaka back?
The hell if I care!
Let's go, Miuna-chan.
Hikari! Not that way!
The sound is coming from over here!
Manaka...
At that time...
No matter how far I reached,
it didn't get to you.
But never again.
I'm never letting go.
Episode Nineteen:
The Lost, Lost Little...