Oh, so this is the beach in this world!
With all these people here,
it's tempting to just mow them all down
at once, isn't it, Miss Kobayashi?
Don't do it.
The ocean here's salty?
It is.
That's the same, then.
The best thing about swimsuits
is that you can boldly show off more flesh.
No, that's out.
Really?
What do you think, Shouta?
I-I don't where to look...
This is reassuring.
That doesn't make me happy to hear at all.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Yes?
Could you come with me?
Your swimsuit is too skimpy.
Huh? Um, hey!
Well, that's to be expected.
I'm finally back.
You brought a spare swimsuit?
It's my scales.
Oh, that works for your swimsuits, too?
Yes, we looked them up on the internet!
Nice, aren't they?
I'm more envious of what's
filling out that swimsuit though.
I want to play now.
Right, let's go play!
Miss Kobayashi, what will you do?
Hmm, nothing much.
What's the matter, Miss Kobayashi?
You haven't been very excited all day.
To be honest, I'm not a big fan of the beach.
Huh?!
That's too honest.
Well, it's hot, you get sunburned,
and sand is annoying.
Same for me.
I prefer the indoors.
Then why did you come with us today?
Well...
Because I don't have much
else to do this summer.
My manager asked me to look
after Shouta-kun, too,
so I figured going with
everyone would be better.
Oh, I know what's going on here!
That tsundere thing, right?!
Completely different.
I want to play now.
Oh, right.
Then, uh...
First, let's put on sunscreen!
What an inferior species,
having skin that gets damaged if you
don't coat yourselves in such a thing.
Now, here I go, Miss Kobayashi!
Do anything weird and you're fired.
Yes.
Well, Shouta, could you?
There. Go ahead.
Come on.
I-I can't!
I see.
Switch, then.
Well, Shouta?
W-Well what?
Am I coating you right?
You really are a demon, aren't you?
Huh?!
Why are you trying to seduce me?!
Miss Lucoa, why don't you
just try being a demon?
I want to play now.
Next is watermelon splitting.
I'm in.
Further right!
Ah, you went too far. A little left!
Yes, yes, now just go straight.
Okay, stop.
Yay.
Impressive, Kanna!
You obliterated every last trace of it.
Yeah, oh well.
I want to swim!
Sure, let's go!
Don't go too far out.
Why not?
It's dangerous.
Oh, you're right.
He is scary, that Leviathan.
That one time I was nearly
killed really was a disaster.
What did you do?
I saw him from behind and mistook him
for Rahab when calling out to him.
Why you! I'll kill you!
Well, no, it's because no one can
help you if you start to drown.
Oh yeah, you humans can't
breathe under water, can you?
What an inferior species.
You can, Tohru?
I can. Swimming to my heart's
content feels really good.
Does she have gills or something?
Lady Tohru, let's race to there.
You're on.
Miss Kobayashi,
please give us the signal!
Sure.
On your marks,
ready,
go!
Ah, I forgot to tell them to hold back.
Not bad, Kanna.
Impressive, Lady Tohru.
First!
You went overboard.
I'm sorry.
Well, I guess it's time for lunch.
Okay!
Ocean
Beach Hut
Food
Shaved Ice
Thanks for the meal!
What's next?
Well... Miss Kobayashi...?
What's wrong, Miss Kobayashi?
Nothing. I just noticed that old man
hasn't changed much since back then.
Strawberry
Melon
Lemon
Blue Hawaii
Back then?
Yeah. When I was still a kid,
I came here with my family.
Family...
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them!
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Miss Kobayashi?
Hmm?
Could you tell me more about your family?
Huh?
Please?
Well...
I think it was a normal family.
I was raised normally.
They had me go to college.
After that, I left home to work.
Every now and then I talk to my parents
on the phone to tell them how I'm doing.
Oh, I haven't seen them in a while.
That's a normal human family?
Probably.
Then why did Miss Kobayashi
accept a dragon like me?
Why would someone born
and raised normally...
Why?
Does that mean...
the humans of this world
could accept dragons?
Kill them! Humans are evil! Kill them all!
What's wrong, Tohru?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's just, well...
I'm feeling listless.
Tohru.
Can I ride you?
This really is incredible.
It's been a while, so I'm excited!
Hup.
Tohru, aren't you homesick?
That's not the case.
But I feel like seeing my parents
after what we just talked about.
Every now and then I would
like to see my parents.
But it's all right.
Really?
Then what's bugging you?
I thought about introducing
you to my parents.
You should.
I can't.
Why not?
Because I'm sure they'd kill you.
That sounds violent, but I guess that's
common sense in your world, huh.
It is.
From my parent's point of view,
I'm definitely the weird one,
not common sense.
It's sad.
Talking to Tohru about things like
this is kind of heavy. And sad.
It drives home the difference
between "understanding words"
and "understanding each other".
It makes me realize we've lived
in vastly different worlds.
But maybe that's all the more reason I want
to cherish this time we have together.
I think that means you've
become independent.
Independent?
Yeah. You've developed your
own unique set of values.
You mean I've become an adult?
Who knows?
I'm not sure.
Most people don't try to become adults,
they just can't stay children any longer.
Oh, you've hooked something, Miss Kobayashi.
Tiny.
Shall we head back?
Yes.
Dragon fireworks?
Yeah. I won them in a lottery
at the shopping district.
That's it?
Yeah.
Huh?!
A real dragon is way better than that!
Impressive, Lady Tohru!
See, see! How's that, Miss Kobayashi?!
Shee, shee! How'f thah, Mih Chofahashi?!
I can't understand anything you're saying.
Episode 7
Summer's Staples! (The Fanservice Episode, Frankly)
What on Earth is this?!
The admission line for Comiket.
So we're supposed to provide
cover for Takiya here?
Not cover. Help.
Apparently two of his sellers
suddenly collapsed.
Leave it to me!
With my power, it will be easy
to exterminate them all.
Don't.
By the way, was leaving
Kanna behind a good idea?
There's a lot here that
can't be shown to children.
Man, thanks, you two!
You're a lifesaver!
I owe you quite a bit anyway.
You didn't ask Mr. Fafnir?
Water
Dragon
Shrine
Bullet Hell
Games
Oh, he's participating as a circle.
Curse
Anthology
Huh?!
Participating as a circle?
A circle's a group of people like us,
who sell things they made to other fans.
I see. So why did Mr. Fafnir do that?
I recommended all kinds
of anime and games to him,
and at some point he started drawing his own.
He's totally enjoying this world, isn't he?
Well, Kobayashi-san,
if you could handle sales,
and Tohru-chan, if you could
manage the line please.
Sure thing.
Hmph. All right then.
As of this moment,
the third day of Comic Market has begun.
Wh-What's this?
Please don't run.
Everyone's just barely on the verge of running!
Desires
Something powerful is holding
back their selfish impulses!
What in the world?!
Water
Dragon
Shrine
The new one, please.
That's 1,000 yen.
Water
Dragon
Shrine
Here, thank you very much.
The new one and the previous one, please.
Water Dragon Shrine WA-91
End of Line
The end of the line for
Water Dragon Shrine starts here!
I'm sorry, please group closer together.
Hmm, for tens of thousands of
individuals to be able take such
unified action without any
prior exercises or training...
Something powerful must be influencing them.
Um, excuse me.
Yes?
Are you a cosplayer?
No, I'm not.
Oh, I see. I'm sorry.
I thought you were a cosplayer from abroad.
I'm a real maid!
Oh, I get it.
You're in character.
Wonderful.
No, I'm the real thing!
I understand your policy.
If you don't mind, could I please
take your picture later?
I told you, I'm real!
The end of line starts here!
What incredible heat.
It feels like I'm in a fire drake's stomach.
Thank you very much!
I can't believe it's this bad.
Comiket is not to be underestimated.
Still,
what in the world could be attracting this
many people and keeping them all in check?
I don't get it.
Tohru-chan!
Hey, thanks for your help.
Time to switch.
I've been waiting for this!
Summer Homework, Science
Please select one of the following.
1) Sunflower Observation
2) Bug Collecting
3) Daily Weather
4) Electric Circuits
Sunflower Observation:
Observe the growth of a sunflower every day!
Bug Collecting: Catch bugs near convenience
stores, parks, or nearby plazas!
Paste the bugs you've gathered!
Bug collecting...
Crunchy...
Grasshopper
Moist
Butterfly
Flaky
Cicada
Crunchy
Where did you find it?
Let's Stick the Bugs We Found Here!
Uh, I think it's around this area...
What are you looking for?
Mr. Fafnir.
I figured I'd stop by since I'm on my break.
Say nothing.
I'll kill you.
You're the one who looks dead, Mr. Fafnir.
Well, that's what it's
like for first-timers.
Can I have a look at your book?
Hmph, help yourself.
Curse Anthology
Curse Anthology.
Th-These are...
You've printed real, effective curses!
Even how to inflict them...
You could curse someone to
death if you read this!
Hey, hey!
Only 1,000 yen?! That's cheap!
This is a bargain!
Wait, it's way too dangerous
to be selling that to others!
Still, there are a lot of cosplayers here.
There are a lot of humans dressed
up like the races from my world.
They're having fun pretending to be
characters from anime and manga.
You're practically the same, too, Tohru.
I am a proper maid!
No matter how you look at me,
I'm your loyal sex slave!
That's not a maid.
Hmm?
What is it?
The sahuagin, goblin, and witch over there...
Oh, I wonder what they're from.
They're real.
Huh?
Those three are real non-humans.
Huh?!
Excuse me!
You're from the other world, right?
Oh? You, too?
Yes. What are you doing here today?
I came to spread my wings.
I normally live disguised as a human,
but coming to events like this
lets me enjoy time in my real form.
I see.
Why not take the chance to
enjoy your real form, too?
Oh, that's impossible.
I'm a dragon.
A dragon?!
Yes.
That damn monster?!
Yes?
The one that could eat us all?!
Huh?!
Run!
Please don't run!
Dragons must be doing some crazy things.
They're wrong.
Oh?
When dragons get hungry, we
only eat as much as necessary...
And in the end, this world
is the survival of the fittest, so...
You're not denying it, just giving
supplementary explanation?
You there!
Come with me!
Your outfit's out!
Huh? I, um...
Did you not read the participant guide?!
I guess Miss Lucoa came, too.
Wait...
She never learns.
Now that I look closer,
there's a lot more.
Beings in their original form, that is.
That many?
Yes.
Those with great presence have left records of
their stays in this world on different levels,
like Mr. Fafnir and Miss Lucoa.
Uh, umm...
I'd like to return to my real form...
for a little bit.
As long as you keep it where
it won't cause trouble, you can.
Sorry for the wait!
Oh, can I take your picture?
Yes!
Excuse me, can I take one, too?
Huh?
Oh, me, too!
Huh?!
Excuse me, can I get your
eyes over here please?
Over here, too, please!
Oh, it's almost time.
Oh, well.
Hello. I came like I promised.
Oh, hello.
Hey, are you okay?
Well, to be honest, it's pretty rough.
But I can hang in there.
Um, it seems like everyone here is being
drawn to this place by something powerful.
Do you have any idea what that is?
Well...
I think it's something that only exists
in this place in this moment right now.
And I think everyone loves that.
I see.
I understand that very well.
Excuse me.
Could you take your picture soon?
Oh, right.
Geh, there's another line forming?
As of now, Comic Market 90 is over.
Thank you for participating, everyone.
We'll see you again in winter!
I'm back.
Good to see you. We managed fine
without you during the second half.
I see. I'm sorry for ditching you.
It's fine.
We've Sold Out
Oh, Mr. Fafnir, how'd it go?
Poorly, it looks like.
So how was it? What'd you
think of your first Comiket?
Well...
I reconfirmed my love for
you, Miss Kobayashi.
Huh?
Kobayashi-dono! Tohru-dono!
You were a huge help today!
I'm truly grateful!
And I'd like to ask for your help
as staff again this winter!
I'm done with this!
What will we print for our next thin book?
How about a dragon maid girl?
Nice!
Free studies?
My summer homework.
What should I do for it?
Well, I think you should
study something that you find
mysterious or would like to know more about.
I see. Got it.
What are you doing?
Studying you.
Huh?
Next Episode
Kobayashi-san, there's a lot of
talk about Tohru-chan on the internet.
I bet.
They mentioned you, too.
They said there was a sales lady
with dead-fish eyes.
Sorry about that!
And they got turned on by those eyes.
Episode 8
New Dragon, Elma! (She's Finally Appearing, Huh?)
I just felt a chill.