The moon's pretty.
Is that, like...
...a confession?
Sacchan, you're supposed to look at
this person if you're confessing.
R-Right, Hiro-kun?
Otherwise it's like I'm...
Huh?
I'm confessing to both of you.
I like Touko-chan,
and I like Hiro-kun.
Thanks.
I finally said it.
Thanks to Hiro-kun.
And I could say it to you, too.
Yeah,
the moon's pretty today.
Sacchan, I still don't get it.
Touko-chan, let's stay good friends.
Yeah,
the moon's pretty today.
Episode 10
"Jonathan"
Sacchan seems so happy.
Sacchan texts me every day.
She does?
Saying, "For tomorrow."
For tomorrow?
I'm home!
I wonder what's for dinner today.
Scooch, scooch.
Yanagi-san was running today, too.
Really? Yana-chan's really hanging in there.
Hina, have you told Touko already?
What?
Wait until after dinner.
Tada.
It's so cute, Hina.
Isn't it a bit too showy?
Yana-chan gave you that?
She told me Yukinari-san
complimented her in it.
I said I couldn't take it, but...
Should I not have?
No, it looks nice on you!
Good for you.
Right?!
Can I say something?
Here, coffee.
Hina, when you're wearing that—
Don't let it get cold.
Onee-chan, Yanagi-san says she's
going to change into someone new.
Yana-chan sure is amazing.
A new Yana-chan, huh?
I want to meet her.
I want to meet her...
From: Sacchan
Subject: For tomorrow
"Tsuki wo Ageru Hito"
"For tomorrow:"
From: Hiro Shirasaki
Re: For Tomorrow
"Meijinden" is amazing. It makes me
feel really small, or really big.
Looking forward to "Tsuki wo Ageru Hito"
"Meijinden" is amazing.
It makes me feel
really small, or really big.
Looking forward to "Tsuki wo Ageru Hito,"
Hiro.
I still can't hear it.
You can't hear the fragments
of the future anymore?
But why?
Is it because you met Touko?
Maybe you don't need it anymore.
Inbox
From: Yanagi
Subject: Hinode-hama today
Clear skies today. Hinode Bridge, futon.
Inbox
From: Yanagi
Subject: Hinode-hama today
Sunny all day.
In front of the gelato store.
Blacks 1, Whites 2
"Blacks 1, Whites 2," huh?
Issen Ichibyou Monogatari
Welcome.
Hey.
Your order?
Oolong tea.
We don't have any.
Here's your blend.
Hot coffee in mid-summer.
You're totally a grown-up.
Her name was
Sachi Nagamiya, right?
If you know where she lives,
I want you to tell me.
Uh, I can't tell you for nothing.
Figures. What do you want to know?
Do you like Touko-san?
You better be treating her well.
Touko-san's really important to us.
I'll tell you where Sacchan lives.
I haven't answered anything
you wanted to ask.
I can't really find the words,
but you don't have to answer me.
Clear skies today again. The sky is high.
Hello.
I heard from Hiro Shirasaki.
Oh.
Why did the 5:30 guy become a girl?
Boring.
You know something about this, don't you?
Hey, tell us.
That's my 5:30 girl.
Can you tell me about the shiny things?
Yanagi-chan heard the other day.
I see.
You aren't taking care
of Touko-chan at all.
I guess not.
Takayama said that to me, too.
But does Fukami Touko
want to be taken care of?
She makes me feel at home.
I—
Is it okay if she helps me?
I think she's helping me, too.
I don't think I know more than
you do about the shiny thing.
Do you
like Touko-chan?
She's—
no way.
Hello?
Oh.
I—
Are you the one who called
Kakeru the other day?
Yes.
So cute.
Forgive me, but what's your name?
My name's Touko Fukami.
Is Kakeru-kun home?
Unfortunately, he's not home right now.
Oh, I'll be leaving then.
Since you're here, why not have
a cup of tea or something?
Would you like to talk for a bit?
Umm...
Okay?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all.
He's a strange kid, isn't he?
Yes, very.
I mean, a little!
Sorry.
I think it's my fault.
No, I'm quite guilty, too.
Eh? Huh?
Can you move over a little bit?
You'll spill it.
It
doesn't work when I'm alone.
You know what I hate the most?
Washing Japanese mustard spinach
in the winter.
You've never done that, have you?
A long time ago.
Kakeru doesn't have
a place to to call home.
I've been dragging him around
ever since he was little.
We've only ever been in the same
place for two years at most.
He was quick to make friends,
when he was little.
But as soon as there's
a festival or something,
all the kids go into festival mode,
and they forget about Kakeru.
He had a phrase for it.
"A sudden, expected loneliness."
Right, that's it.
I'm surprised you remember that.
It was my fault, after all.
Welcome home.
Thanks.
You've been running the same
route while I was gone?
Yeah.
Ah.
The seaside road is nice and windy.
It helps you recover, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Was the grandpa there at the snack shop today?
That last uphill part,
it's not even that bad,
but it's tough, isn't it?
Yeah.
Yuki.
Welcome home.
Glad to be home.
Oh, yeah? So you were
quite a bookworm.
Back in the old days, everyone
read maybe twenty books a year.
Actually, we were being forced to read.
So you couldn't really call me a bookworm.
So is your boyfriend being discharged?
Yep, he can go back to work, too.
Congratulations.
Oh, man, good for you, Nee-chan.
So I want to invite him here sometime soon.
That's perfectly fine.
You should tell Dad.
No, for coffee. Just coffee.
He's coming just to drink coffee?
Yeah, he said he couldn't
have coffee in the hospital.
He really missed it.
Oh. Fine.
So that's that.
Tee hee.
This is the town I grew up in.
This is what Kakeru never had,
a backdrop to my life.
Short-stop!
What do I do here?
They were such a pain,
but now that I can't hear
them, it's a bit lonely.
Touko Fukami,
I miss you.
You're running again
starting tomorrow, right?
Yeah.
Snow?
Again.
I'm not scared.
Because this is my place.
I want to know about Kakeru-kun's
"sudden, expected loneliness."
I want to know more.
Jonathan.
Are you Kakeru-kun?
No.
You're not Jonathan!
Wait.
One, two, three...
They're missing.
One's missing.
I have to find Jonathan.
I'm not taking care of him at all.
Jonathan.
Wait.
Kakeru-kun.
Kakeru-kun, you came here, too.
I thought here I might
find out why I can't hear the
fragments of the future anymore.
Oh.
Isn't that why you're here, too?
I want to learn
about your "sudden, expected loneliness."
That's—
I heard from your parents.
Can you see the snow outside
the window, Kakeru-kun?
It's snowing?
Yes. The whole time.
It's snowing a lot, and I'm inside it.
It's not a fragment. It's snowing all over.
Touko, calm down.
It's fine. I'm okay.
I'm not scared.
But that's not all!
That's not?
Kakeru-kun,
in the snow, you—
What?
Um...
Kakeru-kun... You kiss me.
You kiss me.
I think I'm messed up.
I saw it before, too.
That was the second time.
What's wrong with me? Right?
You said before that what we're seeing
might not be the future.
Then what?
What is it that I'm seeing?
Or will
that time
come to be?
True, what we've been seeing and hearing
might not have been the future.
But the view you're seeing
outside the window is winter.
There's no mistake that we
heard and saw something.
You're right.
We have to accept that something is there.
Yeah,
and if we do this, it'll make
it a fragment of the future.
Kakeru-kun, what are you talking about?
We were together all day yesterday.
That means the two of us are going to see
the fireworks together again next year, right?
Onee-chan, oh, no!
Episode 11
"Piano"