Hina
Hina was deeply troubled.
Fried chicken and rolled omelette
should be fine, right?
And maybe sweet and spicy kinpira...
No! No brown colors!
PAT PAT PAT
It has to be a cute lunch, or else.
Maybe you don't get it.
The moment you open it,
it's like, "Ta-daaa!"
"Wow, how cute!"
But he's a middle school boy, right?
And if it's after a game,
I would think "delicious-looking"
is better than "cute."
Right, Kiriyama?
Huh? That was fast.
You peeled that many already?
Ah, yes.
Tomorrow is Sunday.
And they're so neat.
You're good with your hands, Kiriyama.
I'm glad I asked you to come over.
After all, I bought 4 kilograms.
The baseball team from Hina's
middle school is having a game.
I've never eaten boiled chestnuts before.
But you can eat this inner brown skin, huh?
That's right.
You have to boil it for a while, though.
It keeps well, so it's the perfect winter snack.
And it seems the boy Hina is concerned about
will be playing in the game.
He's the son of the milkman.
The tall boy named Takahashi.
It's like he drank
every drop from his parent's milk shop.
Takahashi Milk
He was even shorter than Hina
back in elementary school.
Takahashi Milk
And now he's the baseball team's ace
and the idol of Hina's school.
So it seems Hina wants to give this boy
named Takahashi, who she's
concerned about, a homemade lunch.
You've got more competition now, huh?
Even though Hina's had a crush on Takahashi
since elementary school.
I-I do not! It's not like that!
Don't say it like it's that kind of thing!
Stupid Sis!
Yes, yes. Sorry, sorry.
And it's the night before this young lady's
big event, playing out before my very eyes.
HmHm
Loves attentive work
Crunch Crunch
While I peel the skin off of chestnuts
that are due to be boiled.
How about this?
Here, let me see.
Pumpkin croquettes shaped like apples
and a flower bed made of onigiri...
Boil the pumpkin, mash it,
form it into balls, cover them with flour,
then coat them with egg yolk
and bread crumbs...
Let's see.
The game starts at 10, right?
If you leave the house at 9:30...
If you make something
you've never made before, I think it's risky.
You won't know how long it'll take,
and it'll make you panic.
If you panic, you'll make mistakes,
like with the seasoning...
Th-Then what should I do?
Like I said, fried chicken, rolled omelette,
and if you want something red,
maybe cherry tomatoes.
Is there anything I can eat, meow?
No way, that's too normal!
It's like an old woman's lunch! Forget it!
Gong
O-Old woman?
Hmph!
Never mind! I'm going to decide on this one!
Harumph!
Fine! Go ahead, do what you want!
I won't give you anymore advice!
Thump Thump
Nervous Nervous
Oh no, it's already this late?
Maru S closes at 10!
M-My money...
Empty
Um... Sis...
I want to buy all this,
but I don't have enough money.
Roll Roll
Let's see...
Chestnut pumpkin, ground beef,
breadcrumbs, onions, eggs,
black pepper, radishes, olives,
avocado, asparagus, baby corn,
balsamic vinegar, lemons, mushroom,
red and yellow bell peppers,
Pet me some more! Purr, vroom, purr!
king oyster mushrooms, fresh basil,
decorative cups and toothpicks, rosemary...
How much do you intend to make?
Or more like,
how much do you intend to spend?
This is not cost-effective!
At a glance, this'll cost over 3,000 yen.
It's like a box lunch from a fancy restaurant!
Why do we have to take 3,000 yen from
our food expenses for some other kid's lunch?
And we only buy milk
when it's on sale for 158 yen!
Clench!
I don't want to!
What, you say "some other kid,"
but aren't the cats and Kiriyama the same?!
Bloomph...
Glossy
Some other kids
Why do you get to use up all the money
on some other peoples' kids?
Rei, are you someone else's kid?
Where did you come from?
You're not Momo's big brother?
Uh... Well... I'm sorry.
This is awkward...
Um... er... I'm sorry.
No, I'm the one who's sorry.
I tried to pay for my share of the food before,
but Akari wouldn't let me.
But maybe now she will, starting with this.
Then I won't feel so guilty about things.
Ahhhhh...
Sting Sting
Sis will pick up any kind of stray.
Dogs, cats...
She always has. She can't ignore something
that's just skin and bones.
Bark B... ark
Meow Meow
And then, she likes to make them
soft and fluffy.
But I was surprised
when she brought a person home.
Me?
But it's okay. I'm sure Sis will make you
soft and fluffy in no time.
You think so?
Yeah.
I see.
Yep. You'll see!
And then, Sunday morning...
I just rolled the croquettes into balls!
I have to do it over!
Something's burning!
The sweet apple sautee!
Sloppy Sloppy
No way!
It's 8 already? Why?
And I woke up at 6!
Oh no, who is it? I'm busy right now!
New Message
Yoko
It's Yoko!
Um, "I'm running late.
Please leave without me." There.
New Message
Sending
Sent
Oh no, that's right! What should I wear?
I was so focused on lunch,
I didn't think about my outfit!
Is this too stylish?
This looks like I'm way too enthusiastic!
Suddenly, I'm now late!
No!
Curtains and Carpets
Shimoda
Curtains are more expensive than I thought.
But now I'll finally be able to sleep peacefully.
I don't have any matches for a while,
so this is a good opportunity to start
gathering things I need for the apartment.
I still need a chair, a desk, a bookshelf...
Oh, this is...
Hina's middle school.
Concentrate!
You can do it!
Fight!
Takahashi!
So that's the rumored Takahashi?
He's so tall.
Is he really a middle school student?
And he certainly is cool.
Do your best! Smash it!
There she is.
I wonder if she finished his lunch in time.
It's a comeback!
Takahashi!
H-Home run?
Jump
- Takahashi! I love you!
- You're the best!
I've always loved you!
- He did it!
- Awesome!
S-So cool...
He really hit it out of the park...
He totally looks like a main character
from a shonen manga.
I've never seen Hina
with that expression before.
It really looks like springtime in her life...
Like a bittersweet feeling...
Or like she's in love.
Love...
Thank you!
Okay, get dressed, and we'll meet at Matsuda.
What, Matsuda?
For monja? I'm starving!
Um, is Takahashi around?
You're coming, right, Takahashi?
To Matsuda's?
- You were so cool!
- Great job!
Ah, yes.
Takahashi!
- You're going to Matsuda?
- Can we come, too?
All right! Monja it is!
What should I get?
- I'm starving.
- Come on, Takahashi, let's go!
Don't do it.
But, Sis will ask me about it.
She'll ask me why I didn't give it to him,
after all that trouble I went through.
What?
Sis won't understand.
Why is she crying?
It's because she's so beautiful.
She's good at cooking, and I'm sure anyone
would be happy to have a bento she made...
Yesterday evening and even just now,
she looked so happy.
Let's go home.
Let's go home and eat it with everyone.
I don't understand women.
Welcome home.
I see. You couldn't give it to him.
That's too bad.
You worked so hard...
Oh, don't cry. I understand.
The same thing happened to me before, too.
I understand.
You weren't able
to give a lunch you made, Sis?
Of course, just like you, Hina.
I wanted to make a cute lunch
and I got so excited.
I worked hard, but I panicked,
and then I messed up.
Hmph!
Harumph!
So I couldn't help but say something.
But later on, I remembered.
What I said to you last night
is what Mom told me a long time ago.
Like mother, like daughter,
I guess you could say.
Isn't that funny?
Mom said that?
Well, let's eat it with everyone.
Yeah.
What? Do you want some?
Just this once...
Really? I can? Hom nom nom!
Okay, the tea is ready.
So let's eat.
Huh? What happened to the kitties?
Maybe they were so full they got sleepy.
How is it, Kiriyama?
Hina, did you taste this beforehand?
Eh? Nope.
This was something bitter, sweet, and sour.
It indeed tasted like the end of a first love.
Hina, let's do some training together.
Yeah. I'll do my best next time for sure!
Maybe it's a good thing
that she wasn't able to deliver her first bento.
That's what Kiriyama and I thought.
Hina
V. S.
I can see it.
Huh?
Um... I'm the one who won, right?
Yeah. You could say that, as a phenomenon.
Phenomenon... But it's reality.
Yes, yes. I know. Fine, you "won."
If that's what makes you feel better.
W-Wait a second. What?
It sounds like you're objecting,
like, "Yeah, yeah, it can't be helped."
Okay, one more time. I'll go first.
I'll start with a static rook
and you do the bishop exchange once more.
What the heck is that?
It's like I'm a practice board!
That's petty! You're being petty, Kiriyama!
This matter is urgent.
With the bishop exchange,
I can't let you have everything your way!
Then you should use the ranging rook.
I like using the static rook!
Would you have me use a strategy
I'm not good at?
Ugh—
Ugh, geez. How many times have I told you
that studying alone suits me better?
As rivals, we raise each other up,
so losing this precious rivalry
would be a major loss to your shogi life!
You do understand that, don't you, Kiriyama?
At times, haste is required.
I'm saying the two of us need to find it,
without a moment to waste.
In fact, you're the one who has to find it.
The "bishop exchange crusher" silver bullet...
Yes!
Grin
The Nikaidou vaccine!
Ga-blam
In that case, it'd be the "Kiriyama Vaccine"!
It's what I've dreamed of!
The "Nikaidou Vaccine"!
Or the "Nikaidou System"!
To leave a technique with my name
for the next generation!
Don't you understand?
I understand... but I'd rather not!
Good morning!
You suddenly show up at 9 in the morning,
talking about developing a "silver bullet"?
And besides, I'm an "all-rounder,"
so I have nothing to do with it.
Are you even listening to me?
Rumble
Rumble Groggle Grumble
Let's... get some lunch.
What are we gonna eat?
Something fast.
Oh, yeah. How about MecBurger?
GigaMec
#1 Burger
You'd probably like the GigaMec.
GigaMec...
MecBurger
No, I shouldn't.
What do you always eat, Kiriyama?
Me?
When I'm alone, I eat bread, Smiley's Bento,
Mec's, or Yoshidaya's beef bowl...
But lately, I sometimes have dinner
at an acquaintance's house...
Momo?
What's wrong? Where are your sisters?
Quiver Quiver Quiver
Bodoro!
Boing
Whump
Kiriyama, do you know her?
Um... Yeah...
It sounded like this one yelled "Bodoro" at me.
Bodoro is that one character...
The super-popular anime masterpiece
loved by children, adults,
and yours truly, about an intelligent being
who lives in the mysterious forest.
Bodoro.
Well, I do feel a deep connection
to that character's intelligence.
All right, little one.
I shall ask you your name. What is it?
Momo!
All right then, Momo. Shall we hold hands?
Traffic is dangerous here
with all the cars going to and fro.
Bodoro, Bodoro! Bododo, bododo!
Momo seems so happy.
More than when she's with me...
Where do you live? I shall walk you home.
There she is. Momo!
She's with Kiriyama!
Hey, Kiriyama!
Um... Rei, who is that?
Huh? Akari? Your face is really red.
Don't tell me Akari has a weakness...
...for that?
Um, he's, uh...
From shogi... I mean, my club...
Nice to meet you. I'm Kiriyama's best friend,
Harunobu Nikaidou.
Have you had dinner?
You should come over as well.
Fidget    Fidget
Sis, someone else's kid again?
Such kind words. It would be my pleasure!
Come on, Bodoro! Fold some more!
This is an old house.
It's like a movie set.
I-I'm sorry, Kiriyama.
I-It's okay. Nothing for you to apologize, Hina...
Plump Plump
#1 in Japan
Bloomph
Gold
Round and shiny!
Thump Thump Thump Thump
Kiriyama...
What can I say, your wonderful friend
is just like a nice, round, shiny ball.
L-Like a ball?
I've never heard anyone
describe a friend like that.
Sorry.
Sis is extremely fond of soft and fluffy things.
I'm really sorry.
What would you like to eat?
We went grocery shopping today,
so I can make pretty much anything.
Bam
Fried chicken? Salisbury steak?
Salisb... No...
If you could make something
bland and light on protein...
U-Um, I'm sorry. It's nothing. I can eat that.
Oh, I see...
That's unusual. You prefer a mature taste.
That's odd. It's impossible to maintain
a plump body like that with such a strict menu.
Thump Thump Thump
Is he on a diet?
That's not good. If he diets,
that beautiful ball-like shine would...
Ah, but I see, I would worry about it, too.
He is around that age.
Fat
Sugar
A slow metabolism...
Or maybe the situation is even more serious?
Oh, no!
No matter how appealingly soft and fluffy he is,
it won't mean a thing unless he's healthy!
It's okay! Leave it to me!
Delicious.
Sorry for your trouble, Akari.
You promised you wouldn't say that,
remember?
I hate to say it, Akari.
But I can't have melon or bamboo shoots.
Lots of Money
I don't know what to eat these days.
I can't even enjoy booze.
They said I could have just a little.
Poor Mr. Yamamoto!
Okay, I'll look into mild-tasting snacks for you.
I'll search the internet.
I didn't take care of Grandma, and listen
to my customers at the club just for show!
Okay, here you go.
Season it as you like, Nikaidou.
Delicious! Even though it's bland...
I'm glad. Chew well and eat slowly, okay?
Got hooked in,
and also chewing well
Yes. My butler is always telling me
to chew each bite at least 30 times,
but I'm always too impatient.
My, what a kind butler.
Not being cared for by Akari,
so somewhat sad beings...
Huh? Who it could be at this hour?
I am sorry to disturb you so late this evening.
It seems Young Master
has been enjoying your hospitality.
Oh, Hanaoka. Are you here to pick me up?
Oh, you're Nikaidou's...
I'm surprised you found your way here.
Of course, I used a GPS—
Oh, excuse me! My lungs are a little...
Anyway, I happened to be passing by.
He always comes to pick me up,
no matter where I am.
It's always been like that. Like magic, right?
Heh
Magic?!
Eeeek
Wait a second, Nikaidou.
You're totally under surveillance!
He just said GPS. He definitely said it!
Um, if you'd like, please enjoy this.
It's from the neighborhood,
so you may already know it,
but this is one of my favorite sweets.
Oh my, thank you.
Oh, what a coincidence.
I love these sweets, too.
MIKAZUKI-DOU
So much!
Um, won't you come in and have these with us?
I'll make some tea.
Oh, if you don't mind. Then...
Please, come in.
Hina, would you boil some water?
Okay!
V. S.
Next Episode Preview
Episode 5
He was my dad's best friend.
Even though he's an adult,
he really talked to me.
Do you like shogi?
Rei...
Watch the next episode of
"March Comes in Like a Lion," too!
I swear I won't mess up
the next bento!