Contact with DRAGONs established.
What is this?
Coco! Coco!
Villkiss Awakens
Enemy signals captured.
One Galleon-class, 22 Scuna-class.
Twenty-two?!
Dammit, they keep creeping out.
Zola here. Everyone, listen up.
Beginner training is on hold.
Destroy the flies and
establish air superiority.
All units, attack formation.
Use aerial tactical formation.
Yes, ma'am.
Shall I take care of the deserter?
Do it later.
Yes, ma'am.
C-Captain, what about us?
Stay alive until we take care of this.
All units, open fire.
Captain!
Ange, where are you going?
I'm going home to the Misurugi Empire.
Are you serious?
You only have enough fuel for one battle.
I don't know where your country is,
but there's no way you'll make it.
I don't care!
If that means I won't have to go back...
What am I supposed to do?
W-Wait!
Coco.
Coco, you idiot.
Magic nation, my ass.
What were you daydreaming about?
We're Norma.
H-Help me!
You're the last one, you huge-ass monster.
All units, load freezing bullets.
All units, attack!
Here we go!
Die!
This is the end!
No!
Help me!
What the hell are you doing? Let go.
Zola!
Where am I?
What happened?
Four Para-mails destroyed.
Three Mail Riders dead.
We've failed to retrieve
the bodies of the two rookies.
And we didn't eliminate the DRAGONs.
These are the consequences of your desertion.
How do you feel, Princess?
Say something, dammit!
Don't hurt her. She's wounded, after all.
I only tried to go back to my nation.
I did nothing wrong.
It's your fault that Onee-sama—
You killed Onee-sama.
Murderer. Murderer!
Murderer?
Norma aren't human.
You're seriously screwed up.
You're the worst.
What's going to happen to us, now?
Salia.
Starting today, you're the
captain of the First Troop.
Hilda, you're lieutenant.
Got it?
Yes.
We move out again as soon
as we find the DRAGON.
Get to it.
Yes, ma'am.
Salia, the answer to the quiz.
The last one alive? It was Ange!
Be quiet.
Fine.
Princess.
Huh?
Light of Mana.
I could do this myself.
Have you forgotten the words of His Majesty?
"The royal family need not use Mana."
Leave everything to me,
Momoka Oginome, your principal maid.
How long do you intend to sleep?
Momoka...
Did you have a nice dream?
The petition.
Have the nations responded to my petition?
This?
They all refused to receive it.
They don't know of a Princess
Angelise or an Empire of Misurugi.
What?
Officer Emma Bronson says there
is no Empire of Misurugi anymore.
That's been the case since
you were revealed as a Norma.
The citizens must have gotten
pissed and revolted or something.
That can't be possible.
My nation, Misurugi, it couldn't be gone...
Mother?
Father and Onii-sama?
And Sylvia?
They're done.
Let's go.
I didn't think you'd need three in one day.
Sorry to hurry you, Jasmine.
It's fine. We have to hold
a ceremony for them soon.
You're carrying them, Ange.
The survivors are to make the
graves of their fallen comrades,
and pay for them.
It's so that you hold onto
their life and never forget them.
Don't worry, you can pay in installments.
Zola Axberg.
Coco Reeve.
Miranda Campbell.
They're all nice names.
Arzenal girls finally get their
old names back when they die.
Their real names,
given to them by their parents.
Zola.
Her impulsiveness was her only fault.
She was hard-working
and cared for her juniors.
More than anything, she valued her comrades.
So she's gone.
What's going to happen now?
What am I supposed to do?
Fight and kill DRAGONs.
That's all.
What are those DRAGONs?
Why do I have to fight them?
Weren't you listening in class?
We Norma are allowed to live
only as weapons to kill the DRAGON.
Isn't that what you'd want as a princess?
You're fighting to protect the world.
The world?
It's because there are Norma
here fighting the DRAGONs
that the world of Mana is
able to maintain peace.
What?
While your world was drunk on peace,
the Norma were dying,
unknown to anyone, to protect you.
I don't know anything about that.
Now it's your turn.
I don't know.
I'm not even a Norma.
This is the officer's pen. Use it.
Light of Mana.
Light. Light of Mana!
Why?
I just... I just can't use Mana right now...
Just for that, I have to
get thrown into this hell?
It's outrageous.
It was you people that decided that.
You ended up here under the
rules that you people made.
Norma are instinctively
violent, antisocial monsters.
She must be quarantined immediately.
Of course it's outrageous.
Coco had just turned twelve, dammit.
Twelve... the same age as Sylvia.
No. She's not the same as Sylvia.
Because—
Norma aren't human... huh.
Then what are you?
You're not a princess. You have no Mana.
You abandoned your duty.
You're a deserter. You killed a little girl.
Just what are you?
I am—
Commander, we've found the DRAGONs.
Get up, Ange. We're moving out.
Snap out of it.
This world is unfair and unjust...
...so kill or be killed.
That's all there is.
Kill the DRAGONs for your dead comrades.
If you can't do that much, then die.
Then kill me, please.
I can't take it.
No.
Die in battle, just like they did.
That's your duty.
Commander, we don't have a Para-mail.
But we do.
That one.
You don't mean...
Really? We're bringing it?
Yeah.
Then what about that thing?
Who knows.
Can we start it up?
No problem. Give me twenty minutes.
This is your machine.
It's pretty old.
The engine's in shambles.
The energy regulation's a mess.
It's a piece of shit that might fall apart.
It's perfect for someone that wants to die.
It's called the Villkiss.
I can die if I ride this...
I can be Angelise again.
Jill, why?
This machine—
I'll have to deal with you if you
can't follow Command's orders.
Now, let's move out.
It's your first battle as Captain.
I expect great things.
Yes, ma'am.
Course clear. Salia Squad, you may liftoff.
Salia Squad, lifting off.
Why is she coming with us?
We're fighting alongside the
person that killed Onee-sama?
I'll kill her! I'll kill her!
I swear I'll kill her.
I heard she wants to die.
Why don't we watch to
see how Burn Princess dies?
What's that machine?
Salia, isn't that Para-mail pretty awesome?
Isn't it, Salia?
We're on a mission, Vivian.
Enemy shadow confirmed.
It's coming.
What shall we do, Captain?
It's almost dead. Finish it off.
All units, attack formation.
Load freezing bullets.
Yes, ma'am.
Tight formation.
Attack!
Salia, below!
Below?
Rosalie! Chris!
It set a trap, that sly bastard!
There's no data about it attacking like this...
What do we do, Salia-chan?
We're in danger.
What? What can we do?
Captain Zola.
You're the captain, Salia.
Evade!
Salia-chan!
Salia!
Almost. Almost.
Almost. I can say goodbye.
Ange!
No... Once more...
What the hell is she doing?
No... I have to die properly.
Live on, Angelise...
I don't want to die.
I don't want to die!
You—
Die!
I don't know what I'm feeling.
You're getting excited.
No, this isn't me.
I don't want to kill to live.
That's so dirty, so shameful, so selfish...
That's us, the Norma.
Goodbye, Father, Mother, Onii-sama, Sylvia.
There's nothing left for me.
There's nothing I need.
No past, no name, nothing.
I won't die as easily as you did.
To survive, I will claw the ground,
drink muddy water, and vomit blood.
I will live on.
Kill, and live.
Disgusting!
Next Episode Preview
That's so much better.
I've been meaning to cut my hair.
Shampooing it will be so much easier.
And sleeping!
I look nice with short hair, too, don't I?
A Loner's Revolt
I'll become even more popular now.