Rations, four.
Medical supplies, one.
Medications, one.
Maintenance, one.
Bring the containers with the
bras down to my place, please.
Receipt confirmed.
Good work.
See you again soon.
All units, prepare!
Hurry up, or we won't make
it back in time for dinner.
Yes, ma'am.
Ange, sup.
You were awesome out there again.
Dammit, she keeps making all the money.
Why did she come back?
Who's the cockroach again?
I'll bust a screw hole in her head.
Don't, you'll get in trouble from command.
Not if she doesn't get caught.
Right?
Take this, you parasite!
No, no! I haven't done anything!
Attention, all units.
There is an intruder in Arzenal.
Target has escaped onto upper deck.
All units in the vicinity,
provide assistance immediately.
I repeat.
An intruder?
She's over there.
Get her.
You—
The Light of Mana...
Please, stop.
I'm...
I'm just here to see Angelise-sama.
Momoka?
Is it you?
Angelise-sama...?
Angelise-sama!
Momoka's Here!
Momoka Oginome.
Top maid to Princess Angelise.
She took care of the Princess.
Yes.
Understood.
What did the committee want?
As expected, huh?
If we let her return to her country,
we risk exposing the truth about the DRAGON,
and the Norma who fight them.
Isn't there anything we can do?
She just came to visit.
Just came to visit, huh?
Well, there's no way a Norma like me
could change rules made by humans.
Let's at least let them be together.
For now.
I—
Um—
Y-You cut your hair.
I think it's good.
You look more mature.
Like you've grown out of how you were before.
That's what I think.
This is a Norma rehabilitation facility?
I keep smelling metal.
Go in.
Yes, ma'am.
What is...
...this place?
No...
Is this your room, Angelise-sama?
It's too small here.
You're getting changed.
Allow me to—
I-I'll fold it.
Light of Mana.
That's what you use Mana for?
S-Sorry.
So...
Why are you here?
To assist you, Angelise-sama.
Who's?
I'm Ange.
Ange the Norma.
I've been ordered to
take care of you for
the next few days, so I will.
Please don't bother me.
Stop, please.
You're Angelise-sama.
I'm not going home.
I won't go away.
I will take care of you from now on.
You have nowhere to go, do you?
I heard.
There's no Empire of
Misurugi anymore, is there?
I ruined it.
Because I'm a Norma,
Mother died, and the nation fell.
That's not true.
That's—
How long?
How long did you know I was a Norma?
From the beginning, of course.
Father brought you so that
I wouldn't have to use Mana.
Correct?
Well, who cares.
Not anymore.
I'm going to sleep.
You can use that bed over there.
My place is beside you.
I chased you and chased you,
and I finally found you.
Please let me stay here.
This isn't a place for humans.
What an unsanitary environment.
What a meager meal.
Has Angelise-sama always been here?
She really is from a
different world, isn't she?
What's a maid?
It's a person that takes care of royalty.
Wow, she's amazing.
You have ketchup on your face. Jeez.
Then Ersha, Salia, you're my maids, right?
No!
You aren't a Norma, are you?
I don't have anything for you.
If you want to eat, you'll have to pay.
P-Pay?
Buy what you want.
Make money if you have to.
That's how it works here.
How dare you!
Don't make Angelise-sama wait!
Give up your seat.
It's Angelise-sama.
It's none of your business.
Give up our seats?
You're quite high and mighty,
you dumpster queen.
Get off your high horse.
What an eyesore.
What did you just say?
How dare you disrespect Angelise-sama.
Even for a barbaric and uncultured
Norma, such words are—
She's a Norma, by the way.
Sh-She is not.
Angelise-sama is Angelise-sama.
She's just like Ange when
she first came here.
The cringeworthy princess
and her cringeworthy maid.
It's perfect.
Good for you. You won't have to
spend your nights alone anymore.
As crass as always.
We're Norma, after all.
I won't allow any more disrespect.
Um—
That's yours.
Thank you.
I wasn't aware you hadn't eaten in three days.
I'm sorry.
I was busy with the thought of seeing you.
Take care of yourself with that.
So this is what they call money.
Thank you.
I always thought a monetized
economy was an imperfect system.
But this is kind of fun, too.
Yeah?
Stop squirming.
Don't blame me if I can't reattach your arm.
Huh, where's her arm?
Over here.
Maybe we can attach it this way.
What was that?
What is this place for?
Hunting.
Who knows when I'll end up like that, too?
Angelise-sama.
What has happened to you?
That... That isn't Angelise-sama.
You must be hurt.
How pitiful.
Angelise-sama.
I must save her.
I must save Angelise-sama.
Mission clear.
Training complete.
Welcome home, Angelise-sama.
What is this?
You were the fashion leader
of the Empire of Misurugi.
I wanted you to remember how you used to be.
I assorted all the things you used to love.
Return it.
Yes, ma'am.
What?
Return it to the way it was.
Now.
Angelise-sama.
No, I'm just getting started.
My locker.
Welcome home, Angelise-sama.
I redecorated the place the
way you used to like it.
Now you can—
Return it.
Return it to the way it was.
Now.
Welcome, Angelise-sama.
Today, I've prepared your favorite
grilled quail and salad with sauce.
You'll be a hundred times better with this.
Enough, already.
What a waste.
A-Angelise-sama—
My name isn't Angelise.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Stop bothering me.
Aw.
Bullseye.
Impressive.
I can never shoot as well as you, Salia-chan.
What am I doing wrong?
It's your four-dimensional boobs.
Seriously?
You're loud.
Really? That maid's going to get killed?
Wh-What's going on?
Did you know that Arzenal and DRAGON
are classified secrets that only a
handful of humans know about?
Really?
I've heard about that.
A human wandered into here
and learned the truth.
They wouldn't just let her go back.
Exactly.
I get it.
Poor her.
She came here in search of
such a cold-blooded bitch.
No kidding.
Everyone that gets involved with her dies.
Coco, Miranda, and now her.
She sends anyone who
shows her affection to Hell.
She's a wretch, really.
Here we go.
What is that?
Well...
I think this is going to be my last meal here.
So I thought I'd have a proper meal.
I paid for it, of course.
Time to eat.
Th-This is—
She sends anyone who
shows her affection to Hell.
Pretty... good.
Angelise-sama.
Bath.
I will wash your back.
Do as you wish.
Yes.
How long has it been
since you've allowed me to wash your back?
That cut.
This?
I was told it could be fixed with Mana,
but it has sentimental value.
What's going on?
I'm sorry, Angelise-sama.
I broke your doll.
You're hurt.
It's nothing.
It's not nothing.
Angelise-sama, your dress.
Idiot!
We can make another dress
and get another doll.
But you're the only you.
Angelise-sama.
All better.
You can bury the broken doll under
the tree in the back yard.
It's our secret.
Yes!
Angelise-sama...
It's been too long.
I would never forget.
I'm as I am now because of you.
I...
...still adore you.
I will forever and ever...
Angelise-sama.
Leave.
Now.
Yes, tomorrow morning.
So right now—
No, right now.
You can go underwater or go across
the sea using Mana, can't you?
Run, Momoka.
You finally called me...
Momoka.
But please let me be by
you for as long as I can.
Why?
Momoka Oginome is your top maid.
Idiot.
Type 1 contact warning.
Angelise-sama.
Please be safe.
Type 1 contact warning.
You better work hard, so you can
afford that girl's tombstone.
That's morbid.
Soldiers, to your machines.
Ange,
a transport will arrive at dawn.
Your order to care for your
former maid is hereby complete.
Good work.
Runway clear. Ready for lift-off.
Top maid my ass.
She's been lying to me this whole time.
I still adore you, Angelise-sama.
Idiot.
You hopeless idiot.
That freaking bitch!
She kicked my machine during combat!
A pest! She called me a pest!
Ange was awesome out there again.
What are you talking about?
She totally defied her orders.
There, there, calm down.
How can I calm down?
She killed all the DRAGONs herself.
It's unheard of.
Thank you for taking care of me.
It was only a short time,
but I was very happy.
Could you please let Angelise-sama know?
All right.
Over here, then.
Yes. Thank you.
Stop there.
Angelise-sama.
I'm buying that girl.
What?
A Norma buying a human?
With these tattered strips of paper?
That's impossible.
Fine.
What?
I'm calling off the transport.
That girl is hers.
C-Commander.
You can have anything with enough money.
That's how it works here.
I mean—
Wait, please.
I can stay here?
I can stay here by you, Angelise-sama?
Ange.
My name is Ange.
Yes,
Angelise-sama.
Next Episode
I finally got to see you, Angelise-sama!
I so thought you were going to die.
That's so mean.
This director seriously thinks
it's all good, so long as there's
a bathing scene with nudity.
Maybe you'll die next week?
Salia's Depression
Maybe you're the worst, Princess.