I find it hard to say this, but...
If you come back and say, "It's impossible, after all,"
it would be oh so nice...
Marulk...
I've seen off all kinds of people
who leave on journeys they won't return from...
But... today is the saddest I've ever felt.
The Inverted Forest... It's so far above us...
Reg...
Are you ready?
Of course.
Is this the shaft Ozen was talking about?
Yep...
In this world, there is nothing as impartial as death.
For all living creatures,
death is sure to eventually come knocking.
Death is an equalizer - it is an absolute truth...
and it is always lingering right beside us.
Nevertheless, people make the best use
of their wits and courage...
Struggling... floundering...
they cling to life until the very end.
You see, we actually like this unjust and unequal world...
Everyone, unable to resist, goes down in
Make those eyes shine brighter than a torch
The destination we are aiming for is deep
We squarely lose our way
The trap of the open-mouthed netherworld
Let's chase the traces of truth
If an answer can be found now, we don't mind losing it all
The echo is still reverberating
So that we do not part with that voice
The compass is always
Pointed to the darkness
Where there is no escape
In that direction
Even if that is a curse
The pulse is the real thing
Never again will the yearning stop
I wonder where Riko and Reg are right now...
I bet they're somewhere around the Great Fault.
Huh?! How would you know that?
It's the result of a calculation I made based on
the number of days it's been and Reg's abilities...
The Rough Map of the Netherworld?
I made a copy of it back when I "borrowed" it earlier.
"The Great Fault"...
"A vertical wall spanning more than 4,000 meters"...
From there on out,
the strain of ascending becomes more severe,
and people start seeing and hearing things.
It looks perfectly smooth...
How are you supposed to descend that thing?
I don't know...
But, Reg managed to climb it.
Surely there must be a viable route somewhere...
Another exit hole!
Look! It's a madokajack!
Riko, it's dangerous to stick your head out like that!
Anyway, what are we going to do?
Our only options are to start descending the cliff face,
or to brace for the Curse's effect on you and head back.
Any other holes nearby...?
How about that one?
The spot with the critter droppings sticking out!
Riko, go ahead now!
Alright!
Sorry...
I would have rather made a delicious meal
out of you guys.
Unable to fly in the sky or run on walls,
weaklings like us are simply picked off and eaten.
Weaklings have no choice
but to choose the path of the weak, you see.
Riko, hurry and get further inside!
What was that...?
Reg!
We did it! This den extends way, way down!
Hey! Quick! Hurry up!
Ah, I'm coming now.
That sound...
Something about it bothers me.
We've descended quite a ways.
Yeah...
Still, I know it was for the sake of pushing forward,
but we totally trashed this den.
We should be grateful to these little guys.
Yeah, thanks to them we haven't had any trouble
finding food or a place to sleep.
And they primarily live on baracocha fruit,
so their meat is tender and delicious, too.
Are these some kind of ruins?
Reg!
This is part of a ship!
One from a long, long time ago!
"A ship"?!
I wonder if there are still any Relics inside...
Relics, Relics...
But, why is there a ship here in the first place...?
Any Relics out there?
Hello there! Relics...?
What's this?
This is...
a madokajack's...
lair...
It's so quick!
Even if I hurl my fists at it, they'll just get chomped on!
Should I just shoot it?
Now!
Once you fire it, no matter how you push yourself,
you always faint after around ten minutes.
Then it's a full two hours until you wake up.
Just try leaving a helpless child on her own
in the second layer for two hours.
I wonder just how she'll be torn to shreds and eaten...
Still, when you really do have to use it,
go all out to make sure whatever it is
doesn't come after you again in the future.
No matter your opponent or whatever lies in the vicinity,
when the time comes don't hesitate or show any mercy.
This is no time to be indecisive!
Do it now!
Way to go!
I wonder how madokajacks taste...
Riko! Listen to me!
I'm going to fall asleep before long now that I did that!
Two hours...
During that time, you'll be-
I heard it earlier, too, but what the heck is that?
That cry...
Could it be a crimson splitjaw...?
Run!
There's a wound on its head?
That must be the one Reg blasted with his Incinerator!
I know I heard they have lairs on the third layer...
but, this one remembers us?!
A dead end?!
Hey! Please, little guys! Get outta the way!
It's no use...
I'm gonna... faint...
Outta my way!
Please!
Yikes! There it is!
I'm begging you, let me through!
You alright, Reg?!
Riko, until I wake up, stay right here...
It'll be fine!
Reg, I'll protect you, okay?!
I sure am hungry...
I need to look for some food.
And I can't leave Reg lying here, anyway...
Alright, we're going now, Reg!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
I'm so hungry... and worn out.
I...
can't...
keep going!
I can't press on.
I'll wait here until Reg wakes up...
Huh?
That's the smell of baracochas!
They must be bearing fruit somewhere below me!
How lucky!
Oh yeah!
I'm close now!
Where are the baracochas?
Where?
Where, oh where?
Why's the scent coming up from the ground?
What?
This intense scent of baracochas...
What the heck is this place...?
Huh?
Is that...
a neritantan tail?
Could it be...
that I'm inside the stomach on an amakagame?!
Damn it!
This scent must be a trap meant to lure neritantans here!
I need to get out of here quick
or I'll end up getting dissolved!
I survived...
There's so many of them...
What?!
What? What is it?!
Ow!
I get it...
The smell's stuck on me, so they're...
Y-you've got the wrong idea!
I'm not baracocha fruit, okay?!
Ouch!
Here they come!
Don't tell me this is another dead end...
Has it not been two hours yet?
Reg, come on and wake up already!
Light...
An opening to the outside!
I did it...
You've gotta be kidding me...
Why's there an upward slope?
There's no way!
If I ascend that much, the Curse will-
But, I can't turn back now...
Reg... here we go.
The strain of the depths' third layer:
headaches, dizziness...
...severe nausea...
in addition to...
problems with your sense of balance.
There they are! Master!
You can relax now, Riko!
Marulk...
That's right.
Well now, won't you head back with us?
Visual and auditory hallucinations...
Damn...
That's enough already, Riko.
Take a break. Don't overdo it now!
Riko!
Everybody...
You did great, Riko! Just leave the rest to me!
Habo!
Riko...
Mom...
Riko, let's go back together... back to Orth.
Mom!
Mom, where are we?
We're inside a gondola that's heading to Orth.
Huh?!
But what about the Curse of the Abyss?
It's alright...
Your body is no longer affected by the Curse.
Well, we're about to arrive.
It's the city of Orth!
Welcome home!
Welcome back!
Riko!
Welcome back home!
Everyone...!
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Welcome home!
Reg?
Where's Reg?
Mom! What about Reg?! Reg's not here!
Reg is...
at the bottom of the netherworld.
But why...?
I won't have it!
If Reg's not here with me...
there's no point in me even returning to Orth!
The two of us were always together...
Reg... Reg...
If I'm not together with Reg...
I can't bear it!
Now I see how hard it is
being on your own inside the Abyss...
I was being protected by you all along...
Reg.
Enough!
You sure are pesky!
Ah, that's right!
Riko...
Ozen taught me how to use this thing, you know!
Reg!
Reg! Use this!
Sorry I took so long.
Don't be...
It allowed me to think about lots of stuff.
Speaking of that, I understand now.
You understand?
That if I was on my own,
this all would've been impossible!
Reg, it's thanks to you that I was able to make it this far.
Thank you, Reg!
Y-yeah...
I feel the same way.
It's because I had Riko with me...
It's because it's the two of us... that we made it here.
The landscape around here has become a lot spikier.
Our depth is...
Let's see...
6,750 meters, I think.
I hear these spikes are actually eggs...
I wonder if there's a way to make them into a tasty meal...
Riko, I can see something down there!
It's the Goblet of Giants!
The glittering waves that float in the sky
Let's bundle them and build a rainbow bridge
A dangerous foothold, a slope we slide on
A signpost of the past and future
Your left hand, with my right hand
Join it, connect us, and let's begin
I am always beside you
In the past, the present, and also the future
So let's walk along without hesitating
Pile up multicolored dreams
Where will we head toward tomorrow?
If I can be together with you, the world will begin to shine
Let's search for flowers that bloom at the ends of the earth