You're here early, Inspector Ando.
Don't forget that HQ overrode your orders
to bar Salty Dog from the command room.
I'm aware.
I'm told that Hana Mutou's precognitive
abilities have been lost.
In other words, the Independent
Attack Force your plan called for
has been rendered useless by your own mistake.
I'll be blunt.
We are suspicious and distrustful
of the capabilities
of your Midsummer's Knights.
That's rather harsh.
And there are rumors that
your Intercept Faction is planning
an even stupider operation.
Then I'll be blunt, as well.
There are unpleasant rumors
that you've been sent here
to the Tanegashima base to arrest Hana Mutou.
Well, even if that's true...
Unfortunately, she isn't at the base right now.
How's the Tenkaidou? Do you like it?
Everyone's so nice.
Anyone good in Tanegashima?
They're all good people.
Is she that naïve?
Is there a boy you like?
The captain!
Daichi Manatsu-kun, huh?
Hey, you know the boy who
pilots the Nebula Engine?
Teppei?
Yeah!
Teppei Arashi-kun.
He's cute, isn't he?
Does he have a girlfriend?
I don't think he does.
I see!
What do we do?
We have to go for it!
Should we?
When will he be here next?
I wonder if the others are better now...
Ta-da!
Snack time!
Nice!
I'm so glad everyone's feeling better.
Yeah!
Spitz to Doghouse.
Hana Mutou is not currently
at the Tanegashima base.
Hana Mutou, pilot of the Flare Engine
that defeated the Kiltgang Type-5,
is evidently aboard the Tenkaidou.
Over.
We have not received such information
from our agent aboard the Tenkaidou.
They got us.
Nishikubo set this up to protect Hana Mutou.
Those Midsummer's Knights are quite irritating.
Though, they did succeed in buying time.
Cerberus, Sarama, and Garmr are together now.
We don't need the Knights anymore.
The Knights of
Midsummer
Are you lonely without Hana?
Well, nothing I can do about it. That's the plan.
I told Pitz, you know.
There's someone who's even
sadder without Hana than you are.
Okay, I'll break out my healing spell for you again.
You mean...
Belly Button Forte!
Does that work on Pitz?
I'm pretending to cast it on Pitz,
but I'm really using it on Daichi.
R-Really?
Belly Button Forte!
Who are you doing that one for?
It feels like I'm the only one
not showing any skin today,
and my position as heroine is in danger... I guess.
Oh, sir.
Then, goodbye.
I'll be free tonight.
Yes, sir.
With a feather in my hand,
sunlight glowing through it,
like a dancing butterfly...
I want to see you.
Let us go on a journey
toward gentleness, toward warmth.
We've received reports that
large numbers of people
have simultaneously fallen into
comas in the Tokyo ES area.
They're probably gathering
more Orgone energy again.
Hey, Teppei, the pendant on your chest...
This?
The Blue Star.
You two take turns wearing it, right?
It's a game we've played since we were kids.
Whichever one of us is able to
surprise the other gets to wear it.
I'm retaking it!
I like the way you never give up.
You boys are so in love.
Who's that?
She's with Salty Dog.
An inspector?
You really are kids.
If you seriously expect an
Independent Attack Force
comprised of children to accomplish anything,
I must question your sanity.
Thank you, Siren-sama.
This time, I have two capsules.
Then one person will be staying here.
Where are the others?
Leaving it to you.
We have issues with teamwork.
Teamwork?
You've been influenced by the Earthlings, too.
Siren-sama...
Are you still concerned about the Earthlings?
They aren't like us. Their lives are finite.
When a finite life form evolves sentience,
a destructive desire manifests deep within its heart.
In the end, their race's only
purpose is to be eaten by us.
But our lives were once finite, as well.
We've got two Orgone Capsules.
Can we say "ladies first"?
I don't care.
What about the other?
Let's use this to decide.
Tails.
Heads.
Heads, it is.
Sorry.
You weren't cheating, were you?
I wouldn't do that to a comrade.
After all, teamwork is important.
AEOs confirmed!
The Type-2! And one we've never seen, Type-6!
Manifestation point is within
defensive zone 1, Omega sector!
Activate Earth Engine and Nebula Engine
launch sequences immediately.
Roger!
Energy charging confirmed within the
Earth Engine and Nebula Engine.
The Flare Engine's status?
Damaged in the last battle,
and still undergoing repairs.
You're wasting your time.
I ordered Cerberus to launch.
When?
Cerberus?
Impacter signals in the Omega sector.
They'll make contact with the
Kiltgangs in eighty seconds!
The latest unmanned Impacters,
developed by the Ark Faction
to support the Kivotos Plan.
They were already deployed for battle?
Manned Impacters are behind
the times, Science Chief.
The summer is about to end.
Yes, the season of the Midsummer's Knights.
So this is the real me?
Yes, I can feel power filling me!
What's that?
Hm? They aren't the same ones as usual.
Not that it matters, of course!
These guys...
They're fast.
Cerberus consists of three units surrounded
by superconducting magnetic fields
that cause them to move chaotically.
Magnetic levitation-type, high-mobility Impacters.
These unmanned weapons are far more mobile
and more powerful than manned Impacters.
Cerberus, lost!
What?
Was it destroyed?
I don't know.
The signal just stopped.
Video incoming.
What?
What's going on?
They've taken control of them...
Impossible.
Didn't anyone ever tell you that
machines are easy to fool?
Video's back online.
Switch low-orbit Impacters to emergency mode!
Wait.
Earth and Nebula are heading to intercept.
Sixty seconds until contact with the Kiltgangs!
Huh? Aren't there more than usual?
Be careful.
The enemy took over the new Impacters.
Really?
Captain, they're coming!
Off you go.
Captain!
If the enemy's controlling
Cerberus, too, we can't win...
So you've been bitten by your own dog?
They're fast!
Earth Engine and Nebula Engine
are being pushed back.
They're falling back to defensive zone 2.
This is bad.
It'll be okay.
Teppei and the captain won't lose to them.
They won't!
Malkin, Zimbalt, and the new Impacters, too?
This isn't good.
You're sounding pretty wimpy, Teppei.
These guys won't beat us.
Right?
I like the way you never give up.
Teppei! Daichi!
Okay!
It's crazy, but they're working well together.
You boys are so in love...
There!
I've retaken Cerberus!
What?
Hey, Malkin...
You're playing around too much!
You don't need to tell me.
I know!
Siren-sama gave me this precious energy.
I can't waste it!
You never improve at shooting.
We're being pushed back!
What is this?
A back door from when the
Kiltgang hacked Cerberus?
If I can follow it...
If you don't tell them to use the low-orbit
Impacters now, it'll be too late!
Just believe in us!
I'll hit them with my special attack spell.
Die, Earth Impacters!
Captain, I'm borrowing the
Earth Engine's systems.
Wh-What?
Take this...
What?
What's going on?
Captain!
The enemy has stopped moving!
Teppei!
We'll destroy their Ego Blocks!
Roger!
It didn't work?
An Ego Block can only be destroyed
by its owner's will.
At least, for now.
Hana Mutou, I want to ask you something.
How can you have so much faith in them?
Because we're a team.
Even if it was only for a moment,
they were able to interfere
with the Kiltgang's controls.
It was that magical girl.
All of our attacks have been stopped.
Siren-sama,
the next time we activate the Kiltgangs,
perhaps we should all attack at once.
Yeah! We did it!
Good work, you guys.
It looked like they shut down for a moment.
How did you do that?
I did it.
Am I a good girl? Am I?
Inspector...
I'll just say one thing.
We won't abandon the people
who live on this world,
as long as we have this team.
The Midsummer's Knights, huh?
Teppei, Hana, and I return to
Tanegashima from the Tenkaidou
in the Flügel, an atmosphere re-entry capsule.
But a plot by the Ark Faction, which wants Hana,
causes us to crash land in Australia.
And then, we're attacked by Salty Dog's weapons.
Next time, on episode 18 of Captain Earth:
Onslaught Through the Wilderness.
Onslaught Through the Wilderness
Earth Engine, expand!