It wasn't supposed to be
like this, head in my hands
Struggling to escape from
this saturated world
Time passes like whispering sand
These circumstances, unchanging
gazing out at a dreamless tomorrow
Wanna say goodbye to the
confusion of yesterday
I try reaching out, as if to resist
We cry millions of times
and then get born again
Let's go with these red eyes
to that pictured future
Come here right by me,
I'm clapping my hands
Where are you? Who are you?
Strain my eyes in the darkness
Can't see anything, don't know
anything, but I'll still go
To the place of shining
light in which you wait
Episode Eight
King of Paradise
Inspired by Ango Sakaguchi's
Meijikaika Ango Torimonochou
(Meiji-era Detective Stories)
"Foolish Apparition" and The Election Murder Case
The detective isn't back today, either?
I wonder if something happened to him...
Sorry! Is there some
kind of case to solve?
Inga
Detective's Assistant
Isn't it about time the cucumbers
on the roof were harvested?
Water is leaking through
the walls again!
My cell phone reception is lousy!
I want him to give my food
cart's new dish a taste test!
I need him to look for my precious
necklace that I misplaced somewhere!
How can I get back together
with my girlfriend?!
Kazamori! Kazamori!
I know! Since he's not
here, you'll do, Inga-chan!
How about working for me part-time?!
It's really not that shady a place!
Just grilling yakitori
in a bathing suit!
Inga-chan is a boy, you know!
That's even better these days!
It's getting scary here... Come on,
haven't you found Shinjurou yet?!
Don't squeeze me!
Sasa juice!
Where's Shinjurou?!
The firewalls are complex.
I will attempt to retry.
Whatever, just help me!
Sasa Kazamori
Artificial Intelligence (R.A.I.)
Shinjurou-sama! Shinjurou-sama!
Shinjurou-sama!
"Mamori"... "Kaze"...?
Kaza... mori...
Was he there?
Kaishou Rie
Kaishou Rinroku's Daughter
Lives at Home
I found him. He is in there...
The East Kantou Social
Rehabilitation Program Center...
Private-run or not, he's still
inside a prison. Shinjurou...
Shinjurou said he was being used
in that case with the codes.
And he was going to the privately
run prison where that guy is.
A visit should only take an hour or two.
Why has he been gone for days now?
Can't we investigate further?
I have probably the most
secure line in all Japan.
A normal firewall couldn't mess with me.
Because it's a part of me in the cloud.
Still, there's an extremely aggressive,
unknown barrier around Shinjurou-sama.
You can't talk to Shinjurou?
There's also something incomprehensible
about Shinjurou's behavior.
I stole this footage from
a surveillance camera.
It's an honor to be called
upon by you, Chairman.
Well, Rie-san is all fired up...
Kaishou Rinroku
Chairman of JJ Systems
Certainly, it appears
that Yuuki Shinjurou
is imprisoned in the privately-run
East Kanto Rehab Center.
Even though he has no criminal record
and wasn't sentenced by any judge,
the data shows that he's also
been given a prisoner number.
It's possible that someone
has falsified the data.
Hayami Seigen
Director of the Security Bureau
Metropolitan Police Dept.
Koyama Izumi
Public Prosecutor
Joint Coordinating Dept.
Public Prosecutor's Office
What happened to him?
Yuuki Shinjurou
Well, why don't we just get him out
of there? Assuming he's innocent...
Please, Rie-sama! Don't go in there!
Kaichou Family Maid (Head Maid)
Kaichou Family Maid
I'm going too!
Miss...
Please let me go as your
assistant, Izumi-san!
An assistant and maid are
two different things.
Please wait!
I made these.
I'll take them.
I'll use them if the Detective resists.
Visiting Room 1
You attempted to incite the critic,
Calls Himself a Novelist
Prisoner
Mr. Yajima, to commit murder.
You call yourself "the Novelist",
but your real name...
When new characters are added to the
mix halfway in, the plot goes haywire.
Just don't talk too much.
What did you do to the detective?
Who are those women?
A murder occurred during a
movie shoot at a movie studio.
Movie shoot?
The murderer is cameraman
Yuuki Shinjurou.
You're the high society female
police detective, okay?
Don't drag your heels!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Yuuki Shinjurou
Cameraman?
Murder case?!
And Prosecutor Koyama has
arrested the culprit?
It seems like everyone's up in arms.
Anyway, I gather they're
going to investigate now,
so it'll probably take some time.
The prosecutor just happens to be
there with civilian Kaishou Rie,
who I'm sure doesn't have the right
to investigate a criminal matter...
It's like they're all
dreaming or some...
A dream... I see...
This is similar to the
Oono Myoushin case.
The founder of a new religious
cult murdered his followers.
The followers deludedly believed that
everything Oono said was reality.
For example, they would
watch a blank video
but "saw" whatever footage
Oono told them was on it.
Oono had the power to make people
see his words as reality.
That's the power of Bettenou.
"Bettenou"! You mean the founder,
Bettenou, of Oono's group?
Bettenou is a kami.
She's like a deity with the power
to turn people's words into reality.
That's why I've been saying I
smell her ever since we got here!
All you said was that
something smells strange!
But if you're right...
This whole thing could be
some kind of illusion...
...created by Bettenou!
Hey! Give me my phone!
She's showing her story to
Shinjurou and the others!
Hopefully it'll be soon...
Click!
Maybe a little more?
Kazamori!
And one for the road!
So this... is the mystery...
Yuuki-san?
Kazamori, I could've done
without that last one.
Been a while, hasn't it?
What can you see right now?
The truth, right?
Yuuki Shinjurou
Detective
Criminals, huh?
Yes, the Metro Police Department
brought it to my attention...
If it's made public that a person who
just came for a visit was imprisoned...
Right now, all we can
do is leave it to them.
Solving the murder takes priority.
I found the scene of the crime.
Are there shutters without
safety systems these days?!
It's been tampered with so that there's
no record of it opening or closing!
And the safeties aren't working either!
A nonexistent streetcar doesn't run.
This is the murder weapon.
This shutter separates the men and
women's blocks, so it usually remains shut.
Okamoto
East Kantou Social Rehabilitation Program Center
Director of Security
Director Mitaka... I mean, the
security guard, I guess...
He would open this shutter every
night to visit the women's block.
To have contact with
a female prisoner...
That's why the line was cut.
Hey, who do you think you are?!
What's the prime suspect doing playing
detective and investigating?!
It's just as my mistress says.
This young lady is the
pride of the Metro P.D.
She solves cases with money, authority
and old-fashioned selfishness,
and they call her the Glamorous Gumshoe!
I guess that novelist can't
write light novels...
I'll go in myself and
confirm the identity
of that man who's calling
himself "the Novelist"!
And Bettenou, too.
I don't want to be held back anymore.
Huh? You intend to tag along?
You think they'll let a kid in there?
They wouldn't mind me, would they?
As your assistant...
S-Sure, why not?
Leave the handcuffs on.
Without the continued stimulus, you'll
be swept up by the Novelist's tale again.
Oh, and if they get too annoying...
Yuuki Shinjurou!
Like this?
How long do you intend to keep
up this ridiculous charade?!
What have you done?!
If you resist arrest,
I'll have you incarcerated for 780 years...
I'm so scared...
...he said, in a monotone.
The behavior of all the
inmates is monitored
through their uniquely numbered chips.
This is in the area of
the shutter last night...
Yuuki Shinjurou
It's me...
Until the morning, no other number...
that is, no other inmate was there.
In other words, you're the only
possible culprit, Defeated Detective!
Why would I...?
I can picture it!
I'm sure you said something like,
"The truth must be revealed!"
and got into an argument over it.
You're a pro at pretending you're mean,
but have a strong sense of justice.
Are you praising me? Or dissing me?
The numbers...
Do you have something?
I was thrown in here by the man
who calls himself the Novelist.
But was it easy to issue a number
for me, when I'm not a criminal?
The installed chips need
a lot of maintenance,
so it's possible that a guard put it in.
But the monitored numbers are issued
by the court and public prosecutor.
In other words, my number could've
already belonged to another inmate,
but was transferred to me.
That is a possibility.
Then there's another inmate
with the same number?
Our security system would warn us
if two of the same number existed!
Then even if he or she
has the attached chip,
one inmate here doesn't
have a monitored number.
That inmate can move about without
being seen by the security system.
There are surveillance cameras!
The victim probably changed
the angle of the cameras,
just like he fiddled with the shutter.
So that no one could find
fault with his behavior!
I'll check on it at once!
The person who originally had
your number is the killer!
No.
There was no war.
If I solve this mystery, the dream that
the Novelist gave us will disappear...
I want the criminal records
of the female inmates!
I wonder what'll happen to the movie...
I just hope it doesn't get canceled.
Right when it finally looked like we
were about to accomplish something...
We still don't know how it's
supposed to turn out...
Shinjurou-kun!
The murdered Director Mitaka was
looking for movies in the library.
Stuart Rosenberg, Franklin
J. Schaffner, Frank Darabont.
What do these three
directors have in common?
They're foreigners!
They all directed a famous
prison break film.
Prison break?
I saw the director...
You understand, don't
you? You're Papillon!
No! Don't let go!
Please! Don't let go!
He called the woman he was with
"Papillon" and begged her not to let him go?
Let go of me!
A problematic breakup?
No. He wasn't telling
her not to let him go.
Note: Depending on the kanji, hanasuna can mean "Don't let go!" or "Don't talk/tell!"
He said, "Don't tell anyone."
The woman knew Mitaka's secret and he
was telling her not to tell anyone.
If the director had a secret,
wouldn't it make more sense if
he did the killing, instead?
The reason the director snuck into
the women's block every night
was to help the woman who
knew his secret break out.
He looked to the movies to get a
hint for that, no matter how small.
Break... out?
It would be possible if a
monitored number was switched
and you could get around
the surveillance cameras.
I don't understand. What
do you mean by "break out"?
I solved the mystery of your last lines.
"That's right. I was just a NEET
pretending I was some hacker."
What is this?
"It was so much fun leaking the
government's secret information,
but when my blog started getting
attention, I started uploading lies, too.
And then one day, the police came..."
"I had relations with an
innumerable amount of people.
It was because I was insecure...
How long will the war
last? It may never end...
I wanted to be with somebody
so I could forget my anxiety.
But when the war was over, I was
told that I sold my body..."
I was an ordinary mother.
My son wasn't even a year old
and I refused to let him
become a victim of the war.
I just wanted to hold on to
my ordinary everyday life.
That's why I accepted my friend's
invitation to participate
in a demonstration against
the government...
And eventually, I thought,
"If that Prime Minister doesn't
quit, the war won't end...
And if he doesn't quit,
I'll make him quit!"
I researched how to make explosives...
...and one day, the Public
Security Force showed up.
During the war,
a number of terrorist bombing plots
against the Prime Minister were uncovered.
But terrorism by an average housewife
to protect her everyday life?
During the war, Mitaka
Kichitarou also took part
in anti-government demonstrations,
which is where he met Izawa Sayo.
But for him, the demonstrations
were just a fad of the times.
After the war, he became a guard
at this private-run prison,
but if it became known that he
once consorted with terrorists,
he would lose his job,
his future... everything.
So he switched Izawa Sayo's monitored
number and tried to help her escape!
Mitaka asked me something...
Tanimura, Yada are
there... and Izawa, too?
At the time, you were standing behind
that box, so he couldn't see you.
However, Mitaka's tablet displayed
the inmates' numbers in real time,
so even if he couldn't see her,
it shouldn't have been
necessary for him to ask me.
So why did he ask?
Izawa Sayo!
It's because only your
number isn't displayed!
He told me... He said he would get me
out of here if I didn't say anything.
But I didn't understand
what he was saying.
I'm shooting a movie.
I should've been able
to film to the end...
...and then I'd be able
to become my true self!
So why do I have to be
cut from the movie?!
That's why I...
Even though he was trying
to get you out of here!
Maybe he felt sorry for you
because you have a child...
No!
It was the streetcar!
It moved! It moved...
It struck and killed him!
War is a toy, isn't it?
And it isn't just me!
It's you, too. And you!
We've all made war into a toy!
Tanimura Motoko
Information Criminal
Yada Sumie
Sex Offender
Izawa Sayo
Terrorist
Is it that frustrating having
to accept that this time
Chairman Kaishou's
deductions were correct,
and that Yuuki Shinjurou was innocent?
That's a terrible face.
Anyway, I'm going to stick
around here a little longer.
I want to escape, but I
can't pass up this chance...
...to reflect upon myself
here, at the terminus of life.
In the pale morning
mist, a whispered prayer
I'm gonna follow this
twisted landscape with you
Looking for the "truth",
"a 'lie' will do" is it?
Tracing it as if we can see through
Looking for, beyond words
Like a falling feather
Looking for, find it
So we can cuddle close together here
Looking for, unravel it
Like a tattered cloud
Looking for, find it
So we can cuddle close together here
Something's strange...
Answer me. What do you want?
What do you want with Yuuki Shinjurou?
Resistance is futile.
People have no choice but
to answer my question.
Until then, you can't even
call that mischievous kami!
What do you want with Yuuki Shinjurou?
He's my... Great Detective.
I'm a novelist.
I bring forth events onto the
setting that is this reality.
That's my novel.
And my novel needed a great detective.
I put him within my reach so
I could polish my new work.
I've thought of all the
plots I'll ever need!
And so you had the guard
cooperate with you
in disguising Shinjurou as a prisoner.
And then I had that guard disposed of.
It's the detective's first case!
But he shouldn't have been
able to solve the mystery.
Because if he did, the pleasant
fantasy world would be destroyed.
In this world of illusion,
he embraced a mystery that
he'd never be able to solve.
He should've been mine!
Too bad. There is no mystery that
Yuuki Shinjurou can't solve.
Even if it means spilling
his own blood...
He always gives me the
truth... the souls...
What about Bettenou?
You took her away, didn't you?
The way you always do...
"If someone hadn't killed him,
I might've killed him myself.
Instead of going to all this
trouble to look for the criminal,
I'd rather hunt down the
killer of Takeda Shingen,
Note: Distinguished Daimyo in feudal Japan who has various stories surrounding his death
who might've died of natural
causes, suicide, or murder,"
Shinjurou answered with a scowl.
Inspired by "Sneering Demon"
from Ango Torimonochou,
Next time on UN-GO:
"Kaishou Rinroku's Crime".
Episode 9
"Kaishou Rinroku's Crime"
Inspired by "Sneering Demon" and "Red Trap" from Ango Sakaguchi's
Meijikaika Ango Torimonochou
(Meiji-era Detective Stories)
There's a reason I'm so sherious...
I mean serious! I'm serious!