From the news chopper to the studio--
I'm reporting live from
the skies of Hosu City!
I'm reporting on a
different story, but look at this!
There is fire and smoke rising
from different locations on the streets.
Are these from accidents,
or from rioting villains?
We are not getting any
information about any of this.
I will report as soon
as I know the situation!
Okay, cut!
Keep shooting.
I wonder what that is...?
Where?
Over there.
By the water tank on
top of the highest building.
Can you get it?
There are people! Two of them!
Curious onlookers?
In a place like that?
"Villain - Tomura Shigaraki - Quirk: Decay"
"Villain - Kurogiri - Quirk: Warp Gate"
Let's go back.
Were you satisfied with
the results, Tomura Shigaraki?
Idiot. That depends on tomorrow.
"The Aftermath of Hero Killer: Stain"
"Hosu General Hospital"
Were you able to sleep, Midoriya?
No, not really.
I didn't think so.
Me neither.
Thinking about it now,
we did something amazing, huh?
Yeah.
"Izuku Midoriya - Quirk: One For All"
Seeing an ending like that really makes
you feel like it's a miracle we're alive.
With my leg like this, he probably
could've killed us if he'd wanted to.
"Shoto Todoroki - Quirk: Half-Cold, Half-Hot"
Yeah. We were obviously
left alive on purpose.
You're amazing to have been able to face him
"Tenya Iida - Quirk: Engine"
after all the murderous
intent directed at you.
No, that's not it.
I...
"Pro Hero - Manual"
"Pro Hero - Gran Torino - Quirk: Jet"
Oh, are you wounded kids awake?
Gran Torino!
Manual...
Kid, I've got a lot of complaints for you.
Oh! S-Sorr--
But before that, you've got a visitor.
Hosu's chief of police, Kenji Tsuragamae.
Tsuragamae! Ch-Chief?!
Oh, you can just stay seated, woof.
"Woof"!
You must be the U.A. students
who brought down the hero killer, right?
Yes.
The chief of police came all this way... Why?
Regarding the hero killer we arrested...
He had fairly serious injuries,
with burns and broken bones,
and is receiving treatment
under strict guard, woof.
Since you are U.A. students,
I'm sure you already know
that when superpowers
were still becoming the norm,
the police attached high importance
to leadership and standards
and made sure Quirks were
not used as weapons.
And then, the profession of
"hero" emerged to fill that gap, woof.
For an individual's use of force
and power that can easily kill others--
actions that normally would be appropriate
to denounce--to be accepted officially
is thanks to early heroes who followed
the ethics and rules of the profession, woof.
Even up against the hero killer, for uncertified
individuals to cause injury with their Quirks
without specific instruction
from their guardians
or supervisors is a clear
violation of the rules.
The three of you, and the pro heroes
Endeavor, Manual, and Gran Torino
must receive strict punishment.
Wait a minute.
If Iida hadn't done anything,
Native would've been killed.
If Midoriya hadn't come,
the two of them would've been killed.
Todoroki...
No one realized that
the hero killer had appeared.
Are you saying we should've followed
the rules and watched people get killed?
W-W-Wait!
Are you saying that as long as it turns
out all right, it's okay to bend the rules?
Isn't it a hero's job to save people?
That is why you are not
a full-fledged hero yet.
Goodness, what are you being
taught by U.A. and Endeavor, woof?
You dog!
Stop it. He is absolutely right.
Hang on a minute. Hear him out until the end.
That was the official opinion of the police.
And the punishment and such would only
happen if this were all made public, woof.
If this were made public, you would
probably be applauded by the public,
but you would not be able
to escape punishment.
On the other hand, this is a bit
underhanded, but if it is not made public,
the burn scars would support Endeavor
being the hero who saved the day,
and it would end there, woof.
Thankfully, there were very few witnesses.
This violation could be crushed here, woof.
But this would also mean no one would know
about your good judgment or achievements.
Which do you prefer?
Personally, I don't want to be the one
to find fault with promising young ones
because of one big mistake, woof.
Either way, we will need to take responsibility
for being negligent in our supervisory duties.
I am truly sorry.
All right. You'll cause trouble for others!
If you understand, then don't do it again!
I won't!
I-I'm sorry.
Please take care of it.
Because of the unfairness of adults,
you will not be able to receive the
praise you would probably have gotten,
but at least,
as someone who also
protects the peace,
I can say thank you.
Please start with that next time.
Todoroki...
The fight in the alley that
started in an unexpected way
ended like this without
anyone knowing about it.
But its influence would continue to
eat away at us without anyone the wiser...
They said they arrested the hero killer!
Wow! Amazing!
"Hero Killer Arrested"
Seriously? Who beat him?
Endeavor! As expected of the number two hero!
"Riots in Hosu City"
"Were the crimes connected?"
"Good Job, Endeavor"
"The End of the Hero Killer"
I feel better, but it's kind of unfortunate.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
"Special Report: Hero Killer!"
The three villains arrested
and restrained during Hosu City's riots
are all men with unknown
addresses and identities.
"How are they connected
to the League of Villains?"
Based on their distinctive appearance
and the presence of two people
NHA TV filmed by chance,
there are those saying they are
connected to the League of Villains
that attacked U.A. High School last month.
The hero killer, Stain,
has killed more people on his own
since the appearance of All Might
than any other individual criminal.
With his arrest, everyone around
Japan can rest a little easier.
The seriously wounded hero killer, Stain,
is currently receiving treatment
at a hospital under police guard.
The police are awaiting
the recovery of the victims
to investigate further into
the motive behind the crime.
This villain will certainly leave his mark in
the history of crime in Japan--no, the world--
Hero Killer: Stain!
Why did he keep committing crimes?
What is he after?
I'm reporting live from
Ekou Street in Hosu City.
"Hero Kil"
Last night, just after 8 pm, Hero Killer: Stain
was arrested by Endeavor on this street.
It's all anyone's talking about.
Are the Nomus just secondary?
Once the night is over,
the world will have forgotten about you.
Not only have they not forgotten,
but we ended up being the side story.
"Genius"
Regarding the incident last night
in Hosu City in west Tokyo
with the arrest of Hero Killer: Stain
and the villains that resembled
the Nomu who attacked U.A....
You are probably all
worried about that right now.
"Pro Hero - Best Jeanist"
Yes, it is something
I am also very worried about.
People tend to only pay
attention to big events.
However, it is especially at times
like this that heroes must remain calm.
Chaos can sometimes tempt people
and draw out the cruelty that
lies sleeping inside them at their core.
Which means, it will be business
as usual for us today, as well.
Let us brace our minds
and bodies with our tight jeans.
Sure, Best Jeanist!
"Katsuki Bakugo - Quirk: Explosion"
I... I want to go home right now...
"Fourth Kind Agency"
Oh, I got a reply from Midoriya!
"Eijiro Kirishima - Quirk: Hardening"
It was at Hosu City, so that location
information was an SOS after all, huh?
I'm glad I reported it.
Hey!
"Tetsutetsu Tetsutetsu - Quirk: Steel"
Fourth Kind's gonna hit you!
Let's get going!
Wait a sec! I'm gonna reply.
"Pro Hero - Fourth Kind"
Didn't I tell you that
you must always be punctual?!
S-Sorry, sir!
"Chivalrous Hero"    "Justice"
All right, we're going on patrol!
Yes, sir!
No matter how damaged your hair,
the new ingredient,
U008 will penetrate deep into each hair.
Curl...
Curl, all you want.
Easy curls with just a spritz!
Hair spray, UNERI.
Letting women ride the waves of the times.
They sure work fast.
This is a demo, so it'll
air on TV in about a month.
With lots of CG!
"Momo Yaoyorozu - Quirk: Creation"
"Itsuka Kendo - Quirk: Big Fist"
We're gonna be on TV, huh?
Heroes... We are heroes...
"Pro Hero - Uwabami"
Now, shall we go on patrol?
Yes, ma'am!
"Mind, Skill, Body"
I see, well, I'm just glad
you and Iida are both okay.
"Ochaco Uraraka - Quirk: Zero Gravity"
When I got just the address,
I got really nervous.
Sorry, Uraraka. There was a lot
going on, so I couldn't contact you.
I know you went through a lot.
Get some rest! And tell
me more about it later.
Okay.
Uravity, we're starting basic training.
"Pro Hero - Gunhead"
Oh, right, sir!
Well, I'll see you at school.
Sorry to bother you while you're busy! Bye!
Your boyfriend?
N-No! That's not it!
"Uraraka"
"Telephone Corner"
Talking on the phone with
a girl is... amazing!
Man, her voice was so close!
Oh, Iida, just now, Uraraka said...
Midoriya.
Iida just finished getting examined.
My left hand might have long-term damage...
Long-term... damage...?!
"Izuku Midoriya"
"Quirk: One For All"
"Smashes villains with a super power passed down from one generation to the next."
"Affiliation: U.A. High School Hero Class 1-A"
"Birthday: 7/15" "Height: 166 cm"
"Blood Type: O" "Likes: Pork Cutlet Bowl"
"All Might (True Form)"
"Quirk: One For All"
"Smashes villains with a super power passed down from one generation to the next."
"Affiliation: U.A. High School Hero Class Teacher"
"Birthday: 6/10" "Height: 220 cm"
"Blood Type: A" "Likes: Yakushima Cedar"
Long-term... damage...
Both of my arms were pretty beat up,
but it looks like the damage
to my left arm was especially severe.
There was damage to my brachial plexus.
But it just means that I'll have
trouble moving my hand and fingers
and experience some numbness.
Apparently, there's a possibility that it
can be healed with nerve transplant surgery.
When I found the hero killer,
I stopped being able to think.
The first thing I should've
done was tell Manual.
But I forgot myself in my anger.
Being taken in by the hatred before you
and trying to fulfill your own desires...
That is the furthest from
what a hero should be.
I hate him, but he spoke the truth.
That's why,
until I become a true hero,
I think I want to leave
my left hand as it is.
Iida...
Back then, if I had been more emphatic...
No, stop.
Iida's already accepted it.
It would be rude of me to apologize.
Iida, I feel the same way.
I will let this hand guide me.
Let's become stronger... together.
I feel... kind of bad...
About what?
I feel like if I get involved...
other people mess up their hands...
Is it a curse?
"Hosu General Hospital"
Todoroki, I didn't know you could make jokes!
No, I'm not joking.
I'm like "The Hand Crusher" or something.
"The Hand Crusher"!
"Staff Room"
A phone call... is here!
"Pro Hero - Present Mic"
"Pro Hero: Eraser Head - Quirk: Erasure"
"Pro Hero - All Might - Quirk: One For All"
A phone--
Yes, hello?
That ringtone is annoying as usual.
S-Sir!
Izuku Midoriya! Goodness!
"Telephone Corner"
Thanks to him, I'm getting a pay cut,
and my teaching license
is being revoked for six months.
Well, considering the extenuating
circumstances, it couldn't be helped.
The part where he just starts moving
without thinking is just like you, Toshinori!
I humbly apologize!
It is because of my insufficient teaching...
To cause you such trouble...
Oh dear...
I don't care about my teaching
license anymore anyway.
I only got it to teach you so I could keep
my promise to your predecessor, Shimura.
And I truly appreciate what you did.
I am who I am today because of your teaching.
You say that, but you never come to visit.
I-It's just that...
my new life as a teacher is so busy...
I called today to talk about the hero killer.
I only saw him in person for a few minutes,
but even so, he had me shaking.
"Lounge"
To be able to frighten
someone like you, Gran Torino...
But he had already been
tied up, so what was it...?
The pressure I felt from him
was probably his strong ideology...
...or the intimidation from his obsession.
I'm not saying this to praise him,
but it's the same quality as that
"Symbol of Peace" thing you have.
The same quality...
To put it simply, it's charisma.
"Hero Killer: Stain's Ideology"
As the investigation continues, his ideology
and opinion will be all over the media--
online news, TV, magazines...
The current age, for better
or worse, is one of suppression.
People influenced by
his ideas will definitely appear.
It's true that there will be
those influenced by him,
but they will probably appear sporadically.
When they appear one by one, heroes
will take care of them like they did this time.
That's where the League of Villains comes in.
The Hosu incident suggests that Stain
and the League are connected somehow.
With this,
the League will go from being thought of as a
bunch of juvenile delinquents that attacked U.A.
to being recognized as
the group with that ideology.
In other words, there's a
receptacle ready to receive them.
Even if the malice of each individual is small,
if all that evil gathers under one will,
it will swell up to hundreds of times that.
If the enemy general knew
this would happen from the beginning...
...then he's pretty good.
He's steadily getting rid of obstacles,
trying to create conditions
to further his own purpose.
When I heard from Tsukauchi
that Nomu had multiple Quirks,
I had a bad feeling...
The man who killed my
sworn friend and your master,
the previous One For All holder, Shimura,
and opened that hole in your stomach...
All For One must be starting to move again.
For him to have survived after that injury
is a reality I don't want to believe.
Toshinori, that child
admires you so bravely...
You should find time to tell him properly
about everything concerning
you and One For All.
Two days after the Hosu incident,
the hero killer's identity started
being exposed from various angles.
Recently, there've been
less people willing to break the law.
My buddies are all complaining
about not being able to sell anything.
It's a pain.
'Cause it's a serious crime to develop or sell
support items and costumes without a license...
On top of that, there have been rumors
recently that legit support companies
have been selling on the black market
to people without hero licenses.
I miss the days back before All Might...
I was still young back then, too.
The villains were wild and impulsive,
and that turned into enthusiasm
the whole country was teeming with.
It was a good time.
But when All Might appeared,
everything changed.
It's all thanks to that Symbol of Justice.
Maybe it's time for me to retire.
About that.
Listen to this.
Just between you and me,
I know of a way to make some cash.
I'm only telling you because
I know you guys have quality goods.
Have you seen this video?
Huh? Who's this?
It's a video of the "hero killer."
He's hot right now.
Hero Killer: Stain. Real
name: Chizome Akaguro.
All Might's debut left a deep impression on him,
and he set his sights on becoming a hero.
He enrolled in a private hero high school
but was disappointed in the fundamentally
depraved view of heroes taught
by the educational system.
He dropped out in the
summer of his first year.
Until the end of his teenage years,
he called for a return to the old idea of heroes
making speeches on the street until he
realized resignedly that words had no power.
For the next ten years,
in order to fulfill his "duty,"
he studied and trained
in killing techniques on his own.
During this time, his parents passed away,
and that affair was considered non-criminal.
He emphasized a return
to the old idea of heroes.
Heroes should not seek compensation.
The title of "hero" must only be granted
to those who epitomize self-sacrifice.
The present-day heroes
are fakes who are all talk.
He wanted society to realize this
through his purges one after another.
Someone must be dyed in blood...
I must take back what it means to be a hero!
Come! Try and get me, you fakes!
The only one I'll let
kill me is the true hero...
...All Might!
This keeps getting uploaded and taken
down online, like a game of cat and mouse.
Both sides have realized...
Especially the last part...
This guy's way of life is infectious.
From scoundrels with countless
previous convictions to felons on the run,
all the major players...
Including me, of course...
Not that many people have noticed yet,
but the evil that was scattered,
hiding deep and quiet in places
where no one could see them,
has now been hit by a single fever...
To go to the organization
Hero Killer: Stain is part of...
They have started heading
to the League of Villains.
"Preview"
Here's the preview!
I wonder how everyone's internships
went while I was in the hospital...
You curious, Midoriya?
Asu... I mean, Tsu!
Then we'll respond to your request
by showing Class A at their internships.
I'm looking forward to that.
But then, your part in
the episode will be smaller.
Ribbit, ribbit.
Next time, "Everyone's Internships."
You can enjoy watching me
in this anime-original episode!
Go beyond!
"Next time: Everyone's Internships"
Plus Ultra!