I'm sorry.
Senpai, what is this?
What's this all about?
What happened?
And are you okay?
It's all my fault...
I...
Hey, where are you guys?
Nee-chan?
Where'd everyone go?
What is this?
What's going on?
This is...
This is where...
That's right.
I...
Ta-Takatsuki-senpai?
I... came to this planet on this ship.
I'm...
...not from this planet.
That's right.
I knew this.
That's why...
I'm not surprised.
This is kind of... sci-fi.
Yeah.
It doesn't work?
I got into an accident on
my way to this planet.
It can't fly now.
And there's a problem with the system.
I'd been planning on just living here...
That's why you went to
Kirishima-kun's house?
There are other reasons, too...
So what's that mecha thing we just saw?
It attacked you, maybe?
No, that... that's an
emergency rescue pod.
The ship automatically
sent a distress signal,
and it came to rescue me.
And you broke it?
Well... It just happened that way.
Happened that way?
This ship doesn't fly, right?
Are you sure you don't
want to be rescued?
Not really, but...
I wanted to stay on this planet.
Why?
I came to look for a certain
place on this planet.
A certain place?
A place in my memories.
I don't even know if it really exists...
But I want to go there.
That's why I...
Don't worry, Senpai.
We won't tell anybody
you're an alien, right?
W-Well, sure.
Nobody would believe us anyway.
But if the Men in Black find out...
Huh?
There is no such organization.
A-And dissection?
Won't happen to you.
Was that worrying you?
B-But...
Takatsuki-senpai, I won't tell anybody.
Neither will I.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
There's no need to apologize.
Um, since we're here,
can we wander around?
Tetsuro, how can you say
that at a time like this?
But this is a once in a
lifetime chance, right?
Don't you think so, Mio?
Well, maybe...
It is interesting, isn't it?
Right?
This is amazing.
Really convenient!
Tetsuro-kun.
Look at the time!
Everybody's gotta be really worried.
I'll walk you home.
Oh, crap, I forgot about my sister!
I'm sorry.
Keeping you this late...
Making you listen to me...
Don't worry.
Just act like you usually do, Ichika.
Yeah.
I'm really surprised that
Takatsuki-senpai's an alien.
In fact, I still can't believe it!
I'd be more likely to believe
it was all just a prank.
Oh my, I'd suspected it.
Really?
It sounds like a lie,
but I can't totally say so.
It's true.
Because I'm an agent of the Men in Black.
That's a lie.
And what kind of joke is that?
Takatsuki-senpai would get scared!
What's Kai gonna do?
That's right.
It's been a really long day, hasn't it?
Let's get home and...
Kaito-kun...
There's something I haven't told you yet.
What?
When I first came to this
planet in my spaceship,
I... You were...
You saved me.
If you weren't there, I
might have died, right?
You knew?
I remembered, actually.
I used the technology from
my planet to heal you,
so I was worried there
might be some problems.
That's why you stayed with me?
I'm sorry.
No, don't worry about it.
Whether it was an
accident or whatever...
It led me to you, and that
makes me really happy.
That's right.
The problem isn't that she's an alien.
That's not the problem, it's...
You don't have to apologize.
I actually feel better
after telling everybody.
But when the Federation Police find out
that their rescue pod was destroyed,
they might send somebody to investigate.
That might cause problems for everyone.
I might hurt him again.
I don't have much time.
Not much time left...
It's been a long time since
you came to my house.
Sorry for just saying I wanted
to stay over all of a sudden.
That's fine, but why?
Because I thought you
weren't sure what to do.
Yeah, that's right.
Now that I know
Takatsuki-senpai's an alien...
Not that.
About Kirishima-kun.
What's he going to do? If she's
an alien, then someday...
Don't say it!
When I think about that, I hate myself.
I feel like I'm not being fair.
That's fine.
You can't help loving someone.
You can't, huh...
Wait, how do you know how I feel?
It's obvious, isn't it?
Kaito-kun, thank you so
much for everything!
I'm going home.
I'll never forget you or the
time we spent together!
Senpai!
I'll get a job or do whatever I
have to, and come to see you!
But my home's in Andromeda.
2.3 million light years?!
Space is big.
Senpai?
Good morning, Kaito-kun.
I'm going out for a while.
Going out?
Are you going to look for that place?
Yeah.
I made breakfast.
I'll be back by dinner.
Bye.
What am I doing?
Staying on this planet will
cause problems for everyone.
I should call for rescue right now.
Why don't I go home?
H-Hey, Mio?
Why don't we stop?
Why?
Because it was just yesterday!
Actually, today!
I don't know what to say
to Takatsuki-senpai!
Don't think about that.
Just act like you normally do.
I do think about that!
Come on!
Mio, has your personality changed
since you cut your hair?
Did something happen?
Nothing... really...
Huh? What are you doing?
I see. So she's gone out.
She said she was looking for the
place she talked about yesterday.
She went alone?
Why would she be so secretive?
We'd help if she asked.
She's got a lot to think about, I bet.
Wanna film?
Yeah.
Okay, go to the side.
Now get hit.
I first learned about him...
...from the rumors my classmates shared.
Transfer student?
I heard he's the grandson of
old man Kirishima at the town hall.
Oh, the weirdo?
He lost his parents in an accident,
and came back here, my mom said.
Poor kid.
Everybody, sit down.
I'll introduce your new classmate.
My name is Kaito Kirishima.
I've come from Tokyo.
Nice to meet you all.
The smile on his face made it impossible...
...to believe he'd just lost his parents.
When I put myself in his position,
I don't think I could smile at all.
But the way he kept trying to smile...
I think that's when I started to like him.
That expression on his face...
It's just like the one he has now.
Episode 9
Senpai
I can buy more film if I run out.
Maybe I should take an umbrella, too.
Oh, good morning, Senpai.
M-Morning.
You're up early today.
You're going to look again today, right?
Let me help.
I asked everybody to put the
filming on hold for a while.
From now on...
Um... I'll go by myself.
I can't cause trouble for you.
This is my problem.
But...
Thank you.
But I'm sorry.
Good luck with the movie.
Bye!
Senpai!
I said we weren't filming today, didn't I?
Is my coming over a bad thing?
No, not bad, it's just...
It's good.
I'm not talking about the watermelon.
Ichika-senpai's out again?
Yeah.
Why aren't you helping?
She said the problem
was hers and refused.
She said good luck with the movie.
I see.
What's wrong?
I remembered some scenery cuts I forgot.
I'm going to Karuizawa.
If you go home, lock the doors here.
Wai— Kai!
You can leave the key in
the usual spot, okay?
Okay?
What am I supposed to do with this?
Oh...
Tetsuro?
What, more watermelons?
Where's Kaito-kun?
He said he was gonna
get some scenery cuts.
Where's Takatsuki-senpai?
Out.
So what are you doing?
Kanna?
What? What?
This is from when we
went to Karuizawa...
You look really cute!
Takatsuki-senpai.
I didn't know he took this.
Kanna?
Oh, sorry.
It's nothing. Nothing.
Yeah?
Forget it, let's all
eat this watermelon!
O-Okay.
Hey, cutie.
Wanna go on a date with me?
Not in a million years.
You're upset.
Do I look it?
The reason is... Let's see.
Something happened with Ichika?
Nothing.
Actually, she won't let me do anything.
She doesn't know how I feel.
You're a kid.
Sulking because things
aren't going your way.
That's not it.
Then do you know how Ichika feels?
What do you think she
was thinking and feeling...
...when she came to this planet alone?
What is she thinking and feeling now?
Have you thought about that?
After all the courage it must've
taken to tell you who she really is,
have you done anything for her in return?
I...
What should I do?
That's what I'm saying
you should think about.
What can you do for her?
What should you do?
If you care about her, you
should find your answer.
Thank you.
I'll think about it.
That's right.
Move.
Don't stop.
Move forward.
Kaito Kirishima
What is Kai doing?
He's never home.
And he doesn't pick up his phone.
Satoshi, you idiot.
I'm not coming home anymore.
And go home already, Nee-chan!
Kaito-kun?
The person I love...
The person I...
I looked at FT-32, so next is PF...
Where are you going?
Tanigawa-san?
Are you looking for that place again?
Yes...
And when you find it,
you're going back to
your home planet, right?
That's fine with me.
I actually consider it lucky.
Because I...
...like Kaito-kun.
I'll be much happier once my rival's gone!
Tanigawa-san?
You know how Kaito-kun feels, right?
Even I can tell.
So you should know, too.
And I know something else.
You like him, too.
Right?
Wh-What are you talking about?
I...
Can't tell him because you're an alien?
And you can't be with him because
you can't stay here forever?
Are you going to use that as an excuse
to just keep running from him?
I'm not running...
You're running right now.
I'm looking for that place—
You're pretending to
look as hard as you can
so you don't have to look at him.
You're running!
I don't have a choice!
I can't stay here—
You do have a choice!
What is it then?
Tell him you like him!
Why don't you?
You can be with the person you like!
Isn't that a good thing?
It's something I can't have
no matter how much I want it,
and you can have it just
by reaching out.
And all you do is make
excuses and run.
You don't even know what
Kaito-kun is doing right now!
Kaito-kun?
What is he doing?
Find out yourself!
You idiot!
Why?
Why are you here?!
Is it that fun to watch me be rejected?
Were you just pretending to help
me so you could see this happen?
That's horrible!
Leave...
Go home...
Let me cry...
Please, Kanna.
Don't cry.
I love Kaito-kun.
I love him.
There's a tree and a lake...
What's at this place?
I guess that's enough.
Next is...
S-Senpai?
Why?
Jeez... nobody asked you to be so cool.
You were looking for it
for me, weren't you?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have...
I was thinking I had to go home.
Because I'd cause problems for everyone.
But I didn't want to.
Tanigawa-san made me realize
that the reason I didn't want to leave...
...wasn't just because I
wanted to go to that place.
It wasn't just that...
Um...
Is it okay that I'm an alien?
Am I good enough?
Yes.
Can I tell you I like you?
No.
I'll do it first.
I like you.
I always have.
From the first time I saw you, I think.
I don't think I knew,
but I fell in love.
Um, this is my first time, so...
This is my fourth time.
The first time was at the dam.
The second was when you
collapsed in the entryway.
The third was when the
rescue pod attacked.
They were all me?
It was to put the healing nanomachines
in my body inside you.
I'm glad they worked.
No way...
That's not romantic at all.
And...
There's more?
This is the fifth time.
Episode 10
Senpai and our...
Just like joy exists because of sadness,
someone is always crying in the
shadow of someone's happiness.
Even if you know that,
strong feelings don't go away.