I screwed up!
That one actually had me worried there
for a second, primitive creatures!
Once I steal those genes,
this planet is dust!
"Defensive Battle at Cosmopolitan Academy
(Second Part)"
Izuru...
It missed?
Move it, primitive creature!
I won't let you get your
hands on our school!
Gold 4's Mobile Assembly
Extreme Range Cannon
has begun recharging.
It will be done in 15 minutes.
Red 5's Harmonic Level is
continuing to increase.
But I'm not sure if he can
sustain this for very long...
Blue 1, Rose 3, once you've
eliminated your targets,
go offer Red 5 support!
Roger!
Tamaki, what are you doing?!
Rose 3 isn't flying right!
The unit musta gotten damaged here
and there when we
entered the atmosphere.
Jeez, of all the times...!
Hang tight, Izuru!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry it up!
Please hurry and charge up!
I'm going to send you some
of Purple 2's energy.
It should cut your charge time a bit.
All pit ships, direct your
energy to him as well.
Relay the energy to Gold
4 through Purple 2!
Confirming receipt of
the microwave energy.
Firing the energy to Gold 4!
Wow, that's fast!
Actually, isn't this dangerously fast?
We won't make it in time if
we wait for a full recharge.
But without sufficient power,
we can't shoot that enemy down!
Your pathetic weapons can't harm me!
Izuru!
It's the end of the line.
Asagi, Tamaki, now! Attack him!
You better dodge this, Izuru!
No matter how many of you face
me, the outcome will be the same!
Please go straight!
This is bad.
At this rate, I'm going
to run out of energy...!
We have to stop him, no matter what!
Tamaki, ram into him from behind!
Huh? Why?
Just do it!
Suruga, what's your energy at?
Around 70%. It still isn't enough!
When Tamaki makes contact with
Klein's unit, shoot Rose 3.
At the same time, Izuru and Asagi,
you are to help Tamaki escape!
Shoot Rose 3...?
Oh, I get it!
Roger!
Gold 4 is on the brink of overloading
due to forcing it to recharge too fast.
This is our last chance!
There won't be any second
chances if I miss.
Calm down, Ataru Suruga!
You can do it!
You can do it...
Calm down.
Calm down...
The sight's precision is improving!
Could the pilot's heightened
concentration have something to do with this?
Gold 4's Harmonic Level
is also increasing.
This is his highest level thus far.
Crap!
You're finished!
Izuru!
These feeble attacks-
What are you plotting?!
Tamaki, eject!
The enemy squad has been
completely subdued!
All five members of Team
Rabbits are unharmed!
They did it, Rin-Rin!
Yeah, but it was close.
Is that the extent of your power?!
Show me what you're made of!
You still haven't given
me a flippin' good fight!
You need more freakin' fighting spirit!
Grab a pair of balls and come at me!
I wanted to see Tamaki...
Tamaki...
Which side's winning down there?
I'm not sure, but the battle
on Earth should be over soon.
If Rabbits wins, it should
influence our battle
here on the frontlines.
Look! The enemy is
starting to pull back.
Which means Izuru and the
others won their battle, huh?
All of you better be alive
and hoppin', Bunnies!
Klein's squad was annihilated?
I'm afraid it would seem that way.
We are approaching the limit to
how long we can remain active.
May we receive permission
to return to base?
Very well. Permission to
return has been granted.
I shall take a different route back.
I will see you in person shortly.
So the time to implement
his plan has come...
Fully dismantle each unit and
give them thorough checks.
Identify everything that
needs to be replaced.
For anything lacking a spare,
contact Earth and have them
send a replacement immediately!
They might have to sortie again soon!
Commence repair work at full power!
It took an even worse
beating than usual, huh?
We're gonna be up all night!
Hey, we should be grateful that
Izu-boing came back safe and sound.
It's proof that we've done a
good job maintaining this puppy!
Yeah! Now it's our turn to hop to work.
You guys have it good...
You can jump straight to work!
Minus Rose 3's core, everything
is still in pieces down on Earth.
Yup, yup.
The core was all that survived.
Everything else has to
be remade from scratch!
I wish we could fly to
Earth right this second
and retrieve the battered
and beaten Rose 3!
Yup, yup.
Our little lady is all right, isn't she?
Yep! Her unit may have
been terribly damaged,
but I've heard that our pilot
walked away without a scratch.
What a relief!
If anything happened to
her, it'd be our fault.
We'll have to hold a party to
celebrate her victory later.
With a cake and tea!
Agreed!
I've heard that our
Suruga was a big help.
It proves that our theory was right!
Ultimately, even sniping
relies on physical prowess!
His daily bodybuilding workouts
with us are starting to pay off!
Let's double our workout routine!
Two sets of 100 push-ups and
two sets of 100 sit-ups!
Agreed!
Everyone sure is hyped up...
It's normal for people to act
this way after winning a battle.
Izu-boing and the others
did their best out there!
Now it's our turn to
step up and work hard.
I bet they're sound
asleep in bed by now...
The shock from the blast destroyed
literally all of the school's windows.
The building was also destroyed.
Likewise, the inner facilities
were substantially damaged!
Furthermore, you made a massive
crater on school grounds!
Naturally, the outer
walls were also damaged!
Blue 1 and Red 5's transport chains
are damaged in countless locations!
Purple 2 and Gold 4 were mostly
destroyed by the shock created
when the Mobile Assembly
Extreme Range Cannon exploded.
As for Rose 3, aside from the core, it
was essentially blown to smithereens!
It's going to take a long time before
all of the spare parts come in
and your units are made
operational again!
Yeah... But, hey, we
protected the academy!
We should be happy it
didn't turn out worse...
There are limits to such things!
What would you have done if
you destroyed the school?!
But...
Well, you did a good job out there.
Job well done.
Job well-
Izuru?
Don't fall asleep!
Tamaki Irie, would you like
to hang out with me tomorrow?
Why do we have to hold
his hand like this?
Since we're a team,
we're as good as family.
We live and die together, right?
Yo! Great work out there.
Th-thank you. I'm honored.
Would you like to hang
out with me tomorrow?!
Pardon?
Not what I meant! That was a mistake!
That didn't happen! Scratch that!
Dude, you need to calm down.
I think you should pull back for
now and regain your bearing.
It's a tactical retreat.
So we'll chill out with
you some other time, 'kay?
Consequentially, the
enemy forces retreated,
but the allied armies
suffered immense losses.
Earth's forces have been
diminished to next to nothing.
The masses seem to be
greatly distraught as well.
So their sense of danger
is beginning to escalate.
Correct.
Until now, they probably considered
this on the same level
as military terrorists in
the far reaches of space.
But since this last attack was a
direct assault on Earth itself...
And nothing but the AHSMB seem to
be effective against the Wulgaru?
Right. If we don't start
mass producing them...
But will that alone be enough
to drive the enemy away?
I just received an encrypted
message from Legatus Lumes
that was hidden in a
transmission from Earth.
From Lumes?
When he came into contact with
one of Earth's data devices,
it would seem that he infiltrated
and tampered with the system.
At any rate, he gave the
impression that he was already
aware of your presence on Earth.
So he has found out about us...
But I came prepared to
face the consequences...
According to the transmission,
your brother is waiting
to hear from you.
How would you like me to respond?
Not so much as a single unit
from Klein's squad returned?
Sir! Although they
reaped what they sowed,
it nonetheless pains my heart
to lose an entire squad led
by a Military Commander.
Bluntly put, the position
as Military Commander
was too great for Klein.
He was a disgrace to the Wulgaru race.
Next time, we must choose someone
a bit more worthy of the title.
One who has not been fighting
has no right to say such things, Lutiel.
When you get down to it,
was there a stock of
DNA on the primitives'
home world or not?
Unfortunately, I am afraid we were
unable to verify that information.
Then why don't we hurry and
send out the next squad?
If you like, I'd be willing
to dispatch the men.
After this incident, I imagine
Earth will be on heightened alert.
I believe we should wait and
watch for a while first.
What a boring and cautious plan!
It's just like you!
There is one thing I wish to report.
I took a look at Klein's battle
records from his last skirmish.
I've noticed that the humans
frequently sacrifice themselves
in order to rescue another individual.
To meet those ends,
sometimes they take unexpected
measures to throw us into confusion.
Doesn't that simply prove
that they are lower animals?
Rather than leisurely biding our time,
we should finish them
off in one fell swoop!
In certain aspects, the Earthlings
vary from other species
we have encountered in the past.
We cannot afford another mishap
like with Legatus Klein.
What are your thoughts
in regard to Legatus Dolgana's
observation earlier?
About how the Earthlings
defend one another?
After all this time,
it would seem that someone else
has finally noticed that trait.
Then you had already noticed
this, Prince Jiart?
Naturally.
Usually, intelligent creatures have a
tendency to develop overall equally.
If one forms a weakness, its own
kind will target that individual.
But what if, one was guaranteed
to not be attacked by the others?
The various individuals
could develop their talents,
allowing them to compensate
for their weaknesses while
functioning in society.
It would almost be as if
they were one life form...
But that is impossible.
If the animals possess a certain
degree of intelligence,
it is only natural for the species
to begin warring amongst
themselves for personal gain.
That's right.
Cooperation is only a possibility if
both sides have something
substantial to gain from it.
As is the case with my clan and yours.
My family has served your clan
for generations, Prince Jiart.
I am grateful that you
allow me to serve you.
The Earthlings are
completely alien to us.
But that is precisely
what makes them amusing.
I take it you were unable
to make contact with Teoria?
Correct. Instead I followed
your instructions
and sent a transmission to Daneel
through the Earth's
communications circuit.
Unfortunately, I was unable to
confirm whether he received the message.
I take it no one noticed.
Sir, not even King Galkie.
Keep it that way.
We shall give Teoria some
time to see how she responds.
Rada!
It looks like he overheard us.
What would you have me do?
I learned something I shouldn't have!
I'm dead!
He's going to kill me!
Legatus Rada, under orders by Pleguzes
Jiart, you are under arrest!
Under arrest?! What have I done?
Please take your question
directly to Pleguzes.
"Treason," you say?
Yes, your Majesty.
Legatus Rada just came before
Pleguzes Jiart and me
and invited us to join him as
conspirators in his rebellion.
Naturally, we rejected his offer
and are currently tracking Rada down.
Rada did that...?
Pleguzes Jiart requests that
you leave the matter to his discretion.
Very well. It is in his hands.
How do you perceive this?
The weak always lose.
It's as simple as that.
He outmaneuvered me!
What should I do?! Where can I run?
I must hurry and inform King Galkie!
I must hurry!
I must hurry or else...!
Why aren't I getting through?!
Don't come after me! Don't! Don't!
That's it! I'll use that gate.
If I can just make it through that...!
Almost there!
This is the Wulgaru way, Teoria...
"Deep Recon"