"Genes of Destiny"
Please look after them.
Certainly!
Everyone, you gotta eat
to keep up your strength!
Guys, we gotta eat to
keep up our strength!
Why are you repeating her?
Huh?
I still can't believe it.
What?
They were here with us,
but now they're gone...
I know...
Hey!
Uh, um, none of us really
know what to say...
I'm the same way.
I'm still trying to cope
with what happened.
I... can imagine.
But Randy and Patrick
fulfilled their mission.
Here.
It's from Patrick.
He was planning on giving this to you.
He said it's your favorite.
PREMIUM PICKLED SQUID GUTS
Tamaki, he knew how you love that stuff.
I-I'm gonna have some!
Are you okay?
Here is some water!
It's good...
It's super good!
Excuse me!
Here is the data.
The gate is located in
the Outer Solar System.
The Wulgaru are using this
gate to invade Earth.
So if we seize this gate, the
invasion will come to a halt?
The remaining Wulgaru would be unable
to survive for long without
replacement cartridges.
If we could just destroy that gate...
I wish it would be that simple.
It will be incredibly difficult for us
to approach the gate
unnoticed and destroy it.
Isn't it your job to devise plans?
That will be tough enough,
but it'll be impossible
to carry out the plan
if we don't get all
of the economic powers
to consent and offer their support!
We must do this, even
if it's impossible!
Yes, sir!
We cannot cast aside the
data that two of the
Dobermans died to deliver.
Very well!
Here I am!
You have a grain of rice on your cheek.
Huh? Where? Where?
Might be because I had some
more pickled squid guts.
You're going to get a tummy ache.
Hey, Tamaki!
Let's sleep together.
Just this once.
Uh-huh!
Hey-
Say...
Yes?
Do you think that just
maybe Patrick liked me...?
I never even noticed.
What should I do?
Why don't you act like always, Tamaki?
Like always?
Stay the pickled gut-loving,
lively yet dense,
naïve and kind Tamaki...
Kei...
Thank you...
You know, I can't seem
to fall asleep myself.
Me, too.
And my tummy hurts!
What?!
Here's your water.
You shouldn't gobble it down.
I couldn't help it...
So...
...what are all of you
doing in my room?!
That doesn't resemble them...
But won't they be immortalized
if Izuru draws a picture of them?
Izuru?
Izuru?!
This looks similar to Progeria Syndrome.
What does that mean?
His telomeres are shrinking.
On top of that, there is a decline
in his cellular regeneration.
It's creating a phenomenon
similar to premature aging.
He's declining faster than
when I examined him last.
If this continues, it
could prove fatal...
It could kill him?!
Could piloting an awakened
AHSMB have caused this?
The AHSMB awoke...?
What is this about?
I knew that there could
be some side effects...
But I never expected
something like this.
I want the full story!
Try to get some rest.
Okay!
You've been through a lot.
You must be mentally and
physically exhausted.
Yeah...
Izuru!
Are you all right?
Yep.
Here.
Thanks.
Maybe you should get some sleep.
But not until after you eat.
I know! I'll go get my special
pickled squid guts for you!
I'll pass on that!
Then I'll stay here
until you fall asleep.
I'm going to report to
the captain right quick.
I'm gonna head on out, okay?
How's Izuru?
He's going to sleep now.
Kei said she's gonna
stay with him for a bit.
Got it.
Where's Ange?
Ange is getting reexamined.
Commander Simon, I'd like
to ask a favor of you.
What is it?
I want to know about
his genetic background.
I'm sure Lt. Commander Suzukaze
has already told you,
but he is gravely ill.
And I cannot find an
effective treatment.
In order to further his treatment,
I need to know who his DNA donors were
along with the circumstances
under which he was born.
I will give it some thought.
Thank you.
Commander Simon, this is Amane.
What is it?
I have a favor to ask of you.
Another one?
Sir?
No, it's nothing.
Regarding the plan to destroy the gate.
I summoned the leaders of the various
economic powers to a conference.
I would like to ask them to offer
their unreserved support when we meet.
However, I was only able
to successfully negotiate
with the Organization of
American States beforehand.
And?
There is something that
I absolutely must have if
I am to make this operation succeed.
Commander Simon...
For those of you here,
I am most grateful that you could
make today's conference
despite the lack of notice.
Today, we of the GDF have decided
to launch a full-scale attack
operation on the Wulgaru.
Upon analyzing the information
that the MJP retrieved,
we've learned that mankind now
has no choice but to work together
to carry out this operation.
GDF Chief of Staff for Operations,
Captain Amane, explain the operation.
Yes sir! Thank you for coming today.
I will explain the details
of the operation at
another time to protect
their confidentiality.
In order to make this operation succeed,
I request that every economic
power offer their support.
We can't blindly pledge our support...
We are ready to offer our full support.
We can't help when you
can't disclose any details!
Here is the plan.
This gate is what the Wulgaru have
been using to invade our world.
It is possible for a fleet
to pass through in formation.
Until we destroy this, we cannot
stop the Wulgaru invasion.
It is the target for our operation.
After retreat upon retreat,
we have allowed them to
set foot on Earth's soil.
Fortunately, we were able
to repel their forces.
However, we lack the forces needed
to protect Earth indefinitely.
This is not about our beliefs or ideals.
We are fighting for our very survival.
To destroy the gate,
we must bring all of our forces
together and hit that one target
with everything we have!
How likely is that plan to succeed?
If we combine all of our
forces and that plan fails,
wouldn't that spell
instant annihilation?
Now Ange is getting
reexamined! What gives?!
True, both Izuru and Ange tend to
get so excited on the battlefield
that they act like completely
different people.
They must get pretty stressed out...
Asagi! Just who I wanted to see.
Red 5's pit crew were hoping
that you could stand
in for some test runs.
Thank you for helping out.
It's nothing...
We heard that Izuru was
still in the hospital...
Is Izurucchi gonna be okay?
Yeah, probably.
Really? That's great!
We were told that no matter
what happens to Izuru,
this has to be ready to
go at a moment's notice.
Sorry, but could you help
us out with some tests?
Each AHSMB has its pilot's
DNA programmed into it,
so I doubt I'll be able to pilot Red 5.
You can't activate it, but isn't
it the same type as your Blue 1?
We're just going to run some tests,
so all we need you to do is sit in it.
But...
At any rate, you should
quit your griping and groaning.
Go give it a try.
Come to think of it, I've never
been inside another AHSMB before...
We have to get ready for the
test run, so hang tight.
Uh, okay.
It started up?!
Why?
There is a possibility
that they won't attack us!
Isn't there some way to
resolve this peacefully?
Even if it means giving
up some planets and bases,
wouldn't that be preferable
over this foolhardy operation?
Peace is not an option.
What makes you so certain?
I believe you will come to
understand after you hear her.
I present to you the Wulgaru
defector, Imperial Princess Teoria.
A Wulgaru defector?!
Hey! I never heard about this!
A vessel belonging to one of the
economic powers in the Pacific Rim
just so happened to stumble upon her
royal highness and
offered her sanctuary.
Why was this kept secret until now?
To avert unnecessary panic.
Furthermore, her royal highness
was apprehensive that
this could end in all-out war.
However, she does not wish
to see us get slaughtered.
Everyone, first I wish to apologize
for the great calamity my planet,
which you refer to as, "Wulgaru,"
has brought upon you.
My world has attacked a great many
planets throughout our history.
This act, which we call "hunting,"
will not end until we have annihilated
all life on our target planet.
You could say that this is
both part of our unique
culture as well as a behavioral trait.
However, I began to question
and loathe our ways,
which led me to leave my people.
In an effort to prevent
your annihilation,
I have offered Earth my
assistance throughout the war.
Unfortunately, repelling
our army has proven to be
an extremely difficult task.
However, if you destroy that gate,
the invasion will come
to a complete halt.
I believe that is the only
option left before you.
Is that really a Wulgaru princess?
If she's from the enemy
side, why is she helping us?
Can we actually believe
anything she tells us?
A heat source located
above satellite orbit is
quickly approaching GDF Headquarters.
I repeat: A heat source located above
satellite orbit is quickly
approaching GDF Headquarters.
Please remain calm!
The unidentified flying object will
reach GDF Headquarters in- uh...
Confirming the identification code!
The identification
code belongs to the...
...MJP!
That's a Wulgaru ship?!
What's it doing here?!
What's going on...?
Commander Simon...?
This is the Imperial Princess
Teoria of the Wulgaru!
Please forgive my unseemly entrance.
In order to prove what
I said to be true,
I wanted everyone to
see the Wulgaru unit
that I used to fly here.
Our technology served
as the foundation for
the AHSMB units developed by the MJP.
I will participate in this operation.
If everyone does likewise, I shall
share my information with you.
I implore you to offer your cooperation.
There! That's it for our tests.
Asagi, thank you.
Uh, it was nothing.
We weren't able to get
everything done...
What are you up to?
Oh, Boss!
We asked Asagi to help
with Red 5's tests,
and then the unit turned on!
Huh? How did you activate it?
Uh, well, like I would my own...
What gives?
I wonder if Asagi and
Izuru share similar DNA.
Like siblings?
I see. So that's why Red 5 activated.
Of all the unlikely...!
So you didn't know about this?
No...
Asagi is rather shaken.
You should be the one to
explain things to him.
This is classified information!
But don't those two have
a right to know the truth?
I take it this is about
how Red 5 activated.
Yes, ma'am. Commander Simon explained
how our DNA is programmed
into our AHSMB units.
So each unit can only be activated
by its designated pilot.
But I...
There was a system recognition error.
Are you telling me the truth?
Yeah.
I want to know what actually happened!
I can't fight feeling as I do right now!
Very well...
You know  that the MJP was originally
an organization dedicated
entirely to manipulating DNA
to develop humans suited
for space, right?
Yes...
But then the war with
the Wulgaru began...
That's when Imperial Princess
Teoria defected to Earth.
After she fled to Earth,
the organization was
transformed into the MJP,
which was meant to
cultivate AHSMB pilots.
You know about this, yes?
We used DNA brought from Wulgaru
to create those pilots.
But we needed to use as close to
pure Wulgaru DNA as possible...
As such, it was decided that
we would use Imperial
Princess Teoria's DNA.
Is that, uh...?
We used Imperial Princess
Teoria's DNA on Izuru.
Huh? Then how come I was
able to activate Red 5?
Your paternal DNA came
from the same source.
You mean-
I've said all I can.
Was it... Commander Simon?
You knew?!
No, I wouldn't say that.
So, in a way, you could say that
Izuru and I are like brothers.
Is that about right?
Asagi, could you please
keep this to yourself?
I never should have asked...
Asagi!
What is it?
Uh, it's nothing...
Where's Kei?
She was worried about Tamaki,
so she went back to her room.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing!
Are you okay?
Why don't you get a checkup, Asagi?
Nah, I... just have an ulcer.
You're acting kind of weird, Asagi.
No, not really.
I know!
Huh?
I bet you've got a crush
on someone, right?
Wh-where'd that come from?
You just mentioned Kei...
And then with talk about Patrick, too.
Kei? No, I don't really like anyone...
You do!
Moron! I just said that's not the deal!
Okay, got it.
Seriously. It's really
not like that, honest.
If we...
If we have something
we want tell someone,
we really should tell
them, shouldn't we?
While we still can.
Izuru, I want to tell you something.
I think you should know about this.
Asagi, don't tell me you...!
Izuru, you already knew?
Don't tell me...
...you like me?
HELL NO!
Sorry, but... But I...
Listen up!
The two of us share the same DNA!
In a way, we're brothers.
We're brothers?
You and I...
Big Brother!
I appreciate your cooperation
in this operation.
Captain Amane will be the
commanding officer presiding
over the operation to destroy the gate.
"Night before the Decisive Battle"