How enjoyable! How truly enjoyable!
But this isn't all!
This isn't the extent of my power!
Not by a long shot!
I hope you haven't forgotten me!
Burst into bloom, Antirrhinum majus!
Amagiri Shinmei Style,
Intermediate Skill...
Six Slaying Wasps!
I'm not done yet!
Clinching Victory
The figures for this rate
of increase are insane!
You need to stop him right now!
But RM-C's already ceded Limit Control,
so there's nothing I can do now.
You can still force-quit, can't you?
The puppet's central system
could sustain some damage,
but that's what should
be done if necessary!
That's your responsibility.
Responsibility, huh?
See, it might not be so obvious,
but I really do have faith...
in them, that is.
Ayato...
What on earth is that?
We should've realized it sooner.
No matter how ironclad
that protective wall may be,
it can't possibly trade blows
head-on with the Ser=Versta.
The only thing
that was able to do that was...
The Gravi-Sheath, eh?
That's right.
Unless it's another Ogre Lux,
it shouldn't be able to block
the Ser=Versta's attacks.
AR-D must be using
Ulm Manadite as his engine.
Wait!
You mean that was AR-D
rampaging out of control right now?
No, though I'm sure all that
power's more than he can manage,
most likely AR-D is...
I see!
So this is it! This is my true power!
No wonder my master
warned me about it!
He has it under control?
Now, then, I hate to see this end,
but what do you say we settle this now?
Let's go!
Ayato, get back!
Come out, Rafflesia!
Impossible...
Now, then, it's my turn to pay you back!
No way!
Now, then... you will explode!
Now, then, why don't we
pick up where we left off?
Ayato, are you all right?
Julis!
I-I'm all right.
Or at least I'd like to say so,
but maybe not this time.
If only I could eclipse his speed,
then I could strike a decisive blow.
Speed, eh?
H-Hold up!
Julis, what are you...
I remember Claudia telling me once
that the Ser=Versta is known to assume
the form that best suits its wielder.
If we can make it do that, wouldn't that
give us some chance of winning?
Look, I'm not good at making
minor tweaks to my Prana.
I mean I'm hopeless.
Then let me handle that part.
All you have to do is pour
your Prana into this sword.
A-All right!
Ayato, try to picture it.
The ideal Ser=Versta
that you can wield most comfortably
in terms of shape and size!
It's done!
This is your...
Ayato Amagiri's Ser=Versta!
This is...
the ideal form for me?
This is all that I can do in this match.
Julis!
I'm leaving the rest to you, Ayato!
Roger that, Julis.
Sorry. Did I keep you waiting?
No, no, as it happens,
I was a bit out of shape myself.
Now I'm going to end this!
This match is mine!
I won't let you!
Amagiri Shinmei Style
Hidden Technique...
Moon of Carnage!
AMAGIRI SHINMEI STYLE
HIDDEN TECHNIQUE
MOON OF CARNAGE
Ernesta Kuhne... Badge broken!
Winners, Ayato Amagiri
and Julis-Alexia von Riessfeld!
We lost!
I have been trounced!
A-At last! At last, it's over!
After a showdown of epic proportions,
the Phoenix Festa has been won by...
Seidoukan Academy's Ayato Amagiri
and Julis-Alexia von Riessfeld!
The two-week-long Phoenix Festa.
Once again, we've seen
numerous epic battles.
And we were particularly astonished
by AR-D and RM-C's fighting skills, right?
Oh, yes!
And the team that prevailed against
them in that slugfest of a final was...
Seidoukan Academy's
Amagiri/Riessfield team!
And now, offering his
congratulations to Ayato Amagiri
is the Steering Committee chairman,
Mr. Madiath Mesa!
Ayato Amagiri
and Julis-Alexia von Riessfeld,
I commend you both
for your brilliant triumph,
your unbreakable spirit
and this glorious victory.
I found your matches
extremely compelling.
I'm looking forward to seeing
what you'll accomplish in the next festa.
Congratulations on your victory.
Thank you very much.
Ladies and gentlemen, please give
Mr. Amagiri a warm round of applause!
All right, everybody, see you again
next time, at the Gryps Festa.
Festa commentary was brought to you
by yours truly, Meeko Yanase and...
Your analyst, Pham Thi Tram!
Grimalkin...
Golden Eye... Number 7.
And your name is...
Verner, right?
That scar on your cheek...
I know it well.
You're a Shadow Star shinobi, right?
You... Whose orders
are you carrying out?
You tell me.
Congratulations on winning!
That's my Ayato!
Thanks, Saya...
It was a truly magnificent match.
That's my Ayato!
I owe it all to you guys.
I mean it. Thanks!
No, it wasn't just us.
Kirin, Yabuki and MacPhail
all pitched in, too.
Lester?
Th-There's nothing to thank me for!
That bastard Yabuki blackmailed me,
so I had no choice
but to help out. That's all!
Thanks, Lester. I owe you one.
Huh? Come to think of it,
where is Yabuki?
The bastard bounced
in the middle of the battle!
Dragging me out there,
then ditching me...
Next time I see him,
he's gonna wish he was never born!
It's called a Transformation Spell.
Oh, crap...
That was brand-new, wasn't it?
But sorry, Ayato.
We couldn't capture the perpetrator.
No need to apologize.
I mean, you all got out of there safely.
That's the most important thing.
Ayato...
All right, I'm out of here.
See ya!
Oh, wait...
What's up, Lester?
Well, uh... you know...
What the heck...
Let me just say, "Congrats."
Lester?
That MacPhail...
He just can't show
his honest feelings, can he?
Uh...
Can we help...
What do you want?
Saya Sasamiya...
I wish for a rematch with you.
I don't see why. We lost to you.
During yesterday's semifinal,
you and Dr. Sasamiya's Lux
was clearly superior to RM-C.
But not enough to beat the fused AR-D.
Using the fused AR-D is virtually
the same as using an Ogre Lux.
Ferrovius's philosophies are incompatible
with anything as unstable as an Ogre Lux.
Therefore, I personally cannot
acknowledge that as a victory.
Gotcha. Let's duel again
and settle the score.
Next time, I'm going to pummel you
until there's nothing left
and finish you off once and for all.
In that case,
we'll have to be better than you.
Right.
Why don't you give me
your answer from the other day?
Answer?
Whether or not
you're going to join forces with us.
Oh, that! Right.
Of course, my answer is...
No!
You guys just aren't my cup of tea!
But...
are you sure you're really going to
be able to finish the third puppet?
You can't find any compatible
Ulm Manadite, can you?
So I see. Hats off to you!
I still haven't even
told Camilla about her yet.
Just what you'd expect of Rewolf, right?
All right.
I guess I can at least
listen to what you have to say.
Fine. I'll be in touch.
All righty, who knows
what's going to happen next?
Congratulations on your victory,
Ayato-senpai.
Thanks.
But I was only able to win
because you guys did such a great job.
You did great, Kirin.
O-Oh no, not at all...
I didn't do anything.
Oh, Julis...
Are the police done questioning you?
Yes.
I gave them an earful about
what a heinous guy Dirk Eberwein is.
Right, Flora?
What are you doing, Flora?
What's wrong, Flora?
Oh, uh, everybody...
I know I caused you all
so much trouble!
Hey, listen.
It wasn't your fault
that it happened, Flora.
But it was such an important match
for you and the princess.
And to make matters worse,
Lady Toudou got these terrible injuries!
It's high time you let it go, Flora.
You're a good kid,
but you're still only ten.
It's all right to cry when you feel like it.
Y-Your Highness...
Your Highness!
I was so scared!
You were so brave, Flora.
You're safe now.
Whoa.
Well?
Julis?
Well...
True, I did summon you here
because I wanted to talk to you.
But when push comes to shove...
Um... in other words...
L-Listen, you!
S-Sorry!
Oh, hey, this is nothing.
I appreciate it, but you don't have to.
If I stained your
precious handkerchief,
you'd challenge me to another duel.
If I hadn't teamed up with you,
I couldn't have gotten this far.
Thanks to you,
my wish came true, as well.
I never thought I'd come
this far either... not without you.
But this is merely one checkpoint for us.
We have a long way to go.
I'll join you for the ride.
For you and for myself.
You will?
Yeah.
Then let's start with a toast!
To celebrate today's victory.
Right.
Hoping for our next victory.
The perpetrators have been arrested.
The abduction was carried out
by a mafia gang running the casino
where Ms. Klem was held captive.
Impossible!
That was clearly the work of...
Unfortunately,
we haven't been able
to find a shred of evidence
linking the Dante Ms. Sasamiya and
Ms. Toudou fought to any specific academy.
It looks like the investigation
will continue,
so I'd like you to take
a more long-term view of this.
Very well.
- By the way, Amagiri...
- Yes, sir?
I hear that as the winner
of the Phoenix Festa,
you've requested a search
for your older sister.
Right.
If she went missing here in Asterisk,
I'm sure there must be
some clues left behind.
I'll be praying for her safe return.
Thank you very much.
Seriously, thanks to you,
I'm completely swamped!
I only did it out of concern for you!
Even so, your methods
were too violent this time.
Next time, I wish
you'd try to hold back a little.
Talk to you later.
By the way,
aren't you going to tell him about
your relationship with that woman?
Sorry, but I have
no intention of going there.
Because it's a private matter.
Now, then...
what am I going to do about this?
Now...
That's strange. For some reason,
I'm recalling a scandal...
Oh, but there's nothing
we can do about the past.
Julis, my Ayato...
Congratulations on winning
the Phoenix Festa!
Episode 22
Lieseltania
Let's just zip through the next one, too!