Episode 12   Umaru and Everyone
Being big is a good thing!
It's an elephant.
It's so big.
Yep.
It's a whale.
Being big is a good thing!
It's so big.
Yep.
It's a dinosaur.
It's so big.
Y-Y-Yep...
It's a titan...
La, la, la, la, la, la...
It's so big.
It's going to eat us! Run!
I know! Let's go for a drive!
But I have to knit.
I'd rather stay home and play games.
No problem!
Because our car is a Dekantea!
Being big is a good thing!
Take your whole house on
a drive with Dekantea!
Being big is a good thing!
Yay!
Visit your local dealer for a test drive today.
Umaru, hurry and get up. It's time for school.
I'm still tired.
I guess it can't be helped.
Just sleep in the car, then.
Wake me up when we get to school.
A c-car?
You have a license, don't you, Onii-chan?
Well, yeah, I have one,
but how did you know?
Bomber said you got a perfect
score in driving school.
He just had to open his big mouth.
Well, you know, I commute by train.
But you said we'd go to the ocean sometime soon.
I did, but...
No, wait.
I did promise her,
but it's rare that Umaru is interested
in anything outdoors-y at all.
I probably shouldn't let
this opportunity slip by.
Well, I guess I could just take a look.
What? Really?
By the way, about this car...
You have good taste, sir!
Hybrids are a great buy right now.
So its fuel consumption is low?
Of course!
They might be the same car, but just
look at how much you save on gas!
Working in sales must be rough...
Onii-chan! Onii-chan!
She's in the car?!
Doesn't this one look good?
I-Isn't this...
Car Name: TOMODA Dekantea
Body Color                  8 Passenger Seating
Three million yen?!
Please... Get in!
Umaru, there are only two of us.
We don't need such a big car.
This would fit more than six people.
Huh? B-But, you know,
if we were to go out with Ebina-chan and
Kirie-chan, a bigger one would be better.
Oh, and if you include Bomber, that's five people.
She was thinking of her friends, too?
But three million yen...
What do you think?
Why not take it for a test drive?
We will!
W-We'll be off, then.
Have a safe trip.
Start!
Onii-chan, go!
R-Right.
See you soon!
It's so spacious!
There's a TV! Switch on!
Being big is a good thing!
It's an elephant.
It's so big.
Yep.
It's that commercial!
Being big is a good thing!
La, la, la, la, la, la...
Tokyo Mouseney Land!
Being big is a good thing!
Take your whole house on
a drive with Dekantea!
Being big is—
Yay!
Huh?
Onii-chan?
Local streets... Kids will jump out.
This is different from practice...
My life... is in danger.
An accident on a test drive...
This car is huge.
Awful things happening...
Umaru getting hurt...
A cat!
A dog!
A manga artist!
Onii-chan, let's just go in Bomber's car.
R-Right...
Hachiouji Driving School
Damn, you got a perfect score
even in driving school?
For the written.
Oh, hey, Taihei.
Huh? My car?
Sure. Are you going somewhere?
Huh? The ocean?
Sure. Sounds good.
Do
Not
Enter
Do
Not
Enter
Bomber said he'd drive.
Aw, are we actually going?
I'd rather just laze around at home.
You're totally looking forward to it.
Hey, where are we going to visit the ocean?
From here, I guess there's the
Miura Peninsula, or Shounan...
Maybe Enoshima?
What? If we're gonna go, we should
go to Okinawa or Hawaii.
How many nights are you planning
to stay? This is a day trip.
Hey, you think we should have the
pet shop take care of the hamsters?
Again, this is a day trip.
Umaru's actually pretty excited about this.
It's always important to be prepared in advance.
First, we need to deflate
the inner tube and fold it.
'Kay.
We should probably pack some extra towels.
Ice Pack
We're taking a thermal bag,
so we need to freeze the ice packs.
I'll leave the lid open so
we don't forget to pack it.
We need sunscreen, too.
And there might be mosquitoes,
so we'll take anti-itch ointment.
Nau
Cool
Kick+
All right, we need to get an early
start, so let's get plenty of sleep.
'Kay.
And the alarm clock has been set.
All right, I'm turning off the lights.
Onii-chan?
Hm?
You're really excited about this, aren't you?
Yeah.
Yeah, in front of our building is fine.
We're already ready.
How many? Um...
Kirie-chan
Kirie-chan!
G-Good morning, Kirie-chan.
Um... I heard from Umaru-chan that
we were meeting here this morning.
It's me, my little sister, and her
two friends, so it'll be four of us.
D'oh.
All right, thanks.
Good morning, Ebina-chan.
G-Good morning!
Thank you so much for inviting me today.
Sure. Let's make this a fun holiday.
R-Right...
Oh, he's already here.
Heyo!
Thanks for driving today, Bomber.
Man, it's been forever since
I've been to the ocean.
Th-Thank you for taking us.
Yeah, sur—
Oh, this is Umaru's friend Ebina-chan.
U-Um... Nice to meet you.
R-Right... Hi.
H-He... He's going to find out!
Taihei, is this Tanukichi's friend, too?
Huh?!
Yeah, she's...
Everyone!
Sorry for taking so long.
Umaru                           un
Hey! Who's the babe?
Oh, right... This is the first
time he's seen this Umaru.
She's Umaru, my little sister.
Shikuwasa
Oh, your little sister...
Wait, what?!
L-Little sister?
And why does she have the
same name as Tanukichi?
His two younger sisters
both have the same name...
If I remember correctly,
Taihei's family is super loaded.
Could they have some tragic
soap opera-like relationship?!
Why are you suddenly crying?
Taihei!
Wh-What?
I won't ask you for details.
Just know that I'll always be on your side.
R-Right...
Kana Order Correction     Enoshima
Change Area     All Areas     Change Genres     All Genres
Enoshima Station (Enoshima Railways)/Kanagawa Prefecture Fujisawa City
Enoshima Railways Enoshima Station/Kanagawa Prefecture Fujisawa City
Katase-Enoshima Station (Odakyuu)/Kanagawa Prefecture Fujisawa City
Shin-Enoshima Aquarium/Kanagawa Prefecture Fujisawa City
Enoshima Shrine/Kanagawa Prefecture Fujisawa City
Our destination is Enoshima.
Enoshima Station
We should get there by about 10:00.
All right, let's go!
Let's go!
I'm happy to be with Umaru-san,
but I wonder where Master is.
Kirie-chan, what do you want
to see when we go to Enoshima?
Um... Maybe the aquarium.
Sounds good! Let's go!
Could it be that she caught a cold?
I should ask Onii-san.
O-Onii-san.
Hm? What's the matter, Kirie-chan?
What?!
Idiot! Keep your eyes on the road! The road!
What'd you start shouting for?
Kirie is the same name as my younger sister.
Oh, really?
I thought she looked similar,
other than the hairstyle,
but to think she had the same name, too...
Man, I guess coincidences like that do happen.
Huh...
Anyway, Kirie-chan,
you wanted to ask me something?
It's nothing.
That stupid brother of mine!
U-Um... Kirie-chan?
Eek!
Y-You seem a bit down, so I was worried...
U-Um, I'm sorry!
N-N-No, it's not...
Th-That's... not...
We'll be there soon...
At Enoshima!
The ocean's so pretty!
I'm started to feel hyped up now.
Let's walk around the island.
Let's go, Kirie-chan!
R-Right!
Love Bell
Enoshima's bigger than I thought.
Yeah, we've walked for quite a while.
Ah!
Octopus crackers!
Whole Roasted Octopus Crackers
Fresh whitebait bowls!
Why don't we get some lunch?
Agreed!
I had them pick some recommendations for us.
All right, let's eat.
Yeah! Let's eat!
Let's eat!
Super tasty!
Oh, here's one.
It looks so tasty—
So big!
Seaweed!
Eek!
What are you doing?
They look like they're having fun.
U-Um... Umaru-san?
Hm? What is it?
Today, was Master... No...
Was Komaru-san not feeling well today?
Huh?
Um...
Uh... My sister is...
K-Kirie-chan.
The thing is, I...
I'm...
Taihei, save me!
Black kites! Black kites are attacking me!
They think your head is a nest!
Stay away from me!
Don't be so cruel!
Th-That's pretty intense, huh?
I-I'm sorry. That's actually my older brother.
Oh, I see— What?!
I just changed my hair slightly,
and he doesn't even realize I'm his sister.
He's seriously a complete idiot.
He's been like that ever since I was little.
So, um... When he tries to pick on
me at home, I hit him and stuff.
Arayada High School
Entrance Ceremony
At the high school entrance ceremony,
he showed up instead of my mother...
Heyo, Kirie!
So I picked a fight as usual,
and my classmates started to fear me.
B-But, um...
Ever since I met Master and Onii-san,
I've been able to talk more...
A-And you started talking
to me more at school.
So, um...
I-I'm really grateful.
S-So... I'm worried that something
might have happened to Master.
Thanks, Kirie-chan.
H-Huh? I didn't do anything...
All right. Shall we go?
Huh?
You wanted to come to the aquarium, right?
My sister told me.
I'm sorry. Komaru couldn't come
because something urgent came up.
I see... I'm just glad she's not sick.
I might have said this before,
but thank you for always playing with her.
I should have brought my little sister.
She really loves fish.
Your little sister that has
the same name as Kirie-chan?
She's super violent, though,
always punching me and kicking me.
Easy, easy...
She barely speaks to me anymore since I
went to her high school entrance ceremony.
Maybe I shouldn't have gone.
U-Um...
I don't think that's true.
No little sister wouldn't be happy
that her big brother showed up.
Sh-She's such a nice girl.
Wh-What's wrong?
It's just... It's been so long since
someone's been so kind to me...
That long?
Man, if only you'd been my
little sister, Ebina-chan.
R-Right...
Enoshima
Souvenir
What the heck?! Did the high
school girl lose her mind?!
Ow! Somehow that blow seems really familiar!
What the heck are you doing?
I'm sure he somehow offended Kirie-chan, but...
I'll keep an eye on him, so why
don't you guys go play in the water?
What? Are you sure?
It's the ocean!
Yay!
It's so cold!
It feels so nice...
Indeed.
It takes a little courage to get in the
ocean at first, since it's kinda cold.
R-Really?!
Hmm... It seems like they're almost there...
Oh?
Eek!
The ocean's so much fun!
Huh?
S-Sylphyn-san?
U-Umaru-san? What are you doing here?
Um... We all came to play.
Oh, it's Kirie-san and... Ebikouji-san, right?
I told you, it's Ebina!
I'm enjoying a summer holiday
with my older brother.
See? He's right over there.
Onii-sama!
A summer holiday on a yacht...
That aside, I never thought I'd
run into you here, Umaru-san.
Shuba                             an
We must battle!
Huh?
Long-distance swimming, beach volleyball,
watermelon breaking!
Anything will do!
Oh, um, Sylphyn-san...
Since we're at the ocean,
why don't we put the battles aside,
and all play together?
Huh?
P-Play with you, Umaru-san?
Yep, yep.
W-Well, if you insist...
All right, everyone!
Let us play to our hearts' content!
Bomber, I bought you a drink.
Huh? There's a new one with them.
Take that! Indeed!
Take that!
I feel like I've seen her before...
I guess she's another friend.
Eek!
Take that!
It's evening already.
Playing with everyone was indeed very fun.
Yeah.
I hope we get to play together again,
even after summer vacation is over.
Yeah.
Yes.
Indeed.
I'm beat.
Way to hang in there.
I kind of feel like I was sleeping
the whole time, though.
By the way, where's Tanukichi today?
Huh? Oh...
She's asleep. She must have had a lot of fun.
I see, I see.
She must have had some party
last night and stayed up late, huh?
Work is killing me.
I wanna go to the ocean again.
Just tough it out until our next day off.
The Mountains Are Calling!
Umaru seemed to have a lot
of fun at the ocean...
All right!
I'm home!
Hey, Umaru. Want to go somewhere
again next time I have a day off?
How about the mountains?
What? The mountains?
If you'll carry me up and
down it on your back, sure.
More importantly, would you go
buy the Jumpu I forgot to buy?
Actually, if you'd just bought it
on your way home from work,
you could have saved the hassle.
You sure are unreliable.
Y-Y-You little...
himouto!