It's summer.
Summer means vacation.
Vacations are awesome.
I'll do radio calisthenics every morning,
eat hiyamugi noodles,
and eat shaved ice.
I'll swim in the pool,
eat cold ramen noodles,
and eat ice cream.
I love summer!
Anyway, I am Gouda Takeo,
a first-year in high school!
Report Card
In its own way, it's awe-inspiring.
Yamato
Oh, Takeo-kun?
The beach?
Yeah, I was just talking with my friends
about how it'd be great if we all went
to the beach with your friends.
Sunakawa-kun... Invite Sunakawa-kun!
Would Sunakawa-kun come, too?
The beach sounds great!
Okay, let's go!
My Ocean
Huh?
Go to the beach with Takeo's
girlfriend and her friends?
Sure, I'll go!
Me, too!
Let's go!
When is it?
The ocean, huh?
It's wide and vast.
It's a nice place!
Suna, you're coming,
whether you want to or not.
Huh?
I'm so looking forward to seeing girls in swimsuits...
Don't come!
Huh?
You aren't coming!
Why not?
Congratulations                           Big Catch
Swimsuits are for swimming!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
If you go to a beach, it's all about watching
girls in swimsuits, of course.
Yeah, totally.
Aren't you looking forward to seeing
your girlfriend in a swimsuit?
Yamato's coming in a swimsuit just to swim.
I'll never turn into a scumbag
that'd stare at her like a perv!
Don't worry, Yamato.
It won't matter to me what you wear.
Which one are you gonna choose?
You're lucky! You have a big rack!
You have nice legs, too.
You have a nice figure!
Oh, this is cute.
You're right.
What about this one for me?
A high-cut...
Oh, I guess that's too much...
How about this one, then?
Oh, then... Maybe this?
What's wrong, Rinko?
Huh?
But I mean, Takeo-kun's so hot.
Yeah, he is...
Of course he is to Rinko...
Compared to him, I'm like a stick.
I wouldn't go that far.
I don't have a good figure like him.
Not sure you'd call him "hot."
First of all, he isn't built like a
normal high school first-year.
He has ridiculous muscles.
He's like a heavy weightlifter in the Olympics.
But I wonder what your boyfriend's going to wear.
What if he brings a school swimsuit?
Totally possible!
What if it's like the competitive kind?
The really tiny ones!
I bet he'll swim a ton.
So hot!
So, anyway...
He always makes my heart skip a beat,
so I want to make his heart skip a beat!
I'm going to give it my best shot!!
I get it now!
Of course!
Of course you want your boyfriend's
heart to skip a beat.
You want him to think you're cute.
All right, let's help Rinko pick out her swimsuit!
Yeah!
This one's nice.
Nah!
What about this one?
Those bottom frills are definitely gonna turn up.
Nice, go for it!
Suna, I'm coming in.
You're already in here, dude.
What, are you running away from home?
I was packing up for tomorrow.
I want to go over what I have,
to avoid doubling up on things.
I have enough canteens to cook
rice, and tents for everyone.
Aren't we going to the beach to swim?
It's possible that we'll get stranded.
There's nothing to lose by
preparing for a rainy day.
I don't think there'll be one.
It's Yamato.
Hello?
Oh, Takeo-kun? They're forecasting a typhoon.
Do you think we'll be okay tomorrow?
A typhoon?
You always bring good weather
with you, so it should be fine.
Suna says we don't need to worry,
because I bring good weather.
Oh, I see!
I'm at Suna's place getting ready for tomorrow.
I'm getting ready, too.
I'm really looking forward to tomorrow.
Yeah, same here!
See you tomorrow, then.
Yeah, see you.
Takeo...
Hmm?
What's in that?
Watermelons.
We'll be doing the watermelon game, won't we?
But isn't that a bit much?
How many did you pack?
Also, shouldn't you wait till we get there
to inflate the floats and stuff?
It takes up too much space.
I see...
Takeo, are you really all right?
About what?
Uh, well...
The weather?
Never mind.
I love the ocean.
When I was little, I saw the sun set into the sea,
and it blew me away.
All right!
I want to see that sunset again with Yamato.
Takeo-kun, it's sunny!
Yep!
Long time, no see, everyone.
Hey!
How have you been?
How are we getting there?
Train and bus.
How were your finals?
Why ask that?
Oh, sorry!
What's wrong, Yamato?
Are you hot?
Huh?
Nope.
Um, yeah...
He's so close!
Yamato's so cute.
Hey, you can see the ocean!
It's the ocean!
Can I set up the beach umbrella here?
Maybe we should get another one...
Yeah.
Wow, Takeo!
You inflated that with one puff.
Where are the girls?
Changing.
Swimsuits, yeah!
Uh...
The beach is where you swim, split watermelons,
and catch crabs.
There you are.
Sorry to make you wait!
Hey, don't stare.
Hey, you're all way too cute.
You sound like a dirty old man.
Why don't you change, too?
Right, okay.
Summer
Ocean
The beach is where you catch crabs and clams,
split watermelons,
swim till you drop,
get weird tan lines,
get so sunburned, your skin peels,
and win the suntan contest at
the end of the summer.
But what's up with the beach today?!
What's that?
A sea monster?
Weird, I can't get near them!
Rinko, isn't Takeo-kun awfully far away?
The thing that looks like a whale swimming
out there is Takeo-kun, right?
Takeo-kun, the sun suits you so much.
You're so hot.
Now isn't the time to stare at him, Rinko.
You're going to make his heart skip a beat, right?
How long will you keep that hoodie on?
Huh?
Right...
Takeo, you have to spin around ten times.
Fast.
That's Takeo for you!
I just have to avoid looking at Yamato.
Hey, Takeo!
Wrong way!
Where're you headed? Hey!
Sorry!
Left! Left!
A little more to the left.
Okay.
Yeah...
Keep going straight ahead!
Four more steps.
He's so hot...
Rinko!
Wait, Takeo! Stop!
Yamato-san's—
What?
Jeez, Rinko.
What're you doing?
You're totally spaced out.
Right...
Calm down, Takeo.
They're only clothes.
Clothes?
That's right.
They're clothes you can wear underwater.
That's all.
Just clothes, huh?
There's not much to them.
Right, they're clothes for swimming.
Clothes.
I just have to think of them as clothes.
Clothes for swimming.
Got it?
Have you calmed down now?
Okay, go!
Clothes.
That's right!
Sorry I made you wait, Yamato!
Takeo's Back!
The beach is a great place!
Let's enjoy it together!
O-Okay.
All right...
Let's play beach volleyball!
Got it, got it...
One!
Okay, two...
Three!
Oops, sorry...
Hup!
Uh...
Bam!
349!
355!
Dropouts
Rinko's boyfriend's getting every single ball.
356!
357!
Takeo-kun's so hot!
358!
Wow, just listen to the crowd.
359!
Hmph.
360!
Hup!
361!
362!
363!
364!
365!
What the hell? When will this end?
366!
367!
I want to go home...
There!
Whoo!
Takeo, throw me next.
Me, too!
Sure!
There!
One more time!
Want me to throw you, too, Yamato?
Eh?
What, me?
Give it your best shot, Rinko.
Oh, um...
waver
fidget
Huh, wait.
But this means...
ba-dum
I'll get to feel Takeo-kun's skin?
OMG
What's wrong, Yamato?
Is this what you want?
Huh?
Tha...
Thanks.
I guessed right.
Satisfied
I'll pull you along.
Eh?
Takeo-kun, you're so fast!
Aw, looks fun...
Hey, Takeo-kun...
There!
Watch out!
Hey!
Oh?
Who's playing with our kids?
Hey! That guy has so many muscles!
Yeah!
My husband has nothing on that guy.
Look at his abs.
They're like an ice cube tray.
Oh, stop it!
ba-dum
Takeo-kun's popular, after all.
Yamato,
want to get back on the beach?
S-Sure.
Center of Attention
I knew he'd be popular!
Ocean Home Aoba
Curry Rice
Rinko, you have corn stuck in your teeth.
Huh?
Why's she flailing around like that?
It's cute.
Calm down, Rinko.
Drink some water.
I want to make his heart skip a beat...
But he's always one step ahead of me.
You really like your boyfriend, huh?
Why don't you go snuggle up to him?
Rinko would die first from excitement.
Right...
I'll try.
I'll go over there.
Good luck.
You sure eat a lot.
What's wrong, Yamato?
Takeo-kun, um...
Um...
Can the two of us go to the rocks over there?
The rocks...
Sure!
You want to catch small crabs. Right, Yamato?
Just leave it to me.
I'm super good at catching crabs.
There!
Okay!
Watch out, Yamato.
You'll step on it.
Oh.
S-Sorry, Takeo-kun...
I was only thinking about myself.
I'm so embarrassed!
Sorry!
Yamato?
Oh, sorry.
He's so clumsy.
Suna...
Just go.
I've got this.
This is big.
Sorry, Suna.
Yeah, yeah.
Yamato!
Takeo-kun...
What's wrong, Yamato?
Um...
Well, I was just so embarrassed.
You keep an eye out on what's
going on around you,
but I was too focused on myself.
I'm so self-centered...
Ugh, I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so bad today...
I'm not that much better.
Can I sit next to you?
Huh?
Okay.
It's a nice sunset...
Oh, you're right.
Right... I remember now.
I wanted to see this sunset with Yamato today.
I'm glad we're doing this...
I'm a happy man.
It's so beautiful.
I want to become a person with
a mind as open as the ocean.
And stay with you forever.
Rinko             Takeo
Yamato...
You're beautiful.
Rinko             Takeo
It's okay.
Thanks.
Is it because of the sunset?
Is that why my face is burning
and my heart's pounding?
Yamato, I love you.
Yeah.
I love you lots, too, Takeo-kun.
Yamato...
ba-dum ba-dum
I...
Oh, there you are.
What're you guys up to?
Let's do fireworks! Fireworks!
C'mon!
Oh...
I guess you didn't manage to make
his heart skip a beat, after all.
No.
And you tried so hard.
But it was still fun.
Yeah, it was.
Maybe we should all go see
fireworks and stuff together.
And wear yukatas.
Yeah, definitely.
Yukatas?
I wonder if I can make Takeo-kun's
heart skip a beat with a yukata.
Rinko, you don't give up, do you?
Suna...
Today, I was blown away
when I watched the sunset with Yamato.
Oh, I'm happy for you.
Yep, thanks.
Hey, Takeo-kun...
Sometime, do you want to go to a
fireworks festival with everyone?
Fireworks, huh?
Sounds great. Let's go!
I'll make Takeo-kun's heart skip a beat for sure.
Yamato and fireworks...
I'm sure I'll get blown away again.
Do you like fireworks, Takeo-kun?
I love fireworks!
These two really aren't on the same page.
Well, whatever.
They sure look happy enough.
Rinko             Takeo
My Grades
Next time: My Grades.