From One Year to the Next
Coffee Shop
It'll be Christmas soon.
That's right.
I'd like to do some kind of event.
Something to bring in more customers.
Yeah...
Why don't we put on another play
on Christmas Eve, then?
It would be the Hitotose Troupe's
second performance!
Yeah.
But we don't have much time until Christmas,
so we probably won't be able
to do one as big as last time.
We won't have time to practice.
A short play is fine, too!
Let's do it!
Right, Principal Hina-chan?
Yeah!
I bet our second play will go
even better than the first!
That settles it! It'll be about...
Hmm, let's see...
For the end of the year...
Maybe Chushingura?
Since it'll be Christmas,
maybe it should be more of a Christmas story.
A Christmas story, huh?
Okay, how about this?
A tragic love story between
Santa Claus and a reindeer.
Wherefore are thou a reindeer?
Like that.
Or maybe...
A revenge drama about Prince Santa Claus
driven mad with the need for vengeance.
Get to the convent!
Aww!
How about that?
Um, what do those have
to do with Christmas,
other than having Santa and a reindeer?
I like it! Santa and his reindeer!
I'll have to start preparing
the costumes right away!
Mayu-chan's switch just flipped on.
Yeah.
I can't wait until the costume fitting!
Oh, I know! You'll need dresses, too, right?
Uh, Mayu-chan...
What?
Like I said before, we won't have much time,
so I was thinking of borrowing
costumes from the theater club.
D'oh...
Mayu-chan's switch just flipped off.
Yeah.
Okay, then, how about something
based on A Christmas Carol?
That might be nice.
On Christmas Eve night, a cruel,
miserly girl is haunted by a ghost,
who asks Santa Claus and
his reindeer for a certain gift...
You won't budge on Santa
and the reindeer, huh?
Nope!
Wait, but if it has that many characters,
won't we be short on actors?
We have the landlady, Hina-chan,
and Yua-chan, right?
You're right.
If we can get a real reindeer,
we should be able to manage.
If a regular deer will work instead of
a reindeer, I might be able to get one.
W-We can do that?!
Animals do like Hina-chan, after all.
Do you think you could summon
Santa while you're at it?!
Huh?! Um, um...
I-If you think my grandpa
would be good enough...
Oh, I don't know if I can act...
Hina-chan, you don't need to
worry about it that much.
Used Bookstore
Hitotose
~ The Next Day ~
I heard the news!
We're doing a play on Christmas Eve, right?
Let me help... you... with that...
Thanks.
Oh, welcome, Yua-chan!
Huh?
So...
I went straight to the theater club
to borrow costumes!
They're in the bag.
And I also came up with a practice schedule!
Thanks.
Here, Hinako.
And you, Kuina.
And Mayuki-senpai, here's yours.
Oh, Chiaki-senpai!
Please try on your costume!
I think it'll fit, but it's a little different
from normal costumes, so...
Okay. I'll try it on.
Is that a spirit costume?
It's pretty extreme.
I-It fit perfectly when I tried it on...
Is this what you call an
"unequal bodily society"?
Fujimiya
Girls'
High
School
We'll be holding a play on the 24th!
Please take one!
Here you go.
How cute!
Please take one! And be sure to come!
Here you go!
It'll be really fun, so please come!
Sensei!
Here you go!
The Hitotose Troupe
December 24
Mini Drama
Place: Coffee Shop Hitotose
Starting at 5:00 PM
December 24th... A mini-drama...
You're putting on another play
at Hitotose Manor?
Yes! We hope you'll come watch it, too!
Of course.
What kind of play is it?
It's based on A Christmas Carol.
That's certainly a classic.
We'll have a real deer.
And Chiaki-senpai will strip!
Huh?
Not really.
Yes, really.
Which is it?
You really did call a deer.
Okay, you two,
take the deer with you
to draw in customers, okay?
O-Okay...
W-We'll be holding a play
here in our shop today!
P-Please come and... w-watch...
Wh-Why did I have to dress like this, too?
Hina-chan, I can't do this!
It's too embarrassing!
Hina-chan's a scarecrow already?!
I have to try harder!
A deer!
So it is!
How cute!
Oh, wow!
Hina-chan, Mayu-chan, how goes the...
The deer's doing all the work.
Performance
in Session
Oh, Sensei, welcome.
Looks like business is booming.
Yeah, it's a full house!
Please... Please grant my wish!
Your play is getting a good response.
I cannot grant the wish of a miser like you!
No, it's not so much the play.
I beseech thee, grant her wish!
It's the landlady's costume
and the deer that are popular.
Wow. So you actually have
a real deer in the play.
Yeah.
Next time, I'll try to win people over
with the actual story!
A deer... a deer...
Maybe I'll try to use that
in my next drama script.
Huh?
Thank you for coming!
Everyone, since this was
your second performance,
your acting felt much more
natural than in the first.
It was wonderful.
Oh, gosh!
Well, that's to be expected!
Being praised by Sensei
really gives me an appetite!
It should give you inspiration,
not an appetite!
Oh, yeah.
Well, I'll have to take my leave now.
Huh? You're leaving already, Ruri-chan?
There's still lots of cake
and other things left.
I've had plenty.
Oh, I forgot!
You need to go home and get to bed,
or Santa won't come, right?
I'll go to bed early today, too!
Hina-chan, do you actually
still believe in Santa?
Hinako-san is right.
I need to go home and get to bed early,
or Santa Claus won't come.
Yeah!
Bye, Ruri-chan!
Don't forget to hang your stocking!
Okay.
Sensei is so mature...
Yeah.
Mayu-chan, I'll go buy presents later.
Yeah. We don't want to
crush Hina-chan's dreams.
Oh, Hinako!
Mom! I'm home!
Welcome home!
Welcome home.
Yes, welcome home.
Have you been well?
Yes!
Oh? Your face looks different, somehow.
You usually get all nervous and stiffen up.
I've been doing theater in Tokyo,
so I don't get nervous as easily anymore.
That's why I can talk
this normally to people now!
I won't let anyone call me a scarecrow...
Hina-chan! Happy New Year!
Look at that! It's the
first sunrise of the year!
Kuu-chan, you're so energetic
this early in the morning.
Well, the start of a new year
brings all kinds of firsts!
I can't help being excited!
F-Firsts?
Yeah!
The first snack!
Yum!
The first mochi!
Delicious!
The first bite snitched!
Tangy!
And the first book!
Discourse on
Decadence
All you're doing is eating.
Happy New Year, everyone.
Happy New Year!
Oh, by the way, you were in my
first dream of the year, Mayu-chan.
Yeah? What was it about?
A giant Mayu-chan looking down on Mt. Fuji.
Yay!
I-I was that big?
Mayu-chan looks happy.
But Mt. Fuji was actually a miniature,
and you were actually even smaller
than you are in real life.
Yay! Yay! Yay!
What?
She's shocked!
Do you all have any goals
for the coming year?
I do!
My goal is to read 300 books this year!
I'm going to work on my acting.
I guess mine is still to be able to talk
in front of people without getting nervous.
And mine is to keep supporting Hina-chan
and the others as their senpai.
I want to get the coffee shop's
business on the right track, too.
She's drinking so much milk...
I guess what she really
wants to do is get taller.
Please continue
to support
Coffee Shop Hitotose
this year!
Oh, Kuu-chan, Mayu-chan...
Are you going out somewhere?
We're going to visit our families.
Huh? Really?
Yeah.
We'll be back in about two days, though.
Two days? Won't you just spend
all that time on trains and buses?
Uh... Our families live in Tokyo.
They're only about an hour away.
O-Oh, I see!
I've always wondered this...
Where in the countryside does
Hina-chan live, exactly?
I'm not sure, either...
We'll be going now, Hina-chan.
I'll be so lonely...
We'll be back before you know it.
This isn't goodbye forever.
Oh, I forgot!
Just a second.
If you get lonely,
just imagine this doll is me.
Thanks, Mayu-chan!
And I'll send this little one
with you in return.
I can't take something that's alive...
Here, I'll give you this book!
I'd rather not take something half-eaten...
Miss Landlady, I'll help you!
Thanks.
It's so quiet with
both of them gone, isn't it?
Uh huh.
What should I do?
The conversation isn't going anywhere!
I have to think of something
she'd enjoy talking about!
If there's one thing I know
she likes, it's theater.
But I don't know that much about theater...
What else does she like?
I don't really know anything
about her at all, do I?!
Hina-chan, what's wrong?
I-I want to know
everything about you!
So, what do you want to know?
Stuff about acting?
Y-Yeah...
Okay. Ask me anything.
A-Anything?
When she puts it that way,
there are too many things I'd like to ask...
Like how she moves her body so gracefully,
or how she prepares physically
for each of her roles...
Um... um...
I want to know about your body!
Hina-chan, calm down.
Um, so what do you like, other than theater?
Other than theater?
Well...
I do like small animals.
Small animals?
Yeah. When I was little,
I had a golden hamster.
It was so small, and its eyes were so round,
and its golden fur was so soft...
It was so cute.
Golden hamsters
really are cute, aren't they?
Yeah.
Huh? Small, round eyes, golden...
That sounds like something
I've seen before...
Are you all right, Mayu-chan?
Y-Yeah...
Oh, right. I'm leaving for my
part-time job this afternoon.
Do you want to come?
Part-time? You have a part-time job?
Yeah.
Every year on New Year's,
I go and help a friend of mine
who likes theater.
I see!
And what kind of work is it?
Well, serving customers, I guess...
Serving customers?!
I'll have a chance to overcome my nervousness
right from the start of the year!
What do you say?
I'll go!
This is not what I had envisioned...
The landlady really does look good
in anything she wears, though.
All the men here can't take
their eyes off of her.
Th-There's someone suspicious...
But that hairstyle...
Yua-chan?
Wh-Why are you here?!
Huh? I'm working here with the landlady.
Wh-What?!
She gets to see Chiaki-senpai
in her miko outfit up close...
I'm so jealous!
Huh?
Oh, did you come to see the landlady?
Yes! Got a problem with that?!
Then why don't you go talk to her
instead of sneaking around?
It's a fan's job to watch over her
from the shadows!
Huh? Yua-chan?
What brings you here?
Ch-Ch-Chiaki-senpai...
She said she was looking at you
in your miko outfit.
Hinako!
Want to try being a miko with us, Yua-chan?
Huh? Huh?!
How about it?
I-I'd love to!
Yes! I get to see Chiaki-senpai
in her miko outfit up close!
Um...
Are you sure we don't
need to ask the priest?
I think it'll be fine.
Having two cute mikos
should bring in more visitors.
Don't put unnecessary pressure on me!
Did you eat lots of mochi?
Really?
I ate lots, too.
The landlady talks
a lot more than I realized.
Wow, four? That is a lot.
Oh, you didn't know?
She's really outgoing with young kids.
Oh...
Come to think of it...
I guess she does talk a lot
with Mayu-chan and Kuu-chan.
Yua-chan...
I wish I were smaller.
Huh?
Are you picking a fight?
Thanks for helping me today, you two.
Sure!
Um, Miss Landlady...
I'd...
...like to talk with you more!
Would that bother you?
It doesn't bother me at all.
I'm happy you feel that way.
Really?
Yep.
Thank you!
No fair, Hinako!
I'm glad I got to know the landlady
better today, even if it was just a little.
I have a feeling I'll be able to
talk with her even more tomorrow.
Hitotose
Mayu-chan's doll is all wet with my drool...
My goodness, Goro. You really
love Mayu, don't you?
S-Stop!
New Year's is almost over...
It went by so fast.
In three months,
I'll have been here for a year.
I wasn't sure how it would go at first,
but then I met everyone,
started our theater troupe,
became friends with Yua-chan...
I was in the play
at our culture festival, too,
and the Hitotose Troupe
had its first performance.
So much has happened.
But I think it's all helped me
grow up a little bit...
Or maybe not.
But...
I'll keep trying my best at everything!
Yeah!
I'm back.
I'm back!
Kuu-chan! Mayu-chan!
Welcome back, you two.
I bought lots of souvenirs.
This is Tokyo's specialty, Ahiru!
Huh?! I got Ahiru, too...
So we have lots!
Let's all eat them right now!
Huh? Shouldn't we put our things away first?
Eating the year's first souvenir
takes priority!
Eating really is all you ever do, isn't it?
Yep!
Let's hurry and eat these!
Yeah, let's eat!
The Place We Longed to Reach
I came to Hitotose Manor because
I wanted to change myself,
and I met precious friends there
who can never be replaced.
I'll keep working toward my goal
along with all the people I love!
Next time, "The Place We Longed to Reach."