Akaashi...
Don't toss to me anymore!
All right.
Huh?
Then please calm down in the time
that I'm not tossing to you.
I don't know what's going on,
but their ace doesn't seem to be doing well.
Let's keep it up!
Yeah!
Haikyu!!
Episode 11: "Above"
All right!
Nice kill!
Yeah!
All right!
Karasuno                    Fukurodani
M-Maybe I'm just imagining it,
but it doesn't seem like
Fukurodani is fazed at all.
Yeah...
Chance ball!
Here.
Right now, there are two attackers
in Fukurodani's front line.
Is it going to be a quick from the center,
an attack from the back,
or is their #4 finally going
to do something again?
A dump!
Karasuno           Fukurodani
Fukurodani's turning the tables again.
And the ace hasn't even hit anything!
Bokuto may look like the big brother,
but he's actually the baby of the family.
Nice, Akaashi!
Thank you.
He is pretty amazing on his own, though.
Nice receive!
We're used to Bokuto's slumps.
The slightest thing can bring him up or down.
Left!
Oh, for crying out loud...
All right!
Karasuno                 Fukurodani
Fukurodani match point!
Just one more point!
Apparently Fukurodani isn't
a team that Bokuto pulls,
but is a team where all of the
other members pull Bokuto.
One touch!
We now know that Fukurodani is
not Bokuto-san's one-man team.
And yet...
There's still no one scarier
on their own than Bokuto-san!
Totally shut out!
All right! Just one more point to a deuce!
Karasuno                 Fukurodani
Wow...
Well done.
If I mess up this serve,
the match will be over.
I'm...
...definitely getting this one in!
Komi-yan!
Yeah!
Nice receive!
I'm sure Karasuno's figured out
what kind of team we are by now.
Which means...
Their attention is off of the ace.
And Bokuto-san wants to hit so
bad that he's getting restless!
We'll give you the good part...
...so...
...pick yourself back up...
...ace!
Karasuno                    Fukurodani
If you would.
Leave it to us.
Whoo! Ace!
You're so cool!
Nothing beats the ace in the end!
Birds of prey!
Your hair's like a great horned owl!
I'm the best after all!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey...
He's able to pick himself up so quickly.
That's what they call a simpleton.
The ace's weakness brings
out the others' strengths,
and, at the same time,
becomes a strong root for the
team that's hard to break.
Apparently, this is another form of strength.
To be honest,
I was thinking we might be okay if
we were able to stop Bokuto-kun,
but I guess that was naïve.
The reason he's able to
be that free and selfish,
and the reason the others
are able to ignore that,
Aren't I awesome, Akaashi?!
must be because of how much
they trust each other.
For sure, Bokuto-san.
Our team isn't at the point where
any of them can be that selfish yet.
I'm sorry!
My last serve ended up being an
"I freaked out, so please attack," serve!
If you can figure that out
on your own, you're well off.
In that situation, how much
one is going to get blamed
will affect our ability to win.
No one wants the game to end
because of their mistake.
He must be talking about you.
Shut up.
But there's no one who tries
to hold back a winning serve.
Right!
Now that it's over, that
was definitely our loss,
but there's one thing that's for sure...
Your plays will be effective at
a national level of competition.
Right now, your serves and combinations
can't match the other teams'.
Because you started so late
on them, it can't be helped.
But you mustn't stop.
You mustn't think that this
is the limit of your power.
When you mix colors, they become
muddled and dirty, right?
But once you finish mixing,
you get the color black,
which won't be overtaken by any other.
Please make our team's color black,
which fits us crows.
W-Was that metaphor a bit hard to understand?
No! Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
All right. This is gonna be our
final training camp penalty...
One lap of diving drills!
Right!
Asahi-san!
There's still a little time left,
so could you hit some of my tosses?
Oh, sure.
Noya-san! Let me hit some, too.
Yeah! Sure thing, Ryu!
Oh, me, too.
Ah! Are you going to toss
some up for us, too?
Thanks!
Oh, no, no.
I'm going to hit some.
Damn it. If our quick was just
a little more complete,
we might have been able to
get a set from Fukurodani.
But now we can fight.
Even if they read us or catch up to us...
We can fight!
That all depends on my tosses.
You'll get it eventually, so it'll be fine.
Don't decide things for me!
So you're saying you won't be able to?
Of course I'll be able to, dumbass!
So you can!
Let's go practice that quick!
You can actually feel how stupid
they are from that conversation.
Yeah!
As soon as we get back, we have the
first spring tournament prelims.
Yeah. If we're going to come
here again, it'll be after that.
I wonder if it'll be cooler by then.
There'll still be some lingering summer heat.
What's wrong, Suga?
If we don't make it through,
the three of us won't be able to come back.
There it is! Negative goatee!
What the...
Of course we're all coming back, dumbass.
You're right. Sorry.
Negativity, begone!
Ow!
Actually, you sounded
like Kageyama just now.
Dumbass! Hinata, you dumbass!
You sound just like him!
Do it again!
I-I feel like I'm getting doubly yelled at.
Huh?
All right, meat!
I'm starving!
Could you take this plate to Miyanoshita-san?
Sure.
There we go.
Apparently, even Bokuto-san has his bad days.
Yeah. Well, he self-destructs
at the most random times.
Kalbi, skirt steak, tongue, offals, liver,
sirloin, tripe, large intestine...
But it doesn't bug him
if our enemy is strong,
so we're usually okay.
When everyone else on the team loses hope,
he's usually still pretty energetic.
Despite everything, he's pretty reliable.
Bokuto-san!
Oh?
W-We're not gonna lose in an actual match!
Oh, yeah?! Bring it on, then!
Before the spring tournament,
we need to have our meat war, Hinata!
Ahem.
Well done on the week-long
training camp, everyone.
Nothing puts a smile on your face more than
filling your stomach with good food!
Eat all the meat you can.
Thanks for the food!
So then, Kenma...
Hey! Bokuto, you bastard!
Don't you steal my meat, you jerk!
Have a riceball.
Oh, thank you.
What?!
You understand, don't you, Ryu?
Of course.
Tora.
Yes, Master.
Don't you dare let any of them
try to use this opportunity
to get closer to Kiyoko-san.
As you wish!
Go, go!
You go.
I wonder why Nishinoya-san's the master.
Apparently, it's because he's the only one
that's ever been slapped
by Shimizu-senpai before.
Ah...
Tsukishima!
You need to eat more!
Er... I can't eat that much...
Come on, eat some veggies, too.
You, too, Kenma, damn it!
Eat some rice!
You mean meat! Eat some meat, Tsukki!
Or you won't grow anymore!
Are they, like, some pushy uncles?
Along with the defiant, hip youngster.
The generals totally see that
and are having fun with it.
Hey, Suga-kun.
Hm?
That girl from Karasuno's acting
really strange... Is she okay?
This is like...
The titans' jungle!
I smell meat... I want some so bad!
Hey, is this ready to eat?!
But if I carelessly stormed in there,
I might be eaten by accident!
Hey, I was planning on eating that!
They might barbecue me by accident!
Can you reach? Would you like
me to get you something?
I promise I don't taste good!
Er, I mean...
I'm fine! Thanks!
I was thinking about eating this.
Huh? Oh.
S-So good...
It tastes like life.
Ya-chan... The one you ate right now
was really charred. You okay?
Want some tea?
There's water, too.
It looks pretty dangerous over there.
Yeah... They'd probably get the cops
called on them if this was in the city.
I definitely don't want them surrounding me.
I'd rather have them surround me.
How much are you going to eat?
The third-years in Karasuno
all seem pretty mature.
Our Fukurodani managers
are already top tier,
but combined with the Karasuno managers,
they've gone up even higher!
What do you think?
I cannot argue.
Our ace is weak-willed, though.
What? Really?
Even though he looks that scary?
Though I think that's still better
than our simpleton ace...
What?!
You're in the nation's top five?!
That's awesome!
Right? Right?!
But Ushiwaka's from your area,
and he's in the top three.
Top three?!
Hey! If you say that, it knocks me down!
Top three means there's two others, right?
Ushiwaka from the Tohoku region,
Kiryu from Kyushu,
and Sakusa from Kanto.
They are this year's top
three high school aces.
Ooh...
Of course, one of them had to be in Miyagi.
Hey, Tsukki!
You've been practicing with my spikes,
so you're not allowed to
freak out about Ushiwaka!
Could you please not call me "Tsukki"?
But just because the aces are the top three,
doesn't mean that their teams are, as well.
Yeah! Yeah!
Though Itachiyama where Sakusa plays
is the top pick to win nationals.
Then...
...if we beat them, we'll be number one?
You talk big, for being
the top two for sucking.
Hinata must be number one.
Kenma said that my serves
and receives were better!
D'oh!
Nekomata-sensei.
Again, thank you very much for inviting us.
You never could stop my spikes, Tsukki!
It appears their change
happened because we came here.
No, no. It looks like we
got some good motivation,
Lev, you got a cat out of a tree?
Kenma-san's arms were too short to reach.
so it goes both ways.
In six months, none of these
teams will be the same.
They'll be new teams with different members.
Man, I'm stuffed!
They don't know of any
matches without regrets...
Ah, so the prelims are later in Tokyo...
Well, we have a lot of schools.
Well, I don't, at least.
But all I can do is hope that they
get to play without any regrets,
and I'll do my best so they're able to do that.
Right.
I hate being weak, but...
Huh?
Knowing that there are so many
players better than me...
...makes me feel so excited!
Well, see ya next time.
Yeah, see you next time.
The summer vacation training camp away games...
...are now over.
Haikyu!!
The Japanese National High School Volleyball Tournament
Miyagi Prefecture Qualifier
First Preliminaries (Boys) Lineup
If we can win twice at the prelims tomorrow,
we'll go to the qualifiers in October
to decide the representative team.
The eight schools that make it
through the first prelims
will be joined by eight
more powerhouse schools,
and they'll play the tournament that decides
the representative team in October.
There are only two games
in the first prelims?
We were able to make it into
the top sixteen at the Inter-High,
so we're exempt from the first games.
Wow! We're awesome!
All right! Let's start our calisthenics!
S-S-So we're finally playing
o-official matches...
Right!
I-I'm getting nervous...
One, two, three, four...
Well, it is your first tournament,
isn't it, Hitoka-chan?
Five, six, seven, eight...
Yup.
One, two, three, four...
Well, for us...
Five, six, seven, eight...
It's our last.
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight...
Sorry, sorry! Don't get all teary-eyed.
I-I'm not! A mosquito just flew into my eye!
A mosquito?!
Bring it!
Don't hit to the libero,
don't hit to the libero...
Don't hit to the libero...
Why is it whenever I think that,
that's exactly where it goes?
Yamaguchi, nice serve!
It was hard to get!
Oh, right...
He totally got it, though.
One more time!
What are you concentrating
so hard on, Sensei?
Oh, Ukai-kun.
Well... our first-years are amazing,
but I was just thinking there are
so many other amazing first-years...
Yeah.
Kakugawa Academy
That guy, huh?
Yeah...
I'm home.
Whoa, Kei.
You grew even taller.
You totally passed me a long time ago.
Ni-chan.
Hey, it's been a while.
It's been so long since I've talked to you.
Has it?
Even when I come home,
other than when we're eating,
you just stay in your room.
Do I?
Your expression has changed a bit.
You went to the away games, right?
Was it a rough trip?
I-It was normal...
You've got "rough" written all over your face!
You're still playing volleyball, aren't you?
Yeah, I'm on a team.
Do you guys have tournaments?
Yeah, we do.
You want to know why I'm still playing
after what happened in high school, right?
It's...
...because of what happened in high school.
Karasuno Volleyball Club
Even now, when I think back on it,
it's seriously frustrating,
and I can't even think of
it as a good experience.
Not to mention, you ended up
seeing how pathetic I was.
I didn't do anything in high school.
I didn't get to experience any
of the good things in volleyball.
But I already found out
how great it feels to get a spike in,
the pride you feel when
you hear the cheers...
It all depends on if you
have that moment or not.
I want to be in a place where I can
do my best until I'm satisfied.
Right...
I see.
Ukai
You have a match tomorrow, don't you?
That's probably enough, then!
One more! Just one more!
We'll finish after this one!
Please!
Hey, I've never seen that tall kid before.
Just one more.
Thanks!
He said he didn't get enough practice today
All right, Hinata! We're going to nail this!
and begged to use our
courts until we started.
Yeah!
Let's go!
I know!
Apparently he's the setter
from Sho-chan's school.
Huh...
Here we go!
I've been watching for a while,
but they keep messing up.
Hey, Aone, did you grow even taller?!
Oh, my. You're here again, Kamasaki-san?
Date Tech
Are you that bored?
Is finding a job going okay?
Aren't your sleeves rolled up too far?
Niro, you bastard!
You should be more respectful to your elders!
Hey, Kunimi.
Is it true about Oikawa-san?
Probably?
He always goes to extremes.
Huh? Torino?
It's Karasuno.
Where's that? Never heard of it.
If you've got the strength
to beat Shiratorizawa,
you can beat any school in the prefecture.
Simple as that.
The Greater Serves for the Lesser
I'm Hinata Shoyo, from the concrete.
I'm going to beat you,
and go to nationals.
One more!
August 11th.
The Japanese National High
School Volleyball Tournament,
otherwise known as the High
School Spring Tournament.
The first preliminaries
of the Miyagi Qualifiers
start today!
There are times you can tell who's gonna win
just by seeing if a team
has someone super tall.
I'm not so tall that you need
to add "super" before it.
I'm telling you, your height is your weapon!
You're so not cute...
Please don't look for cuteness in in a guy
Episode 12: "Let the Games Begin!"
who's almost 190 centimeters tall.
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Let the Games Begin!"