Second Dish
Episode 1
Totsuki Tea House Culinary Academy:
a culinary bastion that continues
to produce world-renowned chefs.
Cooking in Progress
Their high school first-years are
contestants in the Autumn Elections,
which is now coming to a head.
Those who have survived the preliminary round
are now preparing for the next battle.
Polar Star Dormitory
All right!
Did I pack the petty knife?
There it is...
Did I pack the timer?!
There will only be an explanation
about the main tournament today.
Do you really need your tools?
Oh, right.
Yeesh. You never change.
Hey, Tadokoro.
Our ride's here.
Let's go!
The eight elites, none of whom
lack individuality and expertise,
will wear themselves to the bone
to ascend to the top!
The Autumn Elections'
main tournament will now begin!
What Fills the Box
Soma-kun, about the lottery results...
You'll be competing in the very first round.
The theme for the round is bento.
Bento?
You mean that bento?
That's right.
Finish all the necessary preparations today
for the match tomorrow.
Bento, huh... this academy's more
down-to-earth than I thought.
Ha.
What are you talking about?
You're ignorant to the extreme.
Bento is a food culture unique to Japan.
Gourmands have long loved bentos
created from high-end seasonal ingredients.
Even prominent chefs overseas
are familiar with bentos,
and the word has even been added
to a French dictionary.
It is a theme that is justifiably
appropriate for a celebration of food.
It's an entirely different beast from the
B-grade "gourmet" food you're an expert in!
I've gotta say, I'm still not a fan
of that side of your personality.
I'm pretty good at talking with people,
but man, Nakiri, you're something else.
What?!
Things were pretty tense between us
on our way back from camp, too!
What's your point?!
I have no idea what you're getting at!
You're irritating me!
Oh, this is odd.
She don't usually raise her voice.
Ah, I have a visitor regarding
an unrelated topic.
Excuse me.
Yukihira Soma.
Try your best to make it through the rounds.
It'd be quite a downer if you were
to fail in the very first round.
So, who am I going up against?
The 43rd Autumn Elections
The Following Day
Getten Hall
Thank you for your patience!
The main tournament of the
Autumn Elections is finally here!
We will begin with the
first match in round one!
Judges
Academy Director
Nakiri Senzaemon
Our first contestant is
Candidate Yukihira Soma,
who was tied for second place
in Block A preliminaries.
All right!
Good luck, Yukihira!
And his opponent is Candidate Nakiri Alice,
who was the undisputed winner
of the Block B preliminaries!
Nakiri Alice.
Granddaughter to the Academy Director,
Nakiri Senzaemon,
and the grand champion of a countless
international competitions.
A prodigy, she is called
the darling of molecular gastronomy.
Her curry dish, which received the
highest score in the preliminaries,
made use of cutting edge techniques,
and had great impact.
How will you counter that, Yukihira?
Yukihira-kun, today, I'll make
your knees buckle with my cooking.
Wow!
It's the newest in cooking equipment!
Even sitting in the audience,
I can feel the tingling tension on my skin.
I can't believe he has to face
one of the Nakiris in this atmosphere.
Yeah, I wonder how much pressure
Yukihira's in right now.
I deeply regret
that I'll only be able to see
your cooking once on this great stage.
If you lose, you can keep watching
my cooking from the audience.
Oh, I doubt that could ever happen.
Antiquated ideas and workmanship
that rely on circus theatrics
are not sufficient to overcome
the limits of culinary knowledge.
Oh, you didn't get a good night's rest?
Oh, I was up pretty late testing my dish.
It was dawn before I realized the time.
But don't worry,
this is just a normal day for me.
Foodie customers with high expectations,
shining knives honed to a razor edge,
and an array of ingredients...
The only thing that's different
is that I have a formidable
business rival in front of me.
I'll gain a lot today
from winning against you.
I'll use all that I'll gain
to grow even stronger!
On to the first match!
Autumn Elections
Main Tournament
The topic is "bento."
Round 1
Bento
The time limit is two hours!
Let the cooking begin!
Standby Room
Good luck, Soma-kun.
It's like watching a chemistry experiment.
Marui, explain!
No, this is beyond
the limits of my knowledge.
Are those glasses just for show?!
This makes my Japanese DNA very happy.
What?
Oh, you were making fun
of workmanship earlier,
but you do have skills.
Of course!
How rude!
You shouldn't stare at people like that!
I remember being stared at during camp...
He's up against the
director's granddaughter...
Damn it!
Yukihira, you'd better have
some trick up your sleeve!
I bet he can win...
Come!
Both candidates are close to completion!
Who will finish first?
It's Candidate Nakiri Alice!
Come, let's serve lunch.
What?!
What is that?
Is that... mist under the transparent dome?
Damn, it's so easy for her
to take us completely by surprise!
Huh, there you go serving
something weird again.
What an excellent display
that piques one's interest!
It is entirely befitting
a celebration of food.
Temari sushi, is it?
Yes.
I used every technique I had at my disposal
to create this temari bento.
It's so beautiful!
Hmm, the mist was from liquid nitrogen.
It also had the purpose of keeping the sushi
fresh with the chill, I presume.
If I may,
I'd like to ask that you eat the bento
starting from the upper left.
First, the bounties of the sea.
There's foam on top of the abalone.
That foam is kelp stock.
The abalone was also wrapped
in kelp during preparation.
By wrapping abalone in kelp,
you can get rid of excess moisture
and prolong its freshness.
It's a method well-suited for making bento.
You're right.
But I doubt that's the
only reason for the kelp.
For that sushi,
I used bonito that has been aged
for two days at low temperatures.
Hmm...
The umami is out of this world!
This umami isn't coming
from the bonito alone...
It's inosinic acid from the bonito
and glutamic acid from
the kelp used in the first sushi.
Those umami factors have
a synergistic effect.
This bento dish forms a
complete picture in your mouth
as you eat each sushi in succession.
Wow.
I want to try that!
It looks delicious.
The second row is next.
They are a type of sushi using vegetables
called "sushi cakes" in some circles.
Pumpkin
No nori was used in these sushi.
Instead, paper-thin slices of vegetables
are used to wrap the sushi.
Beet
Nozawana
This bento has no use for heavy, dark colors.
Zucchini
And finally, the third row.
This practically screams, "I'm the main dish!"
It is aged beef fillet sushi.
Beef Fillet
Here comes another wave!
The two umami factors
just spread through your mouth...
I can see where the inosinic acid comes from,
given that there's meat involved,
but where's the glutamic acid coming from?
Tomatoes.
Tomatoes?
I don't see them anywhere.
It was a component of the sushi cakes.
I used a centrifuge to separate tomatoes
into pigment, fiber, and jus.
Pigment
Fiber
Jus
The jus was filtered several times
to remove impurities.
A few drops of that jus
was added to the sushi cakes.
I see!
To think that the original ingredient
was rendered completely invisible!
Now, the last item.
What is the sphere nestled
next to the sea bream sushi?
The sphere...
...is concentrated stock!
This is a sea bream chazuke
that comes together on your tongue!
"The darling of molecular gastronomy."
Her techniques does justice to her moniker.
She was able to entertain her guests
with her cooking from start to finish.
This deep satisfaction
is as though we just enjoyed a feast at a
luxurious traditional Japanese restaurant!
From this tiny bento box
roars forth such...
...culinary wisdom!
He's bared his chest!
There he goes!
The director's gone bare-chested!
Well done.
This is Nakiri Alice's true strength.
How can such a chef be the same age as us?
Even if I spent my entire life
trying to reach her level, I never will...
When one's genius shines too brightly,
it casts a shadow.
That is her karma.
This is Totsuki Academy.
I have no need for weaklings
who would falter by this display.
Look.
Five bentos, all done!
There's at least one chef
who is not deterred.
Yukihira Soma, what is your dish?
Nori bento.
What?!
Did he say nori bento?!
How can he possibly hope
to beat Nakiri Alice with that?
Soma's Nori Bento (Assumption)
Nori bento?!
What the hell?
He's finished.
Yukihira-kun.
Huh?
What's a nori bento?
What, you don't know?
I can make one for you later.
It's not just any nori bento, though.
It's Yukihira-Style Evolved Nori Bento!
Enjoy!
They're called lunch jars.
They're made of stainless steel,
and can retain the heat of rice and soup.
Hmm, Japanese bento boxes
are pretty advanced.
More recent models can retain
their contents' heat for up to half a day.
Sides
Rice
Soup
If you heat up the soup before
you put it in the jar,
it does a better job of
keeping the rice warm.
Oh, how clever!
Where's the tension?
It's not like the match is over.
She's being condescending toward Yukihira.
She's all smiles because
she's convinced she'll win.
Hmm, first, there are three side dishes.
Hmm!
This fish cake fried with nori is amazing!
I made the fish cake from scratch.
He used beer in the batter.
Alcohol is more volatile than the batter,
so it becomes light and crispy.
Huh?
Why do you know what he did, Ryoko?
I saw Yukihira-kun testing his dish
at the dorm last night,
so I asked for a taste.
Oh!
So much umami's bursting forth!
I can smell the sea!
I'll envelop you.
Wh-Who are you?
The kinpira-style sauteed burdock
also has a mellow, deep flavor.
I've added just a bit of mayonnaise and
balsamic vinegar as secret ingredients.
I see.
You were very meticulous with this dish.
Oh!
Look how easily the chopsticks
cut through the fried cod!
The cod must've been first simmered
in stock and seasoning before it was fried.
That step gave it its soft, flaky texture.
What?!
What a pure, mild flavor it has!
It is like a gentle highlands breeze!
What refined flavor!
Where is this coming from?!
The answer to that question
can be found in the stock.
This is dried tuna stock.
That's right.
The cod was simmered in stock
made from dried tuna and rishiri kelp.
Dried tuna...
That would've been made from yellowfin tuna.
Yes.
While it is not as rich as bonito stock,
it has a very delicate and elegant umami.
Cod also has a light umami,
so the dried tuna is a perfect match.
What a light dish!
The soup is next!
Oh!
It's bacon and onion miso soup!
Ah, this too...
The unique fragrance of the
tuna stock fills your nostrils.
Combined with the meltingly sweet onions,
it's as though the soup
envelops your entire body.
Also, there is a trick to
taking advantage of this bento box.
Just by putting the stock, ingredients,
and seasonings in the container,
you can have a sweet soup a few hours later.
The vegetables will be cooked through.
Oh, that's useful.
Today, there won't be any time delay,
so I've cooked the ingredients already.
You know a lot about bentos.
Sure. I've made them at my family's diner.
But that's not enough, Yukihira-kun.
Your efforts are all too conventional.
Even bentos should be full
of spectacular surprises.
Just like my Temari Bento.
Yeah, yours did look really tasty.
Let me try it sometime.
Yes, of course.
But was your dish really amazing as a bento?
What did you say?
I'm asking you what we
should be putting in bento boxes.
Diner Yukihira
One of my diner's regulars
was a granny called Kiyo-san.
She came almost every day,
but one day, she hurt her back,
and couldn't come.
Hello?
Granny Kiyo!
Is your back okay?!
Soma-chan, isn't your diner busy right now?
Ow...
Here you go!
What?
You haven't had dinner yet, right?
Later!
You came here just to deliver this?
The diner was super empty,
so I made this for you.
Eat this and get better!
P.S. Lift up the nori
before eating the rice!
Diner Yukihira
A person should taste
what I was trying to deliver
in the bento box that day.
The flavors, and what lies beyond!
What?
What is this rice?
I... Is this...
...really nori bento?!
There are strange black grains
on top of the rice.
What's that?
Caviar?
Fish roe?
It's black.
How curious!
Nonetheless, I must try this.
Knock on wood!
It feels like salmon roe
bursting in your mouth!
What gushes forth from within
is the umami of nori!
The nori's salty umami goodness
bursts forth to coat each grain of rice.
I can't stand it!
It's addicting!
You made those spheres
by extracting the nori's umami
and adding sodium alginate
and potassium chloride.
Molecular gastronomy!
But that's...
...Nakiri Alice's specialty!
How do you know this technique?
I was invited by Isshiki-senpai the other day
to help out at a kids' cooking class.
Huh?
I got to be buddy-buddy with the kids.
At the end of class,
they gave me snacks and stuff.
One of the snacks reminded me of something...
Pop-A-Spheres
When I was a kid, I'd tried one of these.
What?
A cheap candy product?!
What are you talking about?
This is one of those so-called
educational snacks.
Potassium chloride and sodium alginate...
It's a snack that lets you
make artificial fish roe.
I was really into it as a kid.
I played around with it quite a bit.
Look, Dad!
I made miso soup solid!
Wow, that's cool.
But don't ever serve that at our diner.
These black beads are nori umami bombs
that I made from seasoned nori.
He thought of a molecular gastronomy
technique from a cheap candy product?
Hm?
There's something else in the rice...
So much flavor!
It's dried tuna simmered down in soy sauce!
It was a four-layer dish!
If Nakiri Alice's dish was a
meticulously-arranged jewel box,
this nori bento is a treasure box
full of marvels waiting to be discovered!
It reminds me of my field trips
and picnics as a child...
That excitement
when I'd open the bento box...
It's all coming back to me now!
My Temari Bento included even
a finishing dish: the sea bream chazuke!
The overall taste quality
was higher in mine—
Oh, please stop!
Can you leave about one-third of the rice?
There's yet another compartment
under the very first lid.
It's kudzu sauce!
That kudzu sauce has three times more
dried tuna and rishiri kelp than the norm!
Pour it over the piping hot rice and dig in.
Let's finish up.
Of course that's...
...going to be...
...delicious!
Ah, kudzu sauce!
It's so good!
Combined with the nori bombs...
...it's a whole new level of flavor!
Those judges...
They're eating like it's really fun,
unlike when they were eating
Nakiri Alice's dish.
Yukihira-kun.
Are you trying to make the point
that bentos should contain "heart"?
What's important is the flavor, isn't it?
Don't get all "mind over matter" on me—
No!
It's not about that, Alice.
Grandfather!
When'd he get bare-chested?!
Alice, your bento
took advantage of the cold.
Yes, because bentos should be chilled.
Yukihira Soma didn't get fixated like that.
He first thought about the bento container,
then filled it with entertainment
whose flavor was enhanced by warmth.
That's what this bento is.
Of course, your dish was
delicious in the extreme.
But wouldn't you say that you
would've served the same dish
if the theme had been sushi?
You merely used your skills to fill that box.
There are flavors that can
only be communicated through bento.
There are creative techniques
you can devise to advance bento culture.
Bentos can be fun and
innovative in their own way.
Did your dish capture any of that?
Well, sure...
but what's important is the flavor.
I don't disagree with that.
Dig in, Nakiri Alice!
Alice-sama, you look well.
How is Erina-sama?
Please give Erina-sama my regards.
Erina-sama.
Erina-sama!
Erina-sama...
Father, I would like to go to
your research lab in Scandinavia!
Please take me there now!
What's cutting edge... the most advanced...
I must gain weapons that are mine alone,
so that I won't lose to Erina...
I can't lose to anyone...
...before I win against Erina, and yet...
Bring me the brush!
It's so warm...
Round one, match one!
The victor...
Yukihira Soma
...is Yukihira Soma!
Glad you liked it!
He won!
Woohoo!
Yukihira!
Miss Alice...
Yukihira, you're really interesting.
Soma
Soma-kun.
Wow!
You're amazing!
The second match is about to begin.
Please get ready.
Oh, o-okay.
Charm for
Academic
Success
It's my turn next...
The Second Dish
Next Episode: The Interplay of Light and Shadow
Food
Wars
Next episode: "The Interplay of Light and Shadow."