I'm hungry, Nako.
Me too.
Give me a second.
Jeez, it's not often I'm off work early,
yet look at what I'm doing...
Oops...
I don't want onions.
Me neither.
You won't grow if you don't eat-
If you don't eat your veggies,
the old man from the third district is
gonna steal your belly button!
No!
I don't agree.
Praising a child too much
is counterproductive.
What if they get accustomed to it
and grow up to be lazy?
No, children are clever.
If they're praised,
they'll work even harder to become
someone that deserves the praise.
You're thinking way too positively.
Can't you discuss this kind of thing at school?
Now, get changed before dinner!
And clean this place up please!
Sorry... Sorry.
Nako, you make our
lives so much easier.
Yeah, definitely.
What would we do without you?
Considering what I heard you just say,
those words don't hold much credibility.
Nako, the meal's gonna burn.
Coming...
Hey!
How many times do I have to tell
Nako's so reliable.
you not to steal food?!
I bet it's because I
raised her by praising her.
Now you're going to say
Hey! Raising a child and
teaching aren't-
that you're full when dinner's ready!
Hey!
Sorry.
The mermaid princess who admired
the prince wanted to
see the outside world.
The prince, seen
from above the water,
was very handsome…
If I were a mermaid princess,
I wouldn't admire a prince...
I would swim freely in the water,
and take a break
whenever I got tired...
because land is... scary.
To me,
my home is like the ocean.
I'm off!
Nako, I can't find my right shoe!
What?!
How many times do
I have to tell you to
put them away together?
Really!
Looking after my
siblings is a difficult task,
but I'm most like myself when I do...
Bad boy!
Morning, Nako.
You don't have work this morning?
N-No...
Good morning…
Nako, my shoe!
My job doesn't start
until late this afternoon...
My shoe! My shoe!
Nako!
Yes... it's difficult to breathe above the water.
Shoe!
Episode 18
A Mermaid Princess and a Shell Bra
Excuse me,
do you happen to
know what flower is especially in
bloom right now around here?
Oh… which flower?
Yeah, I'd love to take some pictures of
wild, dynamic flowers
instead of just small ones.
D-Dynamic?
U-Umm…
Oh, don't worry about it.
Looking for flowers in bloom
while going on our walk
sounds pleasant as well, right?
Yeah, we should sleep early tonight
in preparation for tomorrow.
"Buckwheat flowers grow in clumps past the lake."
"They should be really
pretty this time of year."
"But the path is filled with steep slopes,
so hiking boots would be..."
Why couldn't I just say this to them earlier?
As I thought, I can't swim the
way I want above the water.
What's up?
N-Nothing.
There you are!
You two,
we're meeting in the office!
What?
It's the payday we've
all been waiting for!
All right!
I-It's gone down by 15,000 yen...
You broke the vase
in the Crane Room, didn't you?
I-I'm sorry,
but a child bumped into me from behind, and-
If you prefer, I can deduct the
entire cost of it from your salary.
That was very expensive Kutani ware.
It's definitely worth more than
twenty to thirty thousand yen.
What do you want to do?
I'll gladly take this.
Huh?
Wow!
This is more than I usually get...
I bet she has high expectations, Nako.
If they're praised,
they'll work even harder to become
someone that deserves the praise.
Madam Manager…
What do you say to leaving me
in charge of that money, Miss Nako?
I'm in the middle of writing a
novel about currency exchange, and-
Don't you dare ask a high
schooler for an investment!
Man…
The kinako mochi-flavored tirol
chocolates are 20 yen each,
so if I had 15,000 yen,
I'd be able to buy...
750.
That's a lot!
You can buy a lot, can't you?
I'm so jealous!
Can I have one?
But I'm not planning to buy any.
I think Madam Manager
wants me to change.
What?
I think she wants me to work hard to
become someone who deserves
the amount I was given.
Yeah?
In that case, I'd better...
I think you're the type
who gets carried away
when praised, so...
"Get carried away..."
I-I'm so sorry!
I meant in a good way! A good way!
I started working here
because I wanted to change.
Oh yeah, you've mentioned this before.
I'm pretty happy with
the way I act at home,
or, well, I think that's the real me.
But outside of my home...
So the person speaking to me now
isn't the real Nakochi?
What?
When I'm with you or Minchi...
I guess just a little bit...
Come out, real Nakochi!
Stop it! Not the forehead!
I don't want you to see it!
Please! Not the forehead!
Pay, huh?
I'm jealous.
I had 15,000 deducted,
so a lot of my freedom money is gone.
Oh, is that empty? Can I have it?
Sure, but why?
I'm gonna fill it up
with water to drink!
Ohana…
That's kinda depressing.
What are you gonna
spend yours on, Tsurugi?
Tilefish.
What? Tilefish?
I've always wanted to try out
the Matsukasayaki method of cooking.
There's no way they're gonna let
me use expensive ingredients, so...
I-I see...
What about you, Oshimizu?
I don't really have any hobbies...
nor is there anything
I really want to study... Yeah,
I guess I'll just save it.
What?! That's such a waste!
Money is meant to be spent!
But…
My grandmother said that
money "polishes" people!
Polishes people?
I know!
Let's go shopping after school!
Shopping?!
That's a great idea!
Why don't you buy
yourself a drink if you have
the money to go shopping?
I'll pack some barley tea
for lunch tomorrow.
I like this.
Yuina likes clothing that shows too much skin,
and Minchi only looks at the 3 for 1000 yen T-shirts.
T-Shirts on Sale
3 for 1000 yen
Wow, beige polka dots!
So cute!
Ohana actually has
pretty good taste.
She's from Tokyo, after all.
Man, these puffed sleeves are so cute!
Maybe I'll try them on!
You don't have the money for them.
Jeez, at least let me dream!
I-I want to try that on too!
I can't believe it's the same dress...
I didn't realize it was a sexy dress.
I wanna be sexy too...
No… No!
You're wasting your body!
Okay, one more time, Oshimizu!
House!
H-House?
Hey, you done yet?
Y-Yeah…
Okay, then!
Wow! You look great!
You look so mature, Nakochi!
I'm showing too much leg… Umm…
Girls really do change after
you give them a new outfit!
Change?
Nakochi?
Thank you!
Excuse me...
Hello!
I'll buy all of this!
All of it?!
She's so rich…
Madam Manager…
Financially, we're not in the
best state at the moment.
Did we really have the
money to raise Nako's salary?
Are you in any position
to talk about this?
Well, no…
Karaoke
These flowers cover the entire field...
Oshimizu looks a little
more fashionable now,
but did she really have
to pick such a lame song?
What should I sing...
Oh! The spirit boat progression song!
Where's Houzen Temple's
Alleyway in the Moon…
You still haven't decided?
I always just have my siblings' leftovers,
so I don't really know…
Ginger pudding is pretty unique,
but this hamburger steak with
10 different vegetables...
I wonder which vegetables they used.
Oh, you can order however much you like!
I'll just eat your leftovers.
What?
Oh, don't worry! We can
split the bill in half.
Excuse me!
Are you ready to order?
I want the cheapest one…
The house blend!
With extra milk! Lots of it!
Milk?
I can't drink coffee
because it's too bitter,
but I do like cafe au lait.
But I don't have any money, so…
This is just too sad!
What's wrong, Nakochi?
I did so many things today
that I'm not used to,
that it's left me tired.
I'm having fun, though.
Ohana?
See, although we work
together all the time,
it's the first time we've
been out together like this.
Now that you mention it,
you also don't seem to have any friends, right?
What?
I don't mean it in a bad way!
In a good way!
I don't seem to have any friends in a good way?
No, that's not what I meant!
How do I put it...
You're always so frank and straightforward,
I figured you'd have a lot of enemies!
Umm…
In a good way!
Do you think anything can be forgiven
by just tacking on a,
"in a good way" at the end?
N-No!
My throat…
I'm gonna die!
I'm so thirsty, I'm gonna die!
Water!
No, how about tea instead?
We'd like to have tea
with you pretty girls!
Performers planning to go pro?
Else we're gonna die!
That's so funny!
Then why don't you die?
Y-Yuina, that's not very nice!
They're trying to pick us up.
"Pick up"?
What does that mean?
Sorry, it's a girls' night out!
Don't say such a thing!
Like I said…
You're an oasis…
in this city desert!
Nakochi's getting hit on!
What? What?
What?!
Wait, Nakochi!
Nako!
Wow! What's all this?!
There's so much cake!
Hey, is it someone's birthday?
Is it your birthday, Nako?
What's with the cake
and your outfit, Nako?
It's not like you, N-
That's right!
This is change,
but it's not the right kind of change!
Now that I think about it,
appearance has nothing to do with work...
Jeez, I wasted money!
But it's not like I want money…
I don't get it anymore!
N-Nako?
"An oasis in this city desert," huh?
I can't swim in a desert.
I want to swim freely.
Princess Nakochi!
Why, hello, tilefish.
The Queen's calling for you.
Th-This outfit…
It's an era where mermaids
should also dress nicely.
B-But this is too heavy!
Work hard in order
to become someone
who suits all of that jewelry.
What's the matter?
No…
It's too heavy. I'm going to sink…
Both the ornaments and the
expectations are too much…
I might not be able to change,
but if I could just act like my regular self...
Oh, Mr. Ren.
It's almost autumn, after all.
I decided to spend a
huge amount of money.
It cost 150,000 yen.
Umm…
It looks very cool.
Good morning!
Hey! Morning.
You can't dress up all
funny like that at work, Mr. Ren.
"D-Dress up all funny"?
Mr. Ren!
Well then, if you'll excuse me!
Good morning!
What?
Oh, good morn-
Okay, I'm doing well!
I'll just act like my regular self.
The way I normally act towards my siblings!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
That's right… Good! Good!
Fight! Fight!
Sir, do you mind if I take your luggage to your room?
That's the spirit… That's the spirit…
Go! Go!
Come! Come!
Good! Take it slow… Good!
That's right… Fight! Fight!
Just as normal... just as normal...
Yes… Yes…
Then, I'll take these to your room.
There's no need to rush.
Don't touch that!
I was filming the flowers blooming!
Jeez, now I have to start
from the beginning!
I'm so sorry!
Well, he forgave you.
Just don't do it again
in the future, understand?
Y-Yes, Ma'am.
What's wrong? Get back to work.
U-Umm…
I… Well…
About my salary…
I-I'm not a waitress
that deserves a raise.
I just made a huge mistake.
I bet you're expecting me to improve
because I'm bad at my job, but...
I'm a poor talker and it takes me
a while to get the hang of things,
and I'm bad at interacting
with customers.
I…
Let me tell you one thing:
this isn't a school.
What?
I wasn't thinking of improving your will
when I gave you a raise.
What? B-But…
Read this.
To: Kissuiso's Madam Manager
The customer from yesterday
went home while you were at school.
The flower field atop the mountain was just beautiful.
We were right to listen to the
waitress's advice to purchase hiking boots.
We'll definitely come back
to see that waitress again.
There are customers
who like the work you do,
and that's why I gave you a raise.
Is there anything wrong with that?
The work I do?
But the real me is a lot
more cheerful, louder, and…
When you're at Kissuiso,
you're quiet and nervous,
but you notice things
that no one else would notice,
and you give a welcoming service.
That's the kind of waitress you are.
Minchi.
The customers in the
Crane Room can't eat
wild blue-skinned fish.
Got it.
Oh, Nakochi.
Swimming freestyle in the air?
That was weird.
Almost as weird as kinako
mochi-flavored snacks, huh?
This isn't the ocean,
but…
Even though I was pretty mean to the prince,
I'm still going to aim for the land!
I feel like I can swim anywhere now!
Cultural festival, huh?
Let's fest it up together!
Yeah, let's make it a
great cultural festival.
I don't mind working my shift…
Episode 19
Sloppy Omelet Rice
We're young and restless!