Huh?
Good morning!
It's the Hero, Rico-chan,
and Eclair-san.
We brought you some provisions.
This morning, we and the imperial guard
helped bring in the harvest.
We wanted to bring you guys some, too.
Thank you so much.
You guys are up early.
Looks like it's the Hero's party.
My lady!
Isuka-san.
Good morning.
Are you two going out somewhere?
That's right.
An old friend is coming over.
Wow!
A Dragon?
Ina! Isuka!
It's been a long time.
We're here with Kratos to pick you up.
Adele. Valerie.
It's been ages!
You two are going somewhere with them?
We're old friends.
Been that way for a long time,
for better or for worse.
Battle at the Cave of Sealing!
We're off, then!
Back in the day, when the Hero King
was actively being a hero,
those two were members of her party.
The Hero Adel, and the
Summoning Princess.
The Demon King Valerie and
the Swordsmith Isuka.
And the young Master Swordsman, Hina Maxima.
Hina... Isuka-san calls her that, too.
The name Brioche d'Arquien is something
she received from the ruling lord
when she became a knight of Biscotti.
Both names seem to be important to her.
Once again, I'm surprised.
I had never seen a dragon before, either.
Kratos is a member of
the Hero's party, too.
Speaking of, where might they be off to?
I heard they were headed for
the Fraise desert in the south.
Something about verifying the
integrity of the demon seal, or something.
So hot...
Just as hot as it used to be.
Kratos, just a little further
until the Cave of Sealing.
We're counting on you.
I haven't been here in quite a while.
Quite right.
The sprites of the land seem to be well.
It's so peaceful.
It looks like there is no problem
with any of my sealing swords.
That's amazing, Isuka!
I just hope that the demons
who are sealed away
are returning to their uncorrupted
form in their sleep...
If my theory is right,
then it will definitely
work out that way.
Demon transformation is something
that happens because the gods
or sprites of the land are sick.
With the right treatment,
they will always return to normal.
I suppose the long sword demons disappear,
if the root cause is removed.
The sealing method
in this cave is to
return the naturally occurring
demons to their sprite state.
The experiment is progressing well.
Now we just have to check the results.
Not that it'd normally be my concern
if demons were to run wild!
This seal is quite worn down.
The third seal...
It was quite a long time ago.
What was this demon?
I believe it was a huge mouse.
Yeah, that was quite a handful.
At the time this sword was
quite a masterpiece...
The third seal has been broken.
Commencing emergency shuttering
of this portion of the cave in order to prevent the
demons from moving freely.
I didn't expect that.
Well, these things can happen.
If it's coming back, then we'll
just seal it away again!
We'll strike the moment it comes out!
Would the person in charge of the seal
please deal with the demon?
Little mice?
Was it that kind of demon?
Mice, slow down!
You mustn't run wild!
Did it split itself during the sealing?
That's unexpected...
Yeah.
In any case,
we have to catch them.
Heavenly Crimson Blade!
They turned into balls?!
Then that means these little ones
already have the protection
of the Flogna power?
They are part way to becoming sprites!
At the very least,
they are no longer demons!
You're right!
Hey, you honeymooners there!
You can rejoice later!
They are half-sprites with
unknown eating habits
and breeding speed!
This means they pose a very real threat!
You're right.
Hina, can't you talk to them?
They're all hungry!
They're not in a state where
you can reason with them!
We have no choice.
Indeed.
Adel! Valerie!
You two!
Owww.
Damn mice!
You two...
What is this?!
We got younger?!
This one, too!
In any case...
Hina, above you!
S-So heavy...
Hina!
This way, Hina!
You guys, too!
This is bad.
I'm sure I can handle this somehow.
Adel, that's...
The recoil!
Adel!
It's not safe here, either.
Adel, Valerie!
Isn't there something we can do?
It's no good.
My Demon King seal isn't working.
Hina's in a sad state, too.
We have no choice,
we have to call for help.
Help?
Last time we set up a
network with the Heroes.
Its name: BraveConnect!
Hello, my successors!
Do you have a moment for me?
Adel-sama?
You seem a little...
Did something happen?
To be honest,
we're having a bit of
demon related trouble.
Heroes, could I ask you to assist us?
Of course!
We'll leave right now!
We should all go!
We're facing small animals.
Please bring nets and cages.
We're counting on you.
Right!
There are some fishermen here, right?
We have an emergency,
please lend us your fishing gear.
Sure! If we can be of
help to you, ask away!
We can get everything we need here.
Now, let's hurry!
Okay!
It's starting to get bad...
Indeed...
Adel-sama, the Biscotti group is ready!
The Galette and Pastillage alliance...
is ready, too!
Wonderful, my lovely Heroes!
BraveConnect, Link!
This... is a summoning circle?!
Summon Hero!
You guys!
This is great.
Isuka-san!
Adel-sama, you guys are so small...
Even you, my lady...
Mice!
There's a ridiculous number of them!
Watch out, everybody!
Mercurius!
Nanami! Prince!
We need to deal with these mice!
Leave it to us.
We'll do it!
Rebecca, Couverte, thanks!
Don't worry.
I'm glad that my ancestor needs my help!
Since all three Heroes are here...
Sink, Yukikaze, Eclair!
Leave it to us!
One... and...
Lion King - Lightning Wave
Rebecca!
Yes!
Palette card! Gravity Ball!
Nice, Rebecca!
We got quite a lot of them.
Yeah, we should soon be...
Ecle! Yukki!
What a catch.
I wonder if everybody's okay.
Let's split up to cheer them on.
Those guys...
Becky!
Couverte!
Guys!
Why is everybody so small?
We let our guard down...
I used one of my ninja skills
for our clothes and shoes...
I'm so ashamed...
Cou-sama, please take
everybody to a safe place.
There aren't that many left.
Sink and I will go get them!
Sink, Gaul...
take these.
These?
Jewels?
They will protect you.
Roger that, Adel-sama.
We will keep them safe!
Let's go, Gaul!
Wait! I'll go, too!
Me, too!
All right. There should
be a dead end ahead.
You're really making us work!
It's huge!
Why is there such a huge one here?!
This must be the boss!
Without a doubt!
A Bright Power cannon?
This is bad!
Defender!
That was too close.
Sink, Prince Gaul!
Are you okay?
Becky! Nanami!
We're fine!
Of course we are!
We can't let a dangerous
demon like this roam free!
We're going to beat it
down and capture it!
Grown ups?!
Indeed.
This mouse has used
the stolen life-energy
to turn itself into a giant!
No, not that!
It's not...
Not that it matters!
With Sink's and my...
...anti-demon ultra combo special
move, we'll blast you away!
Furious Lightning!
Conflagration!
Heavenly Edge! Sealing Strike!
Wow...
Cool...
Sink, you're...
You too, Gaul.
You're huge!
You notice now?!
So you two materialized
the Hero Crystals' power in that form.
A seal appeared on the bottom
of the crystal, however.
On this one, too.
It looks like it's carved in.
This is proof that the Hero Crystal
has accepted you as its rightful owner.
That means both Sink and the
Prince are Hero material.
By the way, why do you think we
haven't returned to normal yet?
We'll be normal soon.
I do hope so.
But Gau-sama, you're so cool!
So handsome.
That's true, of course.
I don't want to admit it,
but you're not bad.
Sink, it looks like you're going to get
much taller than me.
You just think that because
you're small right now.
That's a really strange
sight to behold...
It warms my heart.
You're returning to normal.
Indeed.
That means...
Gau-sama, don't look!
Sink, you can't stay here!
Hero Stinger!
We're normal again!
And my spell...
You're heavy!
I'm not heavy.
...is no longer effective.
I knew it.
Everybody, I have your clothes here!
Oww, my eyes!
What a day...
Thank you, Becky,
for being so considerate.
Don't mention it.
We're turning, hold on tight.
Okay.
N-Not there, maybe somewhere else.
Oh, sorry. Did that tickle?
That's not it...
It's just that,
when you're in that state,
it feels...
...kind of illegal.
Illegal?!
I didn't mean it like that.
It's just that you look like that,
so it just doesn't look right.
Illegal...
Come on!
So, after all that had happened,
the mice have been
heavily sealed up again.
I hope that they will be
reborn as gods and sprites
of the land without further issues.
We're back to normal!
I'm a little sad.
Well, in a few years,
those two will look like that again.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm glad, I do prefer
this version of Sink.
So you're not going to treat me
like a criminal when I touch you?
I won't! See?
It's fine!
Me, too!
Cou-sama!
Ecle, come join us!
No, thank you!
Thanks to your help,
everything worked out fine.
So that's what happened.
What?! That's so mean!
Everyone else always gets to have all the fun!
That's not fair!
It's mean to leave me behind!
Sorry, it was so sudden.
But I promise that I'll
play with you tomorrow.
Really?!
Of course!
I'm so happy!
Rebecca-san, was the adult Sink cool?
Uh... actually, very...
I wish I could've seen him!
I wanted you to see him, too.
So what was he like?
Those two get along so well, as usual.
Yup.
I have to say, a stroll
through the night sky
with my descendant is quite nice.
If I'll do, I am always
available for it.
Damn, that was horrible.
My eyes still hurt.
It's because of your usual behavior.
Exactly.
My eyes hurt.
Are you the hero whose special
move is eye gouging?!
I accidentally unleashed
my secret move...
Esnart Arts and Music Festival
So, next time...
Make sure to tune in!