Today I promised to play
with Saikawa in the park.
I see. Have fun.
Mm.
Do you have any plans for today,
Miss Kobayashi?
I guess I'd like to spend my day
off relaxing at home for once.
Understood!
I'll give it my utmost best as your
maid to ensure you can relax.
Well, just leaving me alone is fine.
Kanna!
Take care.
Yeah.
I hope the sun comes out today.
Cute.
Shepherd's purse, huh?
Flower Language
Dictionary
Flower language?
Yes. It's a book about the language of flowers.
Georgie lent it to me.
It's interesting.
Saikawa.
The meaning of shepherd's purse is...
There!
Shepherd's Purse
Flower Meaning:
I'll offer everything to you.
Brassicaaceae Family,
Capsella Genus, Annual.
I'll offer everything to you?!
My everything for you, Kanna-san!
My everything?
Here you go, Miss Kobayashi.
Yeah, thanks.
How is it?
Oh, it's good.
I've been trying to change
the temperature and such,
depending on how you're feeling.
You dragons are amazing.
It's not because I'm a dragon.
It's because I'm me.
Well, I should go shopping soon.
What should I make for tonight's dinner?
Omurice.
Sounds good!
Let's go with that, then.
Make us proper ones today, please.
Leave it to me!
I'm heading out.
Okay.
Omurice, omurice!
LED Light
Campaign
On Now
Their lifespan is short!
Yes. For example, the house mouse only
lives for a year to a year and a half.
House Mouse
Lifespan
Human
Ah, how sad!
That's not so.
Every living creature has
its own perception of time,
and applying human standards
to them is mistaken.
How long are you planning
to keep doing this?
Are you me?
That's right.
I'm the doubt within you.
Don't avert your eyes.
Don't deceive yourself.
And with that...
I ask you. How long are you
planning to keep doing this?
I just want to enjoy this time I have now,
and spend time with
Miss Kobayashi, that's all...
How long?
You understand, don't you?
One day you will have to go back.
I won't go back.
I don't intend to go back.
Because I'm Miss Kobayashi's maid.
You're not. You're a dragon!
What will you do if you
have a reason to return?
If the war back there worsens?
If you long for battle?
If Miss Kobayashi were to...
Die
Miss Kobayashi... The place I belong...
Father?
You understand why I'm here, yes?
You're coming home with me.
Tohru, this isn't where you belong.
Lady Tohru!
Welcome home, Kanna-chan.
Yeah.
Tohru's still not back yet, huh.
Just how far did she go to shop?
Lady Tohru went home.
No, she's not—
She went home.
Huh?
To the other world.
I think the Emperor of Demise,
Lady Tohru's father, came to pick her up.
What do you mean?
I don't think she'll come
back to this world anymore.
Huh?
She can't go against the Emperor of Demise.
I see.
Seriously?
Episode 13
Emperor of Demise Arrives!
(It Was the Final Episode Before We Knew It)
Crap!
Kanna-chan, wake up!
You'll be late!
Shoot, shoot.
I totally forgot!
Hot!
Oh, man...
I'm sorry, Kanna-chan.
It's okay.
Kobayashi-san.
Kobayashi-san?
Huh?
Oh, Yamashita-kun.
About those revisions...
Yeah, I'll take care of them.
Sorry.
Kobayashi-san, did something happen?
Tohru went home.
To the other world.
I see.
Yeah.
I'm home.
Kobayashi, welcome home.
Sorry I'm late.
Let's have dinner.
Yeah.
Burnable Trash
Time Set
Are you all right?
How so?
Staying this late, pulling overtime.
Kanna-chan's staying at
Saikawa-san's place tonight.
I see.
Want to go for drinks after we're done?
I'll pass tonight.
All right.
Next time, then.
Yeah.
Well, Kanna-sama, young lady, good night.
Good night.
Wh-What's the matter, Kanna-san?
Tohru.
Hades7: Well, time for me to drop off.
Ebony Holy Knight: Oh, me, too.
Ebony Holy Knight: Ooyama-san, good night.
Crystalite: Pulling another all-nighter?
Crystalite: That's crazy. Later.
I'm home.
I should've told her the
omurice was good,
if things were going to turn out like this.
Miss Kobayashi, it's me!
Me, Tohru!
Tohru?
I'm home, Miss Kobayashi!
Oh, I can't fit inside in this form.
Why?
Huh?
I thought you went home.
To the other world.
Yes.
But I came back.
This is kind of awkward.
Yeah.
I'm home, Miss Kobayashi.
Yeah. Welcome home, Toh—
What?
Tohru.
Father.
This is Tohru's...
Why did you come back without permission?
Because I want to be here.
Please!
No.
I told you. We're forbidden from
interfering in this world.
You're coming home with me.
I don't want to!
What you want doesn't matter.
You understand. You can't be in this world.
You can't throw the world
into chaos over your whims.
I want to be here.
Because this is where I belong.
You would live a quiet life as a human?
One day you'll fray apart.
You've sensed that, haven't you?
Come back, Tohru.
Before you get hurt.
Is it okay if I speak up?
That was a mean way of phrasing it.
But it's not nice to butt in
between a parent and child.
I should probably respect Tohru's decision.
I don't want to!
Umm...
Miss Kobayashi!
Choose your words carefully.
You might be the one eliminated,
depending on what you say.
I'm home, Miss Kobayashi.
What is it?
Tohru said she doesn't want to go back!
You...!
You can't interfere in this world, right?
Then you can't kill me.
But I can leave you just shy of death.
That won't change how I feel!
We must obey the rules of the world.
If the dragons charged with defending
order are found to be in this world,
others will be influenced by
that and make their way here.
Things may be fine now, but eventually
some will plot an invasion.
What then?
That wouldn't be Tohru's fault.
You're just twisting this
into her responsibility!
It's a possibility.
Who cares?!
Why are you so fixated on Tohru?
Don't tell me you like Tohru?
I can't believe a human like you would.
Really?
Tohru's a great girl!
I know that.
She's bright and cheerful,
and sometimes she feels down,
but she hides it with a laugh.
And to top it off, she's a maid!
Do you get it?
Don't take my maid away!
She's mine!
You overstep—
I see.
In that case, this space is too small.
Tohru.
This is a first.
You rebelling against me.
I'll decide where I belong on my own.
Hmph.
I respect you, Father.
I admire you.
But that's as a dragon.
Miss Kobayashi is my...
my...
my light!
You know nothing.
In that case...!
If you defy me, I won't show mercy.
Come home, stupid daughter.
I won't go back!
I won't allow it!
Not with a human!
Miss Kobayashi's special!
There!
This is your last chance. Come home.
I won't go back!
You hardhead!
Wait, wait, wait!
Kanna? Miss Kobayashi?
Why are you two fighting?!
Stay out of this, human.
I'm sorry, Miss Kobayashi,
but could you step back for a bit?
Why are you dragons like this?
You'll never get anywhere
if you can't compromise.
What are you getting at?
You're being extreme!
I can never understand that.
Of course. Humans could never understand us.
Not so.
Hmm?
Knowing you're different is only the start.
You grow closer or more distant,
again and again,
while realizing those differences.
And then you start finding
the aspects you like.
You can even build respect.
Respect?
Then you can forge both trust and bonds.
Do you genuinely believe you
can live alongside her?
You're wrong!
We've already been doing that for a long time.
It's about whether or not
you believe it can last.
I believed it would.
What about you?
Try having faith in your daughter!
I won't approve.
Not with something like a human who doesn't
even have the lifespan to live alongside her.
Tohru. My foolish daughter.
Sorry for being selfish.
What should I give you?
Everything. I'll give you everything!
I don't need that much.
Good morning, Tohru.
Good morning, Miss Kobayashi.
Good morning, Lady Tohru.
Morning, Kanna.
Okay, I'm heading out.
We're out of conditioner.
Okay, I'll buy some.
Also...
8 o'clock, right?
I know.
Kanna-san said she was coming
over to play again today.
In that case, I'll prepare chocolates.
Chocolates?
Take care, Shouta.
Stop it!
Try our new waffles!
Thank you very much.
Tohru.
Yes?
I'm thinking of going home for
the first time in a while.
Oh, sounds nice.
Please, you should go.
Will you come with me?
I'll never be able to grow
old with Miss Kobayashi.
One day, the time will come
when we have to part.
Even so, I would never think
I was better off not meeting her.
I just want to treasure this time we have.
I'm home.