Episode 11
"Piano"
You surprised me.
I'm happy,
but...
Kakeru-kun, I wonder if you really like me.
I—
Am I
just trying to make myself think I like you?
Are you?
Am I just trying to validate myself?
It's still snowing around me.
But you can't see it.
We don't understand anything
about each other.
Yeah,
I don't see the snow.
I'm hoping to get my mom
to play piano for me.
I want you to come, too.
Your mom's piano?
That's great.
She's a professional. I think
she'll take it seriously.
Then—
Then, what?
I want you to come.
Will we learn something about
the two of us if we're there?
I'll call Mom now.
Let's ask her to do it tomorrow.
Okikura speaking.
Mom?
Kakeru? What is it?
I have a new friend.
Could you play the piano for her?
That's an unusual request.
It's the first time you've
ever said anything like that.
Yeah.
Sure.
I might as well play a few pieces.
Why don't you invite her parents,
too, if they're available?
Good idea.
Thanks, Mom.
Kakeru,
so, about what we were talking about.
What about it?
Want to come with me?
I'm thinking about it.
Your friend that lent you this phone—
Fukami-san, isn't it?
I met her once.
She came by when you
happened not to be home.
I see.
Yeah.
She's kind and indecisive.
She gets pushed around.
She has trouble with it.
And I'm making her even more confused.
She made me realize I don't know anything.
I see. You like her.
Yeah.
Let's go home.
I'll stay here a little longer.
I feel like this summer started here.
I want to stay here longer.
This is my place, I think.
Your place?
Sacchan told me.
The season,
and the time, and the people you're with,
make an ordinary place special.
You should go home before it gets too late.
Okay.
See you tomorrow afternoon, at my place.
Got it.
Hina-chan?
Yes, please.
I'll be home by tomorrow morning.
Make sure Mom and Dad don't
get too worried. Thanks.
Please. Okay, I'm hanging up.
Onee-chan, oh no!
I'm home.
Welcome. You're late.
Yeah.
Welcome home, Onee-chan.
I hope she's doing well.
Dinner, you two.
Coming.
Onee-chan says she'll eat later.
Thanks for the food.
She says she's not too hungry today,
so she only needs a little.
That sister of mine's so selfish.
Oh.
I want to go to the mountains again.
Yeah? Mountains are nice.
I wonder if Nee-chan can make it this week.
No, I want to hike from the bottom.
How's your
knee?
The trainer who's been helping me out
says it's a lot better now.
Oh.
I'm glad I went to training camp.
Are you joining the club
again second semester?
Coach says I should.
I think I will.
Maybe
I don't really know what Yanagi's doing.
Want to come watch my lessons?
You didn't go home?
That's my line.
You were supposed to go home after a while.
I wonder if this'll become
my place if I stay here all night.
Well—
If I had my own place...
Will you not have to be with your
"sudden, expected loneliness"?
Is it still snowing?
No, not anymore.
Morning, Kakeru.
That call—
Is he sleeping out again?
Morning.
Can Fukami-san's parents make it?
Probably.
Let's have them come a bit early
and have a light meal with us.
Sure.
You're going to have a real
talk with Touko, aren't you?
Yeah.
You still can't decide?
Just because you have Touko doesn't
mean you can't escape from that.
Yeah,
I know.
What?
You sure have guts when it really
comes down to it, Onee-chan.
What?
That was the highest compliment of the
Hinode-hama Middle School Girls' Swim Club.
I see.
I don't have to carry it?
This isn't a service.
It's just to be safe.
You don't trust me?
Honestly, I'm worried,
but I'm not going to let you force yourself.
What?
I'm here for you.
Yeah.
Morning.
I don't want breakfast.
That's pretty unusual, Hina.
Stuff happened yesterday.
I ate too much.
"Stuff"? What?
I'll have lots.
I'm so hungry.
It looks so good!
Mom, Hina-chan says she's not
hungry, so I'll have hers.
Use that root.
Hinode Dance School
Sounds good. I'd love to be there.
What about you, Mom?
Definitely.
So we're set.
All right! I'm going to wear that outfit.
I'll start early on work, then.
I'll help.
What's that about?
Everyone's all like, "Who's that?"
"What is he to you?"
Oh.
So, what'd you think?
What'd I think?
Yeah, your thoughts.
You danced the best out of everyone
there, and you were the prettiest.
You're
leaving after you graduate, aren't you?
Hey,
I did my best yesterday.
Are you going to
Hinode-hama High School
with Onee-chan starting next semester?
That's my plan.
I haven't officially transferred yet.
What are you two talking about?
He's all yours.
Would you like cake?
I'll have some!
Kakeru, how about you guys?
Sorry, we're going for a walk.
I'm starting by 5:30.
Okay.
Are you sure you want to run with me?
No one said that.
I just got into a habit of running.
Here you go.
It's really good!
These are Chinese onions, tomatoes,
and boiled spinach.
Deep-fried vegetables and fried eggs.
Sorry, chopsticks.
Here.
Thanks.
The other day,
at Kirinkan...
Yeah, what about it?
There was something I couldn't say.
Sorry.
I did something awful, and
I got you wound up in it.
I'm sorry.
Sure,
this hike, too.
"For tomorrow."
It is, isn't it?
I've always been seeing shiny things,
partly because of my dad's
job as a glassblower.
I don't know what they are again.
I wonder when I started seeing them.
Can I see that for a second?
Sure.
Our experiment's about to begin.
I hope we learn something.
Yeah, but
maybe we don't have to.
I never thought our families would
get together to listen
to my mom play piano.
But maybe
that's enough.
Kakeru-kun, are you—
Yeah,
I think I'm afraid.
Can you see it too, Kakeru-kun?
Yeah.
Your knees get so messed
up on the way down.
Can you hear my voice?
Yeah, I can.
The other person is nearby,
but you can't see her.
Isn't that weird?
Can you see me?
I can't see too well yet.
What's wrong?
I think I might be afraid to be with you.
Mom's asking me if I want to
go on tour with her around the world.
Kakeru-kun, what are you talking about?
Are you saying you might leave soon?
I think I've had enough of experiencing
the sudden, expected loneliness.
But we were together all day yesterday.
I'm home.
Onee-chan, come on! We're starting.
Have a seat over there.
If that's really a fragment of the future,
it means we'll see the fireworks
together next year, right?
Once we're down the mountain,
I want to go to Kazemichi.
Sure thing.
What's wrong?
I need to talk to Touko again.
It's been a while. How about
we go to Kazemichi later?
Yeah.
Just hurry up and introduce yourselves.
I'm Hiro Shirosaki.
Yanagi Takayama.
I'm Yukinari Imi.
I'm Sachi Nagamiya.
Um, you can see me?
Episode 12
"Fireworks (Once Again)"