Gust of wind leaves fall leaves falling
Got it!
That was big!
I moved so fast!
Not as fast as Chihaya though.
She's not even watching.
Kana-chan and Desktomu-kun are
pretty even in terms of reflexes and speed.
But...
one of them is pulling ahead.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 19
As
the
Years
Pass
Desktomu-kun has two faults.
Kana-chan has zero.
Those faults give Kana-chan
a two card lead by default.
I've always believed that
you can make up for faults,
but after playing Kanai Sakura-san,
I realized something.
Faults can be fatal when you're playing
an opponent who doesn't make mistakes.
You're giving up more than just a card.
You lose your cool.
Two faults against Kana-chan...
This is bad.  Really bad.
I need to make up those cards.
You lose your rhythm,
while allowing your opponent to relax.
His two faults have done more
than cost him two cards.
As this trip takes me away in haste,
Good, I finally took a card
from the opponent's side.
A comeback!
Time to stage a comeback!
Huh?
for I could not recognize you,
like the moon hidden behind the clouds
This is a one-syllable card!
I sent the wrong card!
Why?
I've never sent a
one-syllable card before!
First, I commit faults.
Now, I'm sending the wrong cards.
Why do I keep screwing up?
It's like I'm playing against
Kana-chan and myself at the same time.
I've seen him do this in practice.
When Desktomu-kun is losing
near the end of a match,
he tends to give up
and look ahead to his next chance.
The match is almost over
and I'm down 8 cards...
I don't have a chance.
I'm down 8 cards.  Down 8 cards...
This is the final.
There is no next chance, Desktomu-kun!
We can train ourselves.
So we can focus when we're tired.
So we're able to play
ten hours straight.
Please wait!
I'm going to move my cards.
Huh?
What?!
Is that allowed?
I've seen people move cards
together when they only have four left,
but he still has ten cards.
That was a bold move.
If she has two cards left
and I have ten left,
have only autumn leaves as an offering
for the gods watching over me.
there's a higher probability that one
of my cards will be read.
So spring ends...
I know that my heart...
He's hitting...
All of the cards on his side!
He's going to gamble on
his cards being read?
That's reckless.
I'm cheering for the girl!
Attack his side!
I have a six card lead.
and by no fault of mine
It's okay.
When his cards are all grouped together,
it's easier for me to attack.
I'm in good shape!
Long last we meet,
only for me to leave hurriedly,
It's the one-syllable card he just sent!
Desktomu-kun was dead set
on taking that card.
for I could not recognize you,
like the moon hidden behind the clouds
I don't want to lose to Kana-chan,
but I definitely
don't want to lose to myself!
I have a five card lead.
Focus.
Listen carefully.
Desktomu-kun is hitting all of
his cards at the same time,
but I still have a chance.
I just have to reach straight
for the correct card.
Straight and swift...
Play on the edge, the way Chihaya-chan
did against the Queen!
I hear the beating of cloth...
It's too hard without
any preparation first!
But!
Impassionate gods have never seen
the red that is the Tatsuta River
are joined at river's end
Wow! Kana-chan was so
fast on "Impassionate"!
Desktomu-kun was
looking at the "Impassioned"
card on my side.
until the day waves crash over Mount Suenomatsu
covered by the smoky mountain fog
It's just like how Desktomu-kun
the red that is the Tatsuta River
took "While it pains" from me.
I've gotten better at the
cards my friends are good at.
One more card.
No.
The storm will soon carry...
A night spent waiting...
No.
I won't let you win!
Nobody wishes to see...
covered by the smoky mountain fog
Thank you very much.
Huh?
Kana-chan, congratulations.
Kana-chan, your swing is too big!
You aren't using the form I taught you!
Desktomu-kun, you should use
a thrust for that card!
Stay focused!
Kana-chan...
Desktomu-kun...
You came in first.  You came in second.
That's incredible...
Yes!
Oh!
I completely forgot about them!
Retro-kun, Retro-kun.
Give me an update.
Huh?
long as the nights I spend alone
Luck of the draw?
When each player only has one card left
and they play defensively,
the match comes down to
whose card is read first.
Pure luck.
So the final ends in luck of the draw.
I was watching this match to
see if I could learn anything,
but in terms of reflexes,
speed, and memorization,
I'm clearly better than both of them!
There was nothing for me to learn!
But still...
After all they've been through,
the winner will be determined by luck?
They worked so hard to get here...
"The tail"...
Give me "The tail."
Give me "The tail"!
Give it to me!
I'm going to defend this card!
Focus.  Reassess the situation.
I have "Swift waters"...
A one-syllable card on "Swift."
Nishida has "The tail,"
and six dead cards
haven't been read yet.
"The sky may," "The sight
of Mount," "Feel sorrow,"
"For the," "Would this," and "My own sleeves."
"The tail" can't be taken on
the first syllable yet!
The sky may hold the same moon
H-He went on the attack?
He's trying to
take the opponent's card
in a luck of the draw?!
You're supposed to protect
your own card, right?
Yeah...
Why aren't there two of me?
Why didn't I watch this
important match?!
Luck of the draw?
Screw that!
I'm not leaving this match
to luck!
Toda Municipal Spor
Luck of the draw.
Each player only has one card left.
If both players try to
defend their own card,
they each have a 50% chance of winning.
But Taichi is trying to improve
his chances of winning.
By attacking the opponent's side.
When it comes to luck of the draw,
it's normal to defend your own card.
It's the golden rule.
However, Mashima went on the attack.
His card is "Swift," a one-syllable card.
So the question is:
are there any other
"The" cards left besides "The tail."
Think...  Think...
Were they all read?
Are there a few left?
Dammit!
There are sixteen "The" cards in total...
There are definitely other cards left!
He's going to attack again!
which shines over Mount Mikasa
Feel sorrow wash over
me when I see the moon,
though autumn is not mine alone
My own sleeves are like the sands
at the edge of the ebbing tide,
Would this old palace courtyard
and the eaves strewn with weeds
Another dead card.
They're running out of cards...
The intensity when each card is read
is similar to when sumo
wrestlers face off.
Focus, then relax.
You haven't moved an inch,
yet you feel completely drained.
I hate it when you get a bunch
of dead cards in a row.
Just read one of the
two remaining cards!
They aren't relaxing...
Because they care.
are joined at river's end
Because they want to win!
be as dear now,
those were the good old days
The sight of Mount Arima with the bamboo
leaves fading across the plains
Another dead card!
But "The sight of Mount" has been read!
So there was still a "The" card!
But that should be all of them!
It comes down to whether
"Swift" or "The" is read.
A 50/50 battle!
Wait, there's another one left?
Chihaya...
Would you able to hear the
sound that comes before "The"?
The sound that comes before "Swift"?
makes me wonder how I ever
let you fade from my mind
Chihaya...
What would you do?
The tail feathers of...
long as the nights I spend alone
Thank you very much.
Toda Municipal Sports Center
Well, I'll be waiting in the lobby.
Y-Yeah, sure.
Nishida, did you know
which cards were left?
Uh, wasn't Swift the only card left?
Swift and For the.
Huh?  Really?
Isn't that right, Mashima?
I guess you got lucky.
Huh?
There's no reason for me to blame him.
I...
I didn't lose because of luck.
It's my fault for not winning
before it got to that point.
There were plenty of cards I should
have gotten in the first half!
Nishida was able to fend
off my weak attacks.
Nishida did a better job of protecting
his multi-syllable cards.
There was plenty of
room for improvement!
It hurts.
I tried my best...
But that's no excuse.
Sorry.
Oh.  Taichi.  Porky.
I'm glad you're president
of the karuta club.
What's this about?
You're giving me the creeps.
Well, I mean...
compared to Ayase,
who gives people weird nicknames
like Porky and Desktomu,
and she's such an airhead	 that
we let her get away with it.
You're the only one
who calls me Nishida.
I want to keep playing karuta with you.
Chihaya-chan?
Okay, everyone.
Make sure you don't forget anything.
Let's get going.
O-Okay.
I'm starving.
Wanna grab something to eat?
Oe Traditional Clothing
Thank you for driving us home.
Don't mention it.
Anyway, the Mizusawa
Karuta Club did great!
Four of the five members placed,
and three members advanced in rank.
Huh?  Really?
That's right!
The top three finalists in
Class D advance to Class C,
so both Kana-chan and Desk-
Komano-kun get to advance.
Komano-kun?
Everyone worked really hard.
I still can't believe that I won.
You shouldn't say that.
I was really amazed today.
In your match against Desk- Komano-kun,
I could tell that you've
really improved.
You were taking cards without making a sound,
without using too much force.
I wish I could do that.
What?  You've done it
before, Chihaya-chan.
Huh?
The last card you took in
the finals against Hokuo.
I can still remember it.
I can't remember.
What?!
I don't believe it!
It's so hard to be relaxed
while taking a card!
What a waste!
But...
I feel that I was playing
120% in the finals today,
but that was because I was
playing against Desktomu-kun.
Huh?
I wasn't so much worried
about winning as I was focused
on playing my style of karuta,
so I didn't feel any pressure.
Pressure...
Pressure, huh?
Taichi and I are always under pressure.
I want to play a team match.
I want to play as a team again.
Our team is a lot stronger now.
Two Class A players, one Class
B player, two Class C players.
That's right!
Oh.  That means I might run into Pork-
Nishida-kun at the next tournament.
Ayase, you've been acting weird.
Yeah.
Oh!  You must have heard what I said!
Huh?  Er, um...
It's okay.  You're supposed
to be an airhead.
Wouldn't feel right otherwise.
What?!
You've helped me learn
a valuable lesson.
I have no expectations of you.
My team.
That's very important to me.
What?  Why not?!
What's this?
The results for the Saitama
tournament last weekend.
Our Murao-kun was there,
and he placed third in Class A.
The Kanto region is competitive.
You said you wanted some
more time to think it over,
but have you made a decision?
Count me in,
Class B
Winner     Nishida Yusei
Runner-up  Mashima Taichi
for the west Master qualifier.
I'm aiming to be the Western finalist.