Damn you...
Lt. Marito!
All units, spread out!
No go, huh? I thought that if it was
also using lightning to attack,
there would be an opening
while it switched over.
Looks like it isn't going
to be that easy.
In which case, what are
our other options...?
Lt. Marito!
Message from the Deucalion!
HQ has ordered us to pull out.
Pull out? All our forces?
Dales and Orlov Platoons should
have gotten the order by now.
But...
But what?
Retreat! Retreat!
Dales 22!
Where is he?!
Where's the enemy?!
Commander!
That invisible Kataphraktos we failed
to destroy is over there.
Crap.
Clydesdale Leader to Orlov
Leader, can you hear me?
Retreat!
This is... Orlov Leader
Impossible...
I'm the... only...
Lightning and Invisibility...
And one other?
Order them to continue.
Encircle and eliminate.
As you wish, Milord.
Princess Asseylum?
What is this?!
I have done all I can.
The rest is up to her.
I'm sorry, Slaine...
No...
Dales 11!
Clydesdale Leader!
Kaizuka Jr.!
Please pull out! The smoke screen should
obstruct the enemy's vision a little.
Go!
R-Roger!
Plus... We can use this
smoke to attack.
Found him.
To the right! Get clear!
Mustang Leader!
What's going on, Kaizuka,
I thought you were going
to keep Lightning busy!
Sorry.
Its fire suddenly shifted, like it was
concentrating in your direction.
Crap...
We're surrounded?!
Looks that way.
The Deucalion?
Damage report!
We're okay! We're managing
to discharge it!
Set us down and extract
all Kataphraktoi.
Here, ma'am? That's right in
the middle of the enemy!
We're landing!
KCAS, 10 knots.
You're descending too fast,
and there's a strong tail wind!
We're okay! The Aldnoah drive
is handling it!
Antigrav device to maximum!
Vertical speed, 1,200 feet per second!
Get aboard!
Guide in Dales Platoon, hurry!
Open ventral hatch!
Retrieve all Kataphraktoi!
At our 9 o'clock!
Enemy Kataphraktos closing in!
Fire main guns!
Kataphraktoi retrieval complete!
We're leaving!
What's that?
Another enemy Kataphraktos to aft!
Same type as the one we just destroyed!
Reinforcements?
Another at our 2 o'clock! These
aren't reinforcements! They're...
Enemy returns, 12... 16... 24...
Number keeps climbing!
A duplication ability?
All ahead full!
Damn it...
Weather radar, Doppler radar,
both offline!
Crap... Our discharge system must've
been damaged by Invisibility's arrow.
Radio's out, too!
GPS display lost,
2D radar also offline!
No way!
Stay calm! Continue ascent!
Yes, ma'am.
I see. You are amenable to serving
Count Troyard, then?
Yes.
I shall pass word along at once.
There is one other favor
I would ask of you.
What is it?
Might I be granted an audience
with Princess Asseylum?
What? A personal audience
with Her Highness?
Yes. And if possible,
with Count Troyard as well.
That is no small task... However, I will
endeavor to see that you are accommodated.
It will come at a price.
I understand.
I must say, defeat normally causes
a man to lose his way, but not you.
Beg pardon?
Getting into the good graces
of not only Count Troyard,
but Princess Asseylum as well,
would be most beneficial.
However, do not wear your
ambition on your sleeve.
There is a chance that
it might trip you up.
Of course...
Princess Asseylum is an imposter.
I'm going into space.
Prepare a shuttle.
Congratulations on your victory,
Milord Slaine.
This is no cause for celebration,
not when the enemy escaped.
The objective of securing territory
was accomplished.
Is that not success enough?
This is sure to cause more knights
to swear loyalty to you.
We cannot let our guard down. Nothing is less
reliable than a knight's vow of loyalty.
I am well aware, Milord.
And about that request from Count Barouhcruz?
What answer shall I give?
Go ahead.
Milord?
Mazuurek, his name was? If he wants to
see the princess, let him see her.
She is happily fulfilling her role
of extending our power base.
For the time being, at least.
It's no use. This goes
way beyond a quick fix.
You're kidding... Night vision's also out,
so I can't even fly by eye.
What's malfunctioning?
The sensor system?
How did you know, Lt. Kaizuka?
It's easy to tell. It's faint, but
the fuselage is carrying a charge.
With this ship, engine-related malfunctions
are unlikely. In which case...
A-Anyway, help us out!
We're all kinds of screwed!
You should lower our altitude a little.
Low enough to keep us off enemy radar.
But the altimeter and GPWS are both dead,
so I'm scared to take us too low.
I can tell how high we are.
We're at 9,200 now.
You can see all that?
Can you also pick up
VOR stations?
Yes.
Once you have both signals,
tell me. I'll calculate our radial.
All right.
What's our heading?
I was trying to put us on 110.
You're almost there.
Fly at an offset of 3 degrees for 2 minutes.
Then straighten out and maintain heading.
This is bad... Are we caught
in some nasty turbulence?
It looks like it goes on for a while.
Just to be safe, you should...
I've got this.
I can handle this much.
Same goes for earlier.
So I see. From here on out, it looks like
it's experience that's most important.
Once I pick up an LLG,
I'll let you know.
Right!
Thank you.
Actually, we should be
thanking you for earlier.
Lt. Marito was pretty surprised that
you would do something so crazy.
"You're the last person I want to hear
that from." Tell him I said that.
Oh, is that so?
Preparations for the founding
are proceeding smoothly, then?
Yes.
I can hardly wait for
this new kingdom.
And to be able to go
to your homeworld.
It is a world inhabited
by vulgar trash.
It is hardly the restful place
conjured up by the word "home."
Rather, I never had such
a place to begin with.
Neither did I.
There is nowhere that
I might find solace,
neither on Vers
or in royal standing.
Slaine. Anywhere that I may
be together with you,
more than anywhere else,
that is my...
You honor me.
I shall call on you
again later, then.
Slaine, dinner is ready.
My apologies, but there are still pressing
matters that I must attend to.
Please forgive me.
Ina-
Oh, Inko.
What's the matter?
Um, about yesterday. Nina was gushing
about how you helped out.
Oh. Sure.
Uh... Is something wrong?
What would be wrong?
What do you mean, what?
Look, it's nothing, but...
What do you think about the enemy
coordinating their actions?
Maybe they're so hard pressed that they've
been forced to swallow their pride.
Judging from the outcome, I don't
think we have much to fear.
Do you suppose it's connected
to that proclamation, then?
That Orbital Knight named Slaine Troyard
who is behind Princess Asseylum...
The way I hear it,
he one-ups even Kaizuka Jr.
If this opponent really is setting things
into motion with a goal in mind,
it's not a simple scheme that we can
counter with just superior resources.
Enter.
PFC Matsuribi, entering.
Message from HQ, ma'am.
A request for reinforcements?
"Launch all-out attack on
captured territory and retake it."
Throw sheer numbers at them?
That's the long and short of it.
And how have you
been feeling since?
Physically, I feel fine.
My memory, however...
It is still rather hazy.
That is hardly surprising. The very fact that
you regained consciousness was a miracle.
Please...
Please do not force
yourself to remember.
Thank you, Slaine.
I'm afraid that I must take my
leave now. Please get some rest.
I will.
I shall return.
Please look after Her Highness.
Excuse me, Milord Slaine...
I can guess what it is
that you wish to ask.
The proclamation, yes? Taking me as her
husband and founding a country...
That proclamation issued
by Princess Lemrina
was entirely the result of
the weakness in my heart.
"Princess Asseylum
is sure to wake up."
I tried to hold on to that belief but failed,
having given up somewhere deep down.
But then a miracle happened, as if to
reprimand me for being such a fool.
With the situation having
changed so drastically,
what I must think about now is,
how can I make Her Highness happy?
That, and that alone.
But what of Princess Lemrina?
As to what she is looking for...
I can tell.
The same thing as me, I suspect.
A place where she can find solace.
But that is something that
neither of us will ever obtain.
We mustn't tell her everything yet.
But even if she looks down on or derides
me for what I am doing here,
I do not particularly mind.
It's ironic.
I had waited with such hope
for Her Highness to awaken.
But now, what I hope for is that
her memory never returns.
Your newfound resolve to serve
my trusted Count Troyard
fills me with such joy
that I cannot contain it.
Your Highness is too kind.
I am fully prepared to serve
both Your Highness
and Count Troyard with
wholehearted devotion.
I, too, was touched by
Count Mazuurek's drive
as he swore to rise up once again
for the sake of Vers' future
even as he was held
prisoner on Earth.
Begging Your Highness' pardon...
I am given to understand that you once
underwent similar hardships on Earth.
Yes, something similar.
Terrans are all such... vulgar trash.
There was not a single one that
Your Highness grew close to?
Close to? I think not.
I left all interaction with Terrans
to my handmaiden.
I once entertained the notion of
reconciling with those people,
but I now see what a fool I was.
Why is Slaine not here
at a time like this?
Lord Slaine is rushing about, making
preparations for the new operation.
He said as much earlier.
He has been locking himself away in
his castle far too often lately.
Whatever he is doing,
can he not do it here?
I am told that precious
resources are involved.
Then I shall go to him.
Highness, you-
I shall go over
to the Landing Castle.
Your Highness!
Are you unharmed, Highness?
I do apologize.
How long will it be...
Tell me, how long will it be...
I shall see you
to your room, Highness.
Please pardon the delay, Count Mazuurek.
Please follow me to the parlor.
You seem to have finished
checking my credentials.
I deeply apologize.
Not at all, it is I who
committed a grave blunder.
To think that my
ship broke down...
How fortunate for me that
you were in the vicinity.
Oh, I see... Count Troyard
is still at the moonbase.
Yes, Milord. I regret to say
that you have missed him.
Lord Harklight is on
his way here now.
I made my move as soon as I was
certain that he was not here.
Troyard is commuting between here and
the moonbase more than is necessary.
Meaning that the princess'
location must be...
Please wait here.
Are these Terran flowers?
Yes.
This castle has undergone
quite the transformation.
You can tell, Milord?
I was an acquaintance
of its former master.
He detested all things Terran, fearing
that they harbored microorganisms.
There is no such worry here.
Terran flowers are perfectly safe-
Oh, you have been to Earth, then?
N-No, that is only
what I have heard.
I had heard that Princess Asseylum had
an attendant, but I did not expect-
No. I mean... Her Highness
went to Earth alone.
No one is speaking of Earth.
I-I must be going!
You truly have not gone there? Do you
know what happened on Earth?
What about a boy named
Inaho Kaizuka?
How long will it be...
Tell me, sister...
How long will it be before you release
your grip on his feelings?
For me?
Yes, Milady. He said that he
wanted me to give it to you.
To the princess who
knew about Earth.
This is...
Milady!
I...