Where am I?
I see...
You lied? To let Seylum escape?
So that's it...
That was your conclusion
when you guessed at what I wanted.
Milord Slaine.
What is it?
There is a firefight in the hangar.
Their assassination team?
No, Milord.
Princess Asseylum!
I will cover you!
Run!
Eliminate the Terrans!
Enemy attack! Enemy attack!
Perform emergency launch.
It's not safe, Milord.
There is a battle outside.
There is one in here, as well.
Get us away from the battle zone
at maximum combat speed.
Retreat!
Highness...
Inko...
Where is Princess Asseylum?
Still no word from her!
She didn't...
...manage to escape?
No...
Mission complete...
Inko, come pick me up...
I am terribly sorry, Count Klancain.
It was not my wish to get you involved.
Not at all. This is part of my mission.
Mission?
Yes, I came here under orders
from His Majesty himself.
From Grandfather?
Emperor Rayregalia had misgivings regarding
the subjugation of the Earth system
after the death of the previous Count Saazbaum.
And so, he commanded me to both
investigate that and to ensure your safety.
Then I must get in contact with Grandfather!
It is possible to make contact. However...
Count Klancain, transmission from the moonbase.
Put it through.
Lord Klancain, where are you
taking Princess Asseylum?
Ah, Lord Troyard.
I am in the process of evacuating her
to protect her from harm.
The moonbase is a fortified installation.
There is no safer location.
And yet, a battle was in progress there.
Rest assured, the enemies within the base
have already been eliminated.
Please return at once.
No. I will not go back!
I...
...watched birds on Earth.
Highness....
Earth was recovering,
and humanity and nature were coexisting.
It was you who taught me this.
That humanity and nature...
Earth and Vers...
could prosper together!
Yes. You are right.
I did indeed say that.
I have dispatched
the Stygis Squadron to pursue.
Seize the ship at the first opportunity.
I beg you, Slaine.
Please, stop the war.
And make peace with Earth.
Perhaps you are right.
Very well.
Let us discuss the matter.
Slaine...
That sector is dangerous.
Please return immediately.
Count Klancain, please turn back at once.
I am afraid I cannot comply.
I must obey Princess Asseylum's orders.
Stealth to maximum.
Yes, Milord.
The spaceship Hadriacus
has vanished from our screens.
Continue your search.
Yes, Milord.
We needn't worry about
any pursuers for the time being.
Thank you.
But... what am I to do now?
Earth's military is trying to kill me.
And Slaine has the backing
of the Orbital Knights, as well...
I must make contact with the crew
of the Deucalion somehow.
Milady.
There is one knight
who is on your side.
The one who delivered the message
from Inaho Kaizuka.
Count Mazuurek.
Now is the time to demonstrate
my loyalty to Princess Asseylum.
Landing Castle, lift off!
Clydesdale Leader to all units!
Target the enemies off the ship's starboard bow!
Don't let them get close to the Deucalion!
Enemy formation closing in!
3 o'clock! Angle of elevation, 60!
Increase AA cannon fire to starboard!
Message from HQ!
Orders to withdraw, ma'am!
Withdraw?
Looks like they got their results.
Results, ma'am?
The real operation that used us as bait.
Prepare to withdraw!
Order all units back to base!
Mustang 00, 11 closing in.
They're on a return course!
It's Inko and Inaho!
They're cleared to land.
Get them aboard ASAP.
They fled when they saw that they
were no match for us, eh?
What are they playing at?
Count Troyard, the UFE is withdrawing.
Shall we pursue?
No. All units, return to base.
They are to rearm for our next offensive.
Also, summon the Landing Bases.
Assign them to moonbase defense.
Yes, Milord.
Does that belong to my sister?
Princess Lemrina...
Did my sister–
I see. Will I ever see her again?
Yes. Count on it.
I feel sorry.
For her.
And for you.
Inaho...
What is Lt. Kaizuka's condition?
It's nothing life-threatening.
What worries me is that the Analytical Engine
is putting a strain on his cranial nerves.
I told him not to, but look at how far
he expanded its domain...
What does that mean?
He's ceded part of his brain to the machine.
Damn crazy kid...
I must do something to put an end to this war.
I will address all of the Orbital Knights.
With all due respect,
that alone may not suffice.
Why?!
From the very beginning, the Orbital Knights
have desired to fight Earth and occupy it.
Count Troyard has given them a pardon
to do just that in the form of a royal decree.
He has unified them with guarantees
of status in the new kingdom
and Aldnoah activation privileges.
Princess Asseylum, it was his betrothal
to you that clinched it.
If you simply call for an end to hostilities,
you will only lose their trust.
As long as your younger sister is at his side,
pretending to be you.
Ah, Princess Asseylum.
It is good to see you well.
Thank you for being so kind as to assist me.
You give me too much credit, Highness.
I am relieved to be able to repay my debt.
Your debt?
Yes...
...to the Terran boy.
To Inaho Kaizuka.
I've received reports that a part of
your force went to the moonbase.
Would you mind explaining why,
Capt. Magbaredge?
It was an on-the-spot call.
If we lose the princess now,
we lose any chance at peace for good.
Why would Slaine launch a war like this?
Milady...
The Slaine I knew was kind,
adored nature, and loved the Earth.
He was not someone
who would engage in pointless war...
Why would he do this in spite of that?
Milady...
Lord Slaine has not changed at all.
I do not know if his actions are right or wrong.
But he has always cared deeply for you.
He has always wished for
what was best for you,
even if it jeopardized his position,
or even his life.
Always... believing that you
would awaken one day...
Yes... I suppose that is true.
What you say is right, Eddelrittuo.
Are you able to make contact with Vers?
Yes. However, His Majesty is...
This is no time to stop at half measures.
Count Klancain. I require your assistance.
I shall use the Hadriacus' audience chamber.
As you wish, Princess Asseylum.
Attention, all forces.
Operation will commence
as planned at 1500 hours UTC.
Man your battle stations and stand by.
Lt. Marito, you're going into battle?
Yeah. I'd hoped to have
one last drink with you, Doc,
but never got the chance.
That doesn't sound like you.
Well, we're in a low-pressure environment.
I don't want to drink myself sick.
No, not that.
This won't be the last time.
Sure, when I get back!
Is this one of those "final showdown" situations?
Maybe. If we finish 'em off, wouldn't it be?
Whenever somebody dies in action,
I guess that was the final showdown for him.
Sheesh!
Don't jinx us, okay?
He's right! We're all going to
make it back in one piece!
Milord Slaine,
the UFE has begun to mass its forces.
What shall we do about them?
This changes nothing.
Launch all forces and intercept the UFE.
In the meantime,
we will request the assistance
of the Orbital Knights who back us.
Assistance, Milord?
We will launch an all-out offensive
against the entire Earth.
They will know how it feels
to have nowhere to go home to.
Nao!
Yuki...
Are you okay, Nao?
Yeah...
Thank goodness...
You did good today.
Take it easy for a while.
He's going to launch an all-out attack.
Is it almost time for the mission?
Don't even think it!
Stay in bed!
Sorry, Yuki. Something's come up
that I have to do.
Nao!
Please, let me go.
There's that face that says
you're going even if I say not to.
And there's that voice that says I'm going
to be stubborn, so you may as well give in.
Damn it. When you get back,
let's have dinner together.
That's a death flag right there.
Hey! Don't talk like that!
You're coming back alive, you got that?
Sure. You do the same, Yuki.
Hey, Inaho. Feeling better?
Yeah. Is this...?
Yeah, the Sleipnir Final Showdown spec!
Isn't this payload a bit much, though?
Getting close enough to use this
in a space battle would be nuts.
It looks like things are going to get nuts.
Are you serious?!
He's not taking this seriously at all!
Inko...
Why are boys always like this?
Inaho, you're in no condition to go into battle.
Let us handle it from here!
I can't do that.
Why not? Do you think you're some
hotshot ace? That you're special?
I've never thought that about myself.
Darn it, Inaho!
Why are you acting like you don't see it?
If you go out now,
you might not make it back this time!
There won't be another miracle like last time!
I don't want... to go through that again.
I can't be the only one taking it easy.
He's right, Inko.
At a time like this, the kindest thing to do
is say nothing and see him off.
We need to worry about ourselves right now.
Compared to Inaho, our odds of survival
are probably lower, you know?
Get real! I'm an ace, too!
Thanks, Inko. Calm.
Don't worry.
Everyone will make it back.
My left eye says so.
Master switch, on.
Fuel cell batteries, heating.
Voltage, check.
Activating pump.
Accumulator pressure, check.
Force feedback checking program, start.
Ejection seat functional.
IFF confirmed.
Tactical data link, activated.
All systems green.
Mustang 00, ready.
Grandfather...
...it is I.
It is Asseylum.
Do you recognize me?
Ah, Asseylum...
You look well.
I am weary...
How goes the subjugation of Earth?
I have come to you today
to ask a favor regarding that.
I want you to make peace with Earth.
Please give a direct order
to the Orbital Knights to cease fighting.
That, I cannot do...
Grandfather...
Earth can never be forgiven...
Do not let our assault falter...
Bring them under our dominion...
Grandfather... Why do you hate Earth so?
Where is Gillzeria?
What has become of my son?
Conquer the Earth at once!
Father passed away...
During Heaven's Fall.
Filthy Terrans, you killed my son...
And even my granddaughter, Asseylum.
I am right here.
Vers.
That is what the ancients called this world.
What they called Mars.
Grandfather...
Rejoice...
For I have discovered
a Martian superscience...
It is called... Aldnoah.
Magnificent... Mankind will
make even greater strides.
Aldnoah is the technology we dreamed of...
It will make mankind happy.
Yes.
It is a great power.
It must not be misused.
Nurture it with care.
I will.
Who is that there?
Is that you, Asseylum?
How you've grown...
You've grown beautiful.
Become a fine princess.
And lead our people to happiness.
I will.
Klancain. I ask you to put your rank
and all of your connections at my disposal.
Of course, gladly.
Thank you for your loyalty, Count Cruhteo.
Martian bastards!
Glory to Vers!
What the hell is that?!
Slice them up!
My servants, wipe them out!
Open a channel.
I wish to address all Orbital Knights.
Yes, Milord!
An all-out battle has begun between the
moonbase and the United Forces of Earth.
My fellow knights who have gone down
to the Satellite Belt and to the surface.
Launch a concerted attack against the
UFE in your respective locations!
Demonstrate our vast power
to the Terrans once again.
And show the UFE
that resistance is–
Hear me, Orbital Knights of Vers.
Princess Asseylum...
I am Asseylum Vers Allusia,
Princess Royal of the Vers Empire.
The conflict began from a single spark,
and has grown into a massive war.
What's this?
A pirate broadcast?
It's being transmitted on all bands.
A multitude of people had myriad
hopes and dreams that were at odds,
resulting in great tragedy.
This is a sad thing indeed.
This war has brought me great sorrow.
I feel both shame and a deep regret over
our use of power that was not meant for us.
I hereby...
...succeed the previous emperor,
Rayregalia Vers Rayvers,
and name myself Empress of the Vers Empire.
I also take Count Cruhteo,
member of the Orbital Knights' 37 Clans,
to be my husband.
We, the imperial family of the Vers Empire,
wish to make peace with Earth!
Prayer of the Skies