Over here! Over here!
Hurry, you wimp!
Wait...
We'll leave you behind, slowpoke!
I said wait...
I can't fly...
Oh, is that them?
Excuse me. I'm with the Shinjuku Ward Office.
Where have you come from?
What's your name?
Where... Where?
Name? Name, huh?
Now, who was I?
Storage #1
An Another with amnesia, huh?
So you just brought him here?
#12 "Shinjuku Ward Nocturnal Community Relations Division"
Yeah. I wanted your opinions.
That doesn't mean you can just...
Sorry. But...
I can't leave its side. But it's broken.
My home is gone...
He's saying that the stone statue
where he lives was broken.
Apparently, he can't leave it.
Some Anothers need a vessel to call home.
A vessel?
So his vessel was broken,
and he lost his memories, huh?
It's no good. I'm getting nowhere.
Oh, dear...
Let's have a meeting, I guess?
All I can tell you is that it's part
of a very old stone statue.
It's hard to say more with the equipment here.
I'll scrape off a bit and have a guy
I know at a university analyze it.
This is a problem... If only we knew his name.
Okay, I'll go see if I can find clues
about what kind of Another
he is, including his name.
Sakaki-kun, you've got to go
help your sister, right?
Ah, y-yes...
She's finalizing her post-graduation plans...
Huh? Oh, I see.
Oh, man. I'm behind on
updating the database, too.
I'll handle it, then.
I'm the one who brought him here.
Alone?
Yes.
Sounds good.
He'll be fine.
Well, I guess it's all right.
Okay, I'm leaving it to you.
Sure, I got it!
What's wrong?
I'm... hungry...
Oh, of course.
Is there something you want to eat?
What I want to eat... What I want to eat...
That's right. What do you want?
Honey. I want honey.
Honey?
Yes.
Got it.
I brought you honey. How do you eat it?
On bread?
I'll open it for you.
He got it.
Wait!
Are you okay?
Sounds like a rough one.
Well...
Oh, I forgot to mention.
If he is the kind of Another that
needs a vessel, there's a problem.
What is that?
Without his vessel, he has no place to go.
Oh...
Which means we have
to give him a place to stay!
Give him a place?
Good luck!
Oh, fine. I'll take him
home for today, I guess.
Who's this?
Who's he?
Who is he?
What are you doing, bringing somebody
who smells like a bear here?!
Why are you so mad?
He's not even trying to hide his divine
aura. He's spreading it everywhere.
If he stays here, I'll go crazy!
B-But it's my job.
I'm leaving! Forget you!
I'll go, too, then.
Hey!
Sakaki Kyoichi-san.
What do you think about your little
sister's post-graduation plans?
Yes, well, for my part, I think
my older—I mean, younger sister..
should do what makes her happy.
So, um...
I'm sorry, Sensei. He's very nervous.
Kyo-chan.
Sorry.
Calm down, mister.
Here's breakfast.
Don't spill it today, okay?
Let's go find you a place to live today.
What about this?
Hell no! We're not letting someone
like that live with us for this!
Go away!
That's right!
Well, that's a problem...
Leave!
Is it just me, or is that Another doing better?
But he's...
You seem tired, Miyako.
Yeah, I've been walking
around all day for days now,
and it's more exhausting than I thought.
Sorry. I'm getting nowhere myself.
It's fine. I can keep going.
Finding clues is my job. Leave it to me.
Okay, I'm off to keep looking
for a place for him to go...
Done eating?
Let's search around the neighborhood today.
A home, huh?
What kind of place would be good?
Huh? He's gone!
There he is...
Oh, jeez.
I like the atmosphere here. It's good.
A worthy home for me.
Wait! This is...
Hey!
Who said you could come in here?
You should feel honored. I am making
this place my temporary home.
Temporary home? Yeah, right.
You look like a hunting god, which
is probably why you're so reckless!
What did you say?
Wait! Wait!
What, you again, Seimei?
He just lost his vessel and memories,
and is having a rough time.
Not my problem.
Get him out of here, Seimei.
There won't be a next time.
This won't work.
Shrines already have gods in them.
But there is power here.
It's hard to give that up.
Wait. You almost got into a fight, though.
If you find a vessel with no
occupant, that would be one thing.
But failing that, a fight is inevitable.
If you try to go inside,
there'll be big trouble!
What's wrong?
Wake up! Wake up!
Huh?
Good. You're awake.
You have him to thank.
That Another brought you in.
You should take better care of yourself.
Job or not, you're pushing yourself too hard.
Sorry.
No, that's not all.
Arata's life force is leaving
his body and going somewhere.
That's why he collapsed.
Does that have something
to do with him feeling better?
He looks surprised, which means
he didn't steal it deliberately.
Is he the type that drains you
just by being nearby?
No.
He's probably unconsciously taking energy
from any human who focuses on him.
Where are you going?
I'm leaving.
If I'm sucking away your life force,
staying here any longer will mean killing you.
Wait! We haven't found your
name or a home for you!
I have my pride.
I cannot take the life of an innocent man,
let alone one who's done so much for me.
My job's not done yet!
My job is to find clues as to who you are!
I can't have you leaving!
Aren't you scared?
No. We've been together this whole time.
I'm sorry.
Hey, I hate to interrupt your
touching conversation,
but I have no idea what you're saying.
Interpret.
Oh, sorry. Actually...
I see...
Theo, what's your take?
The name's the thing.
If we can find his name, we can
find a new vessel for him.
Then we keep doing what we've been doing.
I'll stay with that Another
and find clues to his name.
You just collapsed!
I'm fine. We found the cause...
And like I said. This is my job.
And I may have lost my own stamina,
but that Another is doing better now.
We're moving forward.
You're a stubborn guy.
Fine.
Hey, Kyoichi!
Let's do what we can.
And we're the ones who
gave him the job, after all.
Oh, fine.
Contact me ASAP if something happens.
Right!
Thank you very much!
What's wrong?
I didn't know there were so many
people, and of so many different kinds.
Well, that's especially true for Shinjuku.
And I've never met a human like you before.
It's a big world.
Did you remember something?
Not really.
But it feels like something is coming back.
Good.
If you notice anything at all, tell me.
It may be a clue.
Then first, I request an offering.
I didn't get any food after
the fuss back there. I'm hungry.
You must be hungry as well, right?
Yes. I'll get something
ready when we get home.
I just got some good honey there.
It's imported, and supposedly delicious.
I can't wait!
Here you go.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Here you go.
Thank you!
I may know this honey.
This beauty, like jewels...
A sparkle like dew on leaves
changing color in fall...
A sweet scent that tickles the heart...
I remember this!
I'm sure of it.
Men made an offering of this honey to me.
They would make offerings to me,
praying for peace for their cattle and
children, and for fertile harvests...
This honey is from my homeland!
Ukraine?
Here we go!
That Another is Volos!
A god of the forests and the hunt,
worshiped in the Slavic myths
that center around Ukraine.
He also protects cattle in the form of a bear.
That Another seemed to not want to kill you.
That narrowed it down a lot.
Well?
We found it.
Oh, dear. I guess we won't need this, then.
What's that?
Oh...
The Mental World of Ancient Ukraine
Is this...
I thought it'd be a clue.
But if you know who he is,
then you don't need it now, huh?
It's in Ueno. Wanna go now?
Th-This is it!
This is my new vessel! My new body!
What will happen to this statue after this?
Um...
It doesn't belong to this museum,
so it'll be sent back to its old museum,
or travel the world in the same
way that it was brought here.
The world, huh?
Places I don't know, that I've never been...
I've seen many things
over these past few days.
If I can see more, then I am very lucky.
The gods need human emotions to survive.
Faith, fear, gratitude, wishes, and prayers.
But I was forgotten, and my power was lost.
Without you, I would've done
nothing but wait for death.
But you turned your heart
to me, and saved me.
It's fine, Volos-san. That's my job.
A wonderful job, one you can be proud of.
Thank you for everything!
I still never got your name.
Tell me.
Arata.
Miyako Arata.
A good name.
I am Volos, God of the Rus!
I, my name, and my power
have returned here!
Thank you, Miyako Arata!
Arata!
I'm back!
Yuki!
You're back, huh?
Welcome back.
The bear guy finally left, huh?
You're back too, huh?
Huh? You seem kind of weak.
It's because you tried to help a guy like that.
You okay, Arata?
I'm fine.
This is my job.
Hey, want to go have some fun?
I found some pretty cherry blossoms.
I'm going back to the ward office.
I'll be waiting at home, then!
Let's go!
No way!
Hey, if we can't go see cherry
blossoms, how about fishing?
Some other time.
You're no fun.
Fine, then. I'll go with you to work.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Yokai, angels, devils...
Most of the occult
creatures you see in fiction.
We have a name for all these non-human
creatures we use in our work.
"Anothers."
Maintaining relations with the Anothers,
and if they get into any problems
with civilians, taking care of it.
That's the job of the Nocturnal
Community Relations Division,
and our job at the Shinjuku Ward Office.
Good morning!