My brother, my brother...
My beloved brother.
My brother.
I've come... I've come...
I've come to see you!
Anybody home?
Sakura Hall
Hey, Shiina! Your underwear!
What?!
U-Um...
Sheesh!
You need to realize the
importance of underwear already!
God's Little Prank
They're not just scraps of—
You're...
You're... you're...
You're with a naked girl?!
#07 Her Homesickness
We are...
Earthlings...
Testing... testing...
Hey, Mom. It's me.
Image by Shiina Mashiro
It's me.
D-Dad?!
Perfect timing. There's
something I wanted to tell you.
Wh-What's that?
Image by Kamiigusa Misaki
I'll never let you have my daughter!
We are...
Earthlings...
Image
Mother
Here's a question for you. Who am I?
Option 1: Yang Guifei.
Option 2: Cleopatra.
Option 3...
Hello, Mom?
We are Earthlings...
Sorata, what's wrong? You sound tired.
Of course I'm tired!
At least answer the phone
like a normal person!
I have enough on my plate as it is...
Why?
It's Yuko. She's turned up here.
Oh yeah, about that...
Mother! Mother!
Why won't my dear brother come home...
even though it's summer break?
Because he's living with a girl
in Tokyo in secret to you...
and he's doing lots of
unmentionable things with her!
Oh, no!
After I told her that,
she insisted on going to see you.
So, this was your doing...
Image by Aoyama Nanami
Well, that's how it is,
so take care of Yuko for a while!
What are you saying?!
Image by Akasaka Ryunosuke
Oh, that reminds me:
She wanted to talk to you
about her future plans,
so ask her about them.
Did she just gloss over
the most important part?
Starting Station: Harajuku -> Shinjuku, Yoyogi, Shibuya
Fare Quota: 160 Yen
I don't have time to babysit...
"Let's Make a Game!" Pitch
Train Train (Temp): Original Puzzle Game
Downloadable Mobile Phone Content
The results haven't been announced yet...
Sorata.
Who is this woman?
She's my little sister, Yuko!
Who's she, Bro?
Don't you act like this is the
scene of an affair, too!
Who are you to Sorata?
Shiina's just a classmate...
Didn't I just say that she's my sister?!
Wh-Who are you?!
What's your relationship with my brother?!
Why don't you just listen to what I'm saying?!
Sorata is my owner.
Sit.
Why would you say that?!
Master.
My beloved.
Shiina! You're out of control today!
Let's hit the brakes, shall we?!
The brakes! The brakes, Kamiigusa-san!
Let's accelerate instead!
No, no, no! Hit the brakes!
I beg you!
I'm home.
Hey, Kanda-kun, they gave me
two free ice creams at work.
If you want, we could...
K-Kanda-kun has a lolita complex.
No, I don't!
That's my sister! My real sister, Yuko!
Oh, she's just your sister.
I knew I could count on you.
I'm glad you listen to me...
Nice to meet you! I'm...
What are we going to do, Kumakichi?!
A second woman has appeared!
Kanda-kun has been helping me out a lot.
Helping you with what?!
What? Uh, well...
Have you been doing...
things like that to her?!
Y-You idiot. She just said that to be polite!
Suspicious...
It's not suspicious!
I can't leave you in this "Oh! There's
Women Everywhere" harem dorm!
Come back home to Fukuoka with me!
There are guys here, too!
Hey, Akasaka.
I know you can hear us through the wall.
Help me out.
"Shut up!"
...he says. If you don't keep quiet,
I'll sew a zipper on your mouth.
Parentheses, heart, end parentheses.
From: Maid-chan.
A third woman!
Wait!
I can't wait another second!
Calm down!
Come home with me right now!
Why has our hallway turned into a river?!
Sorata.
The bath just broke.
What?!
It finally stopped.
Come on, let's go home.
Listen, I'm not living
here just for the hell of it.
I'm living in a dorm because
there's something I need to do.
You're lying.
When we lived near here,
you said you wanted to go to Suimei High...
because it was the
closest school to our house.
I-I can't have you underestimating me, Sis.
There really is something...
I have to do over summer vacation.
Do what exactly?!
So, you really are doing those unmentionable
things with Mashiro-san and Nanami-san...
Like hell I am!
Sorata.
Shiina? What's wrong?
It's ready.
What? Congratulations?
Wh-What the heck did you do?!
Nothing! I didn't do anything!
I'm innocent!
Dinner's ready.
Say that first!
Thanks for the food.
Huh?
Misaki-senpai isn't here.
I bet right now she's...
... out making trouble for someone somewhere.
Ralph the Ripper's heading
towards the suburbs!
The target is a white sports car!
Found him! Boom!
He counters with eye beams! Blammo!
That must be it.
By the way, Yuko-chan,
what year are you in?
My third year.
I see.
You're pretty tall for a third year.
She is a third year, but she meant
her third year of middle school.
What?!
O-Oh, I see. I should've known.
Yes!
What should I do, Bro?
Everyone's saying I'm really mature.
How can you be happy about the
route this conversation has taken?
You're too optimistic,
or too positive... or something.
That's what's so great about me.
Sure, sure.
Great about... Great about...
Great about me.
Sora—
Mashiro, look at you.
You've got food on your face.
You've got some on yours, too.
What?!
Huh? What?
Aoyama-sama, you're surprisingly
assertive, aren't you?
N-No, I'm not!
That was a coincidence!
Getting worked up like that
just makes you more suspicious.
No! I'm really not!
It's fine.
No, it's not!
I'm telling you, I'm really not like that!
Well, I'm going to take a bath and
head over to Kana-san's place.
Senpai!
The bath is actually, well...
I'm really not... That was just...
It's nice to do this
every once in a while.
Yeah.
Oh, wow! Mashiro-san,
what's up with your body?!
Your skin's so white and smooth.
I thought you were flatter than this...
Your boobs are surprisingly large,
and your waistline's a knockout!
It sure is...
I can't believe you're a human like me!
You're a fairy!
Yuko, you're a dwarf.
Dwarf
Ow!
H-Hey, Yuko-chan?! Stop it! Stop!
Mashiro-san's making fun of me.
Nanami-san's are bigger.
She's a formidable opponent.
Nanami, you're soft.
Mashiro, why are you touching me, too?!
I see. So, Aoyama-san's soft, is she?
Sorata, whose naked body
are you visualizing?
What?! N-Nobody's!
K-Kanda-kun, don't fantasize about us!
What a waste.
In this country, the law recognizes
our right to free thought.
It doesn't give you the right to fantasize!
Boys are always so—
Huh? Wh-What?
Nanami-san, you seduced my
brother with that body.
I-I didn't do anything of the sort!
Anyway, he has someone
more amazing closer to him...
Kaboom!
Nanami-san, you're plenty big!
Why am I the only dwarf?
It's okay, Yuko-chan.
I'm sure they'll get bigger
once you start high school.
Big and bouncy, just like Aoyama-san's.
Mitaka-senpai!
You're right. My battle is just beginning!
Just you wait, Bro.
I'll save you from the clutches of evil!
The Clutches of Evil
If that's a TV show, it should be canceled.
It's tough being popular.
Student Driver
You're late, Nancy!
Nanba Shiori
Who are you calling Nancy?!
No announcement of the
screening results yet...
I can't relax!
Um, don't you think...
that the population density of my
room's been awfully high lately?
This is an emergency report from Nancy.
Carlos, the wanted bank robber,
has been spotted on Route 301.
Gotcha!
Be the way, Yuko,
didn't you want to talk
to me about your future?
If you don't hurry,
you'll run out of time.
That was just an excuse to come here.
I actually just came to impose on you.
Take a look at the available jobs!
If you don't need anything
here, go back to Fukuoka.
Don't you have anything to
do besides playing games...
and reading manga day after day?
Then, take me out somewhere!
Let's go on a date!
A date...
A date?
What?
Date.
Date?
Date!
What's going on here?
It's so big!
So it is...
You should be more excited, Bro!
Should I?
How did it end up like this?
N-No, I just...
I don't have work today, and I didn't
get to go anywhere last year...
What about you, Shiina?
Don't you need to work on your manga?
Ayano said I should experience
lots of things this summer.
Experience?!
The ABCs of love?!
No, plans A, B, and C.
That was your "annihilate" plan!
A!
B!
C!
W-Well, I slept in the same
bed as my brother last night!
Hold it! You've got the wrong idea here...
So did I.
What?
I've slept in Sorata's bed.
Go, go, Yuko!
Don't lose, Yuko!
What are we supposed to do now?!
It's a disaster.
You're the one who complicated things!
Don't lose, Yuko!
I only told the truth.
Yeah, choosing the exact words...
that would cause the most confusion!
I'm starting to feel like I don't
have enough HP to survive today...
What's wrong, Aoyama?
Huh? Oh, nothing.
I was just thinking that you
always seem to enjoy yourself...
when you're talking to
Mashiro and Yuko-chan...
What's so fun about this, exactly?
Maybe I should push you around, too.
What?
N-Never mind!
Why did she get mad at me?
Don't lose, Yuko!
Shiina, I can't walk like this.
Back off a little.
Sorata, you'll get lost.
If anyone's gonna get lost,
it's gonna be you!
If Yuko backs off, I'll consider it.
You heard her, Yuko.
If Mashiro-san backs off,
I'll think about it.
W-We don't want to get separated.
My contract's been terminated
on my phone, so... well...
Nakamise
Okay, just like that!
Fortunes: 100 Yen
What will I get? What will I get?
Bad Luck
Very Good Luck
I wish that Yuko will become smarter.
And bigger.
I wish that my pitch will make
it through the screening process.
I wish my brother would spoil me.
I wish my sister would stop being so stupid.
I want to eat baumkuchen.
I wish that Kanda-kun's pitch gets approved.
And also...
N-Never mind!
With milk tea on the side.
I'm exhausted...
But maybe it was good to get
out of the house for a bit.
If you'd stayed in your room,
you would've been thinking
about the mail all day.
Did you wish you'd become a voice actor?
I-I guess I did.
Th-That was just an accident or...
What are we going to do?
I'm really sorry!
Mashiro and Yuko-chan are missing!
What?
Candy Apples
What am I going to do?
I got separated from my brother!
Sorata's lost.
You want one? That'll be 300 yen.
We're lost strategy-wise, too!
Um, can I have some money for that?
Did you find them?
No...
Did Mashiro answer her phone?
Oh, about that...
What am I going to do?
I didn't bring my phone,
and you're not any help at all, Mashiro-san.
I bet I'll never see my brother again.
It's okay.
What?
Sorata will find us.
Where does that confidence come from?
Because Sorata...
My brother...
...is on Mashiro Duty.
That doesn't make any sense!
You're the only one who doesn't understand.
Look.
Bro!
I'm here!
Yuko!
Wh-Who are you?!
He seems to want money.
It's because you're eating that!
After all the fuss she made,
this is how she ends up...
But we had a lot of fun.
It must have been a nice break for
Yuko-chan before her entrance exams.
I hope she passes.
Yeah.
Huh? Where is Yuko applying, anyway?
I don't know.
Thanks for everything.
See you again, Yuko-chan.
Bye.
I know what I want to do now, Bro!
Really? What's that?
I'm going to apply to Suimei High!
What?!
If I get into Suimei High, I can be with you.
Then, you can look after me
like you look after Mashiro-san, right?
It'll be the birth of Yuko Duty!
Shiina-san, did you give Yuko ideas?
I gave her my everything.
That sounds impressive!
It's not that impressive.
Yuko-chan, good luck on your exams.
Why are you acting so casual about this?!
Nanami-san, I won't let
you have my brother!
What?
I know!
Mashiro-san needs my brother because
she can't take care of herself.
But for a responsible girl like you,
Nanami-san, my brother is special—
Th-That's not really what I...
Well, anyway, let's go home.
HQ Driving School: Looking For Students
You know, I haven't seen
Misaki-senpai recently.
We did it, Nancy!
Please... stop...
A swimsuit episode?
It'll be worth seeing how many frames...
#08 Set Off a Huge Firework
are dedicated to bouncing breasts.
Sorata-sama, are you prepared
for monumental nosebleeds?