I just hope he'll get used to the stables.
He'll be fine. He's a calm one.
That's good, because one
wild horse is enough to handle.
Sawa!
Are you all right?!
Excuse me, but can you
please not butt in?
You did the same thing during our audition.
But it was fun, wasn't it?
We're pros.
If anything, you should be thanking us.
You're pros?
We're in a band.
Though, we're missing a member.
Hey, girl!
We even have a hit song.
But I guess you youngins haven't
heard of the Condor Queens.
We were even on a commercial once.
Condor Queens?
And now a tune to make men merry.
Co-Co-Co-Condor! Co-Co-Co-Condor!
Will you cut that out?
You're embarrassing.
These days, we're mostly touring the
country playing some modest live shows.
I'd say music isn't so much a job anymore,
but a way of life.
The Condor Queens?
This is your grandpappy's theme song!
Oh, no!
Episode 4
Getting Angry and Dancing
Vocal Training
Wakana?
Taxi!
Follow that bike!
Wakana, what's going on?
Stalker! Stalker!
I've been your fan since I was a kid!
That gives me an idea!
Would you play at the World Music Festival?
Wouldn't they be just perfect?
They sure would!
So does that mean you
withdraw your audition?
Are you okay with that, Konatsu?
Of course! We can't beat them!
That'd be great, if you'd take us...
We try to not be picky about our venues.
We did it!
We didn't do a thing.
Why don't you put them up
at your place until the event?
You want me to do what?
It's not like you're short on rooms.
Sawa lives in a temple.
Hold it.
We're no Buddhas;
we've got no business
staying at a temple.
We've got enough cash,
and our own trusty abode.
Unless your temple has
a nice, big parking lot?
Parking lot?
You could've just told me from
the start that you knew my mother.
Sorry! I just couldn't contain myself!
What a wonderful day!
Hey!
What're you doing down there?
Is there choir practice today?
It's been cancelled.
Really?
They're going to Okita's house
with some band, instead.
What a great spot.
It's been a long time since
we could kick back like this.
If you ask me, Japan's too cramped.
Please let me know if you need anything.
Thank you, you're too kind.
Would you like some, too?
I'd love some!
Thank you, but I'm fine.
Enjoy your stay.
Sawa, wait!
Can I sleep over?
I want to have enough
time to talk to them.
Then why don't you sleep in their camper?
Huh?
It was a joke.
A joke?
Amigo!
I found her!
I found Mahiru's daughter!
Will you look at that.
Come, sit down, sit down.
Um, I can't stay long.
We met Mahiru back when we were on tour.
We wrote a song together.
"Amigo, Amigo."
Yup. That was
our one-hit wonder.
Saying we wrote that
song isn't quite right;
it's more like it was born.
Mahiru never mentioned it?
No, she...
I see.
Well, we considered her a
dear friend and benefactor...
You might even say we
were in love with her.
But we're not your daddy!
Hey!
No dirty jokes around the girl!
You look a lot like she did back then.
But she was more cheerful.
And her hair was a touch longer.
Feels like only yesterday...
I still can't believe
that Mahiru's gone.
Feel like galloping, Sabure?
Careful now.
I don't want my Poem gettin' spooked.
Poem?
Watch out, Poem, he'll eat you.
He will not!
Okay, let's go.
Sawa!
I wanted to talk to you
about today's practice.
You don't have to work,
so we're having it at school, right?
Yeah, but I was wondering if
it's okay if I skip it.
Why?
The guys said they're going to do
a test run at the beach house stage.
I figured it might be good
to watch the pros at work.
Oh! Why don't we all
skip, and check it out?
Go by yourself.
We haven't made any progress!
Is this a game to you?
No matter who I'm riding with,
or how much I respect them,
when we ride together,
I want to be the best!
You need to sing.
If all you want is to be in a fan club,
then I'm quitting the choir club!
You jerk! Idiot!
Wakana?
Yes?
Is that falsetto?
No, I don't think so...
Hmm. I see.
All right, let's get started!
We should leave soon.
A pro should never be late.
Umm, I...
Would you like us to give
you our slot on stage?
You're a senior, right?
You can keep on singing
long after graduation,
but it won't be the same.
You've got a song you can only sing
with the people and feelings you've got now.
Would you like our spot?
Yes.
You can't have it.
You think graduation's a big deal?
We're about to graduate from life!
We're not old enough to
give up the things we love.
You need to go back to
your own stage, amigo.
Shiho-san!
You're just in time!
Here are your clothes.
Sawa's not home, though.
I didn't come for her.
I want to ask you a question.
What's that?
Is there a stage left
that we could sing on?!
Was that falsetto?
Falsetto?
I mean this.
Where's Miyamoto?
Without her, all we can do are sit-ups.
I'm sure she's on her way.
That reminds me.
Sakai's in this club, right?
And she used to be
in the music school?
Vocal Training
You know, I've never actually heard her sing.
She's taking a supplementary class.
Should I invite her next time?
Yeah.
Hey, that's pretty good!
Can I see that?
Me, too!
It might be...
...too late?
I think so.
Hang on.
There's one place that hasn't
found a performer yet.
Where are they?
Right here.
I don't know if they'll use
you, but it's worth a shot.
I'm going to try!
Good luck!
Jeez, your family!
Excuse me!
Have you chosen a performer
for the World Music Festival?
Yes, just now.
She said she knew someone who might be
interested, and would introduce us.
I think she might still be around.
Friends
Sakai Wakana
Oh, there she is.
Sakai-san!
Thanks!
No problem. I'm just glad you found a stage.
Yeah. I haven't ran that hard in ages.
So, have you found an answer?
If only I was a virtuoso...
I bet by now I'd...
What?
I can't do it. I can't sing alone.
What are you talking about?
When you said you quit
music, did you mean...
I'm no virtuoso, either.
Oh, yeah.
Miyamoto-san, do you know
anything about this song?
You can call me Konatsu.
Oh, this? I'm not all that familiar with it.
Okay.
It's really pretty, though.
See you later.
Yeah.
Sakai-san, thanks!
You can call me Wakana.
Miyamoto never showed.
I want you guys to listen to the
CD and practice your parts.
We need to maximize our time.
Especially you, Tanaka!
I know!
I don't want a consolation prize,
so let's win the popularity vote
and sing on the main stage!
Fight!
Heave ho!
Let's give our best!
Not one match...
Lasso?
Let's give our best...
Together, guys!
The waves break on the
shore. The waves retreat.
My thoughts ride...
...the surf. In the distance, I see a white...
...beach. Under the...
...hot sun, aloha...
Wakana!
You came.
Konatsu, is everything okay?
The beach is far from us,
so nobody's come.
At least there's the consolation prize.
Ouch!
Everyone's really into their show.
Not surprising.
This is the song that your
mom helped compose, right?
Come on in.
Shouldn't you be on stage?
Nobody's there.
You don't wait for an audience to sing!
You sing to make the audience come!
We know that.
Want us to go out with
you for an encore?
No, thank you.
That stage is ours, even if it's a small one.
Are you sure?
We have to do this on our own.
Let's go back to our stage!
Yeah!
Bye.
Thank you.
Wakana.
I heard that you gave up music.
I did.
Whether healthy or sick...
Whether happy or sad,
I want to write songs that always fit.
At the time, we didn't understand what she meant,
and laughed it off as some crazy dream...
But maybe she was talking about you.
You can't give up music.
It's not something you do or don't do.
Music is a constant companion.
Even your heartbeat is music.
That's what your mother
told us, long ago.
You can't quit.
Encore!
That's a letter we got from your
mother when you were born.
I'd like you to have it.
We should talk sometime.
There really is nobody here.
Not true. We've got three people.
You better sing good.
That kid is so not cute.
He's just like you.
The waves break on the shore. The waves retreat.
My thoughts ride the surf.
In the distance, I see a white beach.
Under the hot sun,
aloha...
Thank you so much!
Can I have your picture, too?
No way. Nothin's gonna steal my soul.
Hey!
So, where's Wakana?
Congratulations On Your Win!
Shirohamazaka High's Tanaka Taichi!
Huh? I got cake for you, too.
Giving up is not an option!
Horses for me.
What's with that look?
Episode 5
Throwing Away and Holding On
I've been thinking about
getting rid of the piano in my room.