You're alive, Ichika.
I knew the whole time.
Are you okay?
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm not hurt.
Why are you here?
Did you come to see me—
I was looking for you!
Do you know how worried we
were after you went missing?
Missing?
How am I...?
You sent out a distress signal, didn't you?
Huh?
Th-That was an accident.
Then why was the signal lost
from the unmanned pod...
...that went to rescue you?
S-Some things kind of happened...
I...!
Uh, that was me.
I thought Senpai... I mean,
Ichika-san, was in danger...
So I...
Who are you?
I'll introduce him to you.
This is Kaito Kirishima-kun.
He's my, um...
Boyfriend... kinda...
N-Nice to meet you.
Wh-Wha...
What were you thinking, Ichika?!
U-Um...
Not only are you interacting
with the locals,
but now you've got a
boyfriend?! What the hell?!
You know Federation law, right?
That hurts...
You know what it says, right?
You're interacting with Kaito-kun, too...
I came here to save you!
This was an emergency!
I had an emergency, too...
Do you realize how worried
your family has been?!
You don't get what's going on, do you?!
It hurts...
Remon-senpai, you're late.
I was thinking too much about
how the story should continue.
Where are Ichika and Kirishima-kun?
They haven't come yet.
I wonder if they got the time wrong.
Tanigawa-san, sorry to ask,
but could you go take a look?
I'll introduce myself properly this time.
I'm Emika Takatsuki, Ichika's older sister.
I'm Kaito Kirishima.
Kirishima-kun, right?
Thank you for taking Ichika in
after she'd been in an accident.
I thank you on behalf of our family.
Oh, it was nothing.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
I'll be taking Ichika back myself.
Huh?!
Onee-chan!
A distress call was received
from a remote planet...
And contact was lost with the
unmanned pod that went to save you.
Ichika, they haven't just declared you a
crash victim, they've labeled you missing.
Do you know how worried we
were when we heard that?
All our relatives are talking about it.
What?
So I took a paid vacation,
rented the latest ship,
and came out here to
do my best to find you.
And what do I find?
I was so worried, and you're just living
here without a care in the world,
and you even have a boyfriend.
I-I'm sorry.
I didn't think people would make
such a big deal about it...
U-Um, Onee-san!
I think I might like the sound of that.
It's not bad to have a younger guy
call you that once in a while.
Now that you know Ichika-san is safe,
there shouldn't be a
problem anymore, right?
That's true!
They've already formed a search party.
Huh?
But if you report back that I'm safe...
You were designated missing on a planet
that's a grade F on the industrial scale,
where interaction with
the locals is forbidden.
From the Federation's point of view,
I'm sure they'd want to verify the
situation as quickly as possible.
If they found you and found
out what you've been doing,
you would be arrested and
taken into custody on the spot.
You would be prosecuted in
accordance with Federation law.
But...
Is there anything we can do to stop that?
That's why I'm here.
Ichika, you'll be coming back with
me before things get out of hand.
No way...
I don't want to.
I'm not going to leave Kaito-kun.
I never will.
If you stay here, you'll cause problems for
Kirishima-kun and the rest of the planet.
I haven't done anything wrong.
That's not the problem here.
Why can't you understand?!
Senpai, calm down.
Let's listen to what your sister has to say,
and then we'll figure out what—
There's only one choice.
Ichika, you already understand
the situation, right?
Rinon!
Senpai!
Senpai...
I'm sorry, Kirishima-kun.
You had to see something that
wasn't exactly pleasant.
It's okay...
Takatsuki... senpai...
Tani...
...gawa-san.
What are you doing?
We're supposed to be filming... already...
Why aren't you wearing any shoes?
Senpai?
Uh...
Does Sen— I mean,
Ichika-san...
Must she return home?
She must.
Could she go back home and
then come back here again?
Given the situation, I imagine
that would be difficult.
Then...
Then could you take me
into space with you?!
I'll do anything!
My sister's not very
elegant and she's stubborn.
Are you sure about that?
Yes!
Let's... get a change of scenery, shall we?
Y-You're going back?
They're already looking for me.
And I couldn't get away
from them if I tried.
I don't think they'd listen
to what I had to say, either.
So you can't do anything about it?
No.
And if I try to stay here, things
are going to get really bad.
So I have to...
So you're just going to leave?
You're going to leave Kaito-kun
behind and go back to space?
But I can't do anything about—
So you're going to give up on
being with the guy you like?!
So you dated Kaito-kun knowing
that you'd just give up,
knowing that your feelings for
him weren't really that strong.
Do you know...
Do you know how I've felt?
Tanigawa-san...
Just do whatever you want!
Just give up already, leave him,
and go back to space or whatever!
This planet is nice...
There's so much nature left.
My planet doesn't look a thing like it,
but it still feels like I've been here before.
Ichika-san said the same thing.
She said that there's an image
of a place in her head,
and it's somewhere on this planet.
That's why she came to this planet.
That image is inside me, too.
That image is probably...
...something our ancestors put
into themselves as genetic data.
And now we've inherited that.
Why would they do that?
Who knows?
Maybe that's where they buried a
bunch of treasure or something?
I didn't really care that much about it,
but it may have been on
Ichika's mind this whole time.
When I looked for Ichika, I
scanned this whole planet,
but there was no place here
like the one I have in my head.
I—
I know you said you want
to go into space with us,
but there's no way I can
take someone from a...
...planet that's a grade F on the
industrial scale into space.
This planet would first have to develop
the technology for interstellar flight,
make contact with us,
join the Galactic Federation,
and then what you want could happen.
For that to happen, this
planet would probably require...
...hundreds of your years of development.
Is there... Is there another way?
Unless Federation law was amended
somehow, it's just not possible.
Thank you, Kirishima-kun.
You care about Ichika so much.
But...
I'm going to take Ichika back home.
It's for her own good.
I never thought she'd get a boyfriend.
I only came here to get her.
I never thought I'd have to do this instead.
You're Ichika Takatsuki-san's
sister, correct?
Who's there?!
Kanna hasn't come back yet.
Remon-senpai went somewhere, too.
And what are Kai and Ichika-senpai doing?
I hope he's not fooling around while
we're supposed to be filming.
Might be kind of lucky for me, though.
You think so?
Yep.
What are you talking about?
Kanna.
Wh-Where are Kai and Ichika-senpai?
I don't know.
What's wrong, Kanna?
Takatsuki-senpai said she's
going back to space.
Someone's come to take her back.
What?
She said some stuff's going on.
She has no choice.
So we're not making the movie anymore.
There's no point in being here
any longer, so let's go home!
W-Wait a second, Kanna.
What?
Does Takatsuki-senpai really
want to go back to space?
I don't...
What about Kai?!
Are you okay with this?
She's going to go and leave Kai behind.
Are you okay with all of this?
Are you really okay with all of this?!
Of...
Of course not!
I was talking to your sister
until just a little while ago.
I asked her to take me into space
with you, but she said no.
I'm not going to give up...
on finding a way to stay with you.
Tanigawa-san got mad at me.
Huh? Why?
Senpai, you aren't...
Rinon, jump me...
Se—
Senpai!
I don't think so.
Senpai, aren't you giving
up a little too quickly?
Tetsuro...
Kitahara-san...
We heard what was going
on, so we came here.
We couldn't just let you go like that.
I-It'd be a problem for us.
I mean, if you left, we wouldn't be
able to film the movie anymore.
Tanigawa-san...
I want you to stay here.
Me, too.
B-But...
Kirishima-kun's here.
But...
Say how you really feel!
What do you really want?!
I don't want to go...
I don't want to return home...
I don't want to leave him...
I love Kaito-kun.
I love you, too!
I want to stay with you!
I don't care if all of
outer space is against me!
Kaito-kun...
Then that's what you should do!
Thank you...
So what are you going to do?
Are you going to run?
Are you going to hide somewhere?
Th-That's...
Seems like you have a
problem on your hands.
Remon?
I have some good news for you.
Episode 11 Don't go, Senpai.
Senpai can stay here on Earth?!
That's right.
There's a low probability this
will actually work, however.
But it's not zero.
What do we have to do?
Ichika, you were searching for the
image you had in your head, right?
Yes...
Then that means there's a possibility...
...that aliens have come to
Earth before, correct?
B-But that's just something
I saw in my head...
Reference Room
Senpai's sister said that she also has
an identical image in her head,
but she also said there wasn't
any place like that on Earth.
Leaving behind an image like that
is a rather complex piece of work.
They may have used some method
to make it impossible to find...
...with the technology that
Ichika and her sister possess.
Then how can we find it?
We can try comparing the
data you've gathered...
...with maps of the Earth.
I get it.
If there's a place on the
map that's not in her data,
then that means...
Remon, how did you figure that out?
Someone gave me some advice.
You mean...
Onee-chan...
I was being so selfish, but you still...
Thank your friend, Ichika.
There's not much time. Get to work.
Right!
If we can find that location,
and find something that proves Earthlings
and aliens have come in contact before...
Then Earth will lose its status
as an F on the industrial scale.
If we can find that before
the search party arrives...
Senpai, we only have to look
at areas in Japan, right?
Yeah, judging by the plants and
surroundings in the image I have,
I think we can limit our
search to just Shinshu.
We're going to find it!
Yeah!
Something's coming... from the right...
You should sleep a little bit, too, Kai.
But we don't know when
they'll come for Senpai.
Then I'll tell you something
to help you stay awake.
Something?
I told Kanna I liked her the other day.
No way!
You— What?!
I knew how she'd respond, though.
That's why you told me about Tanigawa...
I was thinking too much about myself.
So I don't want you to
end up the same way.
Tetsuro...
Also, Mio told me she liked
me when we went to Okinawa.
Seriously?
Seriously.
After I got into high school, I
hadn't really been doing anything,
so I was thinking I wanted
to at least do something,
and I guess a lot of things
happened, after all.
Yeah, especially after
Senpai came, right?
This summer's unbelievable.
Yeah, I mean, we're talking about...
...outer space and everything.
I can't really do anything else,
but I hope you find it, Ichika.
The place you're looking for,
and your future...
When did I...
You can sleep a little bit longer.
We're already up.
You wanna sleep in my lap?
No, I...
Why are you guys acting so lovey-dovey?
I-I wasn't trying to...
Yeah, I wasn't...
What?!
I-I found it!
This place hasn't been checked!
All right!
Senpai.
Right.
Ichika, can you hear me?
Onee-chan?
The search party is close to the planet.
You need to hurry—
Onee-chan!
Senpai!
Rinon, hurry up and jump
us to that location!
Rinon?
What's wrong?!
What?
There's a linkage anti-field?
Deployed over the entire planet?
We can't teleport?
What should we do?
It'll take three hours to get there by train.
There's someone coming after her, right?
We have to hurry.
What's going on?
There's no one driving?
It's me.
Remon-senpai?!
I thought this might happen,
so I'm glad I got a car ready.
Senpai, you have a license?
Yes, most of them.
Most of them?
Who's going to be coming after you?
I wonder what else she has...
Probably another rescue pod like before.
Ichika, they're going to come after you by
scanning for your biological data, right?
Yeah, but why do you know that?
Put this on.
It'll reduce the biological
responses you're giving off.
Also...
These devices.
When you turn them on,
they'll transmit biological
data identical to Ichika's.
Remon...
Did you also get those from...?
That's right...
I had your sister's help.
Onee-chan...
All right, let's keep heading towards—
It's creaking!
I-It can't be...
It's coming after us!
It's making another pass!
Ishigaki-kun.
Got it.
Me, too!
I'm going, too!
Mio!
Let me go with you.
Tetsuro!
Make it there, Kai!
Good luck!
Mio, turn it on!
Okay!
Come on, come after us.
Bingo!
Tetsuro!
Mio!
What is it?
You wanna go see a movie sometime?
Huh?
Without Kanna or Kai!
Just the two of us!
Yeah, let's go!
Remon-senpai, take Route 70.
We have a little bit more
than ten kilometers to go.
Behind us!
There's more of them!
I'll go.
Tanigawa-san!
I'm not doing this for you.
I'm doing it for the person I like!
I want the person I like to keep smiling.
Tanigawa!
I'm going to make you regret
this three years from now!
Be happy, jerk!
It doesn't look like
anything else is coming.
Kirishima-kun, take this.
It's my camera.
What are we going to do?
Isn't it obvious?
We're going to film.
The heroine evades her pursuers' attacks
and heads toward her destination.
Seems like we'll be able to
film a pretty nice climax.
And we'll leave the epilogue up to God.
That's the best part of making a movie.
I'm ready here!
And... action!
Persistent, aren't we?
Wh-What's up with this car?!
Episode 12
Waiting there, in the summer.
We won't forget...
...that special summer
we all spent together.
No matter how much time passes...
We'll be...
...waiting there, in the summer.