Why do I feel this way?
It's the first time
this has ever happened.
I don't know what I want to do,
what I should do...
How do I get rid of
this strange feeling?
Shizuku, Takaya
How are you doing?
Are you still working hard?
Your mother is so busy that she's going to die soon.
I want some of Shizuku's pork squares when I make it home.
Oh, is it from Yoshino-san?
What'd she say?
She wants to know how
Takaya and I are doing.
Anything for me?
I don't see anything.
Are you still working hard?
Girls Feeling
Melancholy
Handouts?
Okay, I'll give them to the teacher.
Thanks, Oyama-san!
S-Sure...
All yours, then!
It's Oshima.
New Message
To: Yuu-chan
Sub: Can't take it anymore~
I still don't have any friends,
and people are calling me Oyama-san.
I should have gone to the same high school as you.
Right before school began,
I got sick and had to be hospitalized.
It was a week before I was
able to come to school,
and everybody had already
formed their little groups.
Having missed my chance to join
in, I was left all alone.
It's so hard to breathe
in this classroom.
I find myself thinking
that I'm worthless.
Read Message
From: Yuu-chan
Sub: LOL
LOLZ
Want some cheese with that whine? LOL
They seriously call you Oyama-san? LOL
ROFLMAO
Sorry, Yuu-chan...
I can't understand what
you're saying anymore...
Oh, look over there.
It's Yoshida-kun.
Na—
Nagoya...
...laid an egg!
That's impossible.
It's probably a prank.
A-And...
It's boiled!
He's so fine...
Yuu-chan, I think I'm in love.
But you know...
Yoshida-kun is always with that girl.
Are they a couple?
Okay!
Let's decide on our class
officers for the second term!
Class Representative
Asst. Class Representative
Treasurer
Secretary
I'll take volunteers,
but we don't have any so nominate away!
First come, first serve!
Let's start!
Ooh!  I think Shimoyanagi-kun
would make a good class rep!
Wait!  Hey!
Okay, we have our man!
Yay!
Good luck!
Next up is the assistant class rep!
Any takers?
Shizuku!
Shizuku.
Expand
Domestic
Demand
-Yoshida Haru
Why is he talking politics?
And I'm pretty sure that reforms
and spending cuts come first.
Okay!
We have our secretary!
All done!
EXPAND DOMESTIC DEMAND!!
Class Representative: Shimoyanagi
Assistant Class Representative: Hachigasaki
Treasurer: Inokuma
Secretary: Sato
Huh?  Where did Haru-kun go?
Yoshida walked out with
a sad look on his face.
Did he want someone to nominate him?
No way!
So...
What do you think about
that little encounter?
I knew this was coming.
Those were the eyes of a girl in love.
When did Haru-kun manage
to make that happen?
What's this?
Someone making a move on Yoshida?
It was a girl from class A with
long black hair and glasses.
Oh, that's Oshima-san.
Everyone in my club was talking about her.
She's quiet but cute, apparently.
Did you hear that, Mitty?!
I couldn't care less.
Top National Mock Exam Scores
29 Mizutani Shizuku
Right now, I'm concerned with
my disappointing mock exam scores.
I'm going to the faculty office.
She finally gets herself a rival,
but she isn't excited at all.
Maybe she's mad because
you were teasing her?
I can no longer look Haru in the eye.
I must be flustered.
It's the first time I've
wanted something so badly
that isn't related to studying.
Mizutani Shizuku
This won't work.
It can't work...
Lovely weather...
Hey.
Yo-Yoshida-kun!
You said that glasses were the
key to becoming class rep.
Huh?!
Oh.  Er, gla—
Nobody nominated me!
Sorry...
It was such a good idea...
Hey.
Yes?!
Do you always eat lunch out here?
Don't you have any friends?
A class rep without friends?
Because you look so gloomy?
H-Hard to say...
Well, I didn't have any friends,
but now I do.
Cheer up.
D-Do you mean
the girl who's always with you?
Sh-She's very cute. It's, um...
Natsume-san.
Natsume?
Natsume is a nice person.
She's my friend.
A friend?
Yep, Sasayan's also my friend,
but he pisses me off sometimes.
Oh, and there's that other girl.
The one with pigtails and good grades.
Shizuku?
I love Shizuku.
Huh?  What do you mean?
Huh?  Haru-kun!
What are you doing out here?
What are you doing?
Yo, Natsume.
We were talking about you guys.
This is the class rep.
She doesn't have any friends,
so she always eats lunch here.
Wait!
I know how you feel.
What?!
All right...
Let's get this "Oodles of Friends for
the Class Rep" council started.
Yay! Applause!
Why are you doing this here?
I-I'm sorry...
But Mitty!
Oshima-san doesn't have any friends!
Ideas
Lovability
Personality
Haven't you ever felt the pain, Mitty?
When you feel like a stranger
in your own classroom!
When you have to hide in the restroom
to eat lunch by yourself!
I really want to leave.
That's stupid.
Forget it.
I'll leave.
What are you so upset about, Shizuku?
Just do your thing and
ignore us while you study.
That's your identity.
I can't concentrate.
Now, now.  Let bygones be bygones
and give her a hand.
Why should I help?
If she is unhappy about
her current situation,
she should do something.
If she can't, that's her problem.
That was a spiteful
thing to say, Shizuku.
I really hate that about you.
Really?
I'm disgusted by the self-righteous
act you people put on.
Eh?
Huh?  Huh?
What's going on?
Why is this happening?
I-Is it me?
Is it my fault?
Wh-What should I do?!
Gather 'round!
Pair up and start stretching!
Begin!
I-I'm the one left out...
Th-This sucks.
I should have skipped school today.
Excuse me.  I don't have a partner.
Uh, anyone from class A need a partner?
W-Wow...
She doesn't mind being alone.
U-Um...
Sorry about yesterday.
It got kind of awkward.
Oh, that wasn't your fault.
If they're bothering you,
you should tell them to stop.
You never know what those
two will try to do.
Th-They're not bothering me...
Why are you so timid?
It's not that I'm timid.
I just lack confidence.
Yeah, that's it.
I'm always just waiting.
Waiting for someone to reach out to me.
But at the same time,
I'm really self-conscious,
and a coward.
Yo, class rep.
Have you seen Shizuku around?
You haven't made up yet?
She's been ignoring me the whole day.
What's her problem?
Um, Yoshida-kun...
You can stop.
This is my problem.
I guess I don't like myself.
You sound gloomy.
What did you mean when you
said you love Mizutani-san?
Do you mean that in a romantic way?
W-Wait, forget it!
Forget I said anything!  Sorry!
Why am I asking for answers that
will just depress me more?!
Haru-kun!  Oshima-san!
Wanna join us?
Here I go!
Yeah!
There!
Whee!
Hey!
Gotcha!
Here!
Rolling Thunder!
This is brutal!
Champion Smash!
Hey, Shizuku.
Tell me why you're ignoring me.
Fine.
When I'm with you, my chest hurts.
I can't focus on studying.
So, I don't want to see your face.
Huh?
Wait, wait, what?!
Hold on!
She might as well be saying
that she loves him!
But...
I guess even she feels those things...
Shouldn't you go to the nurse's office?
Y-You've got it all wrong!
Th-That's not what Mizutani-san
was trying to say!
She wouldn't be hurting if
she didn't care about you!
Why don't you understand that she
was telling you she's worried?!
So!  That's why you...
Do you...
Do you!
Have any balls?!
I do!
Don't I, Shizuku?
D-Don't ask me!
He did.
Oh, she ran away.
Haru-kun, you should go after her!
What?  Me?
Yes, hurry!
Why does nothing go right?
I want to go back to middle school.
You okay?
Uh-huh, I-I'm okay.
Yeah, I was just moping by myself.
I'm no expert,
but I think people mope when
their expectations are too high.
It's tiring when you always
have to overachieve.
Don't overdo it.
Just work on achieving what you can.
Yeah?
Uh-huh.
Yuu-chan.
I think...
...I'm in love.
Shizuku,
the somen's ready.
Okay.
They called me Dry Ice at school.
You're just like your mom.
I'm done!
Can we use this?
Grandma had goldfish in hers.
Do you like goldfish, Shizuku?
No, not really.
Yeah...
When we go watch the fireworks
with Mom next week,
we can buy goldfish.
Multiplication
How to Care for Goldfish
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh, okay.
Good luck.
Mom's busy with work.
I see.  That's too bad.
The fireworks started.
What do you want to do, Shizuku?
You, Takaya, and I can still go.
Takaya's asleep,
and I have homework to do.
You really like to study.
Studying was fun.
I enjoyed solving problems quickly,
and I was always rewarded
for the effort I put in.
Studying made me feel complete.
Good morning, Haru.
What?
Well, you're acting normal today.
Oh, something was wrong with me before.
Sorry.
We're friends.
Let's not ruin that.
I don't know why I let
myself lose control.
My mind should be on studying,
and ensuring that my future is bright.
H-Hey, Shizuku.
A-Are you okay?
I don't need anything that would be
a distraction.
What do you mean?
What did you mean when you
said you love Mizutani-san?
Do you mean that in a romantic way?
What's wrong, Haru?
I'm guessing...
The pot is still empty.
In retrospect,
I've been through a flurry of
changes since meeting Haru.
It's all been more than I could handle.
So I will jettison everything
that distracts me.
Misawa
Batting
Center
A date?
Oh, they didn't tell you?
He left this morning to go
on a date with Shizuku-chan.
I had no idea.
When I called Mitty's home,
I heard that she was studying with Haru-kun.
Oh, so they're on a date.
I see how it is.
I guess they're making progress.
I was starting to wonder since
they always act the same.
Seriously, Haru should be ashamed.
Shizuku-chan's the one confessing her
love and asking him out on dates.
I should give him a whipping.
Shizuku-chan's more aggressive
than you'd think.
She has weird taste, too.
Maybe she wants to mother him?
That type might actually be...
Nah.
Public Library
Hey, Shizuku!
Do you know why we're here today?!
To study for exams?
I knew it.
You've been studying by
yourself all morning.
This is supposed to be a date!
You told me to take you to the library!
Oh.
Sorry, I didn't realize.
Really?
Well, as long as you know now.
What's wrong, Natsume-chan?
I had no idea...
She didn't say a word
about her confession or this date...
Mitty never tells me anything.
I have a feeling that Shizuku-chan
never considers asking
other people for advice,
since she's never done it before.
It's not that she doesn't want
to talk to you about it.
I'm sure she'll talk
to you soon enough.
Love requires more than one person.
She'll realize that she
can't do everything alone.
And you'll be there for
her when that happens.
It should be sooner
rather than later.
They're probably running
into a few bumps.
Really?
They look like they could
hook up at any moment,
considering how honest
they both are.
Honesty isn't necessarily a virtue.
Plus, Haru's a coward.
He might run away when the time comes.
He's staring at me...
Stay calm.
Don't let him get to me.
I won't let him distract me now.
Um, Haru...
What is it?
Nothing...
Are you in love with me?
I want to just blurt that out.
Haru, I want to make something clear.
I wasn't sure if I needed
to tell you this,
but I no longer feel attracted to you.
Huh?
He needs to stop overreacting.
I realized that I wasn't able
to control my emotions.
I can't let my grades suffer any more.
I'm not like you.
I have to work through a problem
multiple times before I can solve it.
I think you mentioned that once.
Can I ask you something?
Am I a distraction now?
No, this is a problem on my side.
Okay...
Mitty!
Let's talk about love!
Huh?
U-Um, don't run away.
So, I was just hoping
you might tell me about
your date yesterday or something.
Nothing happened.
That's impossible!
There must have been
something happy or sad!
No, nothing happened.
Natsume-san, you should
study for our exams.
Phooey!
Stupid, stupid, stupid Mitty!
How did she get into this high school?
Nagoya, scoot over.
Looks like Haru's getting
along with the other kids.
Hey, look!
You've got a bald spot.
Are you stressed out?
Next Episode
The Distance
Between Us