Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
I want you to deliver that
book to someone for me.
I can't do it anymore.
Hurry.
Stay here, and you'll really
be unable to go home.
Miura-san.
This is my memory.
It's the regret that's been
woven shut inside that book.
That night, I had a promise
I needed to fulfill.
A promise?
Someone was waiting for me.
Niikura Mayumi-san.
The owner of that book.
Which one are you going to borrow today?
I can't decide.
The master's books are all so impressive.
When they say "bookworm," they
must mean people like you.
Not as much as you.
Hey, I...
The master told me...
that you were going to get married.
Congratulations.
Is that all you're going to say?
What more could I say?
My happiest moments are when
I'm reading the last page of a book.
The story ends.
But it makes me feel as though
it's going to go on somewhere.
You can borrow this.
Mayumi-san.
Please don't forget to give it back.
I was just a lowly student.
She was the daughter of
the wealthy family I was indebted to.
I never thought our relationship
would ever bear fruit.
But...
Wait for me on the final platform
She extended her hand to me.
I had no choice but to go to her.
No matter what.
I have to go to her.
I have to go.
I have to go!
I was drawn to this library.
And I became a captive.
I don't even know how
long I've been here now.
But...
You reminded me.
When you smiled and said you
like the last page of a book.
To her...
To Niikura Mayumi-san.
Hatori-san.
There's no one else I can ask.
Now, go.
Please.
Now, hurry.
No one will ever wander into here again.
Niikura
Um...
Are you Niikura Mayumi-san?
My great-grandma?
You're from this neighborhood, right?
Grandma Mayumi's in the hospital right now.
You know the huge hospital by the river?
She's there.
What did you need?
We just got here yesterday.
We don't really know our way around.
If you need something...
Hey!
Niikura-san?
With all due respect,
how are you two related?
I'm sorry, I can't tell you her
room number unless you're related.
Niikura-san?
I think her grandchildren's families
were coming to visit today.
Oh, really?
Come on, then.
Come.
Niikura Mayumi
Niikura-san.
You're out of bed again.
I'm so bored.
I've read all the books I brought with me.
Your great-granddaughter's here.
Already?
She's here early.
Weren't you going to eat lunch first?
You're...
What can I do for you?
Are you Niikura Mayumi-san?
I am.
Spring Will Be Missed
My...
This book... Where did you...
There's no mistake.
This is my book.
This is our book.
Are you his granddaughter?
His great-granddaughter?
Is he doing well?
I'm sorry.
I'm so happy.
I'm really happy.
He never did come to me,
but he did fulfill his promise.
He gave this book back to me.
So I'm happy.
Thank you.
Let me get a good look at your face.
Come over here.
What's your name?
Hatori Chise.
What a beautiful name.
Thank you, Hatori Chise-san.
Grandma, shouldn't you be asleep?
Grandmama, look!
I got second rank in swimming!
I got third rank!
Hurry up and get better, Grandmama.
Um, hey...
Let's go to the pool.
Did a girl come by?
Red hair, about this tall.
Ow.
What was that for?
Let's go already.
Hey, are we really going
to the forest today?
Are you scared?
It's not my fault if we get lost.
We won't!
The Lonely Little Star
I gave her the book.
Mayumi-san said, "Thank you."
"The child of a star asked,
with a voice like a bell,
'God of the Stars, why do you leave
me here by myself in this dark night sky?'
'I have no way to talk to the other stars,
or to show each other our light.'
To which the God of the Stars replied,
'Look very carefully.'
And so the child looked very hard. So hard
that their eyes could have fallen out."
Then, off in the distance, a myriad
of tiny, twinkling stars could be seen.
'See? You can see them if
you look really carefully.
The sky is endlessly connected.
Just try, and you'll see even
the faintest of lights.'"
This is the book I need?
Hatori-san.
Hm?
You might see nothing but
pitch-black darkness right now.
But, you have to keep trying and
trying, looking into the dark world.
Yeah.
And off in the distance,
you'll surely find some light.
Like the child of a star?
Yes.
Like the child of a star.
And when you find the child of
a star, they'll surely find you, too.
And you'll shine light on each other.
And then your world will
no longer be pitch-black.
Really?
Just look.
There are so many stars out there.
I truly believe you'll meet a child
of a star who will light your world.
Really?
Life is a lot longer than you think.
Live your best, and you will...
I can't believe that.
Yeah.
We're ready when you are.
I truly believe you'll meet a child
of a star who will light your world.
Boys, can you come help?
The Lonely Little Star
Okay.
You will.
I can't believe this book
is here, after I let it go.
Show me more.
Show me.
Elias?
Chise, may I?
Huh? Um...
Elias, what is it?
Found it.
That story you just told me...
I believe I've seen
something like it before.
See?
"Mayoiga"?
Yeah.
It shows itself in a spectacular light
to those who get lost in the forest.
So that's how it draws people in.
Huh.
That's so odd.
How so?
Those who wander in are allowed
to bring home just one thing.
You don't see this kind of
thing very often around here.
People do steal things by force.
I see.
That's probably the condition for
their returning to their own world.
That Miura man gave you something every
time you left from the library, correct?
A library card, a picture
book, and that book.
I wonder if it counts if it's
given to you by someone inside.
What if you can't be given anything?
You'd likely be stuck there.
That's what it means to
wander into the other side.
Though I don't know how
much he was aware of that.
Miura-san...
He must have known everything.
He must have given the
book to me knowing that.
What makes you say that?
If it wasn't that book that he'd given me,
I probably wouldn't have left him there.
Chise...
Yes?
Is this memory a painful one?
Angie really shouldn't have sent us this.
That's not true.
Really?
I don't mind this book, either.
Yeah.
You're right.
It's already getting dark.
We've really been talking away.
We didn't finish cleaning.
We can continue tomorrow.
Yes.
It's way past tea time, too.
Stare...
Silky.
You made tea for us?
Sorry.
I'll have it with dinner.
You sure you want to make
a promise like that?
I'll... I'll do my best.
All right, it's time for dinner.
It's going to be chicken stewed with tomatoes,
tomato compote, and dried tomato muffins.
There sure are plenty of
tomatoes during the summer.
Chise, what are you going to
do with that picture book?
I think I'll give it another
proper read through.
I feel like I can read it
differently this time.
If you do, would you talk
to me about it again?
Yes.
There's more to the "Mayoiga" story.
There's more?
Anyone who takes something home from
that house is met with good fortune.
That might be true.