Impossible... The Chancellor
is one of those monsters?
Orders, ma'am?
What about the attack?
We haven't received instructions. Wait.
Wait! Stop!
What are you doing?
Fire your cannon!
Look at that live feed!
Something weird is going on!
- What live feed?
- Switch your drones to standby mode!
The enemy's withdrawing?
This is bad... What is the Council
going to do about this?
L-Let go of His Excellency!
Stand down! This is not someone
who deserves your oath of loyalty!
- It's war!
- What about those students, then?
- It's Dorssian soldiers who are doing this!
- Like you can believe anything Dorssia says.
If the Chancellor himself is one
of these hazardous organisms,
how can anything
Dorssia does be trusted?
I don't believe it...
How much of what
he said is true?
- We did it!
- Not much fun, is it, you Dorssian bastards!
This will turn the tide!
This also spells the end of the
Dorssia-ARUS alliance, doesn't it?
Can we... go back to school?
Of course!
Though that all depends on
what stance ARUS takes after this.
Things look bad for Dorssia.
They're looking at a civil war at this rate.
We staked it all on one roll of the dice,
and that turned the tables!
We did it!
We did it, Yamada!
It's fast!
- What the?
- What's going on?
You lowly Valvrave knockoff...
Akira-chan!
Cain, Pino is in there!
Plu. I'm going to fulfill
my promise to you now.
What's going on?
Things were just getting good!
According to reports we've just received,
the scene we just witnessed
was doctored by Class 7
Special Hazard Organisms.
So it was all a ploy by those students?
Or rather, those monsters?
- What the hell, it was fake?!
- See, what did I tell you?
- Boy, what a relief!
- So those students are the only monsters, then?
How could this have happened?!
They probably leaned on the media
behind the scenes.
This quickly?!
This means that we can't just
slug it out with these people.
Give them doctored footage to analyze and
have them lend credence to the story.
For the time being, the situation
appears to be quieting down.
Magiuses are in their shadows,
and all is right with the world.
The Council of 101 is composed of the
world's most influential people.
How many incidents and accidents do you think
we have arranged over the centuries?
It's powerful...
This is Unit 2?
Cain! This is for H-neun!
Now it makes sense. L-elf's infiltration
was your handiwork, wasn't it?
They're fighting each other?
Did L-elf set this up?
Don't! Stay back, Akira-chan!
But...
You can't do anything,
not with damage like that!
X-eins, don't go too far
ahead by yourself!
Wow, you're turning traitor
too, Highness...
Q-vier!
Valvraves and now the Perfection Army...
It's a veritable feast today!
Thank goodness you're
all right, Mr. President!
At present, ARUS forces are keeping their
distance from the Valvrave battle.
Assemble all staff officers
aboard my flagship!
All forces are to cease hostilities
until we reach a decision!
It can do things that are
that different from ours?
I can still fight! This is
no time to be stingy!
I can still fight!
I can fight!
This pilot is more competent
than before, but still...
...readiness evaluation, D.
Stop this, Q-vier!
Cain killed H-neun!
So what if he did? Killing a traitor
is a good thing!
Hear me out!
"Death to traitors."
That's what we swore, remember?
Though I'm just happy to get
the chance to fight someone tough!
Cain!
You'll pay!
You betrayed H-neun!
And my heart!
Sacrificing oneself for one's friends
is noble. I don't begrudge you that.
At point blank...
It'll be worth dying
if I can take you with me!
An attack you staked your life on.
Brilliantly played, X-eins.
I'll give you a readiness
evaluation of A.
H-neun,
even at a time like this,
I know you'd be cracking wise...
Haruto Tokishima!
Someone like you, who only recently began
combat training, can't defeat Cain!
Maybe not, but I have to try!
My point is, I will fight with you.
I have reasons to defeat him
that surpass even yours.
So use me.
Oh, right! Body-jack you!
Between my body, which has had combat techniques
drilled into it by him, and your curse...
We can do it together!
All right, let's
wrap this up, shall we?
That speed and that precise sword
technique... Is that you, L-elf?
We're still alive!
We won't be silenced by you!
You know, Haruto, when I heard that
your memories were disappearing,
I was actually looking
forward to it a little.
I mean, who can compete against
a childhood friend?
If you lost your memories,
I'd be on an even footing with her.
I'm a horrible person, aren't I?
The JIORan Module is moving!
A Valvrave!
There's more left!
Q-vier!
Cannon fire has been forbidden!
Don't forget that VIPs from
our own country are inside!
Two Kirschbaums are en route.
Lieutenants A-drei and Q-vier!
A-drei... I can't offer you
any direct support.
I know that Haruto
will choose Shoko,
but I promised myself that
I wouldn't give up.
Hostilities have been suspended!
I'll deal with you after I
take out that Valvrave!
So that's why he'd been
using a Waffe's shield...
That's my A-drei...
I knew you'd be tough!
Q-vier...
I knew you'd be the best...
You're so cool...
You understand nothing.
The Council of 101 is no evil secret society.
We are champions of justice who
safeguard the peace of the world.
You're saying the Council
is the good guys?!
It was humans
who attacked us first!
We desired only coexistence, but
humanity feared and attacked us.
Legends of supernatural monsters around the
world are a chronicle of Magius suffering!
It is for that reason that we,
over the course of many years,
made deals with
the world's leading figures.
We Magiuses have lived in secret so as
not to arouse the fear of humanity.
And in return...
...they tacitly allow us to prey upon
a certain number of humans!
It is only because of the Council system that humanity
has been kept safe from fear and chaos!
In short, the ones who threaten
the peace and order of the world
are you people
and your Valvraves!
That's your excuse?!
Was what we did right?
You saw it! You saw how
Haruto Tokishima didn't die!
I did. But I didn't see him
killing your father, Iori.
Let's go find out.
Ma'am, are you okay?
A teacher can't sit idly by
at time like this.
Find out? Find out how?
We'll talk. That's all.
The thing about the truth is, you'll never know
what it is unless you come out and ask.
Stop it, big brother!
I don't hate this human!
I can't do that! He's one of the people
who locked us up in these machines
to try to use us
as a power source!
No! We're leaking Runes!
Can't we... win against him?
We walked hand in hand with history,
were hurt, and came to a realization.
A system where there could be no conflict
between us meant living separately
Very well, let's put
an end to this.
I'll eliminate you two
and reclaim our peace!
We're coming, Pino!
You're wrong!
What's that?
You had considered trying to live
together with humanity, too?
But you gave up because
you had been hurt.
You built up a wall of lies
so neither would hurt the other.
He was my friend even after he
lost his guiding light,
he picked himself up
to make her dream a reality!
And the girl that I love,
even after losing her father,
even though he was the
prime minister, she kept on fighting!
Its power is increasing?
For all our friends who haven't given up
even after being hurt again and again,
we can't lose to you!
A coup?!
Now, of all times?
In seven locations
that we know of.
They're breaking out simultaneously
all across Dorssian territory.
We Royalists have long awaited
the right time to take action.
Regardless of the veracity of the information
brought to us by the boy named L-elf,
it provides sufficient pretext.
Yes, Excellency. This is a golden opportunity for
the Royalists to rise up and turn the tables.
- What's the "Council of 101"?
- Looks like a list of those monsters.
- Check this out!
- Hey, that's the president of the Winkers Company!
What in the world is this?
This is a hoax!
Perhaps, but some of it is true!
It is not a problem.
We will deal with it.
New information, sir!
The president of the Global Bank
has been taken into custody!
Preposterous! He isn't
a member of the Council!
They're being whipped into a frenzy
by some made-up stories?!
Targets have been apprehended.
Was it wise to trust
that list, sir?
Our only option is to take action now!
Before the monsters can band together!
If we play this right, we might be
able to get rid of the Magiuses.
We don't want a future that was given up on
and closed off from the very beginning!
I mean...
...our friends never gave up,
so I can't, either!
You stupid boy who knows
nothing of history!
I'll do it!
Plu!
It's all over!
Cain! Cain!
Plu...
Haruto Tokishima!
We've done it!
We've won!
Haruto? Is that my name?
He used up all his Runes.
I don't understand any of this.
Where am I?
Who are you?
You don't remember?
Anything at all?
Not even our pact?
Our fight on the Moon?
Sorry.
You and I, we...
You know me, don't you?
You know who I am?
Yes, you're...
You are my friend.
Imperial Calendar, year 0.
This would later be known as the year
the Third Galactic Empire began,
but it goes without saying that we never
could have imagined that at the time.
Afterwards, pandemonium
broke out across the world.
Seeing monsters everywhere, people sought
out Magiuses all over the world,
and eventually, neither the Council of 101 nor
the existence of Magiuses could remain hidden.
- They found the Magiuses!
- They're for real this time, right?
I think it was because the world had become
too connected for secrets to be kept.
Shoko-chan cried her eyes out.
For what seemed like forever.
After a while, she went back
to being her usual self.
But every once in a while...
In any case, we found ourselves
a place to call home.
Our Galactic Empire started
from such a tiny country?
Historical beginnings are often
surprisingly humble.
T-There's an emergency!
There's an intruder in the Memorial Core!
It's thought to be lifeform 53s!
What were you expecting,
a secret weapon?
These are the statues of the heroes
we call "The First Knights."
People who were dear to me who died
one by one when we founded this country.
Let's try to be friends.
I won't pretend that that will
suddenly solve everything.
But if we do, we'll be able to take
all our pain and joy and go halfsies!