No matter what you say,
you are the criminal who hurt my brother!
That's why you'll die.
"Villain - Stain - Quirk: Bloodcurdle"
M-My body won't move...
Goodbye. You're an offering
to a more just world.
I won't forgive you...
I'll kill you!
Smash!
"Izuku Midoriya - Quirk: One For All"
I came to save you, Iida!
"Shoto Todoroki - Quirk: Half-Cold, Half-Hot"
You made me late.
"Tenya Iida - Quirk: Engine"
Midoriya...?
Todoroki...
The two of us will protect them!
Why are you two...
Why...
Please, stop!
I've inherited my brother's name.
I have to do it...
That guy's mine...!
Sorry, Todoroki.
Please stop...
I'm... already...
If you want us to stop, then stand up!
"Climax"
Do you know the Turbo Hero, Ingenium?
Of course!
He's a really popular hero who has
65 sidekicks working at his Tokyo agency!
He is my elder brother!
He is a likable hero who
honors the rules and leads people.
I set my sights on being a hero
because I want to be like my brother.
Iida...
The only words I can say to you are:
Look properly at what you want to be!
Ingenium. It is the name
of the hero who will defeat you!
What kind of hero am I?
Protected by my friends...
Having them bleed for me...!
Save that guy first.
Hero Killer: Stain.
In order to teach him a lesson,
I used my brother's name.
I only saw what was in front of me...
I couldn't see anything except myself...!
Tenya, you want to be a hero, too?
Yes. You're cool.
What are you, a robot?
Will you tell me something
for my future reference?
"Pro Hero - Tensei Iida"
Why do you continue working as a hero?
Well, our grandfather
and parents were all heroes,
so I was expected to be
a hero by those around me.
Anyway, it's simple, really.
If someone sees a lost child,
they take the child to the
service counter for lost children.
I think people like that are the coolest.
Then why didn't you decide to work
at the service counter for lost children?
Think about what I'm saying!
What are you, a robot?
You really take everything literally, huh?
You're way smarter and
more athletic than I was at your age, so...
Wait a sec.
Then that means--
If you admire me, Tenya,
then I might be an amazing hero.
Because you're fakes.
It's just as you say, Hero Killer.
From the right!
I'm different from them.
I'm immature. I can't hold a candle to them!
Even so...
Ice and flame.
I'd like to see you dodge this!
No one's ever told you?
You're too focused on your Quirk.
You're being careless!
He's a monster...!
Todoroki!
If I don't stand right now...
...I'll never, ever be able...
...to catch up to them, or Tensei!
Damn it.
It stopped working, huh?
Recipro...
...burst!
He's fast!
Iida!
You got free?
That Quirk isn't as great as I thought.
Todoroki, Midoriya, this has nothing
to do with you two, and I apologize.
You're saying that again?
That's why I can't allow
you two to bleed more than this!
It's no use trying to be
reformed for appearance's sake.
A person's essence does not change so easily.
You will never be anything but a fake
who prioritizes his own selfish desires.
You are a cancer to society
that warps the idea of "heroes."
Someone must set you straight.
You're an anachronistic fundamentalist.
Iida, don't listen to the logic of a murderer.
No, he's right.
I have no right to call myself a hero...
Even so,
I cannot give in.
If I give in, then Ingenium will die.
Out of the question.
Idiot! The hero killer is after me
and that kid in white armor, right?
Don't fight back.
It'd be better if you ran away!
It doesn't look like he'll
give me an opening to do that.
Something clearly changed just now.
He's flustered.
There's the uncertain element of blood type,
and he needs to get in close for it to work.
On top of that, it doesn't last very long...
Looking at just his Quirk,
he's not especially powerful.
Taking on multiple opponents
alone must be hard for him to deal with.
He's gotten desperate trying to kill Iida
and this person before the pros come.
He's got crazy tenacity...
Oh no, Recipro's done.
Did I break the radiator during my kick earlier?
Todoroki, can you regulate temperature?
I'm not used to it with my left yet. Why?
Freeze my legs!
Without plugging up the exhausts!
You're in the way!
Iida!
You stop, too!
--Iida...
--Just do it! Hurry!
I... I can move.
Can I do it...?
No, right now...
Damn it!
Thanks, Todoroki.
I will fight.
I'll throw away my arm!
Recipro...
...Extend!
One For All...
...Full Cowling!
If I just...
Go!
...have my leg...
...have my fist...
...that's all I need right now!
"Affiliation: U.A. High School Hero Class 1-A"
"Birthday: 8/22"
"Height: 179 cm" "Blood Type: A" "Likes: Beef Stew"
"Tenya Iida"
"Quirk: Engine"
"He can run very fast using the engines in his calves."
"Affiliation: Unknown"
"Birthday: Unknown"
"Height: Unknown" "Blood Type: Unknown" "Likes: Unknown"
"Stain"
"Quirk: Unknown"
"Unknown"
"Minutes earlier"
He's fast! But--
Not faster than I can handle!
Hey--
Stop it, you little--
"Pro Hero - Gran Torino - Quirk: Jet"
I do not know who you are, honored elder,
but leave the rest to me.
Seriously?
Why are you here?
"Pro Hero - Endeavor - Quirk: Hellflame"
Isn't it obvious?
It's because I am a hero.
Even though I used a
lower temperature as a warning,
this is the first time anyone's been able to
stay conscious after being on the receiving end.
Be careful!
This guy's...
Absorption and release, huh? But since
the damage from the absorption remains...
It's just a small fry's Quirk!
That's strange...
No, Todoroki!
This guy's got multiple Quirks!
I see, so that's how it is.
Those two bystanders ran away, right?
In that case...
I cracked the road...
It's been a while, so my control's not great...
Huh, you're not bad, honored elder.
There should be a lot of
heroes gathered over there.
It's been at least two or three minutes.
Even though they're all
gathered there... Good grief!
Let's restrain this guy quickly and
turn him over to the police so we can go help!
Shoto, there's trouble! Follow me!
I'll show you what it means to be a hero!
Midoriya...
Shoto!
--It's just his location...
--Don't look at your phone, look at me!
Where are you going, Shoto?!
An alleyway at 4-2-10 Ekou Street.
If you finish what you're doing or
find any free pros, send them there.
I'm leaving you to take care of the trouble.
I'm sure you'll be able to resolve it quickly.
My friend might be in trouble...
Shoto...
Leave that villain to my sidekicks.
Honored elder, go now
to the address I'll give you.
I, Endeavor, will be sufficient support
for those over there by myself.
Go!
Did I release a little too much power?
It's not broken... is it?
They stopped him!
Here's my chance!
I will defeat you!
This time, you, as a criminal--
Keep after him!
And I, as a hero!
Stand up! He's still...
He's probably knocked out
after all that... right?
Then, let's restrain him
and get out to the street.
Is there anything to tie him up with?
Just in case, let's take
all his weapons off him.
Good idea.
He's too strong!
Damn it!
Let's all attack him at once!
Right!
Damn it, I can't see!
Where is he?!
Run away!
Endeavor!
He can regenerate, huh?
Then--
How about this?!
Carbonized cells cannot regenerate.
Look out!
Those heroes with Quirks that
are not effective against the villain,
go to Ekou Street, District 4 to help there!
There's a villain there, too?
I don't know, but I'm counting on you!
He's fast! Then--
I won't let you get away!
Native, can you move?
Yeah, I'm okay now.
U-Um...
You hurt your legs, right?
Let me do this, at least.
Th-Thank you very much.
That's my line.
You can find anything
at a trash collection site.
Todoroki, I'll pull it!
Your arms are all messed up, right?
Sorry...
Even though I'm a pro, I was just in the way.
No, I don't think you could've done anything
one-on-one with the hero killer's Quirk.
He's too strong.
Fighting three-on-one with the guy making
mistakes himself, we still barely won.
He was probably flustered and
forgot about Midoriya's recovery time.
And he wasn't able to deal with Iida's last
Reciproburst or Midoriya's movements.
Now, let's quickly get him to the police--
Wha...? Why are you here?
Gran Torino!
Gran Tor
I thought I told you to
stay seated on the bullet train!
Who's that?
The hero I'm interning with,
Gran Torino. But why?
I was told to come here all of a sudden.
Well, I don't really know what's
going on, but I'm glad you're okay.
Gran Torino, I'm sorry...
Jeez, this part of him is
also exactly like Toshinori.
It's around here!
Huh?
Endeavor told us there was
a request for help here, but...
Children?
Those injuries look serious!
I'll call an ambulance right away!
H-Hey, this is...
Don't tell me... it's the hero killer?
--What?
--Call the police, too!
Can you walk?
If you prop me up, I can...
And you?
I only received minor injuries.
But Iida is...
He's bleeding badly...
The ambulance will be here soon! Until then...
You two...
You were injured because of me.
I am truly sorry.
I couldn't... see anything...
through my anger...
I'm sorry, too.
Even though you were feeling
so cornered, I didn't notice at all.
Even though we're friends...
Pull yourself together.
You're the class rep, right?
Yeah.
The fight against the hero killer
probably only took about ten minutes.
But to us, it felt like a very long fight--
Get down!
A villain?!
--Hey!
--Midoriya!
There's blood! Did he escape
here after being beaten?
Oh no, if he get's too high, then I won't
be able to reach him with my Quirk!
This society overgrown with fake heroes...
...and the criminals who wave
their power around idly...
...should all be purged.
So noisy...
The idiots have come out, huh?
I'll dispose of them later.
This is all...
...to create a more just society.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What the hell?!
Why'd that Nomu have to go and get killed?
Why is that kid there?
"Villain - Tomura Shigaraki - Quirk: Decay"
"Villain - Kurogiri - Quirk: Warp Gate"
There's so much I want
to say that I can't keep up!
This is a mess!
Why...
Why won't things go the way I want?
He saved the boy?!
Idiot, he took a hostage!
He killed someone with no hesitation.
Anyway, get ready to fight for now!
Why are you all standing around in a group?
The villain should've escaped this way.
How are things on your end?
Things got a little rough.
--But don't tell me that man is...?
--Let... go...!
Endeavor.
Hero Killer!
Wait, Todoroki!
You fake...
I must make things right...
Someone must be dyed in blood...
I must take back what it means to be a hero!
Come! Try and get me, you fakes!
The only one I'll let
kill me is the true hero...
...All Might!
He's...
He's unconscious...
I heard later
that a broken rib had pierced
the hero killer's lung at that moment.
He hadn't licked anyone's blood,
but at that place, for that one moment,
the hero killer was the only one
who stood up to fight against his opponent.
"Preview"
The preview is here!
And I am here, too.
Why is it you, sir, and not Young Midoriya?
Who are you?
I'm All Might.
I said, I am All Might...
Toshinori?
Th-That's me...
Who are you?
This is endless! But let's stop that--
Next time, "The Aftermath
of Hero Killer: Stain."
That young man called Todoroki
will become "The Hand Crusher"!
Go beyond!
"Next time: The Aftermath of Hero Killer: Stain"
Plus Ultra!