Higashinohashi High School
Well then, any suggestions for
the cultural festival next month?
Suggest some ideas, please.
Me! I want to do a maid café
with all the girls dressed up!
What?!
No way! I'd never do that.
I agree! Totally agree!
What are the guys gonna do, then?!
The boys can work behind the scenes!
Who really cares?
Right?
Don't give me that crap!
Yes! I agree with the maid café idea!
I think everyone in the class should
dress up! I really want to see that!
Huh?!
Agree! Totally agree! Boy maids!
Screw off! Who would benefit from that?
Come on, it'll be fun!
Topic
Ideas for the cultural festival
Café?
So, after much debate,
the class decided on a cosplay
café as a compromise!
I'm so pumped!
Kiss Him, Not Me
The Clear and Blue Autumn Sky,
and Passionate Otome
I'm definitely not excited about it.
It's annoying that we all have to do it.
I think it sounds fun.
What should I wear?
So you're up for it?
Um, Nanashima-kun...
I've got the perfect idea
idea for your costume.
Just leave the design and everything to me!
You, too, Igarashi-kun!
Design the costumes?
Does that mean you intend to make them?
Our club has an exhibit, too.
Will you have time?
I'll take care of everything
the at history club, too!
It's a festival! I'm going all out!
Shinomiya-kun, what's your
class going to be doing?
Huh? Uh... Um...
A... play.
Oh? What kind of play? Do you have a part?
Yeah, well... yeah...
What's the deal? Spit it out!
I-I'm playing the princess.
Princess?
Seriously?!
I-I lost at rock-paper-scissors!
Score!
A pretty boy dressed as a girl!
Shinomiya-kun.
I know you can pull this off.
You can be the best princess ever!
It'll be okay!
Allow me to be in charge of your production!
I'll be sure to make you shine!
H... Huh?
Shi
B-But, Senpai, you're already so
busy with your class and club,
I couldn't possibly—
It's fine! One more costume is no problem!
I-Is that so?
Nanashima-kun, Igarashi-kun
and Shinomiya-kun.
I can't believe I'm in charge
of making costumes for them!
This is the chance of a lifetime!
Looks like I'm gonna be busy!
You sure are excited, Serinuma-san.
10 Days Until the Festival
Excuse me!
Shoulder width is... 45 cm.
Measurement Points
Shoulder width
Chest circumference
Arm circumference
Inseam
Just a second, sorry.
Chest is...
Let's see...
Serinuma-san, you have a visitor!
Measurement Points
Shoulder width
Chest circumference
Arm circumference
Inseam
Okay!
Wow, he's so cute!
You're going to play the princess?
You totally look the part!
Okay, okay, that's enough, all of you.
Okay!
See you later, First-Year-kun!
Wh-Why does everyone know?
Oh, sorry. I kind of let it slip.
Please don't!
Sorry! But I just can't help feeling that
you're going to be the cutest princess!
Cute? Senpai...
I'm a man, too, you know.
Shinomiya-kun...
If only I could say that...
Wow, Shinomiya-kun.
You look very delicate,
but you really are a man, huh?
Your shoulders are broad,
and your hands are big, too.
S-Senpai!
I... I...!
Hey, you're right!
He's got a thick neck, too!
What do you want?
I'm complimenting you here.
I said you have a manly neck.
Serinuma, I'm up next. Thanks!
She's not done with me yet! Back off!
Well, too bad! Her classmate comes first!
What?!
What's wrong with you?
Are you in elementary school?!
You're such a child!
Haunted House
5 Days Until the Festival
Kae-chan! About the costumes!
Wha... This is horrible.
Are you okay? Maybe you bit
off more than you can chew.
Yeah... but I'm in charge of this.
I'll do my be—ouch!
Hey! I'm free, so let me help.
Igarashi-kun!
But...
It's okay, really!
Rely on me. Okay?
Thanks!
Well, then—
Hey!
You can count on me, too, ya know?
Nanashima-kun!
Senpai! I came by to help out!
You, too, Shinomiya-kun?
What the hell, Princess?!
Don't skip out on your own class.
My class is already finished for the day!
Serinuma-san.
Sorry, but can you come help
out at the history club now?
Huh? Th-That's right, I totally forgot!
Sorry! I'm on my way!
Sorry to ask when you're so busy,
we don't have enough hands.
No, no! It's my responsibility.
This still needs buttons, though...
But, the history club!
I'll go in your place, then.
You come, too, Igarashi.
And you.
Is that okay?
Totally! Come to think about it,
sewing doesn't suit us, anyway!
Thank you! Sorry, but I'd be really grateful!
Social Studies Material Room
Whoa, your writing is so messy!
What a letdown.
You don't get to talk when
you get kanji wrong
even when you're copying them!
Shut it!
No need to rush.
Okay...
Huh? What am I doing here?
It's for Serinuma-san,
but she's not even here.
Hey!
Nana.
Is this fun for you?
Well, it's not so bad.
It feels real festive!
I see.
And so, preparations moved along steadily.
And with a lot of commotion.
The Day Before the Festival
All done!
Good job!
The accessories are done, too.
Thanks so much, A-chan!
How about we try them on?
Okay!
What about everyone else?
I think they're changing right now.
Here they come.
It's so good!
Can I take a pic?
Those three look better than I ever imagined!
Shion.
Y-Yeah...
Whatever way I look at you,
you're Shion! Shion in 3D!
Wonderful! Shion, you're wonderful!
You, too, Shinomiya-kun!
You're incredibly cute, just as I expected!
No one would even think you're a boy!
I-Is that right?
She doesn't even see you as a man.
And she doesn't even
see you as a real person.
Igarashi-kun, you look perfect!
Such a great figure!
I'm so happy that you're all
wearing the costumes I made.
Thank you, guys!
I can't wait for tomorrow!
I'm glad you managed to finish.
Our class is amazing! You have
to come see the cosplay café.
Sure.
I'm going to go see your
play, too, Shinomiya-kun.
It starts at 2 PM, right?
Huh?!
I'll go see, too!
I'll make sure you're not allowed in.
What did you say?!
I know! If we have time, let's go
around the festival together!
Sounds good!
Sure!
You can count me out.
I'll pass.
What? But, it's a one-time thing,
and if we all make the time...
Sorry.
I'm not interested in playing
buddy-buddy with everyone anymore.
Kiss Him, Not Me
Igarashi-kun.
I like you, Serinuma-san,
so I'd like to see the
festival with just you, alone.
Sound good?
Not at all!
Right, I forgot! Why do I have
to do anything with you?
I don't like it, either!
I don't want to play
buddy-buddy with everyone, either!
Same.
What's with this deja-vu?
I mean, why does it have
to be like this anyway?
I just want to enjoy the festival!
Hold on a minute.
Everyone, calm down.
S-Senpai!
What if we make a schedule so we
all get equal time alone with her?
Huh?
A schedule?
In short, we decide a time for everyone,
and in that slot, we each
get alone time with her.
And during that time,
the others can't interfere.
Sounds good to me!
Okay, we'll go with that!
What?
The Day of the Festival
What?!
Current wait:
20 minutes
Welcome, sirs.
This way, please.
Kae-chan! It's about time to change shifts.
Okay!
13:00 Nanashima
13:30 Mutsumi
14:00 Igarashi
14:30 Shinomiya
Four dates lined up with four hotties, huh?
Stop! Cut it out, A-chan!
I really don't know how to
handle being alone with a guy!
It'll be fine.
It's not like you'll be completely
alone with any of them.
Just have fun the way you always do!
I-I see! You're right!
Hey!
Let's get going.
Sure.
I guess I should probably change first.
No! Stay as you are!
Let's go with you as Shion!
The Usual
You two, advertise the café for us!
Here, take these.
Huh?
2-A
Cosplay Café
Open for Business
Can I take a pic?!
Me, too!
Give me a flyer, Maid-san!
They're nowhere close to being alone together.
I guess that's a relief.
Damn, our time's gonna end before we know it.
PC Club's Special Event Purikura Corner
Serinuma, this way!
Okay, here you are!
Thanks.
Kae's Wish
Amazing!
Amazing?
Yeah. To think I'd get to
have a picture with Shion...
I'm so happy.
That right? That's good.
But, you know...
I'm a real, live man. Don't forget that.
Um...
Sorry, it's time.
Get a clue, Senpai!
But your time's up, and we promised.
You could give me just a little—
Go on, Mutsumi-senpai!
Let go of me, you bastard!
Best in the world? Yakisoba
Yummy Takoyaki
That got me flustered.
My face is still hot.
Serinuma-san? What's the matter?
Are you feeling unwell?
Not at all! I'm all right.
Really? Are you up to eating yakisoba?
Of course! Thank you.
That's a relief.
Delicious!
Mutsumi-senpai really is comforting.
The takoyaki is good, too.
Want to try?
Sure!
Okay. Wait a second.
Here.
Huh?
H-Haven't we got the
maid-master roles mixed up?
And wait, these are Mutsumi-senpai's chopsticks!
Taste good?
Time's up.
If you'll excuse me.
Igarashi-kun...
You're pretty smooth, aren't you?
Huh?
Class 1-D's theatrical
program will begin shortly.
Wh-What a trap that was...
I ran because we were short
on time. Sorry. Are you tired?
Huh? Oh, no. Rather, I'm grateful to you.
I'm glad you're here to watch
Shinomiya-kun's play with me.
My name's Snow White.
I came here today to pick flowers.
Wow! He's so cute!
What a beautiful flower.
There are more here!
And over here.
Don't like it?
N-No, that's not quite it...
Great.
That concludes Class 1-D's theatrical program.
Pretty fun, wasn't it?
Huh? Uh, yeah.
Memory
Ka
M-My memory is totally blacked out.
Senpai! Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hey. Your play was good.
Th-Thanks.
See ya, Serinuma-san.
Uh, yeah. Later.
Haunted House
To another world
The girls in my class said
this was pretty scary.
Really?
I've got to show her my manly side.
A haunted house? I get it.
You really didn't pull anything
funny during the play?
Who knows?
You did! You totally did!
I never should have left you
two alone in the dark like that!
Yeah? Then what about Shinomiya-kun?
That's true. It's dark in there.
He's fine.
He's not the sort to pull something.
A-Are you okay?
P-Perfectly fine.
Maybe he's no good with spooky things.
How cute.
Look. The exit's close by. Let's go.
She doesn't even see you as a man.
Please, don't treat me like a child.
I'm a man, you know.
Sh-Shinomiya-kun?
Wait! That's dangerous!
Ouch!
Wh-What was that?
That was no joke!
Was it really that scary?
H-Hey! What happened?
It was an accident. An accident.
Nanashima and the others
should be coming back soon.
Yeah, it's about time.
I wonder if things went well with Kae-chan.
A-chan!
I can't anymore.
Impossible! Impossible! Impossible!
Impossible Impossible Impossible Impossible
Impossible!
Jojo?!
Awesome! It's like an otome game! Too good!
Meanie! You're laughing too much, A-chan!
Sorry.
I was a fool to think I could take it easy.
It wasn't easy at all! There
wasn't anything "usual" about it!
It was way too much for me to handle!
Too much?
Well, you know!
This is the best place for me! Right here!
And yet, here I am, thrust into the
center of some otome game-like story!
It's impossible for me!
Calm down, Kae-chan.
It was so much fun working with
everyone to prepare for the festival.
Can we really not stay like that?
It might be tough.
The guys want to make progress
in their relationship with you.
There, there.
Want something to drink?
I'll go buy you something.
Don't worry about coming
back, just chill out here.
Igarashi-kun
Are you okay? Where are you?
It's from Igarashi-kun.
Maybe it was a bad idea
to leave them all behind.
But, going back is hard, too.
Huh? There's no one around.
Oh, look! Isn't it that girl?
It is!
I was just looking at this flyer
and thinking about going.
Lucky!
What's your name?
Wh-What's with these guys?
Oh, no.
I-I'm going back now. I have work to do...
Come on, don't be like that.
Let's have some service.
Let go of me!
Wh-What the hell are you doing?!
I'm sorry! It wasn't on purpose!
Wait!
Don't run away!
H-How did things end up like this?
I hate this! I'm scared!
Jeez! Stop running!
No!
Help me!
Hey!
What are you—
That's my line!
Nana! Behind you!
You think you're funny?
I'm gonna kill you!
What's all the ruckus about?
Are you with them?!
Come on, cut that out.
It's a fight! A fight!
How did this happen?
Why did things turn out this way?
I don't want this at all.
Um. Can you just—
Asshole!
For heaven's sake...
Knock it off!
I'm fed up. This is impossible.
Real life is just... is just...
A shitty game!
Scream
Social Studies Material Room
History Club Exhibit
Edo Castle Land
Uh... Um...
I'm so sorry about what
happened in the haunted house.
It really was an accident, though!
That really shocked me.
So I just bolted out of there...
I'm sorry.
But, being cornered against the wall.
Nana
Being fed...
Mu
Holding hands.
Iga
Getting hugged really tightly.
Shi
Why these little... Can't let
'em out of sight for a second!
I-I just don't have enough of an
immunity for these real life events!
It's just too much!
And then there was that big mess.
I'm just beyond my limits!
Sorry, Serinuma-san. I may have
rushed things a little too much.
I don't want to upset you. So...
How about we take it slow?
I guess that's all there is to it.
At least there's never a dull
moment with this bunch.
I don't have any objections.
Me, neither. I like all of you.
Are you dense?
Huh?
Figures.
Thanks, everyone.
Sorry for going missing!
No, no. You had it hard yourself.
Now for the cultural festival's finale!
The folk dance!
Everyone is free to participate!
Whoever wants to dance,
please partner up and gather in the center!
Serinu—
Let's not have anymore of this today.
Are you really one to talk?
Okay! Let's dance, Nana!
Huh?!
Cut it out!
What's up with them?
Well, shall we go, too?
It'd be a waste not to.
Why?!
A-chan.
Yeah.
This really is the best place we can be.
Yeah!
The Way of the Fujoshi
This is my way of life!
Kae-chan, do you know a
good place to have cake?
Huh? A cake shop? Why?
I thought it'd be nice to have
cake with Mi-kun for Christmas.
But there's no time. Maybe
a reservation somewhere?
I wonder? I always go to events on
Christmas so I don't really know.
Huh? On Christmas?
Yeah! Last year, there was a Noel with
Shion event! We partied together!
By Shion, you mean that cut-out thing?
I have a picture of us together. Want to see?
Next time:
Christmas in the Holy Land
Look forward to it!!
So it really was a cut-out.
A Christmas party devoted to Shion! Amazing!