Hey, Umaru.
What kind of cake should we have for Christmas?
I'm hanging out with friends this year,
so don't worry about it.
O-oh...
Big Brother! If you're gonna make a cake again next year,
you should make a Santa doll too!
On second thought, I WILL have cake
on the 25th so go on, make one!
R-really?
Dude, you're making a cake from scratch?
You're better than most DADS.
Well, I enjoy it...
Taihei, if little Tanukichi wasn't around,
you'd have nothing to do and just shrivel up, huh?
Anyway, it looks like we won't have to work
overtime today, so how about we go somewhere?
And you're overdue to join us, Alex.
I'm going to a Christmas concert of anime songs.
Would you like to come with me?
Tanoshiku nareba ii desu wa
If you can enjoy yourself, that will be good indeed!
Woo-hoo!
Sore nara kitto kachi desu wa
Do that, and you're sure to win indeed!
Woo-hoo!
Just us three?
Christmas will be kinda boring without Tanukichi around.
No, we SHOULD go to that concert.
Huh? For real?
Yes, please!
O-okay...
It's Christmas indeed!
Where should we go?
I-I'm fine with wherever!
Hey, Ebina, you're okay with not
going back to Akita this year?
Yes, it's fine.
I've gone back because
I felt sad ringing in the new year alone...
But with all the fun we've been having together,
I haven't felt lonely at all.
And we shall have fun indeed!
The reason being... it is indeed Christmas!
Sylphin is pretty excited, huh?
It's Christmas! Christmas! Indeed!
What a child...
Don't you celebrate Christmas at home?
Now you, Ebina!
Um, correct! We do not!
"It's Christmas"!
Oh, really?
It's Christmas day...
I'm spending Christmas with Umaru!
WOO-HOO!
Hey, do you want to go see the lights?
Wow...!
These are pretty indeed!
Still...
It's nothing but couples here.
Yeah...
Ah! They're dressed like Santa!
You're right!
They're selling cakes. And...
they're even selling costumes.
Big Brother sure looked pretty sad...
Kyou kara holiday! Mankitsu shichae!
Our holiday starts today! Enjoy it to the fullest!
This is way more fun than I thought it would be, Alex!
I know, right?!
Three-day weekend!
I-I don't really follow...
Wherever you go, there are so many people...
Everyone wants to do something on Christmas, right?
So, do none of you have a special someone
with whom to spend this time?
Ebina, do you have someone?
Huh?! N-no, I don't!
What about you, Kirie?
O-o-of course I don't!
In that case, why don't we all go back to my house?
We'll have a Christmas party!
I thought we were going to talk about relationships,
but she was just inviting us over...
Here we are indeed!
Someone spent a LOT of time decorating...
Kirie, are you all right?
I-I-I... I think so!
You can sit where you like, indeed!
Huh? There's an extra cushion.
Ah! Actually, one more person will be joining us!
Could she mean... Alex?
I've invited my good friend UMR!
What?!
Oh, really?
Wh-who is that?
UMR?
The champion of the gaming world!
And the person who gave me this badge!
Oh, that badge is from a game?
UMR is SO cool!
Is it a guy?
What should I do? Did I promise to meet her today?
And it's thanks to UMR that we were able
to get together like this today!
I haven't had many friends since coming to Japan.
Even after enrolling in school,
I had little idea indeed as to how to make friends.
But then, I learned the Japanese custom of
making friends by challenging others and beating them!
Something's not right here!
I wanted to make friends with Umaru,
which is why I challenged her at school.
But it was UMR who taught me... you don't make friends
by beating them, you do it by having FUN with them.
And the strength of that becomes a dream
that will lead to the future!
Did I ever say that?!
It was UMR's advice that let me
become friends with you all!
It was a lesson well learned:
If something is bothering you, just ask for advice.
Otherwise, you will regret it!
There are indeed many, many things
for UMR and I to discuss!
I'm sure she's worn out.
And I bet...
she decorated this room all by herself.
Let's make sure not to wake her as we leave.
Okay.
Hold on a second.
Oh! Me too!
And YOU, Kirie.
O-oh... O-o-o-okay!
Well, till next time.
Ah! I had a lot of fun today!
From Sylphin...? She woke up?
This was sent two hours ago...
Oh! All these texts being sent
on Christmas must be causing delays.
Is something wrong, Umaru?
No, not at all.
UMR is SO cool! SO cool! SO COOL!
Sorry, Ebina. I left something at Sylphin's house.
Are you okay going home alone?
S-sure!
Sorry!
Huh? Ebina?
T-Taihei!
Weren't you supposed to hang out with Umaru today?
Oh! I was, up until a little while ago.
But she said she forgot something, so...
I can't believe she just left you on your own.
No, I'm perfectly fine!
How about we go back together?
O-okay!
Mom! Look, a couple!
Stop that!
U-um...
It's just, I... I... I...
I'm sorry for putting you out like this.
No, don't worry about it.
It's dangerous to be out alone at night, right?
If something is bothering you, just ask for advice.
Otherwise, you will regret it!
Um, there's something I'd like to talk to you about.
It's...
It's Santa!
Well hello there, Sylphin! Merry Christmas!
Now then, tell me what you'd like for a present. Anything!
Ho-ho-ho!
Really?!
In that case, I... I would like some Japanese friends!
Huh...?
Oh? So, that's what you wished for?
Santa seemed most disturbed!
The old man... I mean, even Santa
couldn't make FRIENDS happen, huh?
But, I want some friends
I can talk to about Japan, indeed!
Just ask for a computer once you're in middle school.
You can talk to people from Japan
just by using the internet.
Is this true?!
Look.
This is my Japanese friend, Shinra Rasenken Sirius.
That's an impressive name indeed!
And I'll be able to meet him soon.
Huh? Brother, you're going to Japan?
Yup. I'll be going to high school there.
School... in Japan?
I'm sure you'll be a little sad when Alex leaves.
You two have always been close...
Big Brother!
Brother's friend...?
UMH is unstoppable!
That is one fearsome Japanese fighter!
This hard-fought battle has forged mutual respect!
By challenging others, one can make friends...
such admirable fighting spirit!
Merry Christmas, Sylphin!
Here, it's a fighting game controller!
Indeed, made by HORU!
She sure has started to want some strange things...
Thank you so much, Santa!
Huh? Santa?
Oh, no. I fell asleep.
What...?
Today was so much fun, Sylphin!
I was very happy that you invited me.
M-m-merry Christmash!
I guess they've all gone home.
Sylphin!
Merry Christmas, TSF.
Santa...? UMR, why are you dressed like that?
Well, I saw them selling these,
so... d-does it look okay on me?
I'm sorry I'm late. Um, do you mind if I come in?
I want a Japanese friend indeed!
Yes!
Happy New Year...
Happy...
Here. For you.
WOO-HOO!
Thanks, Big Brother! It's not like you
to hand this out first thing in the morning!
Uh... sure.
Huh? Is he still half-asleep?
Well, let's eat!
Let's eat.
Oh, yeah...
Here, Umaru. It's your New Year's allowance.
Wh-what sorcery is this?!
Am I being tested?
What's wrong? You don't seem happy at all.
Ah!
Thank you, Big Brother!
I got TWO of them...
and I sure am grateful!
It's like when a vending machine messes up
and gives you two drinks instead of one.
Would you, dear Consumer, pay for both?
No, you wouldn't!
This mistake is all on my brother!
The thing is...
Take yer average ramen shop.
What if you order one bowl but you friggin' get TWO?
I sure feel lucky to have gotten two!
Thanks, that was great!
But you gotta pay for that other one, right?
Otherwise, the fault now lies with YOU!
Hold it right there!
Think about game arcades!
If I put in one coin but end up getting two prizes,
they're both still mine!
That's just the nature of the game, right?
And life is like a game, right?!
"Life" is about goals and aimin' for the top!
Life is Cannalad!
More to the point, why would Big Brother
have prepared TWO envelopes?
Yeah, he should only need one, right?
That's true...
Ah-ha! This whole time, something has felt off.
Two envelopes... Big Brother spacing out...
It can only mean...!
"Can only mean"?!
That he'd planned on giving two
New Year's allowances all along!
Guess I'll give her two this year.
Wh-what was that?!
Big Brother...?
Oh, Ebina.
Um, Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
U-um, I hope I can be of help to you this year as well.
Yeah, same here.
Um-!
U-um... i-is Umaru here?
Yes, but... she's still asleep.
Hey, I'm awake! These two are acting WEIRD!
Oh! I have a New Year's gift for you.
Huh?! N-no, I couldn't!
It's no trouble. Hold on a second.
Let's see...
Huh? That's strange. I put it right here, next to Umaru's.
La-la-laaa...
Sorry it's not in an envelope.
Ebina said she's going to check out the New Year's sales.
O-oh.
Um, Big Brother? Let's talk about vending machines...
Huh? Where did Taihei go?
He got called to the meeting room a little while ago.
The meeting room? That's unusual.
He seemed quite happy, though.
Huh? Your brother said that?
Yeah. He gets all mad if I leave even a small mess.
By a "small mess," does she mean...?
Come on, Umaru, you need to put this away.
It really was small.
Umaru! I told you to clean up after yourself!
He really is too strict.
Still...
he's a good listener, and he's really kind.
Huh? A "listener"?
Ah! N-no, never mind.
Ebina sure is nice...
All Big Brother ever does is get mad!
Still, that's not to say I'm entirely without fault...
Huh? It turns out Big Brother is SUPER nice!
On the other hand, I'm just...
Get me some cola and potato chips.
Oh, and more manga, okay?
Yup, I ate yours too!
Come on! Just one more billing charge!
I might... actually be selfish!
From the outside looking in,
all I do is push Big Brother around!
This is bad... I have to do something!
I'm home.
Welcome back, Big Brother!
I'm sure you've had a long day at work!
Wait, what's going on?
Come on, just have a seat...
Umaruuuuun!
and welcome to the Umaru-style Space of Happiness!
Hurry up and step right in, Big Brother!
Umaru, I need to talk to you.
Huh?
I have to go on a business trip.
Huh...?
So you... you won't be coming back?
Yeah. I got chosen as a member of the project team,
and I'll have to go out of town.
I won't be able to come back here for a while.
No! You can't leave me, Big Brother!
I'm sorry.
No! You can't just leave and not come back!
I'm sorry, Umaru. I'm worried about this too,
but the decision has been made.
How long will you be gone? A month? Wait, a year?!
Two...
Two weeks.
Two weeks...?
Yeah. If I'm gone for two weeks,
you'll make a real mess around here, right?
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT?!
And, wait! What makes you think I'll make a mess?!
You always do, right?
Yeah, but... look, just get out and stay gone,
for at least two weeks!
Tanukichi! It sure is fun to enjoy Christmas
with some anime songs, right?!
Bomba, you finally get it, huh?
I GET TO ENJOY THE SEASON EVEN THOUGH
I DON'T HAVE A GIRLFRIEND!
IS ANYONE OUT THERE LISTENING?!
Stop that! There are people crying
in front of their TVs right now!