Come in.
I feel bad for the people at Globe.
They don't know that you're the one
choosing all the participants in the Kivotos Plan.
Indeed.
I feel bad for CEO Kube.
I'm sure he never even dreamed
that we were using him...
Albion may have an attachment
to his avatar body.
I don't mind mine.
This is a ten-year-old photograph of a
Seton Company research facility
in the Hawaiian Islands.
It was cleverly hidden, but they're
a Macbeth Enterprises subsidiary.
These two.
We believe they are the two
that attacked yesterday.
Then it was indeed Macbeth Enterprises.
These two are designer children, right?
And they were overseas during the Kanda incident.
Then all six that were taken in,
except Teppei Arashi, are missing.
Just like Teppei, the other designer children
can use the Machine Goodfellows
to become Kiltgangs.
I think the fact that the Kiltgangs
have entered their active phase
suggests that their preparations are complete.
Why don't they attack more frequently?
When Teppei became a Kiltgang,
Hana used the energy built up in the Blume.
Teppei says that
the craft equivalent to the Kiltgang
mothership is orbiting Uranus.
They've run out of energy, and can't move.
So they're using the Machine Goodfellows
to get the energy they need
from the people of Earth.
The human libido... Orgone energy.
Anyway, we won't notify HQ about this yet.
If Salty Dog learns about the relationship between
the Machine Goodfellows and the Kiltgangs,
they might decide to detonate
a nuclear bomb themselves
in Tokyo, where Macbeth has offices,
and blame it on terrorists.
And even if that saved the rest of humanity,
you wouldn't accept it, would you?
Anyway,
it's peculiar that word of such a huge danger
hasn't leaked to the public yet.
During the Cuban Missile Crisis...
The media said that if the Russians
brought nuclear missiles to Cuba,
it would incite a full-scale nuclear war.
In the end, the Soviets gave in,
and the danger was averted.
Publicly, at least.
In truth, however, the Soviets had already
sent over one hundred missiles there.
Only the President and a few
of his close advisors knew,
and the truth wasn't revealed until
thirty years after the Cold War ended.
It's strange that news of such a dire
threat never leaked to the public.
Why tell the public they might
have only five minutes to live?
If a thing is truly dangerous, it's kept secret.
Throughout history, that's happened many times.
Ta-da!
Snack time!
Watermelon again?
Is that a problem?
Not at all.
Times like these won't continue for much longer.
Pitz was saying that.
It's nice you can talk to Pitz.
It makes you seem like a heroine.
If even a single Kiltgang makes it to Earth,
it will drain all humanity of their libidos.
I think so, yeah...
When I first sensed them,
I had this awful feeling.
Well, if we need him, we have Teppei.
To be honest, if I become a
Kiltgang again, I don't know
if I'll return to who I am now.
At any rate, we shouldn't underestimate them.
Didn't the Planetary Gears try
to make you fire the Livlaster
because they wanted infinite energy, Hana?
Yeah.
And none of them can fire the Livlaster?
Right.
You know,
we're pretty amazing, talking about this
stuff while eating our watermelon.
We are, aren't we?
And get this... I have melons, too.
Melons!
Melons?
But the melons are for tomorrow.
I'm so disappointed.
Tomorrow, let's all eat together again.
For now, why not eat?
Melons...
Pitz?
I saved the seeds, Pitz.
What's wrong, Pitz?
The Kiltgang are going to act?
"Soon," he says.
Who says?
Pitz.
Th-The squirrel?
At the moment, there's no
sign of any AEO or NEO.
He says he knows the rough
time and the location
where the Orgone energy will be used.
Shall we request a nuclear strike on this area?
They aren't there yet.
But they'll act tonight.
Commander!
Daichi Manatsu is standing by
in the Earth Engine's cockpit.
The Earth Engine is fixed now, isn't it?
What are you thinking, Daichi?
I learned the basic controls in the simulator.
Science Chief!
His Earth Driver training was ordered by HQ.
He's been doing it for a while.
How will that stopgap training help?
You almost died twice...
Aren't you scared?
I'm scared.
Actually, I'm really scared.
After all, I'm only a teenager.
But if I don't defeat them,
we have no hope.
And hope is only born of choices.
Please begin the launch sequence.
The lights of these foolish people...
I can't imagine that Albion
would betray us for them.
Can you even imagine not being immortal?
No way.
This really is the greatest!
AEO sighted... It's a Kiltgang.
Manifestation point in Gamma sector,
inside defensive zone 1.
It really did appear.
Wow...
Is this predictive ability your singularity?
Pitz told me, that's all.
Pitz doesn't lie.
The ability to predict the use of Orgone energy?
Pegasus rocket taking off.
The Earth Engine's energy is charging!
The Pegasus rocket is purging Earth Engine.
Earth Engine, expand!
The one from the first time?
Earth Engine has made contact with the Kiltgang!
Its attacks aren't hitting!
If it could land a hit, we could shoot it down...
Abreaction.
Something else is coming?
Daichi is in danger?
Teppei, come with me!
I...
Please, Teppei...
Help Daichi!
If I return to that body,
I don't think I'll be able to stay who I am!
Suck-It-Up Forte!
Quit dilly-dallying!
You need to get this done,
so we can have our melon tomorrow, right?
The four of us are eating it together.
It has to be all four of us!
Tomorrow, let's all eat together again.
Protect Daichi for me, Teppei...
Amarok, huh?
Another Kiltgang!
It's the Type-1!
A voice that resounds throughout infinity
sings a melody of gentle memories.
I'm counting on you two.
The light of the promise
I know we once shared.
These guys...
In close quarters, you're at a disadvantage.
Try to keep your distance, Daichi!
You're mine!
Daichi!
Teppei...
Albion, are you going to betray us?
I am your opponent!
Today's the day I devour every last Earthling,
and snap Albion out of whatever's gotten into him!
And you're first.
Crap!
Daichi!
Shoot through both of us, Malkin.
That's right...
As long as our Ego Blocks survive, we won't die.
Because you're Albion, you're the same way.
But what about that Earthling?
I'll shoot, whether you move or not, Albion.
After all, you won't die.
I am Teppei Arashi.
I am...
Teppei Arashi!
No way!
His Ego Block...
An Ego Block explosion?
Teppei destroyed his own Ego Block?
Teppei...
Impossible!
That destroyed the vernier thrusters
on both legs, huh?
I don't have the momentum to take him out.
What do I do?
Are you the one who made Albion crazy, Neoteny?!
Use this.
You know what to do, Daichi?
So that's it?
What?
Teppei...
Albion destroyed his own Ego Block.
It's been a hell of a night.
My Machine Goodfellow broke, too...
Is Teppei safe?
His pulse, temperature, brainwaves,
and blood pressure are all nominal...
For a normal human.
Teppei!
Teppei, what's that in your hand?
This is...
A Livlaster?
This is the third one, then.
Are you canceling the request for
Akari to be a Kivotos sleeper
out of respect for her wishes?
That's part of it...
But not everything.
You've always been too stubborn
to listen to anyone.
Honestly, her personality is just like yours.
My personality isn't as nasty as hers.
You've found some hope, haven't you?
Why do you think so?
I can tell...
You're my ex-husband, after all.
I'll leave Akari to you.
Thank you.
I've reported the situation
to HQ's Supreme Council,
and they've agreed to keep it classified for now.
I got them to allow Hana to stay here, also.
Both HQ and your wife trust
you on a very deep level.
Ex-wife.
What do you think, Commander?
Thanks, Teppei.
I...
You beat Amarok.
You're really amazing, Daichi.
You keep surprising me.
So here.
Daichi Manatsu.
Teppei Arashi.
Hana Mutou.
Akari Yomatsuri.
I hereby designate you members of the Globe
Tanegashima base's independent attack force,
the Midsummer's Knights.
Midsummer's...
Knights?
"Manatsu" means "Midsummer."
Then that's it?
Daichi Manatsu,
I'm officially designating you
driver of the Earth Engine.
And you are the leader of this team.
From now on, you are Captain Earth!
What does a captain do?
For now, let's eat our melons.
The Midsummer's Knights
battle the Planetary Gears.
That's us!
Hana's predictive abilities send
us to a casino in Odaiba,
where we find Amarok and Malkin.
And a new member of the
Planetary Gears awakens.
Next time, on episode 8 of Captain Earth:
Sign From the Dark
Sign From the Dark.
Earth Engine, scramble!