The water is alive.
Once you dive in, it will immediately
bare its fangs and attack.
But there's nothing to fear.
Don't resist the water.
Thrust your fingers into the surface
and carve an opening.
Then you slide your body
through that opening.
Moving your arms, your head, your chest...
His swimming always looks so smooth.
Yep, like a dolphin!
Who's that?
Matsuoka Rin-kun.
He transferred into our class last week.
Nobody can beat you when
you're in the water, Haru-chan.
Stop calling me -chan already.
That was so cool, Nanase-kun!
I wanna swim like you!
You're as fast as the rumors said.
What was your time?
I don't care about my time.
That's just like the rumors said, too.
Hey, Nanase.
You interested
in entering a relay with me
at the next tournament?
I only do freestyle.
That's right, I don't care
about swimming faster times.
All I want is to feel the water.
With my skin, my eyes, my soul...
To never doubt what it makes me feel.
Believe in myself.
Don't resist the water.
Welcome it.
We accept one another.
Yeah...
There was some funky stuff going
through my head back then.
There's an old saying my
late grandma taught me.
When you're ten, they
call you a prodigy.
When you're fifteen,
they call you a genius.
Once you hit twenty, you're
just an ordinary person.
About three years until I'm ordinary.
Man...
I can't wait to be ordinary.
Reunion at the Starting Block!
Good morning, Tamura-san.
Good morning, Makoto-chan.
Take this with you.
Oh, thanks.
See ya around!
Take care now.
Good morning.
Oh, come on...
Excuse me.
Naturally, he's here.
I'm coming in.
Good morning, Haru-chan.
I told you to lay off the -chan.
You were in the bath with
your swimsuit on again?
Buzz off.
You're gonna be late.
That's my line.
Wait, why are you grilling fish?!
I haven't had breakfast.
And you're wearing an
apron over a swimsuit.
Aren't you cold?
I don't want to get oil on my swimsuit.
Toast and fish?
So?
Why did you come get me?
You didn't show up for the
opening assembly yesterday.
I called in sick.
Do you know which class you're in, then?
We're in the same class again.
Class 1.
We've got a new lady as
our homeroom teacher.
They already gave her a nickname.
She teaches classical literature,
but she's a little on the odd side.
It needs to get warmer so
I can swim in the ocean.
I hope it gets warmer
soon so you can swim.
Mr. Tadokoro Junichi.
Here.
Miss Tezuka Kaori.
Nanase Haruka
Um...
Miss Nanase Haruka.
I'm used to being mistaken for a girl.
Ma'am, Haruka's a guy.
Oh, you're right!
I'm sorry, Nanase-kun.
No worries.
You were absent yesterday, right?
I'm Amakata Miho, your
new homeroom teacher.
Nice to meet you.
I heard Miss Ama-chan is from this area.
She went to college in Tokyo
and found a job there,
but she came back after
her dream fell through.
What was her dream?
Beats me. Maybe she
wanted to go into music?
We're supposed to be
learning from a woman
who became a teacher as plan B?
I want to go home.
So, lunch...
Wanna eat on the roof?
He needs to get a clue.
Gou, what are you doing? Hurry up!
Hold on!
And don't call me Gou!
Sorry!
I didn't bring lunch.
Go buy something, then?
Or do you want some of this?
Squid.
Haru-chan! Mako-chan!
It's been forever!
I'll be joining you here
at Iwatobi High School.
Mako-chan?
Haru-chan?
Nagisa?!
How many years has it been?
I don't think I saw you after the
swimming club was shut down.
Yep, because I went to a different school.
There are cherry blossom
trees next to the pool!
Weren't there cherry blossom
trees next to the pool
at your grade school, Haru-chan?
Can you stop calling me that?
But that's your name, Haru-chan.
But that pool is old and not in use.
There's no swim club, either.
Where do you swim, then?
I quit swimming competitively.
What?!
Why'd you quit?!
I was all excited about getting to
swim with you again in high school!
We're not little kids anymore.
Things aren't the way they used to be.
Haru-chan...
Well, he stopped swimming competitively,
but he still loves water.
Haru can't live without being in water.
During the summer, he
swims in the ocean,
and he was soaking in
the tub this morning.
What does that have
to do with swimming?
That just means he likes baths.
I know! How about a hot springs club?
Let's start a hot springs club!
I can't stand the heat.
Nagisa hasn't changed one bit.
Don't be like that!
No.
Okay, then...
I refuse.
I didn't say anything yet.
Aw, I should have gotten
the same thing you did.
Hey, have you heard?
The swimming club we went to in grade
school is gonna be torn down soon.
So before that happens,
why don't we pay a visit?
To dig that up?
Exactly!
We can sneak in at night...
You can go by yourself.
Don't say that!
Come with us, Haru-chan.
I'm not going.
Don't you think it'll be fun?
I don't.
Why don't you just humor him?
No, it's too much effort.
But there's a pool there.
A pool is much bigger than a bathtub.
Wow...
You live by yourself, Haru-chan?
His mom went with his dad when
he had to move because of work.
Wait, fish again?
Nobody's forcing you to eat it.
Looks delicious.
Haru-chan was always a good cook.
So, are you sure about this?
Weren't you all for it earlier?
Are you getting scared?
It's not that.
Is it okay for just the
three of us to dig it up?
Can't do anything about that.
Rin-chan isn't in Japan anymore.
I won't be attending middle school here.
Huh? What do you mean, Rin?
I'm going to Australia.
You mean you're going
to a different country?
Yep, I'm going to a swimming school.
What are you trying to do?
I'm going to become an Olympic swimmer.
Why didn't you tell us?
What about the relay?
I'll swim in the relay.
I'm leaving the day after the tournament.
So this will be the last time
the four of us swim together.
I only swim freestyle.
That's why you have
to swim in the relay.
This is our last chance.
Let's swim together, Nanase.
If you swim with me,
I'll show you a sight
you've never seen before.
The place is pretty trashed.
Here, just in case.
Purifying salt.
Salt?
They say the place is haunted.
Don't scare me.
I'm not lying.
People have been seeing
shadows moving around
and hearing sobbing voices.
Stand still.
Okay. You're next, Haru-chan.
Hey.
Wh-What is it?
This isn't salt. It's sugar.
Well, it's all mental anyway,
so sugar will still get the job done.
Clichéd as hell.
It is one of the oldest mistakes out there.
What?!
My foot hit an empty can.
You're doing this on purpose, aren't you?!
You always were scared of the dark.
You're not helping any!
Sorry.
This brings back memories.
It's not as trashed inside as I expected.
This is...
The lounge.
Hurry up!
Look.
This is the picture from
when we won the relay.
I'll show you a sight
you've never seen before.
The four of us won this together,
so it doesn't make sense for
one person to take it home.
So let's put it in a time capsule
and dig it up when we're grown up.
Romantic, right?
Haru...
Let's go, Haru.
Yeah...
Think the marker is still there?
Can we pick up the pace a little?
Yo.
Huh? Who's there?
I can't tell.
I didn't think I'd run
into you guys here.
Rin!
Rin-chan!
You're back from Australia!
What are you doing here, though?
This must be fate!
Some unseen force brought
us all here at this exact—
Haru, you're still hanging
out with these guys?
You never learn.
What are you talking about, Rin?
And what about you?
Have you learned anything?
Haru?
I'm glad you asked.
Why don't I show you?
Let's race, Haru.
Race?
Wait, Haru!
Did they just ditch us?
Looks like it.
Wait!
I'll show you how different we are now.
Sure.
Go ahead.
They're going to swim here?
Wait, hold on.
Haru, that's a bad idea!
Wait, you've been wearing
that the whole day?!
Rin-chan too?
We have to stop them!
Do we really?
Hey!
Let's do this, Haru!
Ready,
go—
There isn't any water.
That's why I told you to stop.
Lame.
Oh, yeah. Did you guys
come here for this?
Oh, our trophy.
I don't need this thing anymore.
Hey!
Rin-chan...
He's kinda changed.
A dream?
No, it wasn't a dream!
I don't get it though.
Rin-chan was really weird.
Look-alike.
Why would a look-alike
challenge you to a race?
A ghost, then.
He wasn't floating.
Doppelganger.
Oh, that takes me back!
We used to do that at the swimming
club! Super Fusion: Doppelga—
Keep it down, Makoto.
What's wrong with you guys?!
Sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
Hey!
Do you know those guys?
Uh-huh.
Don't you remember, Haru?
Nanase Haruka.
No.
Tachibana Makoto.
What? Why not?
Hazuki Nagisa.
What they have in common is
Must be a generation gap.
that they used to belong to
the same swimming club.
I'm only one year older than you!
And Haru's the same age as me!
And they're all boys with girlish names.
What's your relationship with them?
That's a secret.
That means you have something
in common with them, too.
Since you're a girl with a boyish name.
Seriously. Stop calling me Gou!
Faculty Office
Come on!
The place may be abandoned,
but it's still trespassing if
you enter without permission!
Do you understand?
I apologize.
We're sorry.
Huh? Where's Nanase?
He left early this afternoon.
Again?
Now, now. I think that's enough.
Think back to what Li Bai once said.
In human life, accomplishment
must bring total joy.
Do not allow an empty
goblet to face the moon.
You only have one life, so
you should do what you want.
It would be foolish not to drink
from the glass placed before you.
Right?
Huh?
Matsuoka Rin, Matsuoka Rin...
Does he really go to our school?
If he's back from Australia,
he might have transferred
into our school.
But I didn't see him at
the opening ceremony.
Matsuoka
Found him!
Really?
No, hold on.
Matsuoka Gou
Matsuoka Gou?
That sounds familiar...
I remember now!
That was Rin's sister, Matsuoka Gou!
So you also chose Iwatobi
High School, Gou-chan.
Don't call me Gou. Everybody calls me Kou.
Huh? Why?
Your name is Gou, like the Sengoku warlord
Azai Nagamasa's third daughter, right?
Yeah...
But the typical reading
is Kou, so call me that.
That would be the nice thing to do.
Uh, putting that stuff aside...
That stuff?!
Sorry.
But what are you doing at Haru's place?
Oh...
I wanted to ask him about my brother.
So Rin is really back from Australia?
He returned last month and he's
attending Samezuka Academy now.
It's a boarding school,
so he hasn't come home.
Samezuka?
The swimming powerhouse?
No.
Let's visit Samezuka Academy!
Don't you want to see Rin?
We saw him yesterday.
Here I was thinking you'd finally
get to swim if you came.
Samezuka is supposed to
have an indoor pool.
Samezuka Academy
Hey! You're slowing down, Nakagawa!
Move!
Do you see Rin-chan?
Can't find him.
Maybe he's out today.
Hey, Haru...
Don't take your clothes off here!
You're the one who brought
me here to swim!
Hold on, Haru-chan.
Let's wait until practice is
over and everyone's gone.
Okay?
We'll still be trespassing.
It'll be fine.
That teacher earlier told us to
do what we want with our li—
Can't you wait?!
I still think this is a bad idea.
Wait!
Come on...
Haru-chan still reminds me of a dolphin.
Mako-chan, let's swim with him.
Hell no! We'll get in trouble if they find us!
Anyway, we need to look for Rin.
We can take a little dip first.
Nobody will find us if we
don't turn on the lights.
But you didn't bring a swimsuit.
A little skinny dip, then.
What?!
I can swim!
Hey, wait!
Mako-chan, come over here.
What now?
I'm not gonna join you—
You gotta be kidding me!
You looked like an elephant falling in.
Seriously...
Nagisa...
Take that!
Hey!
There!
Take that!
Take that—
What are you guys doing here?
Rin!
We came here to see you.
Get out!
Rin-chan...
Free...
Huh?
Did you forget?
I told you that I only swim freestyle.
Haru-chan?
Haru...
About three years until I'm ordinary.
I guess it couldn't hurt
to wait a little longer.
I want you to show me that sight again.
I've forgotten what it was that I saw.
Sure, I can do that.
But it won't be the same this time.
I'll be showing you something
completely different.
So is there a reason Nanase-san
can only swim freestyle?
Haru-chan doesn't want to answer.
Mako-chan, can you answer for him?
Uh...
Should I use salt or miso on my fish?
He's thinking about dinner!
Next time: Memories in the Distance.
Memories in the Distance!
You even did the preview for him?
I'm up for some Meuniere sauce.