This is Maison de Ayakashi.
Also known as Ayakashi Kan.
Yes...
Yes. Is that so?
I understand.
I'll say it one more time. This is...
...Ayakashi Kan.
Everything is fine.
Please do not worry.
I will do everything
in my power to protect you, Miss Ririchiyo.
minutes
earlier
.
Thank you, Miss Ririchiyo.
It was an honor to be allowed
Their Night Alone
to receive you after school again today.
I shall come for you again, for the next meal.
Today is the day
I will tell Miketsukami how grateful I am!
You won that in a supermarket raffle?
Yup, hit the jackpot!
Not bad, huh?
Chino is so cute,
with her maid costume and
her smug little face!
Where should I put it?
I'll help you find a place!
I'm heading out.
Chino, turn around.
Chino...
Maybe I should put it in the lounge...
Why don't we go together?
Hey.
Is that...
This is a...
Both of you, this way!
This is...
Excuse me.
Hurry, Chino.
Wait...
Hurry up, you idiot.
Do I sense discrimination here?
I do apologize.
What was that?
Wh-What?
Huh?
Yes, you be careful, too.
It appears that everyone is safe.
That's good.
Seems like they're fine.
Okay.
Wh-What's going on?
It looks like Ayakashi Kan's security
system has been activated.
S-Security system?
To put it simply,
a force field is activated
to protect the occupants
whenever an enemy tries
to enter the premises.
It's pretty amazing that it
was in the flowerpot...
It was probably in a dormant state.
A dormant state?
She really is too cute!
That's just another way of
saying it was asleep.
That's why it could enter without
any of us noticing.
I don't really understand all that,
but does that mean it's my fault?
I'm very sorry!
It's not your fault.
Anyway, look...
We have many more force fields,
and each is bound to one door
and one security base.
See that, over there?
That floating security base is proof
that the field is working properly.
So even without blocking
the entrance like that,
it wouldn't be able to come in here,
as long as all the doors are closed.
And what if we open a door?
If even one is opened,
the force field is weakened.
Then I won't open any.
The monster will be gone by morning,
and the security system will reset.
So we just need to hang on until then.
Yeah!
Until morning, it's carnival.
You mean survival.
Something like that.
That's the deal,
so you should listen to me until morning.
Can you keep that promise with Mr. Rabbit?
The end!
And that's it!
But...
Why do you look like that?
Shut up!
It was sudden, so I got startled
and transformed! That's all!
But never mind that. Where's Karuta?
Where's Karuta?
What do you mean?
She's under a different force field.
Karuta!
You mustn't break your
promise to Mr. Rabbit!
So, is this a dangerous monster?
Very much so.
Words cannot describe how terrible it is.
Really?
Yes.
Well, it looks like we have no choice
but to spend the night here.
That's true...
It's what I said, but...
Isn't this too carefree?!
I knew you hadn't had your dinner yet.
Don't! I'll do it myself!
Where did you find this, anyway?
It was over there.
Over where?
Well? Where was it?
Huh?
Over there.
It's going to be a long night.
Miss Nobara!
I found all these over there!
Yay!
Yes! It's going to be a long night!
I'm going to go and protect Karuta!
How?
She's in another force field, right?
I'll go over there.
I don't care what happens
to this force field.
I'll open the door of fate, to save Karuta!
It won't open?
Wrong!
Is it this one?
Sorry, but no...
Where's the door?!
Who can say?
Do you really not know?
How mean!
A rabbit never lies.
But...
Karuta.
But there's something you
can do for Karuta here.
Huh?
This force field is set up
like an infinite hallway.
In here, time moves separately
from the outside world.
One hour in here equals one day outside.
More like two, to be precise.
There are actually quite a few places
well-suited for training.
Really?
Take this hallway.
The floor is quite wavy and perfect
for honing your sense of balance.
If you train until morning,
you'll get stronger for sure.
I see.
Which brings me to this.
Don't let anyone say you're a wimp again.
Let's train!
For Karuta.
Karuta!
Good luck!
You're always so calm.
Is that how I seem?
You don't look any different than normal.
That's actually not true.
When I think about the fact
that I get to serve you in this
room until morning,
I couldn't possibly stay calm.
Is that so?
Then calm down.
We can't open the windows or the doors.
I'm in this room with him until morning...
Wh-What am I even thinking?
This is why I hate puberty.
Wait a minute.
This is a chance to tell him how grateful I am.
That's right...
If you're in a good mood, then I'm happy, too.
Mother Earth. It's been over
4.5 billion years since...
Here you go, Nekozuki.
Why do I have to hang out with you guys?
This is great...
It's like a joyous family gathering.
I never thought I'd experience one again.
Why don't you sit down?
You don't want to do that.
Oops, I sounded a bit gloomy there.
Get mixed up with me, and you'll get hurt.
I'm sorry.
Right, partner?
I'm sorry. He's always like that.
Dad, why don't you come here?
Miss Nobara, isn't that going too fast?
What about here?
B-But that's...
You're adorable...
But I told you to be gentle
because it's my first time.
Now I know what to do, too.
Chino, you're wonderful!
You know exactly where to go...
Checkmate!
I win!
I am the champion!
Can we play cards now?
I want to play cards!
But I don't know how to play...
I'll teach you!
One more thing...
How should I thank him?
Maybe this isn't the right time.
Stop chickening out!
Miss Ririchiyo,
would you like to have your bath now?
A bath? At a time like this?
We're stuck here until morning.
I think it could help you relax.
I guess you have a point. All right.
Please take your time.
Oh, yeah... I still have to thank him!
Miketsukami...
Yes?
Th-Thank you, I suppose.
I'm just doing my job.
Wrong!
However...
I really ought to go with you,
to help you wash your back,
but because I am a male,
that remains impossible for me.
No problem. Don't worry about it.
Once I get out of the bath...
All right!
And...
Where did this come from?
It was over there.
What?
Being allowed to gaze upon
your form clad like that
is like a dream.
Good for you.
You look so cute.
I wish I could preserve this moment.
Take a picture. It lasts longer.
Mind if I make it my wallpaper?
No way!
May I blow it up and hang it on my wall?
Certainly not!
Why don't you take a bath, too?
I cannot.
I am a dog.
For me to enter the same
bathroom as you,
to use the same water as you,
would be unthinkable.
It's fine. You don't have to.
I've made your bed for you.
I'm not sleepy yet.
Miketsukami...
Yes?
Y-You are...
You aren't going to sleep yet?
No!
I shan't.
I shall stay awake until morning,
to protect you.
Would you like to lie down, though?
That might help you relax.
Y-Yes.
I suppose I shall do that.
I'll be over there.
So if you need anything, just call for me.
Y-Yes.
Good night.
Yeah.
What are you...
Is something wrong?
Nothing! My mistake!
Sorry! Ignore me!
He really isn't going to sleep all night?
Miketsukami?
Yes?
Don't worry about me.
Just go to sleep if you get tired.
Please get some rest and
do not concern yourself over me.
Miketsukami...
Yes?
Today...
was quite hard, wasn't it?
I didn't mean that!
Not at all.
I have school tomorrow, also.
What am I babbling about?
Miketsukami.
Yes?
Thank you...
I'm not worthy of such words.
I already told you.
I exist solely for you.
If I can't protect you, I have no meaning.
After all, I am your dog.
He actually said that to someone like me.
That's
precisely
why
.
I want
to
reciprocate
.
I think it's nearly dawn.
I did it!
But it really feels like the
training is working.
It really is different inside the force field...
Huh?
You believed all that?
But I had to say that, or you would have
worried about Karuta all night...
That's the door.
So that's where it was!
Then...
Miketsukami!
It looks like one of the doors was opened.
What's going on?
Stop getting in my way, would you?
Watanuki, what are we gonna do?
Don't worry... I'm a delinquent!
Watanuki...
Karuta!
What the...
They're weak...
Sou!
Chiyo!
It's you guys!
Yup.
Chiyo...
Sou!
I thought I'd never see you again...
I'm glad you're all right, Natsume.
What are you all doing here?
Natsume brought us here.
Some idiot broke the force field,
so we thought it would be quicker
to wipe out the invaders.
Wipe them out?
Isn't that dangerous?
I think it's more of a bother than dangerous.
What does this mean, Miketsukami?
Well...
Earlier, you said...
The Obariyon is also known as
the piggyback monster.
It appears on dark paths at night,
and jumps on your back.
They say it won't do much more than that.
Get off me...
I said get off!
Ririchiyo!
Miss Ririchiyo, I am so sorry that
I allowed you to endure that.
That's fine.
But didn't you say this was some
really terrible monster?!
It is...
Just the thought of such a
creature touching you...
It's morning.
And that's that.
Looks like it's over...
That was quite fun.
There's no endless night. Right, partner?
Let's sleep.
Yes! We survived the carnival!
Next time I'll teach you
a more naughty game.
Don't you want to show them
the fruits of your training?
Shut up!
I'm going to eat breakfast.
Miss Ririchiyo,
let's return to your room.
Let's do that.
Hello, everyone!
My name is Chino Kotomura,
and I'm a maid at Ayakashi Kan.
I love to clean!
Hey, this isn't an introduction for you,
but a preview for the next episode.
Are you sure you can do this?
Of course I can!
The next episode is about how Ririchiyo,
all steamy after taking a bath,
invites Miketsukami in, during the
middle of the night.
I don't think that's quite accurate...
Next time, on Inu X Boku Secret Service:
Tea and Distance.
I did it! Oh, yeah!
Why do you look so smug?
Tea and Distance