I asked you to go get the
corruption for me, didn't I?
You have that much trouble
with a simple errand?
Well, fine.
I did get to have a glimpse of him.
If you don't want your apprentice
to be turned into an ingredient,
don't mess up next time.
Master, why do you listen to that psycho?
He took your arm!
You don't need to concern yourself.
A master protects his apprentice.
Have faith in me.
But...
It's fine.
I have a plan.
Wasn't I supposed to protect you?
One mandrake petal.
Please.
Sound, sound through the night forest.
Sing, sing, young hawthorns.
Let your thorns pierce the creeping hooves.
Chise.
When do you think you can finish the order
for the old lady at the foot of the hill?
I just finished mixing a pint of hops and five
leaves of lavender for the insomnia pillow.
And this is an enchanted potion
for warding off nightmares.
Just as I taught you.
You used too much magic.
It's turned into a sleeping potion.
Work a little harder on the proportions.
Okay.
This is hard.
Since I learned of his goal,
Elias seems to have decided
to begin seriously teaching me magic.
What has an effect on what, what needs to be
helped along, and what needs to be avoided...
Strange traditions from long ago.
Things that can be both
medicinal and poisonous.
Wooly bugs, aethonic...
Chise, we're going out for a while.
Okay.
A black dog?
Yeah.
Also known as a church grim.
An excellent watchdog who protects
the church and the graveyard.
One seems to have made himself
at home at a nearby church.
Our task is to see if he's hostile or not.
There are hostile ones?
They're fine so long as
you don't do anything.
Usually.
Usually?
This is the third one.
Their last request.
Why does the church, um...
Why do they ask you to do things?
I made a mistake a while ago.
They've had an eye on me ever since.
I don't like dealing with them,
so I take care of some of their business
in exchange for their leaving me alone.
Come to think of it, that man
called Elias by a different name.
Pilum Murialis.
There's so much I don't know about him.
Right, I forgot.
Chise.
I'd asked Angelica to make this for you.
A ring?
You know why Sleigh Beggies
are short-lived, don't you?
We're frail despite our strong ability
to create and soak up magic, right?
Right.
So what you need is a ring to slow
down your production of magic.
However, the ring can only do so much.
Become excited, and it'll function more
actively, just as your body does.
So, stay as calm as you can.
Okay.
It's all right.
As your buyer, I'm responsible for you.
I'll look for better solutions.
Thank you.
The right index finger
is the guiding finger.
P.S. You're not ready for
your left ring finger!
Elias hasn't really said anything
about what happened since then.
Chise.
Coming.
I'd like to assign a familiar to you soon.
A familiar?
A creature that consumes its
master's magic, and serves them.
They're useful and loyal,
and would make great servants.
Like the one at Angie-san's place?
They get to be more familiar with their
masters than the masters themselves.
They'd be perfect for supporting
someone as quiet as you are.
S-Sorry.
Look, we're here.
That's the church.
Has something happened?
Elias?
This could be a bit complicated.
We may need to hurry.
I'll go talk to the ones in charge here.
Go take a look around.
Let me know if you find anything.
Don't put yourself in danger.
Okay.
All right, get lost.
This is awful.
They're bitten and scratched all over.
Were there ever any wild dogs around here?
Don't look.
There's something bad growing here.
Where are you from?
Where?
This is one of the bad ones.
Where are you going?
Where?
I can't answer its question.
Who does the seamless shirt go to?
Answer even one thing, and it'll take me.
I have to escape.
I'd let my guard down because
Elias was with me these days.
Where are you going?
Where to?
Where from?
Where to? Where from?
Isabelle.
Where to?!
Get lost, scum.
This person... isn't human.
It's not safe here right now for
someone as sensitive as you.
Go home.
U-Uh...
Thank you—
What's wrong?!
These cuts...
Elias.
I need to get Elias.
Or should I treat him with
what medicine I have?
You remind me of Isabelle.
Yeah.
Isabelle.
Your wounds...
Isabelle...
The black dog...
No.
Wait.
You're way too hurt to move, even for a fairy!
Bite wounds and shred marks.
It's a lot like that corpse.
It wasn't him who did it.
You.
Hand over that dog.
You're from before.
I don't have any business with you.
Hand over the dog. That's all I ask.
That's not a problem for you, is it?
He helped me.
Unless you have a proper reason, I refuse.
Just hand it over!
I need to take him!
What the hell did you—
I messed this one up, but it might
actually be useful against humans.
Ulysse.
Come.
What's the matter, Isabelle? Did they make
fun of you for being a redhead again?
It's such beautiful, sunset-colored hair.
I'd love you no matter
what color your hair was.
Isabelle...
Are you up?
I'm burning fairy repellent.
The weird ones will leave us alone.
Where are we?
In a forest nearby.
Are your wounds okay?
I put medicine on them, but...
You resemble my younger sister.
Your sister?
Isabelle.
She had sunset-colored hair and
eyes like spring seedlings.
She was about your height.
If you've lost each other, it's
dangerous here, so I'll help find...
There's no need.
She's sleeping under the dirt.
So she's dead?
You're quite a strange dog.
Dog?
Isabelle and I are both human.
I'd watched over her ever
since she was little.
Ulysse.
Always.
I always thought she would
call me with that voice.
I've met someone like you before.
Were they able to be with the one they love?
You could say so.
But you could say otherwise, too.
Say what?
Where did you get those wounds?
I don't know.
Are you all right?
I'm glad the medicine
doesn't last very long.
What the hell do you think—
Alice-san, was it?
You scared me a bit, so I took
the liberty of tying your wrists.
Damn.
You aren't going to do anything?
I have no reason to do anything to you.
Um...
Can I ask you a question, then?
Why do you want him?
Depending on your reason,
I may be able to let you go.
I need him as raw material to make a chimera.
Material?
Do you know what a chimera is?
They're creatures made by combining
two creatures using magic.
Some weird brat came to us asking
to help find the materials for it.
Master refused.
But there was nothing he could do.
I don't care what happens to me.
You love him, huh?
Absolutely!
Nothing good's ever happened
to me since I was born.
But I had a bit of talent,
so Master took me in.
You're the same way, aren't you?
I'm not very smart, but I would
do anything for Master.
I wonder what I think of him.
He has ulterior motives, but he's kind.
He's important to me.
And ultimately, I couldn't
go on if he kicked me out.
Never mind that.
I gave you my reason.
Now let me go, already!
I see what's going on now.
You were hiding him from me!
Sorry.
Is Renfred nearby?
I came out here by myself!
Master is...
Yo, mage.
Why are you guys here?
To inspect that there.
A mage? Inspect me?
Why?
It's only recently that he
awoke as a black dog.
That thing won't be a problem.
That thing?
Sorry.
Well?
Like I said, there's some
creepy kid threatening us.
He took Master's arm as well.
No wonder.
Please.
Do something about him.
How does that benefit us?
He's already got chimeras
wandering around.
The corpse up front and the dog's
wounds are both his chimera's doing.
Concern yourself with the dog, and
your kitten will be in danger, too.
Was that not a good enough reason?
Sure, I don't mind.
Why the flimsy voice?
No, I didn't think you'd
be so quick to agree.
If he's left running around, the church will
come complaining to me later, anyway.
So what does this "kid" look like?
I don't really know.
He looks like a kid, but I see
all kinds of things overlapping.
He's, like, blurry.
He has this...
What's wrong?
...creepy grin.
What are you—
Renfred's puppy is so poorly trained.
She spilled everything.
You!
Huh?
Did I get the wrong one?
Oh well, what does it matter?
That girl's just a guinea pig, isn't she?
There's no way you'd become
attached to a human.
Right, Pilum Murialis?
Master said he's a mage
from a fantasy story.
At times, he lends a hand, and
at times, he shows his fangs.
Something incomplete that tries
to pretend to be human, he said.
No.
He's not that half-assed.
This thing could never become human.
The mage becomes a monster.
Having lost himself to rage,
he shows his beastly instincts.
The wounded girl comes to a decision.
Elias!