Gustave Marlowe?
Yes.
I'm told that the man from last night
is an internationally-wanted criminal.
He's a member of the group
behind Jade Dusk,
a terrorist plot carried out in Asterisk.
You mean he's a terrorist?
No.
He seems to have joined Jade Dusk
for monetary reasons.
Most likely, there was nothing political
about his motives last night.
It did sound like he was
carrying out someone's request,
so maybe a big organization's
behind this?
But still, why would anyone
make such a request?
The police want to put you under protection.
What do you want to do?
I think I'll pass.
I'll be all right, too.
Looks like none of us
will be needing protection.
Understood.
I'll let them know.
Now then, I have some research to do,
so please excuse me.
If that's all, then we'll be leaving, too.
Oh, one second, Julis...
Can you and Amagiri stay a second?
Didn't I tell you yesterday there was
something I wanted to discuss?
The Lonely Strega
So...
what did you want to talk about?
Right.
There are two things, actually...
Amagiri?
Yes?
Would you mind marrying Julis?
Wh-Wh...?
What are you talking about, Brother?!
What kind of a sick joke is that?!
Well, how about if you started out
by getting engaged?
N-No, wait!
I think you have
the wrong idea about us!
Julis and I don't have
that kind of relationship.
R-Right!
Oh, sure, I've heard
all about your relationship from Flora.
But it doesn't matter.
Under these circumstances,
it's not that big a deal.
It's a huge deal!
I'm saying this for your sake, Julis.
At this rate, you're going to end up...
That's none of your business!
What's this all about?
If we don't act now,
Julis will end up like me.
That is, married off to someone convenient
for the Integrated Enterprise Foundation.
In that case,
you should at least pick someone
you get along with now, while you can.
You don't dislike Amagiri, right?
Well... Needless to say,
I don't dislike him, but...
Don't tell me you forced that
victory parade on us yesterday so...
Yes. I thought I should
introduce you two in a casual way.
B-B-But why all of a sudden?
When I've always
turned you down for such things!
The situation's changed now, Julis.
Because you've won the Phoenix Festa.
Until now, the Integrated Enterprise
Foundation wasn't all that serious.
But thanks to your recent victory,
your value has skyrocketed.
W-Well...
But we can still strike first now.
Nothing can top his status
as your partner in the Phoenix Festa.
So what do you say, Amagiri?
It's a small nation, but I'm sure
you can live quite comfortably here.
I don't think it's a bad proposition.
True.
But at the same time, there would
always be certain strings attached.
Am I wrong about that?
As long as you live in this world,
you can never expect complete freedom.
I think you have no choice but to accept
some kind of constraint or other.
You should be able to choose what kind
of constraints you're going to accept.
After all, Julis came to Asterisk
to break those constraints.
I can't allow myself
to be the shackles that bind Julis.
You're more serious than I thought.
Fine, fine.
Let's forget we ever spoke of this.
Oh, but if, for some reason...
Yes?
If it turns out that Julis herself
desires such shackles,
will you accept her wishes then?
B-B-Brother, what are you...?
Well... I can't say
until it actually happens.
I see. So there's a chance.
If that's all, please excuse us!
Let's go, Ayato!
Hold up a second.
Didn't I say there were two things?
If it's something stupid again,
I won't let you get away with it!
It won't take a second.
Julis,
would you mind not competing
in the Gryps Festa?
Are you being serious, Brother?
Naturally, I'm totally serious.
And your reasons?
You saw it during the victory parade,
didn't you?
Right now your popularity
is mind-blowing.
If you reach even greater heights,
you could drive me into irrelevance.
And so I'd like you
to stay out of the Gryps Festa.
Declined.
What am I going to do?
You're not serious, are you?
Totally serious, that was me
begging with all of my heart.
I'm on the throne in this kingdom
because I'm obedient
to the Integrated Enterprise Foundation,
and I'm a good-for-nothing
with no interest in politics.
If Julis were to win the Gryps Festa
and ended up wielding
more influence than me,
then I wouldn't put it past them
to put Julis on the throne.
And then she would try to change
this country to help the poor.
But this country is controlled
by the Integrated Enterprise Foundation.
Julis would only end up suffering.
Now, then, Amagiri...
I'm going to ask you again.
Do you think you can find
a way to persuade Julis?
No, I can't.
I see. All right, then.
Oh, well.
Then I'll have to be an even bigger
good-for-nothing than I already am.
You'll find Julis at the orphanage
across the lake.
Ever since she was a child, she's always
gone there whenever she was upset.
Sorry, but I'm leaving her to you.
Yes, that's right.
Please do it as quickly as possible.
You got it!
Okay, I'll let you know
as soon as I find out.
Later.
All right!
Come at me from any direction!
Hey, now you've done it!
Hey, look out!
It's Ayato Amagiri!
- You're right!
- Wow!
You got here faster than I thought.
Did my brother tell you where I was?
Well, yeah.
Oh, my!
Sister Therese...
Welcome, Ayato Amagiri.
I'm Therese.
I'm in charge of this church
and the orphanage.
Welcome back, Julis.
I saw the Phoenix Festa. Not bad!
Well, what did you expect?
Hey, pretty cocky!
What happened to that kid
who used to snivel 24/7?
- There she is!
Long time no see, Julis!
Time really flies, doesn't it?
Our little Julis grew up into a fine
young princess in the blink of an eye!
Well, I don't know about princesses
who end up winning the Phoenix Festa.
What did you say?
I'm so glad.
That Julis chose a person like you.
Hey, hey, never mind that.
Is that her partner?
Oh, hey, I'm not...
He's pretty hot!
Hey, you're right!
It's all right.
You need to tell us all about him!
I can tell just by the way
you looked at Julis now.
Oh, please, there's nothing to tell!
All right, enough!
Go on back to work now!
Yes, ma'am!
- See you, Julis!
- See you!
See you!
Bye!
Let's ask her again later.
Absolutely!
I know we caused you a lot of trouble
over that incident with Flora.
Once again, thank you very much.
Oh, but it actually wasn't me
who saved Flora.
Just go ahead and accept her thanks
on behalf of the group.
Right... Thank you.
I see that there are some Genestella
members among the sisters here.
Yes, including myself,
there are four of us now.
For me, Sister Therese
is my Strega mentor.
Yeah?
I still teach self-defense to the children.
Is that a greenhouse?
Yes.
It was the favorite spot of one of the girls
who used to live here.
She didn't like fighting...
and she was a truly kind-hearted girl.
I think I'll go get some air.
Julis?
U-Uh, sorry! Excuse me.
I see it's still too soon for her.
I'm sorry.
I seem to be rather unstable today.
Jolbert seemed really worried about you.
I know that.
I know!
That my brother cares for me
more than anyone else in the world
and how blessed I am.
That's precisely why I can't accept
this country's condition.
I think you're doing
the best that you can, Julis.
That orphanage has nothing
to worry about anymore, does it?
It's true that by winning
the Phoenix Festa,
I've attained my goal
of rescuing that orphanage.
But it's just a drop in the bucket.
At the end of the day,
the system this world is built on
just keeps churning out
more and more slums like this.
Places like that orphanage...
And children who have no choice
but to cling to them.
I want to free this country,
at least, of that curse.
Is that your wish
for the next Gryps Festa?
Yes.
Don't tell me that was...
No way!
Julis?
No, there's no doubt about it.
I'm sure it was...
Hey, Julis!
What's up with that
all of a sudden? Julis!
Is the ground rotten?
It's been a long time, Ophélia.
Ophélia? Surely you don't mean...
Why did you come here?
What's it been, about a year?
I never thought I'd run into you here.
How many times did I warn you
not to concern yourself with me?
My business with you
is the same as it was a year ago.
Come back, Ophélia!
That's not the world you belong in!
Stop it, Julis.
I'm only following my own destiny.
You don't have the power
to reverse my fate.
I don't buy that at all!
At this time, my destiny is here.
If you insist on making me
do as you say, then...
Oh, you don't have to tell me!
But don't think it's going to end
the way it did a year ago!
H-Hey, hold up, Julis!
Ayato, don't you lift a finger!
This is between me and Ophélia!
Julis...
This time for sure,
I'm going to smash that school badge!
Burst into bloom...
Livingstone Daisy!
So that's that power
of Ophélia Landlufen.
Oh, Julis.
It's no good.
Once again, you're in over your head.
I'm not done yet!
Burst into bloom...
Anemone Coronaria!
Let's go, Ophélia!
She's not actually...
blocking it with just her Prana?
Impossible!
Your destiny is weak.
Didn't I tell you?
Turn... to... dust.
Julis!
Julis! Julis!
So that's the miasma of Erenshkigal.
Are you Ayato Amagiri?
You've already won!
This is enough!
It's very sad,
but even I can't stop the wheels
of fate once they start turning.
If you don't want to get dragged into this,
you should leave right now.
Sorry, but that's just not gonna happen.
What a pity.
Amagiri Shinmei Style...
Repulsing Crow!
So that's the Ser=Versta.
To be honest, I feel like I have
zero chance of beating you.
No way!
I see...
Tasteless, odorless, colorless,
transparent miasma, huh?
Pretty mind-blowing...
I'm sorry.
But you'll be out of your misery soon.
I wonder if you'd be so kind
as to hold off a bit, young miss?
The thing is, I've been hired
to take out those two myself.
And I get paid on a per head basis.
If you don't mind, could you
possibly let me have that prey?
Hey, Ophélia...
Where the hell
have you been fooling around?
Which part of "don't leave the lab"
don't you get?
I'll be heading back now.
Do as you wish.
I am truly grateful.
Hold up!
Really, I have to say
that was bone-chilling.
I've heard stories about her,
but I never thought
she was a monster of that level.
Heaven forbid!
Now then, why don't I take care
of my own business, then?
Allow me to introduce you.
These are my creations,
Orthrus and Cerberus.
What do you think?
Aren't they as imposing
as their legends describe them?
Not good.
Amagiri Shinmei Style, First Sword...
Fugaku!
There's our Phoenix Festa champ.
However...
This... I can't evade!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Ayato.
That was a close shave, wasn't it?
Claudia!
Well, well,
this is quite a dilemma.
Who knew I'd be thwarted like this?
What would you like to do,
Gustave Marlowe?
I wouldn't mind
taking you on now myself...
but that's not what you want, is it?
I see, you're an annoyingly
smart young lady, aren't you?
Although this is a golden opportunity,
I'm not going to push it
and shall now withdraw.
Ayato?
Are you all right?
Ayato!
Oh, woe is me!
These previews
that you've all enjoyed until now...
We've now reached the very last one!
However! Please don't be sad!
Episode 24
Reunion
In the next episode, the one true heroine
will finally be left standing!
And the victor will of course be...
me!