Time has really flown.
Has it already been three years?
Wataya Family Grave
I can still hear Master
Wataya's voice sometimes.
Arata, it's getting hot,
so let's head back.
W-Wait!
I just put those sandwiches
there as an offering.
I can understand why Grandpa
and Dad never got along.
Your grandpa didn't like me
because I wasn't interested in karuta!
Your quarrels were the reason you took
a job in Tokyo and forced
Arata to switch schools.
B-But!
It was a good experience, right?
You made friends in Tokyo.
That's right.
The Tokyo High School
Regional is today.
Are your friends doing well?
You exchange e-mails, right?
No, not as often as before.
You need to send more e-mails
or your friends in Tokyo
will forget about you.
Really?  I doubt that would happen.
Cell phones are incredible!
Like the misty bridge!
Chihaya...
In my mind, our misty bridge...
is not a cell phone, but something else.
Mom, Dad.
If I win the National High
School Championship,
I want you to grant my request.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 4
To tell the
people in
the capital
that I make
for the
islands
Man, I'm so excited.
I hope we don't miss the finals.
They should have made it
past the prelim stage, easy.
Yes, yes, Doctor.
Mashima-kun hasn't sent any
e-mails about them losing yet.
Eyebrows...
I wonder what his problem is.
Based on his play during practice,
he should be a Class A player now.
He's put in so much effort,
so why can't he win a tournament?
Doctor, I ran into
Mashima-kun at the Kyoto
and Hiroshima tournaments
and watched him play.
It seems like...
...he just has terrible luck.
He can never catch a lucky break
when he needs it the most.
Mashima-senpai!
I made them                    myself <3
Please, have some!
Sorry, I try to avoid eating
anything solid before a match.
Wait. Mashima, you're
copying Dr. Harada?
I'm gonna eat up.
If we win our next match,
we're in the Nationals!
You can have some, boys.
Yay!
Don't think too much.
If I lose after doing everything
I can, I can accept that.
Group C Preliminary
What's important is that I do my best.
Oh, there they are!
Dr. Harada!
Sounds like you're doing well.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thanks for coming to cheer us—
I'm certainly here to cheer you on,
but that's not the only
reason I'm here this year.
It's twice as exciting for me,
but also quite distressing.
Huh?
Oh?  Haven't you heard?
Let's go, guys!
Homei
Yes!
The team to defeat last year's
dark horse, Mizusawa,
will be this year's dark horse, Homei!
Yes!
Tsuboguchi-san?
High School Championship Tokyo Regional Final
Tournament Bracket
Mizusawa High
Homei High
Hokuo Academy
Shoyo High
This could be dangerous.
Yeah, they were
completely off my radar.
The data from last year won't help.
What's the problem?
Homei's advisor, Tsuboguchi-san,
was the East Representative for
the Master match last year,
and he's the ace of the Shiranami society
Chihaya-chan and the president are in.
Did you know, Chihaya?
I don't understand what
gets you excited...
Everyone's worked hard
to make it this far!
You're playing much better than two
months of practice can account for!
Every Card Counts
Your advice was spot on, Coach!
After changing my form,
my swing is much smoother!
Me, too!
I followed your instructions
for sending cards
and my opponent made four mistakes!
Lost that one, lost that
one, lost that one...
"I hear," "As this," "Note that,"
"The storm blasts," "May it"...
Sasa, you need to learn to let go!
"My fear is not," "The autumn wind," "Like the"...
Mizusawa is strong,
but the practice and hard work you've
put in since spring will pay off.
Will you take me to Omi Jingu?
Yes!
Th-That's youthful spirit...
They changed orders every match.
It's hard to see any patterns.
Go easy on us, reigning champions.
I've known Tsuboguchi-san
since I was a kid.
He wants to win.
What order will they use?
Who's their strongest player?
What order do we use to
guarantee three victories?
Good Luck
Taichi-kun!  Taichi-kun!
Good luck!  I bought this for you!
A lucky charm!
I bought one, too!  Take it!
All you're missing is the luck!
You have the skill!
Sorry, I need to come
up with our order!
Will the semifinalists please
turn in their orders?
Damn, there's no time.
Eyebrows...
An individual match is a team match.
A team match is an individual match.
Homei High School, Takei-kun.
Mizusawa High School, Komano-kun.
What did he mean?
Homei High School, Toda-san.
Team matches and individual
matches are different things.
Mizusawa High School, Mashima-kun.
The side that does better
as a team will win!
Homei High School, Sasa-san.
Please begin placing your cards.
After a fifteen minute memorization
period, the match will begin.
Amazing...
Group C had strong schools like Kase
High and Eiko University High.
They must have improved a lot
with Tsuboguchi-san's teaching.
I knew it!
You're totally my type!
Give me your number after the match!
Wh-What?!
Good!
Chihaya-chan isn't used
to romantic stuff,
so we can use that.
Still, I know that she'll go back
to being crazy about karuta
once the match starts,
so we're only pretending
to go after her.
So how about it?
It's a promise.
What do I do?  What do I do?
That's dirty!
You're taking advantage
of Chihaya's personality!
I know what you're up
to, Tsuboguchi-san!
In reality, we're throwing
Eyebrows off his game.
Chihaya-chan may be Mizusawa's ace,
but Eyebrows is their mental leader.
You pay too much attention
to your surroundings.
Are you sure that you
should be glaring at me?
Dr. Harada.
Oh, Mochida-kun.
It looks like Hokuo is
winning their games.
Yes, thank you.
By the way, did you notice, Doctor?
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
They're switching readers
every round this year.
It must have been difficult
to find five readers.
Oh, that's impressive.
I know.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Here comes spring, now
the flower blooms
My life means nothing...
What was that pause about?!
Mochida-kun, is he an amateur?!
No, Tashiro-kun is certified!
...to see you again
I wish I could show the...
He didn't wait long enough this time!
Tashiro-kun's nervous because he was
just certified as a Class B reader!
He's not following the correct rhythm!
Mizusawa's at a disadvantage!
The strange rhythm will affect
experienced players more!
Taichi-kun's luck is so terrible!
Karuta is similar to dance.
Irritated
You can't dance if the
music is off beat.
Oe-san.
Focus on the first card.
Make your own rhythm.
Yes.
...with tears of blood
A mountain village grows...
Chihaya and Nishida are fine.
What about Komano?
Komano, attack the next card!
Yeah!
My opponent's card
placement is very familiar,
since their coach is Tsuboguchi-san,
and he's playing the Shiranami
offensive karuta style.
Offensive is my style, too...
I'd love a girlfriend
who's good at karuta.
You're perfe—
Focus on the opponent's
bottom right side!
I feel that my love...
Chihaya-chan's gotten better.
I never expected to defeat the
two Class A Mizusawa players.
But...
Yes!  I took one from
my opponent's side!
Same here!
Good, keep it up!
He's taking all the
cards I'm not watching,
while sending all the cards
I've been targeting.
Tsuboguchi-san's taught
them all the nasty tricks.
A mountain stream dips...
Crap, I was too late.
I need to focus.
Come on!  Come on!  Come on!
I'm pretty sure I want to ignore that.
Nobody wishes to see...
I knew it would come!
Come on!  Come on!  Come on!
Some kind of curse?
What's with her?
She's the only one acting so strange.
I've dreamed about becoming the karuta
queen since I was a little girl.
However, I didn't have the courage
to enter a karuta society,
so I had to practice and work
on my positioning by myself.
Our high school had a karuta club,
but they just sat around chatting.
That was when my savior arrived.
Everyone, karuta is fun!
Huh?
I guess it's not karuta that's fun...
It's the act of trying
your hardest that's fun!
I was shocked.
I wasn't the only one
who wanted to try hard.
I was shocked...
The sky may hold...
It came!
She guessed two cards in a row?!
He's trying to attack, but
he's not getting any chances!
Horrible luck!
So spring ends...
That's it!
Eyebrows doesn't believe
that he just needs luck.
He continues to believe
that he lacks the skill.
Why?
She can guess cards this
well after two months
of instruction from Tsuboguchi-san?
I've been working my ass off for years.
But when he tells himself that
it's skill that he lacks...
Her sense is better than mine?
he falls victim
to the belief that he
doesn't have the talent.
Is it because of the reader's rhythm?
We aren't leading the way
we were in the prelims.
What about Nishida?
He's up by ten cards?
Impressive.
Porky.
You're too nice.
Why let Mashima, who's stuck
in Class B even though
he tops you all in skill, be your president?
Stuck in Class B...
Which card is she aiming for?
Check the card she just sent.
Talent...
She's watching "When the,"
but being careful since the empty card
"When I" hasn't been read yet.
Talent...
"When winds blow" and "When winds
send" are still out there.
Talent...
This won't work!
Focus!
Refresh my memory! Check everything!
Huh?
The air conditioner above
Taichi-kun isn't working.
Why now?!  Why that one?!
Horrible luck!
It's so hot...  I need a towel...
My memorization...  My hard work...
The emotions experienced...
There it is!
Aren't doing anything for me!
This is a good match.
Eyebrows is up against
a strong opponent.
Well, she's hooked on your teachings.
"Play like you can guess
what card's coming next."
"If you end up taking a different card,
talk like it was the
one you were expecting."
The sound of birds crossing...
I don't care about that card.
It's a simple strategy,
but it's not easy to pull off.
If she can convince him that the flow
is on her side, and not on his,
she might be able to overwhelm him while
he's worried about leading the team.
You're pretty passionate about this,
considering that you're the biggest
Class A slacker in our society.
I had to ignore my own problems...
It's the act of trying
your hardest that's fun!
...to inspire them.
I didn't try my hardest,
so I was left with regrets.
Every match is close, and it's so hot...
What do I have to do to become
Mashima-senpai's girlfriend?
Huh?!  What are you talking about?!
There's nothing else for me to
do right now besides think.
She's
really
crazy
about
love...
After watching him for two
months, it's become very clear.
Mashima-senpai is in
love with Ayase-senpai.
Why?
Ayase-senpai doesn't pay any
attention to Mashima-senpai.
Yes, that's right.
The air conditioner in the very back.
Can I start after this match is over?
It's a sauna!
Plus, it's only affecting my kids!
This sweat feels gross...
I don't want to wipe it off
with a loaner kimono,
but I don't have a towel...
As I wait for...
Yes, got it!
Go on the attack!
Yes!
E-Excuse me!
Can I have a towel?
Thank you very much.
I always try to play it cool.
I feel embarrassed about losing,
so I run off to tournaments
far away in secret.
I know that I'm not alone...
But...
I want to be strong, even when I'm alone.
my body burns like the seaweed
drying on the shores of Matsuho
The storm will soon carry...
Yes, that's one card!
He's keeping his eyes on
the cards while speaking.
He's not turning to look
at his teammates.
That's right, Eyebrows.
A team match is an individual match.
You must trust in your teammates
while playing by yourself.
Huh?  Where are you going?
To watch the other match.
I can scout out our
opponent in the finals.
"There's nothing else to do
right now besides think"?
There has to be something else!
I'm a member of this team!
A member of the Mizusawa karuta club!
No matter where I stand
on the shores of Tago,
He caught up!
I can look up and see the
snowy cap of Mt. Fuji
When winds blow oak leaves...
None are left...
I feel as though...
Look for the sound...
The hazy early morning
light comes not from...
He's built a lead in no time.
She was able to make her sense
work in the first half,
but in the second half...
I'm moving my cards.
I'll bring them together
and hit them all together.
Waves creep closer...
Feel sorrow wash over me...
I'm not giving up yet!
I want to win!
1 to 4.
He just needs one more card, but the cards
have all been on his opponent's side!
His luck is still horrible!
"My life," "I wish," "A mountain
village," "May it," "The sky is,"
"The tail," "Though my," "Gust," "Impassioned was," "I feel that,"
"Feel love," "The autumn paddy," "While it pains," "Impassioned vows,"
"A mountain stream," "Nobody,"
"The sky may," "So spring ends,"
"While autumn," "May the
time we," "Said bed,"
"The emotions," "Swift," "Since the,"
"The sound of birds," "As this," "As the years,"
"May the time spent," "The night,"
"While it may," "Rain," "My only thought as I,"
"After many," "Would the,"
"As my," "The storm will"...
though autumn is not mine alone
"No matter," "When winds blow,"
"None are," "I feel as,"
"Look," "The hazy early morning light,"
"Waves," "Feel sorrow"...
The...
...sight of Mount Arima...
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much...
Did everyone win?
What's the score?
Man...
I'm a failure as the president
if I don't know that.
Thank you very much.
Hey, Sasa.
I-I'm sorry, Coach!
My dedication wasn't strong enough!
Eyebrows, how many cards were left?
95 cards were read,
so there were only 5 cards left.
None of them were empty cards.
What?!
He knew that?!
The last card had become
a first-syllable card,
but you didn't move fast enough,
because you thought there might
be other The cards left.
You lost your lead in the second
half because your opponent
was more aware of how
many cards were left.
Isn't it creepy when someone
can memorize cards like that?
He practices like crazy every day,
but I'm inspired by the
effort he puts in.
Thank you very much, everyone.
I'll wash these towels
before returning them.
It's okay, Taichi-kun!
It's because the air
conditioning wasn't working!
You can have all the towels you need.
Good luck in your next match.
Does it really matter if he's good
at karuta when he's so popular?
Thank you too, Hanano-san.
Oh, it was nothing.
I have to be on my guard!
Ayase-senpai is watching
Mashima-senpai!
Though, I can't be entirely sure.
Mizusawa High
Homei High
Hokuo Academy
Shoyo High
Our next match is against the
strongest school in Tokyo, Hokuo.
They'll give us their best shot!
We have to play to win!