What do you think?
It's really warm!
Really feels like summer...
Make sure you get your fill of it!
You won't be touching any warm
surfaces for a while, after this.
Hey.
What?
Let's do this in Antarctica, too.
Well, shall we?
Ready to sail!
It's done, huh?
No.
We did it.
The boat left the land.
I don't know what this
trip will mean in the end.
We'll be taking time off from
school, missing tests...
It might even affect our entrance exams.
But as of now,
we are no longer high school students
who can never take a step forward.
We are not 17-year-olds and 16-year-olds
who try but accomplish nothing.
It's all ocean!
Of course it is.
The world really is big, isn't it?
That's enough!
Hey, guys, I'm taking a picture!
Look up here!
Okay, say cheese!
A Place Further Than the Universe
Howling,
Maddening,
Screaming
20 Likes
12 Comments
#LaundryDuty #MysterySolved #ArmyNice
High school girls are conducting
intervews!!
^i     .
*Please explain what your job is.
One person is enough.
Ready to go?
I see! Thank you very much!
Yeah, yeah. Very cute.
We're not live, so you can do it again...
We rocked!
They said the waves were
gonna get pretty rough...
We really need to be efficient with our time.
They wanted us to help out later, right?
Yes, that's right.
Why didn't you wake me?
I did.
Then you need to wake me harder!
Excuse us!
Wait! Wait! Thirty minutes more!
Fifteen, at least!
Okay. We'll wait outside.
Did she not have eyebrows?
It's not uncommon among women.
I'd actually say it's typical.
Is it really?
Ow!
As we go further south,
we'll be stopping at places in
the ocean known as "stations"
to gather bacteria and seawater.
We have tons of equipment on
board to help us with that!
This is a water sampler and a CTD monitor.
Wow! This is a water sampler
and a CTD monitor, huh?
We'll be gathering rocks like these
and performing geological
surveys in Antarctica.
We'll investigate the stratum
several thousand meters down
The mic is too close!
to learn more about the
conditions on primordial Earth.
She has normal eyebrows, right?
Would you just listen to her?
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
We're late! We're late!
Which way was it, again?
This way!
High School Girls' room!!
You gotta KNOCK
Ow!
Sorry we're late!
Yeah, yeah, we've been waiting!
Hey, dessert!
You make that here, too?
Well, with whatever we have, anyway.
Now, if you don't mind, start up on those.
Those?
This is why I wanted to bring a peeler!
Stupid Rin!
There are still so many more to go...
But this kind of thing is fun, don't you think?
You like grunt work, huh, Kimari?
Seems like it takes the four of
you just to reach one horsepower.
Are we that slow?
It's clear you don't help
out at home very often.
Still, don't rush yourselves.
We don't want you getting hurt.
She's fast!
I am a pro, after all.
Are you a cook somewhere?
I'm usually a lunch lady.
I'm constantly thinking
up and preparing dishes
for picky eaters like you guys.
Anyway, work hard,
so you can get up on deck soon.
Get up on deck?
From 1100 hours to 1700 hours, training is
permitted on-deck. Counterclockwise.
What's that?
It means we're allowed to train topside.
In other words, we can go
outside and get some exercise.
Exercise?
I'll take you up when you're done.
It's sort of a duty for expedition members.
Wow, the ocean.
W-We're going to run here?
Yep.
Hey, wait up!
If they announce clockwise,
you'd go this way.
If they announce counterclockwise,
you go that way.
The direction changes by day, so be careful.
Okay!
About how long do we have to run?
There's no particular rule.
But as we've told you over and over,
stamina is crucial on an expedition.
You might be working all day
in sub-zero conditions,
so you need strong bodies
to meet the challenge.
Mom was always exercising, too...
If you run out of stamina and pass out,
not only will you not contribute anything,
you'll be an active drag
on the people around you.
You don't want to get to
Antarctica to be a drag, right?
See you!
She's fast!
Okay! We'll do our best, too!
Hey!
Kimari-san doesn't realize, does she?
She'll catch on soon enough.
I thought so...
Hey, are you okay?
Why... is it... so big?
You've walked around here
countless times, haven't you?
But... everyone else... goes so fast...
Even she can run that fast...
She looks like a scientist,
but I guess she still has tons of stamina.
We're going.
W-Wait!
Eighteen!
By the time we get to Antarctica,
we'll be Amazons!
It won't be that easy...
Okay, last one!
It itches!
My nose!
Yuzu, can you not lift your arms?
If you do anything, I will just kill you...
I will kill you ♥
You idiots! You idiots!
So this is a seawater bath...
It's pretty big, huh?
Definitely worth experiencing.
Would you get out already?
Seawater is more permeating than I expected.
My hair is so crusty...
I think that's why everyone cuts their hair.
And the men shave their heads...
Okay, maybe we should cut it!
I'll cut it!
The boat has barber facilities, right?
Not even if the fate of
the world depended on it.
Ditto.
How come? I'm good!
I cut my own bangs all the time!
At last, the mystery...
...is solved.
That's why...
...her hair looks like that.
What? What?
Provisions ready!
It's time for dinner.
No way! Already?
Missed meal cards go here | Already eaten: Black
Samejima Yasumoto
Yumiko    Honami
I'm all sticky!
Because you didn't wash off
properly in the shower.
But I didn't have time!
Hey, meat and potatoes!
Are these the ones we peeled?
Have we forgotten to do anything else?
Dinner, bath... laundry?
Don't we have to do that
at a certain time, too?
It's because you two were
playing around in the bath.
Take responsibility and go do it.
Wait, but what about our dinner?
But didn't we pick someone to do it
because it seemed easy to forget?
Oh, that's right!
Yes.
As I recall, we did rock-paper-scissors...
Hey!
Laundry Room  Bath
Regarding use of fresh water
Fresh water baths permitted during ship-wide training
(Salt water baths are allowed, too!)
Please try to conserve water ♥
That'll do it.
What do you mean, "that'll do it"?
You actually sat there
and ate your whole meal!
I still made it in time,
so what's the problem?
Don't.
She must be tired.
They kept us busy a lot
longer than I expected.
Yeah, true...
And it all starts again tomorrow.
You think we'll hold out?
We just have to do our best, right?
We don't have any other choice.
Feel sick...
I feel... sick.
When using the toilet,
turn this valve
counterclockwise
to flush.
After flushing,
please close
the valve.
Going to die.
The world is spinning.
Don't talk. If you talk...
How'd it go?
Don't ask.
You're really seasick, huh?
But we were totally fine before.
We took medicine for it...
Didn't that wear off?
It can wear off?
It's medicine. Of course
it'll wear off eventually.
I see.
I've never been on a boat this long.
I didn't even think...
Hinata, you idiot.
Why am I the idiot?
You need to take medicine
and get a good night's rest.
Then have a proper meal.
I know you probably don't have an appetite,
and you're afraid that if you
eat it'll just come back up.
But if you don't eat,
you'll just keep losing stamina.
If it gets bad enough, we might
have to give you an IV supplement.
I see.
If that happens, none of your
training will mean anything.
Okay.
Provisions ready!
Remember what Kanae-san said?
If we don't want to be a drag in Antarctica,
we have to eat, whether we like it or not!
It all came up.
Yuzuki-chan, did it all come up for you, too?
Don't say it.
Stop rocking!
Just stop for a little bit!
I think it is stopped.
No way!
They said they're collecting seawater.
And still...
Yumiko-san said we'd get
used to it eventually.
But it's not happening.
Great Knot-Tying Competition
Winning team gets a steak dinner!!
Sizzle sizzle sizzle! Pictured: the steaks from three years ago
This time, it's meat! Meat!! Meat!!!
Meat is the great motivator!
If you're planning on winning, please bring your
provided army -n-i-c-e- knife, please.
The steaks are not pre-cut.
You were given an army
knife for cutting steak
They've probably been on boats so often
their semicircular canals are busted.
From 0800 hours to 1400 hours,
training is permitted on-deck. Clockwise.
What'll we do?
Yeah, there's no way I can run...
But it's a little better outside,
with the wind, at least...
I could probably manage it
if not for the rocking...
I wanted to see the whales...
Whales? Can you see them?
They said earlier that they were in sight.
Can you see them?
Um... Tamaki-san, was it?
Yes.
There's one right now.
You see it?
She self-destructed just now.
Because she was focusing
on a single point, right?
Lay off. Just thinking about
it makes me want to puke.
There they are. Hey!
I looked in your room earlier,
and it looked like you weren't
ready at all. Are you okay?
Ready?
53 degrees?
Though we set that record a long time ago.
The last time I came here,
it felt to me like we rocked so far,
this desk was up there.
No way!
When you go to Antarctica,
you must surpass these things...
The howling 40 degrees.
The maddening 50 degrees.
The screaming 60 degrees.
Wh-What do you mean?
It's about latitudes.
Earth is a water planet, remember?
It spins on its axis, and that
creates wind and water currents.
But Earth has continents,
so those block the currents and weaken them.
But around this area of
the southern hemisphere,
there's no land in the way,
so there's nothing to interrupt the current.
Mom said they were going to plow
their way right through it.
How long will it take?
I don't know all the
details, but pretty long.
Your insides will go woo,
like on a roller coaster!
A roller coaster? I like those, but...
But do you want to go on one now?
Here it comes...
Though I like this kind of thing...
the feeling, like I'm fighting.
I'm falling!
That was the biggest one yet, right?
I think that was about 15 degrees.
No way.
Here it comes, here it comes,
here it comes, here it comes!
I floated.
My body floated.
You'd better stay in bed.
But the blood is rushing to my head...
Ouch...
You okay?
I'm dizzy.
No getting to sleep tonight, huh?
Yeah...
You think we'll really make it to Antarctica?
Of course we will.
We're on a boat going there.
I know that...
but we might not be able to
do anything once we get there.
Everyone has so much stamina,
and they can handle the boat...
It's almost like we're completely
different organisms.
Then we have to become stronger, too!
You really think we can be like them?
We just have to do our best, right?
We don't have any other choice.
That's not true.
We always had a choice.
But we chose to be here.
Kimari-san?
We chose this ourselves!
Well said!
Where are you going?
The toilet.
I think I'm getting used to throwing up.
Same.
I'll eat anything! I'll puke anything!
That was an actual hill.
Yeah, when I get home I can tell them...
expedition ships are amazing.
Yeah, I'll tell them it was really fun!
You must be joking!
I'm not!
I'm sure that when this trip
is over, that's how we'll feel!
I'd like to go outside for a bit!
That sounds good!
I wanna see, too!
Let's go!
It's pitch black!
This is the ocean we're crossing, huh?
To a continent of ice protected
by storms and raging waves!
We really did choose to go there, didn't we?
What's that? Rain?
It's salty! It's the waves!
You're right!
It's salty!
Feeling better?
Yeah, we're totally fine!
Because we saw the whales yesterday!
Sounds like you've gotten used to the boat.
Yes!
But...
Once we make landfall,
you're gonna get landsick.
For real?
Left ten degrees, five miles!
Where are they?
No clouds.
No birds.
The view is a single sheet of blue.
I strain my eyes,
but the horizon is all I can see.
I know I was probably hearing
the sounds of the boat,
but that overwhelming scenery seemed
to render everything silent.
I was looking out on an infinite
world reminiscent of outer space.
No way...
Is that...
It is.
Those are...
In that moment, we knew for sure.
It really lay ahead... Antarctica!
We're back, aren't we?
Though it'll be a long time before
we're even opening the front door.