Coming.
Morning, Chise!
Stella.
What's wrong? You look shocked.
Er, I didn't think you'd actually come by.
I'm not a liar.
I-It must be cold. Come in.
Thanks.
Wow, this is amazing.
You made all this?
I-It's not a big deal.
It was our contract.
Are you sure you should be
wandering out by yourself?
No one's going to abduct
me right after Christmas.
You were abducted on Christmas, though.
Stop it!
Jeez.
I thought a mage's home would
have a more ominous vibe.
But it's spacious and clean.
Y-Yeah.
I guess I shouldn't tell her there's
all kinds of creatures on her.
I'll be in my study.
You can enjoy yourselves.
Okay.
Ah, um...
Want to come to my room?
Really?
I smell herbs.
When are you going back to London?
Tonight.
I'll come hang out again next month,
so you come to my place, too.
Okay.
This is good.
Do you want to take some with you?
Really? Thanks!
In return for the snacks.
A return for a return... It's gonna
be Christmas every time we meet.
Say, Stella,
it's been a long time
since I've made a friend.
I don't know what to do.
It'd help if you could tell me.
Invite me to do whatever you want to do,
and just talk with me.
What if they don't like it, though?
You're obviously not the
same person as your friend.
You're obviously not gonna
have all the same interests.
Words aren't for understanding each other.
They exist for the sake
of talking to each other.
Or so my Dad says, but honestly,
a jerk is a jerk from beginning to end.
You're so mature, Stella.
Even though you're about my age.
I hope so.
Oh yeah, how old are you again?
I'm ten.
Hm?
Ten.
Ten...
How about you?
Almost sixteen.
I'd decided I would say what I mean
to say, but it's pretty hard.
Let's practice, then.
Practice?
You can't be selfish, though.
Although you don't seem like you would be.
I'm really selfish.
I'm hoping to come over to your place soon.
That's not practice, though.
That's just a plan.
Elias...
Silky, did he leave a note?
Where are you going?
Sorry, Ruth, can you walk Stella home?
Yeah, are you going after him?
Yeah.
You're both strangely dishonest.
Sorry, Stella. Let's hang
out again sometime.
What's up with her?
"Say what she means to say"...
She talks more with her arms
and legs than with her mouth.
It's no use. He keeps getting further.
What's gotten into him?
I'll take on the form I need to
take to do what needs to be done.
I can't keep up with the legs of a fox.
I'd be too big with the body of a bear.
I have to run faster.
I have to run further.
I have to catch him.
This is my wish.
Hey, did you hear something?
It sounded like a wolf.
Probably a dog.
Maybe it's looking for
its pack or something.
I'm not outside?
You're a proper wolf this time.
Um...
I'm sorry if we were making too much noise.
I'll be more careful next time.
Do you feel all right?
Is there something that upset you?
Elias?
Listening to your voices oddly
made me want to leave home.
I wanted Stella to go away.
I thought I wanted to be alone,
but as soon as I knew you were
chasing me, I felt better.
And yet, I couldn't stop running.
I don't get it.
That's...
Why don't we go home and have tea?
Elias must be more confused
about himself than he realizes.
I thought he was leaving me.
Elias might have been the same way.
Can I allow myself the conceit of thinking
that's how much he thinks of me?
You're in a good mood, Stella.
When are we going to
Grandma's place next time?
You're so impatient.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm home!
Are they not home yet?
I'll take another look around.
Our connection's being interrupted.
Chise, where are you?
This might be bad.
Elias.
Elias!
Ruth.
Ruth!
He's going to eat me.
He's going to consume me.
That's...
That's not good.
I don't want that right now.
Fly!
Over there!
Which shadow?
Chise!
Are you looking for your master?
Is she...
You all made an offering of raindrop
fruits and branches to Mother.
In return, I'll lend you my flame.
Thank you.
Next winter, when I become Mother,
I hope you'll offer me raindrop
fruits and branches again.
Chise!
Ruth...
Yeah.
It's all right.
I'm here.
Thanks.
Is it Elias?
Yeah.
I think he had some kind
of temper tantrum.
A tantrum?
What did my mom tell me in these situations?
What you're feeling is probably
what's called jealousy, Elias.
A feeling of envy, of wondering
why you're singled out.
But being jealous of someone—
of something...
Being envious or resentful
will only bring you misery.
That's not something you're
meant to throw at people.
It's something you have to
deal with inside yourself.
Even though I'm the most envious of all.
Do you get it?
Keep being selfish, and I'll have
to take matters into my own hands.
Ruth.
Chise!
There's no telling where
this knife will land!
Are you done now?
You really scared me.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I'm not angry anymore.
So you were angry.
A bit.
Let's talk lots when we get home.
Talk?
Yeah.
Together.
Stella taught me a lot today, too.
I'd like for you to listen.
Let's stay up for a while in bed to talk,
and fall asleep together tonight.
Come on, let's go home.
Yeah.
They were like father and daughter
until just the other day.
Now they're like mother and son.
I'm leaving now.
Yes?
H-Hello, is Angelica-san available?
Oh, nice to meet you.
I'm David Burley. Angie's husband.
Sorry, do you think you
could wait for a bit?
I don't mind.
Are you a mage, too, David-san?
I'm an ordinary human.
I'm lucky enough to both have a job,
and have a good relationship
with my family.
Other than that, I'm nothing special.
Dad, is there a visitor—
Hello.
Sorry, she's been a bit difficult lately.
It's fine.
I just met a similar kid recently.
David, did you call me?
Ainsworth's not waking up?
Not since the night of the 26th.
Are you sleepy?
One, two, where do you bloom?
Under the window where the children sleep,
white flowers on the night of a pale moon...
Three, four, where do you bloom?
On the frame of Mother's mirror,
a little blue flower blooms...
You sang him a lullaby, and he fell asleep?!
That thing did?
That thing did.
I did some research, too, but I'm scared.
You say that, but you tried a few things.
Don't tell Elias.
If your magic compounded with
your song, that's magic itself.
Magic?
It doesn't normally happen
unless you intend it,
but that might be your talent, Chise.
My talent?
Then why am I bad at making sleeping aids?
Just a second.
Thank you.
Angelica-san...
Thanks for the bracelet.
I'd like to get you
something next Christmas.
I look forward to it.
Want some more tea?
I'm good, thank—
Are you all right?
You should get some sleep there
if you're not feeling well.
I heard you often push yourself too far.
Thank you...
You can't really go to
the hospital for it, right?
You should take it easy.
You know about that, too?
There's someone who talks about
you like you're her own child.
Angie hasn't changed ever since I met her.
I'd been asking her out ever
since I was a snotty brat.
After more years than I
can count on two hands,
she finally accepted.
It was only after our daughter was born
that I finally got a sense of why
she'd always turned me down.
I'm lucky.
I don't have to think about dying by myself.
But Angie...
Our daughter...
They have to continue sending people
off, and there's no end in sight.
It's painful to think about how many days
are left that we can laugh together.
But unlike me, if things pan
out for you, you can keep up.
So let's live as long as we can
without stressing or forcing it.
You and I both.
You're right.
There.
Yo, Chise, want some he—
Ah, you're awake.
Was it the medicine or was it that?
Thank goodness, Elias.
I was so worried...
I'll explain.
We're going to get in trouble
for coming out this far.
It's fine.
But kids aren't supposed to
go this far. It's not safe.
Whoa, there's something shiny!
Ah, wait up!
Let's hurry.
Poachers, yet again.
Fools.
It's the caretaker!
Surrender and return to the soil.
Nice to meet you, mister caretaker.
The wandering sorcerer,
Joseph, is on the move.
Joseph's scheming leads the girl
and the mage to frantic London.
Depending on price and terms,
I'll take on your work.