Sakimitama, Kushimitama... protect her.
"The Fateful Two"
Who's this, Mom?
Is he dead?
Don't worry about him.
Are you being pursued?
Yes.
Huh? W-Wait!
You're not going to save me?
Why would I?
I...
We have no quarrel with you,
but since you've seen the girl...
You must die.
Eliminating witnesses?
How vicious.
Wh-What?
Stop screaming. You'll bite your tongue.
Om Marici Yeh Svaha!
Marici? You're...
He's thought to be invincible
because of his immense strength.
Do not falter!
Ougi Tendagaeshi!
I couldn't let you go and
become their target.
Excuse me...
Sheesh. I'm already hungry and
now I used all that energy.
Wait!
What?
If you're that strong,
it should be no problem for
you to protect one girl.
I might be assaulted again
by more men like them.
Please come with me!
Not my problem.
What's wrong with you?!
A real man would want to protect a lady!
You're pathetic!
That's not very nice.
I already saved you.
Besides, who calls their savior
pathetic without even thanking him?
Thank you? Let's see...
Okay, then why don't you come
with me to Shinshu Ueda?
Are you even listening?
What if I buy you some soba to thank you?
What?
You're hungry, aren't you?
Rest Stop
She sure eats a lot.
Those marks are gone.
Great meal!
That was delicious.
You're still on your first bowl?
You don't eat much, do you?
You just eat too much.
I have a name, you know.
It's Isanami.
What's your name?
What do you do for a living?
Saizo.
I'm a samurai.
Saizo...
I'll call you Sai-chan.
I'll kill you, you bitch.
If you're a samurai, does that
mean you serve a master?
It's none of your business.
So you're a wanderer.
That explains why you're so poor that
you followed me just for some soba.
You...
I-sa-na-mi.
Listen... Thanks for earlier.
I finally get to hear you say it.
It's been days since I've been
able to relax like this.
It's probably because you'll protect me.
I'm serious.
I didn't think you would at first.
You didn't seem to want
anything to do with me.
But when you threw
me over your shoulder,
I knew you would do it.
Somehow, I felt so safe.
I knew you would protect me.
Don't decide for me.
I wasn't going to die there.
But you could've left me.
You wouldn't stop screaming
for me to rescue you.
Saizo, you're a good guy, aren't you?
If you're done eating, let's go.
Wait.
I'll leave our payment here.
All right!
Hey, that thing's gonna fall off your head.
Oh, whoops.
I can't lose this.
Saizo, can't we walk slower?
Ueda's just up ahead.
You should be fine from here.
Walk along the dike so you'll be seen.
See ya.
Go with me a little farther.
I don't know how to get into the castle.
What? You mean Ueda Castle?
Huh? Yeah.
Don't be ridiculous. I'm not doing that.
I won't let you leave.
Who are you?
This guy...
We're not criminals.
I'm a priestess of Izumo.
What?
What's a priestess doing
with an Iga assassin?
The Iga are all trash.
Shut up.
I've had enough of you and your friends.
Koga coward!
Run back to your master, you dog!
Why don't you see if he'll give you a bone?
I won't let you get away
with defiling Sanada lands.
Stop breathing on my face, dog breath.
I'm no dog.
I am Sarutobi Sasuke, head
of the Sanada Ninja Clan.
Identify yourself.
Don't get ahead of yourself, Koga monkey.
Those who hear the name Kirigakure
Saizo don't live to tell the tale!
He's Kirigakure?
I hate you Koga bastards!
The feeling is mutual.
But you will lose.
Paralyzing plants?
Saizo!
How weak.
A decoy.
Thanks for the fun, you bastard.
You're not too bad, monkey.
Who is your master?
My master?
Don't assume I'm like you.
Masters don't mean shit to me.
Stop!
Enough already!
I came here to see someone
named Sanada Yukimura!
So this is the formidable Ueda Castle.
It's awfully plain, isn't it?
I thought I'd be excited
to see my first castle.
This better not be trouble.
What?
You idiot!
Well, whatever.
Sit up!
You're not even bowing.
This is the eccentric and clever lord,
Sanada Yukimura.
That's fine, I guess.
Terrible personality.
You're a priestess of Izumo?
Yes.
Then that would make him...
I finally found you.
Please help me.
Please!
First, let's hear your story.
The shrine was a sea of fire.
Everywhere I looked was red...
Red!
Their corpses covered the grounds.
The smell of blood made me sick.
Isanami, hurry!
But the others!
Don't worry about them! Just hurry!
You must survive!
Master!
Seek out Sanada Yukimura of Shinshu.
But what about you?
Sakimitama, Kushimitama... protect her.
Master!
They pursued me, the only survivor.
If Saizo hadn't saved me,
I wouldn't have made it here.
I don't know what to do.
A harsh story for a girl
unfamiliar with war.
And? What do you want me to do?
What?
The priest only told me to
ask for your assistance.
Yeah, but I don't want to be
an accomplice in your revenge.
I never asked you to avenge them!
You said you're being chased?
What if they come after me?
I don't get involved in dangerous work.
Sorry, but there's nothing I can do for you.
But...
Still, even I'm not that cold-hearted.
You can stay here tonight.
Rokuro, prepare a room for her.
Very well.
Hey.
I'm gonna go.
Don't let it get you down.
All lords are like that.
How would you understand?!
Do you know how I felt
coming here from Izumo?!
I left everyone and escaped alone!
I'm the only one who survived...
Hey.
Why are you following me?
Be a good girl and stay in the castle.
But even if I stay there, I don't
know what I'll do tomorrow.
Stay with me.
You're strong.
Besides, maybe we were meant to meet.
I can't have you following me.
Go.
My legs hurt.
I can't take another step!
Fine, then.
I'll just camp out here by myself tonight!
If a wolf eats me, at least
come and collect my bones.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not what you think I am.
Even if you died here, I wouldn't care.
Stop following me.
Saizo!
Their approach was undetectable.
They're stronger than the
ones from this afternoon.
That monkey's owl.
I thought I smelled some raccoon dogs.
You're Ieyasu's men, aren't you?
You used us as bait!
Forgive me. I had to see
what we were up against.
But you're not a man who falls so
easily to enemies like this, are you?
Bring it on.
Watch carefully, Sanada
Yukimura, Sarutobi Sasuke!
Ougi...
Shunko!
Why?
Why did this have to happen?
What did we do?!
Those who mock us will be destroyed.
Hey, Isanami!
Those marks again?
Are you—
Saizo?
You really did save me, Saizo!
Hey.
That was impressive.
The trees rotted away in an instant.
What's going on, old man?
You know something about this?
Who knows?
But those raccoon dogs
won't give up so easily.
Yukimura-sama.
Don't worry.
I'll look after you.
I won't let them have you.
Saizo!
Yukimura-sama, Saizo has no master.
Could you take him in as your own?
What do you think you're saying?!
I've got nothing to do with this.
Don't be like that.
Stay with me in Ueda.
Gimme a break! Just being
around you wears me out!
But I bought you soba.
Don't be ridiculous. That was just...
You owe the girl a favor?
How embarrassing.
As a man, you'll have to repay her.
You'll do physical labor.
I'm counting on you, Saizo.
I don't believe this.
I didn't expect the two of them
to end up here like this.
I suppose you could call it a coincidence.
Rokuro, you saw it, too, didn't you?
Yes.
The power to destroy all living things.
The one who controls that
power controls the world.
That raccoon dog desires
more than he deserves.
It's time to teach him a lesson.
Then...
Hold on. No need to rush, Rokuro.
I don't have enough yet.
I need one brave warrior for each
finger on these two hands.
Besides...
Damn it. My head's pounding.
What are Sarutobi and that guy up to?
Gather brave warriors?
I don't trust that lord,
but it'll be interesting to see
what Sanada Yukimura's planning.
What did he do to me?
It's morning?
What was that for? Ow...
What are you doing half
naked in my futon?
Why not? It's warmer if we sleep together.
But—
Food.
Breakfast?
Isanami? What are you doing here?
Breakfast, breakfast.
Thank you, Sasuke.
Sure.
Monkey, you're not...
Bastard!
Let's get out of here!
Don't screw with me, Sanada ninja!
My breakfast...
This is Saizo's food. Yours is in your room.
Breakfast, breakfast!
What's for breakfast today?
This isn't worth the trouble.
Hey, monkey.
Just so you know, I have no
intention of being your friend.
Nor do I.
You're an insincere womanizer.
Who are you calling a womanizer?!
They're noisy and always
getting in the way.
Sasuke, I didn't get enough food.
Understood. Starting tomorrow,
I'll give you extra.
You biased little monkey!
The next episode of Brave 10
is "Dark and Light."
Bring it on!
Dark and Light