The ice here is in the way.
Then why don't we have
two boats set off here,
and have this boat circle around?
Tomorrow's finally come...
Preparations sure go by fast
when adults are around.
Yeah, definitely.
Thanks for your hard work.
I brought a present.
Oh, thanks.
Though it's just unsold bread.
It's plenty.
You're such a good boy
for running errands.
Hey!
Akira-kun...
Hasn't he been weird lately?
Don't worry about it.
This should be fine.
Oh, Akira, you're here, too?
Come to think of it, this'll be
Akira-kun's first time at an Ofunehiki.
Well, we hadn't done one for a while.
Do you want to take a closer look?
Namaka's.
Yeah.
This pendant...
is filled with Manaka-san's love.
Namaka's love...
Hey.
Akira!
Miuna!
It's so fast...
Why?
There's not even a current...
Huh?
It's melting!
I love Hii-kun.
"I love...
Hii-kun..."
I knew it.
Tsumugu?
"Knew it"?
What do you mean?
I admired it.
Beyond the sea, beyond the sky...
The sun that was so far, far away.
It was so bright.
It shined down on me.
It made me warm.
It made me excited.
But...
"But"?
Hii-kun's the sea.
What?
When I came out of the sea,
the surface that was filled with sunlight was so much fun, and exciting...
But... I realized it's
because the sea was there...
that's why I was able
to admire the surface.
If I'm not by the sea,
my Ena dries up, and I can't breathe.
Does that mean you love Hikari?
Why are you crying?
Because I know how Chii-chan feels...
What?
She said not to tell anyone
that she likes Hii-kun...
I don't want you to
tell anyone either...
Are you sure that's what you want?
Why...
Why didn't you say
anything this whole time?
Because she asked me
not to say anything.
But...
Hikari's worked so hard!
He believed Manaka-san's
love was for you!
He really worked so
hard to get it back...
Hikari said it himself.
To get Mukaido's feelings back,
the person she loves has to work for it.
If that's the case,
Hikari's already done more than enough.
Love is probably like the sea.
Love and the sea?
It's not just all fun and love...
You also have to embrace the sadness,
pain, and everything else...
That's when new feelings are born.
So it wasn't...
one-sided...
Episode Twenty-Five:
Love is Like the Sea
Hikari and Manaka-san
loved each other.
If Manaka-san gets back the ability to love someone after the Ofunehiki...
Then...
I have something I want
to talk to you about.
Is that all right?
I'm sorry, Manaka-san.
No, it's my fault.
Because I don't understand what love is.
Huh?
Manaka-san?
The sound of waves won't go away.
Sound of waves?
When you do that, Miuna-chan,
for some reason,
I feel a little better...
Can we stay like this for a while?
Chisaki.
Can I come in?
Huh?
Sure.
What are you doing?
It's the outfit we're wearing
as the Ojoshi-sama's attendants.
I thought I'd adjust the hems a bit.
I heard from Kaname.
Huh?
About your feelings.
Wh-What are you...
You don't have to lie...
about anything anymore.
No.
Not only you, but Mukaido as well.
What?
Manaka loves Hikari...
I really am awful...
I've hoped...
since a long time ago, and even now...
that Hikari would always love Manaka.
And that Manaka would always
be protected by Hikari.
I didn't want anything to change
between the four of us because
we loved each other so much.
I really wanted Hikari and Manaka
to be in love with each other.
Because that would keep
our relationship unchanged
from how it's always been.
That's not the case now.
It's not because you wanted to protect
the relationships between you four.
You're in love with me.
That's why you were hoping
that they loved each other.
You think way too highly of yourself.
That's just what I thought
when I tied it all together.
Was I wrong?
All right.
I'll think it over again.
Are you really still thinking about it?
About who I really love?
No, I still think that
you're in love with me.
But I'm trying to figure out
how to get you to admit it.
I'm serious.
I know.
You're not going to deny it this time?
Can I hold you?
No...
Chisaki.
No, no, no...
I can't be the only happy one...
No...
Sea Salt
Hikari!
What's the matter?
Hikari, where are you going...
at this hour?
I just thought I'd go
check out the boat.
The boat?
I was just thinking that
tomorrow's the day.
So I wanted to make sure we didn't
miss anything in the preparations.
I hope Manaka-san's love comes back...
But that's not the only thing at stake.
Hopefully we'll be able to do
something about the surface, too.
Yeah, but I hope it comes back.
Apparently that's all girls think about.
You should be more concerned
about the bigger pict—
You love Manaka-san, don't you?
Wh-What are you talking abou—
You love her, right?
Well...
Yeah.
Say it more!
Huh?!
Say it more.
Say that you love Manaka-san more.
A-Are you stupid?
Say it.
In return for all the
things I've done for you.
What kinds of things are you into?!
Say it.
Please...
I'm in love with Manaka.
More!
I love Manaka.
More...
More!
Hey, would you give it a res—
Miuna?
Where are you—
I'm going home!
It hurts...
The love that I feel
for Hikari... hurts.
It needs to hurt more and more,
to push my feelings for
Hikari to a breaking point,
so I can feel like throwing them away.
And then, will I...
Will I be able to give up on Hikari?
Nishiura
Thank you very much.
Congrats, old man Kihara.
Glad to hear that you're
finally allowed to go out.
It's finally time.
I'm so nervous!
I need to check the program.
All right, look up a little.
O-Okay.
Yes, like that.
So...
first we need to get the sacred
fire from Uroko-sama...
This time, the Ofunehiki won't
have any help from the sea.
So it's different from usual
and a bit complicated...
Akira-kun.
Um...
There's something I forgot to tell you.
Thank you for the letter.
Kancho!
Jeez...
So love means...
thank you...
Really, that outfit...
looks so much better on adults
than junior high kids.
Kaname.
Um...
Hm?
Thank you...
Because I played telephone with Tsumugu?
About a lot of things.
Chisaki, you're not thinking
anything weird, are you?
Huh?
Like thinking that you'll become the
Ojoshi-sama instead this time...
All of us were always together.
Then I was the only
one on the surface...
No.
Kaname.
You can't.
Right.
Uroko-sama has arrived!
This way, Uroko-sama.
For the love of...
How dare you trap me
in such a small space?
Hm...
Not bad.
You sound all important.
That's because I am important.
It can't be helped.
So that's the Ojoshi.
Just like every other time, it
looks nothing like the real thing.
So the original Ojoshi
was a lot prettier?
No, not at all.
Huh?
She was a shrimp with
freckles everywhere,
and her body was weak...
Though they call it a sacrifice,
I'm assuming for the
humans on the surface,
it was a convenient way
to get rid of some people.
You... loved the Ojoshi, right?
Well, yes.
Before you fell off the Sea God,
you were the same person...
or rather, the same god, right?
Was it really okay to return
Ojoshi-sama to the surface like that?
I was more...
around the Sea God's
shoulder blade area.
Huh?
If I were the right hand's scale,
I could have touched her hair.
If I were on the left hand,
I could have held her.
However, as soon as I fell off, the
Sea God became something distinct.
Once that happened, I
became but a mere scale...
Not to mention a scale
of a shoulder blade.
What could I speak of the Ojoshi?
Uroko-sama!
It's about to begin so please...
So show me, Hikari.
What you're able to change,
and what you are not.
Look, it's Hikari and the others.
Hey!
Do your best!
Sea God...
How will you respond to the
workings of your children?
Under your divine benevolence,
we, the people of Shioshishio,
have always respected, honored and served
our father, our god, the mighty Sea God,
throughout the years since the beginning of time.
O Sea God, most exalted one,
protect us, your children.
Bless us, and give us prosperity.
A storm's coming...
The lull of the sea...
Manaka!
Manaka-san!
I have to save her!
Manaka doesn't have Ena!
Chisaki!
Everyone!
Kaname!
Everyone, hold onto the boat!
Don't get thrown off!
No...
Namaka!
Miuna!
Get Manaka!
Hikari!
It's so hard to breathe in the sea...
It's so rough...
it hurts.
I'm scared...
The sea that had always
protected me is...
Manaka-san!
Miuna-chan!
The sea is responding
to Miuna's feelings.
What?
Mukaido loves Hikari...
And so does Miuna.
Mukaido's feelings and Miuna's
feelings are very similar.
That's why Mukaido's feelings that
melted into the sea are shining.
Manaka-san!
I understand...
I can sense them.
I can feel your feelings, Manaka-san.
I knew it.
When I'm with you like this, Miuna-chan,
I feel so at ease.
That's because my Ena is
shouting that it loves Hikari.
Huh?
Not just Hikari,
but it's shouting that it loves
the sea and everyone else.
Manaka!
Chisaki!
Take care of Manaka!
Hikari!
This presence...
That's...
The Ojoshi-samas' graveyard?
Miuna!
Sea God, you bastard!
Hikari!
I love Hii-kun.
I love Hii-kun. I love Hii-kun.
Hikari...
I love you...
I love...
Hikari...
I love... you
Miuna!
Love is like the sea...
If she didn't love me...
I'm glad I fell in love with you...
"Miuna"... the beautiful sea...
The calmed sea begins to move.
Final Episode:
The Color of the Sea. The Color of the Earth. The Color of the Wind. The Color of Your Heart. Your Color.