Excuse me!
I'd like a Baby Star monja and a
cod roe mochi cheese and seafood monja!
Wow...
You're still hungry?
Shut up!
I need to eat my mind out!
My heart's still pounding...
Probably because I was so surprised.
That must be it.
I've never had anything
this good before.
I guess everything tastes
good when I'm with you.
The strange throbbing in my chest
shows no sign of slowing.
I more or less know
what's causing it...
A mixed monja with a
double helping of pork!
Huh?  You're still not done?
In any case,
I enjoyed my first experience
with monjayaki,
so it wasn't all bad.
Weird
From a young age, my only
concern was my grades.
I didn't care about anybody
else or anything else.
My world began and ended with me.
1,300 yen for a box of potatoes...
To achieve a 30% margin,
each 700 gram bag
should be priced at 138 yen.
Oh?
What's going on here?
Something on your mind?
That's rare.
If my father knew how to
calculate unit prices,
I wouldn't have to waste my time.
Keep it up!
Cucumbers 100 yen each
Something's wrong with me these days.
Half Price
I'm unable to concentrate
on anything I do.
Samejima-san.
Could you stop putting new
half-price stickers on these?
I certainly understand why that is...
Make-up exam?
Every student who failed a midterm
is required to take the make-up!
Since you forgot to put your name
and received a zero in every subject,
you have to take make-ups!
Are you taking make-ups?
As if.
I had the highest score in our grade.
Then I won't take them either.
Huh?
He would have
scored higher than me
if he had put his name...
B-But, I saw him walking around
in the rain on my way to school!
Don't you feel bad for him?
Right?
Tsk.
Come see Yoshida in 1-B
if you want him as a pet.
Pick on him and I'll kill you.
Whoa!
Oh, this is Yoshida's?
The students had gotten used to
Haru's bizarre behavior by now,
but there was a small
revolution going on inside me.
Why are you ignoring me?
I've been trying to get your attention.
I'm painfully conscious
of his presence.
Can you blame me?
I've never been close to
another human before.
How am I supposed to ignore him?
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?!
Don't pick on the rooster!
He doesn't seem to care.
Um...
What's going on?
I'm acting like...
Um...
...I'm in love with Haru.
Syoyo
High
School
This could be difficult.
Haru.
Hmm?
You said that y—
You love me.
Yep.  I love you, Shizuku.
In a romantic way?
I would totally do you.
What's that supposed to mean?
Anyway, can you take the rooster?
If you don't mind me deep frying him.
Mi—
Mizutani-san!
Cleaners
Please help me study!
Tecchan
Okonomiyaki
Monja
My name is Natsume Asako.
Do you know who I am?
No?
We're in the same class.
By the way, Yoshida-kun
keeps glaring at me...
With that rooster...
Just ignore him.
He's scared of you.
Oh, excuse me.
Can I get another pork and
egg with cod roe mochi?
And I'd like the kimchi
tempura and curry mix.
Sure.
You girls really like to eat.
So, as I was saying before,
if I fail the make-up exams,
I'll have to take a
remedial class next week.
However, I have an important
appointment with my friends that day,
so I can't fail the exam.
Mizutani-san, that's where—
I refuse.
I've done what I can,
but...
I'm too stupid!
No kidding.
You answered every question
and still failed.
Sorry, but that's your problem.
If you're so stupid, you should
take the remedial class.
Er, um...
There you go then.
W-Wait!
Please wait, Mizutani-san!
Tecchan
Okonomiyaki
Monja
I beg you!
Oh, it stopped raining.
I don't have time
to take a remedial class!
Sorry about that.
I had too much to eat.
You were forcing yourself
to eat all of that?
If I were a light eater,
too many boys would fall for me.
I'm sure you've noticed how cute I am.
Boys always flock to me.
That's why I'm always shunned by girls.
W-Wait for me!
That spot is dry.
Please look at this.
High School Community
The appointment I mentioned earlier
was an offline gathering for the members
of an online community that I belong to.
The members are all strangers,
but they're the first
friends I've ever made.
That's why you don't want
to take the remedial class?
Yes.
I still refuse.
Evil!
This is what you get
for being a slacker.
Give up.
Mercy, please!
Hey.
I can help you study.
R-Really?!
Yeah, I got you covered.
In return, take me with you.
Okay!  Okay!
Will I be able to make friends
at this offline gathering?
You bet!  You bet!
Oh, but please don't
fall in love with me.
It'd be a hassle.
Yeah, not a problem.
That's never happening.
Math I
Let's start with math.
Thank you very much!
Yep, you're welcome.
Why are they doing this here?
Okay, watch closely.
Yes!
You do this...
...to get this.
I don't understand!
Okay, memorize that.
And for Japanese, English,
and history, read the textbook.
All done.
Well, at least I'm not
alone with Haru...
Idiot.
You make the x squared an x.
Yes...
No, how did you get 5, stupid?
Here, look closely.
Not at me.
Oh, yes!
You do this...
Hmm?  What was that?
You don't get any.
Have you seen that girl around?
Y-You mean Natsume-san?
No...
Damn, where'd she go?
Oh, there it is again.
I feel so agitated.
Nagoya, want some cabbage?
H-Ho—
How's the studying going?
I-It's too late to trade places now!
I'm the one going to the offline event!
Not my point.
Is it really such a big deal?
You and Natsume-san are so odd.
Does it really matter that
people don't like you?
You're really special, Shizuku.
What was that look about?
Have you ever felt empty inside?
Huh?
So empty...
you can't feel a thing.
Surrounded by darkness.
It really scares me.
But I'm not scared anymore...
because I have you.
As Haru spoke,
it almost seemed that he
couldn't see anything at all,
even though I was right there...
Listen up.  Black holes are...
What's that?
Please help me study.
There's definitely
something wrong with me.
I never would have thought
about these things before.
I didn't care what other
people thought about me.
I need to study.
Final exams are coming up.
Tests, tests, tests...
There's so much background noise
that I can't concentrate.
Man, it's hot...
The upperclassmen aren't being fair.
I know.
Mizutani-san.
Who are you?
What?
You should try to remember the
faces of your classmates.
I'm Sasahara.
You can call me Sasayan.
Oh...
So, did you need something?
Not really.
I'm interested in you.
Why?
Because I like you.
You're lying.
You can tell?
You've been hanging out with Yoshida,
so I was wondering what you were like.
So, how did you get that
truant to come to school?
Beats me.
I have no idea what he's thinking.
I'm guessing he just wanted a
friend.  Didn't matter who.
I went to the same middle
school as Yoshida.
Did you know?
He basically went three years
without coming to class.
What?
Well, anything's possible with Haru...
My point is,
the "who" must have mattered.
Sasayan, we're heading back!
Okay!
See ya, Mizutani-san.
Sasayan-kun!
I have a favor to ask.
Um...
What are you doing, Natsume-san?
Please don't mind me.
I'm in despair right now.
Yoshida-kun!
Shut up!
You're not supposed to
bring roosters to school!
You're such a pain!
Hold it right there, Yoshida-kun!
It's all over...
I didn't understand anything
that he taught me,
and there's no time left...
Well, students are supposed to
spend their time studying.
Hmph!  Who cares about school?!
The real me lives on the Internet!
On the Internet,
I'm constantly surrounded by friends.
Everyone comes to me for help.
I'm just an ordinary girl
with hair problems.
Wouldn't that be considered
living a lie?
Just leave me alone.
Someone who's smart and unfeeling
would never understand.
I-I'm not...
I don't care if I'm living a lie.
I want to be close to other people.
It's lonely when everyone
keeps their distance.
Here, here, and here.
If you focus on these
sections, you should pass.
There's a certain pattern
to the test questions used,
so if you nail these key
points, you won't fail.
H-Huh?
Mi-Mizutani-san?
I still don't know what
they're thinking,
but I think I can understand
how they feel.
Haru.
Do you want to go to
the offline gathering?
Yep!
Well, he's set on going,
so you need to pass the make-ups.
M-Mitty!
The make-ups are tomorrow.
Is that enough time?
What?
No turning back now.
Stop sleeping!
Why can't you memorize
a simple formula?!
Evil!
You realize I'm pulling
an all-nighter for you?!
Why are you kids studying here?
Stop sleeping!
Can I go home yet?
Thanks to my hard work,
Natsume-san was exonerated
from the remedial class.
My highest score ever!
But on Monday...
Haru-kun ruined everything!
I'm never going to one of those again.
I didn't get a chance
to talk to any girls...
Then, Haru-kun got in a fight.
Moron!
The Qilin is an OOPArt!
Science
Classical Literature
Music
World History
English\Home Economics
When I logged on to the community again,
everybody gave me the cold shoulder.
High School Community
Told you so.
I quit.
Hey!
Yoshida-kun!  Ow!
How many times must I tell you
not to bring this rooster?!  Ow!
Oh.
I forgot to tell you.
Huh?
Sasahara-kun volunteered to
take care of the rooster.
Sure, I like fried chicken.
Where are you?
Hey, Shizuku?
Mitty, Haru-kun's looking for you.
He reminds me of when my
dad's looking for his socks.
Don't say anything.
If he finds me, it'll get noisy again.
You look tired.
Oh.
I'll buy you something to drink.
To thank you for helping me study.
Finally, some peace and quiet.
I've been spending more time
around other people than
I thought was possible,
so I'm exhausted.
Mitty, I bought you some juice...
Shh.
I'm cheering for you, Haru-kun!
Yo.
Ha-Haru?!
When did you...
Oh, I'm missing class!
Go back to sleep.
Why didn't you wake me up?
Hmm?
You were out like a light.
I thought it was cute.
Seriously...
I have to wonder if he's
doing this on purpose.
This is the first time
I've ever skipped class.
It's a beautiful day.
The old me
would never have known how
blue the afternoon sky
looks from the roof.
My world is growing.
What I once considered background noise
is now comforting.
It feels so good.
Haru.
Hmm?
I'm glad we met.
Before, I only cared about studying,
but I'm going to start enjoying myself.
I love you, Haru.
My values are changing.
Perhaps, my world has also changed.
If so,
my world was changed
by Haru.
Natsume-san, do you have a moment?
Y-Yes!
Helpful Advice from Golubaeser Asako
New Entry
into a human shape
and your own hair
burn
First, secure two strands of hair from the target
to make him or her yours
How did you get here?
Are you lost?
Oh, have you heard this song before?
Chicken, chicken, chicken!
Chicken, chicken!
Next Episode
Nuisance
Time to chow down!