Souta.
Oneesan.
You're on vacation.
Why not go talk to a girl?
No one wants to talk to me.
I'd rather just take a nap here.
A hat?
Thank you.
So, who are you?
Me?
I'm Sakura.
Sakura.
Hey, would you like to
play a game with me?
A game?
If Her Flag Breaks
Flag 2
Girls are in the Dorm.
But I can't say it yet. Wait Until Tomorrow.
Good morning, Nanami.
Leave me alone, you perv.
I already explained that.
Hmph.
I needed to do something to
overwrite her death flag.
Hmph. Like I believe that.
Souta-kun.
H-Hi...
Good morning.
Oh, hi.
Akane, you should be more careful around
a perv who'd kiss a defenseless girl.
W-Well...
If Souta-kun wants to be a perv,
he should have just said so!
Don't break her flag!
You shouldn't just
brush people off, okay?
I know.
I can't break her conquest flag, anyway.
Sou-kun!
Huh?
Is that you,
Okiku-nee?
I knew it was you!
It's Sou-kun!
Sou-kun!
You're alive. You're alive!
It's the real Sou-kun, right?
H-Hey, wait.
She tackled him!
Are they a couple, or something?!
Why is she on top of him?
I was worried about you this whole time!
I couldn't get a hold of you.
Your mom and dad...
Yeah...
Also Oneesan...
Oneesan? You're an only
child, aren't you?
I see...
I guess you don't remember, either.
Hey! What are you two doing?!
No! No!
I've known Sou-kun since we were kids!
Since you were kids?
Sou-kun transferred
away in middle school,
and I haven't seen him in two years!
He's gotten so big!
Why are you in this class when you
should be with the second-years?
Well, last year, I was studying overseas,
so I ended up a year behind.
This was my seat! Right next to Sou-kun!
I didn't think he'd transfer
away while I was out sick!
What a troublemaker.
R-Right...
Huh?
Kiku's Eye
Sou-kun, you look like you're warn out.
You can sleep on my lap
and I'll clean your ears.
You liked that, didn't you?
I'm sure that'll make you feel better.
W-Wait...
She's being too nice to him!
She's spoiling him!
She's an older sister type!
This is terrible! Terrible!
This is where you're living?
You just feel terrible
for Sou-kun, don't you?
Not you, too, Akane.
You already knew he was living here.
Kikuno-senpai started crying,
so I started crying, too...
Akane-chan, so you're
crying for Sou-kun, too!
When did Akane-chan and Nanami-chan
Kiku's Eye
get so close to Sou-kun?!
Huh?
Sou-kun is spending time with other girls,
and he kept them secret from me...
That can't be...
O-Okiku-nee...
She went crazy!
Onee-chan's happy!
Huh?
I mean, Akane-chan and Nanami-chan,
you're both good girls.
I approve!
Take good care of Sou-kun.
R-Right!
I'll take care of him with Nanami-chan!
Why me, too?!
Hey, Souta!
Don't just stand there! Say something!
I'm actually happy the two
of them are getting along.
So what's the problem?
Don't sacrifice me for their friendship!
Kiku's Eye
Sou-kun looks so lonely...
It's okay, Sou-kun!
I'll make sure both of them
stay good friends with you!
On, no!
I can't believe I let
Souta-kun become lonely!
I'm a failure of a friend!
If we stay like this,
we can all be friends!
Hey.
So what are we going to do?
What's going on?!
Is this some kind of dark art?!
So that's when I...
Souta, does Kikuno have a flag, too?
Yeah...
That's the sibling love flag.
I see.
So that's what makes
her act like this.
Try breaking her sister flag.
You told me not to break
them this morning.
You're going to end up
being treated like
a little brother your
entire life at this rate!
Is there a problem with that?
You like being a little
brother that much?!
I don't like it.
That should be enough for you!
Don't be ridiculous.
Sou-kun.
Telling Nanami-chan a secret?
You should let me in on it, too.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Just leave me alone!
What?!
Oh, I know.
You're just embarrassed
because other girls are here.
Silly boy.
It doesn't seem to have been effective!
The flag dodged it.
Dodged it?
Yeah, at mach speed.
Tea club
A baby?
Ryuukishibara Tsumugi, the Elder.
It's said that she's been here since
before the school was founded.
She's in our class.
Didn't you notice her?
R-Right.
But why... aren't you wearing a skirt?
You don't know how to wear
Japanese clothes properly?
Everyone's forgetting tradition
because of the West.
Anyway, can we do something
about this, granny?
That'll be difficult.
That building was constructed
when the school was founded.
It's going to take some
significant work to clean up.
The Japanese population is dropping,
and we don't have a large budget—
getting the place rebuilt
is a tall order.
Please do something for Sou-kun!
Young'uns these days rely
on others far too much!
You should try to do something on your—
I think that's enough nonsense
for one day, granny!
You call this "nonsense," Mimori?
Don't come in here with shoes on, either.
You called for me,
so you already had
something in mind, right?
Anyway, I'm here now.
I'm the student council
president you can depend on.
My name: Seiteikouji Mimori!
Student Council President
Student council president?!
It'll be faster to just
rebuild the whole thing.
Leave it to me!
I've already called
in the professionals.
Professionals?
Hatagaya Academy's Engineering
Research Society.
Why does the school even have
an organization like that?!
Takumi
Engineering here!
Engineering Research Here!
I can see you wrecked another place.
That's rude!
It wasn't me this time!
How long will it take for you to fix this
place up so he can live here?
I'd like you to do something as
soon as possible for Sou-kun here.
It's going to take a
month to do all of this.
That might be different if we could
get some more people on the project.
Then will this work?
Hm?
You're living in this place?
If we'd only known sooner...
I asked the class to help.
Good work, Akane!
This'll be more than enough.
All right, guys!
We're doing this in a week!
Right!
I'd like to thank you all
for listening to my request.
Thank you for helping Sou-kun!
I guess I owe you all...
Leave it to us!
Aren't you glad, Souta-kun?
It's all thanks to all
of you, Akane, Okiku-nee.
Akane's eye
It's all thanks to you, Akane.
Wh-What's up?
You've got a wonderful smile!
What?!
Just seeing it makes me so happy!
Jeez.
Bliss
You're like a cake made
out of bliss itself.
Poet-san
Nanami-chan, you're a poet!
No!
Way to go, Nanami-chan!
I'm coming, too!
Me, too!
Souta, was it?
Granny?
Remember this.
This isn't a favor.
Everyone's doing it out of their hearts.
You don't return goodwill with goodwill.
You keep it in your heart.
It will grow inside you, and change you,
and then one day you'll grow into
a person that can have
goodwill towards others.
Yeah.
That's impressive.
It's like a whole different place.
Keep flattering me!
You didn't do a single thing, though.
We only have finishing
touches left to make,
so feel free to start moving in.
Okay, everyone!
Time to finish this bad boy up!
Right!
I can't get this by myself.
Sorry, could you help me here?
I need a man to help me here.
Huh?
Me?
I'm a boy?
Uh, I'm sorry if I was wrong.
No, you're right. I'm a guy.
People always treat me like a girl.
This is the first time someone thought
I was a guy the first time we talked!
Th-These are friendship flags, right?
How do I destroy these...
Wait... Can I even destroy these?
My nice is Touzokuyama Megumu!
Nice to meet you, Hatate-kun!
You can call me Souta.
Then you...
You can call me Megumu, Souta-kun!
You can tell men are friends when
they call each other by name.
Men, huh?
Everyone in our class calls
me Megu like I'm a girl.
I-I see.
So, what's up with that uniform, Megumu?
Onee-chan said I look
a lot cuter this way,
and got approval from the school
to have me dress this way...
I see.
I understand how you feel.
Your sister must be a tough cookie.
Thank you!
You're the only one who understands!
Why do you smell so good?
And your skin's so soft.
Souta-kun, do you need some help—
I-I'm sorry!
I'll help you out!
What are you going on about?!
I always help couples find new partners!
Then you're not helping at all!
No! No!
We were just being friendly!
How nice.
I wish I could do that.
Men and women can be great friends!
Clench
Akane, Megumu is a boy!
Look at his uniform!
Oh, I didn't notice.
Sorry about that.
That's why I never saw Megu-chan
with the girls in PE.
But everyone still calls me Megu...
Sou-kun...
Hey!
I take my eyes off of you for a second,
and you're already with another girl.
I... just don't know what to do!
Okiku-nee! Megumu isn't a girl!
Look he's wearing a men's uniform!
I didn't notice!
Sorry, but Megu-chan's always
in the girls' bathroom.
H-Hey.
When I go to the men's bathroom,
everyone always gets uncomfortable.
So the girls are okay with
me using the girls' bathroom.
I-I see.
So this is where you've been, Souta.
Hm? You couldn't find another guy?
Well, this is a problem.
Hatate is the only one
in this dorm, right?
That's right. Why?
According to the rules, any dorm with
a single resident will be shut down.
You tell us this now?!
Take away our careless
student council president!
You need to have at least five people!
Those are the rules!
Mimori says that,
but I'm sure you'll get five
friends together in a hurry.
That's a terrible rule.
I can't trust her.
Even if you don't have any friends,
you do have an "oneechan."
It's fine.
I'm used to being alone.
That's not good! You shouldn't be alone!
I-I'll move in here!
This is a men's dorm, isn't it?
It's an old dorm.
No need to worry about formalities.
Yeah, but there can't just be two of us
there... We're the opposite sex, and all.
I'll move in here, then.
That's even worse!
U-Um...
I-I want to move in too.
You, too, Megumu?!
Three women and one man.
That balances out well.
Now we only need one more.
Please not another girl.
I don't know any men...
Um, Nanami-chan is...
Hey, it's just a joke, Nanami-chan.
Sou-kun's good friends with you, Nanami.
Of course you can come.
I never said I wanted to live here!
If I don't get that corner room,
I'm not moving in!
H-Hey, you can't just...
Well, I guess... it'll be fun.
Not the black arts again!
I said it'll be fun,
but why are we all gathering in my room?
No choice.
We all suddenly decided to move in,
so you're the only one with any stuff.
Then you didn't have to move in today.
No. Everything's going to end if
we leave you alone for even a second.
It's true I'm alone in the world, but...
It's my first time in a
room of a male friend.
I'm kind of nervous.
It feels more like you've entered your
boyfriend's room, not your friend's.
If we're all going to live together,
then we need to decide
a bunch of things.
Like who's going to be in charge,
or who's on duty for what.
You've sure thought this through, Okiku-nee.
I am the "oneechan," after all!
But before that we need to take a bath.
Bath
Girls are Bathing
No Peeking
That's nice.
Yeah, but I wanted to
get in with Sou-kun,
like we used to do.
You mean a really long time ago,
when you were small, right?
Oh, you jealous?
If you're jealous, you can go
ahead and call me "oneechan."
Did you finally fall
for him, Nanami-chan?!
You finally stopped being
that weird "tsundere"?
What is that even supposed to mean?!
Akane-chan, are you rooting
for Sou-kun and Nanami-chan?
I-I just want
to make Souta-kun happy...
Akane-chan, you're a nice girl.
You're a member of the
"Make Sou-kun happy" alliance.
What do members of that do?
They watch Sou-kun be
happy and feel good.
Aren't we supposed to be
the ones making him happy?!
Even Akane can't keep
up with her craziness.
This is awkward...
I need to get a conversation
going with Megumu.
Hm?
Men
Men!
A-A "men" flag?!
Souta-kun, we're going
to look in the bath.
Huh?
We're going to go,
walk straight in, and get an eyeful.
Now come.
W-Wait a second!
You know,
I'm pretty sure that
real men wouldn't look.
Crap!
Souta-kun, don't look!
It's not manly!
Okiku-nee!
Akane!
Keropon
Why are you here?!
Man, that hurt.
That really sucked.
Hm?
That was...
Hatate Souta
A letter?
What's this about?
Oh well.
I thought I'd be able to
put up a better fight.
The knight, magician,
samurai, dragon knight, bishop,
ninja, thief, summoner.
The magician is troublesome.
If possible, you should
get rid of him first.
You need the knight for protection.
He will always follow the Royal Banner.
The bishop acts as a decoy, and
the ninja attacks from behind.
I get it.
So that's what I should have done.
Oniisan, you haven't forgotten
your promise, have you?
The person who loses will listen
to whatever the winner says.
Right?
I wonder you're going to tell me to do.
I'm not going to tell
you to do anything.
I want to ask you for something.
I didn't win because I was good.
Above my head I have the "victor" flag,
and above yours, you
have the "defeat" flag.
Flag?
I will give you my power.
And in exchange,
you must learn the ultimate
truth of this world.
I wonder what answer you'll
give when you find it...
I'm excited.
W-Wait!
Sakura!
"Princess knight, magician, clergyman,
ninja..."
Flags...
The Premium Ambriel"...
My forgotten "nee-san."
Sakura...
The ultimate truth of this world...
Roar! Gawo!
So we're having our athletic meet and I
don't even remember having much class.
I'm going to find the best
place to film, for Sou-kun!
Now you're acting more like a
dad instead of an older sister!
We're all going to get together
and cheer for Souta-kun.
Akane-chan is going to get me a great
outfit that showcases just how manly I am.
I think that's obviously
the "cheerleader girl" flag.
Flag 3
Leave it to Me,
There is a 99.9% Chance We're Going to Win This Athletic Meet
Roar! Gawo!
If Her Flag Breaks
I hope you watch us next time!
Illustration: Fujima Takuya