Looks like another hot day.
Good thing Kana-chan said we
don't have to wear hakama.
Yeah, I would die if I
had to wear that thing.
Are you okay, Chihaya?
I'm okay.
Well, let's get going.
Nobody forgot anything, right?
No!
Listen up, everyone.
There is no preliminary round
for the individual tournament,
so there will be over 400 competitors.
Ayase-san is in Class A.
Mashima-kun and Nishida-kun are in Class B.
Komano-kun and Oe-san are in Class D.
You'll be playing in different rooms,
but I want you to play your very best
against your rivals from
all over the country.
Yes, ma'am!
That makes us enemies today, Desktomu-kun!
I won't lose!
I'm aiming to win Class B!
Y-Yeah...
What's wrong with you, Mashima?
Show some fire.
Nishida.
Class B players...
only get matched against
other Class B players, right?
Of course.
Next time, we'll meet in a match.
-Arata
Chihaya Furu
Verse 14
For There
Is No
One
Else
Out
Here
Please sit down in your assigned seat
once you've checked who your opponent is.
Um...
Ayase Chihaya
Oh, there I am.
Hanamoto Ruri
I'm playing Hanamoto-san from Kagoshima.
I wonder what she's like.
Ayase.
Whoa!  Sudo-san!
The Queen is here.
Huh?
Look.  She's playing our
Amakasu in the first round.
Amakasu Nayuta
Wakamiya Shinobu
Wakamiya...
Wakamiya Shinobu.
She made Class A when she
was in fourth grade.
She's a first-year high
school student in Kyoto.
Huh?
The youngest Queen in history.
Oh, it's her.
The girl I saw at Omi Jingu yesterday.
She's wearing another lame T-shirt!
And it's tucked in!
Always the...
Why a snowman?
She's cute, but she has the
fashion sense of a rock.
Oh?  You came to play, Sudo-san?
Hello, Queen.
Please don't call me that.
I was so relieved when
I found out that I'm not
playing you in the first round.
But...
You came all the way out here to
play in the individual tournament
after failing to make the team tournament?
You must really love karuta.
Well, please go easy on me if we end up
playing each other.
I'm gonna kill her!
Huh?!
She's rubbing it in my face!
I'm gonna crush you, too!
Payback for regionals!
The Queen:
the top female karuta player in Japan.
My goal...
High School National Ogura Hundred
Poets Karuta Championship
I wonder how she plays karuta.
I wonder how strong she is.
Good luck.
I need to win fast so I
can watch the Queen play.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
No more can we hear...
Yes!
As my love first came...
Huh?
The tail feathers of...
It was silly of me to
think I could win fast.
Every player here is Class A!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much...
Huh?
They're already finished?
No.  Concentrate.
Remember the positions of the cards.
Double check.
Play this one card at a time.
May it be...
Wakamiya Shinobu
She beat Amakasu from Hokuo by 24 cards?
Does that mean he only took one card?
She's good.
No wonder she's the Queen.
She brought her own cup.
Hot tea...
We will now post the
pairings for the second round.
I want to play the Queen.
I don't want to play the Queen.
I'm gonna take her down!
Anyone but the Queen!
I'm too scared to face her!
I can't do it!
I want to play her...
Wakamiya Shinobu
I don't want to play her...
I want to play her!
Ayase Chihaya
Oh, Ayase-san.
I borrowed a camcorder from Oe-san's mother.
I'll be recording everyone's matches today-
Memorization time is over!
Good luck.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower blooms,
but for winter
We're right next to the reader.
Close enough to hear her breathe...
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Hear her exhale...
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Listen for the first syllable!
Loo—
—k for the sound...
What was that?!
but instead you see a pale
moon in the dawn sky
Her hand is still a blur in slow motion!
I feel as—
I can't see her move.
—though I am like...
The hazy field...
Her hand slices through
the air, like a needle.
Silent karuta!
The second round for Class B
is about to begin.
Please sit down in your assigned seat
once you've checked who your opponent is.
Oh, I win by default.
No fair, Mashima!
You're going to cheer for
Kana-chan in her Class D match!
Why do you think I'm going to watch Oe-san?
I told Kana-chan to come cheer
me on if her match ended early.
So if you're going to watch Class D,
tell Kana-chan that I'm rooting for her.
Hey!
Let's see...
Ayase Chihaya
Wakamiya Shinobu
Wakamiya Shinobu?
Chihaya's playing against the Queen!
She's moving so fast that I
can't tell what's happening.
But one thing is clear,
Ayase-san's field has the same
number of cards as before.
Please remain quiet
during matches.
hear the beating of cloth,
as a chilly autumn breeze
Chihaya...
descends from Mount Yoshino
upon my long-forgotten home
While it brings me no joy...
Sh-She's fast!
What was that?!
She's so fast.
She's so fast that I can't see a thing!
Ms. Miyauchi,
can I have a look?
Y-Yes...
Chihaya reacted first.
As soon as she heard "While it",
she moved towards the "While it may"
card on the opponent's side.
She was positioned perfectly to come back
for the "While it brings" card on her own side.
But the Queen didn't move until
she heard the third syllable...
She's so fast that she can afford to wait?
So the flower pe—
—tals are scattered like the
snow by the passing storm,
Chihaya...
Here we go again.
She's already up by ten cards?
Wakamiya Shinobu's on a
whole different level.
I feel bad for the girl playing her.
She's probably ready to throw in the towel.
Chihaya is just as fast as the Queen
when she's focused on one card.
But there are dozens of cards on the field.
She can't focus on that many
cards at the same time.
But the Queen can do it?
Stay calm...
The Queen must be vulnerable somewhere.
She left the "May the time spent" and
"May the time we" cards next to each other,
even though "May the scarlet" has been read, so
I could just hit both cards after hearing "May the".
I am stunned!
Why wouldn't you separate those cards?!
It baffles me!
She's asking for it...
Go!
Hit both cards at the same time!
Chihaya, it's so obvious what you're doing!
My fear is no...
The sight of Mount Arima...
See?
This is what happens when
you focus on one card!
But that first card is always big.
You haven't given up yet, right?
Chihaya, show everyone your
ability to go on the attack!
May the—
There it is!
—time we spend apart from one another be
What?!
Mashima-kun, who took that card?
It was hard to tell.
Yes...
What happens when neither player
is sure who took the card?
They can ask the judge or
discuss it between themselves.
However, the best players always know.
I was aiming to hit both cards,
but the Queen was aiming for
a single point on the field.
What am I supposed to do...
What am I supposed to do?
Chihaya-chan, go on the attack.
Your primary focus should always be
to push the opponent's side.
I'm on the attack.
I don't know how to do anything else!
Daddy Bear?!
Huh?
Excuse me.
Huh?  What?!
Is she talking about my T-shirt?!
The Queen is wearing a Snowmaru T-shirt!
Snowmaru only has an official shop in Osaka
so you have to order everything online!
He's a super cute character with a topknot
when he takes the bucket off his head!
It's my most attractive feature.
No, concentrate on the match.
Right.
The Queen is a 16-year-old girl,
just like me.
I can beat her.
as short-lived as the reeds of Naniwa Bay
That was bad.
Stay focused.
Said world offers no change...
Did you see that?!
Wow...
Grr.
What was that about?!
She made a weird move.
Yes, she was covering her own card.
Covering?
"Said world offers no change"
was on Chihaya's side.
"Said world offers no escape"
was on the Queen's side.
These are multi-syllable cards,
and you have to wait to hear
the next syllable after the "no",
so players cover their own cards
to prevent them from being taken.
You can do that?
Both players were covering their own cards,
then the card on Chihaya's side was read.
All she had to do was
press down on the card.
But before Chihaya was able to do that,
the Queen slipped her hand underneath.
I can't do it.
I don't see how
I can win.
I feel so bad for her.
This is like a public execution.
I really hope I don't have to play her.
At this rate, she'll lose before
she can take a single card.
If you fall too far behind,
when the fisherman who casts
his nets can seem dear
it becomes difficult to go on the attack.
Since there's a higher chance
that a card on your own side will be read.
You unconsciously shift
to a defensive posture.
My own home is...
Plus, she has total control
over her own side.
The Queen is playing defensive karuta.
You can't break through,
but Chihaya doesn't have a choice.
Hang in there, Chihaya!
While it may be...
What was that, Chihaya?
Why didn't you attack that card?
Oh, not again.
My opponents are always fired
up when the match starts.
I get to play the Queen!
Time to make myself look good!
But...
Soon enough, it's like I'm back to playing
karuta by myself again.
Well, I don't really mind.
Let's make this quick.
She's up by 15 cards?
Yeah.
Huh?  What?
What happened?!
Sorry!  I'm sorry!
Taichi...  Ms. Miyauchi...
You can do this, Chihaya!
Keep trying, Ayase-san!
But I don't know what I should do.
I can't take a single card off
her if I play my usual karuta.
This has never happened before.
I never show mercy.
I'm mad.
I want to take a card.
I should at least be able to take one card!
Excuse me.
Whenever Sudo was in a bad
position, he would stand up
and act all arrogant.
Huh?
Is the Queen left-handed?
Ugh, I just now realized this?
I'm really out of it!
Sorry about that.
I can't be mentally weaker now
than I was when I was 12!
Oh?
She's back?
Hmm...
I wonder how long she'll last this time.
I volunteer to shield the
people with my dark sleeves
When winds send waves...
She attacked before coming back!
It's close!
Who was first?
The Queen was faster
because she went straight
for the attack while
I attacked before coming back.
But this is how I learned to play karuta!
Chihaya-chan, think about it.
If you can take a card from
the far row of a player
who's big on defense,
you'll give them a big shock!
This is how I get back in the game!
I recall how my own efforts were in vain
May the time spent in our...
She hit my hand?
So it was close?
Oh, impressive.
You did it, Chihaya!
It's your first card!
No, we touched it at the same time,
and the card was on your side.
Why?!  Take the card, Chihaya!
Nobody turns down a card!
Oh.
Ah!  Oops!
Every card on the field is yours.
Contest every card that you can.
I just broke one of Dr. Harada's
cardinal rules of karuta...
But this is the Omi Learning Center.
The Master and Queen matches are
played on this tatami floor.
I don't want any flukes.
The first card I take from her...
...will lead me to that January final.
Ogura Hundred Poets Karuta
Master & Queen Finals
Such a strange girl...
bring a life of everlasting love
—ust of wind leaves fall leaves falling
She took a one-syllable card
from the Queen's favored side!
Whoa, I've never seen the Queen
lose a one-syllable card before!
Didn't she start moving
while "Gust" was being read?
The "G"...
This is what Dr. Harada meant.
Chihaya can hear "Gust"
before it's actually spoken.
Her ears pick up that hard "G"...
"Gust of wind" is one of Chihaya's best cards.
hence the name fall leaves
My first card...
This is my first card again.
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Chihaya!
hence the name fall leaves
Impassionate gods...
She got it!
Chihaya!
She converted on the card she sent!
Two in a row!
This card...
will lead me to the Queen title!