Koumei Private High School
List of Accepted Candidates
General Studies
(Late Exams)
Kotarou Azumi
Not Accepted
I've lived a life full of embarrassments.
Sorry.
I didn't get in.
It's okay.
You worked so hard for me.
That's more than enough.
Thanks.
I'm going to apply for a municipal school.
Okay.
Yeah?
You know...
They say nothing an author
goes through is in vain.
It all gets put to use in writing.
Why not write?
You might feel a little better.
That's how it goes sometimes.
Yeah.
What are you going to do now?
With your boyfriend.
Long distance?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
About what?
Boys see that kind of thing as a hassle.
I don't want to see you cry.
I'll be fine.
Why don't you break up?
You're a jerk, Nee-chan.
I can't stop you if you like him, I guess.
Azumi-kun: Are you awake?
I'm done studying
Good job
Thanks
What's up?
Making this lol
That gives me strength
Good!
Okay, see you at school
Yup, goodnight
Goodnight,
sleep rhine
Acceptance
Announcements
Exam Ticket
Candidate No. 1067
I got in
Congrats
Hey.
Did you get in?
Yeah.
Me, too!
Yay!
I was actually kind of worried.
We'll be together in high school, huh?
Looking forward to it.
Me, too.
I'm super, super happy.
It's not that big of a deal.
It is.
I feel a bit bad for Akane, though.
Sorry, should I stop talking about this?
It's fine.
What are you going to do now?
With Akane.
What? I guess...
we'll keep things the way they've been.
Hey, I was never able to tell you...
Especially since Akane's a friend,
and I don't want to hurt her...
But...
I have to tell you properly.
I've always liked you, Kota.
Would I not be good enough?
Sorry.
I'm glad I got that out.
I'll see you in high school.
Right.
Okay, later.
Yeah.
Self Study
Thanks!
Let's hang out after we know where
we're going, just the three of us!
Yeah! I can't wait
I passed
Congrats!
And then
I confessed to Azumi-kun
He rejected me, of course
Sorry, Akane
Nah
Will you still be my friend?
Yup!
Thanks!
Now that exams are over
Kotarou-kun
Want to hang out?
Let's do it!!
How about the day after grad?
Sure
Okay, it's a promise
Pinky promise
Prologue
If there's such a thing as a god of fate, he must be quite a troll.
He's a real jerk, always setting up seeming coincidences
just to bewilder us for his own entertainment.
But right now, I wouldn't mind thanking that jerk of a god.
He hooked us up on equipment duty of all things, after all.
It was spring when I met her.
Crying already?
We're going to be BFFs, okay?
Azumi!
Come on, stand closer, Azumi.
Okay, here we go.
You're both so stiff.
All right, see you.
Okay.
Thanks.
You lucky bastard!
You looked like crap, Kota.
Really?
Your eyes were dead.
I stayed up all night writing.
Are you writing again, Sensei?
I guess.
What's it about?
I'm not telling you.
You're writing smut, aren't you?
I bet you are!
I'm not.
I want to read it.
Hell no.
What's the point in writing, then?
Post it on a novel board.
A what?
Mizuno.
You better keep running in high school.
Yeah.
You, too.
I'll see you on the field again.
Yeah.
Become an Author!
Title    Required
Subtitle    Required
Posting story. Continue?
[Back]       [Post]        [Preview]
Story posted.
Akane-chan.
Sorry.
Did I keep you waiting?
No.
Moving must be a lot of work.
We're used to it.
It's tomorrow, huh?
Yeah.
When can we meet again?
Whenever.
Can I come visit you?
Yeah.
I'll come every week.
Yeah...
Should I not?
No, I mean, train fare costs a lot.
I'll find work.
I will, too.
What about track?
I want to continue, but...
Don't worry, I'll go.
I can make enough for train fare
if I work, like, three times a week.
But...
Two hours each way?
Yeah.
I'll take the first train.
So we can have more time.
It'll be the same as always.
We have LINE, too.
But...
You're taking on the whole burden.
It'll be fine.
I have money saved up, too.
Don't worry about it.
That's not it!
Akane-chan...
I want to ask you something.
Okay.
Did she confess to you?
Chinatsu told me.
She did.
Why?
Why didn't you tell me?
Well...
I turned her down.
Shouldn't you tell me that?
I get worried.
What's wrong?
I don't know, but...
Why?
I keep getting anxious.
So anxious...
I keep causing trouble for you.
That's what hurts me the most.
What should I do?
Honey, can I throw this out?
What is "this"?
Don't get in the way of the movers.
Mom, the movers are calling you.
Tell Dad.
Akane, do you have everything?
Yeah.
That's everything.
Crap, my nose hurts.
Got it.
Thanks for everything, guys.
I'm going to be so lonely.
Not again...
Stop it, would you?
Come on, please!
See you.
Yeah.
Akane!
Want to catch the train later?
Can I?
Your friends are here.
Don't you want more time to talk with them?
Yeah.
Hey, Akane.
What about Azumi-kun?
Oh, yeah, well...
Oh, wait, hang on.
Look.
I found this.
She was a 100-meter sprinter. When she set a new personal
record, I was so ecstatic that I could have been the one who ran.
I'm the president of the literature club.
I would watch her run along the track
as I ran my pen along paper.
My work never got published, but
you said I was awesome anyway.
Isn't this...
The first day we met at the shrine,
I was so nervous that I couldn't say a word.
About me and Kotarou-kun?
End
Posting story. Continue?
[Back]       [Post]        [Preview]
Story posted.
Kotarou-kun.
Isn't the move today?
Oh, yeah, I read your story online.
Uh...
Hey, it's updated.
Yeah.
You've got quite a few comments.
See, look.
Did you not notice?
Posted by: miki
I love these kinds of stories.
I can't wait to read the rest!
Posted by: Ryokucha
I cried...
I couldn't help tearing up.
I'm looking forward to more.
Posted by: suzaku12
I don't normally read these kinds of stories,
but I have a feeling I'm going to like this one
Posted by: Marshmallow
It warms the heart!
Posted by: Shinseiki Leader
I'd love to go back in time and
fall in love like this again lol
Good for you.
It's popular.
Posted by: Akane
What happens next?
All right, take care, Akane.
Come hang out with us once in a while.
Thanks.
Okay, well...
Akane just went through the gate
She said she wished she could see you
Dazai once said, "The true
substance of love lies in the act
of howling words of love with the
desperation of a man jumping into high seas."
Kumano Shrine
Become an Author!
No.
End
"End"...
I want to tell her that no
matter how far apart we are,
my feelings for her will never change.
You're leaving for an unfamiliar town.
I love you!
And I'll always love you.
She was my first love.
I knew nothing.
I was so nervous.
How to hold hands, how to kiss...
We'd never even told our friends.
It was so embarrassing.
I never had any idea what to do.
But that day, he found the courage to tell me.
I could believe we would
always walk together.
To think someone I loved
would love me back...
I thought it must have been a miracle.
And Then
My Honey
Aren't you going to bed?
I don't want to
Hehe
I'm getting paid next week
I'll finally be able
to see you
Aren't you?
Me neither
Hehe
I can't wait
My Darling
Sorry about yesterday
I said too much
But
I still think
I love you more
Jeez!
We're going to fight again!
You suck! I hate you!
I love you more
Benippo
I didn't think they'd
be home so early
I told her we'd be
studying for exams
My notebook was
blank, though
I don't think she believed us
ikr
Yeah I guess lol
My Man
Are you okay?
Yeah, I took some medicine
I might have pushed myself
too much at club
Sorry to worry you
No
I'm sorry too
I can't be with you
at a time like this
Why?
The Boyfriend
You went?
Why?!
Yeah...
I mean, it was a mixer
But it was just a gathering of
people from my seaman class
Seminar
It's not what you think
Seaman?
I know, but still
The Girlfriend
Still not home?
You don't message me much
since you joined that club
I'm worried
Ughh
Sorry, I just got home!!
I ended up on the last train
Are you asleep already?
Sorry!
Goodnight...
The Girlfriend
I told my mom
I'm going on vacation
with my friends
I think so
Really?
Will that work?
My mom said
she'd help me out
Yeah
She said she'd figure out what to tell Dad
Oh, wow
The Girlfriend
Ughhh
So tired
Hang in there
Once you pass
the job interview
You'll be in
the real world
Yeah
Just a little longer
Hold me
Huggggg
The Boyfriend
What if
I get a job,
and get stationed
in the middle
of nowhere?
jk
Yeah?
Huh?
Marr
The Wife
I think they were happy
That's good
Your dad,
when we were
drinking together
He was kind of tearing up
Said he's really proud of you
Yeah?
Seriously?
Aww
The Hubby
You're late!
I need you to
check the guest list
I had overtime
Sorry
I'll buy you ice cream
Juice?
Nope