What's this?
Oh...
Sorry.
Excuse me, sorry.
I'm Gouda Takeo, a first-year in high school.
For the very first time in my life,
a girl I like actually likes me back.
She's my first girlfriend.
You okay?
Yeah.
I love her!
Um, it's the first time I've seen
you on the morning train.
Do you always take this one?
Yeah.
Maybe I'll switch to this one, then.
But this would be cutting it close.
It's nice to be on the same train,
but I shouldn't be late to class, right?
Yeah.
That couple there is pretty amazing.
I shouldn't, yeah...
No way, they must be father and daughter.
I shouldn't be late.
But that man's in a school uniform.
Class 1-6
I'm Dense
We'll pick up where we left off
yesterday, on page 24.
Kurihara-kun...
You're late.
Sorry!
All right, page 24, people.
I already got to see a good show today.
Seeing it revved me up.
I'd have gone for a first
kiss right there and then.
Takeo'd never do that.
He wouldn't.
Never.
But afterward...
Please mind the closing doors.
Sorry, I'm getting off!
Sorry—
Go.
Okay.
Takeo-kun!
Takeo missed his transfer.
Great.
It's amazing!!
He was so cool, I couldn't
resist taking a video.
Takeo's amazing!
It was a limited express, right?
So cool
Takeo must've gone all the
way to the final stop.
But why did she pick Gouda-kun?
Yeah, she's cute...
Right?
Hey, you guys!
Is this a Koizumi Girls' Academy uniform?
Cut it out.
Are they really going out?
Okay, starting at page 24.
Is this a Koizumi Girls' Academy uniform?
Are they really going out?
No way (lol)
No normal girl'd like Gouda-kun
Wow!
I didn't know it was possible
to take such nice videos.
That's what you notice?
Can I see it again?
Oh?
Huh?
How do you work this?
Someone, help!
My boy fell into the river!
Anyone!
Takeo!
Take him.
Mom, I was scared!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Well, I didn't do anything.
I don't know how to thank you.
It wasn't me. He saved your boy.
Suna, let's hurry!
I'm running late to my date!
You okay?
You're dripping wet.
I'm fine.
I've never been sick!
You're some superhuman.
Takeo-kun!
Yamato!
I'm late!
Oh, what's wrong?
You're drenched, but it isn't raining.
On his way here, he saved a drowning boy.
What?
Sunakawa-kun, you're pretty dry.
I only handed the boy to his mom.
He's the one who jumped in.
You jumped in?
Oh...
You jumped in.
I love her!
I have a towel, but it's hardly big enough.
You should have gone home to change.
I didn't want to keep you waiting.
You could have called or texted her.
Suna,
you're so smart!
I've been thinking that, too.
You're really smart!
I have gym clothes. Want them?
Sure.
Thanks!
Sorry.
No, it's okay.
I guess girlfriends
call or text you, even when
there's no real reason.
Today, I made a roll cake.
A friend asked me to make some for her,
but I'm not sure how good it is.
This one has whole strawberries in it,
And they bake you cakes, even when
it isn't your birthday.
and I tried adding banana to
the batter for this one!
What do you think?
It's delicious!
You always say everything's
delicious, Takeo-kun!
It's delicious, right, Suna?
Yeah.
It's such a small thing,
but she laughs like hearing
it makes her really happy.
Don't move...
There was a bug.
I already got rid of it.
It's fine...
Oh, sorry for touching you.
No, it's okay! Thanks!
Earlier, she was blushing, too.
She's really pure!
She's the total opposite of my mom,
who was once an amateur wrestler.
I'll get going, then.
Okay.
Make sure you wash that before you return it.
That was subtle, giving us a moment alone.
What a considerate guy!
Takeo-kun, do you want
to go through the park?
Isn't that a detour?
You get a really great view of the stars!
You're right!
They're beautiful.
It's dark, so you can see them really well.
There isn't anyone around here, huh?
Yeah, it's quiet!
It's just the two of us...
Don't worry, Yamato!
Huh?
Until you're all grown up,
I won't touch a single hair on your head!
So don't worry.
Th-Thank you.
Later!
Good night...
I'll treat her right.
I'll do everything in my
power to treat her right.
Today was a good day.
I'm back.
Oh, Makoto, welcome back.
Oh, you're back, Sis.
Yeah, I took the afternoon bullet train.
Here's my present.
Where's Takeo?
He isn't with you?
There's a lot in there.
Why not share with him?
You can call him over.
He's walking his girlfriend home.
Takeo has a girlfriend now.
Huh?
Takeo has a girlfriend?
Eh?
No way!
Don't pull my leg.
I'm serious.
She's pretty cute...
Huh?
No way...
You've got to be kidding me!
Wait a minute... Don't tell me
you had feelings for him.
Seriously?
I had no idea.
Since when?
What's she like?
Are you sure he isn't being duped?
He's so trusting!
There's no way Takeo would get a girlfriend!
Not a big, lumbering gorilla like him!
So do you like him or hate him? Which?
Are you sure he isn't being used?
Like, for a bodyguard?
He looks happy.
I've never seen two people
genuinely in love before.
Let me meet this girl!
Only a woman would understand
another woman's true nature!
Oh, really?
It's impossible that any girl other than
me would have feelings for him!
There's got to be something going on!
Let me meet Takeo's girlfriend!
No, I smell a fight.
What? Let me see her!
Takeo's still his lame self, isn't he?
He still has his weird
hairstyle, doesn't he?!
Do you really even actually like him?
Hey, gimme your cell...
Hey, wait.
To: Takeo-kun
Subject: Um
Um, Takeo-kun.
I have something I want to tell you...
I couldn't tell you this until now, but...
To tell you the truth...
Cancel
Discard changes?
Cancel    OK
To: Takeo-kun
Subject: Hello
Takeo-kun,
today was really fun.
When can I see you again?
I'll bake cookies.
Subject: Re: Hello
I'm free Wednesday.
I had fun, too.
Love
Sincerity
Don't you think it's about time you
stopped having me tag along?
Yamato seems like a very pure-hearted person.
When it's just the two of us,
I think she gets nervous.
If you're there, she'll be more relaxed.
Uh-huh.
So, who is it?
That one?
This one?
Oh, she's cute...
No, she can't be the one.
Oh, Takeo-kun!
Over here!
Seriously?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No, I haven't been waiting at all—
Takeo!
Oh, hello.
Hey, been a while.
I heard you have a girlfriend.
GPS...
It's Suna's big sister.
Hello!
I'm Yamato. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
She's pretty!
Yeah.
Suna's sister is good-looking,
so as a kid, I used to get nervous.
You don't get your homework?
I'll take a look.
Takeo!
Your pants are on backwards!
Takeo,
your nose is dripping.
And just like Suna,
at heart, she's a kind person.
Hey, Yamato-san.
What do you like about Takeo?
Eh?
Oh...
Um, well...
It's hard to explain,
but I really like him!
Hard to explain, but likes him just the same.
I see.
Maybe that's how it is.
Oh, I baked cookies.
Would you like some, too?
Only if you'd like.
Wow, they're amazing!
You made these cookies?!
They're really well-made.
Lately, I'm really into icings,
so I used icing on langues
de chat-type cookies.
Langues de chat-type?
Yamato's really good at baking.
Her cakes are great, too.
Sounds like she's a girly girl.
That's right.
Yamato is a girly girl.
Okay, okay
She's a nice person.
She's a very nice person!
That isn't true!
I'm not a good person at all...
Don't be modest.
You're a good person.
Digging in!
It's salty!
I see, it's savory.
Eh?
This is new...
Huh? It's salty!
Oh!
I mixed up the sugar and salt!
I'm so sorry!
Sorry, Takeo-kun!
Please don't eat them!
Oh, my god! I can't believe this!
I'm so sorry!
Yamato, it's fine.
I want to eat them.
Give them all to me!
*Blush*
I like sweet things and super salty things.
It's the truth.
Actually, is there anything you don't like?
Nope.
Then what do you like
about Yamato-san, Takeo?
Oh, my god! That's so sudden...
Well, everything, of course,
but if I had to choose...
She's pure-hearted.
I'll walk Yamato home.
Goodnight.
Night!
Well?
They look happy, right?
She has a secret.
Aren't you overthinking this?
You didn't notice?
She's hiding something from Takeo.
She hasn't been totally honest
about herself with Takeo.
Maybe she's two-timing
him or having an affair.
She has something she
doesn't want to tell him.
Yamato...
Look at the sky.
The stars look great today, too.
You're right.
They cheer you up.
Takeo-kun...
Um, I...
To tell you the truth...
I think I'm dense.
It's nothing!
Goodnight!
Oh...
Yamato
Good night.
It's nothing...
I see!
Wait, really?
What's wrong, Yamato?!
When she said she'd fallen for Takeo at first sight,
you should've known something was off.
She wouldn't have fallen in love with him
unless she had a real reason to.
I bet she's hiding a big secret.
Hey, are you listening to me?
I need some space.
Oh, there you are.
Ai, can you go shopping?
Oh, come on.
Your daughter hasn't been home for a while,
and you're already abusing her.
Jeez!
Seriously, it's creepy.
This is seriously scary.
It's hilarious!
Takeo?
What are you doing?
Oh, hello.
I'm learning about how girls think.
Huh?
I'm probably dense.
I'd thought that Yamato
had feelings for Suna.
So I can't read girls.
If Yamato won't tell me,
I won't have a clue.
If only she'd tell me, I could help her.
It might be something she can't tell you...
Something she can't tell her boyfriend.
It could be that she's two-timing you,
having an affair,
or that she's found someone else.
Even if that's the case, I'll be fine.
It's more important to me that
Yamato's in knots about it.
I can ask her...
It might be easier for her
to talk to another girl.
You'd do that?
So stop reading those!
You're creeping people out.
Thank you.
You're a nice person!
Let's go home.
I did wonder if a guy reading
that stuff might be creepy.
But you still read them.
I was desperate.
Did it help you figure anything out?
Nope, not at all.
My Wish
Next time: My Wish.