I'm late!
Huh...
Oh, yeah... it's summer break now.
Hey, Rinon!
Don't get in the way.
Stop that! It tickles!
Oh, good morning, Kaito-kun.
G-Good morning.
Dear Sister,
it's your humbled brother.
It's the first day of summer vacation,
and I'm already in trouble.
I don't really think...
...I can stay...
...sane at this rate.
Kaito-kun.
Yes, what is it?
Did you buy that camera?
It looks pretty old.
It was in our shed.
I think it belonged to my
grandfather, who's passed now.
I like it for some reason.
How do you use it?
It's pretty simple.
You put in this film,
and then focus the lens and
press the shutter button.
I see.
Um...
What is it?
You're really close.
You're already being really
frank with each other,
and it's only the first day of break.
Th-That's not true!
'Sup.
Hello there.
What are you doing, Kaito-kun?
Stretching, I guess.
Let's begin the fun of
creating our movie.
Hey, Kai.
What are we filming today?
I don't know.
Remon-senpai's the one
writing the script.
It'll be fine.
I have the script we'll
need for today done.
The script for today?
I write scripts in the Hong Kong-style.
Huh?
I figure out what we're going
to film the morning of the shoot.
So you're just winging it.
We're done changing.
Wow, that looks great on you, Senpai!
R-Really?
What's up with this outfit?
It looks really expensive...
I asked the cosplay club
at school for help.
There's a cosplay club?
I dunno.
So how is it?
It's not weird?
I-It looks good on you!
It really does.
Good, then.
Today we'll be filming the scene where
the heroine first meets the guy.
So it's a love story.
That might be really good.
Also, the heroine is an alien.
That's pretty avant-garde.
That's why she's wearing that, then.
After arriving on Earth,
the heroine has a fateful
encounter with an Earth boy.
We'll be ad-libbing all the lines.
I'll leave the rest up to the director.
That's asking too much...
And who'll be playing the Earth boy?
I have to run the camera...
So that leaves me, then?
I think that'd be good!
That'd be really good.
Hold on.
I was just planning on helping
out behind the scenes.
Ishigaki-kun.
Huh?
You respond based on
the situation at hand.
A set is a living creature.
You talk like you've
been on one before.
Sounds good to me!
You'll get to be in a scene with
somebody as pretty as Takatsuki-senpai.
I'm sure it'll be an
unforgettable memory.
These are supposed to be
the best days of my life?
It'll be fine.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
Of course I'm not.
I'll be playing an alien...
What's wrong?
Nothing at all.
Let's see...
Kaito-kun, I'm all ready here.
All right. Then...
And action.
This is Earth,
a planet in the F stage of
development on the edge of civilization.
They've just started moving into space.
The only place they've managed to reach...
...with a manned craft is
their satellite, the moon.
Pretty realistic dialogue.
She's speaking kind
of stilted, though.
Ishigaki-kun needs to enter next.
Okay.
Th-There's a reason why
I came to this planet.
Th-This is where...
Oh, there you are!
Y-You're...
I've been looking for you!
F-For me?
That changes the setting
so they've already met.
It's fine.
I've been watching you
this whole time...
You're an alien!
And I'm a Man in Black.
M-Man in Black...
No!
Okay, cut.
That was wonderful,
Ichika, Ishigaki-kun.
I just got into it all of a sudden.
The main guy died...
Is this going to be okay?
You did a really good job ad-libbing.
Yeah, it just came to me.
So what are we doing now...
Since the movie's story changed,
we're waiting for ideas
from Remon-senpai.
Supposedly the heroine starts to run,
and the Men in Black try
to catch her, or something.
I see...
What do you think?
Hm?
The scenery here.
There's a lake a little
further up here, too.
You told me there was a
place you wanted to go.
There's a tree there, and a lake.
It doesn't really have anything
special to identify it.
That'd make it hard to find.
Yeah.
But I'd still like to go there.
Kaito-kun, you remembered.
I picked a place similar to that,
but I guess this wasn't it. Sorry.
No, not at all.
Thank you.
I'll keep looking.
You silly.
Hey.
Silly.
What?
Stop that.
Kanna, take those drinks over
to Ichika-senpai and Kai.
What is it?
I've been wondering for
a while now, but...
Tetsuro, do you know how I feel?
It's pretty obvious.
How long have you known?
I forget.
Are you going to help me out?
Hey, we've been friends
since we were kids.
Thanks.
You too, Tetsuro!
If you find someone, tell me!
I'll help you, too!
That's not gonna happen.
That hurts, Kitahara-san.
S-Sorry!
I sort of spaced out...
I'm done.
Let's start filming again.
In order to escape her pursuers,
the heroine returns to her spaceship
and meets up with a friend.
A friend?
Who's going to play the part?
This guy will.
Rinon?!
When did she...?
He'll be the biological entity that acts
as a terminal for the spaceship.
I'll be counting on you, Ichika.
O-Of course...
Okay, let's get started.
Remon-senpai, we're ready here.
Roger that.
I'm not sure who the
director is anymore...
Camera, you ready?
Yes, I'm ready!
And action.
Rinon!
People are after me. Please help me.
It won't be that easy.
Huh?
U-Um...
Wh-Why...?
I'll be taking revenge for my brother!
Huh?
All right, cut.
That was wonderful, Ichika,
Ishigaki-kun, Rinon.
Thanks...
Why did you just run in there?!
I guess it's just my actor's spirit.
I think you're getting
a little too into this.
Uh, so what are we going to do now?
Isn't it obvious?
We sit and think about it.
You have no place to stay?
Th-That's right.
How about staying at my place, then?
I live by myself, and I have extra rooms.
Really?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
All right, cut.
We've finally gotten into the story now.
Indeed.
Good work.
When did I become an
actor here, anyway?
I'm not running the camera.
Who cares?
You get to be who
Ichika-senpai ends up with.
Wait, did you do that on purpose?
Who knows?
Kaito-kun's become the
lead guy in the film.
Seems it ended up that way.
How do you think things are going
to play out between you two?
Huh?
I'm not really sure...
Then what way do you
think it should go?
Hm...
It'd be nice if they could end up happy.
It would.
Episode 5
Senpai is the heroine.
It would, wouldn't it?
Both the director and camera operator
ended up being Remon-senpai.
Who knows what's going to happen?
Sorry for taking a bath first.
No, it's fine.
The bath was great.
So are we filming again tomorrow?
Seems that way.
It all depends on Remon-senpai, though.
What are you doing?
Remon-senpai said she wanted me...
...to get as many scenes as
I could possibly film...
...of the heroine getting used
to life here on Earth.
You don't have to film me right now.
You know...
Hm?
Talking about the movie here,
what would you do if you found
out who the heroine really was?
Remon-senpai'll be the one
to figure that out.
I want to know what you
would do personally.
I guess I would think it
was pretty amazing...
Not that.
I guess I would ask her to
take me to space with her.
There's regulations against that.
Huh?
Would you be okay being with
someone from another planet?
As long as they don't
excrete any weird fluids.
There aren't any!
Then sure, why not?
It wouldn't really bug me.
I see.
Um... Senpai?
I'm going to make some tea.
Huh?
Senpai...
What was that about?
Yes, Tanigawa residence.
Oh, Mio. It's me.
So no filming then, huh?
I guess it'd be hard, with this rain.
Okay, got it.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
What were you two talking about?
Nothing really.
Nothing important.
Yeah.
Takatsuki-senpai, have you
gotten used to living here?
Yeah, I'm doing pretty well.
But Senpai's kind of strange.
She made chocolate flavored
curry the other day.
That's bad?
Yeah, kind of.
I see.
Oh, yeah, I need to buy ingredients.
Okay, let's stop by the grocery
store on the way home.
Sure.
And we're almost out of tissues.
Detergent, too.
In that case, let's stop
by the pharmacy, too.
Sounds good.
Yes, who is it?
Tanigawa?
Hello there.
My mom told me to give this to you.
They're greens.
Oh, thanks.
There's a lot here.
So, um...
Kaito-kun, this is a problem!
What is it?!
This house is pretty old.
I'll take a look at the
roof when it clears up.
Sorry about that.
I was surprised.
Well, it's not something
that happens every day.
Wow.
Oh, Tanigawa-san.
Oh, sorry for walking in.
No problem.
Actually, it's not really
my house, but...
I know. How about we
eat lunch together?
No reason to say no.
In that case...
Huh? Kanna went somewhere?
It's raining pretty hard.
That's right.
She took the greens we had
in the house with her.
She's my daughter, but
she's pretty weird.
Okay, when she gets back,
tell her I called.
Yeah, thanks.
Kanna...
You made sandwiches out of the greens?
I thought I might as well
use them since I got them.
This...
Is something wrong?
It's good.
It's kind of like vegetable dumplings.
R-Really?
Well, since I got over that
grapefruit and rice stuff,
I can pretty much take on anything.
Don't say that!
You're filming again?
I was told to film as much as I could.
Tanigawa, you help, too.
Huh? Sure...
Try having a normal
conversation together.
A normal conversation might be kind of...
Yeah...
Come on.
Tanigawa-san, do you have any siblings?
I'm an only child,
but I've played with
Tetsuro since I was little,
so I was never really lonely.
So you've known Ishigaki-kun
for a long time, then.
He's kind of like a dumb
little brother to me.
Really?
Ishigaki-kun kind of looks
like an older brother to me.
You just think that because he's tall.
Do you have any siblings?
I have an older sister
and a younger sister.
So three sisters then!
That's nice.
There are only girls in our house,
so coming here was kind of different.
I guess this is what it feels like
to have a guy in the family.
Who would Kaito-kun be if
he was part of your family?
Her younger brother, right?
Hm, it does feel like that sometimes,
but he can be really dependable, too.
It's kind of hard to explain.
Just now...
That was good.
Keep doing that.
I don't know what I did.
That's fine, just act
like you did before.
Yeah, but...
Um, Senpai.
You're here studying abroad, right?
Yeah, I guess so.
How long will you be here?
Six months?
A year?
Well...
Sorry! I shouldn't have said...
No, it's fine. Don't worry.
Why...
...did I...?
Why did I ask that?
I'm a bad person.
I'm a terrible person.
I'm a lousy person.
I'm not cute at all.
Why are you here?
Coincidence.
Mio, huh?
I guess so.
You went to Kai's house, didn't you?
You were pretty courageous.
I shouldn't have gone.
Why?
I shouldn't get involved.
I get uneasy just watching
the two of them talking.
I don't like when I get like that.
Just tell him you like him.
Kai still hasn't—
I can't.
Why?
I just can't.
If it doesn't go well, things will
get awkward between us.
It'll be weird.
We're all making a movie together.
If that happens, I won't
be able to participate.
I'd make Kaito-kun uncomfortable.
Then...
Are you just going to keep feeling
uneasy and not do anything?
You're not in love so you can't understand!
You just wouldn't understand...
Yeah, I guess so.
Sorry about that.
I said too much.
I'm sorry.
It's cleared up.
That's good.
Hey, Kanna.
I'll stay normal.
We're all going to have fun filming
that movie over summer break.
We'll make the movie, and
show it at the school fair.
And I'll just keep being
the usual Kanna Tanigawa.
That's what I've decided.
Right.
Come on. Let's go, Tetsuro.
Sure.
I had no way of knowing what
was going on back then.
Tanigawa's feelings...
Tetsuro's feelings...
Kitahara's feelings...
I had no way of knowing.
Back then, only one thing filled my head.
Knowing that Senpai was
eventually going to leave.
H-Hey.
Huh?
What are you doing?
L-Let me in...
My arms won't last.
A lifeform reading?
At this hour?
What do you want at this hour?
And you should have just come
in through the front door.
Sorry.
So what do you want?
Kanna.
Tanigawa?
Tanigawa was here toda—
She likes you.
Kanna Tanigawa...
...likes you,
Kaito Kirishima.
Episode 6
Senpai has a rival.
It's Okinawa.
Yeah, Okinawa.
Very stimulating.
Yeah, very alluring.
This is awesome!