Are you all right?!
Hang in there!
Punch Line
It's over.
Campanella Kick!
Miyazawa Kenji has arrived!
You! How...
I happen to be clairvoyant.
Nor losing
to bullets
You should have known...
I still have bullets.
The hero of justice,
Strange Juice, is on the scene!
So, now what? It's two against one!
Fine, then.
I'll have to show you my true power.
It's...
It can't be.
Indeed.
I can Yubafy, just like you two.
Except I have an expression
rate of 2,000 percent.
You understand what that means, don't you?
Who cares?!
Bastard!
What is your goal?
I guess you could say it's the
creation of an ideal world.
To destroy inferior humanity,
and to rule the world with only the superior W.
W?
Stop!
Move.
Stop.
Please.
You're in the way.
Die.
Stop it!
I won't let you have your way any longer!
Why say that now?
I'm doing this to carry out your wishes!
But you can't!
Not Ito!
Please.
Lend me your strength.
You.
I'm talking to you, Yuta!
You can see me?
Just use this, quickly!
Cinnamon...
Shit, my power! My power!
Now!
Wh-What? What?!
P-Panties!
Impossible...
How?
How is it that even you can Yubafy—
Shut up!
I didn't ask to become this way!
Huh?
Why am I...
Meika!
Meika! Meika!
Please, wake up!
Meika!
What are you crying about, Rabura?
Muhi!
Now then, let's have a look at your face.
No way...
You know him, Ito?
Tomoda Chihaya.
My homeroom teacher.
Why would a teacher do something like this?
It's all because I loved you, Ito.
What are you saying?
It's because I loved you that I edited the video
and sent out the emails.
Then the person who killed Meiko and Moena...
I was possessed by the spirit of the
Qmay Group leader, Tsubouchi Qmay.
He's the one who killed them.
What's going on?
I made a contract with Tsubouchi's spirit.
In exchange for lending him
my body, I would get my wish.
Your wish?
Revenge.
I knew that
Ito was being harassed at school.
I couldn't forgive them.
I was destined to be with Ito.
The people in our class got in our way.
What are you talking about?
You don't have to hide it.
I knew you loved me.
In order to respond to your love,
I have to punish them.
That's a true test of love, right?
Isn't it?
This guy gives me the chills.
Say, so that Tsubouchi's spirit is still inside you?
My body's useless to him as it is now.
Because of the Yubafication.
You know about it?
More accurately, it's Yubamenschification.
When you're infected with the
so-called Hercules virus,
you undergo epigenetic effects
that toggle genetic switches.
It changes your body's composition,
and you become able to exert
power beyond your limits.
You can't do that all the time, though.
Normally, there are limiters on it.
When those limiters come off...
You Yubafy.
Right.
But Yubafying comes with huge risks.
Doing it over and over
causes severe damage and atrophy to the body.
And then...
You die.
That's what happened to Tsubouchi, as well.
And that cub was created in order
to allow his body to regenerate.
With his extraordinary regenerative capacity,
he could evade death and Yubafy regularly.
You disgust me.
You're still so dishonest.
Hey, I have one last wish.
Ito, don't die.
Survive.
That's my—
You're full of shit!
Ito!
You pervert!
How dare you say all that selfish crap?!
Stop!
Possessed by a spirit, my ass!
You seriously piss me off!
The Next Day
It's New Year's Eve! Meikaemon
And... why are we having nagashi soba?
It's New Year's Eve. Soba is a mainstay.
I get the soba part, but why nagashi?
It's totally off-season.
Isn't it, Ito?
Whatever.
It's New Year's Eve! Meikaemon
Why are you being so gloomy?
Meika, can I ask you something?
Are you sure it's all right?
What's all right?
You know, the servers.
At AFSPC.
I told you, I hacked into
the U.S. military servers,
but everything was normal.
Really...
Besides, if an asteroid were
really going to hit us,
the whole world would be
freaking out right now.
It's New Year's Eve.
Let's go back to Meikaemon's party
and raise the roof!
Okay?
It's New Year's Eve,
Meikaemon
Sushi rice, sushi rice, chirashi sushi,
I'll wait for you,
Kuzushi...
Not your best.
It's New Year's Eve! Meikaemon
But it's for our upcoming musical!
It's just lacking in girlish sentiment.
Have you ever been in love
or anything, Mikatan?
In love?
I guess I haven't met anyone.
Yes, you have.
There's one person, isn't there?
Oh, yeah, there's Yuta!
Why don't you try falling in love with him?
Look at her face!
She already has!
I-It's not like that!
He's a girl, though.
You're kidding, right?
Biologically, he's unmistakably female.
I kept it a secret until now
because it's a delicate issue.
Iridatsu Yu
His true, registered legal name is
Iridatsu Yu.
"Yuta" is just a name he gave himself.
It's New Year's Eve! Meikaemon
S-Speaking of, where is Yuta?
I invited him, but...
It's up to you, then.
Hey, do you have any more
secrets or anything?
About Iridatsu?
That works, but...
Tell me about your and Mikatan's past.
All right.
Just a little, then.
It was eight years ago, in the summer,
that I met Narugino.
It was a stormy night.
Stop crying!
Who are you?
I'm Daihatsu Meika.
I'm a robot that's come to shelter,
raise, and support you.
Why did the apartment burn down?
Narugino escaped from a facility with
the help of someone named Ishigata.
But they were found right away.
And Ishigata took the
pursuers down with him.
I decided to take Narugino away from Tokyo.
We went further and further
north, and ended up deep
in the mountains of Aomori.
We rented a shabby old shack
and started to live there.
It's over. I'm superior.
I trained her, day in and day out,
to bring out the strength that
she possessed within herself.
It was when she was 13 years old and
out shopping that my efforts bore fruit.
You'll pay...
You'll pay!
Ever since then, she's been
kicking ass all over the place,
catching bad guys one after another.
The people of Tsugaru saw
Narugino, and called her...
The Hero of Tsugaru
Pantyhose Girl
"Pantyhose Girl"?! No way!
We can't help that. It's to protect your identity.
That's why I didn't want to become a hero!
My dream is to become an idol!
Give up on that dream.
You have to become a hero,
or we can't form the secret
Justice Punch squad.
That name's so lame. I hate it.
What do you want to call it, then?
Like, Pretty Cutie Moon—
Too long! And you're ripping
off a bunch of things!
In any case, you were born to become a hero.
That's your destiny.
You can't get away from it.
Destiny?
What's this?
Your new costume.
Starting today, you're Strange Juice.
You're going to fight evil as a new hero...
in Tokyo!
So that's why you came to Koraikan?
We're thinking of calling off
the hero thing, though.
Huh?
Can't you tell?
Narugino is a Yubafier.
Is her body...
I don't know why I didn't notice.
After we were together this whole time...
Yuta-kun wasn't home.
I think he's out somewhere.
Well, then.
Let's get started, shall we?
With what?
Meika, we're out of fireworks.
Don't worry.
I have a bottle rocket that
I've kept for a special occasion.
A special occasion?
I never saw one.
Just come with me.
Mikatan?
Oh, I just remembered I have something to do.
Go ahead without me.
Really?
Okay, come by soon.
No way!
I forgot to refill my medicine.
Narugino!
I have to let everyone know.
Miyazawa Kenji?
Wh-What is this?
I call it the Kaku-maker!
Kaku-maker
Uh, where's the bottle rocket?
There!
See it up there?
What's the matter today, Miyako-chan?
Sensei, I—
We interrupt this program
to deliver breaking news.
Asteroid VR-1, which until
now was not expected to
Two kilometer diameter asteroid strike imminent
collide with Earth, will imminently...
Will imminently collide with Earth.
I repeat, Asteroid VR-1's collision is imminent.
Well, it couldn't be helped.
Unbeijini nyopurasara,
I'm going to put a spell on you.
Unbeijini nyopurakura,
I'm going to protect...
That song...
How...
Mikatan, what's keeping you?
Now, go!
Hurry up!
Your friends are calling.
But—
Just go!
Come on! Hurry up, or I'll launch the firework!
I promise to listen to you more later.
A promise for later, huh?
You're there, aren't you?
Come down here.
What's your deal?!
Why can you see me?
Why?
Meika said everything was
normal on the AFSPC servers!
And the Qmay Group was trying to
make W, but it's not finished yet.
You'll know the answer once
you have your body back.
I need some book called
the Nandala Gandala for tha—
You mean this?
Indian Holy Text
Nandala Gandala
Are you messing with me?!
You could have made a better fake than this!
Just look inside.
I did!
It's all blank, with just one word!
What the hell is a U-turn?
Just as it says.
No, what does it mean—
Are you telling me to go back in time?
If I were, when would you go back to?
To before everything began...
December 21st.
That alone isn't enough
to take you back in time.
There's one other thing you need.
A strong desire to save someone.
I don't need to tell you the rest.
Yuta, this history is a mistake.
It's a future that mustn't happen.
Change this history.
I failed in my mission.
Many of me have attempted it
and made the same mistakes.
Still, I leave my hopes with you.
No, all of our hopes.
Why?
Yuta, wish for it.
Wish hard, from the bottom of your heart.
That desire will grant you power.
You're going to change destiny. History, Yuta!
I'll do it.
I'll change history.
For Meika. For Rabura.
For Ito.
For Narugino.
I'm going to protect them.
I promise. I promise. I promise!
I'm counting on you, me.
The asteroid
hits.
Humanity falls.