Episode 9
"Moon"
To: Yukinari
Subject: Hinode-hama today
Good weather all day.
In front of the gelato store.
What am I writing this for?
Why? Just why?
Message from Sacchan
For tomorrow?
From: Sacchan
Subject: For tomorrow
"Ten Nights of Dreams."
What's that?
May I help you?
Not really.
Nee-chan...
Fine, fine.
It's the name of a novel, isn't it?
By Soseki Natsume.
Oh, really?
It's on the shelf at the store.
Oh, yeah?
It's an exam question.
I see.
Issen Ichibyou Monogatari
Did you tell your boyfriend
that you're coming home?
I did.
Soseki Natsume
Ten Nights of Dreams
Inbox
Yanagi
Hinode-hama today
What did Touko see
about me?
I can't hear the fragment.
Navel?
Why?
Hina-chan?
Sorry to interrupt your running.
Oh, right.
I—
Right, we promised to go shopping together.
Come over tomorrow if you have time.
Thanks.
Don't tell Onee-chan yet.
Trust me. I get it.
See you tomorrow.
Has something happened recently, Onee-chan?
Say, Kakeru, what are you
going to do after you graduate?
I wonder.
You sure haven't changed.
I think you should start
thinking about your future.
That's true.
You should find a stable job.
Not that I'm in a position to talk.
Your father and I both knew what we wanted
to be ever since we were little kids.
That wasn't the case for you though, was it?
Because Mom wouldn't stay put, huh?
You're going overseas next, aren't you?
It looks like I'll be gone for a while this time.
I see.
I'm going back, now.
That boy said he liked it here,
so I thought he found something he wanted to do.
His girlfriend, I'm sure.
I want to see her just once.
If you come back again
during the summer break.
Just don't get in their way, please.
My happiness is partly thanks to him.
If he asked me, I'd support
him with everything I have.
You're really just lonely, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
Of course I am.
To: Yukinari
Subject: Hinode-hama today
Good weather today.
Hinode Bridge, futon...
New message
Yes?
Hi, it's Hina.
Come in.
Thanks!
Oh, this.
Yeah, Touko gave me that.
So, I was thinking,
I have a lot of clothes
that I can't wear anymore.
Do you want to try them
on before we go shopping?
Yes, please!
It's perfect. So cute.
Maybe not that skirt. Something more frilly.
Hey, Yanagi-san...
Did you find something you want to wear?
About Onee-chan...
That's what you've been wanting
to ask since yesterday, right?
I think she's in love.
You think so too, right?
But it's not a broken heart, is it?
I don't think so.
But I don't think I know
any more than you do.
Oh.
Oh, but I
have a one-sided promise
to ask someone who probably
knows a lot about it.
"One-sided"? That's not exactly
a "promise," then, is it?
Maybe not.
Don't worry,
Touko's really important to me.
This is so cute.
Right? Do you like it?
Yes.
You can have it, then.
Sorry it's a hand-me-down.
I'm so happy. Are you sure, though?
I can't wear it anymore, anyway.
That's an outfit Yuki complimented me for.
He probably doesn't
remember anymore, though.
I can't take it.
I'm going to become a new me.
Even though you're already cute?
Even more.
I—
I'm pulling for you.
Thanks.
Tada!
That's cute.
Yanagi-san gave it to me.
But I think it might be...
Yanagi-san's got such good taste!
...a bit too tight around the waist for me.
How've you been doing lately, Touko?
I'm doing speed sketches and life drawings.
You're lucky you have no written exams.
I kind of do.
Sorry, phone.
Hello, Sacchan?
Sure, I'm fine.
We ended up talking a lot
about Onee-chan today.
Yana-chan was being nice to you,
because you're so worried about your sister.
Oh, yeah.
Sacchan, how were the tests?
I don't get the results for at least a week,
but I'm fine.
Yeah?
Hey...
I want to go to that place we promised to.
The place we promised to go before?
Yeah.
Okay, let's go.
Can we meet tomorrow at Kirinkan at four?
Sure.
Thanks.
See you tomorrow.
Yep.
Mom, I'll make dinner today.
Oh, that's unusual.
New camping techniques
From: Sacchan
Subject: For tomorrow
Please come to Kirinkan tomorrow at four.
"Meijinden"?
"Kirinkan"?
For tomorrow?
There's so many things I want to say but can't.
The place we promised to go.
Hina-chan!
I wasn't listening to your monologue.
To: Yukinari
Subject: Hinode-hama today
Cumulonimbus.
What are you being so fidgety about?
Are you expecting a message from your girlfriend?
No way.
Just call her. Don't worry about us.
Not that we won't be listening.
Lights out, unless you want your precious message deleted.
Sir!
I'm turning it off.
Go ahead.
That was close.
He can delete the email,
but he can't delete love.
Gross.
Unread emails
Yanagi
Hinode-hama today
Clear skies all day.
In front of the gelato store.
Blacks: 1 Whites: 2
"Blacks: 1, Whites: 2."
"Clear skies today."
"A futon on Hinode Bridge."
"Cumulonimbus. Strong winds."
Cumulonimbus.
Strong winds.
High tides.
"High tides."
It couldn't be helped.
Just hear me out as you are.
I want to go to the art room.
I don't know what I'll see this time.
Can you talk about what
you saw at the art room now?
Well—
We might learn something
about the fragments if we go there.
Do you really want to know about
the fragments of the future that badly?
We don't have enough
information about the fragments.
We don't?
We haven't discussed it enough either.
That's why I want to create the same conditions in the same place.
That's not it!
That's not what it's about!
I saw snow. When we were there.
It was a world of silver.
Snow everywhere.
I'd never seen anything like that.
I'm not going.
I see.
That's what you saw.
I haven't been able to
hear the fragments lately.
I may never hear them again.
Apparently Taniguchi broke
39 minutes in the 10,000 meters.
Seriously? He just started.
From: Yanagi
Subject: Hinode-hama today
Clear skies today.
The Sea of Japan is
breezy during the summer.
"Clear skies," huh?
Hello?
It's me.
Thanks for the messages.
Sorry they're so weird.
They made me happy.
The waves are
blinding right now.
It's raining over here today.
Oh yeah?
My knees...
They hurt a little.
I told Coach too.
It's nothing.
I might have rushed it too much.
Lots of things happened this summer, huh?
Summer is always like that.
All kinds of things
happen during the summer.
It's not just this year.
I guess.
Our parents got remarried
in summer as well, right?
They wanted only a modest wedding,
since they'd both been married before.
Yeah, right, huh?
Mom changed her wedding outfit three times.
Yeah...
Yeah, I feel relaxed when I talk to you.
Oh. When are you coming home?
Umm, when does camp end again?
I don't know exactly.
We might be done tomorrow, I think.
Same old you.
I'll be waiting.
Yeah, see you at Hinode-hama.
Hiro-kun!
Did you get invited, too?
You too? By Sacchan?
Yep. Let's go.
Sacchan.
Thanks for coming.
Are you doing okay?
I'm fine.
I see.
Thanks, Hiro-kun.
Can I expect an explanation?
Yes.
Is this where you wanted to come?
Yeah.
One of your pictures was
put on display here, wasn't it?
A long time ago.
You can see the Hinode-hama
breakwaters from here, too.
And there's a swallow nest on the roof.
Oh yeah?
You're pretty amazing.
Even if you didn't know,
it's still a lot more wonderful that
you've been living here all this time.
You think so?
Where is it?
I want to be here after closing.
Will you stay here with me?
What you need "for tomorrow"?
I don't know anything.
About this city, or about Yana-chan,
or about Yuki-kun,
or Hiro-kun, or Sacchan.
Just like I don't know what's about to happen next,
I don't know anything.
You know how you can vaguely
see the shadow of the moon today?
It's called earthshine.
It's like that because the earth
is reflecting the sun's light.
So we came here
today to see the moon, Sacchan?
Yeah.
The moon?
This time of the year, this Kirinkan—
It becomes a totally different place,
depending on the season and time.
I'm so glad I could come here,
to my special place,
with you two, Touko-chan and Hiro-kun.
This is your promised place.
Your special place, huh?
Oh yeah?
Sacchan, thanks for bringing me here.
I don't get it.
The moon's pretty though, isn't it?
Oh, that I get.
I heard it becomes a confession
when you say it like that.
A confession?!
I looked it up recently.
When Soseki Natsume was an English teacher,
that's how he taught how to translate "I love you."
Soseki Natsume? You?
So?
No, nothing,
but why?
It's, like, more tasteful that way.
That would really get your feelings across?
Yeah, I bet it would.
As long as there's love.
Natsume-san was a romantic, huh?
The moon's really pretty.
And those are my lines.
I haven't kept it at all.
Do you like Touko-san?
You haven't been protecting Touko-chan.
Touko Fukami, I miss you.
Episode 10
"Jonathan"