I can't hear...
Did Uroko-sama just fart?
Why the hell are farts
all you ever hear?
Shh!
Hikari!
We heard about Akari-san...
Shh!
Akari...
Episode 3: The Tradition of the Sea
Thank you, Namiji Junior High
There's saltflake snow
even in the classroom...
Entrance Ceremony
Old Man Hayakawa is always so nice...
Why did he seem so scary...
They were talking about
the rules of the village.
There might be some reason
that people get banished.
Who the hell cares about that?
This is all Akari's guy's fault.
But he seemed nice.
Chisaki, your taste in guys sucks.
Ain't that the truth...
Damn it.
Since it's come to this, I'm going
to find out everything about this guy.
And if he's an asshole,
I'm going to punch him!
And if he ends up being a decent guy?
I'll punch him gently!
V-Violence is wrong.
It's his fault for putting his hands on a
girl from the sea when he's from the surface!
But...
You stupid girls go over there.
This is now a guys-only planning meeting.
Let's go, Manaka.
Yeah.
Music Room
I hope Hikari calms down a little...
He's impossible when he's like that.
Manaka?
Chii-chan! A sea slug!
Wow, it's one with a red belly.
If you tell a red-bellied sea slug about
feelings you can't tell anyone else,
it'll tell you what's going
to happen in the future.
Yeah, if it spits up a black rock,
your feelings are wrong,
and if it spits up a pretty rock...
...those feelings will continue to
shine on forever like a jewel.
Hey, Manaka.
Do you like Tsumugu-kun?
Wh-What...
What are you talking about, Chii-chan?!
I'm not really sure.
All right, we'll do this tomorrow.
I wonder if this will even work though.
That car had a fishery
cooperative mark, right?
Even if he tried to run...
But if I like him,
I wonder if I'd want
to go out with him...
If I went out with him, um...
maybe we'd kiss like Akari-san...
Did you think I'm a pervert?
No, not at all.
Continue.
And if I thought about getting married,
I wonder if I wouldn't be
able to come back here...
You don't have to think about that yet.
You're not even sure if
you like him yet, right?
Yeah...
But I like you, and Hii-kun and Kaname.
I know that much.
But Tsu—
It's a little different
with Kihara-kun...
and I'm not really sure.
I see.
Hikari...
We're going home, Manaka, Chisaki!
Oh, Hii-kun.
You're done already?
Th-That was faster than expected.
That night...
Welcome home.
Dinner's ready.
R-Right...
Dad and Akari acted
like they usually do...
and didn't say a word about anything
that happened at Uroko-sama's.
How stupid.
But...
All throughout the night,
I could hear soft, soft, crying...
There were two nights like this up until now...
I used to call Akari "Nee-chan."
Sea that's full of compassion, waves
that flutter, the bright light...
The sea that nurtures all life.
The turning storm,
the tide that takes all...
Mom! Mom! Mom!
The abyss that opens Agito...
The master of the sea, Sea God,
the exalted one I am born from,
save the soul of Sakishima Hokage.
Nee-chan!
Guide her soul along with the
sacred fire to where you are.
She didn't cry at all.
Let us praise all of the good
she did in this life...
Nee-chan?
I thought that it was weird that she
was acting like an adult and wasn't
crying even though she was a kid too.
So...
Akari!
What's going on?!
Didn't I tell you?
I'm going to start working
at Oshiooshi's Saya Mart.
Why?! You said you wanted
to be a manga artist!
That you were going to go to
school for it on the surface...
Oh, but they said they'd let
me draw the signs at the shop.
I'm totally going to create a famous
mascot and bring in the sales!
Cut the crap, Akari!
Stop trying to gloss things over!
We don't have enough money for
both of us to go to college.
I don't plan on going to college! But you did!
You don't know yet.
You might change your mind once
you're in high school, Hikari.
Then I won't even go to high school!
I hate studying anyway!
Wha— L-Let me go, Akari!
I love you, Hikari.
Nothing changed with me
calling Nee-chan "Akari."
What I called her didn't
change anything between us.
I realized it was my fault that she
was becoming an adult more and more.
I'm pissed off at her guy...
and I don't really understand it,
but I was sort of relieved.
About the fact that Akari finally
started thinking about herself.
Not to mention...
And if I thought about getting married,
I wonder if I wouldn't be
able to come back here...
I was frustrated about Manaka too...
But I knew that Manaka was
probably even more frustrated...
About the people on the surface
and the people of the sea...
Oshiooshi Fishery Cooperative
All right, let's go.
Hey, you're not going to start
punching out of nowhere, are you?
I get it.
We'll talk for a while and then I'll
look for an opening to punch him.
You don't get it at all!
Hey, that's...
Th-That's...
Wait, you cheater!
You're trying to run away?!
It's not like we made plans with
him, so it can't be helped...
Hii-kun?!
Hikari!
This isn't good!
H-Hikari... How far did he go?
Hii-kun...
Shh!
Hey, this is...
Kihara-kun's house!
So that'll be the shipping
date starting next month.
See you.
That bastard!
Hii-kun!
You said you wouldn't
start suddenly punching!
Hey! You!
Damn it! What the hell?!
Who the hell are you, old man?!
These eyes...
They're a storm.
U-Um... kid?
Hii-kun!
Hikari!
Hikari? Are you Akari's younger brother?
Why are you...
Whoa!
Akari's crying because of you!
And all the old guys of Shioshishio
are on her case because of you!
What?
You there. The girl didn't tell you?
Tell me what?
It's not an ordinary thing
for a person from the surface
and a person from the
sea to get together.
Old man?
I'm aware of that.
There's the rivalry, as well as the
issue with fishing grounds...
But that doesn't—
That has nothing to do with it.
Are you trying to have babies?
Wh-Wha—
Is this old man senile?!
That's the problem, though.
Kihara-kun?
The biggest difference between the people
on the surface and the people of the sea,
is the Ena that covers
the people of the sea.
Ena is similar to the amnion
that covers the fetus,
and the people on the surface break
through this when they're born.
But the people of the sea are born
with this being a part of their skin.
Just like scales on a fish.
The people of the sea are able to
breathe underwater because they have Ena...
A child born between a person from
the surface and a person from the sea
is born without Ena.
Th-Then if Akari-san had a baby...
That baby wouldn't be able
to live in the water?
I see...
That means there'd be
fewer descendants...
That's why if you marry
someone from the surface,
you're banished from the village.
Banished from the village?!
Why...
Why didn't Akari tell me anything...
Hey, you!
Believe me, Hikari-kun!
I'm not messing around with Akari!
Huh? Then do you plan
on marrying Akari?
That's...
What?!
You're dating her but you have
no plans to take responsibility?!
That's the worst!
Hii-kun!
Hikari!
I don't really remember
what happened after that.
He kept taking punches
from me for a while,
No!
and when I realized it...
Good morning.
Just stay down.
Your friends went to soak in the water.
You need to keep wet, don't you?
It's surprising if you
do that all of the sudden!
I always wondered what
happened to your clothes
when you come up to
the surface all wet...
When we're on dry land,
apparently the Ena sucks up any
extra moisture and stores it.
That's convenient.
Really?
Yeah, I want it.
I thought this earlier too,
but how do you know so
much about Shioshishio?
Because I think it's great.
I'm asking you why you
think it's grea—
Is it weird?
I'll go get some more water.
Oh, don't worry about it. I'm fine.
I'll be leaving.
Don't get up too fast.
Kihara Tsumugu is a good guy.
I realized that early on, but...
U-Um...
Thank you very much.
I'm the one who threw you.
R-Right...
Yeah, I guess it's weird
for me to thank you...
Ena...
Old man, are you from Shioshishio—
Oh, Hii-kun!
Thank goodness. You're awake.
Welcome home.
I heard you got thrown around.
How do you know about that?
Did that guy contact you?!
Yeah. He called me.
Akari! Give up on that guy!
He's totally not—
Yeah, I'm going to.
Huh?
It wouldn't have worked
out with him anyway.
H-Hey, you're giving up that easily?
It's fine.
No, it's not!
You can worry about the baby
when you actually have one...
Oh? You're supposed to learn that in
health class your third year in junior high...
but you already found out?
It's fine. Really.
People on the surface
and people of the sea...
shouldn't be together anyway.
Akari...
But you know...
Right now, there are only a few
single guys in the village, right?
So getting married is pretty hard...
How can you laugh?
Well, I guess I'll just have
to resort to forbidden love.
Akari! Stop messing around! Let me go!
You're so cute.
Hey! What are you—
Akari...
Morning!
Hey, it's Kihara-kun.
Good morning.
Morning.
How are you feeling?
R-Right...
Tsumugu, thanks for yesterday.
Huh?
I-I was trying really hard
not to call him by his first name!
You said that it was
perverted if I did, Hii-kun!
I-It's fine if it's between guys!
What?!
I see. Then I'll call him that, too.
Tsumugu.
Hey, no fair, Kaname!
Then I'm going to do it too!
It's okay, right, Tsumugu-kun?
Huh? Uh, sure...
Oh, you guys...
It's decided, then.
Thank goodness.
I'm glad you and Tsumugu-kun
are a little closer now.
Now you're calling him Tsumugu, too?
Well, Tsumugu-kun is nice.
I was thinking he'd be able to be
friends with you someday, too.
You really do worry too much.
You're just like my sister.
S-Sorry. I didn't mean
to act all mature again.
Sorry for making you
worry all the time.
I'll try to be more mature, too...
Hikari?
Wood Shop Room
Looks like you're making good progress.
Yes.
If you guys keep it up,
you'll be done soon.
I know!
Since you did so well, I'll
treat you guys to some ramen.
I've always wanted to treat
my students to ramen one day.
Seriously?! Awesome!
I want miso ramen!
But...
It's almost five...
Oh, right...
Sorry. Then next time—
Hey.
It's done.
Hey, this...
Tsumugu-kun was making this for us so
we could get work done at any time.
Tsumugu-kun...
I thought the fish might
want to breathe, too.
Thanks, Tsumugu.
No problem.
Hey, Manaka?!
Manaka?
I'm sorry!
Huh?
I was lying!
Your curse was lifted?
Curse?
But... if Uroko-sama curses me again...
Um, that was a curse!
Because I threw some food at him...
Though he didn't curse
me again last time...
If I try to do something bad again,
he'll probably do it!
Let's meet again.
Manaka... what are you doing?
I'm impersonating the fish from the curse.
That's not what I meant!
Huh?!
Hey, Hikari!
Thanks!
You're welcome!
Me too.
You're all wet!
Um... what about the ramen?
You really do dry up.
But you're all soaked, Tsumugu-kun.
Hikari?
I forgot that I had
to stop by some place.
You guys go on ahead!
Eh?
Wh-What the hell?
Oh, it's you guys again.
Huh? But on TV, they lost
consciousness after that.
Something's not right!
You need to soak it with
chloroform to do that!
It's not going to work
with just a handkerchief.
The damn media got me dancing to their tune.
Yeah, dancing like an octopus.
You're the octopus, octopus-head!
Hey.
What? If you're her friend, do
something about this idiot—
Help me.
Huh?
Help me break up my dad and that woman.
D...
Dad?!
That's a rather blunt
criminal declaration.
Let's keep this between us, Kaname.
That's not fair!
Am I the only bad guy?
Forgive me! Please!
Episode 4: Because We're Friends