Watanuki...
If you push too hard, you'll hurt yourself.
Shut up.
Next time I see that guy,
I'll settle this, once and for all.
He's gonna regret making a fool of me!
I know right now I'm no good...
It's so nice out today.
Don't interrupt me!
It feels so good...
When the weather is this nice,
Are you listening?!
it makes me want to go out
and do something...
You do this every single time!
Ayakashi Kan Walk Rally
Good morning, Miss Ririchiyo.
Good morning, Miketsukami.
This time, I am going to ask you.
Would you be my Secret Service agent?
How embarrassing...
It made me so happy yesterday
when you asked me to enter into
this contract with you.
Now I can serve you again.
I just thought it could be handy
to have a bodyguard around
in case something happens.
Yes.
But still, it made me very happy,
knowing that you will allow me
by your side again.
However,
I never imagined that taking you
to school would bring such sorrow.
It's just like divine punishment.
It isn't just school.
Seeing me go anywhere makes you sad.
You're right.
But I feel like it makes me
sadder than it did before.
May I at least hold your
hand on the way?
Yes.
Thank you.
What is this?
My heart rate's been weird
since this morning...
I can't seem to settle down.
You've received a message
Soushi Miketsukami
I did nothing to deserve
your thanks.
Rather, I must
thank you for continually
sending me such
kind e-mails.
I am very grateful
for your kind
treatment.
Miketsukami replied...
And my heart is doing that thing again.
Could this be what they call...
an irregular heartbeat?
With the move, it's been so hectic...
I need to take care of my health.
I wonder if he lives here.
I've never seen him before.
What are you looking at?
You started looking at me first.
Stop staring at me.
Look somewhere else.
You first.
1 minute later...
My eyes...
I knew you couldn't walk the walk.
You're that fox spirit's partner, aren't you?
Your attitude stinks!
Huh?
Bring it on!
I love you.
Frenetic dance.
Kamikaze Attack!
Best regards.
We only respect ourselves.
I'm Banri Watanuki, room one,
and I'm a delinquent!
Top of the world.
I'll choke you!
I love you.
Wind, forest,
fire, mountain
Divine demon.
Delinquent
You say that like you're proud of it.
How kind of you to warn me.
I'm Ririchiyo Shirakiin, from room four.
Another person who won't
take me seriously?
Because I'm a...
tiny tanuki?!
You transformed just for me?
That really is kind of you.
Shut up!
I transform easily because I'm unstable!
What of it?!
Just because I look like this
doesn't mean I can't hurt you!
I'm a...
What are you doing?!
I'll feed you a knuckle sand—
That's no way to speak to a lady.
Hello!
It's so nice to meet you!
Oh, who am I?
I'm Zange Natsume.
I'm Watanuki's Secret Service agent.
You're his agent...
I was born twenty-three years ago,
at St. Maria hospital,
with a weight of 3020 grams.
I quickly grew into a quirky boy.
Virgo, blood type B.
No girlfriend!
However, as I am descended
from a Hundred Eyes creature,
I see things I don't wish to.
That is my sad story.
While fighting my distrust of humanity
and my loneliness,
I took to the east, the west...
Um...
What's that?
You want to know more about me?
Sorry, but I think a little mystery
can be quite an enticement.
How-ev-er...
I know everything about you,
Ririchiyo Shirakiin.
I also know what's causing
your irregular heartbeat.
I know your past and your future.
I know of your past life and your next one.
Even the color of your underwear.
All that can be seen,
and all that cannot be...
You're...
But if you win tomorrow's match,
I'll tell you absolutely anything!
Match?
I've come back to challenge that
damned fox spirit to a death match.
That's right!
Hey! Let me go!
Okay.
I look forward to tomorrow.
Let's go, Rascal.
My name's not Rascal!
Fox spirit...
Does he mean Miketsukami?
And what match?
Good morning, Miss Ririchiyo.
Are Sundays not lovely?
To think that I can behold your
supreme beauty all day, and...
Hey, you.
Now isn't the time for that, is it?
So what's this match about?
What are you talking about?
Sou, baby!
Sou...
Wow, I never thought I'd
be working with you!
Hi, Chiyo...
I saw you just last night.
Y-You know each other?
We're old friends, right?
It has been a while.
I apologize for not keeping
in touch, Natsume.
Quite an attitude difference here.
Businesslike as always, I see.
Still, for you, I'd even offer myself.
I am honored.
Really?
What the hell?
Fetish
Two guys? Gross.
Seriously?
Well, different strokes for
different folks, I guess.
Natsume was my old master's friend,
and he's always been kind to me.
He was thoughtful enough
to call us old friends.
And indeed, we've known each
other for a long time.
Then do me, Sou!
So what, like childhood friends?
Hey!
Stop consorting with the enemy.
The guy from yesterday...
I'm settling this here and now.
It's been a while, nine-tailed fox.
Our meeting here spells your end.
I hope you're prepared to
meet your fate, nemesis!
It has been a long time.
I apologize for not keeping
in touch, Mr. Watanuki.
Once again, quite a difference
in attitude here.
He's also one of our childhood friends.
I am not your childhood friend!
You...
All you did was bully and abuse me!
We're going on a walk.
Come on, Rascal!
But that was fine.
We were just kids.
Naturally, it's survival of the fittest.
My master ordered me not to,
but I am sorry I could not help you.
I feel so... So pathetic!
You were not.
You were very cute.
That's when my pride was obliterated!
I'm afraid I've said the wrong thing.
Please forgive me.
Too little, too late!
You won't be calling me cute ever again.
Don't think I'm the same as back then.
Now, I'm...
Hello! I'm going to explain the rules!
The contest is an Ayakashi Kan Walk Rally.
The first person to gather signatures
from each Ayakashi Kan resident,
and return here is the winner.
Then I shall forfeit.
You can't do that!
But this is Sunday,
my day to spend with Miss Ririchiyo.
It might sound weird coming from me,
but maybe you should humor them.
You think I'm gonna let you forfeit?
So noisy in here...
But if you insist on backing out,
let me punch you ten times!
Fine, if that would make
you feel better.
I cannot involve you in something like this.
It's fine.
I'm already involved.
Anyway, we're partners now.
If you just stand there
and let him hit you,
it will make me look bad.
Miss Ririchiyo.
Then I'll be Ririchiyo's ally.
What?
But in exchange, can I
slip a finger under your knee sock
and feel your thigh?
You haven't given up on that?
That would be too embarrassing...
But if we lose, Miketsukami will...
I want to do something for him.
Come on, it was a joke!
Not really, but...
Which is it?
If...
Huh?
If it's only a little bit...
Just get it over with.
I'll sign, a million times,
on whatever you want.
Hey, sign mine, too!
Then you'll have to do an impersonation.
If it's funny, I'll sign.
Right...
If we do this, we're doing it to win.
Yes.
Oh?
Hello, miss.
Oh, me?
Cook
My name is Joe.
I'm the wolf with a kid,
who works in a run-down bar.
This isn't a bar, Dad.
I'm sorry, but could you sign this?
Is it something dangerous?
I can dig that.
I'm used to it.
And please don't make cocktails
that no one ordered.
Come back when you're
all grown up, miss.
I'll make you a cocktail that
suits you perfectly.
Dad, enough. Please grate the radish.
Okay, we got his signature.
Let's go see some of the other employees.
Yes.
What do you think of that?
So-so.
What? Why?
I don't wanna hear it from you!
I guess I'll be generous.
Here you go.
You signed it!
Well, I didn't say I wouldn't.
I just gave my opinion.
You...
Come now...
You'll lose if you keep wasting time.
I'll remember this!
I wonder where the other employees are.
Let's go in order...
That was close!
Wha—
I thought I was going to get stepped on!
S-So tiny...
I'm a koro-pok-kuru.
Maid 1
It's really handy for cleaning tight spaces.
So tiny!
Ouch...
No, I wasn't talking about your chest...
Maid 2
You want my signature?
What? Why do you want it?
This is all very suspicious.
I won't do it.
You can't fool me.
Excuse me.
I really do hate to interrupt
your work for a game.
We certainly wouldn't abuse your trust.
This I swear to you.
So I beg you...
Very well...
Warashibe?
That's right.
I'm a zashiki-warashi.
Want to bring luck and me into your home?
I'm already as happy as possible.
You want my signature?
Maid Three
I feel like a star.
This is a maid?!
That's right...
For some reason, I am a maid.
Beats me why.
You know, I once worked for
a company, but they fired me.
Like, I was another victim of
the bad economy.
Why do I suspect the economy wasn't
the only reason he was fired?
Could you please sign here?
You have a sharp tongue.
My wife said the same thing.
Though we're separated right now.
My signature?
Is this all right?
It looks like you're having fun.
Can I come, too?
Psyche!
Oh, does no one say "psyche" anymore?
Was that before your time?
He sure is a cheerful guy...
This man is the concierge here.
Concierge
His name is Homare Nekozuki.
Bodyguard
Shouldn't you switch places?
Concierge
He's a very introverted person.
They say he's very shy about
showing his face.
Um...
He's a nekomata?
They say he has cat ears
when he transforms.
I guess Miss Roromiya is the last one.
I haven't seen her since this morning.
Why don't we try searching where
we haven't been yet?
You're right.
Not here...
Not in the lounge, either.
Let's go up to the third floor.
I didn't know there was a bar here.
Weren't you downstairs before?!
Yeah.
I told you to return when
you were grown.
You're a quick-spirited young lady.
And we can't seem to hold
a real conversation.
Will you wait for me here?
Yes.
Oh, Ririchiyo!
Oh, it's you again!
Are you still doing the Walk Rally?
Y-Yes! I was looking for Miss Roromiya...
I-I-I didn't mean to interrupt.
You needn't get so embarrassed.
B-But...
Is everything all right, Miss Ririchiyo?
Your face is very red.
I'm fine.
There she is!
But that's...
Sou, baby!
Nice to see you again, Natsume.
Sou, you're actually quite manly.
Wh-What are you doing?
We're supposed to be
doing the Walk Rally!
Shh!
You should keep it down.
You were yelling, too.
It would really embarrass him
if he knew we were spying on him.
Spying?
Um...
Sorry to ask right after getting back,
but would you sign this?
Okay.
I asked Karuta to wait there.
You asked her to wait?
Is this okay?
Yeah.
Well, thanks...
Watanuki.
You were gone for so long,
I was worried.
Sorry.
Actually, I brought you a present.
Maple bean cakes from Hiroshima.
He felt like he had worried her,
being away for so long.
And that made it hard
for him to talk to her...
Unless he had some reason.
Are you saying—
So where do you think Watanuki was?
He was training! That's right, training!
He told me he wants to protect
the girl he loves.
Not that I don't understand,
but going off to train?
And Karuta's so strong,
he needn't worry about protecting her.
You shouldn't laugh at him.
So that was the reason behind
this whole match.
But that wasn't all...
I told you, I can see you.
You really should interact
more with others.
You say, "Until I can properly
interact with other people"...
But that's a skill that can
only be learned by
hurting and being hurt by others.
He really
can see...
You...
Who, me?
I'm everyone's big brother Zange,
who's just a tiny bit overbearing!
My motto is "Let's all get along."
So come on, Sou...
Let's be closer friends than ever!
If that's what you want, I'd be happy to.
Really?
Ririchiyo is so adorable...
I'd like to sink my teeth into him.
What a man...
I wanted to thank you for
spending the day with me.
You're mistaken.
Natsume's real targets were
Watanuki and me.
It isn't like I was hanging out with you.
That reminds me...
Even though we supposedly won,
I didn't ask him my question.
I also know what's causing
your irregular heartbeat.
Irregular heartbeat...
Miss Ririchiyo?
I wanted to ask him why that's happening.
We're here.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
You appeared to be deep in thought.
I wondered if, perhaps,
something was troubling you.
I would be happy to listen, if you'd like.
I'm fine.
Is that so?
Because I am not.
Only a few days ago,
I was happy just being by your side.
But now, every day...
No, every hour, I become more
and more demanding.
I wonder what you were discussing
with Natsume.
What he meant when he said "last night."
It even makes me,
the lowly dog, dare to be jealous.
T-Too close!
Miss Ririchiyo!
Are you all right?
"Irregular heartbeat.
Irregular heartbeat is a layman's term
for extrasystolic arrhythmia.
Related conditions are tachycardia,
a rapid heartbeat,
and bradycardia, a slowed heartbeat."
I hope it isn't anything serious...
Heartbeat
Pulse
Arrhythmia...?
I never expected Natsume to be
working at Ayakashi Kan.
I'll have to make sure he
doesn't say too much.
They say that a late-night bar is
the scramble crossing of life.
Dad, this is the morning dining hall.
Could you please hurry and grate the radish?
The place where worn-out people come,
to feel the momentary warmth
of Midnight Heaven.
Whatever, can you please boil the eggs?
My eggs are already boiled.
I'm hard boiled.
Next time, on Inu X Boku Secret Service:
Kagerou of the Spring.
Was that a little too pretentious?
Kagerou of the Spring
Please permit me to accompany you again next time.