Dad? You mean him?
So he's having an affair?
Break them up? How?
You're in junior high,
figure it out, octopus!
You. What's your name?
Miuna.
Sayu!
I don't like your dad either.
He's got a kid and he's trying
to get with a younger woman...
He's not fit for Akari...
my big sister.
Your sister's the one
who's tricking him!
But...
Hey!
Wh-Why you—
I don't like playing
dirty like you, Miuna.
See ya.
Wh-What's his problem?!
He won't get away with that!
Miuna! Let's fry him up!
We'll make him into takoyaki!
Miuna?
Episode 4: Because We're Friends
Wow, that's amazing, Hii-kun!
You're really good.
It's not a big deal...
Your cheek's twitching.
You're really good too, Tsumugu-kun.
When did you learn how to cook?
I've always been cooking.
It's always been just
me and Gramps, so...
I see. That's very admirable.
W-We don't need that
much Chinese cabbage...
So good!
All right. Let's all go around to
the other groups and try their food.
Okay.
Huh?
Hey, give me some.
What is this? The carrot's so big.
What do you want to do?
I'm not sure...
E-Excuse me...
Please... try this if you'd like.
Manaka!
"Try this"?
Like there's any way we could eat
anything you sea people make.
Wha...
It smells pretty fishy.
Right?
B-But... there isn't
even any fish in it.
I don't want any.
I think it's fine...
I said I don't want any!
Why you...
Apologize.
Tsumugu-kun...
What for? My hand just
accidentally bumped her.
Yeah...
Right?
Hey, what's going on here?
Oh...
Sorry...
You're not going to eat your lunch?
We just ate...
I'm gonna go work on Ojoshi-sama.
Oh, I'll go, too.
Hey...
Maybe we should try harder
to get along with them.
Wood Shop Room
With the guys that waste food?
Wha...
This is horrible!
Who would do this...
It's them.
Wait, Hikari!
Half arm suplex!
Hey, stop!
Chest!
Hikari!
It's wrong that the Ojoshi-sama
was broken, but still...
We didn't do that!
Stop lying! Then who the hell did it?!
Hey, stop. Stop.
Hii-kun...
You're a little too excited today,
so this isn't going anywhere.
We'll talk about this further tomorrow.
Right.
Hikari, you can go home for now.
I'm the only one you're sending home?!
Am I the only bad guy?
Hikari!
Well, excuse me!
Hikari...
I'm going home, too.
You, too?
Aw, but you can't.
You still have fourth period...
I want to go home, so I'm going home!
O-Okay?
Manaka is really stubborn
when she gets like that...
This isn't coming off very well.
Manaka's so cute.
She's a scaredy cat, but
has a strong will...
a gorgeous body... big, round eyes...
and she's always trying so hard.
And you're big.
You're too blunt, Kaname.
There are guys who prefer bigger.
You think so?
Apparently middle-aged men prefer
it when girls aren't so skinny.
I saw it on TV.
Following with that doesn't help.
You should just be honest and be happy.
You're right...
I really should be more
honest like Manaka.
"Sayu has arrived"?
Sayu?
Do you know her?
Yeah.
She's one of the mysterious grade
school kids that has a grudge against Hikari.
Grade school kids...
That's a rather blunt
criminal declaration.
So it wasn't the guys from our class.
Chisaki?
Let's keep this a secret.
Let's keep this between us, Kaname.
Huh? Why?
Because if everyone else
finds out about this,
Hikari will end up the bad guy.
But...
I can't watch Hikari
being hurt any further.
Bad guy or not, it's true that
it was a misunderstanding.
It's not a good thing to lie.
It'll just isolate you even more.
That's not true!
They're people who were saying
that our food smelled fishy!
They're really not bad people.
The people who purposely
spilled the sushi bowl?!
I thought you were a good person,
but I guess you're a person
from the surface after all.
Don't take it personally.
Chisaki loses her head when
it comes to Hikari or Manaka.
I know.
I love the ocean, and
the people of Shishio.
So I don't want everyone
to misunderstand Hikari
just because he
misunderstands all of them.
I'm sorry, could you say
that one more time?
I don't want everyone
to misunderstand Hikari
just because he
misunderstands all of them.
Ah, got it.
Go a
I don't like playing
dirty like you, Miuna.
Miuna!
I did it!
I gave it to 'em good!
What?
You know they were making
an Ojoshi-sama, right?
I totally ruined it!
Ruined?
Yeah!
I drew all over it
and ripped the clothes so that you
can't even tell it's Ojoshi-sama anymore!
For real!
Why would you do that...
Huh?
That's really playing dirty!
M-Miuna?!
I... I hate playing dirty like that!
Miuna!
Hii-kun, wait!
Why'd you follow me?
Oh...
An octopus...
Here, boy...
Octopuses are cowards.
You know, you're probably
like an octopus.
You're going to call
me an octopus, too?!
Huh? "Too"?
Oh, nothing...
When they get scared by fish
they don't know, they spit out ink.
Like dark black stuff.
But the ink is really
good if you eat it.
Squid ink pasta, for example.
Or would it be octopus ink?
I've never made that so...
What are you trying to say?
Wh-What was it...
Hey, why'd you bring them
the sushi bowl in the first place?
Huh?
You wouldn't usually
do something like that.
You're usually hiding behind us.
That's because...
Another octopus?
No... Look!
That's... Akari's...
Hii-kun, the bottom's turning black!
What?
You can't even make rice
porridge by yourself?
I guess we can just put in
some miso and cover it up.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I've caused you some trouble.
I'm sorry.
You have something else to
apologize for, you criminal.
C-Criminal?!
You have a kid and yet you're
trying to get with my big sister.
Oh...
The hell were you drowning for?
I haven't been able to contact Akari.
She won't come to the supermarket,
so I thought I'd come
see her directly myself.
Directly? You mean to Shioshishio?
Yeah...
I borrowed some diving
equipment from my friend,
but it kept filling up with water...
Where do you get off
playing the sad victim?!
D-Don't, Hii-kun!
You're a criminal. A perpetrator!
Affairs are totally unforgivable!
Uroko-sama, could you
spare some sacred fire?
You're quite the sinner,
walking over the servant of a god.
That's fine.
Despite how much I've cleaned up around here,
and despite all the things I've done for you,
I still ended up having a terrible time.
How long do you plan not to go to work?
I've been thinking about
finding a job around here.
Though there's not much around here.
You're going to give up on him
because his daughter didn't approve?
You seem to know a lot of gossip
despite being cooped up in here all the time.
It's only been three years
since she lost her mother...
I can understand why she
can't approve of me.
The girl's mother was Miori, who
lived in a house just off the rocks.
So you remember her.
Indeed.
She was a real beauty
with an enormous ass.
Despite Miori-san being from here,
they treated me really well.
Café Triangle
Miuna-chan is actually really cute...
like a little baby sister.
And with Itaru-san, they were
the family that I had admired.
Everyone was always smiling.
But...
Miori-san's funeral...
Miuna-chan...
was bawling.
It was the first time I ever
saw her cry like that...
and it reminded me of Hikari
when he was younger, and...
And...
I thought...
I wanted to stay by them.
I thought I could fill the hole
that Miori-san left behind.
It's all about how you say things.
Huh?
That's just illicit love.
Miori was gone and you
wanted to steal her place.
That's harsh, Uroko-sama.
I wouldn't mind putting a curse on you.
A curse?
A curse to make you forget
the man you fell for.
I don't need that.
I'll take care of this on my own.
Akari is still such a child.
There's only so much
you can do on your own.
I know, Lord Sea God.
We can't let the surface have
the people of the sea right now.
Ojoshi-sama.
Huh?
I did it.
What?
I'm the one who ruined it!
Why?
Why didn't you get mad at her, Hii-kun.
Because it's not like I don't
know how she feels.
Huh?
After my mom died, if some
other woman came into my house,
I probably wouldn't
have liked it either.
Wh— Why are you crying?!
Uroko-sama told me...
that I'm always being protected
by you and Chii-chan and Kaname...
Uroko-sama did?
And I think that's true.
Uroko-sama says something
good once in a while.
You're nice, Hii-kun.
Really nice.
You can protect others...
Tomorrow, let's go apologize
to everyone together!
Yeah...
Even though they're gonna
have a lot to say in return.
And they'll say a lot to me, too.
Huh?
I want to protect you
from now on, Hii-kun.
I'm going to protect you.
Manaka...
Thanks.
Yeah.
Manaka...
I was supposed to be the
one to protect Manaka.
But instead, Manaka protected
me as if she were Ena.
Hey.
Do you have a sec?
What?
Hikari!
I'm... really sorry!
I was wrong.
You guys...
I mean, I'm sorry for thinking it
was you that destroyed Ojoshi-sama.
S-Stop, Hikari...
Dude, he's totally on his knees.
I never saw anyone do that.
Manaka!
Please!
Manaka?!
Hii-kun feels really bad.
Please forgive him. Please!
Manaka...
Forgive them, already.
Tsumugu.
You guys were responsible
for the sushi bowl, too.
You're both equally responsible.
We're not equal!
You guys threw around
the sushi bowl...
But I blamed you guys,
and then chested you.
Huh?
Forgive me...
and come at me!
Hii-kun...
Come on!
Chest!
D-Damn...
That's enough. This is annoying.
I forgive you.
When do you actually go to school?
Y-You!
You're pretty much the one responsible
for Hikari apologizing on his knees like that.
Hikari is my very dear friend.
And as his friend, I won't forgive you.
But I'm... I'm Miuna's friend too!
Huh?
She's my... she's my
really good, dear friend!
When I was in second grade,
everyone picked on me.
But Miuna didn't pick on me.
Then, people were picking on Miuna...
And I was sort of relieved...
that it wasn't me getting picked on.
But Miuna...
No matter how much they ignored her...
She was totally fine.
Hey.
Why are you okay with that?
Why are you okay with getting picked on...
and people not liking you.
Because it doesn't matter.
Because they're people I don't care about,
that have nothing to do with me...
And I don't care what they think of me.
That's when...
I thought I don't care what
people think about me.
I don't care if people hate me.
I wanted to be dear to Miuna.
Can you apologize to Hikari?
Huh?
Since you understand how dear someone
can be to you, you can, right?
Yeah...
Good girl.
I-I-I... I'm really sorry!
And so, please forgive her.
You did...
Hii-kun...
Then why did she...
What's wrong?
Oh... nothing.
Man, how lame.
You've got snot coming out your nose.
Sh-Shut up, you octopus!
Octopus-sama!
Putting "sama" on the end
doesn't make anything better!
I...
I wanted to defend Hikari...
But...
You'll never be able
to replace my mom!
Dad is a man of the sea, after all...
Will you become a sea slug?
If you find a red one,
what will you tell it?
Episode Five: Hey, Sea Slug