Sharl,
are you okay?
You really
are Heroes.
We were telling the truth, huh?
We're the Heroes from Biscotti and Galette.
I found our stuff, so we can
communicate with people.
I hope it connects.
The Dragon Priestess
Um, what is that?
This allows us to communicate
with Biscotti and Galette!
Shinku!
Princess!
I'm so glad I reached you!
Shinku!
Nanami-san!
I'm so glad!
Are you safe?
We are!
I'm sorry, Princess; we're going to be late.
Not at all!
Where are you now?
Each of the three countries just
sent out search teams for you!
Um...
Where are we again?
The south side of the continent.
The Dragon Forest on the Corone Plateau.
So she said.
Great.
That's surprisingly close.
If I send out someone now,
we should be able to meet you today.
I'm glad.
Um...
Oh right! I have to introduce you!
Sharl!
Princess, this girl saved us.
I-I'm Sharl.
A Dragon Priestess.
I'm the leader of Biscotti,
Millihiore Firianno Biscotti.
Thank you for saving
Shinku and Nanami-san.
I-I'm honored.
We'll probably be
getting close to the entrance
to the dragon's forest.
We'll likely be intruding
on everyone there...
Um... it's okay.
So yeah, I'm safe!
I'm relieved.
I'm glad you're safe.
Sorry to worry you.
Gaul and the others already
went looking for you.
We'll be on our way, too.
Thanks!
I'm glad they're safe.
That's right!
Sorry, sorry.
Anyway, we're safe for now.
We and Pastillage's high-speed flyers
are on our way.
We should see you soon.
Just wait a little while longer.
Thank you, Kuu-sama, Becky.
But you don't need to hurry.
I want to take the chance to explore
this place before we meet up with you.
I see.
Dragon Priestess!
Take care of our two Heroes, would you?
R-Right!
Wow!
There's only half as much water as normal.
Even though it's so amazing?
Do dragons live here, too?
Yeah.
Where are they?
That is the True Dragon of this place.
She controls water and thunder.
Wow!
The True Dragons control
the blessings of the land.
Water, fire, wind, and greenery...
So they're like the land gods?
Perhaps they're the same to you humans,
but to us they're very different.
The dragons are the life and
nature of this land itself.
This is amazing, but...
Is it normally even more amazing?
Yeah.
That's the fire dragon.
It gives energy to the land
via the power of the volcano.
Sorry!
It's fine.
Once upon a time, the dragons were thought
to be harbingers of natural disasters.
They would cause storms
and make volcanoes erupt.
But we realized that after the disasters like
heavy rains, storms, and volcanic eruptions,
the land would always regain its energy.
I think Rico-chan might've
told me that before.
It's said that the dragons
restore balance to the scales of nature,
and undo the damage caused by
humans and other life forms.
I see.
And it's the Dragon Priestesses who
connect the dragons and humans.
She tells us what the dragons are going to do
ahead of time, so that we
don't become enemies.
And sometimes she lends the power
of the dragons to arid lands.
So they're amazing people.
I see.
That must've been rough
for Shinku and Nanami.
They've both been confirmed as safe,
so we'll be waiting here.
I see.
But the Dragon Forest is
a rare place to end up.
It may be a good place for them
to expand their knowledge as heroes.
But I've heard something about
demon-like creatures appearing there,
so I'm worried.
In the dragon's forest?
Yukikaze, I'd like you
to give me more details.
Okay.
This is my home.
It's on the edge of the forest.
Even if a lot of humans come here,
it won't surprise the dragons,
and won't bother anybody.
Wait here until your people come to get you.
So then
the things that attacked
you back there were...
Demons.
Around the end of summer,
they suddenly appeared.
They attack dragons,
and hurt the creatures in this forest.
Ever since they appeared,
the dragons have been scared
and the land and the plants are going crazy.
So there are others besides
the one we defeated?
I keep defeating them and
they keep appearing.
I think they're being born
somewhere in this forest.
That root is sucking away the
life of the forest and the
power of the dragons,
and using it to create demons.
I have to find that root and destroy it.
The dragons always help me.
I'm a Dragon Priestess.
At times like this, I have to help them.
Then we'll help, too!
It's a Hero's job to fight demons.
This is the Dragon Priestess's job.
It's not for human Heroes to get involved.
I'll be okay on my own.
I always have been,
and I always will be.
Sharl...
They're here.
They're angry because one
of their kind was slain.
They're close!
We'll come, too!
You stay here, Heroes.
This is the Dragon Forest's problem.
Don't leave this room. Okay?
Wow.
She's an archer, huh?
Is that crest magic, too?
Hero!
I'm glad.
I told you not to come.
And we said we would!
Boomerang Blade!
Go!
Oh, no!
There are still so many!
It's okay!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Pastillage's Sky Knights
are here!
That's...
I'm glad we made it in time.
Yup!
Now let's get rid of those demons!
Yeah!
Sky Knights, go!
Right!
Wow.
Look at all those knights on birds...
Those are the Pastillage Sky Knights!
Shinku! Nanami!
Becky!
I'm glad you're safe!
You're Sharl-san, the
Dragon Priestess, right?
Yeah.
I'm sorry to cause so much noise in
the skies over the dragon forest,
but the tri-country alliance
of Biscotti, Galette,
and Pastillage will defeat the demons.
Tri-country alliance? Does that mean...
Yup!
Well, Rico?
Can you see the Heroes?
I can!
Heroes!
Rico! Eclair!
There are a lot of them.
Yeah.
But no real Galette warrior would
have a problem with these wimps!
Yeah!
Now here we go!
Let's knock them out of the sky!
Explosive...
Lightning Wave!
Gaul and the Genoise, too!
Everybody who left to
find you met up midway.
So we can take care of any demons!
By the way, Hero Shinku.
Yes?
Don't you think that's
rude to the Dragon Priestess?
I-I-I-I'm sorry! I didn't mean to!
Um...
This was just for safety reasons...
It's okay.
I know.
Liscia and the others are here.
We probably won't be caught
off-guard in the sky.
Yes.
The problem is that, even if
we defeat the demons here,
it probably doesn't mean the end.
Yes.
We've wiped out all the
demons in visible range.
No sign of reinforcements!
Okay!
All right, Aria and Lucy will
continue to search for enemies.
Everybody else, head down to the ground.
Roger!
We have to greet the Dragon Priestess!
Hero!
Rico!
Sorry to worry you.
I'm glad you're okay.
It's okay to worry us, but why
did you make the princess worry?!
You're the Hero!
I'm sorry.
Thanks, everybody.
Anyway, I'm glad you're safe.
Really.
Sorry to worry you.
I'm grateful for all your cooperation.
Don't worry about it.
We help each other when we're in trouble.
I'm honored to meet you, Dragon Priestess.
Take a drink from these, if you like.
It's Sachi fruit.
Here you go.
A crash-landing, huh?
That must've sucked.
You're right.
Thanks for coming to save us, Gaul.
It was nothing!
What is this? It's great!
You're right!
Priestess!
May we talk to you for a moment?
I'm part of Galette's anti-demon squad.
This is Rico...
A scientist with the Royal Academy.
Is it about those demons?
Yes.
I've never heard of a
demon who attacks dragons
and who can steal power from
a True Dragon.
I'm worried it may be
a very dangerous dragon.
There's a legend passed down among
dragon-users and priestesses.
"When a demon appears that attacks the dragon,
a priestess must defeat
it with her own blood.
That is the job of a priestess who lives
with the dragons and draws from their power."
I'm glad I was able to give you
the missing Heroes safely.
It's getting late.
Rest tonight and leave early
tomorrow morning.
Wait, Hero!
Over here!
It's really close from here!
Wait, I said!
Hero!
So it seems
the priestess doesn't really
know the details, either.
We didn't get any good information.
Yeah.
Good work.
But Noir and I did some looking into it,
and the demons we fought
are transformed forest creatures.
The real demon must be
somewhere in the forest.
Unless we find it,
the damage to the dragons will continue.
Well done, Rico, Noir. Smart thinking.
In regards to the identity of the demon,
we asked an expert about it.
They're looking into it now.
Jeez. I was enjoying a peaceful day off,
and you brought this bothersome work in.
No complaining.
Our descendants are in trouble.
Thank you so much.
From what you've said,
it's a demon who feeds off the land.
It's probably a plant type,
so if you can find it,
it should be easy to defeat.
But it's concerning that it can
take power from a True Dragon.
Yup.
What's this?
Hey kid, contact the little one right away.
The Pastillage's elite air-land
knights are heading out.
And ask Galette and Biscotti
for help, as well.
Y-Yes. But...
What...
There's going to be war.
A war with a demon army
in the dragon's forest.
If we don't hurry, it could
threaten the entire continent.
Commando unit, hurry!
Right!
Listen! This isn't a game!
It's a real war against the demons!
Right!
But we do the same as always.
Follow the plan and stay in formation.
Defeat the enemy that appears
with all your strength,
and protect your allies!
Right!
Biscotti Knights! Camp 1, head out!
Anyway, our Hero seems to
have the oddest destiny.
This time he's fighting demons
with the priestess in the Dragon's Forest.
Yeah.
There's no end of trouble around that child.
Shinku is a hero, after all.
I'm sure
he goes wherever people need help.
Just wait.
The tri-country alliance is on its way!
You're getting close to another new girl?
Shinku!
No! It's not like that!
Big Battle!
The Dragon Forest
Valerio-sama! Behind you!