If the heroes are fighting each other
instead of the Waves of Catastrophe,
then for the sake of the world,
I must kill the Four Cardinal Heroes.
"Kill the Four Cardinal Heroes," eh?
Naofumi-sama?
Not yet!
Never mind. It's nothing.
They've really taken to you.
Right?
Liberation: Wind Prison.
Melty!
What's going on?
What are you doing to Mel-chan?!
Mel-tan,
I need you to be my hostage.
The Rising of the Shield Hero
"Hostage"?
A Promise Made
What's the meaning of this?
Shield Hero, promise me.
Promise me you'll make up
with the other heroes.
Let Mel-chan out of there!
And if I don't,
you're threatening to hurt Melty?
I thought I told you it wasn't happening!
Even still, I must ask you to.
Why are you so obsessed with
the heroes working together?
Because I made a promise
to the hero who raised me.
And because the heroes must cooperate
in order to save the world from the Waves.
Please.
It doesn't matter how many times you ask.
I have no intention of
reconciling with those morons.
In that case, new heroes
will have to be summoned.
And to enable that, I'll kill
all the current heroes.
So that's what you meant last night?
That will help the world in the long run.
Yeah, doing that would be easy for her.
Please reconcile with the other heroes.
Even then,
I can't do it.
You don't need to take Melty hostage.
If you want to kill me, feel free.
But...
Naofumi!
Naofumi-sama!
Just know that I'm not going
down without a fight!
Don't.
Detecting transformation jamming
Not again!
I understand how you feel, Shield Hero.
What?
If that's how it is, prove to me that
you and your party can
fight the Waves alone.
Prove to you?
How do we do that?
By fighting you right here and now?
Shield Hero, I more or less
know how strong you are.
I want a one-on-one with Filo.
Me?
If you prove to me that you're strong,
I'll release Mel-tan.
And I won't kill the heroes for a while.
I'll give you time.
I don't really understand, but if
I win, Master won't be killed,
and Mel-chan will be freed too, right?
Wait.
Hang on, Filo—
Then I'll fight.
I'll fight in this form,
so you fight me in human form too, Filo.
Gotcha.
I said wait!
This way.
Here I come.
Whenever you're ready.
You're slow.
Huh?
Filo! Above you!
Filo-chan!
Ow...
Why did Fitoria choose to fight
Filo and not Raphtalia?
And why are they fighting in human form?
Damn it.
Filo!
Don't just charge in blindly!
Use your head!
Master...
And regenerate your clothes
when you have the chance!
Pour your mana into it and increase
your defense as much as you can!
Gotcha!
As source of your powers, Filo orders you.
Decipher the laws of nature
and blow my target away with
a vicious vacuum burst.
Zweit Tornado!
Nullify the vacuum burst.
Anti-Zweit Tornado!
Watch out! It's jamming magic!
You're wide open.
She has no time to regenerate
her clothes at all.
Melty.
Filo's in trouble if this keeps up.
I'll try to get rid of
this cage with my shield.
Naofumi!
Naofumi-sama!
She cut through the shield's
defense with ease!
Master!
Eyes on me.
He got what he deserved for trying
to cheat and rescue Mel-tan.
But do you know why he did that?
Because you're weak.
What do you fight for?
Isn't that obvious?
For Master!
You couldn't beat the dragon last night,
you can't beat me now,
and you expect to be useful
to the Shield Hero?
I'm not gonna lose!
I'm gonna become strong for Master!
Not with such a shallow will!
Are you all right, Naofumi-sama?
Yeah, somehow.
I won't let Master get hurt any more.
I'll... I'll be much, much stronger!
Really?
What is she...
Is she absorbing the mana
particles in the air?
Is that even possible?
Filo!
Master...
I'm fine.
Calm down, and watch her attacks closely.
I know you can do it!
I know you can do it.
Yeah!
Too slow.
Okay, but I'll still beat you!
Spiral...
Strike!
Go!
Filo!
Naofumi-sama!
Did you see that magic
attack Filo just used?
Yeah.
I...
I won't lose.
Master, I'll grow stronger.
Strong enough to protect you, Mel-chan,
and Raphtalia-oneechan.
Strong enough to protect everyone.
Okay.
So...
I'll never lose.
That's enough, Filo.
You win.
I'll free Mel-tan.
You did well.
Filo-chan!
Mel-chan...
Master...
I won.
Yeah.
You did amazing, Filo.
You did well to pass the trial.
Filo, you were being tested.
Yes.
If you hadn't passed it, you would've died.
And the Shield Hero would have, too.
What is that?
A symbol proving that you overcame my trial.
Lower your head.
Filo, I appoint you my successor.
Successor?
You mean she'll become
the next filolial queen?
That's amazing, Filo-chan!
Is that the symbol of being next in line?
It's just a cowlick!
C-Cute!
Something weird grew on my head!
Get it off!
It grew back!
And it'll keep growing back,
so get used to it.
And you'll gain more of them as you grow.
Am I gonna look like you?
Her stats have increased.
Does that cowlick increase her
base numbers across the board?
Since Filo's level is capped right now,
this is perfect for her.
I also have something for you, Shield Hero.
For me?
I don't want a cowlick!
What's a cowlick?
It's something better.
I'll heal your wounds, too.
Now show me your shield.
Like this?
Shields were force unlocked
Force unlocked?
I can't use many of them because
my level's not high enough,
but it looks like the entire
Filolial Series has been unlocked.
Now I just have to meet their requirements.
Well, thank you.
You're welcome.
But I still have something I wish
to discuss with you in private.
There's more?
Uh...
You didn't use us just to
test Filo-chan, did you?
I did. I feel bad for what I did to you.
Is there anything you desire?
Huh?
W-Well, you see...
You know...
Wow, amazing! I'm so high up!
Ah, I'm living the dream!
Is a ride really all she wanted?
I wanna be really big soon, too!
Who knows how many cowlicks
you'll have by then?
No!
That was so much fun!
The day has only just begun.
Get some more rest before you leave.
But...
Well, if Fitoria's offering, why not accept?
Really?
This is a celebration, after all.
We need to show you some
real hospitality as well.
A party to celebrate the
appointment of a new queen?
You mean me?
Don't go making decisions for me!
Congratulations, Filo-chan.
Me too?
Picking up where you left
off this afternoon?
Did you really try to make up with them?
Not this again.
Did you try to clear your name?
Well...
I guess I didn't bother,
thinking they'd never believe me.
If you don't tell them they're wrong,
you're basically admitting your guilt.
Maybe.
I'm going to drop you off close
to another hero when I take you back.
You're coming with us?
I won't involve myself any further.
Show me you four are worthy
of my involvement.
You want me to talk it out
right then and there, right? Got it.
I'll try my best.
Is that all?
No, there's more.
If even one Cardinal Hero is
missing when a Wave hits,
fighting it off will be
exponentially more difficult.
If that looks likely, it's better to
kill you all and summon new heroes.
So if all four of us don't
talk it out and reconcile,
you'll kill us anyway, huh?
I can't tell you after how
many Waves it will happen,
but there will come a time when the
world demands sacrifices from all life.
The world will demand sacrifices?
The heroes will be forced to choose
what they fight for in that battle.
I'm waiting for that time to come.
Choose what we fight for?
Will you fight for the world,
or will you fight for its people?
If you choose the world,
many lives will be lost.
But you'll be able to fulfill your duty.
And what if we choose the people?
It'll be a thorny path.
How much do you know?
There is a lot I have forgotten,
but there is one thing I remember.
Saving the world isn't the
same as saving its people.
Past heroes wished for their
successors to save the people.
Not that I get it, but it makes sense for
heroes of the people to choose them.
You can't do it as you are now.
You can't overcome all
those hurdles by yourself.
Why are you telling me all this?
Wouldn't it be easier to
convince another hero?
I rate you higher than the other heroes.
Why?
You raised Filo, the next queen.
You couldn't possibly be a bad guy.
I am a bad guy.
If you say so.
I believe you have it in you
to talk it out with the other heroes.
Besides, you four heroes are far too weak.
Even if I don't kill you personally,
you'll die sooner rather than later.
Are the upcoming battles
going to be that rough?
Then I'll need the Rage Shield
more than ever.
If you absolutely must use that shield...
What's happening?
Barbarian Armor +1
That will slow down the
Curse Shield's corrosion.
But it won't completely stop it,
so try to avoid using it as much as you can.
After all that talk about killing me?
I guess you're just really nice, Fitoria.
You're really nice,
Fitoria.
Well, given you're doing all this for me,
I guess I'll give it my best shot.
But don't get your hopes up.
Could you get off?
Please, Shield Hero.
Hey, was it the Shield Hero who raised you?
I forgot.
Filolials have short memories.
I see.
But I remember this gentle touch.
This is the place.
Here's where the Four Cardinal Weapons'...
Yes. There's no doubt about it.
Hey, what's the meaning of this?
It's empty!
It can't be.
Everyone, run away!
A Conspiracy Linked