After all, Shiina Mashiro is...
A master painter...
Sorata.
Huh?
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?!
My shower scenes lack
sexiness, apparently.
Ayano told me so.
Oh, you're talking about your manga...
Hey! No, not the face!
Not bad as a love scene.
Do I really look that sexy right now?!
I think I get it now.
Huh?! What?! Get what?!
Wait, wait. Where are you going?! Where?!
To my room to continue drawing.
You're leaving the shower like that?
The deadline for the New
Artist Award isn't far off.
Can't you at least
respond to what I said?!
Oh, forget it...
Go back to your room
and work on your manu—
Man... Manicotti?
Never mind. Forget I said anything.
You're weird, Sorata.
Who's the one that needs to work hard?
#03 So Close And Yet So Far...
I've told you several times already.
It's impossible for Kamiigusa
Misaki to work in a group.
She's the type to suddenly
draw up storyboards...
in her head and start animating.
And another thing:
I'm not Misaki's manager,
so please don't send me work for her.
Goodbye.
Hey, that's some expression
you've got. Constipated?
Don't worry.
You'd think I was voiding
something critical,
considering how smooth my
daily bowel movements are.
I see.
You'd be in serious trouble if you
were expelling love or dreams.
That phone call...
That was a producer
from an anime studio.
Said they want to give Misaki a
better script for her next project.
What? But...
In other words, my scripts
don't measure up to her talents.
It's not as if they need to
tell me that, though.
So, Sorata, what about you?
Oh, um...
Well...
Why don't you have a seat?
Shiina's amazing, isn't she?
I see...
You're bothered by the fact
that the girl you thought...
couldn't do a thing without you is actually...
a world-renowned master painter.
Well...
I'm...
the only one who
doesn't have anything...
in all of Sakura Hall.
Shiina has her manga.
Misaki-senpai has her anime,
and you have your scripts...
Even Akasaka works as a programmer.
You have received a
message from Company S.
You have received a message.
I guess you could call them goals,
or maybe just what you want to do...
The only one in Sakura Hall, huh?
Who cares?
Sorata, you're moving out
of Sakura Hall, aren't you?
Is that "Escape from
Sakura Hall!" banner...
you hung in your room a joke?
Goal: Escape from Sakura Hall!!
Of course it's serious!
I'm gonna return to the
regular dorms for sure.
When?
As soon as I find an
owner for the cats.
Are you looking for anyone?
You haven't really been
looking lately, have you?
Right now, I've got my hands
full taking care of Shiina—
If you're going to leave,
I'll take this off your hands.
Mashiro Duty
Is there still something
holding you back?
Sorata, don't place the
blame on someone else.
If you want to leave,
I'll take care of
Mashiro-chan and the cats.
I'm not kidding.
Sorata, start by deciding...
where you want to be.
If you can do that,
you'll be able to decide
what you want to do, too.
I'm tired of listening to you
pretending you're leaving.
I will leave!
I'll find someone to take the cats!
You're still just a kid if
you take your anger out...
on kouhai who are down in the dumps.
You're right.
You'd better follow up on that.
Game Design Audition
Your big chance to turn
your idea into a game!
Our panel of judges includes prominent figures
from the game industry and designers
from major game companies!
Kanda Sorata: Akasaka, do you have a minute?
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Sure, I just
finished checking my motion control engine.
Kanda Sorata: There's something
I want to ask you.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: About making games?
How did you know that?!
Kanda Sorata: How did you know that?!
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Because you're in the
middle of reading a website about making games.
"Because you're in the middle of reading...
a website about making games"?!
Why don't you start by telling
me how someone holed up...
in the next room can
possibly know that?!
Kanda Sorata: Why don't you start by telling me how
someone holed up in the next room can possibly know that?!
Akasaka Ryunosuke: What answer is there, other than hacking?
"What answer is there, other than hacking?"
That's nothing to brag about!
Kanda Sorata: That's nothing to brag about!
Akasaka Ryunosuke: I'mma hacking (lol)
That's even worse!
Kanda Sorata: That's even worse!
Akasaka Ryunosuke: So, what do you want to know?
"What do I need to do to
become a game creator?"
"Actually,"
Kanda Sorata: Actually, never mind.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: I see. I'm logging off then.
Ryunosuke-sama has logged out.
Looking for Owners
Please contact Kanda Sorata in Class 2-1 for details.
You're looking for owners, huh?
So, you've finally decided to move out.
What do you mean, "finally"?
Give me some. I'll go
put them up over there.
Oh, it's fine.
I want to help you.
Did something good happen to Aoyama?
Must have.
I'll go ask the Swimming
Club if they want some cats.
Oh, thanks.
Well, then...
Kanda-kun.
Are you finished already?
I found someone who wants
to take the cats, but...
Don't tell me...
I'll be the cats' owner.
You're the one who needs an owner!
K-Kanda-kun, what do you mean by "owner"?
I mean Shiina needs someone
to take care of her...
because she's not used to attending
a Japanese high school yet!
Then, Sorata...
Wh-What now?
Go out with me.
What?!
H-How can you confess your
feelings to him so easily?
There's somewhere I want
to go this Sunday.
O-Oh, that's what you meant...
W-Wait, a date?
I'm busy looking for an owner.
Ask Jin-san.
Okay.
H-Hey, Kanda-kun, are you sure about that?
Nothing to be sure about.
It's got nothing to do with me.
Emergency! Emergency!
It's an emergency!
Come on, kouhai-kun, get changed!
M-My underwear! Something's going to pop out!
I don't mind!
I mind a lot!
You pervert.
Whose fault is this?!
What's all this ruckus on a Sunday?
Mashiron and Jin are going on a date!
Who cares if they go on a date?
They said they're going
to a love hotel!
A l-love hotel?!
A hotel for couples?! A love hotel?!
Yes! One of those love hotels!
Don't you care if
Mashiron cheats on you?
Well...
I'm sure they just went to
get material for her manga.
Why are you guys making such a big fuss?
Do you really believe that
playboy Jin-san would go...
all the way to a love
hotel and not try anything?
Well, it's pretty certain
Mitaka will do something.
I know, right? It's as certain as...
the bullet train's arrival schedule!
Kouhai-kun, get dressed and
meet me at the front door!
I'll be there in 60 seconds!
Make it 30!
Roger!
I wonder if we'll be celebrating tonight.
Keep the change!
Wait up, Senpai!
You're too slow, kouhai-kun!
Disengage your limiter!
Take the weights off your arms!
What am I training for?
I'm going as fast as I can...
I still have three more
stages of transformation!
This is why earthlings are no good!
So, you really are an alien.
Let's go!
Senpai, wait.
They're nearby, so let's be careful.
Shiina Mashiro
Leave the stalking to me.
Kouhai-kun, where are they?
10 meters to Mashiro-sama.
10 meters to Mashiro-sama!
Locked on!
There they are!
Kouhai-kun, is this how they're
getting their material?
It looks like a date.
Kouhai-kun, that's because
you're not paying attention,
you weakling!
You weakling!
Why did you say that twice?!
Kouhai-kun, I can't take any more!
Stop that. You're going
to make me hurl...
But! But! I can't help myself!
My overwhelming feelings
are about to bubble over!
What are we going to
do if they notice us?
We'll pretend we just
happened to run into them!
That's not much of a plan!
Senpai!
What are you doing, Kanda-kun?
A-Aoyama, what are you...
I work here on Sundays,
after going to training school.
Really? As amazing as always.
That's it, Nanamin!
You look wonderful in your uniform!
Come on, let's hide together!
What are you doing, Kamiigusa-senpai?
K-Kanda-kun, you're getting too close.
Which one would you like?
This one is cuter.
I agree.
You're going to keep it?
I hope you're joking.
It's a birthday present.
For who?
Someone close, and yet so far...
Excuse me, one of these, please.
They're coming out.
They bought something, didn't they?
Oh, that reminds me.
I need to get back to work.
H-Hey.
My break's over soon.
Oh, okay. Work hard.
I'd work hard even if
you didn't tell me to.
You're right.
Misaki-senpai?
Kouhai-kun...
My chest hurts.
Is it contagious?
I feel a little...
I don't have to be the one
who looks after Shiina...
Do you think pretty,
quiet girls are Jin-san's type?
I think so.
That's what Fuuka-chan,
the first girl he dated, was like.
You've been stalking him
since the beginning?
I would have known even if I hadn't.
Why am I never the
one standing next to Jin?
They really came here.
Are they seriously going inside?
Senpai, we have to stop them!
I've had enough.
I'm going home.
Senpai!
What the hell are you doing?!
Oh, sorry.
You're awake?
Hey, Shiina...
What?
Am I lying on your lap?
Yes, you are.
That hurt.
Say that like it hurts!
It didn't hurt.
Then, don't say it does!
Don't just let people lie in your lap!
What were you thinking?
I was thinking about the world.
That's a lot to think about!
Oh, yeah! Where's Jin-san?
He left.
What did you say?
He told me it was just like he planned,
and that you'd take care of me now.
What? Just like he planned?
Did he know we were stalking you?
What are you doing?!
I'm going to take a bath.
Wait, wait.
Do you understand our situation?
We're a man and a woman
in a love hotel room!
I know.
We'll stay here tonight.
Why, you!
You don't understand at all, do you?
Listen, Shiina...
You need to think a little
more before you act.
What are you going to
do if you come here...
with a guy and something happens?
There's no point.
What?
Even if I think more, I only
came here for reference.
You...
This is necessary to be able to draw.
That's why I came here.
What about you?
Sorata, why are you here?
Why am I...
You said you were busy.
Did you find someone to take the cats?
No.
Then, why?
You're the one who doesn't understand.
Goodbye.
What kind of life have you
been living up to now?
I drew pictures.
What am I doing?
Sorry about that.
I meant to let you get a punch in,
but my reflexes didn't let me.
Jin-san, where are you right now?
Office Lady Rumi-san's place.
Please go back to Sakura Hall today.
Okay, stop!
I can't see Misaki-senpai
like this anymore.
You had to go and say it.
What's can't it be Misaki-senpai?
I can't go home today.
Why not?
When I see her looking all depressed,
I want to do her like crazy.
What? What did you just say?
Anyway, enough about me.
How's Mashiro-chan doing?
Shiina's sleeping.
In your arms?
She's sleeping in the bed by herself.
What about you?
I'm sandwiched between the
shoe rack and the wall.
What are you doing? Did you guys fight?
It wasn't even a fight.
I took an instant kill combo,
and it was over.
I didn't understand anything.
Shiina's crazy, and none
of my common sense...
got through to her.
But Shiina didn't care
about any of that.
Drawing pictures...
and now, drawing manga
are everything to her.
I guess you could say she
has no uncertainties...
In any case, she's amazing.
Mashiro-chan told me today that...
she came to Japan to
become a manga artist.
When I told her that
was a waste, considering...
the praise her talents had
earned her as a painter,
she said she didn't care about that.
She's unbelievable.
You got that right.
But, thanks to Shiina,
my eyes are finally open.
I'll decide for myself
where I want to be.
I'll throw you one hell
of a farewell party.
I look forward to it.
Shiina.
Sorry about yesterday.
I really was the one
who didn't understand.
Next time you ask me,
I promise I'll go out with you, so...
Good luck with the New Artist Award.
Hey, Sorata...
What?
You're leaving Sakura Hall, aren't you?
Huh? What color are my panties?
#04   A World of Changing Colors
You pervert! How dare you
ask me something so dirty?!
Don't try to imagine them either!