Where... am I?
Are you the one who was calling me?
Dammit... Not at a time like this!
That's right.
That was the day when I...
You...!
Don't call me that.
Avrora Florestina.
That is our name.
Avrora...?
Nine months ago, on my way back from visiting Nagisa in the hospital...
I met her.
The Twelfth Kaleid Blood.
Avrora.
Kojou!
And then that happened.
The event that caused me to awaken as the Fourth Primogenitor, and lose Avrora.
The Scorched Banquet.
Senpai! Get a hold of yourself!
Senpai!
What the hell is going on!?
It's fast! A therianthrope?
It got ahead of us!
Run!
You've got to be kidding me!
Just shut up and run!
What... the heck is this!?
Mogwai, what's going on!?
It's exactly as it appears.
Demons all over Itogami Island collapsed all of a sudden,
some monsters appeared, which are going wild after sucking their magical energy.
Shit! How did this happen!?
Don't tell me...
The demon registration bracelets!?
A time-delayed virus has been inserted into the elementary magic circuit used for monitoring.
You mean when the Island Guard got hacked yesterday!?
They got us good.
The criminals weren't after the servers at headquarters, it was this!
Can't you do something about it?
That would be difficult.
They've been cut off from the Island Guard network as well...
And I have no physical means to apply a vaccine!
Not quite. You have a way, don't you, Missy?
A way to forcefully gain access to a demon registration bracelet that has been cut off from the network.
Oh, I see! It's "C"!
Get down!
So that's why they're after you, Asagi!
What do you mean?
You're the only one who can stop this!
Let's go to the Keystone Gate!
What!?
If you want to complain, I'll listen to you later!
We've got to hurry... or Itogami Island might not exist after today!
Wait!
Oh, give me a break!
Senpai!
What's with the pathetic voice, Himeragi?
Senpai! Thank goodness.
You were unconscious for close to an hour.
One hour... only that long?
I had a really long dream.
No... Avrora. That wasn't a dream, was it?
Senpai?
So you finally woke up, huh?
Mogwai!
You don't have the time to be lazing around.
Take a look at the city.
What the heck is this!?
Did Tartaros Lapus do this?
Yeah. They used a virus to hack into the demon registration bracelets and are gathering magical energy.
Magical energy!? Why would they do that?
Look above you.
A rose?
No, that is a magic circle.
It's so dense that I can scarcely believe it.
So this is the true form of Tartaros' Rose.
Asagi is currently on her way to the Keystone Gate to stop this.
Can you keep Itogami Island from falling to pieces in the meanwhile, Mister?
Falling to pieces?
Senpai!
I won't let you do as you please!
Come out, Regulus-Aurum!
They resurrected!?
The summoning magic from that Rose is still in effect!
In that case... Come out! Al-Meissa Mercury!
Thanks Himeragi! You saved me!
I only did my job as your Observer.
But at this rate...!
I know. The situation will only get worse.
Dammit... What should I do!?
Der Freischutz!?
A magical bullet multi-lock on! This technique is... Don't tell me!
Kojou-kun! Yuki!
Yuiri-san, Shio-san, and Kirasaka!
Grenda, you came too!?
Da!
I see.
So we just have to find the magician who is controlling that magic circle, right?
Can you do that?
For a War Dancer, it's the most basic thing.
Boundary!
Authenticate! Freikugel Plus Proto III, unlock!
Rosenkavalier Plus! Boot up!
Kojou-kun, leave this to us and get some rest.
But...
Senpai. I need to talk to you about something.
What's wrong, Himeragi? Why did you bring me all the way here?
It's okay, Senpai.
Umm...
Himeragi?
I'm telling you that it's okay to suck my blood!
Don't make me say it!
Eh!? But why, all of a sudden!?
December-san's ability...
It seals your power to control Familiars.
If I'm not wrong, then increasing your vampiric power
will allow you to keep ownership of them.
Or maybe...
You don't want it to be me?
No, it's not that...
I can't do that in this sort of situation...
I understand.
In that case, Senpai, close your eyes.
Hmm? Sure...
Himeragi... Is this your...?
Don't worry about it!
My handkerchief wasn't long enough.
So it's not your handkerchief?
It smells kind of nice, though...
Smells like soap...
Stop smelling it!
I don't need your comments!
H-Himeragi...
How... is it?
How should I say this...
I want to keep doing this forever.
No! It tickles!
S-Senpai!?
Not there...!
Himeragi...
You musn't...! No!
No, Senpai! Don't stop!
You need to drink more.
I can't do that, Himeragi.
Your body can't take any more of this.
But you might not be able to beat December-san the way you are now.
Himeragi...
Da?
You can't, Grenda!
Yuiri-san?
It's not what you think, Yuki!
Grenda was tired, so I wanted to let her rest...
I wasn't peeking or anything!
K-Kojou-kun...?
Grenda!
Senpai. This is an emergency, so I'll allow it, just this once.
Just this once, you hear?
Yuki... what do mean, "allow"?
Umm... Wait...
I'm not against it, but...
This is my first time...
Bear with it for a little while.
No way!
Yuki, don't look!
Koukarin!
Kirasaka! How many shots do you have left?
Including my spares, six! How about you?
The same.
At this rate, we won't last more than three or four minutes!
Hikawa Shio!
Al-Nasl-Minium!
Are you okay?
Akatsuki Kojou!
Sayaka-san!
Sorry we're late, Kirasaka-san!
Haba Yuiri... and Yukina, too!
Your faces are red, are you two okay?
Wait...
Akatsuki Kojou! Don't tell me, you did it again!?
The Four Heavenly Beasts!?
The mythical beasts said to govern over the four cardinal directions of heaven...
The symbols of power in Feng Shui...
Don't tell me... He used the structure of Itogami Island itself,
which was built to correspond to the four gods!?
So this is what Tartaros Lapus were really after!
I've found the magician!
Direction, three o'clock, distance 6200 meters!
6200? Wouldn't that be on top of the ocean?
Itogami Island's abandoned District 27.
The former site of an early man-made island,
It was sunk only nine months ago.
I see.
If she's going to appear again one last time, that's the only place, huh?
Are you ready, Hikawa Shio?
What about you?
We'll buy you some time. Make it count!
Let's go, Senpai!
Yeah!
Grenda, are you ready?
Da!
Dammit, the Keystone Gate is right in front of our noses!
There aren't any places left to hide and move anymore!
Need some help, Carly?
It's fine. I have them cornered.
It's all or nothing.
I'll be the decoy.
Run to the Keystone Gate as fast as you can!
But...!
We don't have the time to hesitate!
Mogwai, I'll leave you to guide Asagi!
Leave it to me!
I'm starting the countdown.
Three... Two... One... Zero!
Oh no, you don't!
An Air Elemental!?
No, a Wraith!?
Something like that... If I destroy the clone, even the
technique user should receive damage!
And now...!
I'm not done yet!
Sorry... December...
I... In a place like this...
Dammit, I guess I tried too hard.
The rest is in your hands, Kojou...
Carly! What's wrong, Carly!?
You're not going anywhere.
Resistance is futile.
Answer me.
Where is Senga Takehito?
Program.
Tartaros Rose's network infiltration dropped to 77%.
Demon registration bracelets... Signal lost from 4800 units.
Even you can't stop her?
Aiba Asagi really is something else.
Ran, that's enough. Run away.
I can handle the rest on my own.
I'm sorry, I can't run away.
I don't... want to... go away.
Ran...
Stop it, Ran!
She's a monster who has control over this entire man-made island!
These are the memories of "C"... So pretty...
I...
Don't go, Ran!
Sorry, Ran... I love you.
Carly... Rogi... Everyone...
Ran's brain has been embedded with refined neurons,
sixteen times more than a normal person would have.
Of course, such a thing is impossible for a live human being.
So she was given a dead body, one that
moved using the power of necromancy.
Is there anything wrong with a girl like that wanting to
destroy the Demon District, the place where she was born?
What do you think?
Akatsuki Kojou.
Maybe those kids have a valid reason for being angry.
Maybe Senga was right, and this island might
cause a large number of people to be sacrificed.
But just as you guys want to destroy Itogami Island...
I, too, want to protect the people who live here!
So I'm going to stop all of you! Tartaros Lapus!
From now on, this is my fight!
I refuse to accept that kind of logic!
No, Senpai.
This is our fight!
W-We're here too, okay? For what it's worth.
Da!
It's over,December!
Not yet, Akatsuki Kojou.
Appear swiftly! Dabih-Crystallus!
One of the Fourth Primogenitor's familiars, huh?
I was right after all.
We should have realized earlier.
December... was the tenth month of the ancient Roman calender.
The Tenth Kaleid Blood...
You're a seal for the Fourth Primogenitor's power,
just like Avrora was. Right, December!?
Don't tell me... Did you remember, Akatsuki Kojou?
Yeah.
The Scorched Banquet that happened nine months ago.
And Avrora... I remember her too.
You... weren't involved in that, right?
I was the Third Primogenitor's captive back then.
The Third...
You mean Chaos Bride!?
It seems she's very interested in you as well.
I was only released because I told her that I wanted to go to Itogami Island.
You... Your body...!
We, the Numbered, are literally the Fourth Primogenitor's seals.
Once the seal is undone, we have no option but to disappear.
The Tenth Familiar that was sealed within me, which is basically my own self.
Dabih-Crystallus is a being that governs over the vampiric ability to charm.
So we can even do things like this!
Even if the Rose falls, the Four Heavenly Beasts that were summoned will remain!
The power to destroy Itogami Island, which was summoned by my friends!
Dammit, come out! Natra-Cinereus!
Rozenkavalier Plus!
Come out, Al-Nasl-Minium!
Al-Meissa-Mercury!
I, Akatsuki Kojou, successor to the blood of "Kaleid Blood",
now release your constraints.
I, Sword Shaman of the High God and priestess of the Lion, beseech thee.
Dawn light of exorcism, spirit wolf of snowy mist, grant me the divine might of thy steel,
that I may smite a hundred evil spirits!
Come out, Fifth Familiar.
Regulus-Aurum!
It's your win, Kojou.
December!
I have one last request.
Take Ran... Carly, and Rogi to a proper research facility.
The way they are now, they won't live for much longer.
I understand.
Thank you, Akatsuki Kojou.
I'll give you the power of the Tenth Familiar.
Wait, December! I...!
Don't look so sad.
It's fine. I will always be at your side.
Protect the Twelfth, Avrora.
That child is your hope.
So you disappeared, December.
Worry not. I will take care of this island-
You want to destroy the keystone and cause the island to collapse?
I won't let you do that, Senga Takehito.
Why the hell are you still alive, Yaze Akishige!?
Hyper Adapter!?
Sealing off Itogami Island, throwing the Island Administration into chaos...
And now, the Priestess of Cain has entered the casket.
With this, all the preparations have been completed.
You have done well, Tartaros Lapus.
You were using us from the start...!?
You're willing to go so far to slaughter the demons!?
Descendants of the Sinful God....
This can't be real... Don't tell me...
This is "C"? Cain's Coffin?
Mogwai.... You are...!