The World She Saw
The Battle of Trost ( 2 )
Hey.
Hey!
What's wrong, Armin?
Get a grip!
Hey!
Armin!
Hey, Armin!
Hey!
Have you come to?
You okay?
Are you hurt?
Where's your squad?
Squad?
Come on, pull yourself together.
Why're you alone?
And you feel kinda... sticky.
What exactly happened?
Useless dolt!
Just die!
Hey.
Calm down, Armin.
Fucking shithead!
Where's everyone?
Give it up, Connie.
They got wiped out.
Except for him.
Shut up!
Armin hasn't said anything yet!
Can't you tell just by looking around?
We don't have any more time to waste on him.
Why's Armin the only person left in one piece?
Who knows?
Maybe They thought he was a corpse.
It's a pity they ran into a bunch of Eotena,
but why did he have to be the only one to survive?
It just means Eren and the others died in vain.
You bitch.
Want me to shut you up for good?
Stop it, you two!
Everyone's just panicking.
Our friends are all dying so suddenly.
It's only natural!
That's my Krista.
Once this is all over, marry me!
It's true.
She's messing around more than usual.
Anyway, you can't just stay here.
Can you stand, Armin?
Sorry for the trouble I caused.
I'll go join the rear guard.
Hey...
Armin!
Let's go, Connie!
We've been ordered to advance!
This has become Hell.
No, wait.
It hasn't become Hell.
I've just had the wrong perspective this whole time.
This world has always been...
Hell.
A world in which the strong devour the weak.
A world so perfectly simple.
But my friends...
tried to live strong in this world.
They held out a helping hand to a weakling like me.
I couldn't stand that.
To those two...
I'm something that needs protection.
I wanted to live with a strength like theirs.
I wanted to live with them as their equal.
Some good that did.
Because of me, Eren...
Hannah...
What are you doing?
Armin! Help me!
Franz isn't breathing!
I've given him CPR over and over and over again.
But Franz...
Hannah.
This place is dangerous so let's hurry up and get—
We can't just leave Franz here!
But Hannah...
Franz is...
Please stop.
It's pointless...
He can't be saved.
So stop.
Hey, you people!
Don't you have any idea what kind of situation we're in?!
Of course! That's why I'm doing this!
You guys should help too if you want to be saved!
Fuck you!
You're supposed to let the people through first!
They'll eat us all!
Do your damn job, soldier!
Arrest these guys!
But...
Just try it, boy.
I'm the boss of the trade federation in this town.
W-Well...
Who do you think gives you the food you shit out?
Can you get together the kind of money required to feed all the soldiers here?
All of you push too!
This cargo is worth more than you'll make in your whole pathetic lives.
You help me and I'll help you!
Don't worry.
Dad will get all the Eotenas with his cannon.
Mom...
Look.
Push!
Push for your lives!
Dammit.
Why is it ignoring us?
It's an abnormal!
Don't waste time thinking about it!
It's so fast!
We're supposed to be the elite but we still can't keep up!
At this rate...
What do you think you're doing?
Good timing!
You!
Make them help me out!
I'll reward you handsomely!
My comrades are dying as we speak.
The noncombatants haven't evacuated yet,
so they're fighting the Eotenas and dying.
That's only natural!
It's your duty to offer up your hearts to protect us civilians and our wealth!
Don't get all high and mighty just because you parasites have finally emerged from 100 years of uselessness!
If you think it's only natural that people die for others,
then I'm sure you'll understand.
Sometimes, sacrificing one precious life can save many others.
Just you try it!
I've known your boss for a long time.
You're just a grunt. I can tell him to end you!
But how is a corpse going to tell him anything?
Wait!
B-Boss...
Pull the cart out.
Thank you, Ms. Soldier!
You saved our lives.
Thank you so much.
Well done, Ackerman.
I'm impressed.
Thank you, Sir.
However...
I acted far too hastily.
I dulled both my blades in a single attack.
I'll be more careful next time.
Seriously, what happened to make you so—?
Never mind.
Forget I said anything.
Why am I remembering this now, of all times?
Information available for public disclosure
Ultra-hardened Steel ( 1 )
A strong and flexible metal that can cut through Eotena flesh.
The single-edged blades forged from this metal
are widely-known anti-Eotena weapons.
Ultra-hardened Steel ( 1 )
A strong and flexible metal that can cut through Eotena flesh.
The single-edged blades forged from this metal
are widely-known anti-Eotena weapons.
the eotena onslaught
Information available for public disclosure
Ultra-hardened Steel ( 2 )
The blast furnaces in industrial towns are
indispensable to the smelting of ultra-hardened steel,
meaning that it can't be produced anywhere else.
Ultra-hardened Steel ( 2 )
The blast furnaces in industrial towns are
indispensable to the smelting of ultra-hardened steel,
meaning that it can't be produced anywhere else.
the eotena onslaught
Year 844
I did it!
Look, Mom!
Oh my.
Well done, Mikasa.
It's great.
This style of embroidery has been passed
down in our family for generations.
You should teach your kids how to do it too.
So how do I get kids?
Who knows?
Ask Dad.
Hey, Dad?
I-I'm not really sure myself.
But look, Dr. Jaeger should be here soon,
so let's ask him.
Oh, speak of the devil!
Coming!
Mikasa?
That's right.
She's the same age as you.
There aren't any other kids in this area.
So make friends with her, okay?
Depends on her.
Eren...
That attitude is why you've only got one friend.
Maybe they aren't home.
Mr. Ackerman.
It's me, Jaeger.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
Hey...
Dad?
No good.
Eren.
Did you see a girl around?
Did you see Mikasa?
No.
I see.
I'm going to get the Gendarmerie and have them look for her.
You wait for me at the base of the mountain.
Got it?
Eren?
Eren!
Hey.
You really think she'll sell?
We even killed her parents and all.
Take a good look at her face.
Okay, she's fine, but she's just a kid.
Not my thing.
I don't care if she's your thing.
She's Oriental.
In the past, there were different types of humans.
She's the descendent of people who fled into the Walls from a place called the Orient.
We'll auction her off to some pervert at the underground market in the capital.
The other Orientals have died out.
She'll fetch us quite the price.
Her father didn't look Oriental, though.
She's not a pure-blood.
That's right!
Her mother was the one who was really worth something!
Why'djya have to freak out and kill her?
I-I didn't have a choice!
She resisted!
That's your excuse?!
Dr. Jaeger. We've been expecting—
Pardon the intrusion.
Take it easy.
Unless ya want me to split your head open with this.
Bitch!
Run, Mikasa!
Mom?
Hurry up, Mikasa!
Er...
Dad?
Knock it off!
The fuck are you doing?!
I told you to only kill the father!
But she...
No fucking excuses!
Grab the kid.
Don't make this any harder, kid.
Or else...
this is what ya get!
I'm cold.
Excuse me.
You brat!
How'd you find this place?!
Er... um...
I got lost in the forest...
and um...
I saw this cabin...
Now that's no good.
You're just a kid. Don't come into the forest alone.
There are scaaary wolves in here, you know?
But don't worry.
You can come with us—
Thanks, Mister.
I get it now.
So die, you filthy fuck!
No way!
Where d'ya think you're going, you little shit?!
You fucking animal!
Die!
Just die!
This is what you...
This is what you deserve!
Don't you dare stand up again!
It's all right now.
Don't worry.
You're Mikasa, right?
I'm Eren,
Dr. Jaeger's son.
I think you've met my father before.
He was visiting your place for a checkup, so I came with him.
That's when we found...
There were three.
Didjya do this?
Did you do this?!
You?!
I'll kill ya!
Yer fuckin' dead!
Fight!
You gotta fight!
Lose, and you die.
Win, and you survive.
What the fuck are you thinkin', you little shit?!
If you don't fight...
you can't win!
I...
I can't do it!
That's when I remembered.
I've seen this scene play out
many, many,
many times before.
It was always right in front of me.
But...
I pretended not to see it.
That's right.
This world...
is crammed with cruelty.
And with that realization, my trembling ceased.
I've had perfect control over myself ever since.
I thought I could do anything.
Fight.
Fight!
One stab wound from the back and through the heart.
Those kids did this?
Eren.
I told you to wait for me at the base of the mountain, didn't I?
Do you have any idea what you've done?!
I put down some dangerous beasts.
They were just animals in human clothing!
Eren!
Look how long the Gendarmerie took to arrive.
They'd've gotten away ages ago!
You wouldn't've made it in time!
Even if that were true,
you were just lucky, Eren!
I'm criticizing you for not considering your own safety!
But...
I wanted to save her as soon as I could.
Mikasa.
Do you remember me?
I met you many times when you were a child.
Dr. Jaeger...
Where do I go from here?
I'm cold...
I don't...
have a home anymore.
You can have this.
It's warm, isn't it?
It's warm.
Mikasa.
You can make your home with us.
You've experienced too much pain.
You need to rest.
What?
Come on,
let's go home.
To our home.
Okay.
Let's go home.
A place where only the victor survives.
A world of cruelty.
Time to retreat, Ackerman.
We're going over the walls.
I'll go assist the vanguard's retreat.
Hey, Ackerman!
But in this world, I have found a home.
Eren, as long as you're with me,
I can do anything!
The dream where your heart seeks comfort
Is more fragile than your life
You can abandon it, yet always find it again
Now, sleep in peace
My pulsing rage
Defiles the wishes I harbor
Before I forget them
Only to remember once more
In this beautiful and cruel world
We keep on asking ourselves
Why it was we who survived
What will we protect
With our strength and with our weakness
If reason and logic no longer hold sway
Preview
"In this world, I have found a home."
After completing her mission with the rear guard,
Mikasa hurries to meet Eren.
But the only thing awaiting her is the news of Eren's death.
A Small Blade
The Battle of Trost ( 3 )