The Recon Corps left to find a route to Shiganshina,
but instead they encountered a cunning female-form Titan.
As soldiers died one after another,
the column headed into a nearby forest of giant trees,
though none of the troops knew the reason.
If the Levi Squad doesn't stop it, who else will?
Another fatality!
We might've been able to save him!
Decide.
Will you trust only in your own strength?
Or will you put your faith in the Recon Corps, including myself?
I'll keep going!
Fire!
Could it be...
They're going to capture it alive?
See that Eren? Did you?
We captured that Titan!
This is the strength of the Recon Corps!
Don't underestimate us, stupid!
Now do you get it?
Yes, sir!
Looks like we've immobilized it.
We can't let down our guard just yet,
but good work luring it to this location.
We only managed to buy enough time thanks to the rear guard sacrificing themselves.
This wouldn't have been possible without them.
Is that so?
It is.
Thanks to them, we can meet the person inside this thing.
I hope they haven't pissed themselves...
O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
This is a victory for us!
Jetzt, hier ist ein Sieg
Our fame starts here!
Dies ist der erste Gloria
O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
Let us celebrate this victory for the next battle!
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf
"I died for naught" — I won't let it end like that for you
「無意味な死であった」と...言わせない
until I am the last one standing
最後のひとりになるまで...
The enemy is cruel... We will kill—
Der Feind ist grausam... Wir bringen...
The enemy is colossal... We will jump—
Der Feind ist riesig... Wir springen...
In our hands we hold blades of glory
両手には  Gloria
and sing in the name of victory
唄うのは  Sieg
We bear the wings of freedom on our backs
背中には  Flügel der Freiheit
Swearing iron determination upon our hearts,
握り締めた決意を左胸に
we slash apart the circle of idiocy
斬り裂くのは  Ringe der Torheit
and soar through the sky
蒼穹を舞う
with our wings of freedom
Flügel der Freiheit
Erwin Smith
57th Expedition Beyond the Walls (pt 4)
Is it an abnormal?
Or is it like the Colossal Titan?
Did Commander Erwin...
Hey, snap out of it!
Eren, you'll have time to think later.
We need to ride deeper in and stand by!
Right!
Wait, Levi...
An eye for an eye.
Artillery 2 and 3, fire!
Fire all you've got left!
Um, it's climbing up...
So it is.
If it gets this far, I'll be sure to get clear.
But I don't think it'll be too long
before withdrawal orders are issued.
Does that have anything to do with the explosions
we keep hearing from the depths of the forest?
Who knows?
Mikasa, what do you think that sound is?
Are they firing cannons in the forest?
I don't recall them carrying in any cannons, though.
It's really loud back there.
Hey, Bertolt.
Do you know where Krista went?
Sorry, I don't know.
I have no clue what's going on.
What are we doing and why?
I wanna go home.
We're changing positions, Armin.
Okay.
This guy's starting to figure it out.
It seems like they keep getting better at climbing.
It just shows they're capable of learning. Alarmingly so.
Some are better than others, I'm sure.
Armin.
It sounds like something's happening out in the forest,
and I think I've got a good idea what it is.
They lured that female-form Titan all the way out here in order to capture it.
Well, more precisely...
To capture the person inside of it.
That was Commander Erwin's goal...
So that was his plan from the start!
That's it, right?
I can see why he kept it a secret from us new recruits,
but why wouldn't he tell you,
when you've all been with the Recon Corps for so long?
Shut up!
Are you implying the Commander and the Captain don't trust us?
But that's exactly what this means...
Petra, rip out his teeth,
then swap the incisors with the molars and shove 'em back in!
No, Eren's right on the mark..
I think the Commander kept this from us for a reason.
Like what?
There's only one reason he wouldn't trust his fellow soldiers.
A person who can become a Titan,
or a spy working for such people, has infiltrated our ranks.
You think so too, right?
It has to be one of us.
I agree.
A spy?
You really think so?
At any rate, the Commander has suspicions of his own.
I'd imagine the only soldiers who knew of the plan were those
who survived with him from five years ago.
I see...
So that's it.
No doubt.
Understand, Eren?
That's how it is.
If that's the case, it does make sense.
He's assuming that five years ago, when the first Wall fell,
a spy managed to slip in amongst us.
And he narrowed down the possibilities from there.
Then, this spy killed Sawney and Bean?
Back then, the Commander asked me about that.
What do you see?
Where do you think the enemy is?
That question was referring to this?
If we could've answered him then,
maybe we could've been there for him.
I doubt that anyone could've known back then, though.
I knew.
But I didn't say anything.
Do you know why?
Why?
What, can't you tell?
Well, I guess I shouldn't expect much from the likes of you.
You have yet to reach my level.
Hey, are you trying to imitate Captain Levi again?
The Captain would never say anything as dumb as that.
If we succeed, I'll be that much closer to the truth of this world.
Even still... Regardless of our cause, too many people have died.
Do you think the Commander was wrong?
I can't say he was right.
If we'd known there was a Titan skulking around in our ranks,
we could've handled it differently.
Your squad leader and the others could've had that chance too.
No, it wasn't wrong.
What wasn't wrong about it?
How many do you think died for no reason?
Jean, it's easy look back in hindsight and say, "We should've done something else."
However,
no one knows how things will turn out.
And yet you still have to make a choice.
It's unavoidable.
The lives of a hundred fellow soldiers...
Or the lives of everyone within the Walls...
The Commander made his choice.
He chose to sacrifice those hundred.
Eren, you don't know yet,
but soon you'll realize it.
The reason that Erwin Smith is entrusted with humanity's hope,
the Recon Corps.
Just look at how much trust Captain Levi puts in him!
That's assuming you live long enough to figure it out.
I haven't lived that long,
but I'm certain of one thing.
If there's anyone who can bring about change,
it will be someone willing to sacrifice everything they care for.
It will be someone who can set aside
even their humanity, in order to defeat the monsters.
A person who cannot sacrifice everything
won't be able to change anything!
Currently Disclosable Information
Special Target Capture Weapon (pt 1)
A newly developed weapon the Survey Corps
created to capture a specific Titan.
Currently Disclosable Information
Special Target Capture Weapon (pt 2)
The barrels are loaded with seven steel tubes,
each of which has coiled wires with arrowheads
at both ends.
Fire!
How do you like that?
You can't even scratch an itch now.
You won't be able to make a single move... Probably forever.
They're designed so that the more you regenerate your injuries,
the more immobilized your joints become!
Even still, they can't extract whoever's inside?
What are Levi and Mike doing?
It can selectively harden its skin to protect specific parts of its body?
That ability sounds rather similar to that of the Armored Titan.
If we continue attacking with 3D Maneuver Gear and blades, will it weaken?
We don't have the time to find out.
In that case...
Yes, sir?
Prepare the explosives.
We'll blow off its hands.
Yes, sir...
However. it's possible that the amount of firepower we're carrying
could vaporize what's inside as well.
In that case, set the charges to amputate the wrist.
Set them all off together on my signal.
Roger.
Hey...
Why not just come out?
We don't have time to waste.
So...
What do you think will happen to you now?
Do you believe you can escape?
I wish you'd consider all the trouble we're going through...
As I recall, you killed my troops in many creative ways.
Did you enjoy yourself?
Right now, I'm enjoying myself.
Well, you felt the same, right?
I think you of all people should understand me.
Oh, right...
I wanted to ask you something.
Is it okay if we cut off your hands and legs?
They'll grow back, right?
I'm talking about your limbs, not the Titan's.
We need you alive, after all...
Well, that was a surprise.
Were those her dying screams?
Erwin, it stinks.
What direction?
Multiple sources, from all directions at once.
What's up with them?
They're all running into the forest?
Why are they suddenly ignoring us?
What?
They're all abnormals?!
It doesn't matter! Don't let them through!
Engage them!
What just happened?
Wait...
I've heard that scream before.
In the forests where I'm from...
It's the cry of a cornered animal with nothing to lose!
I was taught to exercise the greatest caution when a hunt was drawing to a close!
So be careful?
A hundred times more careful than usual!
If you underestimate the forest, you'll die!
I grew up in the mountains too.
Just growing up tending crops doesn't mean you understand!
I see.
It's true that Sasha's intuition is usually good.
Particularly when it involves any kind of danger.
Armin thought Eren would be in the center, toward the rear...
Ready those explosives now!
Erwin...
The first wave will come from the east.
They're almost here.
Wagon escort team, intercept!
They ignored us?
Are they abnormals?
Three have broken through!
Captain Levi!
You just pulled something, didn't you, bitch?
So they're all after the female-form Titan?
Titans from all directions!
All men, engage.
Defend the female-form Titan, even if it costs you your lives!
It's no use!
Retreat, men!
Fall back into formation!
Return to Karanes!
We've been had.
Just look at you.
Don't tell me...
Our enemies...
...are prepared to sacrifice everything.
I never expected the enemy to destroy itself along with the evidence
by inciting other Titans to devour its flesh.
After all our big talk at the court martial, this is what happens.
If we return empty-handed, who knows
what will happen to Eren, or to us.
We can think about that after we make it back.
For now, our priority is getting home without any additional casualties.
For now...
The steam from its corpse is limiting visibility.
It might interfere with our signal flare message relay system.
I'll call my team.
Wait, Levi...
Refill your gas and blades.
There's no time.
I should have enough.
Why?
That's an order.
Follow it.
Roger, Erwin.
I trust your judgment.
We're retreating.
Everyone, fall back.
Mount your horses and retreat.
Right!
What? It's over already?
We can go home! All right!
What's going on?
Where's Eren?
Looks like it's over.
Back to the horses! Prepare to retreat!
You heard the man.
Let's go see what the bastard inside that thing looks like.
Will we really find out who it is?
All thanks to you.
I didn't really do anything.
You had faith in us.
This is the result of your choice to believe in us back then.
Making the right choice isn't easy.
Hey, don't pamper him, Petra...
What did he even do, anyway?
He was pathetic. He just kept whining.
Well, coming back alive from your first excursion is a pretty good start.
But it doesn't count until the mission's over.
Listen up, kiddo! The expedition lasts until you're at home in bed...
Jeez, I know that!
Auruo! Petra!
You guys pissed your pants and cried on your first mission.
You're all grown up now!
Don't say that!
What if he stops respecting me, Erd?!
It really happened?
Sure did.
And for the record, I didn't, Eren.
Idiot!
I've killed more of them than you!
I've got more kills, stupid!
Your kill count isn't what makes a soldier.
Shut up, idiot!
Petra...
Does that mean you sprayed it everywhere in mid-air?
Shut up!
Do you think you're on a picnic?
We're outside the Walls!
I didn't piss my pants either, Eren.
Oh, that must be the signal from Captain Levi.
We'll rendezvous with the Captain!
Cut the chatter until we get back.
Erwin...
Why did you order Levi to resupply?
There's no time to waste.
The female-form Titan was eaten.
But did you see the person inside get eaten?
I didn't.
You can't mean—
Yes...
If your original hypothesis was correct,
they can still move to a degree after regaining human form.
If they'd prepared 3D Maneuver Gear in advance...
The person inside the female-form Titan is wearing our uniform right now.
Captain Levi?
No, it's not!
Who are you?!
G-Günther!
What? Why?
Günther!
The enemy is now camouflaged as one of the troops.
tatoeba ore ga oreja naitoshite
If we suppose that I am not me,
omae wa omaedato iikirerunoka
Can you say with certainty that you are you?
suna no utsuwa wo kowashite koboreta
Will you be able to pick up after yourself
kokoro wo hirotte atsumerareruka
Once your sand-like shell breaks and your heart crumbles?
dareka no yobu koe ga
I could hear someone calling
miminari ni kawatta
But now my ears are just ringing
toki ga tomatta mitaida
It's as if time has frozen
saa me wo samase
Now, wake up
fukai yami wo ore wa arukidashita
I began to walk through a deep dark abyss
hayate mitai ni nigedashita
As swift as a gale, I escaped for my life
ikita shikabane mitaidatta
I felt like a living corpse
oretachi wa kabe no soto e
We break out of our walls
mata aouze chizu ni nai bashode
To reunite in worlds we've yet to map
The capture operation has failed.
The female-form Titan appears before Eren once more.
All that stands between it and its target
are the master Titan killers,
the Special Operations Squad.
Crushing Blow
57th Expedition Beyond the Walls (pt 5)