I was right!
It is coming!
The female-form Titan!
The female-form Titan emerged again,
defeating the members of the elite Levi Squad one after another.
I'll kill you!
Blaming himself for having entrusted the battle to his comrades,
Eren transformed and battled the female-form Titan.
However, he is defeated and captured by the female-form Titan.
Give Eren back!
No matter where she goes, I'll kill her,
rip her wide open,
and dig you out of that filth.
I'm sorry, Eren...
Just wait a little longer.
Wait!
Wh-What are you—
Fall back for now.
O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
This is a victory for us!
Jetzt, hier ist ein Sieg
Our fame starts here!
Dies ist der erste Gloria
O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
Let us celebrate this victory for the next battle!
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf
"I died for naught" — I won't let it end like that for you
「無意味な死であった」と...言わせない
until I am the last one standing
最後のひとりになるまで...
The enemy is cruel... We will kill—
Der Feind ist grausam... Wir bringen...
The enemy is colossal... We will jump—
Der Feind ist riesig... Wir springen...
In our hands we hold blades of glory
両手には  Gloria
and sing in the name of victory
唄うのは  Sieg
We bear the wings of freedom on our backs
背中には  Flügel der Freiheit
Swearing iron determination upon our hearts,
握り締めた決意を左胸に
we slash apart the circle of idiocy
斬り裂くのは  Ringe der Torheit
and soar through the sky
蒼穹を舞う
with our wings of freedom
Flügel der Freiheit
The Defeated
57th Expedition Beyond the Walls (pt 6)
Maintain this distance.
She's probably tired.
The pace she's keeping isn't particularly fast.
It seems like he was bitten right out along with the neck.
Is Eren dead?
He's alive.
Our target seems highly intelligent,
and capturing Eren is apparently her primary goal.
If she wanted him dead, she could've crushed him in her jaws.
Instead, she's carefully holding Eren inside her mouth
while fighting to escape.
Eating Eren may also have been her goal.
If so, he would've ended up in her stomach.
It makes more sense to assume he's dead.
He's alive!
I hope you're right.
If only you'd protected Eren, this never would've happened!
Now I see...
It was you back then.
You're Eren's close friend.
We'll focus all our manpower on one goal.
First of all, forget about killing the female-form Titan.
But she killed so many of our comrades!
So long as she can crystallize her skin, there's no way we can kill her.
Trust my judgment.
We'll keep hoping that Eren is still alive,
and attempt to rescue him before she leaves the forest.
I'll hack her up...
You draw her attention!
He's fast...
He moves so quickly that she can't get a chance to harden her skin!
We can go for her neck!
She's tired...
I bet she can't move!
I can kill her!
Stop!
Eren!
Hey!
We need to get out of here!
Eren!
I think he's okay.
He's alive!
Filthy, though.
Don't worry about anything else.
We're pulling back.
Don't lose sight of your primary objective.
Is it more important to get the revenge you desire?
Isn't he a dear friend of yours?
No, I...
They're returning already?
What happened?
No clue.
I'll bet they're coming back with a heap of corpses again, though.
Erd is coming home.
I see.
You think Auruo will have time to come home?
It couldn't hurt to make dinner for him, just in case.
Günther's coming home.
I see.
This is the part I just can't get used to.
Nobody gets used to it.
How are my friends going to die?
How am I going to die?
It's all I can think about.
I try not to dwell on it.
If I imagined the way I'm going to die,
I doubt I'd be able to fight at all.
Yeah.
You're right.
How much longer will I be alive?
You're living now, aren't you?
For the moment.
Isn't that a good thing?
You're alive!
How can you say that in front of the corpses of those who died?
I'm not even sure I can go home anymore...
We're almost done.
There were five casualties we couldn't recover.
Not even any parts of them?
We couldn't get close enough because of the Titans.
It's probably better for the families if we don't bring those back.
Report them as missing.
Yes, sir.
We've sighted several Titans near the forest,
but none are headed in our direction us yet.
We're moving out now.
Inform the squads.
Yes, sir.
I refuse to accept this, Commander Erwin!
Hey, you—
We should recover them!
Ivan's body was right in front of us!
There was a Titan right next to him!
We'd just end up losing someone else!
If they attack us, we can just take them out!
Ivan and I are childhood friends from the same village!
I know his parents.
If nothing else, I'd at least like to bring him home!
Stop being selfish!
Quarreling children?
Captain Levi!
If you confirmed he's dead, that's enough.
Whether or not you have a body, dead is dead.
It doesn't change a thing.
That's...
We'll say Ivan and the others are missing.
That's my final decision.
Leave it at that.
Don't either of you
possess any human feelings at all?!
Hey, Dieter! You're getting too far ahead!
Currently Disclosable Information
Recon Corps Wagons (pt 1)
These wagons feature a complicated suspension system
of ultra-hard steel that can only be made in the industrial factory cities.
Currently Disclosable Information
Recon Corps Wagons (pt 2)
Supply wagons hitched to Recon Corps horses
travel around 20 km/h. They can maintain this
speed on varied terrain, including unpaved roads.
Titans!
That's...
Dieter!
That fool...
The rear guard has sighted Titans!
Full speed ahead!
I don't see any tall trees or buildings.
It will be difficult to fight out here.
We're better off trying to outrun them to Walls.
They're gonna catch us!
Will we have to fight?
3D Maneuver Gear has limited functionality in open areas!
And look...
They just keep coming!
Then what'll we do?
We...
No! They'll catch us!
I'll circle behind them!
When I draw their attention, you—
No.
Just abandon the corpses.
Otherwise they'll catch us.
B-But...
On past expeditions, dozens of bodies never made it back.
These guys will be no different.
Are we doing this?
We're seriously dumping them?!
Damn it...
We have no choice!
Okay!
Keep on going!
As soon as we ascertain our location, we'll depart.
Stay alert!
We'll have to take a slight detour to the east...
Captain Levi...
I...
This proves that they were alive.
To me, at least.
This was Ivan's.
Captain...
We're leaving!
Eren, you should give up on joining the Recon Corps.
What? You're going to tell me  it's stupid too?
That's not it...
The Recon Corps is back!
The front gate's opening!
Let's go, Mikasa!
The heroes have returned!
Only this many made it back?
The rest of them must've been eaten.
That's what you get when you venture outside the walls.
It's like all our taxes are spent fattening up the Titans.
Eren?
What is it?
Eren...
Eren!
Don't try to get up yet.
Rest up.
The female-form Titan?
It escaped.
Why?
What happened to others?
What about the plan?
It failed.
Lay still for now.
What's going on?
Did you save me again?
We're almost to the Walls.
Aren't a bunch of them missing compared to this morning?
Man...
Far fewer...
How horrible.
Just this morning they left to raise hell, but now they're back already?
What was the point?
Who knows?
But judging by those gloomy expressions,
they managed to gobble up more of our taxes, if nothing else.
Eren, just bear with it.
So cool!
The Recon Corps are so awesome!
They get their butts kicked, but they keep on fighting!
Captain Levi!
My daughter is in your squad.
I'm Petra's father.
Before I see her, I wanted to talk with you.
She sent me this letter.
She said you respected her skills enough to allow her join your squad.
She swore she'd to devote herself to you.
Well, I guess she's too starry-eyed to consider her father's feelings!
Anyway, as her father,
I think it's still too early for her to marry.
She's still so young, with so much left to experience!
Commander Erwin! Answer us!
Did your expedition learn anything worthwhile to can justify the body count?
Do you really believe the dead leave no regrets?
The costs and casualties of the failed expedition were easily enough
to discredit the faction that had supported the Recon Corps.
As those responsible, including Erwin, were summoned to the capitol,
it was decided that Eren would be handed over.
tatoeba ore ga oreja naitoshite
If we suppose that I am not me,
omae wa omaedato iikirerunoka
Can you say with certainty that you are you?
suna no utsuwa wo kowashite koboreta
Will you be able to pick up after yourself
kokoro wo hirotte atsumerareruka
Once your sand-like shell breaks and your heart crumbles?
dareka no yobu koe ga
I could hear someone calling
miminari ni kawatta
But now my ears are just ringing
toki ga tomatta mitaida
It's as if time has frozen
saa me wo samase
Now, wake up
fukai yami wo ore wa arukidashita
I began to walk through a deep dark abyss
hayate mitai ni nigedashita
As swift as a gale, I escaped for my life
ikita shikabane mitaidatta
I felt like a living corpse
oretachi wa kabe no soto e
We break out of our walls
mata aouze chizu ni nai bashode
To reunite in worlds we've yet to map
That day, Annie was a member
of the guard detail for Eren and the others
as they answered the summons to the capitol.
Suddenly, Armin appeared,
asking Annie for help with a highly sensitive mission.
Smile
Raid on Stohess District (pt 1)