Sorry to call you here out of the blue.
It's okay...
So, did you want something?
The truth is, Onii-san...
I need your help.
そんな優しくしないで　どんな顔すればいいの？
sonna yasashiku shinai de donna kao sureba ii no?
Don't be so nice to me, I just don't know how to react
積み重ねた言葉で
tsumikasaneta kotoba de
With all these words piling up,
見えないよ　きみの横顔
mienai yo kimi no yokogao
I can't even see your face
Mazui Presents
There's No Way My Little Sister 0000can be This Cute
どこだっけ？　なくした鍵は見つからないままで
dokodakke? nakushita kagi ha mitsukaranai mama de
Where is it? I lost my key, now I can't find it
ため息...すれ違いに意地張って疲れちゃう
tameiki... surechigai ni iji hatte tsukarechau
Sigh, I'll burn out if I keep acting like this whenever we fight
ほんの少し近く　きみとの距離が
hon no sukoshi chikaku kimi to no kyori ga
Maybe we're close? I just can't figure out
うまく掴めないんだ　あとちょっとなのに!
umaku tsukamenainda ato chotto na no ni
Just how far away I am, even though you're right there
そんな優しくしないで　ほら　また傷つけあって
sonna yasashikushinaide hora mata kizutsukeatte
Don't be so nice to me, see? We hurt each other again
積み重ねたウソでもう　動けなくなってる
tsumikasaneta uso de mou ugokenakunatteru
With all these lies piling up, I can't even move
すぐに会いに行きたいけど　言葉は見つからないし
sugu ni ai ni ikitai kedo kotoba ha mitsukaranai shi
I want to see you now, but I don't know what to say
最後の一ページくらい　きみには笑顔見せたい
saigo no ichi pe-ji kurai kimi ni ha egao misetai
If this is the end for our story, I want you to see my smile
There's No Way My Little Sister
Can Cosplay Like This
If it's a present from you, she'd be happy no matter what you gave her.
Well...
That's true...
And why would I know what a middle school girl would like, anyway?
Anything you'd pick would be way better.
But then...
It wouldn't be what she wants the most.
What?
What'd you say?
Kirino...
Kirino would be happiest getting something related to her hobby.
That's why I'm asking you for help!
Are you accepting Kirino's otaku hobby?
I haven't accepted it.
I haven't accepted it!
But it's a celebration for her, so I'm making an exception this time...
Also, Kirino has been talking to me a little about anime...
Ones that aren't indecent, anyway.
But it's still not good enough for her.
Last time I visited...
Look at them! Aren't they cute?!
Why do you have so many of the same ones?
They're all different! Look at the colors.
It's hard to collect them all.
What do you do after you collect them?
She wouldn't talk to me for a while after that.
I was on the verge of tears...
Those are on the top three list of things you shouldn't ask.
That's why I want to make up for it now!
I decided to give her something related to her hobby,
so I'm asking you to help me think of what would make her the most happy!
So...
She's thinking about Kirino in her own way.
Got it.
I'll look into what kind of present she wants.
Th-Thank you so much!
What?
Are you thinking of giving me a present or something?
Ew... Gross.
Sorry. I can't do this, Ayase.
Hey, come on.
You made me buy stuff for you on Christmas Eve, didn't you?
That was for my research, so it doesn't count.
Don't take that the wrong way.
And come to think of it,
you've been making passes at my friends recently.
You were all over Ayase.
And you've been meeting with the black one and Saori without me.
Th-They're my friends now, too!
So I can get along with them however I want!
You don't deny it?
Well, whatever. I don't care.
Why are you being so picky?
What are you, my girlfriend?
So you got into a fight and couldn't find out from her?
You really do lack grace.
More importantly, did you tell Kirino about what we did?
It was unavoidable.
Actually, a few days ago...
Hey, the restroom here is the cockpit for the Omega!
That's the Justeen Cafe for you.
I wonder what the men's side is like.
It's the bridge.
How do you know?
Your brother told me last—
What were you thinking?!
Don't worry.
She didn't find out about the anime studio incident.
We said you really wanted to see us and called us here.
What the hell?!
What kind of cheap guy did you turn me into?!
Now, now, now.
Let's get back to the topic.
Basically, you want to know what Miss Kiririn wants, right?
Yeah.
I figured you guys would definitely know better than me.
I see...
Well, we were also thinking of holding a party celebrating her anime.
Oh? Really?
Saori is just saying that.
I've done absolutely nothing.
Oh, okay.
Thanks.
Oh no, it's nothing.
I'm doing it because I want to.
But now that we're ready, let us search for what Miss Kiririn desires!
The first thing that comes to mind would probably be this kind of stuff.
It wouldn't be too hard.
It matches her tastes perfectly.
They don't sell them either, so there's some value to it.
Yeah...
But it doesn't feel quite right...
This seems a bit weird for what she'd want the most.
Then perhaps a visual fanbook for eroge she likes?
Or perhaps rare doujinshi?
Uh... thanks for the suggestion,
but the requester would murder me over this.
There's no point in coming here.
She probably already has everything she wants from here.
Yeah...
The greatest work of art ever to grace the Earth at the hands of Man, for ¥980?
What will they do next?
This please.
You're buying it?!
Man, we can't find anything.
Are you sure a Meruru plushie isn't good enough?
It's probably the best thing we've found so far,
but I get the feeling there's something even better out there.
It's just not coming to mind.
It just has to be backwards compatible with that, right?
Something she would like, and isn't indecent.
Something hard to obtain, with real value behind it.
Something like that won't just pop—
Y-You're right!
This might be perfect!
Please repeat what you just said.
Kirino is a huge fan of that anime.
I know that.
It doesn't look like something indecent.
So I was thinking, maybe a figure they don't sell would be perfect.
It's hard to get your hands on, and for people into the stuff, it's invaluable.
What do you think?
Yes.
Goods for this anime are fine.
But I don't see how we can obtain this item that isn't for sale.
It's the prize for winning a Meruru cosplay competition.
You're telling me to participate?
Well, I mean, you're a model...
And you're beautiful, and you can definitely go for first place...
Ayase-san?
Might you be angry?
Of course I am!!
How could I appear on stage wearing something as embarrassing as this?!
Do you want me to kill you, you pervert?!
C-Calm down!
Listen to everything I have to say!
And you wouldn't look good in Meruru's outfit anyway!
I've done my research here!
This is the winner of the last one, Bridget-chan!
No matter what kind of mind-melting performance you do, you can't win against this!
And I wouldn't do a mind-melting performance in the first place!
Moron! Pervert!
Look closer! This contest is all about fitting the role!
It's more about looking like the character than the impact!
And it's not like you don't have a chance.
You're definitely prettier than her.
And you're a professional model, too.
You know how to bring out the best in clothes.
You can definitely win with the right character.
It sounds like you're saying there's a character that looks like me.
Yeah.
Fine. Show me.
What costume will I wear?
This.
Dark Witch Tanatos Eros EX Mode—
She's practically nude!!
Die!
Look properly!
She's only nude in the transformation sequence!
She's lewd enough even after the transformation sequence!
I will never wear such lecherous clothes!
Then what about Kirino's present?
I can't think of anything she would want more than this!
Y-You pervert!
Why is she acting like I'm blackmailing her?!
We just need to win this contest and obtain the prize, correct?
Well, yeah, but...
You can't win against this girl with any other character.
No. We can win.
We just need an even cuter cosplay that looks more like the character than this girl.
Good grief...
Kyousuke-dono:
I have acquired the item you requested.
I pray for your success in this mission.
Saori
Struggle all you may against futility.
That alone may allow you escape
from the chains of failure.
Kuroneko
Those two...
Sorry!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
This is my classmate, Kurusu Kanako.
Nice to meet you!
I'm Kurusu Kanako!
Call me Kanakana!
Nice to meet you, Kanakana-chan.
I'm Aragaki's manager, Akagi Kouhei.
What? You're not a producer or anything?
Dammit, I acted cute for nothing.
And don't call me Kanakana like you know me.
It's gross.
This brat...
Why don't we go put your clothes on?
Damn, she looks like her!
Is she the real thing?!
We're all good here.
You can go now.
And she cut off her escape route!
Now then, let's head to the event!
What?! The hell's this?!
This is like something out of brat anime crap!
What the hell?!
Sorry, I forgot to tell you.
The contest today is actually a cosplay contest.
Cosplay?!
Why do I have to be in something stupid like that?!
I'm not doing it!
I see...
That's too bad...
I wonder where the car with your clothes has gone now...
You tricked me, damn you!
Stardust Witch Meruru...
Starts now!
Dang, that's a lot of people.
This is an anime for kids, right?
Why are all these adult males here?
You're asking me...
It's proof that it's popular among all demographics maybe?
Welcome to the second official Stardust Witch Cosplay Contest, everyone!
Today we have 23 girls who will be characters from Meruru on stage!
It's going to be fun!
I'll be your host, Hoshino Kurara!
Are you ready?
They're really into it...
What's wrong?
Onii-san...
Look there.
Wahoo! Kurara!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Kurara!
Kurara!
Th-That's Kirino, right?
Yeah, it is...
Well, it's no surprise she's here...
Or rather, we should have figured she'd show up.
Good thing she's not going up there.
I'm glad I'm not participating in this...
If Kirino saw me cosplaying in that, I would die...
I think she'd be really happy, though...
Now then, this is the winner's prize—the trophy!
A special Meruru figure!
There's only one of these in the world!
Special Meruru! Yes! Yes! Yes!
I want it so bad! Dammit!
If only there were a character that looked like me!
She wanted to participate!
It looks like we picked the right present for her.
Yeah...
But Kanako will see her if she's up there making a racket like that.
I'll go warn her.
We should split up here.
It'll be a hard to explain if she sees us together.
Yes.
We can meet up where we were earlier.
Give this to Kirino.
Now then, entry number 1!
We have last year's winner, coming all the way from England again this year, Bridget-chan!
Taste my blade!
Yeah! Real Al-chan, so awesome! So cute! Be my sister!
Quiet down, you idiot!
Dammit, every single time, you!
Why are you here?
And what's with your hair?
I've got my reasons.
We can talk later.
For now, hide your face with that.
You don't want your school friends to know about this.
Is someone here?
Someone you know is participating.
Explain yourself later.
99 points! Did she win it already?
Hey, who's this person I know?
Did they go on already?
No, you should be able to tell once she comes out.
Now then, entry 21, Kanakana-chan, come on out!
Okay!
Stardust Witch Meruru!
Starts now!
What the hell?
She is crazy good at singing!
Wait, how does she know this song?
So cute!
What is this? What is this?
CG? An illusion? Is she 3D? 3D?!
Calm down!
Oh crap. I've got a nosebleed!
Hey, isn't that a bit embarrassing for a girl?
Thank you, everyone!
There we have it! 100 points!
Kanakana-chan got a full 100 points!
Wow, she's amazing.
Hey, so...
When does this person I know come on?
See? Just like I said.
It wasn't just because she's the spitting image.
Right? Kanako's amazing, you know?
Man, this sucks.
What's with those gross otaku freaks?
Like I'd even think of coming within a hundred feet of them.
Ka-Kanakana-chan, you can't say something like that...
They all cheered for you...
Me-Meruru turned into a dark witch!
Gross! Shut up, brat.
Hey! Don't make little kids like that cry!
So, what did you think about my performance?
Oh right, how did you know that song?
Did you know about this anime?
Nope.
But I do idol auditions regularly.
I practice at karaoke places too.
I can remember a song like that after hearing it once.
Amazing, right?
Amazing, sure.
But...
What?
You looked like you were having fun singing it. Was that an act?
Were you just acting like it and making fun of the fans inside?
Well...
It was fun.
I like it when people call me cute.
I think that "moe" stuff is stupid, but I like the feeling of being worshipped when they go crazy over my singing and dancing.
I see...
You might make a good idol.
Of course!
Here.
Thank you so much!
She's late!
When do I get my clothes?!
Ayase!!
Huh?
だってしょうがないんだもん
datte shouganain da mon
I mean, I just can't help it
いつのまに好きになってて
itsu no ma ni suki ni nattete
At some point, I fell in love with it
あたしだってこういうの　普通じゃないって 分かってるよっ!
atashi datte kouiu no futsuu ja nai tte wakatteru yo!
I already know that it just isn't normal!
満たさない僕等の　SNS完全捜索エンドレス
mitasanai bokurano SNS kanzen sousaku endoresu
Never filling, our complete SNS search, endless
君の好きなアニメのヒロインの音
kimi no suki na anime no hiroin no oto
Your favorite anime's heroine's voice,
大人、友達も餌食
otona, tomodachi mo ejiki
Adults, friends, all mine
一歩を踏み出せば
ippo wo fumidaseba
If you take a step forward,
ほら　無限のコアなフレンドシップ
hora mugen no koa na furendoshippu
Look, infinite core friendships
僕の好きなキャラクター
boku no suki na kyarakuta-
My favorite character
クラスの隣の席のシャイなあの子
kurasu no tonari no seki no shai na ano ko
Is the shy one next to me in class there
世界中みんな　お兄ちゃんと呼ばれたいの
sekaijuu minna oniichan to yobaretai no
Everyone in the world wants to be called Onii-chan
老若男女　そう言う時代
rounyaku nannyo sou iu jidai
Old, young, boys, girls, that's the age we're in
誰にも言えないで　隠してたけれど
dare ni mo ienaide kakushiteta keredo
Everyone hides it, never saying a thing
分かってくれるならあんたに言うよ
wakattekureru nara anta ni iu yo
But if you understand, then I'll call you
だってしょうがないんだもん
datte shouganain da mon
I mean, I just can't help it
いつのまに好きになってて
itsu no ma ni suki ni nattete
At some point, I fell in love with it
あたしだってこういうの　普通じゃないって分かってるよっ!
atashi datte kouiu no futsuu ja nai tte wakatteru yo!
I already know that it just isn't normal!
10万ください❤
juuman kudasai❤
Give me a grand❤
There's No Way My Little Sister
Can Be a Maid