Too slow!
Onii-chan!
Secret Technique: Tentacle Cannon!
Go back home!
You have a brother waiting for you.
そんな優しくしないで　どんな顔すればいいの
sonna yasashiku shinai de donna kao sureba ii no
Don't be so nice to me, I just don't know how to react
積み重ねた言葉で　見えないよ　きみの横顔
tsumikasaneta kotoba de mienaiyo kimi no yokogao
With all these words piling up, I can't even see your face
Mazui Presents
There's No Way My Little Sister 0000can be This Cute
どこだっけ？　なくした鍵は見つからないままで
dokodakke? nakushita kagi ha mitsukaranai mama de
Where is it? I lost my key, now I can't find it
ため息　すれ違いに意地張って　疲れちゃう
tameiki surechigai ni iji hatte tsukarechau
Sigh, I'll burn out if I keep acting like this whenever we miss
ほんの少し近く　きみとの距離が
hon no sukoshi chikaku kimi to no kyori ga
Maybe we're close? I just can't figure out
うまく掴めないんだ　あとちょっとなのに
umaku tsukamenainda ato chotto na no ni
Just how far away I am, even though you're right there
そんな優しくしないで　ほらまた傷つけあって
sonna yasashikushinaide hora mata kizutsukeatte
Don't be so nice to me, see? We hurt each other again
積み重ねた嘘でも　動けなくなってる
tsumikasaneta uso demo ugokenakunatteru
With all these lies piling up, I can't even move
すぐに合いに行きたいけど　言葉は見つからないし
sugu ni ai ni ikitai kedo kotoba ha mitsukaranai shi
I want to see you now, but I don't know what to say
最後の一ページかい？　きみには笑顔見せたい
saigo no ichi pe-ji kai? kimi ni ha egao misetai
Is this the end for our story? I want you to see my smile
There's No Way My Little Sister
would go to Summer Comiket
Hey...
You canned yourself into your room all morning during the weekend playing eroge.
You're the one who forced me to play it!
Don't look down on me! You should be praising me!
You're the spitting image of an erogamer.
That's not a compliment!!
So? Have you cleared it once at least?
No, I haven't yet...
This game's special feature is the ability to use the character from your cleared saved game in a fighter!
If you still haven't completed it, you can't play against me!
Go fight with someone else...
Can't you do it online?
I can't win online.
Just go find a walkthrough site.
Why do you think I set it up so you can use the internet?
The SisCaly ATWiki is really detailed.
Read it and spend all tomorrow clearing the game.
It's even a Sunday.
Yeah, fine fine.
I just need to clear it, right?
Tomorrow then.
Oh, I forgot to mention...
I have friends coming over tomorrow.
Make sure you don't come out of your room.
They're cute, but if you try to talk to them, I'll kill you.
Don't even look at them.
You'll contaminate them.
It's not like I give a damn about your friends in the first place.
Right...
I don't get it at all.
Huh? I can login?
Isn't this her character?
Alright!
Time to give up!
Good day, Kiririn-san.
If you have a moment, would you like to chat?
You really are a totally different person online.
Kyousuke-onii-sama?
It has been some time.
Have you been doing well?
Normal.
She's doing too well.
Thanks for looking out for her.
Not at all...
I'm able to put Kiririn-san to good use in this game.
Thanks to her,
I've managed to maintain an 8:1 win ratio.
So you're the reason she's so moody...
Can you show me the ropes for this game then?
She's forcing me to play this,
so I figure if I can get good at it, I can beat her as revenge.
It's lovely to see you two getting along so well.
Like hell!
Hello?
If that's the case then I'll walk you through it over the phone!
Totally different person!
I'll be right there!
I've been waiting for you!
Pardon the intrusion.
Heya!
You can just head upstairs.
I'll bring some drinks up.
Sorry to intrude.
Gross.
I told you not to look!
Why are you here?
I told you to stay in your room.
I seriously don't want you running into them, so hurry up and go to your room!
Yeah, yeah.
You idiot, if you go up now, they might see you!
What's wrong with your brain?
Why am I doing this?!
Yeah, right!
Let's see your phone then!
You can't!
That's an invasion of privacy.
That's so suspicious.
Why don't you just admit it?
I told you, I don't have a boyfriend!
But you've been acting weird recently.
Huh? Wh-What do mean by that?
No way~
That character you're putting on is so gross!
I saw you talking on your phone one time, and you sounded really angry, but you looked kind of happy.
And after hanging up you had this huge smile.
It's definitely a boyfriend!
That's not really...
Come on, stop already!
I don't have a boyfriend or anything!
The goosebumps!! She's making me sick!!
That's enough, you two.
By the way, the person downstairs was your brother, right?
Wh-What about him?
Why do you look so annoyed all of a sudden?
He looks like a kind brother.
You need to see an optometrist.
You definitely have some eye disease.
So cruel!
I saw him too!
It was only for a moment, but he didn't look like you at all.
Shut up, dumb kid.
Leave me alone!
How to describe him...
He seems like the kind of guy who'll end up as your average manager at some office branch in 10 years.
Like, totally plain?
Middle school girls can sure run their mouths.
Why did you get all quiet, Kirino?
No reason...
Thank you!
To: Kousaka Kyousuke
From: Makashima Saori
Who's this?
What's that?
No idea.
That box!
It's yours?
Why does it have my name—
It's an "Eternal" box!
No way!
Why? How?
Is this for me?
Wait...
Wow!
Even I can't buy any of their stuff!
Wait, that's—
No choice then.
I'll take care of it for you.
Now we're even for that unnecessary stress you caused me with your screwup earlier.
That's not what I mea—
Hello?
Mr. Kyousuke? It's me, Saori.
Did you get my package?
It was you?
You mean the cosmetics maker box you sent?
Yes, that one!
You see, I know Miss Kiririn's address and phone number, but I never asked what her real name was.
So that's why you sent it to me?
Well, I gave it to her already.
She looked very happy.
Thanks.
Are you sure you're okay giving that brand of cosmetics to her?
Isn't that stuff really expensive?
The contents of the box are completely unrelated to the box itself, you know...
What?
Then... what's inside?
What Miss Kiririn asked for.
A Meruru and SisCaly doujinshi set.
Wha—
Ero stuff?
To say the least.
I'll call you back later!!
Oh crap this is bad!
Hey!
What are you doing, barging in like that?
Sorry, there's been a mistake...
Get out!
Right now!
Could you give me back that box?
You already gave it to me!
You're not making sense!
Just get out already!
Sorry!
Sorry for interrupting!
Stop!
I'll explain later!
Shut up!
Stop making excuses!
Give it back!
I said no!!
That hurts! Stop!
Die! Die die die die!
Look out!
What is this, some eroge?!
Kirino?
Woah, you're in that kind of relationship with your brother?
N-No!!
Don't you dare come back inside until everyone's gone home, you freaking pervert!
Thanks for having us!
Um...
Uh... yes?
Does that box have something that Kirino shouldn't see?
I didn't feel like you were just trying to harass her earlier...
You seemed desperate, trying your hardest...
So I thought maybe there was a reason for it...
Is it a present for her for some special day?
Nothing like that.
I see.
But there's some reason for it right?
I don't know what it is, but please forgive Kirino!
She's a bit selfish, but I'm sure she doesn't actually hate you or anything!
I see...
Thanks for the advice.
I'll keep that in mind.
Thanks for looking out for her all the time.
Not at all!
We're best friends, after all.
Since we got a chance to talk...
Thank you very much!
My name's Kousaka Kyousuke.
And you?
Sorry for the late introduction.
I'm Aragaki Ayase.
Sorry about that!
What were you talking about?
I get it now,
but couldn't you have done it some other way?
No!!
It's your fault for just grabbing this and running to your room!
What? Are you trying to blame me for this?
Things got this confusing because you went and secretly became friends with Saori!
See, you're already distracted.
Shut up!
And what was with you going all ga-ga for Ayase?
Don't check out my friends like that!
You pervert!
You're calling me a pervert?!
You're going to take responsibility for embarrassing me in front of everyone.
Huh?
I'm going to be busy with my club this summer, so I won't be able to go out much.
I have training camp the second half of August, too.
So...
Basically you want me to take you out somewhere?
Like the beach or the mountain?
I can go to those kinds of places with Ayase.
Where do you want to go then?
Think about it yourself.
Why did I have to get up so early and come to a place like this?
Well, after thinking about it, I asked her in the end.
I proposed we make our Summer Comiket debut.
I was actually already thinking of inviting you.
I had some responsibility for the incident, after all.
Whatever.
How long do I have to wait in line?
My feet hurt.
No one cares.
Quit complaining and just wait.
You're annoying the people around you.
Well, I guess this line is tough on first-timers.
Sorry about this. And you even lent us a chair...
Though, if she really didn't want to be here, she wouldn't have come.
I guess as her brother you know her quite well.
Hot... Gross... Annoying...
Could you please be quiet?
You're making the discomfort index go up.
But why do all these people line up for hours in this inferno for?
Do they want doujinshi that badly?
Not everyone's here for the same thing, but I'm sure you'll understand once it begins.
When does it begin?
This year's Summer Comic Circle Market is now open!
Please enter calmly, and no pushing!
Hot... Loud... Smelly...
What a frail human.
It's better than it was yesterday.
You came here yesterday?
I was actually here two days ago too.
A battle is something you stick with from the start.
Seriously, what's so fun about this?
The answer to that is right over there.
Running is dangerous!
Please do not run!
The ceiling's so high!
Miss Kiririn, did you have any artists you liked from the doujinshi I sent you?
Well, if I had to choose, I'd say Yamanashi Ganma's Meruru book and QQQ's Reika book.
And... Oh, right!
Sakura G. Sakura did the artbook, right?
She's doing Meruru's comic version, right?
That was so cute!
Total recovery!
Actually, those books were all made by people I know.
What?
Wait, seriously?
I was thinking of making my rounds to say hello.
Would you like to join me?
S-Seriousl—
Fine, I'll go with you.
But only if you insist.
Please do join me.
It's a bit cooler because it's cloudy, but isn't it really harsh wearing a costume like that in summer?
If it's too hot, you stuff ice packs in them.
You don't have a drop of sweat on you either.
You do things like that?
Well...
I put up a thin curtain of dark energy which protects me from the sun and heat.
What? What does that mean?
You wouldn't understand.
Just give up.
I'm afraid you don't have the eyes of the "Children of the Night".
You can't possibly see dark energy.
And now you've turned all teen complex again.
You're cosplaying again today? That Maschera character?
Where exactly are you looking at?
You're totally wrong.
These are my normal clothes.
If these are your normal clothes, then you can make them a bit cooler.
W-Wait, don't—
Much better.
I said that this heat was nothing to me.
Sure, sure. Whatever.
You look pretty cute when you're not wearing those thick clothes.
Could you stop giving compliments with your "I'm still better" attitude?
Seriously? Getting embarrassed?
Hold.
What?
West Halls 3 and 4 are for industry booths.
Let's go!
There's something I want at the Alice+ booth!
Alice+? I've heard that name somewhere before...
They made SisCaly.
I'll go ahead! I need to buy that Limited Edition Summer Comiket Disc!
Limited edition disc?
A collector's item with data for the new SisCaly.
But...
Sold
Out
You would have needed to line up as soon as it opened to buy it...
Don't worry about it.
Too bad...
Well, you couldn't really help it.
Shut up. Don't touch me.
Excuse me...
Um... there's one disc left...
It looks like you can get the disc if you can beat him.
Sounds interesting. I'll give it a go!
That staff member's won 50 straight games these last three days.
They don't plan to let anyone win.
He's also a high-ranking player on the PC version.
If you give him an unanalyzed new character...
That was fast...
Damn this crappy game!
Like I could win!
That's such a ripoff!
Well... you weren't great at Siscalypse to begin with...
Saori is much bette—
My deepest apologies.
I thought I had him, but...
It's fine, no one's winning that.
Too slow!
Naive!
You're mine!
She got me!
It'll be over soon.
Impossible!
And you call yourself a little sister? How silly!
Kuroneko-dono!!
How could you!
I had no idea you were so good!
Stifling...
Could you stop that?
Wh-What?
You can have this.
What? What do you mean?
Oh? You don't want it?
Or maybe you don't understand what I'm saying?
If you don't want it then throw it away.
I-I didn't say that!
Why not just accept it then?
Or is my beauty overwhelming you?
What a boring human.
Why is everything you say so annoying?
I don't see a single speck of beauty anywhere on you!
She just can't be honest...
Indeed... both of them.
Well if you insist, I'll take it off your hands.
Be grateful!
Hey! What's so funny?
Comiket can certainly be pretty harsh, but if you put your all into it, you can find all sorts of fun.
That's why I figured we should come here together.
I see...
Well, it has nothing to do with a normal person like me, though.
Could you give me back my coat now?
Thanks a lot.
I'm sure she—
What might you be talking about?
Hey, come on!
Kirino!
Ayase?
強く強く　願っていた
tsuyoku tsuyoku negatteita
Strongly, strongly, I wished
あなたが隠す本当の笑顔
anata ga kakusu hontou no egao
To see the true smile you’re hiding
遠く遠く　見受けたい
tooku tooku miuketai
From afar, from afar, I want to see
私から伝えるさよなら
watashi kara tsutaeru sayonara
A goodbye from me to you
あなたが本当に大切にしたいもの
anata ga hontou ni taisetsu ni shitai mono
I try to understand that
一つだけじゃないって分かっていたいけど
hitotsu dake janaitte wakatteitai kedo
You hold more than one thing dear
ねえ　お願い私だけを見つめ続けてよ
ne onegai watashi dake wo mitsumetsudzukete yo
But please, just look only at me
かき乱されぬ汚れなき心
kakimidasarenu kegarenaki kokoro
With your pure, incorruptible heart
出来るなら認めたい(認められない)
dekiru nara mitometai (mitomerarenai)
I want to accept it (I cannot accept it)
白いキャンバスに描がかれたとも
shiroi kyanbasu ni egakareta tomo
Even if drawn on white canvas
全て背負って生きて行くの
subete seotte ikiteyuku no
I’ll undertake it all and live on
There's No Way My Little Sister's
Best Friend can be this ●●●●
Next time: