Good morning, senpai.
Y-You...
Kuroneko?
You enrolled in my school?
Yes.
Not because of you or anything.
Well yeah, but...
You should've told me!
I had no obligation to.
What does it have to do with you?
Well...
I think it's great!
Let's get along then, kouhai.
Indeed, senpai.
What an idiot.
Kyou-chan, Kyou-chan!
She's a first year, right?
Do you know her?
She's a friend of Kirino and mine.
What's her name?
Kuroneko.
Wait, what's her real name?
そんな優しくしないで　どんな顔すればいいの？
sonna yasashiku shinai de donna kao sureba ii no?
Don't be so nice to me, I just don't know how to react
積み重ねた言葉で
tsumikasaneta kotoba de
With all these words piling up,
見えないよ　きみの横顔
mienai yo kimi no yokogao
I can't even see your face
Mazui Presents
There's No Way My Little Sister 0000can be This Cute
どこだっけ？　なくした鍵は見つからないままで
dokodakke? nakushita kagi ha mitsukaranai mama de
Where is it? I lost my key, now I can't find it
ため息...すれ違いに意地張って疲れちゃう
tameiki... surechigai ni iji hatte tsukarechau
Sigh, I'll burn out if I keep acting like this whenever we fight
ほんの少し近く　きみとの距離が
hon no sukoshi chikaku kimi to no kyori ga
Maybe we're close? I just can't figure out
うまく掴めないんだ　あとちょっとなのに!
umaku tsukamenainda ato chotto na no ni
Just how far away I am, even though you're right there
そんな優しくしないで　ほら　また傷つけあって
sonna yasashikushinaide hora mata kizutsukeatte
Don't be so nice to me, see? We hurt each other again
積み重ねたウソでもう　動けなくなってる
tsumikasaneta uso de mou ugokenakunatteru
With all these lies piling up, I can't even move
すぐに会いに行きたいけど　言葉は見つからないし
sugu ni ai ni ikitai kedo kotoba ha mitsukaranai shi
I want to see you now, but I don't know what to say
最後の一ページくらい　きみには笑顔見せたい
saigo no ichi pe-ji kurai kimi ni ha egao misetai
If this is the end for our story, I want you to see my smile
There's No Way My Kouhai
Can Be This Rotten
Gokou Ruri.
That would be my human name.
Gokou?
That feels weird...
I called you Kuroneko all this time...
Then continue to do so.
Yeah, I will.
So...
Why are you guys here?
With Miss Kiririn away, you must be so lonely, so I was invited to check in on you.
Right, Ruri-chan?
Please stop constructing false realities.
Truth is, I'm feeling more refreshed than ever with that noisy sister gone.
I appreciate the thought, though.
Thanks.
And you're accepting it without a second thought.
This is the present you got that one time...
How nostalgic.
Hasn't Kirino called you guys or anything?
She put up a short update on her SNS blog, but that's all.
I was just getting fed up with that woman, too.
It's so refreshing to have her gone.
To be perfectly honest, I'm kind of angry with her.
I consider her a close friend, and I believed she thought of me the same way...
And yet, taking off like that without consulting any of us...
It's really painful, sad, and hard to bear.
I...
I admire that she's following her ambitions like this, but I still can't agree with how she went about it.
And on top of that, she hasn't called or emailed us,
and I haven't seen her online at all, either...
It's all slowly getting to me.
Don't you think it's okay for me to be just a little mad?
Yeah...
Alright!
How about the three of us go out somewhere then?
And after that, you can post about it.
It'll definitely piss her off.
I like that idea.
Why are you running off home?
I sent you a mail, didn't I?
I said I'd come to your classroom after homeroom's over.
I don't remember that.
So, who's this?
I wanted to introduce you two.
Pleased to meet you! I'm Tamura Manami.
Belphegor!
Belphe?
Never mind...
My name is Gokou. Pleased to meet you.
Kyou-chan, you call her Kuroneko-san, right?
Would you mind if I did too?
Either way is fine.
I'll be going then.
H-Hey!
Wait, wait up!
Maschera's airing today so I have to get back.
Maschera ended at episode 12 in the second season.
It isn't airing anymore.
Don't talk like it's over!
I'm sorry!
I just meant to say that the next season hasn't been scheduled yet!
None of the real fans have given up on it.
Gokou-san!
Are you free?
We're going to karaoke, so if you wa—
I'm not free.
Sorry!
We were just asking her out ourselves...
Maybe next time, okay?
I see...
See you tomorrow then, Gokou-san.
Should I have kept quiet?
Speaking of which, have you picked a club yet?
I'm not joining one.
I have enough on my plate already.
Game Research Club
I didn't know we had a club like this...
Please give it a try if you'd like.
This looks like a "danmaku" shooter...
It looks pretty hard, too.
Our club president made it with the idea that it'd be some sort of entry test.
There's an easy mode, so give it a go.
No, I'm okay...
Hurry up and clear it.
Piece of cake for you, right?
Fine then.
That mode is seriously hard, you know...
No way...
You beat the high score too!
It was a thoroughly terrible game from beginning to end.
Please tell the creator to go die.
Let's go.
U-Um... won't you join our club?
Not interested.
Sorry!
It has nothing to do with you.
I just don't have time to go out with them.
You say that, but you've been spending a lot of time here lately.
I believe what Miss Kuroneko wants to say is,
"I'd rather be with you than go out with my classmates!"
Don't interpret things so weirdly!
I didn't say a thing!!
Anyway, you can't go on like this.
How pushy can you get?
"You don't have any friends, right?"
"I'll help you out!"
What Mr. Kyousuke is thinking is,
"I'll show my cute kouhai how cool I can be!"
"And then she'll pay me back with sexual favors!"
What kind of translation is that?!
Wh-What are you planning to do to me??
Nothing!!
Don't hide behind my sheets!
Well, not all of it is untrue.
I like it when you call me "senpai",
and I was thinking maybe if I help you out somehow, we could get to know each other better...
So I won't say I had zero ulterior motives,
but I really do want to help you solve your problems.
And that's not a lie!
In that case, how about joining a club?
Welcome to the Game Research Club!
I'm Makabe, a second year.
I'm Kousaka, third year,
and this is Gokou, first year.
Let me introduce you to our club president.
This way.
It's all guys here...
Wait, that's OniPan...
President!
Kousaka-san and Gokou-san have come to visit.
Ah, good work.
Ahhh!! Give me back my bike!!
I'm sorry!
So sorry!
So you put my little Fana-tan model to good use?
I guess it was worth it then.
I've kept it safe in my garage.
I'll go pick it up later then.
Sorry again...
I didn't get your name or address at the time,
so I searched around Akiba afterwards, but..
It's okay.
That night was so full of passion for us, it wasn't the time or place for it!
Anyway, I'm great buddies with this guy.
Kousaka-senpai.
I'm sure you've noticed, so let me explain.
This guy's been held back who knows how many years now.
That's why he looks so old.
I see...
Don't just go telling people that!
It's embarrassing!
Forget the embarrassment and just hurry up and graduate!
We make games, but not everyone participates.
We have a lot of inactive members, and the only ones who come regularly are me and these guys.
Yo.
We're holding a welcoming party soon, so I'll introduce everyone again then.
What kind of games do you make?
Just shooters?
No, we make anything.
What tools do you use?
We should have anything you'd need.
Equipment, software, books...
Technical ones, that is.
You're welcome to borrow anything you need.
You're interested in making games?
What do you specialize in?
Can you write scripts?
Can you draw?
Music?
Storyboarding?
Well, I'm pretty much able to use any of the tools without instruction.
Can I take a look?
Go ahead!
With her and Akagi-san, our new members this year are pretty high level.
Akagi?
Yes.
Akagi Sena-san, a first year, like Gokou-san.
She actually had the highest score on that game before Gokou-san came along.
Is something wrong?
Akagi...
She isn't here today?
No...
Even when she's here, it's like she's having a staring contest with the computers and books, so she doesn't really talk about games at all.
And we don't have any girls in the club, so I guess it's a bit awkward for her.
That's another reason why it'd be great to have Gokou-san join us.
Well, I guess it's better than having absolutely no girls in the club...
What do you think?
How about giving it a try?
They have tools and software I don't, and it seems I have freedom to do what I want to an extent,
so I suppose it's a bit more convenient than doing everything at home.
How's the club going for Kuroneko-san?
She doesn't make any trouble when she drops by.
You in charge of cleaning today?
Yes.
What about everyone else?
I see.
Later then.
K-Kyou-chan?
You're always so kind, Kyou-chan.
What are you doing?
Cleaning.
I don't like it.
Are you trying to take pity on me?
What do you mean?
You're not lying when you say you're worried about me.
You said that, right?
Yeah. It's no lie.
I understand. You're not lying.
It isn't a lie,
but have you thought about where those feelings come from?
I thought I'd refrain from telling you,
but the reason you're trying to help me is because your sister isn't around for you to help anymore.
You're doing this because I'm a girl, younger than you, and I look like I'm having trouble.
Because I look like I would rely on you.
That's all there is to it.
I'm not a replacement for your sister.
Don't insult me like that.
Miss Kuroneko may have turned down joining a club and her classmates' invitations for the same reason.
Basically, she's afraid of losing time spent with us.
She has many things to do after school, and because she valued her time with us so much,
she may have been shunned by her class.
If you put yourself in her shoes and think about it, it's not so unexpected that she'd say that.
Don't worry, she'll forgive you if you apologize properly.
Thanks.
Not at all.
So, what will you do?
Are you going to stop sticking your nose in her business now?
No.
Alright!
It looks like you're all here.
Then let's get this welcoming party started!
Let's make this year a blast as well!
Cheers!
We've got some good new members this year.
Indeed.
Good work, Makabe.
What?
Oh, nothing.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kousaka, third year.
Hello. Akagi, first year.
Wait, Akagi?
Is something wrong?
Well, you just don't look like you're having fun.
I don't really like this club.
Why?
Just look.
They're all gross guys, and it's filthy.
They make such weird games all the time, it's ridiculous.
And bringing in all these adult games and figures is just absurd.
Then why did you join?
I wanted to learn how to program.
The president's game, putting aside the setting, was well-made.
And the equipment here is better than expected.
I thought there might be enough benefits despite all the problems.
I've heard this story somewhere before...
But my patience does have its limits.
There are only a few people in here that actually participate, and the room is plain filthy.
You look more like the kind to join the student council than the Game Research Club.
What a relief.
I don't want to be thought of as one of their kind.
But won't you get branded as an otaku by joining a club like this?
I'm sure people will understand if I explain myself properly!
Recent anime have girls trying to hide their otaku hobbies, but those are all just exaggerations.
There's no condemnation like that in reality.
We live in an age where watching anime in theaters is perfectly normal.
But aren't eroge and doujinshi too much for them?
Of course they are!
It's always important to pay attention to the time, place, and occasion, and the situation.
Otaku aren't avoided because of their hobbies themselves.
They're avoided when they do something socially unacceptable.
Like the ones who spew lines and catchphrases anywhere and everywhere.
They're the worst.
Sounds like some runt that can only live by leeching off others is trying to talk.
Ah, Gokou-san, you were there?
You leave such a weak impression, I didn't notice you.
You two know each other?!
The most annoying woman in the class.
The biggest problem child in the class.
Maybe I should confirm...
Hey...
What is it?
You said you were interested in programming, but don't you like games?
I like them as much as anyone else...
Of course.
If you didn't, you wouldn't be so good at them.
It just kind of sounded like an act.
Well, it half is.
What do you mean?
It's not something I need to hide, but I want to be a game designer in the future.
I see...
So that's why you want to learn how to program.
I guess that's how it is.
So you like games that much?
Yes, I like them a lot.
Playing them and making them.
Have you played "Homoge Club"?
YES!! That game is godly, right?!
Please forget I said that.
No, it's already ringing...
Very clearly.
I knew it. You're Akagi's sister.
The fujo—
Wh-Wh-What are you saying?!
I don't understand...
My, my.
How unexpected.
That you would have such tastes...
I'm telling you, I'm not!
I've only heard about it, but I hear Maschera's getting pretty popular lately.
What might you be talking about?
I'm afraid I don't understand...
Don't bother playing dumb.
You were shrieking in joy those nights fantasizing about that Shin x Luci coupling.
You fool!!
That cute seme x tsundere uke of Luci x Shin is the essence of Maschera!
Reversing that coupling?
Impossible!
You fake!
Of course I know.
That's the one coupling that can never be reversed.
But...
It would seem I've made you trip.
You tricked me!
What are you talking about?
Th-That's right...
I like homos.
I am completely rotten!
My, is that so?
If you're so rotten, then I'm sure you can even fantasize about half-real things like the Prince of Tennis musical?
With the greatest ease.
Half-real or two-dimensional or inanimate!
So long as they brush against my heartstrings, I can save them in my mind and fantasize.
As an extreme example, I can take a fork and spoon and draw out some form of love.
I commend your confidence.
But do you even fantasize about real men?
I have nothing to hide!
Last night, I had a dream where Makabe-senpai was gang raped by the other club members!
This exceeds my calculations...
To think that she held such evil within her...
Makabe!!
You've reeled in an absolutely terrifying pervert into our club!!
No!!
I'm sorry Makabe-senpai!
I'm sorry I fantasized about you and the president going out!
But I couldn't hear your polite tsukkomi as anything but being tsundere!
Stop!
Don't cause him any deeper trauma than you already have!
No!!
I did it again!!
Just kill me!!
Kill me!!
Kill me!! Kill me!!
I'm done for!! I'm—!!
Kill me now!! What are you looking at?!
What's up, Kousaka?
Your sister's gone mad! What do we do?!
Tell her, "Sena-chan, you're so cute! Sena-chan, it's not your fault!" until she calms down.
I get it.
You're screwed in the head, too.
Fine, let me talk to her.
I'll calm her down.
I'll do that...
Thank you...
Sorry, Onii-chan.
Um... Sorry to show you such a scene.
No, that's...
Well, not really okay, but...
Sorry.
What are you talking about?
I'll admit it.
I was lonely without my sister.
I see.
Even with the way she is, it's pretty lonely without her.
Right.
You know...
I'm worried about you.
So, I'm going to keep sticking my nose in your business.
Do what you want.
I've already given up.
houkago chaimu ha anata shiru mahou de
放課後チャイムは　あなた知る魔法で
The last bell rings, and the magic of knowing you
tayorinai senaka mo itooshiku saseru no
頼りない背中も　愛おしくさせるの
Makes your unreliable self all more sweeter
uchigawa gara kacchari kagi kaketa kimochi ni
内側から「カッチャリ」　鍵かけた気持ちに
From the inside a click-clack, locking away my feelings
kidzuite hoshii dake bukiyou na ai
気付いて欲しいだけ　不器用な愛
I want you to see, a clumsy love
dore dake omoeba todoku no?
どれだけ想えば　届くの？
How much must I desire for them to reach?
senyou ni kaita kimochi
千葉に書いた気持ち
These feelings, written on one thousand leaves
namida mata koboshi makura nurasu no
涙　また零し　枕濡らすの
Tears, spilled again, wet my pillow
shosen koi saredo koi
しょせん恋　されど恋
All it is is love, but then it is love
hajirau kashikosa ha jama na dake
恥じらう　賢さは　邪魔なだけ
Knowing all this shame just gets in my way
mujaki na kokoro no mama yudanetai no
子供な心のまま委ねたいの
I just want to blur with this innocent heart
anata nara dakishimeru?
あなたなら抱きしめる？　それとも
You might hold me tight, or maybe
sore tomo koi kogare machibouke?
恋い焦がれ　待ち惚け？
I’m too deeply in love, waiting in vain
matenai! inochi mijikashi otome ha
待てない！　命短し乙女は
I won’t wait! A maiden’s life is but so short
There's No Way My Kouhai
Can Be This Cute