< Part B >
< CHANGE STARTS HERE >
< MORE CHANGES HERE >
Kyousuke
< BRANCH POINT: ALL CHANGES FROM HERE >
{Paper:
Report Card
[Name of school. Don't really need it.]
Name: Kousaka Kirino}
{Report card:
Language: Good job.
Mathematics: Good job.
Science: Good job.
Social studies: Good job.
Music: Good job.
Art: Good job.
Physical Education: Let's try harder.}
Oh, good morning.
Thanks.
Here.
Pass it here.
Yours.
Thanks...
Kirino, Kirino!
Yesterday, when Dad was watching you work, he tried to take a picture and got mistaken for a stalker!
Seriously? No way!
You didn't need to...
He got nervous and was all, "N-No, this is my daughter!"
Don't mock me!
Come on, Dad!
そんな優しくしないで　どんな顔すればいいの？
sonna yasashiku shinai de donna kao sureba ii no?
Don't be so nice to me, I just don't know how to react
積み重ねた言葉で
tsumikasaneta kotoba de
With all these words piling up,
見えないよ　きみの横顔
mienai yo kimi no yokogao
I can't even see your face
Mazui Presents
There's No Way My Little Sister 0000can be This Cute
どこだっけ？　なくした鍵は見つからないままで
dokodakke? nakushita kagi ha mitsukaranai mama de
Where is it? I lost my key, now I can't find it
ため息...すれ違いに意地張って疲れちゃう
tameiki... surechigai ni iji hatte tsukarechau
Sigh, I'll burn out if I keep acting like this whenever we fight
ほんの少し近く　きみとの距離が
hon no sukoshi chikaku kimi to no kyori ga
Maybe we're close? I just can't figure out
うまく掴めないんだ　あとちょっとなのに!
umaku tsukamenainda ato chotto na no ni
Just how far away I am, even though you're right there
そんな優しくしないで　ほら　また傷つけあって
sonna yasashikushinaide hora mata kizutsukeatte
Don't be so nice to me, see? We hurt each other again
積み重ねたウソでもう　動けなくなってる
tsumikasaneta uso de mou ugokenakunatteru
With all these lies piling up, I can't even move
すぐに会いに行きたいけど　言葉は見つからないし
sugu ni ai ni ikitai kedo kotoba ha mitsukaranai shi
I want to see you now, but I don't know what to say
最後の一ページくらい　きみには笑顔見せたい
saigo no ichi pe-ji kurai kimi ni ha egao misetai
If this is the end for our story, I want you to see my smile
There's No Way My Little Sister's
Life Counseling Can End Like This
Wait, really?
Yep, really!
The president really likes Kanako.
She's going to have an interview soon.
If it goes well, they might hire her.
Like another step to being an idol?
Maybe it was a good thing to do that crappy gig.
Sorry, but I'm going to blow right past your level before long.
Congratulations, Kanako!
I'm sure you'll pass. Good luck!
My sister would never say "Good morning" or "Thanks" or "Here's yours".
That is not Kirino.
That is something else wearing her face.
You don't need to worry about it.
I'm sure Kirino-chan just feels like thanking you properly now.
No, I don't think so...
Ew.
"Ew"? You don't need to—
Hello, Onii-san.
Thanks for your help last time.
No, don't mention it.
Kirino was really happy.
That's good!
Kyou-chan, do you know her?
One of Kirino's friends.
Pleased to meet you. My name is Aragaki Ayase.
Likewise! I'm Tamura Manami.
Um... I'm Kyou-chan's childhood friend.
Hey, Ayase...
Yes?
She hasn't really been acting differently...
It's the usual Kirino.
I see...
If anything were to happen, I would know.
I'm her best friend.
I guess.
Sorry to ask such a weird question.
Yes. I'll be off, then.
Yeah. See you.
Good bye.
Well, I did suggest the event, but Miss Kiririn was quite active in the preparations.
I don't think she was forcing herself or anything...
Maybe I'm just overthinking things?
Well, I suppose it's natural for you to be concerned about Miss Kiririn.
I'm not, idiot!
Sorry to bother you.
I'm out.
See you.
Nyoro~n.
What's up?
Can you come to my room?
Your room's a lot cleaner than last time.
I cleaned up a bit.
So, what did you want to talk about?
Is it that final life counseling you were talking about?
Well, that's one way to put it.
Well, whatever. Let's hear it.
Wha—
Hm?
Nothing.
I want you to buy me an eroge.
What the hell?!
This one!
"I'd Never Steal Something Like Onii-chan's Pantsu!!"
And this one!
3D Custom Imouto!
OniPan and CusImo.
What kind of abbreviations...
I want you to line up for the midnight release and get them for me.
This is seriously your last life counseling?
Yeah.
Why are you asking me to do this?
Because I want to play them as soon as possible, obviously.
My plan is to sleep in the afternoon until you get it, then play until morning, finishing at least one route.
What is with you? You'd go that far?
Of course I would. Naturally.
But that store is in Akiba, right?
Even if I buy it at midnight, I won't get back until after 1.
If Dad finds out—
I'll take care of that.
I'll give you status updates on him by phone.
I want to play it as soon as possible!
Please? This is the last time...
Please?
Fine! I just need to go buy it, right?
Really? Alright!
Sorry, Akagi. Can you make it look like I'm staying at your place tonight?
Yeah, sure. Go get that Tamura-san, eh?
See you.
Sounds like he's misunderstanding this...
Man, it's cold.
Are these all... Kirino's kind?
All customers for the midnight release, line up here!
Someone came here on that?
Um... Is this the end of the line?
Oh, yeah.
A-Akagi?!
Kousaka?!
I asked you to make it look like I'm staying at your place!
What are you doing buying eroge?!
It's a long story...
Wait! I thought you were going somewhere nice with Tamura-san!
What are you doing buying eroge?!
It's a long story...
It looks like we both have extenuating circumstances.
Why don't we say we never met here?
Neither you nor I was at a midnight release in Akihabara.
We did not line up.
Of course, we did not buy any eroge!
Friends expect nothing in return!
Customers with pre-orders for Homoge Club, line up here please!
Okay!
Y-Y-You!
Is that what they call a full-on homo game?!
Kousaka?!
You are definitely misunderstanding things!
Listen to me! Look into my eyes!
Stay away from me!
I'm not homo!
Sure, that's a full-on homo game!
But my sister asked me to get it!
Your sister is still a middle schooler!
No matter how you look at it, a middle school girl asking her brother to go buy an eroge is totally—
...possible, actually...
Why did you suddenly accept it?
This world is full of things that defy all common sense.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
As long as you understand...
Your sister plays homo games?
My sister is what they call a fujoshi.
Not "fu" as in "wife", but as in "rotten".
She can't help but shriek in joy when she fantasizes about men in love or in intimate relations.
She's all like, "I like homos! I like them a lot! I love them!"
Why are they clapping at us?
Hell if I know.
Whatever, I got it. Don't mind me and get into that line.
Alright. See ya.
Thank you for waiting! Time for the midnight release!
Please follow directions from the staff for your purchase!
Now then, first ten people in line!
Pantsu here!
Onii-chan no Pantsu here too!
The register is over here!
I hope I make the last train...
Did you get it?
Where are you?
Sorry...
What?
I got the game, but the line was really long...
The last train left before I got out of the store.
No way...
Then... you can't get back home?
Yeah.
No way...
So... there's no way for you to get back?
Can't you at least get back by morning?
Leave it to me.
What?
What do you mean leave it—
I'll find some way to get home.
Stay up and wait!
Excuse me!
Please lend me that bike!
What?
Please! It's an emergency!
I'll return it to you later!
If I recall, you were the homo behind me in line?
Please!
My sister is waiting for me at home!
I need that bike for her sake!
Stop that.
You seem to have some extreme circumstances.
Your sister is involved.
Yes.
Then you can take it.
Get on.
Are you sure?
I bought the same game as you.
I've been buying it since the first volume.
It's my favorite series.
That's why I believe!
No one who loves this game can be bad!
What will you do?
I'll play it right here.
Playing a game in public adds some spice to the experience.
Thank you so much!
Where are you?
How big is your head?
I told you I'd make you a pair of nekomimi, didn't I?
So hurry up and tell me how big your fat, round head is.
What, it's you?
Can't you just mail me about that stuff?
The server is down tonight for maintenance, so I thought I would leave a message.
I could have asked tomorrow, but I figured I might as well ask tonight.
Nice to see you up this late.
So, who did you think I was?
How cruel.
It's incredible that Nii-san has enough patience to put up with your insolence.
Shut up.
And can you stop calling him that?
Nii-san?
Frankly, it's gross.
And he goes all dere when you say it. It's just gross.
I don't see that happening.
Well, no matter.
I'll be calling him something different soon enough.
It's good to see you getting along.
Tell Nii-san I said hi when he gets back.
Hey! Where are you?!
Look out your window.
Here.
Thanks.
I'm all sweaty now, so I'm going to take a shower.
Hey...
Want to play together? It's been a while...
Hey, get off me.
I can't help it. I can't see the screen if I don't.
Oh, it's installed!
I'd Never Steal Something Like Onii-chan's Pantsu!!
This game only has one heroine, but it has a lot of routes for her.
Each time you clear a route, you get more choices and the ending changes.
Well, just like most other games.
And there are minigames throughout it, and based on the items you get in them, different flags get raised.
What's with this ending...
It's way too sad!
You think?
It's not like they're separated by the grave or anything.
They can always talk on the phone.
Stupid! You're so stupid!
Don't you get anything?
It's lonely not being able to see each other!
Try putting yourself in their shoes!
I guess...
If you think about it that way, this is a lonely ending.
I got it.
As long as you get it.
Oh, I need to get the other branch.
Well, that's the end. I can go, right?
W-Wait a second!
What now?
Life counseling!
What? You said that this was the end of your life counseling!
I bought your eroge for you!
But it's not over yet...
Fine, what is it? Let's hear it.
Is it growing?
Yeah, well, it's been nine months since then.
Remember what happened that time?
Well, sure.
Actually, there was something embarrassing that I couldn't show you that time.
You kept it a secret, and you didn't make fun of me, and you helped me out a lot, so...
Wait a second...
She has something even crazier than anime and eroge?
It's embarrassing... but I'll let you see.
I don't want to!
That—
Do you... eat poop?
Like hell I would!!
What kind of question is that?!
Gross!
But, that—
I didn't know!
I didn't know what "toro" was...
And I loved the artist, so I—
Enough! Stop! Stop talking!
Can we move on now?
What I'll show you next is the real thing.
Sure...
It's more normal than I thought it would be,
but there's no way anything my sister owns is normal.
Especially that. That album looks bad!
I don't want to know what's in it!
And so...
This album...
Take a look?
Look
Don't Look
Let's stop here for today.
Then, at least look at this.
A report card?
Yeah.
The reason I started track is in there.
Take a look.
Back then, I was really slow.
But I got really pissed off and started practicing.
These are my badges from sports festivals.
I've never told anyone about this, but...
when I'm feeling down or in a slump, I open this up and get pissed off and think "Don't look down on me!"
Wow.
I probably can't beat you in a race anymore.
Of course!
Who do you think I am?
These and those are really important to me.
You said you'd help me protect my collection, right?
Yeah...
You'll be doing that from now on too.
Of course, idiot.
I'm your brother, you know.
Not like I can help it.
I guess...
You're right.
So? Is that it?
Your final life counseling?
Yeah...
I didn't do anything, though...
That's fine.
I feel a lot better now.
Really?
Then good night.
Yeah.
See you, Aniki.
And just like that, my sister disappeared.
Thanks for the food.
Where's Kirino?
Morning practice again?
What are you talking about?
What do you mean?
I see. She said she'd tell you herself.
About what?
Kirino left for America this morning.
She was scouted by a famous track coach.
What did you just say?
She was invited when she was at training camp.
She'll be training there until she enters high school.
She said she wanted to see how far she could go.
Of course, I was against it.
There's no way I could let my 14-year-old daughter go somewhere I can't keep track of her.
I said I wouldn't give a single yen for it...
But she pulled out her bankbook.
Using her savings from working and the royalties from her book, she bought her own ticket to America.
"You don't have any problems with it now, right?"
Honestly, her stubbornness is something to be reckoned with.
What a relief.
Yeah.
I'm fine.
Give it your all...
You idiot.
School Entrance Ceremony
Kyou-chan, you've changed a lot recently.
Oh? Like how?
Let's see...
You're nicer now!
How about now?
Maybe I need to call you Onii-chan?
Anything but that, please.
Kyou-chan?
Good morning.
Senpai.
atashi rashii tte
アタシらしいって
How to be like me?
No cry yuuki ga iru kana
No cry　勇気が要るかな
You might need a little courage not to cry
tsuyogari jouzu de
強がり上手で
I'm good at acting strong
iitai koto mo iezu ni iru
言いたいことも　言えずにいる
And the things I want to say, I just can't say them
ohayou mo nashi ni
お早うもなしに
Without a "Good morning"
miokuru dake no senaka
見送るだけの背中
I watch you walk away
kiite yo sore dake de
聞いてよ　それだけで
If you just listened to me
nani ka ga hajimarun da
何かが始まるんだ
Maybe something would start
sei ippai no jinsei wo saa yukou
精一杯の人生を　さあ　行こう
Living life the best you can, come on, go
muda ja nai kono tokimeki ga
無駄じゃないこのときめきが
That twinkle in your chest isn't meaningless
michi wo egaiteru
道を描いてる
It'll show you the way
sei ippai no jinsei wo tsudzukete yuku yo
精一杯の人生を続けて行くよ
Living live the best you can, come on, keep going
nandemo kandemo suki demo ii ja nai no sa
なんでもかんでも　好きでもいいじゃないのさ
Everything and anything, you can love it all
Let's do the best we can aa
Let's do the best we can　あぁ
Let's do the best we can  Ah