I'm back!
No one's home?
You've done well to make it this far.
Allow me to congratulate you.
This is my home...
Don't be so nice to me, I just don't know how to react
そんな優しくしないで　どんな顔すればいいの？
sonna yasashiku shinai de donna kao sureba ii no?
With all these words piling up,
積み重ねた言葉で
tsumikasaneta kotoba de
I can't even see your face
見えないよ　きみの横顔
mienai yo kimi no yokogao
Mazui Presents
There's No Way My Little Sister 0000can be This Cute
Where is it? I lost my key, now I can't find it
どこだっけ？　なくした鍵は見つからないままで
dokodakke? nakushita kagi ha mitsukaranai mama de
Sigh, I'll burn out if I keep acting like this whenever we fight
ため息...すれ違いに意地張って疲れちゃう
tameiki... surechigai ni iji hatte tsukarechau
Maybe we're close? I just can't figure out
ほんの少し近く　きみとの距離が
hon no sukoshi chikaku kimi to no kyori ga
うまく掴めないんだ　あとちょっとなのに!
umaku tsukamenainda ato chotto na no ni
Just how far away I am, even though you're right there
そんな優しくしないで　ほら　また傷つけあって
sonna yasashikushinaide hora mata kizutsukeatte
Don't be so nice to me, see? We hurt each other again
積み重ねたウソでもう　動けなくなってる
tsumikasaneta uso de mou ugokenakunatteru
With all these lies piling up, I can't even move
すぐに会いに行きたいけど　言葉は見つからないし
sugu ni ai ni ikitai kedo kotoba ha mitsukaranai shi
I want to see you now, but I don't know what to say
If this is the end for our story, I want you to see my smile
最後の一ページくらい　きみには笑顔見せたい
saigo no ichi pe-ji kurai kimi ni ha egao misetai
There's No Way My Little Sister
Could Write a Novel
A screening? Of Meruru?
Yes.
Why do you guys have to do it here?
A few days ago, in Akihabara...
What, you've only watched six episodes?!
Quiet. I'm busy with my own life, you know.
Be grateful that I've even watched to episode 6.
Frankly, it's incredibly boring.
Even with these eyes which far surpass humans', I can't find anything good in it.
Maybe your eyes have gone bad from watching your Maschera.
What did you just say?
There, there, there!
Why don't we have a screening of Meruru and Maschera this Thursday then?
Why?
You two are always having the same argument.
Your prejudices might be preventing you from seeing each other's anime in a different light.
That's not—
If we watch it together and offer commentary, you might find a new perspective.
So, Miss "My parents are always gone Thursdays so I can watch anime on the big screen in the living room! Yahoo!"
...aka your little sister, gave in and agreed.
I see...
Wait, then where's Kirino?
Her room, probably.
And Saori?
Something urgent came up so she can't make it.
So basically, it's just you and Kirino today?
Yes.
I get it.
I get it now.
I get it perfectly.
You got into a fight with her.
Basically.
Mail Inbox
Saori
Mr. Kyousuke,
the rest...
The rest 'tis left to you.
Mr. Kyousuke, the rest ‘tis left to you.
‘Tis really left to me, Miss Saori?
It's more trouble than I want, but...
Mail Inbox
Saori
Mr. Kyousuke,
the rest...
I do owe Saori a lot.
Guess I'll have to.
Alright. Eat up.
Alright.
So, what did you get into a fight over?
Anime again?
Novels.
Novels?
Calling that aberration a novel goes against my principles, but your sister said,
"Oh, right. You wrote novels on some site or something, right?"
Woah, that was scarily good!
She put her soul into that!
"I tried writing one too. Care to read it?"
"Well, it's perfect, like everything else I do."
That'd be enough to get me pissed off.
Right?
So, was it boring?
I wanted to kill her.
It was that bad??
What was it about? I'm actually kind of curious now.
To start with,
the main character was a mirror image of the author.
She refers to herself with "atashi".
That's not all.
She'll start a new paragraph after two or three words...
She'll start a new page just because she feels like it...
There are more symbols and emotes than actual words...
More than half of it is self-glorification.
And in the end, a goth loli character clearly modeled after me gets raped and dies.
That's so wrong!
Wow, yeah, that's definitely something to get angry about.
Go on. Eat up, eat up.
It won't make up for it, but...
Okay.
But you write novels too?
No wonder you can point out flaws so easily.
I wouldn't be able to explain what's wrong with her novel.
It's hard to judge things like that unless you know how to write one properly yourself.
I think you're misunderstanding things.
There is no "correct" for a work of literature.
However it's written, it can't be "wrong".
That's what I think.
Everyone has a different reason for writing, so that's just naturally how it is.
There can be no absolute correct way to write.
My complaints just now simply mean that it was not something I could enjoy.
Don't get me wrong.
I see...
I don't get it at all.
Well, let me just go put this in my room.
Kirino!
You're there, right? Open up—
What are you doing?
Eroge.
What kind of host invites a friend over then goes to play eroge alone?
It's got nothing to do with you.
And anyway, she started it.
Yeah, right!
She said your novel has a character modeled after her that gets raped and dies!
What?
What's she talking about?
Here.
Read this.
Manga and a novel?
That Kuroneko...
That Kusoneko wrote this Maschera alternate ending doujinshi.
You didn't have to start over just to insult her...
So, what about this book?
"Hmph. Then while I read this novel that already smells like crap, you can read this."
Woah, that was scarily good!
She put her soul into that!
Was it boring?
I wanted to kill her.
It was that bad??
What's it about?
After the last boss of the first season, Queen of Nightmare, is defeated by Shikkoku, she gets shifted back in time to the start of the story.
Oh, Shikkoku is Maschera's main character.
So she takes over the corpse of a girl that dies in the original story and gets closer to Shikkoku as a normal girl.
What's so bad about that though?
It actually sounds pretty interesting.
What?
You flipped through the pages a little, and now you think you can comment on it?
The worst part of this book isn't that obvious.
Look at this! The page is practically black!
Over 90% of it is words.
Ever thought of starting a new paragraph?
And there are so many obscure words and idioms too!
Can't you just simply say "Boom!" when something explodes, or "Augh!" when someone gets hit?
On top of that, this doujinshi requires that you read this 200-page encyclopedia of errata, otherwise you won't understand half of it.
Basically, she just wrote this for her own self-gratification!
And what pisses me off most of all...
A loli character clearly modeled after me is the main character's sex slave!
That's definitely something to get angry about!
Right? Right?!
Damn goth loli...
Turning my sister into a sex slave?!
Wait...
Didn't I just do something just like this?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Wait a second...
Did you actually read through that entire encyclopedia?
I wouldn't be able to complain if I didn't.
You guys really are good friends...
Alright. I get it.
I get it now.
How about this?
The point of this visit was a Meruru screening, right?
Let's try doing that then.
Otherwise, it'll just be a waste of your time.
Fine, I guess.
And isn't this your once-in-a-week chance to watch anime on the big screen?
Not like I care.
Saori
Saori?
Hello?
Mr. Kyousuke, it's me.
Yeah. What's up?
I'm done over here.
How are things going on your front?
Right now, it seems the first cannon may be lit at any time.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Now then, let us begin our screening!
Hey, you can't watch it like that!
You need not worry!
I will play it here at the same time.
We may be far separated, but we are of one mind.
A new definition for "live screening"...
Well then, let's start the screening.
Stardust Witch Meruru!
Starts now!
Yes!
Meru-chan! Meru-chan! Meru-chan! Meru-chan!
Why are you going crazy right from the start??
My, it sounds like it's going well.
Stardust Witch Meruru, on the job!
Hey, isn't this kinda sketchy?
Can they really show this on TV?
This is the DVD version.
For the TV broadcast, ribbons hide the little girl's naked body.
Don't call her a little girl!
Fans went wild when some station aired the uncensored version one time.
Yeah... This is...
Kinda dangerous?
The first reason why I can't like this anime.
The opening theme is an electronic song.
With more force than (KIRA☆)
A meteorite (KIRA☆)!
She's basically saying, "I'm going to release my full-power magic into you at point blank, so don't move, bitch".
This girl can bombard her opponent with attacks with a smile on her face.
Disturbing.
Too many things these days mix loli and ero, and not just in anime either.
I can only weep over the fact that people keep buying this kind of vulgar crap.
The public needs to put more attention into maintaining an aesthetic sense.
You don't get it, do you?
The theme of Meruru is friendship.
Don't say things just because the Maschera DVDs line up well together.
Friendship?
Where in this story is there friendship?
Please explain.
In episode six, Meruru obliterates her friend-turned-Dark Witch Al-chan using her Meteo Impact.
With a huge smile on face.
I said that was unexpected!
Nitpicking at all the small details...
And besides, she revives Al-chan during the B part!
You can bring back anyone who dies or anything that breaks in the magical field later!
Mr. Kyousuke? What's going on?
What kind of a cop-out plot device is that?
That's ridiculous.
It's perfectly fine!
Ah whatever, fight all you want...
And she was saved in the end, so it worked out fine!
And anyway, what's with the constant "I'm awesome! I'm awesome!" talk in Maschera?
Well, I guess this is friendship.
I'm back.
What's wrong?
Y-You...
My laptop...
Something wrong with your laptop?
You were looking at porn sites on my laptop!!
Wh-What are you talking about?
The evidence is right there!
How could you even think of making me see something like that?
I can't believe it!
You're the worst!
Come on, don't cry!
I'm not crying!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
I won't look at them again!
I'm sorry I did it!
I'm calling you Porn Hunter from now on!
Please spare me that!
You're going to make up for this.
Make up?
Life counseling!
What is this?
My☆Star
Imouto☆ Planet
By Rino
My latest work.
Another novel.
You're still writing?
What, got a problem with that?
No, not at all!
I figured out my writing style from the last one.
So this time I figured I should just write about what I like.
And that's what this is?
My☆Star
Imouto☆ Planet
By Rino
What's it about?
My☆Star
Imouto☆ Planet
By Kirino
My☆Star
Imouto☆ Planet
By Rino
My☆Star
Imouto☆ Planet
By Kirino
Can't you tell from the title?
It's about me, an astronaut, winding up on a planet full of little sisters and doing amazing things.
That makes no sense to me!
It felt completely different when I finished writing it.
So...
Book
Up
Cellphone Novel
Submission Site
I submitted it here.
You know the light novel publisher Raigeki Bunko?
An editor there read it and asked if I want it published as a book!
Eh? Seriously??
Yeah!
Your book's getting published?!
This is becoming a book??
Don't shout like that!
I don't want Mom and Dad to know yet.
Also, it's not for sure yet.
The editor said that it's hard for readers to get into something like this.
But he said he could feel my passion for little sisters in the writing!
He said it was overflowing with it!
Wow. Her love for little sisters is already at a pro level...
But I don't want to touch "My Star" again.
I kind of feel like I've finished it.
She's acting like an artist already?!
So I decided to write something new!
My☆Star
Imouto☆Planet
By Rino
My City
Imouto
City
By Rino
My City
Imouto
City
By Rino
My City
Imouto
City
By Rino
My City
Imouto
City
By Rino
My City
Imouto
City
By Rino
My City
Imouto
City
By Rino
My City
Imouto
City
By Rino
My City
Imouto
City
By Rino
My City
Imouto City
By Rino
My City
Imouto City
By Rino
My City
Imouto City
By Rino
My City
Imouto City
By Rino
Why on earth did I have to follow my sister here to help her do research?
So, what's it about?
It takes place in a post-apocalyptic Tokyo,
and the main character goes around saving girls and rebuilding the world with them.
Exciting, right?
Can't you write anything normal?
I'm surprised that this Raigeki Bunko place would publish something like that...
I want to see what one of the characters feels for myself, if possible.
I need you to walk into the middle of that and get hit by a runaway car.
Why??
A big one, if possible.
Like a bus or a dump truck.
I'll die!
It's the only way I can learn how to convey the fear and panic to my readers.
And after this incident, the main character learns how precious life is.
And my life isn't??
Why do I have to get turned into a red splatter on the ground on Christmas?!
You're useless...
Fine then.
I'll just figure out how to do it with some pictures.
Be grateful.
You'd better be more useful at the next spot.
Hey, shopping here can't possibly have anything to do with your novel.
Have you even read the plot?
The main character starts by going on a date here for Christmas Eve.
After she leaves, the incident happens.
Shiori-chan survives and appears here too.
So you got this idea from an eroge?
Also, the clothes and accessories bought here are given to the little sisters in other towns.
It's an important point at the start of the book.
What kind of convenient survival is that??
And what other towns are there, anyway?
Akiba, Otome Road, Harajuku, and Nakano Broadway.
That's completely messed up!
Anyway, buy this for me.
Like hell I can!
And why do you need that in the first place?!
You really don't get it.
It's things like this that become emotional support in the future!
Isn't that natural, if you receive it from the person you love?
I'm talking about the story in the novel, of course.
Come on, stop complaining and go buy it already.
There are other places we need to go.
Lend me some cash then.
What?
I've only got ¥18,000 on me.
If you want to give me the difference, I'll go buy it for you.
You're unbelievable!
Why don't you have enough cash on you?
Who would normally be able to just slap down ¥30,000 on an accessory??
What kind of boyfriend is this supposed to be?
A young president for a venture capitalist corporation.
Why don't you just use him for the survival story?
Instead, you're hitting him with a car and stealing his little sister?
You're pretty hardcore.
Fine then.
We can go to my usual shop.
They sell cheap but pretty accessories there.
And why do you want me to buy something for you that badly?
Okay, next is...
There's more?
It's getting cold. Let's go home already.
Why are you complaining?
You've been useless the whole time.
Well, sorry.
I'm a simple high school student.
I'm not qualified to be an author's assistant.
What, are you trying to be sarcastic?
Not really.
I'm just a bit annoyed at having to pay for your "research".
Aren't you just doing this for your own self-gratification?
I don't know what the editor told you, but your story is just ideas out of your eroge in the first place,
so it's not like you need to resear—
Wha—
What are you doing?!
When he first finds Shiori-chan, she's standing in the pouring rain.
Pinned down by the debris, her screams for help are heard by no one.
She's cold, and losing hope...
The main character is the only one who hears her voice.
Well?
Pretty powerful scene, right?
I'm not doing this for self-gratification or anything...
I get it.
I was wrong. Come on!
Where next?
Let's see...
Kyou-chan?
M-Manami?
Need something?
You said you were busy today, right?
Yeah...
I made some Christmas cake, so I was thinking if you wanted, you could come over and try some after you're done.
Alright, if I have time I'll drop by.
Okay! Thanks!
Why are you saying thanks?
Manami
Duration
Kyou-chan... are you...
...with a girl right now?
W-Well, I'm with my sister...
Kirino-chan?
Yeah...
So you're on a Christmas date with her?
Not a date...
That shower brought me back to life.
This hotel's bathroom has some weird gadgets...
Huh?
Manami
Duration
Hotel?
Oh no I'm losing reception!!
Huh?
Were you talking to someone?
Oh, Neighbor-girl?
Put on something, will you?
Gross!
Are you fantasizing about your own sister?
Siscons really are the worst.
You're the one person I don't want to hear that from!!
I'm supposed to spend a night here sleeping with Shiori-chan...
But that's enough research.
I'm sensing danger from you already.
Hurry up and dry your hair and clothes already!
Let's leave!
So did this help at all?
Was it worth ruining your Christmas Eve?
Eureka! I've got it!
I've got a great idea!
About what?
What are you doing?
The light's are going to change.
It was one messed up Christmas Eve.
But at that point I had no idea what was about to happen...
Masquerade! この夜は
Masquerade! kono yoru ha
Masquerade! For tonight
ドレスの黒に身を任せて
doresu no kuro ni mi wo makasete
Leave yourself to the black dress
Now, shall we dance? 踊りましょう
Now, Shall we dance? odorimashou
Now, shall we dance? Let me dance
永遠のワルツ　貴方と
eien no warutsu anata to
An endless waltz with you
午前零時の鐘が鳴っても
gozen reiji no kane ga natte mo
Even if midnight chimes,
私の手を離さないでね
watashi no te wo hanasanaide ne
don’t let go my hand
Masquerade is going on さぁ踊りましょう
Masquerade is going on saa odorimashou
Masquerade is going on, now let us dance
ゴシックな夜を二人で
goshikku na yoru wo futari de
A gothic night together
There's No Way My Little Sister
Could Get An Anime