< Preview >
そんな優しくしないで　どんな顔すればいいの
sonna yasashiku shinai de donna kao sureba ii no
Don't be so nice to me, I just don't know how to react
積み重ねた言葉で　見えないよ　きみの横顔
tsumikasaneta kotoba de mienaiyo kimi no yokogao
With all these words piling up, I can't even see your face
Mazui Presents
There's No Way My Little Sister 0000can be This Cute
どこだっけ？　なくした鍵は見つからないままで
dokodakke? nakushita kagi ha mitsukaranai mama de
Where is it? I lost my key, now I can't find it
ため息　すれ違いに意地張って　疲れちゃう
tameiki surechigai ni iji hatte tsukarechau
Sigh, I'll burn out if I keep acting like this whenever we miss
ほんの少し近く　きみとの距離が
hon no sukoshi chikaku kimi to no kyori ga
Maybe we're close? I just can't figure out
うまく掴めないんだ　あとちょっとなのに
umaku tsukamenainda ato chotto na no ni
Just how far away I am, even though you're right there
そんな優しくしないで　ほらまた傷つけあって
sonna yasashikushinaide hora mata kizutsukeatte
Don't be so nice to me, see? We hurt each other again
積み重ねた嘘でも　動けなくなってる
tsumikasaneta uso demo ugokenakunatteru
With all these lies piling up, I can't even move
すぐに合いに行きたいけど　言葉は見つからないし
sugu ni ai ni ikitai kedo kotoba ha mitsukaranai shi
I want to see you now, but I don't know what to say
最後の一ページかい？　きみには笑顔見せたい
saigo no ichi pe-ji kai? kimi ni ha egao misetai
Is this the end for our story? I want you to see my smile
There's No Way My Little Sister's
Best Friend can be this ●●●●
It really is you, Kirino!
Ayase...
That's so weird!
Fancy running into you here!
Yeah... what a coincidence...
Someone she knows?
Her best friend, apparently.
But why are you here?
I heard you were taking the day off from work because you were busy with the track team...
W-Well... um...
You want me to deal with this??
Yo!
Oh, it's Onii-san!
Might you two be out on a date?
Well, something like that.
Wait, what—
And what are you up to here?
We're doing a photo shoot.
Right now I'm on break.
Well, Aragaki—
You can just call me Ayase.
Ah, Ayase-chan then.
We're in a bit of a hurry right now...
Kirino? Are you feeling okay?
You're kind of quiet, and you look stressed...
Y-Yeah, I'm a bit under the weather.
How about I have someone drive you back?
I'll take your bags.
Thanks, but I'm fine!
Really?
Sorry for interrupting your date.
You know, I've been wondering, but do you know those people behind you?
Um...
Let's go.
If we don't hurry, we'll miss the 5pm anime.
Sorry guys... thanks!
What was with those two?
They looked really strange.
Who knows?
I don't know those weirdos.
Hey, was something going on today?
Um...
It was probably Summer Comiket.
Summer Comiket?
What's that?
I'm not sure myself, but they sell doujinshi and stuff...
"Doujinshi"?
She's hopeless...
Kirino...
Are you hiding something?
Of course not!
Sorry, we'll catch you another time!
Later, Ayase!
Wait.
Ayase?
Why are you running away, Kirino?
I'm not running...
Lies.
You're lying.
Lies, lies, lies, lies!
Don't lie to me.
You tried to run.
You're running away.
You're running!
Ayase? This—
You be quiet, Onii-san!
I'm talking with Kirino.
Sorry...
Kirino, I'm worried about you.
So please answer me.
You're hiding something, right?
I'm not, Ayase...
I'm not...
You should know by now, Kirino.
I hate lies.
You're not telling me?
You don't want to talk to me?
I'm shocked. And here I thought we were friends.
It seems that I misunderstood things.
Ow...
I'm sorry!
I want to help you, Kirino.
Something feels wrong today, and I can't just let you go...
What's in that bag?
"Comic Circle Market"...
Where are you going? I'm not done talk—
I'm sorry.
I can no longer be your friend.
Please don't talk to me at school anymore.
I don't know those weirdos.
I don't think Miss Kiririn was being serious there.
I know that.
Humans are such unfortunate animals.
Thanks for that back there.
Thanks to you, we managed to work it out somehow.
Sorry for using you like that.
I tried calling Miss Kiririn too, but she didn't pick up...
She was pretty tired.
She's already gone to bed.
Indeed? That's good to hear.
Miss Kuroneko was also quite worried.
Sorry again about that.
I'll get her to apologize to her too.
You needn't worry about it.
Thanks a lot for today.
Bye then.
Do your best at training camp!
Of course!
Who do you think I am, Mom?
I'm off then!
You lose!
When she uses her tentacles, Reika's back becomes exposed.
D-Don't get me wrong!
It's not like I looked this up for you or anything!
On your marks...
Get set...
Go!
You win!
Now you can fight against other players!
I'm back.
Hey.
I can use my character against other players now.
Oh yeah?
New term
Something happen to you at school today?
Not really.
Did Ayase break her promise and tell everyone about your hobby?
Ayase wouldn't do that!
Have you made up with her?
Hey!
Look this way!
If you don't say anything, I can't help!
Shut up!
What the hell?
I talk to you a little and now you're acting all gross!
And what's wrong with that?
Huh?
I said I don't care if I'm gross!
After all, I'm a perverted siscon idiot of a brother that thinks he's got something good going on after he got to know his sister a bit.
I'm not letting you leave here till you tell me the whole story.
Wh-What's with you?
You haven't made up with Ayase, right?
How could I?
After what happened...
But you acted like nothing happened the day after.
I had training camp, so I couldn't disappoint anyone.
What's that supposed to mean?
A lot of people wanted to go to camp, and since I was chosen to go, I couldn't just stay depressed and not work hard.
That was a separate problem, and at the camp I had to focus on doing what I had to do.
I see.
So didn't you try calling her or something?
What do you think you're doing?
It's not like I can help it.
Isn't she your best friend?
Are you really just going to leave things like this?
You—
Shut up!!
Stop talking like you know what I'm going through!
Leave me alone!!
I can't stand the way you're just giving up like that!
It's not like you!
Normally you'd try to fix it any way you could, no matter how unsightly or how low the odds were!
What?
Why are you acting all mature all of a sudden?
Getting a lecture from you after this long really pisses me off!
Sorry, but I'm not going to sit and listen.
I'm not going to just nod and do what you say, like Neighbor-girl does.
Why you—
Don't touch me!
You've never cared about me my whole life, and only now you're trying to act the big brother part?
What did you just...
Shut up!!
Of course I can't leave it like this!
I know that already!
Wait—
Not like me?
Try to fix it?
Don't say it like it's so simple!
You don't understand anything!
You just don't understand!
You don't understand!
The life counseling isn't over...
Take responsibility for it till the end!
Just say that from the start next time, idiot.
I must refuse.
I cannot associate myself with someone with that kind of hobby.
Hey—
Let me ask you instead.
What do you think of it?
Though, the answer's obvious at this point.
Well, hold—
It's all your fault.
Kirino isn't that kind of person.
I said hold on!
Listen to me!
What did you say to Kirino today?
It was a futile effort.
I was her best friend.
Isn't it natural that I'd want to make up with her?
Yeah...
So I said to her,
"Drop that hobby and throw it all away."
Do you know what she said?
She told me, "Never!"
That means that hobby is more important to her than me!
How cruel...
I'm not trying to defend her hobby, but you don't really understand what kind of hobby it is, do you?
You've decided you hate it without really knowing anything about it.
I've seen it on the news.
Games and anime where people do lewd things to little girls are becoming more and more widespread in Japan.
A famous journalist reported on it.
Aren't those the kind of things Kirino has?
Well, I suppose they are...
So when I find out that my best friend has such a disgusting hobby, isn't it natural for me to try to make her stop?
That journalist also said...
People who play and watch those things will eventually have their minds broken, and lose their humanity.
That's an exaggeration.
And there was a man who was influenced by those games to electrocute a girl.
The culprit was one of those so-called otaku would-be-criminals, and he said he was trying to mimic what he saw in a game called "Siscalypse".
Don't you see?
Those kinds of games and manga shouldn't be allowed to exist!
SisCaly incident
Anyone who plays them or creates them is a criminal just waiting to come out!
Title: "Psychopath Attacks Girl, Imitating Popular Game"
They need to be regulated and controlled!
Title: "Culprit Statement: 'I wanted to mimic the game'"
This is a hobby that Kirino absolutely cannot have!
Title: "Another Game Copycat Crime, Otaku Numbers Still Growing"
All otaku should die
Make those games and manga illegal
Aragaki Ayase
Call time
So I guess she's seriously worried about Kirino...
It's going to be hard to deal with how all these incidents involving otaku really do strengthen her argument.
Hey Dad, can I ask you something?
What, about your future?
No...
A middle school girl I'm friends with recently saw a big haul of eromanga I got!
What should I do?!
Y-You okay, Dad?
You worthless son!
You came to me to discuss that, of all things?!
I just want to know something.
Please! Just hear me out!
What do you want?
So, what did you want to say?
You can't make up with Kirino because her hobby is indecent, and she won't give it up.
Am I right?
Yes. And so?
After we talked about that, I looked into a few things.
I have heard about that case.
An associate of mine at the station brought me the information.
And I also know about the journalist that wrote the article.
I just happened to be looking into the incident at the time.
Don't misunderstand.
It's not like I looked into it for you.
I'll start from my results.
At first, the culprit in the SisCaly incident did say he tried to electrocute a little girl in imitation of a game,
but he withdrew that statement later.
You're lying!
It's true.
He said that he took out the stun gun because he wanted to get violent on a girl.
It's a pretty sleazy way to go.
How did you discover that?
It was on the news.
The second article was a lot smaller than the first, though.
But then the journalist would have—
He published this apology.
"I apologize for stating something which may have caused a misunderstanding. I made a mistake in collecting information."
"I hope to inform you all of the truth with regards to the incident as the time calls."
They didn't say anything about that on TV...
I don't think everything they say is a lie.
But I don't think all the otaku bashing is completely untruthful either.
But as far as this incident goes, I think that journalist may have just misinterpreted some of the information.
And part of the mass media jumped right on it.
There's more of it here.
Read it yourself.
Lies! No way!
And there's no evidence that playing games causes people to lose their humanity either.
So could you stop referring to otaku as criminals waiting to happen?
Sure, there might be some bad guys among them, but they aren't all bad.
Kirino said the same thing.
I understand.
This was a mistake on my part. I take back what I said.
But it doesn't change the fact that Kirino's hobby is disgusting.
You might see it that way, but can't you try to ignore it?
She keeps it to herself because she knows that she can't let anyone know.
You're right.
She's kept it to herself and lied to us all.
She just never had to tell you!
And more importantly, because she didn't want to lose your friendship!
You're her best friend! Why can't you understand that?
What about you? What do you know about us?
I know Kirino better than anyone!
That Kirino is fake!
Give her back! Give me back my best friend!
Give me back the real Kirino!
Oh, shut up!!
"Fake, fake"...
Can't you say anything else?
Kirino...
Move.
This is something I have to do.
Ayase, listen to me.
I'm not listening to a fake Kirino.
I want to talk to the real Kirino!
What's the real me?
Beautiful, overflowing with style and fashion sense, ace athlete, honor student,
surrounded by friends, the idol of the entire student body,
loved by the teachers, the star of the track team,
working as a model outside school,
depended on by everyone, loved by everyone—
that super-perfect, super-cool, super-cute, super-beautiful Kousaka Kirino?
Is that the real me?
Yeah! That's Kirino!
Sorry Ayase, but you don't really understand.
I like the manga that you call indecent!
I really like those eroge you call disgusting!
I never get tired of watching anime with cute girls no matter how many times I watch them!
I get really happy just looking at my character goods!
I really like those things!
I can even say I love them!
No matter what anyone says, that's who I am!
So I know you're worried about me, but I won't stop!
I won't throw away this hobby no matter what!
I like it!
I like what I like!
If I stop, I won't be me anymore!
Is it more important than your friends?
Is your hobby more important than me?!
Of course not!
I like you just as much as my eroge!
That's no lie!
If I were able to just pick one, I wouldn't have any problems!
But I love both my friends and my eroge!
Things turned out like this because I love them both!
And I don't plan on throwing away either of them.
I need both.
So I've decided.
I am going to make up with you!
And I will not throw away my hobby!
Do you have a problem with that?
You're not lying?
You love me a lot?
I understand how you feel.
I want to make up with you too.
But I can't accept your hobby.
I can't!
No matter what!
What are you talking about?
Didn't you just say you'd make up with me?
But... I can't stand that kind of manga...
It's so gross!
Kirino!
What should I do?
What? You want me to step in now??
Kirino, what should I...
What should I...
Ayase!
Look at this!
What?
What are you trying to do?!
I'll beat you to a pulp!
Filthy!
That right there...
is the symbol of love between me and Kirino!
Wha-wha-wha—
What kind of crazy talk are you—
We in love with each other!
That's why we've been gathering tales of forbidden love!
If I hadn't found that, I would never have realized my feelings for Kirino.
Our relationship would have been frozen over forever!
Kirino's hobby has repaired the bonds between us that were broken!
We were able to become true siblings through it!
You think we'd let anyone deny these feelings?
Listen up, and listen well.
I...
I love my sister!
Kirino, let's make up right now.
Ayase?
This wasn't the time to be fighting about something as silly as what's filthy or disgusting.
I'm so sorry I never realized it.
Get away from her, you freak!
Um... who?
Shut up! Don't talk, you freak!
You were the root of all the evil!
Don't ever touch my best friend again!
A-Ayase...
I'll protect you.
Let's go, Kirino.
Just as planned.
Mr. Lying Brother,
Your pervertedness has allowed me and Kirino to make up.
But if you do anything indecent to Kirino, I will beat you to death.
I'm back.
Don't worry.
He hasn't done anything you have to worry about.
Thanks, Ayase.
See you at school.
Hey.
Are you planning to just keep my computer?
I'm not!
I'll bring it to your room later, happy?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Bring it here.
We're playing.
I'm going to kick your butt.
hoshi sae nemuru mayonaka no niji
星さえ眠る真夜中の二時
Two in the morning, the stars are all asleep
dare mo ienai himitsu no jikan
誰にも言えない秘密の時間
I'm thinking about a secret I can't tell
ashita no asayakezora no orenji
明日の朝焼け空のオレンジ
The sky tomorrow at sunrise will be orange
kitto atashi no kami to onaji
きっとあたしの髪と同じ
I know it'll be just like my hair
itsuka donna kimochi wo wakariaeru
いつかどんな気持ちを分かり合える
How nice if one day I can find
sonna hito ga dekitara ii na
そんな人ができたらいいな
Someone who'll understand me
There's No Way My Childhood Friend
Can Be This Cute
Next time: