< Part B >
Oh, good morning.
Thanks.
Here.
Pass it here.
Yours.
Thanks...
Kirino, Kirino!
Yesterday, when Dad was watching you work, he tried to take a picture and got mistaken for a stalker!
Seriously? No way!
You didn't need to...
He got nervous and was all, "N-No, this is—my daughter—"
Don't mock me!
Come on, Dad!
There's No Way My Little Sister's
Life Counseling Can End Like This
Wait, really?
Yep, really!
The president really likes Kanako.
She's going to have an interview soon.
If it goes well, they might hire her.
Like another step to being an idol?
Maybe it was a good thing to do that crappy gig.
Sorry, but I'm going to blow right past your level before long.
Congratulations, Kanako!
I'm sure you'll pass. Good luck!
My sister would never say "Good morning" or "Thanks" or "Here's yours".
That is not Kirino.
That is something else wearing her face.
You don't need to worry about it.
I'm sure Kirino-chan just feels like thanking you properly now.
No, I don't think so...
Ew.
"Ew"? You don't need to—
Hello, Onii-san.
Thanks for your help last time.
No, don't mention it.
Kirino was really happy.
That's good!
Kyou-chan, do you know her?
One of Kirino's friends.
Pleased to meet you. My name is Aragaki Ayase.
Likewise! I'm Tamura Manami.
Um... I'm Kyou-chan's childhood friend.
Hey, Ayase...
Yes?
She hasn't really been acting differently...
It's the usual Kirino.
I see...
If anything were to happen, I would know.
I'm her best friend.
I guess.
Sorry to ask such a weird question.
Yes. I'll be off, then.
Yeah. See you.
Good bye.
Well, I did suggest the event, but Miss Kiririn was quite active in the preparations.
I don't think she was forcing herself or anything...
Maybe I'm just overthinking things?
Well, I suppose it's natural for you to be concerned about Miss Kiririn.
I'm not, idiot!
Sorry to bother you.
I'm out.
See you.
Nyoro~n.
What's up?
Can you come to my room?
Your room's a lot cleaner than last time.
I cleaned up a bit.
So, what did you want to talk about?
Is it that final life counseling you were talking about?
Well, that's one way to put it.
Well, whatever. Let's hear it.
Wha—
Hm?
Nothing.
I want you to buy me an eroge.
What the hell?!
This one!
"I'd Never Steal Something Like Onii-chan's Pantsu!!"
And this one!
3D Custom Imouto!
OniPan and CusImo.
What kind of abbreviations...
I want you to line up for the midnight release and get it for me.
This is seriously your last life counseling?
Yeah.
Why are you asking me to do this?
Because I want to play them as soon as possible, obviously.
My plan is to sleep in the afternoon until you get it, then play until morning, finishing at least one route.
What is with you? You'd go that far?
Of course I would. Naturally.
But that store is in Akiba, right?
Even if I buy it at midnight, I won't get back until after 1.
If Dad finds out—
I'll take care of that.
I'll give you status updates on him by phone.
I want to play it as soon as possible!
Please? This is the last time...
Please?
Fine! I just need to go buy it, right?
Really? Alright!
Sorry, Akagi. Can you make it look like I'm staying at your place tonight?
Yeah, sure. Go get that Tamura-san, eh?
See you.
Sounds like he's misunderstanding this...
Man, it's cold.
Are these all... Kirino's kind?
All customers for the midnight release, line up here!
Someone came here on that?
Um... Is this the end of the line?
Oh, yeah.
A-Akagi?!
Kousaka?!
I asked you to make it look like I'm staying at your place!
What are you doing buying eroge?!
It's a long story...
Wait! I thought you were going somewhere nice with Tamura-san!
What are you doing buying eroge?!
It's a long story...
It looks like we both have extenuating circumstances.
Why don't we say we never met here?
Neither you nor I was at a midnight release in Akihabara.
We did not line up.
Of course, we did not buy any eroge!
Friends expect nothing in return!
Customers with pre-orders for Homoge Club, line up here please!
Okay!
Y-Y-You!
Is that what they call a full-on homo game?!
Kousaka?!
You are definitely misunderstanding things!
Listen to me! Look into my eyes!
Stay away from me!
I'm not homo!
Sure, that's a full-on homo game!
But my sister asked me to get it!
Your sister is still a middle schooler!
No matter how you look at it, a middle school girl asking her brother to go buy an eroge is totally—
...possible, actually...
Why did you suddenly accept it?
This world is full of things that defy all common sense.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
As long as you understand...
Your sister plays homo games?
My sister is what they call a fujoshi.
Not "fu" as in "wife", but as in "rotten".
She can't help but shriek in joy when she fantasizes about men in love or in intimate relations.
She's all like, "I like homos! I like them a lot! I love them!"
Why are they clapping at us?
Hell if I know.
Whatever, I got it. Don't mind me and get into that line.
Alright. See ya.
Thank you for waiting! Time for the midnight release!
Please follow directions from the staff for your purchase!
Now then, first ten people in line!
Pantsu here!
Onii-chan no Pantsu here too!
The register is over here!
I hope I make the last train...
Did you get it?
How big is your head?
I told you I would make you a pair of nekomimi, didn't I?
So hurry up and tell me how big your fat, round head is.
What, it's you?
Can't you just mail me about that stuff?
The server is down tonight for maintenance, so I thought I would leave a message.
I could have asked tomorrow, but I figured I might as well ask tonight.
Nice to see you up this late.
So, who did you think I was?
How cruel.
It's incredible that Nii-san has enough patience to put up with your insolence.
Shut up.
And can you stop calling him that?
Nii-san?
Frankly, it's gross.
And he goes all dere when you say it. It's just gross.
I don't see that happening.
Well, no matter.
I'll be calling him something different soon enough.
Kyousuke
Hey! Where are you?!
Look out your window.
Here.
Thanks.
Sure...
Guess I'll go to sleep.
I should get at least some today.
Don't be late to school.
W-Wait!
Want to play together? It's been a while since we did.
Hey, get off me.
I can't help it. I can't see the screen if I don't.
Oh, it's installed!
I'd Never Steal Something Like Onii-chan's Pantsu!!
This game only has one heroine, but it has a lot of routes for her.
Each time you clear a route, you get more choices and the ending changes, well, just like most other games.
And there are minigames spread through, and based on the items you get in them, different flags get raised.
What's with this ending...
It's way too sad!
You think?
It's not like they're separated by the grave or anything.
They can always talk on the phone.
Stupid! You're so stupid!
Don't you get anything?
It's lonely not being able to see each other!
Try putting yourself in their shoes!
I guess...
If you think about it that way, this is a lonely ending.
I got it.
As long as you get it.
Oh, I need to get the other branch.
Let Fana go
Stop Fana
Well, that's the end. I can go, right?
W-Wait a second!
What now?
Life counseling!
Wha—you said that this was the end of your life counseling!
I bought your eroge for you!
But it's not over yet...
Fine, what is it? Let's hear it.
Is it growing?
Yeah, well, it's been nine months since then.
Remember what happened that time?
Well, sure.
Actually, there was something embarrassing that I couldn't show you that time.
You kept it a secret, and you didn't make fun of me, and you helped me out a lot, so...
Wait a second...
She has something even crazier than anime and eroge?
It's embarrassing... but I'll let you see.
I don't want to!
It's more normal than I thought it would be,
but there's no way anything my sister owns is normal.
Especially that. That album looks bad!
I don't want to know what's in it!
And so...
This album...
Take a look?
Look
Don't Look
Fine.
Show it to me.
S-So you'll look?
I've gotten this far. I'm ready for anything.
Or rather, it's harder on me if I know about it and don't look!
Come on. Hand it over.
I changed my mind!
What?! You brought all this up!
Shut up! I changed my mind!
That's it, so leave already!
What the hell?!
You have me running around town all night and now you're acting like this?
I said show it to me!
Name
Kousaka Kirino
Itinerary
Tokyo/Narita
Los Angeles/Los Angeles
Flight Ticket Claim Receipt
Huh?
Are you going to America?
Departure Date
Departure Time
Huh?
Tomorrow?
Wait, today?!
Nothing to do with you.
Nothing to do with me?
What are you doing there?
When are you coming back?
I'm getting track coaching there.
I won't be back until high school.
I got invited by a coach from there during the summer training camp.
It's a good opportunity, so I thought I'd take it.
Why so suddenly...
It's not sudden.
I've been saving up funds for half a year now, money from my job and my book.
I talked to Dad and Mom too.
I just need to go to the airport in the morning.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't need to tell you.
It's none of your business if I go away.
But wait, I'm your—
Don't tell me you're going to tell me not to go now.
I've already got everything packed.
And you don't like me anyway,
and I don't like you either!
It's just like you say.
Track... America...
It's a good opportunity.
I don't have any reason to stop you.
Go. Just go!
It's got nothing to do with me.
I'm going whether you tell me to or not!
Yeah! Go!
I'm going!
Go! Go now!
Just go, dammit!!
You—
Wait—
Shut up!
Stop, stupid!
Dad—
Shut up!
Die! Die! Die!
Stop Fana
What's wrong with you?!
What do you want me to do?!
Tell me not to go, Onii-chan!
If you say so, I won't go anywhere.
I can reach my dreams anywhere, but I can only be with you here.
Thank you, Onii-chan!
We'll always be together from now on!
Go.
Do what you want!
When did you get back?
Just now...
I see.
Oh, you're back?
Oh no, I don't think I made enough for you too...
Kirino is—
Shut up.
Out of the way.
Good morning, Mom, Dad.
Morning.
What time's your flight again?
You have time for breakfast, right?
Have you told him already?
About that...
I've decided not to go to America.
Sorry!
Wait a second...
I'm really sorry!
I'll go apologize to everyone today and explain.
Why, all of a sudden?
I-Is that right?
Well, I don't mind...
America is pretty far off anyway, and you're still in middle school too.
You kept pestering me to go so much it got me really irritated and annoyed.
Even though you had nothing to do with it.
That right?
Well, I think I need to study English more, anyway...
And there's the Meruru movie coming out, too.
And I'd be lonely being away from Ayase and them...
It'd be easier to transfer for high school, too.
And they’ll return a bit of my money.
Also, Mom and Dad and...
They'd get lonely without me.
And I wouldn't be able to buy eroge there—
What have you been grinning about all this time?
It's really gross!
I haven't been...
Stupid!
Morning Kyou-chan!
Yo.
You seem to be in a good mood today.
Really?
What've you been thinking about?
Nothing important.
It's just, there's no way my little sister...
Mazui Presents
There's No Way My Little Sister 0000can be This Cute
そしていつも通り　風邪は素知らぬ顔で
soshite itsumo doori kaze wa soshiranu kao de
And as usual, my cold passes like nothing
今日も笑い合える　優しい熱だけが残る
kyou mo waraiaeru yasashii netsu dake ga nokoru
I can smile again today, with just a gentle fever
行ってしまうの　私が先叶う
itteshimau no watashi ga saki kanau
I might be leaving, my dreams might come true
でももう少しだけ　一緒にいようね
demo mou sukoshi dake isshou ni iyou ne
But let’s stay together just for a little longer
いつも話しかける　心の中ギュッと繋ぐ
itsumo hanashikakeru kokoro no naka gyutto tsunagu
You always talk to me, joining our hearts together
この瞬間　旅立つ日まで　練習するの
kono shunkan tabitatsu hi made renshuu suru no
From now, until I have to leave, I’ll practice
きっと当たり前で　在り来りで
kitto atarimae de arikitari de
I know it’s something everyday, something ordinary
掛け替えない　今日に変わる
kakegaenai kyou ni kawaru
But they’ll become an irreplaceable today
私のメモリーズ　キラキラしてる
watashi no memoriizu kira kira shiteru
My memories shining in my eyes
幸せな日々　眩しいね
shiawase na hibi mabushii ne
Happy days are just so bright
I'm back!
You know...
What?
The life counseling...
...isn't over.
Okay!!