This can't be happening.
Takumi... why?
You're in the way.
Get back to your car.
Don't you dare touch him!
Do as you're told.
Unless you want to end up like him.
Do it, then!
Go ahead and kill all of us until
your hands are soaked with blood!
Kajika!
Let's go, Sahari.
Let them clean this up.
Okay.
Let's go home, Takumi-kun.
Chapter
Eleven
Burning
Life
Are you human or a Corpse?!
I'm neither!
I'm a Corpseless!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Corpseless of the Iron Fortress
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world
My father was a cowardly man.
Secret feuds surrounding
the Headquarter's throne.
Which is why that night...
...it wasn't the first time...
...the lights were turned off suddenly.
No, it wasn't me.
It was... fear that did this!
After that...
...my father would only fear me,
continuing to alienate me.
I couldn't forgive my father.
But you said...
...you would help me and my father
mend our relationship.
Your kindness...
...is your weakness.
I will destroy that coward's fortress.
Your strong claws are...
...what will end everything.
Soon.
Goodbye...
...Nameless.
Diamond Citadel
Listen, people of Diamond Citadel!
The Iwato's gate, a key defense for
our capital, has been destroyed.
And not by the Corpses...
...but by other men!
The man behind it is the lord
commander of the Hunters:
Amatori Biba.
What?!
Insurrection?
So the hero has finally revealed his true self.
Could it be resentment against the Warlord?
But there is nothing to fear.
Diamond Citadel is an impregnable fortress.
We are the soaring birds.
The divine bird cannot be broken!
Warlord.
Should we still not tell them...
about the black smoke?
You mean, the monster
that destroyed Iwato's gate?
Yes.
I think we should inform everyone.
Are you the only communications
operator who knows of this?
Yes.
W-War...lord...
Excessive information creates needless fear.
Help.
Help!
Nameless!
I...
It's my fault...
...that Takumi's dead.
I never should have let him fight with me.
No.
I never should have gotten
involved in the first place.
Even Nameless, if she...
...had never met me...
Even my promise to turn her human again...
She doesn't... remember anymore.
A Corpse!
I beg your pardon!
The Iron Fortress has arrived at Platform 4!
The Iron Fortress?
Don't you mean, the Master Fortress?
No, sir.
They say they have captured the men
who destroyed Iwato's gate.
I am Ayame, heir to the Yomokawa family.
I have brought you my captive, Amatori Biba!
Do not forget...
that we have hostages.
I promise to follow your script.
Ayame-dono.
Uncle!
It has been a long time.
How you have grown.
And your father?
The Corpses is...
I see...
That is truly unfortunate.
That should be sufficient greetings.
So you claim to have captured Biba?
Everyone on the Iron Fortress worked together...
...to capture him.
Everyone is tired from the long journey
after losing their homes.
I beg that Diamond Citadel take them in.
Diamond Citadel's inspection requires
everyone to be jailed for three days,
regardless of the existence of bite marks.
So I was told.
You two will come to meet the Warlord.
Ikoma?
Kurusu?
What are you doing here?
Where's Ayame-sama?
Where's everyone else?
They have been captured... by Biba.
What?!
Takumi's been killed.
Nameless's been turned into
an enemy and attacked me.
And so you ran away with your tail
tucked between your legs?!
I couldn't do anything!
There was nothing I could do!
Don't give me that!
Are you quite finished?
So you're alive, Wild Corpseless.
I see a sword mark next to your heart.
Did Nameless do this?
Get up, Ikoma.
We're going after the Iron Fortress.
No... I can't.
I'm better off dead.
Fine.
You can go ahead and die, then.
It seems that I was wrong about you.
It's been a long time, Biba.
Yes... father.
You can drop the act.
I know that you're up to something.
Bring it here.
Yes, sir.
I found something very nostalgic
amongst your belongings.
It is the only thing...
...I ever received from you.
I thought I would return it to you.
Father...
...if you pity me...
...please at least...
...kill me with your own hands.
Very well.
Father...
...before I die...
...there's something I would like to tell you.
I would like to tell you...
...how I was able to survive fighting
the Corpses all this time.
The biggest threat from the Corpses
is their ability to hide amongst people.
Even at this moment,
they are increasing in numbers.
And I am able to tell them apart.
That's how I was able to survive.
Do you mean, the bite marks?
That's why we perform the inspections!
You can't find the Corpses
with your inspections!
As proof of that, they are
amongst you here and now.
Take a good look!
If you find one, kill it before it kills you!
Or else...
...you will become a Corpse next!
Bastard, how dare you aim your gun at me!
Look!
It is the sign of the Corpse!
Warlord!
Keep shooting!
One shot is not enough
to pierce a Corpse's heart!
Biba!
It was not me who killed you.
It was fear.
The Warlord has...
It is not over yet!
The Warlord himself was a Corpse.
There are bound to be
many more hidden among you!
Give it to me!
Let go!
You bastard!
He's a Corpse too!
Stop!
Everyone lower your weapons!
Ayame-dono, over here!
Are you a Corpse too?!
Are you?!
Watch out, or you might
get bitten from behind!
The Warlord was a Corpse?!
Which means... we have been
infiltrated by the Corpses!
By the Corpses?!
Is Ayame-sama safe?!
Calm down!
There is no way there are any Corpses here!
We have carefully performed inspections.
You have nothing to fear!
Well said.
But the Corpses aren't your only enemy.
Their nightmare is about to become reality.
Fight...
...my Diamond Citadel brothers.
The Corpses!
They're already here!
Biba!
This was all your doing, wasn't it?!
You turned the Warlord into a Corpse with this!
Congratulations.
Here is your reward for figuring it out.
You bastard!
This is all your fault!
Hurry up, kid!
We need to get to Diamond Citadel right away,
or I'll miss Nameless's Chimera transformation!
Nameless's what?
I told you to hurry!
He's already given up on life!
He's no different from the Corpse!
He's no use to us now!
I will be the one who decides that.
Let me tell you one thing before we go.
Why do you think you are alive now?
The stab wound Nameless gave you...
...is just barely to the right of your heart,
protected by the steel membrane.
One slight deviation and it
would have been fatal.
What are you saying?
Judging from the location, angle and force...
...it required precise aim.
Are you saying Nameless saved me?
She's still somewhere in there?
But that's over now.
That's because they should be turning
Nameless into black smoke right now.
Wait!
I need you...
...to tell me more about that!
The butterflies?
That's right.
When someone dies, they come
to take their souls away.
The butterflies beckoned him too.
Everyone...
...have been beckoned by the butterflies.
I...
...couldn't save anyone.
I'm sorry.
I can't turn back now.
I was...
...beckoned by them.
Mother...
...soon...
...I'm coming to join you.
What do you mean "it's over"?!
The Corpseless who becomes the Chimera's heart,
loses their soul and their life.
Is there any way to save her?!
If you inject her heart with white plasma...
...you'll be able to fuse
the Corpse's steel membrane.
It should be possible to pull Nameless
out from the Chimera then.
Give me that thing.
"That thing"?
Not that one.
I already told you.
The black blood is an accelerant.
It will stimulate the virus and amplify it.
Just like the other Corpseless.
Do you mean, Fireless?
That's right.
But you won't become a Chimera
because you're a man.
You'll just become a Corpse
burning through his life force.
I need that power.
It will be brief, like the
last light of a dying candle.
I don't care.
I'm going to kill Biba and save Nameless.
That's all I have to live for!
Ikoma, you...!
Remove your restraint, Corpseless.
Or you won't be able to realize your true power.
Ikoma...
This is the moment...
...I...
I...
...become the man I can be proud of!
That's right, Nameless.
Destroy it all.
Fear, sadness...
...love— everything.