Why did you... kill her?
She was pregnant...
Murderer!
The child was tainted as well.
There was no saving it.
How can you...?
Oh, my God.
Ikoma!
You are...!
Bastard!
What is the meaning of this?!
Was I... trying to bite her?!
No way... am I turning into a Kabane?!
You can drop the act, monster!
Corpse wench!
Corpseless.
Anyway, launch the Iron Fortress.
The Corpses are here.
What?
Stop pushing!
Hurry, the Corpses are coming!
We're not done with the repairs!
They can't wait for us to be done!
We have to get out of here first!
Stay back!
Are you sure you don't want me to fight?
I'm sorry...
...but some are afraid of
getting bitten from behind.
Are you human or a Corpse?!
I'm neither!
I'm a Corpseless!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Corpseless of the Iron Fortress
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world
Chapter
Four
Flowing
Blood
There's no mistake.
The Corpseless brought the Corpses here.
The damned jinxes.
I don't want the Corpseless here.
We should be throwing them off the train!
This has all failed so miserably.
That's not true.
Don't worry, there are no bite marks.
Thank you.
I wish I could have a sweet bun...
Is Ayame-sama here?!
I do not see her.
I shall be there shortly!
What now?
Be strong.
How are you going to take responsibility
for this unmitigated disaster?
This is what happens when
you trust the Corpseless!
Watch your tongue!
You are addressing the Yomokawa heir!
The people are uneasy.
They feel it may be too dangerous
to leave the Iron Fortress in your hands.
You bastard!
Indeed...
...it may be true that I am lacking.
Ayame-sama.
So you will admit to it.
Then please hand over the master key.
We will be taking control
of the Iron Fortress now.
Engineer!
Change course for the mountains.
The mountains are dangerous!
It's surrounded by high ground,
and more vulnerable to Corpses attacks!
It's the faster way to Diamond Citadel.
So much for "Corpseless"...
In the end I'm just a Corpse!
You're hungry, aren't you?
I'm starving too.
Stop!
Takumi!
We don’t want any Corpseless lovers!
Did you forget you got saved
by these Corpselesss?
Why me too?
Hurry up and get inside now!
You've got to be kidding me.
Stay back, Takumi!
I might be a Corpse!
Seems like it.
I heard you attacked Ayame-sama.
You dog.
I...
Pervert.
Why?!
Here, I brought you this.
You're not going to let them
order you around, are you?
Takumi...
This is perfect.
We were just getting hungry.
Right, Ikoma?
Huh?
Hey!
Maybe I'll ask you.
Stop it!
I'm trying to give people the choice.
What was that?
It's from outside.
They're going to disconnect our car!
Hey, there's people here!
Shut up, traitor!
Anybody who sides with
the Corpses aren't human!
They're all cowards.
Just as brother said.
Stop!
What was that?
It can't be!
Corpses!
It's the Corpses!
Oh, my God!
Open this door!
It's a Bizarro.
What?
It's learned how to fight from experience
They're formidable.
Move.
Damn it, this won't work.
It's the Corpses!
Save us!
Help--
It's the Corpses!
Corpses are inside!
Co--
The seventh car and back
have been taken over!
The Corpses have invaded the train cars?!
Isn't there some way to disconnect
the cars without the master key?
You're not going to save them?!
Sometimes it's necessary to
simply minimize casualties!
Leave it to me.
We will take care of this.
No, I will go as well.
We are heading to the rear cars.
I ask those who are able to follow me!
Send everyone without weapons to the front!
We need to stop the Corpses!
Let's go, Nameless.
We'll exit from the service
hatch and go after it.
You want to go outside?
It's our only option.
We are... stopping the Bizarro ourselves!
Fire!
Kurusu, go get your sword!
What?
You saw how the Corpseless fought.
Close combat is possible.
As long as you're a trained Knight!
Hold your position!
Well, I said that...
...but this isn't going to be easy.
Damn it.
We'll go as soon as we clear the tunnel!
You wouldn't do that.
We'll be passing in and out of tunnels for a while.
Unless you actually want to get your head lopped off.
I can't quit now!
If I could at least know when we'd clear a tunnel.
The entrance said Yodose Cavern, didn't it?
You could read that?
At this speed?
Then maybe we're lucky.
There'll be a break in
tunnels after three more.
That'll be when we strike.
Kuranosuke!
Ayame-sama.
I am a Warrior as well!
No way...
There's no end.
Ayame-sama, please stay back.
Kurusu...
We'll be able to go after this one!
We take out the Corpses on top
before we reach the next tunnel...
...and then jump into the car in front of us?
That’s right!
Ikoma.
I might be... coming to my limit
sooner than I thought.
If that's the case, you'll be on your own.
Can you do it?
What other choice do I have?!
I figured you'd say that.
Nameless-chan!
I'm sorry.
Um...
I know they may have said
some awful things to you...
...but... please save them!
Hey, I need someone around to keep
this Iron Fortress moving, after all.
We're through!
Let's go.
Don't order me around.
Ikoma!
You can do it!
We're almost there!
You're way slower than Nameless!
What are you spacing out for?!
All right, we've cleared the top.
Nameless?
Kurusu!
Who... is this?!
The Corpse knows sword fighting?!
Kurusu!
Back me up!
Kurusu, hang in there!
Hurry, he needs to be treated!
Ikoma...
You have to take down the Bizarro.
Okay.
Don't get thrown off.
I'm counting on you.
If you're a dead meat... by the time I wake up...
...that would really... inconvenience me.
Ikoma!
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
She's only sleeping!
Take care of her!
Okay!
Me too...?
Jiro!
I will... save them!
More! Send more shields!
Purification!
I will... protect them!
I will... defeat him!
I don't care who...
...somebody just give me blood!
And I'll take him down!
Corpseless?
I see.
If we had his gun...
...we could tear through its heart cage.
You saw it pierce through
the Corpse's heart, didn't you?
A-Ayame-sama!
Ikoma!
This is a contract!
In exchange for my blood...
...you will fight for us, Ikoma!
You're not getting past!
Hurry up!
Your motions are too big.
You've got a lot to learn!
Ikoma did it!
Purification!
Victory!
Purification! Purification!
Purification! Purification! Purification! Purification!
Damn it.
We will have the two Corpselesss
ride with us on the Iron Fortress.
But... the Corpselesss crave blood.
What are you going to—?
I shall offer them my own blood.
I am opposed to this.
You will not be able to provide enough
blood to the two of them on your own.
She won't be alone.
Please use my blood as well.
You won't mind if the blood
comes from a guy, right?
It's true that they are good to have on our side.
Thank you, everyone.
Perhaps the souls of those we couldn't save...
...will eventually... find their way to my sister.
If they do...
...could they relay a message for me?
That I promise to live for her too.
And even if she feels a little lonely...
...just wait there for me for a little while longer.
Fitting in with the crowd
Like a puzzle piece
Is a lie without a shadow
Forgotten glory
Irritation is filled
In a box
Waiting to start
Delusional goal
Don't be above your daydream
Smooth vision
If your dream loses its way
I will sing
I will build a bridge
To sound the silence
Rhythm continues, forever to stay on one side
Passed townscape goes far away with ending love
To undelivered torn image
Resistance is awakened
Disqualified impulse