Help me!
Help me...!
Move, Nameless.
The Young Master has arrived.
Yes.
They're approaching!
Yukina-san!
Taking evasive maneuvers!
Aim!
Fire!
Are you human or a Corpse?!
I'm neither!
I'm a Corpseless!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Corpseless of the Iron Fortress
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world
Chapter
Six
Gathering
Light
Nameless!
Are you awake?
Ikoma...
...you're okay?
Yeah... I was lucky.
Does it hurt?
Yeah.
Hold on.
Damn it...!
Why did it come... to this?!
This is all my fault.
Go ahead and say it.
Yeah, that's right.
You ruined my plan.
But... I was stupid too.
I let go of the crane controls...
when I saw you fall.
We're both idiots.
I'm sure everyone's fed up with us by now.
That's why we can't die like this.
We have to make it right!
So we are getting out of here, Nameless!
Can't we just turn back?
There is no way we can
make it past that monster!
Could we fell back towards Nagi Mountain Pass?
We won't get any speed.
If it were to chase us,
we won't be able to get away.
However, the Black Smoke is
scattered all about right now.
Maybe it would be possible
to force our way through.
The tower has been lifted halfway.
If we brace ourselves for some damage,
we might be able to squeeze through.
Indeed, it does seem worth the gamble.
Wait.. but...
...are we just going to leave Ikoma
and Nameless-chan behind?!
Of course we are!
According to you, that foolish Corpseless
girl charged in without thinking!
She provoked the Corpses and
drew the Black Smoke to us!
What's more, the other one
abandoned his task halfway through!
They deserve what's coming!
I think that's taking it too far.
Yes.
We cannot just ignore the
threat of the Black Smoke.
There has to be some better way.
Damn it!
Just leave me already.
Only the strong get to survive.
The weak just die.
What is that?
Then when can the weak become strong?
I said leave me!
You don't have to help me.
I don't even want to be saved by you.
So are you saying you're
fine being left like this?!
I didn't say that.
I'm saying I'll figure it out on my own.
Earlier...
...I just miscalculated a little.
I'll get myself out of here...
...and take out the Corpses.
I've never even been bitten
by a Corpses before.
I'm...
...not weak!
Damn it!
What are you talking about?
You clearly are weak right now.
You're completely trapped under these rocks.
I'm not weak.
You are.
I'm not weak!
No!
Nameless?!
I'm turning into a Corpse.
No way... is this the end already?
Even though I'm not weak!
No, I don't want to become a Corpse!
I brought some with me.
I'm glad I didn't drop it earlier.
You need to calm down.
You're just a little hungry, that's all.
When we get hungry, will we
eventually turn into a Corpses?
I don't know.
But...
...everyone else in my group
turned into Corpses.
I'll dig you out later.
First, I need to take care of the Corpses!
Don't.
There are too many of them.
You won't be able to take—
Quiet.
About what you said earlier...
We are weak after all... Nameless.
But...
...that doesn't mean we just
roll over and accept our fate!
Over here, come over here!
Run!
They're coming this way!
Get to the Railfort!
You have been bitten haven't you?!
What are you doing?
One of you already turned into a Corpse!
That means all of you are Corpses!
Don't—
The Corpses...
...can get out...
Get out!
Mother?
Mother!
No...
No!
No!!!
Found her! Over here!
All right, pull it up!
Keep pulling!
Huh?
Where am I?
An underground tunnel.
I'm glad we found you.
We'll get you treated soon.
What about him?!
You mean Ikoma?
We're still—
Hey!
What is this?
No way... Ikoma did this?
You have to be kidding me.
No, their hearts have all
been pierced with one shot.
That would not be possible
without jet bullets.
Ikoma.
Hey, Ikoma!
Ouch.
Stop rocking me.
Damn it.
Those bastards...
bit right through my stomach.
Why...?
Even though we're not strong...
...but the both of us are still alive.
Even though we're not strong!
What is this?
I'm in a lot of pain here, so I can do
without the difficult talks...!
Damn it...
Can you move?!
Y-Yes.
It's still dangerous here.
We need to get back!
What is that?
A fused colony.
You know what it is?
We can talk later!
It's coming!
Hurry! Hurry!
What is it doing?
It's absorbing the bodies.
Of other Corpses?
Yeah...
I've heard they're greedy.
They don't care if you're human or Corpse...
...they will absorb anything.
You said it was a fused colony.
This is the first time I've seen one myself.
Can it be defeated?
That's why we came back for
this Type 48 Cannon, right?!
You guys...!
I'm sorry.
You came... even though it's our
fault that we're in this situation!
You two are just extra.
We're only here to work because
I remembered seeing this earlier.
That's why you can help
repay us by working too.
I know.
Hit the core?
Yes.
That's the only way
to defeat a fused colony.
There is a single Corpse inside it
that's become its core.
If we...
So we shoot through it
with that Type 48 Cannon.
No, that won't work.
It will be protected by many other Corpses.
Then what do we do?
If we hit it with the cannon...
...its body will scatter
and expose its core.
That's when we strike.
I understand.
Leave the rest to us.
Nameless-san, please
stay here and recover.
I'll be the one to strike the core.
Are you going to be okay?
I've rested enough already.
I'd be too worried leaving it to you anyway.
So I'll repay you with work too!
Good job today!
That hurts...
I'm sorry.
Eh?
I'm sorry for saying
it was good that Taro died.
Anyway, I'm going to go
take down that big thing.
You can do that?
Leave it to your bodyguard.
It's coming, and it's bigger than before!
Launching!
Takumi, is the cannon ready?!
We're connecting it to the boiler now!
Suzuki-san, go ahead!
Okay!
Finished!
I'm turning it!
Hold tight!
Fatty, make sure to draw it in
until the last second.
What?!
"Last second"?!
It's coming!
Not yet...
Not yet.
That was way too early!
Hey, give me a break!
It's my first time on this thing!
It's the Corpses!
Protect the cannon!
I'll be using the sword you made.
If you die, don't blame it on the weapon.
Very funny.
We're moving up!
Damn it!
Ayame-sama!
We have to increase our speed!
I's catching up to us!
Yukina-san!
Releasing pressure limits.
It's not going up?!
Sukari, can you hear me?
What's up?!
Something's jamming the gear shaft and
preventing the pressure from increasing!
Check it!
Huh?!
That's...!
On the other side of the link bar, isn't it?!
That's right...
The slightest touch could tear your arm off.
So be careful.
What?!
This is my unlucky day.
Type 48 cannon, standing by!
Okay!
Don't mess it up this time, Fatty!
I know!
Fire, Takumi!
Hurry up!
Not yet...!
I got it!
Great job, Sukari!
Now!
Did she do it?
Nameless!
Quickly, inside!
We're going too fast!
Everyone move to the
right side of the train!
We are in danger of derailing!
Push!
Fight!
Even if the stars
That connect you make a sound
There are just dreams in the same rain
And lights are dried up
I am tired of getting answers
By mimicking others
Dawn without the sun
And broken morning
Smashed cry and dream
The ideal only has its doors
City is uplifted and drown in noise
I will still sing and stop turning the rudder
To hush silence