The burial cost one silver.
Fifty coppers for the cremation.
And fifty coppers for the grave.
One person dies...
...and it costs one silver?
I'm going.
Going?
Where to?
It doesn't matter where.
How much longer are you guys gonna stay here?
There's no point anyway!
Idiot!
I don't know what to do in this situation.
And it's finally sinking in...
That Manato...
...isn't here anymore.
One moment, please.
Oh, why thank you.
Two more over here.
Got it!
'Scuse me. One more here.
I don't really want to drink.
Didn't Manato, you know...
Isn't he was coming here sometimes?
Here are your drinks.
I'm seriously can't take this anymore.
I'm not joking.
I'm not doing this because I want to.
It's the same for you guys, right?
Who cares about being a Warrior,
a Thief, a Dark Knight, or a Priest?
I'm done, I'm done.
I'm done with all of this.
As of today, I quit.
What are you going to do then?
I won't do nothin'.
We all came this far as Volunteer Soldiers,
because there was no other choice.
And who the heck decided that for us?
"Who"...
There's nothing else we can do!
Stop it, you guys.
Don't fight—
Shut it!
Yeah, we need to work as Volunteer
Soldiers, but how are we supposed to?
He's not here anymore!
You think I don't get that?!
You don't get it!
How are we supposed to keep going without him, huh?!
You were the one who made him use
too much magic and put us in this mess.
Ranta, is that how you see—
Am I wrong?!
You're saying that's not it, huh?!
You're not wrong, but...
"But" what?!
Stop!
This is not the time to be fighting!
We shouldn't be fighting amongst ourselves.
Calm down.
Sorry.
Wait, you shouldn't be talking—
I will be careful from now on, for real.
I see he's a scary one when he gets mad.
We do need to think about what our next steps will be...
Yeah, you're right.
I wasn't saying all that earlier in a fit of despair.
After thinking about it, I basically realized
that we can't go on without him.
But do nothing?
You can't just do nothing.
It costs money just to eat and sleep.
Maybe I'll look for another job.
I thought that you couldn't quit from the Dark Knight guild.
You forgot?
Shut up.
Look for another job, huh...
Hey, hey, hey!
It's you guys!
It's been forever!
Hey, how have you guys been?
I heard you guys from over there.
Oh, Kikkawa.
Yeah! Hey! Hey!
So how are things?
Going around Damuro's old city?
I heard everything from Manatocchi.
I don't see him here today though.
Yeah.
No way! Manatocchi's getting married?!
Wrong.
He died.
Yesterday.
Woah.
I'm sorry 'bout that.
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
Manatocchi seemed like someone you could depend on.
Different from Renji, though.
Hey Missy.
Another ice cold brewski.
Sure thing!
Kikkawa, you seem well.
Yeah.
I'm in this guy Tokimune's ty-par.
He's an awesome guy.
He's here now.
You want me to introduce you guys? Yeah?
No, maybe next time.
Of course.
Manatocchi was a Priest, right?
Center of the ty-par, huh.
Priests do have a high fatality rate.
They're often targeted.
Really?
Well, obviously.
Enemies know Priests are healers, too.
A Warrior like me's nothing.
I just have to protect my Priest no matter what.
It's usually like that, you know.
It's the basics.
I-I... couldn't protect him.
He was always the one... saving me.
See here, the only thing you can do now
is think about what you're going to do.
Face forward and think positively.
We don't have to listen to what Kikkawa says,
but what would Manato have done?
It's fine, it's fine.
"Think positively", huh?
Our party has no Priest.
Why not find another one?
Find—
Wait wait, let me talk.
You can just see if there are any Trainee Volunteer
Soldiers Priests who want to join your party.
By the way, I'm not a trainee anymore.
You wanna see my badge?
I can show you.
No thanks.
But that's the thing.
There aren't any Priests who'd want to join our party.
That's not necessarily true.
Huh?
Despite my personality, I know a lot of people.
Y-You know someone?
But before that...!
What were your names again?
Sorry, sorry.
I thought I'd remember them eventually while we talked.
Sorry, ok?
Tell me, crescendo!
And this is Merry-san, a Priest!
A Priest...
H-Hello.
Nice to meet you...
So, where are we going?
Damuro?
Y-Yeah... maybe?
Maybe?
Make up your mind.
T-To Damuro.
The old city.
Going after goblins.
Then, why don't you go.
I'll follow you.
Hey, do something about your attitude or the way you talk.
Uh, I don't mind, though.
I hope I didn't offend you.
My bad. Sorry.
Never mind.
Why are you apologizing, Ranta?
Are we going or not?
If not, I'm leaving.
Oh, er...
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
Crying Doesn't Mean You're Weak.
Enduring Doesn't Mean You're Strong.
I can't stand that girl.
Then say something to Merry yourself.
Haruhiro, are you pushing things you
don't want to do onto other people, hm?
I'm dead tired.
Not now.
You're no fun, Haruhiro.
Merry was just the type of Priest Kikkawa had described her as.
She basically doesn't cooperate.
At all.
Wait.
Why do I have to go fight the goblins?
Oh, you can't? Why not?
I won't go to the front lines.
I'm a Priest, so it should be obvious why.
Now look here, bud—
"Bud"?
"Y-You"?
I can't believe I have to be so polite, Merry—
-san.
Merry-san.
Anyway, is that staff just for show?
Yes, it just for show.
You freakin'—
"You" what?
Merry-san?
You're now, you're so, this, how to say...
I don't know, ugh!
No, do whatever you want!
I'll do just that without you telling me.
Well, of course!
I thought you would.
Damn, what's up with her?
Can you clean up your language a little?
You'll defile my ears.
My deepest apologies.
It was my bad.
Why don't you just plug your ears if you dislike it that much?
Why do I need to do something so bothersome?
What about you, Moguzo?
She doesn't make you mad?
W-Well, kinda...
They're mad.
They're probably wondering what we were thinking when
we invited a new Priest to the group right after Manato died.
Especially when it's somebody like her.
Hey, Haruhiro!
Well, I totally agree.
Right?
It's true, Haruhiro.
We didn't even ask Yume and Shihoru.
I'm sure that Manato wouldn't have done something like this on a whim.
Merry! Heal Ranta.
No.
Huh? "No"?
Why?
It's not a wound we need to heal immediately.
Deal with it.
You bastard. Ow!
You guys are a mess.
If it were Manato and not me in charge, we could
have easily beat the goblins of that level.
Manato was a defensive tank on par with Moguzo,
a healer, our strategist, and our leader.
What should we do...
...Manato?
Volunteer Soldier, huh.
I know.
I know what you're going to say, Haruhiro.
Our goal for now is to buy our official badges
to become a full-fledged Volunteer Soldiers.
But it doesn't really feel like it matters anymore.
That's what you're thinking, right?
I have mixed feelings about you knowing what I'm thinking.
That's rude.
I'll kill you.
I'm very sorry.
Don't apologize so quickly.
That's no fun, idiot.
This guy is so difficult.
I do feel that we've lost sight of our goal.
I can't believe things could change so much,
just because he's not here anymore.
Don't make it sound so insignificant.
You're right. My bad.
It throws me off when you apologize so quickly.
This guy is so difficult.
A goal, huh?
Woah.
Woah, it's Renji.
Hey, it's Renji.
Renji?
Man, is he flashy.
Wow.
And he started as a Volunteer Soldier at the same time as us.
Wait, what?
Th-This is...
A-A gold coin?!
I heard that Manato died.
This is a gift.
Take it.
R-Renji, wait!
What is it?
I can't accept this.
I see.
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
You totally stupid, stupid!
A gold is worth a hundred silvers!
We could easily buy our official badges with that.
I-I don't think Manato would be happy if we bought our badges with that money.
Our teamwork is off.
It's not just Merry.
We haven't even properly talked to Yume or Shihoru.
It wasn't like this before.
So we just have to all get along?
Can you make that happen?
I don't know.
I don't know, but if it were Manato...
Yume?
Haru-kun?
Say...
...are you angry?
I'm not angry.
Really?
Did you do something that would make me angry?
I did... I think.
What did you do?
I invited Merry into our party... without asking you or Shihoru.
I didn't think we could go on without a Priest...
...but I probably... rushed things.
That's not it.
That's not it at all.
Yume?
That's not it!
Yume!
That's not it at all!
Haru-kun, you idiot!
Yume, wh-what is it?
What's wrong?
You don't get anything!
That's why me and Shihoru are like this!
Yeah, I don't get it.
I won't get it if you don't tell me.
I'm bad at sharing how I feel.
And Shihoru can't even talk to you guys properly!
I—! I'm too...!
I'm too... not good with words either...
...and was in shock.
And that's the same for all of us.
So it's everybody's fault!
It's not just one person's fault.
It's everybody's.
It's not just your fault, right?
Because we're friends.
The six of us were all friends.
Am I the only one who thought that?
Have I been wrong this whole time?
That's right.
Yume wasn't wrong.
I was the one who was wrong.
It's true that Manato was our leader,
but he didn't do everything by himself.
The six of us together did things that
Manato couldn't have done by himself.
We were a party.
I was just thinking what a good party we've become.
Sorry, Haruhiro...
Entrust you...
Manato...
Manato!
Haru-kun?
Yume, I...
I'm...
Haru-kun?
Manato...
Haru-kun.
Manato's—
Haru-kun...
I'm sorry, Yume.
Ranta, Moguzo, and I just shut you two out.
You and Shihoru must have been lonely.
Yeah.
I was sad, and Shihoru probably was, too.
But I feel warm now.
Haru-kun?
Hm?
I just discovered that it's super calming when you hold me tight like this.
I'll try my best to get along with Merry-chan.
I know you can.
I'll try, too.
Oh, Shihoru.
Haru-kun?
Our current situation could be easily misinterpreted.
I'm... I-I-I'm... I'm sorry!
No, it would be impossible not to get the wrong idea here.
I didn't see anything until now!
I-I'm really sorry!
No, wait. It's not what it looks like!
Sorry to bother you!
No way, wa— wa—
Wait...
Huh?
W-What?
I see...
Don't give me that!
When I try touching
the dry air after a rain,
like a sprouting flower,
fragments of memories overflow.
The warmth you gave this hand
led me to a future I can treasure
always.
I chased your voice.
I wonder when you became so strong.
I will probably find what I searched the vast world for
at the end of this journey.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
Her Circumstances
Also
check
out!
Goblin's
Journey
Now
serialized
on the
official
anime
web
site.