Like... this...?
Yeah.
Say something, Haruhiro.
Hm?
Oh... right.
Did you guys all sleep okay last night?
What the heck is that?
Yup. Nice and soundly.
Yeah.
When I opened my eyes, it was morning.
It's always like that, though.
Man, enough of this.
I didn't sleep that well.
Me neither.
I was actually thinking about Manato.
I have a question... Haru.
"Haru"?!
Are you calm right now?
If I were on my own, and I knew I could avenge Manato...
...I'd probably rush in headlong with just my dagger.
It doesn't seem like me, huh.
That's not... true.
You're not alone, though.
Yeah.
I'm not alone.
You guys are here, and I'm here.
So let's get out of here alive.
Hey, hello? "Haru"?
Ranta, shush.
That day, we let Manato die.
I don't think I'll ever forget that pain.
So we all have to get out of here alive.
We have everyone here now, and we have Merry, too.
I'm a Priest who let my friends die.
And we let our Priest die.
So we won't let anyone else die.
Merry, you feel the same way, right?
Okay.
I will protect all of you.
I will never let another friend die.
Fight!
Go all... out?
Go all out!
So, what with this "Haru" thing?
Huh?
She was calling you that.
Who was?
What, you didn't notice?
Repeating a yesterday filled with scrapes,
We clear the path to a hopeful tomorrow.
I wonder what remains
in both these tiny hands?
The voice I raised upwards scattered into the air.
The reality I've gamed is hazy,
and even if I can't see ahead of me,
I can keep moving forward on this long road
if I'm with you.
Connecting a bond covered in dust,
We join back to back in the past and future.
Repeating an answer full of mistakes,
I will reach out my hands to seek the light, again and again.
Got ya!
All clear.
Here, too.
Okay. To the stairs.
Hatred!
Thanks!
To the top! Quickly!
Did I get him?
No, not yet.
He's coming!
Exhaust!
Come on!
Huh?
Why aren't they coming after me?
'Cause you're too obvious!
These guys know how humans fight.
Om, Rel, Ect, Krom, Dash!
They understand our magic, too.
You bastard, you won't get away for hurting Yume!
It'll be hard on my own!
Haru!
Switch!
Haru?!
I-I'm okay.
O light, return to Lumiaris' divine protection. Heal!
He got away.
Give me a hand here! Hurry!
This is nothing!
Nothing, I tell you!
I'm as tough as can be!
He seems like a different person.
Om, Rel, Ect, Well, Dash!
O light, return to Lumiaris' divine protection. Heal!
Thanks!!
Anger!
All right!
Don't scare me like that.
I-I thought I could get him if I got closer.
That was so reckless!
But good job.
All right, just a little more.
Let's show them that what we've
done so far wasn't for nothing!
He's barely alive.
It's kill or be killed, no offense.
Merry!
Damn it!
No, this can't be happening!
This is just like how Manato... damn it!
Damn it!
Ranta!
Did we get him?
Get down here, you bastard!
Merry? Merry!
Merry!
Sorry... tend to the wound.
Just... hurts more than I thought.
Get back here, damn it!
I'll go.
He's on the rooftop, though!
I can get up there.
That dagger!
It was you!
Haru-kun!
Thanks, Yume.
You're welcome.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
In My
Memories
with You
I'd been thinking this whole time about
what to say to him once this day came.
It seems like we spent a long time together...
...but it really wasn't.
It was actually pretty short.
Too short.
So I kind of know, but I kind of don't know what I want to say.
He was friendly, easy to talk to, and smart.
He could do anything and was reliable.
I thought he was perfect.
But maybe I just didn't realize what his faults were.
He might have been hiding his flaws.
If we had spent more time together,
maybe I would have seen another side of him.
I wish I knew him more.
I wish I knew more about what kind of person he was.
I wanted more time.
If we had more time, we would've
gone through more things together.
Maybe we would've gotten annoyed at each other and fight.
Maybe we would've disliked each other...
or liked each other more.
Manato...
We've become real Volunteer Soldiers.
Back then, we didn't have the money to buy our badges,
and we had to be frugal with what we spent on food.
We didn't know if we could afford lodging for the next day,
and we didn't even have enough for new underwear.
I went commando, like a man.
Eugh...
I'm wearing underwear now!
Despite everything, we've become proper Volunteer Soldiers.
It's not like we didn't have the money to buy the badges...
...but we wanted to buy the badges after
settling things and tying up loose ends.
That's what we all decided.
Hah, it didn't matter either way for me.
You guys just kept nagging me.
Stupid Ranta!
Don't make such maliciousful remarks at a time like this!
You'll just be hated more.
Bring it on!
I'm a Dark Knight, so I'm supposed to be hated!
It's "malicious" not "maliciousful," by the way.
Um, maybe we can give it now?
Oh, yeah.
This is for you, Manato-kun.
We pooled our money with the money you left us.
Merry-san pitched in, too.
Please accept it.
When I try touching
the dry air after a rain
like a sprouting flower
If you can hear us, you might be chuckling and
thinking we didn't have to get a badge for you.
fragments of memories overflow.
You'd think it was a waste of money, and that
we should've used that money for equipment.
The warmth you gave this hand
We wouldn't listen to you though, whatever you said.
led me to a future I can treasure
always.
I chased your voice.
I wonder when you became so strong.
I will probably find what I searched the vast world for
at the end of this journey.
The gentle moonlight
We've become a good party.
and hidden stars smile.
The falling withered leaves
draw near and wipe away tears.
You said everything these eyes see will connect to one path
as long as you reach
the miracle.
I embraced your dream.
Take me to the same place.
A prayer reaching to the heavens.
The endless night is over now.
Merry, how are your wounds?
I healed them with my magic.
I see. Right.
I need to mend my clothes, though.
There are holes.
It'd be nice if you could mend clothes with magic, too.
Yeah.
What's wrong, Haru?
You don't seem that happy.
Even though you finally got to avenge your friend.
About this moniker...
Oh, I'm sorry.
You don't like it?
No... that's not it.
It's just the first time anybody's called me that.
Okay then.
Yeah.
Oh, hey, uh...
Clothes you have to mend by hand...
...and magic can't heal painful emotions either...
..that's what...
...I was thinking.
It was so painful for us just losing Manato...
...but you lost three of your friends, right?
I was just thinking about it.
So you knew.
I'm sorry.
You don't want to talk about it, huh.
Er... I'm really sorry.
Yeah...
There are wounds that even magic can't heal...
But...
But... even though it was painful to hear you talk about it...
...it wasn't bad.
That's all.
Merry...
I—
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
How to Rest
Also
check
out!
Goblin's
Journey
Now
serialized
on the
official
anime
web
site.