I'm sorry.
I, uh... just thought you two were... in a relationship.
Sorry for jumping to conclusions!
Well, you didn't have to come so early just to apologize.
Relationship?!
What's this about being in a relationship?
Who with whom in what kind of relationship?!
Huh?!
It's nothing!
Like hell it's nothing!
Tell me! Got it?! Spit it out!
It was just a misunderstanding!
That's what Shihoru's trying to say.
What kind of situation would make her jump to conclusions?
Well, you see, it's because...
I have a bad feeling about this...
Haru-kun was just hugging me really tightly, and Shihoru saw us.
Oh boy...
Hey, wait, wait, wait!
What the heck! What's going on?
For real?! Really?
Haruhiro, when did you step into that territory?!
What's that supposed to mean?
Anyway, it was a misunderstanding!
No way that's the case!
You were definitely trying to do something there!
Huuuh?!
Haru-kun... was crying.
I was too.
Yes! Tell me more!
And don't cut out the details!
They're very important, you understand?!
Aaaah! Ah, stop!
Repeating a yesterday filled with scrapes,
We clear the path to a hopeful tomorrow.
I wonder what remains
in both these tiny hands?
The voice I raised upwards scattered into the air.
The reality I've gamed is hazy,
and even if I can't see ahead of me,
I can keep moving forward on this long road
if I'm with you.
Connecting a bond covered in dust,
We join back to back in the past and future.
Repeating an answer full of mistakes,
I will reach out my hands to seek the light, again and again.
Tch.
That's it?
That's so boring...
Boring.
You're a boring guy, Haruhiro.
Yeah, yeah.
So you see, me and Shihoru are going
to try to be nicer to Merry-chan.
I-It would be nice if she would just heal us...
Impossible! Not with her.
She has no intention of doing that.
I know we can't immediately treat her as part of our group,
but if we always think of her as an outsider, she'll
never have a chance to become part of our group.
Well, Merry-chan hasn't been friendly with us, but me
and Shihoru haven't exactly been friendly to her either.
Th-That might be true.
Sh-She actually might be a good person.
We added her to our party,
so doesn't that make her a friend?
Well, having her is better than having no Priest.
Wait, does that mean... maybe she'll fawn over me?
Obviously.
That's not half bad!
O-Obviously...
...no way she would... fawn over you.
Shut up, Moguzo!
Moguzo?!
Did you just make a comeback at me?
Hey! For real?!
I can't believe it!
Good morning.
See what I mean?
She gives me that look when I'm just greeting her.
Good morning.
Hurry up and go.
I'll follow.
So Merry-chan, what did you eat for breakfast?
Food.
H-How long have you been a Volunteer Soldier?
Who knows.
Are there any snacks you like to eat?
I like—
I don't care.
Moguzo. Ranta. I'm counting on you to each get one.
Yume and I will get the third.
Shihoru and Merry will back us up from the rear.
Marque, Em, Parc!
Don't pull back from such a weak attack!
Aren't you a Warrior?
Y-Yeah. Sorry.
Damn, she's so stuck up.
You're not even helping!
Anger!
Thanks!
Ohm, Rel, Ect, Well, Dash!
There!
Got him!
I can tell I hit a critical spot by the resistance I feel.
I'll take my Vice!
All right!
Our teamwork wasn't great, but what a huge victory.
I defeated it in one fell swoop, so it was all thanks to me!
But man, my hand hurts!
Merry, heal it!
Sit.
I'm sorry.
O light, return to Lumiaris' divine protection. Cure!
So you will heal us, as long as it's after the fighting.
Hey, Merry!
That's enough for Moguzo, isn't it?
You just have a scratch.
Nu-uh. Look at all this bleeding!
It's starting to clot up, though...
Why don't you spit on it?
Also, don't be so familiar with me.
You're this close from me losing my temper at you.
What?!
Maybe it's your method?
Merry, you have a set way in how you work as a healer.
Huh?
Well, I was just thinking that
there are different types of Priests.
Manato was a perfectionist...
...so he couldn't sit still until we were in the best condition.
Who knows.
W-Will you... tell us?
I'm a Thief, so I don't know much about Priests.
I think it's perfectly fine if you don't know.
No, it's not—
We won't pry into your personal life or anything...
...but it'd be nice to all talk about
our roles and responsibilities in battle.
If you don't like how I work, just say so.
I'll leave.
That's not it!
I just wanted—
Then what's the problem?
Someone tell me...
...the way to properly communicate with Merry.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
Her Circumstances
Hey now.
Calm down all right?
It's just a tavern.
C'mon now, guys.
This place is so full of people.
Should I just get juice?
M-Me too.
What's wrong with her?
Well, Merry-chan doesn't react
the same way as most people do.
But that did hurt a little just now.
B-But, we didn't say anything either.
Maybe she was thinking, "they probably won't say 'hi,'"
and was preparing herself mentally for that.
And then we didn't...
Yeah, that's true.
Why do we have to be so considerate of her?
This is exactly why girls hate you, Ranta.
Shut up!
It's nothing a flat-chested girl has the right to say!
Don't call me that!
Flat-chest! Flat-chest!
Flat-chest! Flat-chest! Flat-chest!
They're not flat!
Yume definitely doesn't seem that small...
My breas—
What are you making me say?!
Someone's talking to Merry-san.
Eh?
You're right.
Isn't that Shinohara-san from Orion?
You serious?
That clan's famous.
And isn't Shinohara the master of Orion?
Manato... said he's entrust me.
So, basically...
Manatto was telling me...
...that I have to do it?
In other words... become a party leader?
Someone has to do it.
But truthfully, I don't want to do it.
I don't want to bear that burden.
This sucks.
You can do it... Haruhiro.
No, I can't.
Manato...
I'm not you.
Show me...
...Haruhiro...
...how our party... will turn out.
Leader, huh?
Moguzo is more cautious than usual,
because he has no helmet.
If he had a helmet, he wouldn't die from a blow to the head.
I'm a Thief, so I usually attack from behind,
but that's not an option for Moguzo.
Thanks!
Our roles are different, so I never
understood Moguzo's fighting style.
No, that's not right.
I never tried to observe his fighting style in the first place.
That's also unexpected.
I never thought Merry to be the type to pray over the dead.
But, I don't actually know anything about Merry.
I never asked.
Moguzo.
I'll chip in, so buy yourself a helmet,
even if it's just a cheap one.
What? No, you shouldn't.
You don't have to chip in.
Don't worry about it.
It's everyone's loss if you don't have proper equipment.
Once you get proper armor,
you'd be able to fight all out, right?
So, it's for my own good, too.
Now that you mention it, that's a good point.
I'll contribute some, too.
Let's all look for a cute helmet together.
I-I want to help, too.
Thank you.
Don't just stand there, dammit.
I'm not just standing here!
Merry said her staff is just for show, but that's not true.
She's learned skills for her staff.
She just doesn't want to fight on the front lines,
but she still protected Shihoru.
Thanks for earlier.
What are you talking about?
Oh, Merry, wait.
What is it now?
She's scary every single time.
Aren't we friends in the same party?
Isn't it better to be liked than hated?
I'd like to say that to her, but I can't.
If I say anything personal, she'll probably leave.
Well...
...it's not that important...
...but you wanna... grab a bite with us?
No, thank you.
Hm? Why are you being so formal?
No reason...
Oh, I see.
Sorry.
It's not...
Hm?
See you...
Man, she's a real nasty one.
You think so?
She was a little different today.
I thought Merry-chan was kinda cute today, though.
"See you tomorrow."
I'm pretty sure Merry was about to say that.
That's what I decided to think today.
Hey, I want to go ask Shinohara-san from Orion something.
Will you all come with me?
You're asking about Merry?
Yes.
You were talking to her yesterday, right?
Yeah...
What about her?
Will you tell us about Merry?
I don't think she would tell us anything if we asked her.
Then... rather than me, Hayashi
would be a better person to ask.
Hayashi used to be in Merry's party.
Merry and I were friends from when we were
Trainee Volunteer Soldiers, just like you all are now.
Michiki and I were Warriors.
Mutsumi was our Mage, Ogu was
our Thief, and Merry was our Priest.
Our party was one that had a smooth start.
We bought our badges after about ten days,
and we weren't exposed to real danger until we
began our hunt for a kobold in the Cyrene Mine.
At the time, we took how easy it was for granted.
That's why we didn't realize how much
of a burden we were putting on Merry.
She was always bright, cheerful, and smiling.
So much that our party was never gloomy.
She would heal us right away, even if it was just a scratch.
And if Mutsumi or Ogu were in trouble, she would
help them right away, so of course we had it easy.
Merry was doing enough for three people.
The more battles we fought, the more our confidence grew.
We weren't afraid of anything back then.
But the difference between victory and defeat is paper-thin.
We didn't realize this...
...and were arrogant.
But Merry always prevented the thing
that could make us fall into utter defeat.
Other parties had also been trying to seize
Cyrene Mine, and we didn't want to lose to them.
Deeper and deeper we went.
And in the fifth layer down, we met it.
It?
A giant, black and white-spotted kobold.
A great number of Volunteer Soldiers had died by its hand.
People called this kobold "Death Spots."
We should have run away.
We had the chance to.
I regret that more than anything.
The kobold hit me, and I fell unconscious.
When I came to, Ogu and Mutsumi were dead...
...and Michiki, who was covered in wounds,
was desperately trying to hold back Death Spots.
Over and over, I shouted to Merry to go and heal Michiki.
This has never happened before...
...so why...
...why now?
Hurry, Merry!
I'm sorry, Hayashi...
I'm sorry.
I've used up all my magic...
That day, we lost three of our members.
And that's when she stopped smiling.
"I've let three of my precious comrades... friends... die.
I have no right to be a healer..."
...is probably what she was thinking.
When I try touching
the dry air after a rain,
like a sprouting flower,
fragments of memories overflow.
The warmth you gave this hand
led me to a future I can treasure
always.
I chased your voice.
I wonder when you became so strong.
I will probably find what I searched the vast world for
at the end of this journey.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
They Were Called
Goblin Slayers'
Also
check
out!
Goblin's
Journey
Now
serialized
on the
official
anime
web
site.