Fire!
That is impressive.
I used their piercing guns as a
reference to invent these jet bullets.
It explodes inside the cartridge,
blasting the metal plate.
The plating melts, propelling the
bullet with tremendous force.
In other words, even we will be able
to take down the Corpse with these.
That's right.
Oh, and didn't you mention that you
did something with a sword too?
Yes.
I tried coating the blade with the
metallic layer around the Corpse's heart.
This should make it more durable.
That's mine!
I did your share of the work too!
So I'm taking this!
What? You've got to be kidding me.
Give it to me! Give it to me!
Please stop!
I said, give it to me!
Hey.
Could you do that outside?
Huh?!
You...
...stay out of it!
What'd you say?
Nameless-chan, you're scaring me!
Please stop!
Is that Nameless-chan?
What is she doing?
You're scaring the children!
Never do this again!
Got it?
Yes. We’re sorry.
Hey.
Are you causing trouble?
No!
I'm—
Make way.
Oh, did you take care of this, Nameless-san?
Ayame-sama!
I came because I heard a commotion, but...
Thank you, Nameless-san.
You are the Iron Fortress's bodyguard.
Bodyguard?
Someone who protects everyone.
A person people can rely on.
That's right!
She's real strong!
If Nameless-chan is our bodyguard
we have nothing to worry about!
What is that?
That's stupid.
Emergency brakes?
What could have happened?
There's no answer from Yashiro Station!
Have they been overrun by Corpses?
Are you certain?
Signal fire confirmed!
There appears to be survivors!
We will send a rescue team right away!
Are you human or a Corpse?!
I'm neither!
I'm a Corpseless!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Corpseless of the Iron Fortress
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world
Chapter
Five
Inescapable
Darkness
This point here.
A watchtower has fallen over the rails
and is blocking us from passing.
What if we turn back and go through Ishikori
Station from Nagi Mountain Pass instead?
That will take 10 days to reach.
Our food rations would not last.
Yes, we were supposed to
resupply here at this station.
They’re survivors from Yashiro Station.
Please give them some food and water.
Did the Corpses get you?
A black smoke...
...suddenly engulfed us.
It was three days ago.
It came over the walls.
The rest was hell.
What?
You guys are such cowards.
I'm sorry, would it be okay
if I went to the bathroom?
It’s over there.
You scared?
Nope.
Not at all.
I'll wait for you outside.
It has been a long time.
I never imagined I'd see you here.
Yes, it has been a long time.
How you been?
I can still help the Young Master
without being on the frontlines.
Did you need something from me?
Twenty days ago...
...the Headquarters were stocking
themselves up with weapons.
And not for the Corpses.
They're weapons to kill people.
Tell the Young Master that
they're acting suspiciously.
Also mention that I, Enoku,
will come to his aid in his time of need.
I don't think that's going to be enough
for him to welcome you back.
Bye.
What?
I didn't hear you answer.
You're no longer my brother's ear.
Try this again, and I'll will you.
Who is about to get killed here?
You've gotten slow, Nameless.
You shouldn't be wasting time
playing nice with the people.
You are the Young Master's Claw.
You only have value when
you’re tearing the Corpses apart.
Falter, and he will abandon you too.
Help!
Fulfill your mission, Nameless.
While you're still human.
Consider it a friendly warning from
an ear who's been tossed aside already.
Is that possible?
I think so.
Please tell us.
If we go to the boiler room at the heart
of the station, and light the boiler...
...we'll be able to operate
the central steam crane.
If we use that...
You can remove the tower?
Yes.
After that, all we'd have to do is...
Nameless?
Where have you been?
Should I go back and explain
my plan from the beginning?
It's fine, keep going.
But I hear the boiler room
is a nest of Corpses now.
If we follow this path around the crane...
...it’s a little out of the way, but they will
only be able to attack us in a single file.
We have Nameless, there's nothing to fear.
What do you think, Ayame-sama?
Yes.
Does anyone know how
to operate the machine?
I thought we could ask Takumi and Sukari.
I'll light the boiler.
Okay, we will back you up.
Will you help them too, Nameless-san?
Okay.
But...
...I won't fight together with you.
What are you talking—?
Why don't you go directly to the boiler room?
You’re going around because
you’re scared of the Corpses, right?
I can't fight with cowards like that.
That's not it!
It's only normal to adapt
the plan so nobody will die.
Stay back!
You'll infect me with your stupidity.
I can't be bothered with some detour.
You can just plod along behind me.
Hey!
Just make sure you don't
mess up working the machine.
Wait!
What happened?
Are you sure about this, Ikoma?
Ayame-sama, I would reconsider.
It will be fine!
We have the jet bullets I've made too!
You're right.
We have to trust this plan...
Ikoma, we're in your hands.
Yes!
Falter, and he will abandon you too.
I will fight.
And kill the Corpses.
That is what I'm here for.
Nameless-chan.
What's wrong?
Taro died.
We won't be able to run together anymore.
He got his leg hurt in the last Corpses attack.
I see.
But Taro was lucky, wasn’t he?
He was able to die before
you threw him aside.
Hey, you!
I mean...
...what good is a dog with a hurt leg?
So it’s good he was able to die.
Are you saying that we abandoned Taro?
I hate you.
Get out.
Get out!
Nameless-chan!
What's wrong with her?
She's just a Corpse in the end.
I'm really sorry!
There was nobody else I could ask!
D-Don't be stupid!
Y-You’re the one taking
on the most danger.
O-Operating a crane is a p-piece of cake.
You sure the Warriors are coming too?
Yes, I can promise you that!
Ayame-sama gave us her word.
Fine, I guess since I owe you.
Great! Thank you!
What were you doing?
Nothing.
Takumi and Sukari said they would help.
Yeah? Good for you.
Did... something happen with you?
Like what?
I don't know.
Why won't you fight with us?
I will.
But...
...I'm just not going with your plan.
Then do whatever you want!
Just one thing!
Stay away from the boiler room!
There's no reason to charge into
the heart of the enemy's nest.
Is Nameless...
...not here?
Initiating brakes.
No signs of the Corpses!
We're counting on you!
This is Car 2.
Kibito's team is deploying!
We wouldn't survive a fall from this height.
How is it?
You think you can move it?
It seems okay!
Okay, I'll leave you to it!
Be careful!
Did you replace the piercing gun's gasket?!
It's okay!
Let's hurry!
Hey, look.
Look how mangled that column is.
What could cause something like that?
What exactly is a Black Smoke of Corpses?
Nameless!
She's heading for the boiler room...!
After I warned her not to!
Damn it!
Hey, are you going back?
What do we do, Kibito?
We can't operate the boiler ourselves.
We'll have to follow.
Damn kids.
If this is where the enemy nest is,
we'd be better off destroying it!
I estimate 90 seconds.
Fifty-six seconds.
I've been cut.
When did that...?
There's more?
Fine, then.
I haven't had enough fun yet!
The Corpses...
She did this all on her own?
Nameless!
What took you so long?
If we followed your plan, you would
still be plodding your way there.
Why don't you get to it already?
What is it?
The shadow... moved...
Shadow?
What are you talk—?
It's the Corpses!
What?!
Are you saying all of those
shadows are Corpses?
Yeah, that’s what I’m saying!
Taking down whatever Corpses were
here didn't matter at all!
All it did was provoke them!
It can’t be.
Damn it!
Ikoma?!
Don't worry.
I'll take of this—
Just shut up for a second!
It's working!
All right!
You finished?!
We need to go!
Nameless!
Where's she?
Hurry up!
They’re here!
Purification!
Ikoma!
There's a horde of Corpses coming!
Leave the rest to me and
get back to the Iron Fortress!
What about you, then?
I’ll meet up with you at the west passage!
But...!
One bite and you're finished!
I'm still a Corpseless if I get bit!
We'll be waiting for you, okay?
Damn it, hurry up!
You're weak.
What are you showing off for?
Nameless!
What are you doing?!
You get back too!
I'm the Claw...
...to tear the Corpses open.
Targets...
...confirmed!
Ikoma said he would meet
with us at the west passage?
Yes!
Nameless is strong.
I need to operate the crane!
Nameless!
Damn it!
What is it?!
The crane stopped.
We can't go on any further!
Hey, are you okay?!
Ayame-sama, the two Corpseless went over the cliff!
What?!
W-What is that?
Don't tell me...
Is that the Black Smoke?
Even if the stars
That connect you make a sound
There are just dreams in the same rain
And lights are dried up
I am tired of getting answers
By mimicking others
Dawn without the sun
And broken morning
Smashed cry and dream
The ideal only has its doors
City is uplifted and drown in noise
I will still sing and stop turning the rudder
To hush silence