Sorry, could you wait a second?
You want to try, Shihoru?
Eh?
No, I-I can't...
It's okay, they won't hurt.
You okay?
Y-Yes!
Um, thank you.
I'm glad.
Eh?
I finally got to talk to you.
You want some, too?
You like animals?
Yeah.
Let's go back.
Oh... okay!
Repeating a yesterday filled with scrapes,
We clear the path to a hopeful tomorrow.
I wonder what remains
in both these tiny hands?
The voice I raised upwards scattered into the air.
The reality I've gamed is hazy,
and even if I can't see ahead of me,
I can keep moving forward on this long road
if I'm with you.
Connecting a bond covered in dust,
We join back to back in the past and future.
Repeating an answer full of mistakes,
I will reach out my hands to seek the light, again and again.
Fight!
Go all out!
What does that even mean?
Who knows...
I feel like I've heard it before, though...
I feel like that too.
I wonder why.
Ranta! One's heading your way!
I know, you don't have to tell me!
C'mon, Anger!
That's Ranta's new skill.
Wh— You're no ordinary goblin, are you!
It's obviously just an ordinary goblin.
Ranta wasn't the only one who learned a new skill.
We all learned a new skill from our respective guilds.
But since they're new skills, we don't have
the confidence to use them in a real fight.
But if we don't try them,
we'll never be able to make use of them.
Really!
What are you doing?!
There!
Yume's new skill, Diagonal Cross.
Yume chose to learn a skill for a
short-range weapon rather than for a bow.
Take that!
Now!
Back Stab.
Wait, did I hit a vital spot?
I'll deal the final blow!
Maybe I didn't.
All right!
I got another Vice!
Dark Knights are such savages.
I think that every battle.
I'm not a savage!
Say "atrocious," it's more elegant.
We atrocious Dark Knights serve the Dark God, Skullhell-sama!
We're cold and ruthless knights having neither blood nor tears!
Ohm, Rel, Ect, Well, Dash!
Shadow Beat Magic.
Mages can use the power from
magical beings called "elementals."
Shihoru decided to learn how to use shadow elementals.
Smash.
Those in the Priest Guild can't use weapons with a blade.
In our party, Manato is both healer and vanguard,
so this is a critical skill for him to have.
Hatred!
Good, they've locked blades.
Moguzo has the advantage now.
This is Moguzo's new skill, Wind.
Go, Moguzo!
Thanks!
Rage Blow, or the Thanks Slash.
For some reason, he always says "thanks!" so we call it that.
Like the name suggests, its strength is nothing to underestimate.
Woohoo!
All right!
With this I get my third Vice!
This will power up my daemon!
Now it'll whisper to enemies and lower their defenses!
Only if it feels like it, though!
Dark Knight daemons are so useless.
Hey, I can't let that slide, Haruhiro.
Stop dissing my buddy, Zodiaco!
I'll curse you!
Ranta named his daemon "Zodiaco."
No, I think his proper name is "Zodiac"
and his nickname is "Zodiaco."
In any case it doesn't really matter.
Zodiaco is kinda cute, which is
the complete opposite of his owner.
Really?
I'm not his owner!
You can't own a daemon, you know!
It's more like Zodiaco's possessing me!
I couldn't care less in any case.
Truly.
Manato?
Oh, I need to pray.
White God Elhit-chan, thanks for everything.
Here's some of my food...
...so please keep watching over me.
Is that a Hunter Guild practice?
Yeah.
Elhit-chan protects Hunters, so we
can be safe while hunting and stuff.
Still, you call him with "chan"?
Yup.
White God Elhit-chan, you know, is a very huge wolf.
And he has a big heart, so I don't think
he would get mad because of that.
I actually haven't gotten scolded before.
I think your God understands your feelings, Yume.
And I think that feelings are really important.
I have lots and lots of feelings.
At night we all go to sleep, yeah?
And when I'm sleeping, I dream about Elhit-chan a lot.
Then I ask Elhit-chan, "Can I ride on your back?"
and Elhit-chan takes off and runs, super fast.
And I'm like, "Woah, this is so cool!"
There better be a point to this story.
I've been patiently listening to you until now,
so I'll whack you if there isn't a really good point.
A point?
There isn't one.
Are you stupid?!
Don't go rambling on if there's no point to what you're saying!
I was just thinking what a good party we've become.
We can now usually defeat three goblins at a time.
If we change our strategy, maybe we can do four.
Moguzo is our reliable shield, like a defensive tank.
He's big, strong, and overpowers our enemies.
His sword strikes accurately, and he
makes good attacks when needed.
I agree, Moguzo's really good with his hands.
Y-You think so?
I don't know why, but I like doing detailed work.
Ow!
It doesn't fit you.
You're amazing too, Ranta.
Especially how you're always ready to attack.
The rest of us are more on the careful side.
If you weren't here, there would have been times
when we wouldn't have been able to advance.
O-Oh...
W-Well, yeah.
It doesn't fit you too, Ranta.
Oh, shut it!
And Yume, you're never afraid.
Out of all of us, you're probably the bravest one here.
I need to be cautious as the healer, but if anything were
to happen, I know that you'll always be there to help.
The bravest?
I guess there aren't many things I'm afraid of.
I hope you'll be patient with
a Hunter who's not great with a bow.
Everybody has things they aren't good at or can't do.
We cover each other's weakness.
That's what a party's for.
Yup.
And Shihoru...
Shihoru is always aware of her surroundings.
Shadow magic mostly has spells
to confuse and bind enemies, right?
These can be used to help friends if need be.
You learned shadow magic because
you want to be able to help, right?
Yes.
We've been here for a while, huh.
Let's start our afternoon work.
Yeah.
All right!
What about me, Manato?
Oh well, I can ask him anytime.
There are many other chances to ask.
Or... so I thought.
Haruhiro!
Ow.
Ouch.
Haru-kun!
It really hurts.
I can't breathe.
Stay back!
Ow ow ow!
O Light, return to Lumiares' divine protection. Cure!
Shit!
Shihoru, fall back!
Okay!
Moguzo, another one's coming.
Retreat for now!
This way!
Are you okay, Haruhiro?
Your idea to map out this place... came in handy, huh.
Manato?
I'm fine.
Eh?
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
Sky Dancing
with Ash
Manato?
Manato!
What are you doing, hurry and use your magic!
Magic is...
You can't use it?
Is that it?
I-If you meditate for a while—
This isn't the time for that!
Manato...
Tell us, Manato!
What should we do?!
Manato!
Haru...
...hiro...
Sor... ry...
Why are you apologizing?
What, Manato? What?!
Entrust you...
Entrust me?
Entrust me what?!
Manato!
You have to tell me or I won't know!
Manato.
Manato!
Manato, no way!
W-We have to stop the blood.
And do mouth-to-mouth!
Lay him down! Gently!
Pull out the arrow!
Ready? I'm taking it out.
Gently!
Ready, pull!
I beg of you.
I beg of you!
Please save Manato!
I'll do anything!
So please!
I beg you!
Please. Please!
Please...
What?
Why?!
No one can bring the dead back to life.
Manato, how could you be so foolish?
A youth who showed such promise.
Alas, your life has fallen away.
You bastard, don't mess with me!
Stop!
This... must be some a mistake.
Yes, we let our guard down a little back there.
But...
But, we managed to scrape by today, too.
Haruhiro...?
And Manato...
M-Manato s-said that it was scary and d-dangerous...
...and t-together we t-thought about
how we could do better... and then...
...if we can overcome this, we can keep moving forward.
And then we can... continue again... tomorrow—!
You must give him a proper funeral.
Because of the curse of No Life King, those who are not
buried properly in these borderlands turn into his servants.
Wh-What the heck is that?!
You have five days at most.
There have been instances when
they become moving corpses at three.
That means...
I am sure nobody wishes...
...to see a comrade in that state.
That means...
That means... we have to... c-cremate... Manato?
Correct.
And that too...
...costs money, I presume.
If you don't have the funds, I will pay it.
No!
No need.
Manato is my...
...is our...
...friend.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
Crying Doesn't Mean You're Weak.
Enduring Doesn't Mean You're Strong.
Also
check
out!
Goblin's
Journey
Now
serialized
on the
official
anime
web
site.