Moguzo, they had them.
Breakfast will be a feast.
You really like cooking, huh.
You're not even on breakfast duty.
Do you like making or eating food better?
Hm...
Oh no!
I like both, I guess.
I think I liked cooking for people.
Aside from whether or not it made them happy.
What are you talking about?
Everyone's happy with your cooking.
Your cooking tastes really good.
Really?
Yeah.
Thanks.
I'll go wake everyone up.
Repeating a yesterday filled with scrapes,
We clear the path to a hopeful tomorrow.
I wonder what remains
in both these tiny hands?
The voice I raised upwards scattered into the air.
The reality I've gamed is hazy,
and even if I can't see ahead of me,
I can keep moving forward on this long road
if I'm with you.
Connecting a bond covered in dust,
We join back to back in the past and future.
Repeating an answer full of mistakes,
I will reach out my hands to seek the light, again and again.
Sorry.
We're very sorry.
What? It was an accident.
An unfortunate accident!
How does a wall just break?
How... the heck am I supposed to know?
What did you say?!
Idiot, leave it!
Just apologize!
It's not like we saw anything.
Quit fussing.
You were trying to!
That's a crime!
I'll call the police!
There ain't any in this town!
Why did you bring your hand towels in with you, anyway?
You're not supposed to.
Just a little more and... damn.
How do you know this?
Huh?
It... It's not like I-I'd want to l-look at a flat-chested girl like you!
Don't call me flat-chested!
Tell the truth. I won't get mad if you say it now.
You won't?
Well, you know...
...when I tried to climb the bath house wall, it broke.
It just means we were too inexperienced.
The wall and us.
Y-You said you wouldn't get mad!
I-I didn't see anything anyway.
I'm never going to talk to you again!
Everyone's in a bad mood.
It's still a little warm.
We might catch up to them.
Found them.
Two... no, maybe three.
It's not a lone poplin, huh.
I think you mean "goblin" not "poplin."
Yeah.
Let's go back.
It might take a while for Shihoru.
No, I'm really sorry.
Maybe it's okay if it's you.
I'm not saying it would be okay if it were you who saw.
It's just that even if you did, you would apologize...
But it's not that just because you apologized, it's okay either...
What's seen is seen...
You're just repeating "seen" a lot...
Then, what's okay?
I'm not the person to ask...
Umm...
But, it wasn't right, huh.
Yeah.
It wasn't right, Haru-kun.
S-Sorry.
So what will we do?
"What to do"?
All we can do is go back to Ortana.
Gray pains but all for vain, huh.
You meant, "great pains but all in vain," right?
Huh?
Did I remember it wrong?
It happens.
No earnings today.
The next day...
...the day after...
...and the day after that...
...we barely earned anything.
When I say barely, I mean close to nothing.
Well, to be honest, we made nothing.
The clothes we started off with quickly began to wear down.
Well, they weren't made to withstand
hiking mountain trails and fighting goblins.
So we do what we can to make them last, but...
I'd give anything for new underwear...
But the clothes in this world are expensive.
At least, because we're so poor we can't buy anything.
We can't even buy underwear.
So at night, we wash them and sleep without them.
Then in the morning, we put them on under our equipment.
It's better than no underwear at all.
All right!
My goal tomorrow is to defeat a goblin and buy new underwear.
Oh, sorry.
I'm done now.
I smelled a faintly sweet scent.
Wait.
We have been going without underwear...
...and the girls?
Oh no.
I'll sink down to Ranta's level.
Oh... I'm, uh...
Good night, Haru-kun.
G-Good night.
Not good.
It's not good if they're dressed like that.
It's just too much if they wander around the lodging like that.
Too much. It's just too much!
They're too vulnerable!
Th-This isn't good, I'll really be on the same—
What're doing, Haruhiro?
No. Nothing.
The heck.
It's this rain.
Nothing's going to dry even if you wash them.
Why don't you wash stuff tomorrow?
I don't know if the rain will let up tomorrow.
You're the one who told me to wash my clothes
once in a while 'cause they stink, Parupiro.
What I'm trying to say is, I regret washing my stuff today.
Yeah.
I can't let King Shameless here get near the girls right now.
This sense of duty drove me to act.
I guess you're right. It's a pain, anyway.
Yeah. Right?
I was thinking maybe the girls were there, muhaha.
Don't "muhaha" me.
That was close.
The way they're dressed is too tempting.
I've got to tell them.
Or should I...?
No! I'll tell them.
This is Damuro.
They say it was the second city of the Arabakia Kingdom.
It was much bigger city than Ortana.
Currently Damuro was a base for goblins.
Goblins found near the new city area are numerous and strong.
Too difficult for us to defeat.
That's why we're going to the old city area
to target goblins separated from their groups.
That said, compared to the forest, we have
more encounters, so it's still dangerous.
One goblin. Looks like sleeping.
All right. Let's do it.
Moguzo's armor will make sound,
so Haruhiro, Ranta, and I will approach first.
If we can close in on the goblin without
waking him, the three of us will finish him.
If we wake him, Yume, use your bow.
Shihoru, back us up with magic from a distance.
Moguzo, you'll run to the front.
If it becomes a head-on fight,
we'll use the same formation as before.
We'll surround him, so he can't get away.
Don't back away!
Dammit!
Is it dead?
It's so easy... to attack them in their sleep.
I need to get a claw or something.
Vice, Vice.
Wow, this is our best record yet.
It's only our second time, though.
Four silvers.
Woah...
It's not over yet.
We were lucky that it was easy today,
but it won't always be like this.
Keep your guard up and look for our next target.
C'mon, don't be such a killjoy.
We just had a huge win, thanks to me!
We should celebrate these times!
You're right.
I don't mind enjoying it.
You were a big help, too.
Right?
Didn't I really seem like a Dark Knight
when I wore a cruel smile as I stabbed the gob?
No, you were just as worked up as usual.
Idiot!
I got him good without a hitch!
Where are your eyes?
Oh, I see them, right there!
Your eyes are such small slits, I barely noticed them!
Really, this again?
At least react to it!
Just say something, you gonna leave me hanging?!
How many times is it now?
It's getting annoying!
We defeated an enemy.
And earned money.
Party's mood lightened again.
Everybody was probably on edge,
because they were worried, too.
Before we know it, maybe we'll be thinking
and acting like Volunteer Soldiers.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
Are Goblin Pouches Filled with Our Dreams?
After that, we targeted lone goblins and defeated them.
In Damuro, we sometimes encountered groups of five or more.
A pair was hard enough, so five was out of the question.
But still, we enjoyed the task of walking
around the old town and sketching out a map.
We'd go explore places we hadn't been to yet.
With that, we had a goal set,
so we learned our way around, too.
We'd get nervous when we stepped into new areas.
And we felt a little better in places we had mapped already.
That'll be thirty coppers.
Thirty?
Aren't these secondhand?
I'd consider it for fifteen coppers.
Brand new, it'd go for a hundred coppers.
Twenty-eight coppers.
I'd go as far as twenty coppers.
I still have other things to buy.
Twenty-five coppers.
I can't go lower than that.
I'll take it.
Hurray!
Wow! This is so freakin' good!
What's it called again?
It's soruzo, right?
Yum, soruzo's so good!
Can we get another order?
Comin' right up!
Shihoru?
S-Sorry...
I'm... still not...
Hm?
Did you actually want him to talk to you?
There were a lot of nicks in the blade, huh.
You noticed?
Before anything else, I've got to
keep my weapons in good condition.
Or else I feel uneasy.
Yeah, I get that.
With thoughts like these, do you think we've become influenced by Volunteer Soldiers too much?
Influenced or not...
...we are Volunteer Soldiers, you know.
Just trainees, though.
Oh, nice.
Ranta-kun kept haggling, so it was pretty hectic.
Stupid, it's common sense to haggle.
That was nothing.
There's too much, the food's going
to go bad before we can finish it.
If it rots, I'll give it to you.
It's okay to buy weapons, clothes, and food...
...but I was thinking we could keep spending to
a minimum, so we could try learning new skills.
Are you sure about that?
If I sharpen my Dark Knight blade skills,
it might be too much to handle!
Whatever, you only have one skill right now.
Shut up!
I'm going to polish up that one skill all the way!
Until it shines with dark light!
Did you buy that, too?
Oh, I made this.
You carved that?
You're more deft than you look, Moguzo.
You could sell that.
Oh, that wasn't my intention...
Carving's relaxing for me.
Oh...
Yume and them might like it.
What made you think of Yume just now?
Shut up.
I just thought they might like it.
You know what Haru-kun said?
"If we earn a little extra...
...wouldn't that be nice to have
clothes for wearing indoors, too?"
Yeah.
That... would be nice.
Right?
Yeah.
Shihoru, that hair clip is super cute.
Eh?
Y-You... think so?
Shihoru, I know you haven't been
talking to the guys this whole time.
But I think it's about time that you could try, just a little bit.
Yeah.
I'll try.
Well, you don't have to try.
But, I get worried when you're always quiet, too.
I'll try.
Sorry...
I'm not too good with words.
Manato?
Er, thanks.
That was unexpected.
S-Sorry.
I was actually about to say something completely different.
What's up with that?
I'm the one who is grateful.
You're grateful?
Why?
That's because... you're all willing to be my friends.
For that, I'm grateful.
It sounds a little fake when I say it like this.
No, I believe you.
But...
How do I say this...
You're the one who's been helping us.
If you weren't here, we'd be in bad shape.
Worst case, we might not even be alive.
Same goes here.
If you guys weren't here, I don't know
what would have happened to me.
You can't live in this world alone, no matter how you look at it.
Don't you... uh...
I don't want you to take this the wrong way...
...but don't you think you could
have made a lot of other friends?
You could just ask for a favor and
see if you could join their party.
I didn't think of that.
I don't think I like that kind of thing.
To ask others for favors.
Maybe I was bad at dealing with hierarchical relationships.
I probably was, too.
I kind of feel like... I'm not the kind of
person people usually treat as a friend.
I don't think...
...that's true.
That's just what I think, but I can't back it up.
It's true that I only know the Manato in this world.
But...
It doesn't matter what you were like before.
Nobody cares.
The Manato in this world is our friend and leader.
We need you here.
Let's sleep.
We have an early day tomorrow.
Yeah.
I wasn't sure if I wanted to see the
expression on his face right now.
Day twenty-three in Grimgar.
I've gotten used to the red moon.
People can get used to any kind of environment.
.At least...
...I think so.
When I try touching
the dry air after a rain,
like a sprouting flower,
fragments of memories overflow.
The warmth you gave this hand
led me to a future I can treasure
always.
I chased your voice.
I wonder when you became so strong.
I will probably find what I searched the vast world for
at the end of this journey.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
Sky Dancing
with Ash
Also
check
out!
Goblin's
Journey
Now
serialized
on the
official
anime
web
site.