Oh yeah.
We decided to take the day off.
Repeating a yesterday filled with scrapes,
We clear the path to a hopeful tomorrow.
I wonder what remains
in both these tiny hands?
The voice I raised upwards scattered into the air.
The reality I've gamed is hazy,
and even if I can't see ahead of me,
I can keep moving forward on this long road
if I'm with you.
Connecting a bond covered in dust,
We join back to back in the past and future.
Repeating an answer full of mistakes,
I will reach out my hands to seek the light, again and again.
After talking it over, we all decided to take the day off today.
We had a lot going on until yesterday...
...and it feels like...
...a good time to take, like, a breather.
But, I wonder what this strange feeling is.
What do I usually do on days off?
A day off, huh.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Now that I actually get a break, I feel a little off.
Ranta-kun went out early this morning.
Really?
That's unexpected.
There are those people who get up
earlier when they don't have to work.
Oh, he's one of them.
This bread's so good!
I don't have the timing down yet.
I'm supposed to change the temperature in between...
...but it's hard with logs.
It's our day off.
You don't have to worry about cooking duty.
Not that I don't appreciate it.
It's fine.
I happened to be hungry, too.
Where did Ranta go?
He had his fishing rod with him.
What about Yume and Shihoru?
I haven't seen them all morning...
Maybe they're still in their room.
They probably stayed up late...
...since Shihoru was crying a lot.
She and Yume probably talked about Manato.
What about you, Moguzo?
Me?
Well...
I'm thinking of taking my armor in to get fixed.
It got pretty damaged in our last fight.
My weapon was beat up, too.
I left it to get sharpened.
Oh, I need to go pick it up!
Isn't that what you usually do?
We hardly get days off.
What are you going to do, Haruhiro?
Me?
Me, huh...
We're all meeting at Shelly's Tavern in the evening, right?
Yeah.
What should I do?
Shihoru, I didn't know you were up, too.
You... like birds?
I guess... it's just become a habit of mine.
Hmm...
Oh, Moguzo baked this new bread.
It smelled good.
Even from here?
Yeah.
I see.
We all watched the sunset from here, huh.
Yeah...
Um...
Haruhiro-kun.
I look forward to continue working with you.
Huh, what?
Same here.
Uh, what gives?
I just felt like it.
Oh...
The sunrise is beautiful from here, too.
I see.
That's why you come here so much.
Yeah.
Mm, Shihoru...
I'm up, I'm awake...  awake...
Oh.
Haru?
Come sit.
I'm staying here.
It's a lodging for women.
I've been here since I left the Volunteer Soldier lodging.
Wait, so I shouldn't—
On the terrace is fine.
If you plan to leave your lodging...
...maybe I will tell Yume and Shihoru about this place.
Yeah.
They'd be happy to hear about here.
Well, they're probably pretty used to our lodgings...
...but it's likely that we'll leave eventually.
I have a lot of memories... in those lodgings.
When Merry stayed at those dingy lodgings, she was...
...probably... with her original party-mates...
...with the comrades... who are no longer here.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
How to Rest
What? In Damuro?
Uh huh.
And it was super ferocious, yup.
There was a lin-gob or something there.
Uh, I only understood the ferocious part.
There were some newcomers, right?
Kie-roos.
Kie-roos?
Oh, rookies.
Were they Volunteer Soldier trainees?
Yeah, those.
Some kie-roo ty-par got into some trouble in Damuro.
It was bad, man.
I'm pretty sure the goblins we defeated were from the new city.
Their equipment and the way they
moved was completely different.
Since we defeated them—
Yup, that's right.
Mad lin-gobs from the new city came
and started angrily patrolling around.
And what are we supposed to do about it?
Leave them laying flat?
Like a pancake?
At least while they're piping hot.
Are you serious?
Hey, hey! How's it going?
Keeping it up?
Two more over here!
Are the gobs making trouble?
Yeah, they are. But the problem is that it's in Damuro.
You heard?
Yup.
So what're we gonna do?
"What?"
Honestly, I haven't thought about it.
We were planning on going to Damuro tomorrow...
If we go to Damuro tomorrow and don't earn anything,
you better take responsibility for it, Haruhiro.
What do you mean by that?
I mean, you better show you mean it by paying up your portion.
Why do I have to do that?
And if we earn nothing, my portion is also nothing.
Well, how about we change our hunting grounds?
The Cyrene Mine.
Oh, uh, sorry, I was talking to myself.
Haruhiro! You say some pretty good things once in a while.
And I mean once in a long while.
I'm totally up for it!
Are you sure?
Isn't Tetra Pods in the Cyrene Mine?
He's got a bounty of thirty golds!
It's not "Tetra Pods" but "Death Spots" from the Cyrene Mine.
No matter what, we'll need to change
our hunting grounds for a while.
But we don't know anything about other places,
so I was wondering where we could go.
We can take extra precautions to avoid Death Spots.
And always being in the same area can get a little...
I guess, it feels boring.
We fall into a routine and make
careless mistakes because of that.
Maybe it'd be good for us to have some
excitement or be under pressure once in a while.
Yeah...
I want...
...to go to the Cyrene Mine.
Then...
Yeah.
Is it bad to do the same thing every day?
We've been in fewer dangerous situations lately...
...and I've been able to save money a little at a time.
I'm okay with how it is now.
Yeah, it's just that we can't go to Damuro right now...
Oh, right.
I guess it's our only choice then.
I guess if we change our prey,
it'll be a nice change of pace, huh.
Merry?
Wait...
I'm sorry.
Merry!
No, I should apologize.
If we go to the Cyrene Mine,
Merry will have to step foot in the place...
where she lost her friends.
That would be difficult.
And very painful.
We actually haven't been near the place
where Manato breathed his last either.
It's to the point that I wish I could forget such a place exists.
In the Cyrene Mine...
I don't think I can be calm in the Cyrene Mine.
Not now...
...and probably... never will be.
Of course.
But, I have to overcome this.
No, I want to overcome this.
Otherwise, I feel like I won't be able to move on.
But, I know I can't overcome it alone.
If I were to have help...
...I'd want it to be you guys.
It'd make me happy if I could go with you guys...
...because you called me your friend.
I'm probably just causing you trouble.
You're not.
There's no way we'd think of it like that.
Haru?
I wonder why...
Maybe these are tears of joy.
I feel stupid right now.
You're fine just like that, Haru.
Thanks.
We decided to be fully prepared before facing the Cyrene Mine.
We prepared our equipment and skills.
I decided to pay forty silvers and
learn the sneak attack, "Spider."
All right, let's get started, Old Cat.
I'm counting on you!
You've gotten a little stiff since the last time.
Make sure only things that are hanging get stiff.
Uh, I'm not stiff th—
If you were, your neck could say "goodbye" to your body.
If I didn't have my dagger, removing your
neck vertebrae wouldn't be bad either.
First step for you is to fully experience my Spider...
...until you're vomiting blood.
I won't die, right?
Not to worry.
There have only been a few people
who have died from my training.
There were people who actually died?!
It's no use if you can't stand.
Take a break.
You need to train even when you're resting.
Sit-ups, sit-ups!
Or would you rather do some
training on how to withstand torture?
I'll die! For real!
Then why don't we just make small talk?
I— I can't!
You'll do as you're told, idiot.
Small... talk?
I don't mind a little story, either.
I don't know any stories!
What a boring guy you are.
No wonder you can't get any girls.
I can't... deny that fact.
You have girls in your party, don't you?
Th-Three.
Make one of them yours.
Well, having all of them would be even better.
Er... I'd rather not...
You're at least interested in one of them, aren't you?
You just pictured someone, huh?
Oh yeah, teacher...!
I had something I wanted to... ask you about.
It has to do with women, right?
That's not it.
Oh-ho, you're changing the subject.
I don't have the energy to do that!
I see.
That's a pretty good sign.
A sign?
However, do not get the wrong idea.
It's not anything special.
I can't get the wrong idea, because
I have absolutely no idea what it is.
How dull can you be?
I guess you are an old cat, after all.
Dull?
Dull!
Although your intuition isn't bad.
Anybody who's gained a lot of experience will
see that streak of light at least once or twice.
In my case... it's not once a day... but I do see it pretty often—
That's not unheard of.
It differs greatly from person to person.
How about you?
I see it here and there.
It's not something you can see just by concentrating.
I see...
To see it with more certainty,
you need to improve your technique.
Your physical strength, too.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
If you have enough breath to say you don't
have energy, I haven't pushed you far enough!
It looks like a normal mountain.
Yeah.
Long ago, the Cyrene Mine was developed
when the Arabikia Kingdom of humans...
...decided they wanted to control the frontier lands.
Under the command of No Life King, a party of kobolds
ousted the humans and seized the Cyrene Mine.
The kobolds have been living in the mine since.
All right.
Let's go.
When I try touching
the dry air after a rain,
like a sprouting flower,
fragments of memories overflow.
The warmth you gave this hand
led me to a future I can treasure
always.
I chased your voice.
I wonder when you became so strong.
I will probably find what I searched the vast world for
at the end of this journey.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
I'm
Not Fit
to Be a
Leader
Also
check
out!
Goblin's
Journey
Now
serialized
on the
official
anime
web
site.