We humans are miserable creatures.
We reject what we fear.
We attack because we don't understand.
Human cowardice...
...breeds war.
I know.
You're scared too...
...aren't you ?
Are you human or a Corpses?!
I'm neither!
I'm a Corpseless!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Corpseless of the Koutetsujou
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world
Last
Chapter
Iron
Fortress
Ikoma, this side has been taken care of.
Hey... Ikoma?
Ikoma....
...what are you?
I'm a... Corpseless.
If you fully turn into a Corpse
and lose what makes you human...
...then I will kill you, I promise.
So you're saying Nameless
can be saved with the white blood?
That's right.
It will be able to undo
the black blood's effects.
But with only one left, you can only save
either yourself or Nameless, not both.
Either way, you have to hurry.
It's only a matter of time
before it takes your mind.
Wait for me, Nameless!
They brought the virus here!
Set them on fire!
Die! Die!
Stop immediately!
Ayame-sama!
Thank goodness you're okay!
They are not the Corpses.
Like we could believe that!
It's your duty to maintain order!
No.
Order exists to protect the people.
We must not aim our guns
at the wrong people.
What we should eliminate...
...are our doubting hearts and minds!
We are going to escape
from Diamond Citadel.
Please join us.
Why are you alive?
You tilled so many...
You can die too!
Yes.
We believe she'll make it to
the castle tower in roughly 30 minutes.
I got it.
We'll meet on platform 13 to evacuate.
Understood.
It... can't be...
What should I...
...destroy next?
Young Master.
Corpseless!
Don't let him near the castle tower!
Get out of my way!
I'm only here for Nameless and Biba!
Sahari-sama!
He may have the body of a Corpses...
...but his head is still human.
Sahari-sama!
Stop the stray Corpseless!
In that case, it's only
a matter of crushing him...
...with greater power!
I will not allow you to
interfere with our plans!
This is where you die!
Ikoma!
Ikoma.
Don't worry...
...I'm still a Corpseless.
How dare you...
...interfere with Young Master's and my plans?
You killed too many!
After all that damage...
...he still does not break?
Ikoma...
Young Master.
The Corpses are spreading
faster than we had anticipated.
Please take this if
the worst should happen.
Is he the next one you
want me to kill, commander?
No, you save our people.
Once this is all over...
...you will take everyone and escape.
What about you?
I must go...
A dying man...
...is calling me.
Kurusu!
I'm fine!
Go, Corpseless!
Nameless...
I have to be strong in order to live.
The weak part of me can never return.
Not anywhere...
Isn't that right...
...brother?
Nameless...
...wait for me.
I'm coming... to save you!
Nameless!
Ikoma?
I'm going to turn you back now!
Biba!
I've been waiting...
...for a soul that knew no fear.
And I am here...
...to hunt it.
Get out of my way.
Biba!
Judging from your appearance...
you must have used the black blood.
What is it you seek that you
would sacrifice so much?
I...
...promised to turn Nameless human again!
That's all!
Ikoma...
...are you there?
Biba...
...I have to end you with my own hands...
I...!
Biba...
...I will kill you...
Kill you.
So you have found...
...a coward.
Nameless!
Are you there?!
Live...
...Nameless!
Stop, brother!
What are you doing?
Get up, Ikoma.
As you can see, I am still standing!
Fight...
...Ikoma!
Nameless...
I told you to stop.
I wish you would listen
to me sometimes... brother.
We are going to live
even though we're weak.
We're going to make rice paddies together...
...and strive for a future
where we can all eat rice.
So... I'm sorry...
...brother.
I see...
...Nameless.
No.
I'm... Hozumi.
It's going to be okay!
There's enough room for everyone!
Don't panic!
We should be able to go
there following line six.
There's no guarantee
that the railway is intact.
But there has to be a path.
Biba would have left a railway for his escape.
Would you like me to tell you?
You're...!
Let's make a deal.
In exchange for telling you the escape route...
...you let us on the Iron Fortress.
You must be joking!
Like we would ever accept that!
Let us cooperate.
Ayame-sama!
They are suffering as well.
Or else they would be
using force to have us comply.
Thanks, princess.
I'll tell you something good for that.
The stray Corpseless and
your loyal dog are both here.
Nameless. You have turned back.
Ikoma!
What are you?!
Kurusu, he's going to be okay, isn't he?
I was able to turn back,
so Ikoma should too!
Tell me, Ikoma.
What should I do?
I'll cut down a million
Corpses if you ask me to.
Nameless-chan, can you hear me?
Kajika?
Kurusu, Ikoma can you hear me?
I'm talking to you from the Iron Fortress.
Signal is good.
Come meet us on platform 13.
We'll have the Iron Fortress head there now.
I always get stuck with these jobs.
Nameless-chan, we'll all be
waiting for you there!
Let's go.
I still haven't gotten his answer yet.
Master key confirmed.
Ignite the boiler!
Nameless.
Please, launch the Iron Fortress!
Out of my way!
Nameless-chan was saying that she
wanted to eat rice until she was full.
To make a word where that can happen.
Platform 13 is right up ahead.
There!
It's Nameless and the others!
Yukina-san!
Yes!
It's the Iron Fortress!
Nameless-chan, this way!
Everyone get ready to catch them!
Ikoma...
...we're returned.
You go first.
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Kurusu!
Welcome back.
I have returned.
Get in!
Increasing speed.
Ikoma.
Hey, Ikoma!
Is he not waking up?
He's going to be fine!
Ikoma promised to turn me human again!
He hasn't done that yet!
Wake up!
Wake up, Ikoma!
Ikoma!
Nameless-chan...
You're my shield, so you can't die!
Wake up! Wake up!
Ow...
Stop shaking me...
Ikoma!
What?
Nameless...
...you're okay.
I'm supposed to say that to you.
Was this...
...the white blood?
My brother did that?
Your body's fine?
Yup.
Oh, that's right.
Ikoma.
Here.
You forgot this.