Are you human or a Corpse?!
I'm neither!
I'm a Corpseless!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world
Chapter
Two
Never-Ending
Darkness
Help me.
I did it.
I did it!
I stopped it.
I didn't turn into a Corpse!
Ikoma!
Are you here?!
What is this?
Takumi!
The piercing gun was a success!
Ikoma, what?!
It was a success!
When I increased the explosives, the metal
steam became pointed like a needle!
You were right!
So then that Corpse there...?
That's right.
I killed him!
Then you weren't hurt?
No.
The Corpse bit me.
Huh?
I got bit.
Huh?!
Oh, but it's fine.
I stopped the virus right at the neck.
It's exactly what we studied.
We might be able to save people
who have been bitten now.
Takumi, we did it!
What is going on outside?
Have you seen my daughter?
Stop making the kids cry!
I want to go home!
Who's that?
Where did she come from?
I calculate about 8.7 kilometers to Iron Fortress.
I have about 30 minutes left.
Can I make it?
Momoya!
Ayame-sama!
Ayame-dono!
How long are we going to wait here?!
We have to head for the Iron Fortress
soon, or we won't make it!
But my father said to wait for his signal.
There won't be a signal!
As long as the lord is absent, we must
obey Ayame-sama in his stead.
Why am I wasting my time with you children?
I won't wait any longer.
We're going off on our own.
You're still arguing about this?
We'd be waiting here till dawn.
Nameless-san?
What are you wearing?
Mind your business, child!
What...?
I'd appreciate it if you kept your hands to yourself.
Is there anyone here who can run a Railfort?
Right here.
I'm just a trainee though.
What's so hard about moving something along a rail?
I'll make a path, so just follow me.
Make a path?
Nameless-san!
Pressure?
Check.
Ammunition? Check.
Wind direction?
A little headwind.
Oh, well, as long as I keep it close range.
Watch out!
Let's try for 100 seconds, then.
Purification!
She's opened a path!
Run to the Iron Fortress!
We have to run! This place is done for!
We have to escape while we can!
Everyone, please wait!
They're mad, totally mad.
I'm not done yet!
Hey, look.
The Corpses...
And you're the last one!
I guess I was wrong.
Can't forget grandpa!
One hundred and 10 seconds.
I went 10 seconds over.
Ayame-sama, we should go.
Yeah...
If we can mass-produce these guns,
we'll be able to fight the Corpses!
Okay, I got it, Ikoma.
First, we need to meet up with everyone else.
Don't push, I was here first!
Let passengers on before the cargo!
Can't we get on yet?
Shut up and let me on!
It's the Iron Fortress!
This is an inspection!
Take off your clothes!
It's okay, we're humans!
Then show us that you don't have any bite marks.
Damn it.
Hold on.
They won't believe you.
I'll explain it to them.
It won't work!
It's the Corpses!
The Corpses are here!
Hurry up and go!
What are you doing, Ikoma?!
If they see me take out the Corpses,
they'll have to accept me!
Don't be a fool!
This girl...
Hey, you.
Hey.
You change your look?
You look different too.
I mean... you're really strong.
I guess a little.
What?
You're not normal, are you?
There aren't any Corpses!
It's the Iron Fortress!
We're saved!
Hurry up!
The passenger car is in the depot!
It won't leave until you're all on board!
Please, no need to rush!
Did you lead everyone here?
No.
They just followed me on their own.
You're getting on too, aren't you?
Yeah.
You!
You're supposed to be in jail.
Yeah, you almost got me killed.
Maybe you're already dead.
That's why you were able to get out of your cell.
You're wrong.
He's not a Corpse.
What...?
I've been saying it this whole time.
I'm not a Corpse!
He's not a Corpse.
Why are we getting on at the very back?
I want to be near the boiler.
Once it's ready, the next step is ignition.
Yes, sir.
Ayame-sama, if you would please.
Yes...
Master key confirmed.
Ignite the boiler!
Seems like you got it to go.
Nameless-san... thank you for your help earlier.
Ayame-san, you're not much for war, are you?
Eh?
That's why so many people die.
That's...
Nameless, was it?
We are short-handed.
We will have you guard the rear cars.
Huh...?
That's not what I was planning.
What?
You're going to have to handle
things on your own for now.
I am out of time.
She's asleep?
She's got some nerve.
Considering all of that fighting she had to do...
...I'm sure she is tired.
Well done.
Do you see my father anywhere?
Not yet.
It's the Corpses!
The Corpses are coming!
Close the door!
Confirming rotation, boiler at critical!
Commencing next phase!
Can't you go faster?
We didn't follow the proper departure procedure.
If we rush it, the furnace could break.
Stay back!
Purification!
Are we going to be okay?
Hard to say.
What?
What are the Warriors doing?!
Isn't this working?!
Hell if I know!
I'm just filling in too!
Are the Corpses really here?
Will we be safe here?
I'm going outside.
You can't!
Watch out!
Ikoma?
Are you okay?
Those damn Corpses...
Ikoma!
Hot!
Just watch me!
Hey!
Did you see that?!
With this piercing gun, we can...
Ikoma, look...
No way!
I stopped the virus!
Why?!
Takumi...
...it should be safe as long as the
virus doesn't get to your head, right?
You know?
We studied those Corpses remains...
Takumi?
Stay back! Where's the Corpse?!
Has anyone been bitten?!
You again.
I knew I should have killed you earlier.
Stop! I'm not a Ka—
Stop talking like you're human, Corpse!
Wai—
Close the doors, hurry!
Ikoma!
Wait!
I'm sorry...
Ikoma...
Kurusu-sama, incoming Corpses at the front!
How many?
Twelve, but... amongst them...
...there's...
What is it?
Kurusu, are there many of them?
No, you should stay below.
No, I want to...
That's...
It can't be...
You're wrong.
Kurusu... but that's...
Fa—
You're wrong!
That was... only a Corpse.
No...
Don't stop!
Run over any Corpse in the way!
Signal tower confirmed.
Terminating speed.
Linking switch bar.
What is it?
The switch isn't working.
What?
Something is in the way.
The drawbridge won't lower at this rate!
Is it the Corpses?
After coming this far...
Damn it.
They got the water tank!
We're leaking coolant!
The Iron Fortress won't be able
to move if we run out of water.
Wait! What are you going to do, Kurusu?
There's a manual lever in front of the bridge.
I'll use it to drop the bridge.
You're going to go outside?!
You can't! It's swarming with Corpse.
We are Knights!
If we don't put our lives on the line now,
then when are we supposed to?
Look at this!
There's someone with the Corpses!
Is he a Corpse?
He's got to be.
Then why is he fighting the Corpses?
Look.
Look at me!
Watch as the man you cast out
spills his blood and dies.
Take a nice long look!
Let's give him a hand.
We can't sit here and do nothing.
It's too dangerous!
If we open the door, the Corpses could...
They're just killing each other.
How could you...?
I will save you all.
I want you to live the rest of your lives
knowing the man you abandoned saved you.
And I will laugh at you from the afterlife.
And tell you that it serves you right!
He did it!
The drawbridge...
It's lowering!
We're saved!
I'm departing.
Grab ahold, Ikoma!
Stop! What the hell are you thinking?!
Why would you save a Corpse?!
That's not a Corpse!
He's my friend!
Ikoma!
Are you crying?
What an idiot.
Hey, you're...
Pull!
Stop it!
Why did you do that?!
I'm a Corpse now!
Oh, shut up.
We already brought you on board.
I feel no shame being saved by you.
If you still have any humanity left,
you will kill yourself for everyone's sake!
He's not a Corpse.
Although, he's not human either.
We are Corpseless.
Something between human and Corpse.
Even if the stars
That connect you make a sound
There are just dreams in the same rain
And lights are dried up
I am tired of getting answers
By mimicking others
Dawn without the sun
And broken morning
Smashed cry and dream
The ideal only has its doors
City is uplifted and drown in noise
I will still sing and stop turning the rudder
To hush silence