I taste bad.
What—I guess they're pretty friendly.
Is it because I'm a Dark Knight?
That stinks!
O Darkness, master of Vices,
Daemon Call.
Wimpy Ranta.
Wimpy wooly caterpillar.
Caterpillar, caterpillar, caterpillar!
You're only calling me a caterpillar now.
Caterpillar, caterpillar, caterpillar, caterpillar!
Hey, Zodiaco.
Caterpillar, caterpillar, caterpillar, caterpillar, caterpillar!
I really need to get out of this mine.
No way, no way, no way, no way, no way.
Die, die, die.
Die, just die.
I'm already half dead...
Just die.
Die and be in Skullhell-sama's embrace.
Be embraced.
Caterpillar, caterpillar, caterpillar, caterpillar!
So I'm a caterpillar after all?
Caterpillar, caterpillar, caterpillar!
O light, return to Lumiaris' divine protection. Cure!
Let's go over our priorities again.
Our top priority is for all five of us to get back alive.
Next is rescuing Ranta.
Yes, we'll do as much as we can, but we can't be reckless.
Um, you probably know that I don't like Ranta.
It hurts my feelings when he calls me "flat-chested,"
and he doesn't stop even when I tell him to.
It's hard to like someone like that, even if you asked me to try.
But, if I were all alone in this mine,
I'd be really scared, you know?
And when I think about how Ranta must be feeling right now...
Don't worry.
If he would die from something like this,
he would have died many times by now.
Let's go.
Ranta's waiting.
Vice, Vice, Vice, Vice, Vice, Vice, Vice!
Not the time to think about Vices!
Oh no!
Ranta?!
He's the only it could be.
Over there!
He got up here after being surrounded like that?
It's pretty amazing if he did.
His strength to live is stronger than most, to say the least.
The rest of us don't have that kind of tenacity to live.
Stay alive, Ranta.
Die! Die, die, die!
Die, die, die, die!
Die, Ranta!
Ranta, die!
Die, die, die!
Flat-chest...
Flat-chest, flat-chest, flat-chest, flat-chest, flat-chest, flat-chest!
I should have fondled her flat chest!
Exhaust!
Ranta!
Don't just call out to someone so suddenly.
You almost gave me a heart attack, idiot!
Thanks!
Marque, Em, Parc!
O light, return to Lumiaris' divine protection. Heal!
Haru-kun!
This is my last arrow!
This way, everybody!
You too, Yume!
Can you run, Ranta?
Of course I can.
Who do you think you're talking to, scum.
Shihoru!
Marque, Em, Parc!
O light, return to Lumiaris' divine protection. Cure!
Oh-ho?
Ranta, are you crying?
I'm not crying!
Your eyes are all watery, though.
I'm hurting all over!
You don't have to get so mad.
We were able to see you alive again.
I wanted to see you guys again!
N-No, that's not it.
No way I wanted to see you again.
Wh-When I thought I would never see all
your pretty little faces again, my chest—
What about your chest?
Did your chest feel tight?
N-No!
Your cheeest?
M-My chest—!
...chest...
Oh?
Chest...
Y-o-u-r cheeeest?
Shut up, you flat-chest!
Don't call me that.
I will, and I'll say it million times!
Flat-chest, flat-chest, flat-chest!
Flat-chest, flat-chest, flat-chest, flatchest,flatchest,flatchest—
Hey.
Be quiet and stay still.
Do you want me to stop healing you?
N-No.
I'm very sorry. Okay.
Hey!
It looks clear.
Let's go back to Ortana.
What a relief.
It's been a long day, huh...
It's not over yet.
Don't let your guard down until we get back to Ortana.
I was thinking about what Ranta meant
when he said, "Aren't you our leader?"
Because to me, Manato was our leader.
And to be honest, there was something inside me
that thought I had to become like Manato, but...
I'm not Manato.
Ah, no, it's nothing.
Manato said that everyone has strengths and weaknesses...
...but I don't know what Manato was bad at.
As for me, I have a lot of things that I'm
not good at and that I need to work on.
My comrades make up for those
weaknesses by helping me out,
and maybe that's how we've found a balance in our party.
That's why I don't know if I'm actually being a proper leader.
But if things are running smoothly,
that's probably the most important thing.
Like for Ranta and me, if we can work
well during a fight, it's all good.
That's because that's the most important thing.
Haru.
I won't be able to use magic for a while.
At the most, I can cast one Cure.
I need to go meditate somewhere.
I don't really understand magic, but Shihoru looks drained, too.
Let's go out, then.
We'll try not to bother the Lesser Kobolds.
Grimgar of Fantasy
and Ash
For real?
You're dogged!
Marque, Em, Parc.
Thanks!
Huh?
Be careful!
Death Spots gets stronger from the wounds!
H-He gets stronger than this?!
W-What should we do?
Run?
That's the only thing we can do, but can we outrun him?
It'll be impossible on this straight path.
Someone... at least one of us needs to stay.
Before I knew it, my body started moving.
Spider!
Everyone, go!
Ranta!
Entrust you!
Haru?!
What are you doing?
We're leaving!
Let go!
Merry...
...are you crying?
Don't cry.
Yes... get out of here... everyone.
I can't hear you.
Don't give up!
Don't die, stupid Haruhiro!
That's right...
I...
It's broken.
Don't give up in a situation like this?
You're demon, shitty Ranta.
But...
...you're so stubborn...
...so I can't give up just yet, huh?
Merry... come back and cast Dispel on me, too.
Then, maybe we can meet again.
Someday...
This is...
...a battle of life and death.
It's a battle of life and death...
...and I'm still alive!
So I'm not going to give up, and I'll keep living.
I'll keep living until I die!
Come on!
Huh?
That's strange.
He stopped—
No.
Wrong.
He's moving really slowly.
Don't think.
Huh?
Merry?
Is this...
...heaven?
Welcome back, Haru.
Oh! You're finally awake.
S-Sorry.
Haruhiro-kun, here.
Thanks.
What's the matter?
What about Death Spots?
You don't remember?
Having fun, laughing, getting hurt, and crying
Here!
This jog your memory?
Living in the presence of one another
A bounty of thirty golds.
Ranta suggested to discuss how we
should split it after you woke up.
Those moments in daily life
He said it was because you're the leader.
Become precious memories
Ranta said that?
The ever-changing twilight becomes a miracle
What? You got a problem with that?
Oh yeah, and when we went back to get you—
Went to get me?
Oh, yeah... when you went back to get me.
You were lying next the Date Spots, you know.
"Date"?
Once, I saw in the sky
Oh you mean "Death Spots."
Oh, so... wait is that—?
Yeah, my sword was broken anyway, and
it seemed wieldy so I thought I'd try it out.
The winds of the future blowing in my reflection
"Wieldy"? You're amazing, Moguzo.
Oh, no.
I can't use it like this, though.
I'm glad I can meet you again tomorrow
I was thinking of taking it to a swordsmith.
I guess we've decided on one of the
ways we'll be using the bounty on.
It's really okay?
When it's done, we need to give it a cute name.
This long, long road I've walked
A name?
Like Cleaver-kun One or something.
I-I guess it's kinda cute.
Will bring me to another new world
Not bad.
I've been through meetings and farewells
Haru.
Here.
I fixed this.
Days pass by one by one
With memories I won't forget anymore
The slight weight and feeling of it settled onto me...
and somewhere inside me, I felt calm.
It was a mysterious feeling.
And suddenly, it hit me.
I'm home, Merry.
Only now?
Drawing what's happening now on the horizon
I heard, I heard all about it, Haruhirocchi!
The next morning will bring tomorrow
You killed Spots, huh?
That's amazing!
I'm super jelly jealous!
Maybe not jelly, eh?
Soon, moving forward and farther ahead
Austraaaliaaa!
Australia!!!
What's was that?
Going towards the future as I am now
I'm glad... really glad.
I'm glad I can meet you again tomorrow
Renji.
Sorry.
Huh?
This long, long road I've walked
For what I did when Manato died.
Oh.
No, you don't need to apologize.
Will bring me to another new world
I don't?
I just... couldn't accept Manato's death yet... at that time.
So I should say thanks, Renji.
I see.
Everybody!
Drinks are on us today!
Drink up!
Here again?
Yeah.
I shouldn't come?
No, you can.
You know...
...there was something I wanted to ask you.
What?
Was being a leader...
...tough for you?
Has it been tough for you?
I don't know.
Haruhiro...
...looks like you've grown.
Oh, really?
I'm different from who I was yesterday.
I wonder what I will be like tomorrow.
Day by day, we live in the today and keep living...
...to meet our future selves.
I'll be back, Manato.
As I continue living in this world...
...I have memories that grow dim.
The memories from what I should call the world I came from.
The feeling...
...that I had forgotten something important...
...worried and irritated me.
It did before.
But now, things are different.
The solid feeling of the stone beneath me...
...and the smell of the air I breathe...
...make me feel like I'm really right here.
And that's everything.
I now have things that I don't want to forget,
and things that I shouldn't forget.
And I don't plan to ever forget those things...
...as long as I live.
Let's go, everyone!
See You Tomorrow...
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash