There you are, Merry.
Sorry, I must have...
...drifted off.
Our princess says she's feeling weary.
Ow!
You're too energetic, Og.
I wouldn't be able to stand it if you were that insensitive to me.
Here you go.
Are we going into the Cyrene Mine again?
Yeah.
The other parties are also aiming to
get farther in, so we can't fall behind.
I give up.
Everything is a competition to you, huh.
Is that a problem?
It's okay.
You are our leader.
Then all you have to do is follow me.
This guy...
He can be kind of pushy, but I like him.
I'd say you feel the same way.
He can get a little tiring sometimes.
So you are tired, Merry.
No, that's not—!
Come on now...
Well, make sure to take care of yourself.
Thanks, Mutsumi.
Merry.
What's the matter?
Merry!
I'm sorry, I...
You okay?
This way.
Repeating a yesterday filled with scrapes,
We clear the path to a hopeful tomorrow.
I wonder what remains
in both these tiny hands?
The voice I raised upwards scattered into the air.
The reality I've gamed is hazy,
and even if I can't see ahead of me,
I can keep moving forward on this long road
if I'm with you.
Connecting a bond covered in dust,
We join back to back in the past and future.
Repeating an answer full of mistakes,
I will reach out my hands to seek the light, again and again.
The first thing we felt when we went down to the fifth level...
It's hot.
It was pleasantly cool up to the fourth
evel, but the fifth level was different.
This level was for metal smelting...
...and this place was...
I'll lead us to a different well.
We can return to the fourth level from there...
Merry-san, are you okay?
You look pale.
I'm fine.
This level is where Merry's friends spent their last moments.
We can't get down from there without being seen.
This way.
Should we take a break?
We can rest, but we'll need to move away from here.
It's dangerous to linger near the wells.
There's a place we used as a resting area.
There...
Careful!
I know!
Is this... that place?
This place used to be a Temple of Lumiaris.
Kobolds don't worship God, so they rarely come here.
This...
...was my staff.
Do you...
...hear some sound...?
Wh-What are you doing?
Y-You're the one who grabbed me!
That's...
Because of No Life King's curse...
...they've become corpses infused with a false life.
This is what they look like after decaying.
Michiki... Og... Mutsumi...
Long time... no see.
Do you... recognize me?
I've missed you!
Get ready!
That's hot!
Haru.
Cover me.
I want to go to the front.
Merry's going to the front?
Merry learned the Light Magic called Dispel.
Using Lumiaris' divine protection,
it breaks the undead king's spell.
She probably learned it knowing this day would come.
It has a short range, so she needs
to get close by going to the front.
We can't stop her.
It'd be no use trying.
Haruhiro-kun?
Moguzo, go for the Warrior.
Ranta, you get the Thief.
Shihoru will be backup.
Yume, you come with me.
Okay.
The undead.
What a sad curse.
They look like people you know well, but they're not.
What remains of their bodies no longer hold
memories, and they continue to move forever.
We have to let them rest.
Huh?! Where are they?
I can't see anything!
A firewall.
Ohm, Rel, Ect, Nemun, Dash!
Nice one, Shihoru!
Swat?
He's also a Thief, so I know his fighting style.
It'd be a tough fight for him if he were up against
Moguzo's heavy slashes, but against Ranta...
Even I could hold off Ranta if I fought defensively.
Ranta might not be able to defeat him.
Haru-kun?
These are Magic Missiles that Shihoru also uses!
I didn't know they could be used like this!
What's with that skill?!
It's like he's doing acrobatics!
Ohm, Rel, Ect, Wei, Dash!
It's not working?!
Shihoru!
Your magic's worn off here.
One-on-one will be tough for them.
I need to help them out!
But how should I?
Merry!
Damn it!
O light, return to Lumiaris' divine protection. Dispel!
I'm sorry, Mutsumi.
Ah!
Haru-kun?
Yume, help Moguzo.
I'll back up Ranta.
Okay.
This guy won't quit!
Ranta!
Gotcha!
It's times like these when Ranta is actually perceptive.
That was close.
He's changed the angles of his attacks.
He's strong.
I'd lose against him one-on-one.
But...
O light, return to Lumiaris' divine protection. Dispel!
Og, I won't forget about you.
I'm impressed you knew what I was going to do.
We didn't plan it out or anything, either.
Are you stupid?
Huh?
If it works out, anything's fine.
It's common sense.
It's "common sense" only for you.
You're so nitpicky, Haruhiro.
You're an idiot, so you can't help overthinking
things and making them more complicated.
Right?
You're not Manato.
Moguzo!
Haruhiro-kun!
That's right.
Right now...
Aim carefully and try not to hit Moguzo!
Here I come!
Exhaust!
O light, return to Lumiaris' divine protection...
...Dispel.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
Between
Life and
Death
Goodbye...
Michiki...
Ash.
Of Michiki-san... Og-san... Mutsumi-san,
and all their equipment...
Ash...
Only ash remained on the ground.
While they were alive, they felt and thought about things.
About happy things, things they didn't like, things they
wanted to forget, and things they wanted to remember.
But they've died and become ash.
It was the same for Manato, too.
It's the same for all of us.
I was finally able to do what I needed to do...
...thanks to you guys.
Thanks.
They were strong.
Michiki-san was strong.
I need to get stronger.
I want to have more attack power.
I want to learn new spells, too.
I have to.
And for me, you know what?
I need to create an original finishing move that's just for me.
He's saying stupid things again.
I want to get a wolfdog.
I can get one for one gold.
But it takes time for them to grow up big, you know...
What are you going to do with it until it grows up?
Maybe I'll keep it in a pocket and walk around with it there...
It won't bond with you unless you spend time with it...
Would it fit in a pocket?
Hm, I don't know...
Maybe that wouldn't work...
What about me?
I do want to get stronger...
...but I'd be happy just to be a stronger leader for this party.
These plain jobs are what I'm best at.
It's been a tiring day.
Yeah, I want to hurry up and get home, so I can take a bath.
Wh-What?
I-I haven't even said anything!
What?!
H-He's here!
Death Spots!
Huh?
Oh no!
No way...
Run, everybody!
Look ahead! Ahead!
Run!
Moguzo! War Cry!
Moguzo!
I— I can't do it again right away!
Shihoru!
Ranta, I'll leave them to you!
I know it myself!
There!
To the left!
It's a shortcut!
Th-Thanks.
Hey!
Over here, quick!
More and more are coming!
Enough.
Get up there, too!
Okay.
H-He's scary.
That guy is too much!
Haru-kun!
Haru!
Go first!
Haruhiro, climb up.
Huh?
Hurry up!
If you die... you know... it's too troublesome, idiot!
Ranta!
Go, Harkiro—
What are you saying?!
Go!
Aren't you our leader?!
Stupid Ranta!
Don't die!
Of course I won't.
Damn it.
Damn Ranta!
It's not like you, damn it!
Damn it!
Ranta-kun!
Ranta's... not coming up from this well.
Eh?
He's staying below.
The scaffolding gave out, and...
Y-You mean...?!
Everybody looked to me, because I'm the leader.
I might be incompetent, but I'm the leader.
If we all die trying to save Ranta, then we'll lose everything.
But he has the devil's own luck.
When I last saw him, he was still unharmed, so we have to go.
Merry, will you lead us to a different
well that goes to the fifth level?
Got it!
Let's go up to the third floor to recoup and go down from there.
Thanks.
Is everybody okay with that?
Yeah.
Yup.
Let's go!
Hey, Death Spots!
Today's your unlucky day, cause today you're gonna die!
Man, I sounded very Dark Knight-like just now.
Arrows?
Come on, put those down!
Hey, it should be, you know, more cooler.
Like one-on-one or som—!
Ranta, you idiot.
Don't die.
It'd be the worst if you came back to haunt us.
Are our enemies the kobolds?
No.
Our real enemies are our overly weak selves.
Hey, come ooooon!
When I try touching
the dry air after a rain,
like a sprouting flower,
fragments of memories overflow.
The warmth you gave this hand
led me to a future I can treasure
always.
I chased your voice.
I wonder when you became so strong.
I will probably find what I searched the vast world for
at the end of this journey.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
See You
Tomorrow...
Also
check
out!
Goblin's
Journey
Now
serialized
on the
official
anime
web
site.