The strong survive...
...and the weak die.
He said that's the way the world worked.
I can't accept that.
He should be taken down.
Just you wait, Biba
Are you human or a Corpse?!
I'm neither!
I'm a Corpseless!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Corpseless of the Iron Fortress
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world
Chapter
Ten
The
Attacking
Weak
Everyone in red armbands head to the back.
Traitor.
Sorry, my policy is to follow
the guy with the biggest guns.
Yukina-san.
This is for Ikoma.
He's with them now.
It makes me sick
Do you think he really is?
Probably.
Ikoma.
Here.
Hold up, Takumi.
You're supposed to go over there.
Please, I beg that you spare my wife.
I will give enough blood
for the both of us instead.
What did you say, sir?
That's fine with me.
No.
Where's the fun... in that deal?
Then I will give enough for three— No, four!
Very well.
You have a deal.
Thank you.
Take the blood.
Yes, sir.
Warabi, I'm tired of you picking on the weak.
How could you do that?!
Let go of me!
Judging from your weight...
...you could probably donate
thirty men's worth.
Would you like to make a deal?
Here.
When are you going to do it, Ikoma?
I can't wait anymore.
Hey, you're in the way.
Hey, Ikoma!
Tomorrow night.
We'll do it when they come to take blood.
Well, let's hear your answer, then.
With your uncle being Elder Makino...
...it should be possible.
I am to get them to open
the gates to Diamond Citadel...
...and arrange a meeting
in front of your father for you.
If you will guarantee me
the safety of my people...
...I will have no other choice but to help.
That is a wise decision.
But what do you plan to do
after you meet with your father?
Ten years ago...
...the Headquarters dispatched 400,000 troops
to Kyushu to exterminate the Corpses.
I know.
You were the commander
despite being only 12 years old.
When we landed in Kyushu...
...we were in a good position.
We established several bases...
...and succeeded in cutting off the Corpses.
However, suddenly...
...the replacement supplies stopped coming.
We were...
...isolated among the Corpses...
...and were obliterated.
My father was behind everything.
I have to punish my father
with my own hands.
You want to take over
Master Fortress's engine room?
The engine room is the heart of a Railfort.
If we can control it...
...there's nothing Biba will be able to do.
He will probably agree to release
Ayame-sama and Nameless as well.
But the engine room is
located in the front car.
How are we supposed to make it that far?
One of them...
...is carrying the keys.
It's most likely to carry the blood to
the front car where the Corpses are.
Once a day during the night,
he brings his keys.
We're going to steal them.
It seems we have no other choice.
The people won't be able to keep this up
Biba plans to destroy Diamond Citadel.
After we cross the Great Sea Harbor Bridge...
...we should arrive there by tomorrow.
I'm worried about Ayame-sama as well.
If something were to happen,
I wouldn't be able to face
Kurusu when he returns.
You're right.
We'll gather whatever
we can use as weapons.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
You think Nameless-chan will come back?
It doesn't matter.
I'm bringing her back whether
she wants to come or not.
That's what I've decided.
Is Nameless-chan a lot like Hatsune-chan?
My sister?
Not even a little bit.
Please don't compare her to that brute.
They might be about the
same height, but that's all.
I see.
It's just...
...that it feels like someone
is telling me to do this.
Someone?
Yeah.
"Go save her this time. You'd better not run."
I wonder who...
Maybe God?
No.
It's coming from you.
I see. You might be right.
I recently finally figured out how you think.
Only now?
Then do you know how I think?
No, but you figured it out.
Because you're simple.
What the hell?
Sorry, I take it back
Are we really going to continue
our plan without Soue-sama?
We have no other choice.
Don't play dumb!
You're the ones who turned Fireless
in to that hybrid colony, right?
Why did you—?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Aren't you Tasuke?
What happened to you?!
Don't move!
Okay, just keep applying
pressure on it with gauze.
Brother!
You're taking blood from the
people on the Iron Fortress?
Why are you doing that?
Brother!
I wonder, what do you think
the Corpses are... Nameless?
They suddenly appeared one day...
...and completely changed the world.
The Corpses are our enemy.
They need to be destroyed.
But... thanks to them...
...the true enemy that must be
struck down has been revealed.
I thought you were going to go meet
with your father in Diamond Citadel.
I... don't understand... what you're—
I see.
Do you fear me... Nameless?
Young Master...
...please check these when it's convenient.
No problem.
Nameless.
I see that you like the people of Iron Fortress.
It must have been a good journey for you.
Okay.
I will send notice that they shall not be
harmed as long as they remain peaceful.
Thank you, brother!
Does she require repairs?
Very serious repairs.
What else should we review?
If we get Takumi to do number three...
...and the support valve needs—
I can offer my support on that.
Thank you.
Well then, please do.
All right!
Okay.
Ikoma, here!
Line up.
Today we're collecting from the blue armbands.
If you want blood so badly...
...why don't you take your own?!
What did you say, you bastard?!
Corpseless?!
Takumi, go!
Everybody down!
Now!
What's going on?
Hey, stop it, idiot!
Let me explain!
There's nothing to explain!
Wait, Takumi!
Ikoma?!
It was all an act!
Sukari was feeding me information
on the Master Fortress!
We were using bamboo pipes
to pass on messages.
No way...
What the hell, so you were tricking us?!
Not exactly, but...
He's a traitor, isn't he?
You should just shoot.
Oh, how kind of you.
Kibito-san, I'll take care of him!
You bastard.
I let you live because they said
a male Corpseless is rare!
Kurusu and Nameless are faster!
Die, you monster!
Don't you call him a monster!
What the hell is that face for?!
Is it really that funny
that I'd save the day?!
Well, yes.
What?!
Bastards, how did you...?!
Understood.
I will take care of it.
Can you handle this, Nameless?
But...
...brother....
If you can't...
...I will have to give the order
to stop giving you medication.
The curse will likely spread
even further throughout your body.
I don't wish to see that.
Be strong, Nameless.
You don't want to end up
like your mother, do you?
I'm sorry...
...brother.
I can't do it.
I want...
...to be with everyone on the Iron Fortress!
I want to be able to eat rice every day
in a world without the Corpses!
So...
I'm sorry... brother.
I see.
What?
Let go of me!
Capture her!
Stop fight—
I made the right decision
lowering your blood dosage.
Tranquilize her.
Yes!
No!
Let me go!
Everyone's here, aren't they?
I want to leave!
Ikoma!
Now you will be able to
hear my voice more clearly.
Go on ahead, Ikoma!
This will take too long!
Okay.
Let's hurry up and finish this so we can eat!
With Nameless-chan and
Ayame-sama, of course!
Yeah, I agree!
What?
Why?
What are you doing, Ikoma?!
They're going to come if you don't hurry!
Damn it!
That didn't work.
We'll go around the outside!
What is it?!
It won't open!
What?!
Biba!
Ikoma...
...I believe you were looking for this.
We will cross the Great
Sea Harbor Bridge tomorrow.
I predicted that if you were to start
a revolt, this would be the time.
So I had the keys switched.
Well done noticing the keys...
...but you fell a little short.
You fail, Ikoma.
Ikoma...
...are you okay?
Takumi?!
I did it this time...
That day you turned into
a Corpseless and got shot...
...I really regretted that
I didn't do this then...
But I finally... did—
Tell me how you feel.
Tell me how it feels to lose your friend, Ikoma.
Depending on your answer, I may
spare you and make you one of us.
What is wrong with you?
What is wrong...!
Why did you do this?!
Are you finished, sir?
Yes.
You'll pay... for killing Takumi!
You'll pay!
Bring her here.
Welcome, Nameless.
I want you to kill him.
Nameless?
Hey...
What did they do to you?
Well done.
That is...
...my Nameless.
Even if the stars
That connect you make a sound
There are just dreams in the same rain
And lights are dried up
I am tired of getting answers
By mimicking others
Dawn without the sun
And broken morning
Smashed cry and dream
The ideal only has its doors
City is uplifted and drown in noise
I will still sing and stop turning the rudder
To hush silence