Sorry!
Sorry, I—
Heal Michiki, hurry!
Merry, hurry! Merry!
I...
I'm sorry, Hayashi...
I've used up all my magic...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Michiki!
Michiki...!
Go!
Get away!
No! I can't do this!
Please, Hayashi!
I can't leave you...
...or the others...
I said, go!
Let go!
No!
Michiki!
Alrighty, then.
No!
I don't remember how we got back above ground.
Maybe my body remembered the way back.
Shinohara took us in, and we
joined Orion, but Merry left soon after.
It was painful for her to be with me.
She didn't say that, but I could see it in her eyes.
When she saw me, she saw a past she couldn't regain.
She couldn't help seeing it.
And that was painful.
After that, Merry moved from
party to party, never staying long.
From what other people say about her,
she isn't the same as she used to be.
I'm pretty sure I brought Merry back above ground.
But I wonder if that's... really true.
Right now, she's an empty shell.
She might have... left herself down there.
Please, help her.
Ah, well...
I understand the pain of losing a comrade.
I've experienced it, too.
Please do not forget that pain.
You will move forward while holding on to that pain.
Please treasure the comrades you have now.
Once they are gone, they will not return.
Usually, you don't realize this... until afterwards.
Repeating a yesterday filled with scrapes,
We clear the path to a hopeful tomorrow.
I wonder what remains
in both these tiny hands?
The voice I raised upwards scattered into the air.
The reality I've gamed is hazy,
and even if I can't see ahead of me,
I can keep moving forward on this long road
if I'm with you.
Connecting a bond covered in dust,
We join back to back in the past and future.
Repeating an answer full of mistakes,
I will reach out my hands to seek the light, again and again.
Tch, that was completely useless.
What was useless?
So now we know her past.
So what?
It doesn't have anything to do with us.
I guess...
We have to be nice to her just
because she's had a rough past?
You've got to be kidding.
I didn't say that.
That's what you're saying, Haruhiro.
How is she any different from us?
Are you saying we haven't had a rough past?
Is it all our fault?
Well...
Why do we have to be okay being friends
with someone who won't treat us as friends?
Shihoru?
I don't think... anyone here... was unaffected...
when we lost Manato-kun... everybody was...
But to make up for it, I think we should try to be nice to her.
It'd be nice if we could... and if she could, too...
Ranta, you said that she's no different from us, right?
So what?
So if we don't try to get to know her,
she won't try to get to know us either.
If we don't treat Merry as a friend,
she won't treat us as her friends either, right?
Then are you trying to get to know me, Haruhiro?
Aren't you guys always ignoring my thoughts and opinions?
You know, Ranta, you always say unnecessary things.
What the heck?
Actually, you only say unnecessary things.
What are you trying to say?!
Like when you call me flat-chested, it hurts my feelings.
It's those things that are unnecessary.
Oh!
Mo-Moguzo?!
Is that how you've been feeling, Ranta?
I didn't know.
It's not only Merry that I haven't been paying attention to.
So that's how it is, huh.
What?
Sorry, Ranta.
Ah?
My bad.
I'll be more careful from now on.
Yeah, because I think of you as a friend.
Wh-What?
Th-Then you better be careful, idiot.
That was unnecessary.
What's wrong with ailing an idiot, "idiot"?
Idiot!
Ranta?
Shut up.
At least give me time to think.
You? Think about it?
Why you—
Anyway, we'll be seeing her tomorrow,
so I need to think about how to face her.
Well...
You know, Shihoru...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make you talk about all that.
Eh?
Woah.
I wonder if it'll rain tomorrow...
You say useless things, too!
No, wrong.
It might snow tomorrow.
Yeah, I think that sounds like the right saying.
Moguzo!
It's true, though.
I'm not sure how all of us will face Merry tomorrow.
It really is raining.
What did you say, Haru?
Oh, I was just saying that it's actually raining.
Yeah, it's raining.
Haru-kun, that dagger...
Yeah.
That's the one I dropped.
Sorry, Yume.
I haven't been myself today.
But I'm okay now.
Let's follow him.
We might find their hideout.
There weren't any goblins that were good targets.
Okay.
Let's go back, then.
The rain doesn't help either.
But before that, Merry...
I want to talk to you.
Right now?
Make it fast.
Before you say anything, if you want
me to leave the party, just say that.
Sorry, Merry, that's not it.
Now that I think about it we've been acting strange today.
After hearing her story yesterday,
we don't know how to treat her anymore.
I don't know how to talk to her.
Merry felt that something was off
and probably prepared herself...
For example, for a parting.
For an end.
Merry, I want to tell you something.
We used to have a Priest in our party.
His name was Manato.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
They Were Called
Goblin Slayers
We used to have a Priest in our party.
His name was Manato.
Manato died.
It's probably more accurate to say we let him die.
Manato healed us, even when we only had scratches.
He and Moguzo were also our shields during battle.
And he was also our leader,
so he was basically doing three jobs.
I thought he was really amazing.
But before we knew it, we took that for granted.
I don't think it was easy for Manato.
He didn't show it on the outside.
I didn't even try to imagine how he was feeling.
But now, all I can do is imagine how he was feeling.
Manato is dead, so he's not here anymore.
When Manato died, I seriously thought that was it for us.
But if we want to keep living, we can't just do nothing, right?
So that's why I asked you to join.
Because we can't do anything without a Priest.
That was the only reason.
There wasn't any other reason.
But you see, we were originally just
the ones left over that nobody picked.
And Manato got us together.
And made us into a party.
And we became friends.
Yeah, we've become friends.
When you're in the same party,
there will be times when things don't go smoothly,
when you get angry, and when you fight.
But, they really are your precious friends.
It doesn't matter why you became friends,
but that you are friends at this moment.
And I also think of you as a friend, Merry.
I-I also think of you as a friend.
Me too. And you're super cute, too.
I-It's reassuring to have you here, Merry.
And I, you know...
I do feel kinda bad about making
a big deal when I get a small cut.
Well, we're friends, right?
Looks like it's about to snow.
Even Ranta is apologizing.
That joke's getting old!
Merry.
Uh, if you want... you want to come
with us to get Moguzo a helmet?
I'm sorry.
I see.
Then, if it's okay with you...
...do you want to have dinner with us?
Sorry...
...not yet.
Not yet?
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
If you keep living, a new day will come tomorrow.
Thanks, everyone.
I'm so glad we found a cute helmet.
And we somehow had enough money, too.
Ranta didn't pitch in even one copper.
That discount I got was what I paid, idiot.
Because of Ranta's aggressive haggling, we got
the price down from forty-two to eighteen silvers.
I feel like maybe we're slowly
getting a little closer to Merry, too.
And once, everyday...
...we always go there.
Hey, goblin slayers!
How's it going, goblin slayers?
You heading to Damuro today, too, little goblin slayers?
They're probably gonna hunt all
the goblins outta this place soon.
Those idiots need to shut it.
Don't respond to them.
It's true, anyway.
This soup is delicious.
Yup.
Maybe I'll try making it, too.
Seriosly?
Yay!
If you're okay with something similar, yeah.
Day after day, it's goblins, goblins, goblins, goblins.
Rain or shine, it's goblins, goblins,
goblins, goblins, goblins, goblins.
At first, they all looked the same, but
recently, I've been able to tell them apart.
There are many males and few females.
According to Merry, most of the females are in
Damuro's new city, surrounded by high level males.
I'm not jealous of that harem.
Like the female goblins would fall for you.
Those that don't understand my charm are useless.
If you understand it, you know right away.
Merry, who would you choose from the three of us?
Eh?
No need to be shy.
What is there to be shy about?
Beats me.
Hey, hey, hey!
How's it going?
I really haven't seen Merry smile before.
We make sure to have nutritious meals.
And it's fine to stay in the rundown
Volunteer Soldier housing.
Even if we had the money to stay in nicer
places, we should use that for equipment.
I especially want to invest in Moguzo's armor.
We definitely can't afford anything
custom made with sheet metal.
Instead, we bought a more affordable
used one and had a blacksmith fit it.
Even so, the pieces all cost a couple silvers or more.
Then there are skills.
I learned Sneaking and Swat to mute my footsteps.
Shihoru's Sleepy Shadow is shadow
magic that puts enemies to sleep.
Exhaust!
...is a skill that immediately creates
distance between you and the enemy.
Avoid!
Ranta just likes shouting out his skill names.
Moguzo's War Cry paralyzes the enemy for a moment.
Yume learned Swift, raising her bow accuracy.
With Mouse Hole, she can also
quickly dodge an enemy attack.
Merry's always been levels above us,
so it's reassuring to have her.
Once in a while, there are moments when
I automatically know exactly where to hit.
My blade easily slips through,
and it's tip touches something.
As it touches, I know I've hit the right place.
Before I realize it, I've already pierced through.
I actually have no idea what this light is either.
I'll ask Teacher Barbara next time I see her.
Isn't it about time, Haruhiro?
Yeah.
Yup.
Finally!
Can't sleep?
Yeah, kinda.
Kind of like how you can't sleep the night before a field trip?
I don't know.
Manato...
...I'm not worried...
...or overexcited or anything.
That's good.
Yeah.
How many days have we been in Grimgar?
I don't remember when I stopped counting.
There's one thing for sure.
Wherever we came from, we're all friends now.
And we're definitely living our lives together here.
Manato...
I want to show you what our party is like now, too.
See you tomorrow.
When I try touching
the dry air after a rain,
like a sprouting flower,
fragments of memories overflow.
The warmth you gave this hand
led me to a future I can treasure
always.
I chased your voice.
I wonder when you became so strong.
I will probably find what I searched the vast world for
at the end of this journey.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
In My
Memories
with You
Also
check
out!
Goblin's
Journey
Now
serialized
on the
official
anime
web
site.