Manato?
Haruhiro.
You're still awake.
Huh?
Were you drinking, Manato?
Hm?
Yeah, a little.
Ohhh, you drink.
There's a place near the square on
Hanazono Street called Shelly's Tavern.
It's become a hangout place for Volunteer Soldiers.
I was gathering information there.
Oh...
I can't believe you'd go out of your way to do that for us.
Drinks are definitely not cheap for dirt-poor people like us.
I've actually gotten used to living like this pretty quickly.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Somehow... sorry.
You do it all while we sleep.
I'm thinking of changing locations tomorrow.
There's a place with monsters
that even we should be able to beat.
You should've taken me with you to the tavern.
Do you drink, Haruhiro?
Hmmm, who knows.
I wonder if I've had alcohol before.
Maybe not.
Apparently, I kind of like it.
So maybe I actually wanted to drink, too.
I hope we can go with everybody next time.
Yeah.
That would be nice.
How was the Thief Guild?
Mm, I didn't expect it to be so rough, and my teacher was crazy.
She was pretty, but scary.
Ehhh, nice.
I had a strict, thick-bearded master with a painfully loud voice.
It was so bad that my ears were hurt.
How much did you get yelled at?
I don't remember.
Enough to make me believe I was born just to be yelled at.
He was constantly yelling at me.
I didn't know stuff like that happens to you, too.
It does.
Of course it does.
Manato...
Hm?
Good work.
The moon... is so red.
Yeah.
I don't know where this place is.
I don't know how we got here...
But... one thing is for sure.
The moon wasn't red at the other place.
A red moon is just... weird.
Repeating a yesterday filled with scrapes,
We clear the path to a hopeful tomorrow.
I wonder what remains
in both these tiny hands?
The voice I raised upwards scattered into the air.
The reality I've gamed is hazy,
and even if I can't see ahead of me,
I can keep moving forward on this long road
if I'm with you.
Connecting a bond covered in dust,
We join back to back in the past and future.
Repeating an answer full of mistakes,
I will reach out my hands to seek the light, again and again.
Is a gobs there?
There is. One.
On his own?
I think so.
He armed?
With sword.
Okay, let's go!
We should have decided on some sort of signal.
Huh? Already?!
Stupid Ranta!
There's no point in a surprise attack if you're that loud!
There!
Nice, Yume!
Who are you fighting? Geez...
What? So I'm attacking first?!
It's not what Thieves usually do!
Our reaches are completely different.
I know, I'll use a Slap to his wrist!
Too shallow?
Don't stop moving!
Hatred!
Ugh, gross.
Marque, Em, Parc!
Moguzo, get in front of the goblin!
O-Okay!
Everybody, surround him!
Don't let him run away!
Moguzo!
Keep pressuring him!
Pressuring! Pressuring!
Did I get him?!
Did I just cut into his... his bone?
Gross.
H-He's scary.
The goblin is desperate, too.
He doesn't want to be killed.
There's no way he would.
"I'll get you before you get me."
Of course I don't understand his words...
...but even I can tell what he's saying.
Don't lose your heads, you guys!
It's kill or be killed!
I-I'm gonna kill this guy and accumulate my Vice.
You're just as scared as we are.
Sh-Shut up!
Gobs is a pretty tough one, huh...
Marque, Em, Parc!
I got him...
Ouch!
We did it!
Haru-kun?!
Were you watching, Skullhell-sama?!
G-Gently, please.
O light, return to Lumiaris' divine protection.
Cure!
Is this... the booty?
Some animal's fang and... it's a silver coin?
And...
...to accumulate a Vice, the monster
must die by the hand of a Dark Knight.
Then, a body part must be offered to the guild's altar.
Well, an ear's kinda big.
A claw should work, right?
Didn't Moguzo deal the final blow?
What?! You're right! Moguzo, you bastard!
This was supposed to be my special first Vice!
Huh?
Ah, sorry.
He doesn't want to die, huh.
Damnit! Damn! Damn!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Da—
Damn...
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
Long Day
of the Trainee
Volunteer
Soldier
This is worth about thirty coppers.
This is a silver coin.
Yes, it's a little dirty and doesn't look like much...
If you don't like my price, go ahead and take it elsewhere.
It'll be about the same everywhere else.
I... see.
Is that a black wolf fang?
I'll buy it, if you'll take one silver for it.
What? This fang is worth that much?
Oh...
Yeah.
They're used as materials to make
charms against evil, among other things.
That's good.
What should we do now?
The sun's still high.
Why don't we call it a day and rest?
Yeah, sounds good.
I'm exhausted.
Me too.
I see.  Okay, then.
Well, then you're all excused for the rest of the day.
I'll see you all tomorrow.
Okaaay.
See you tomorrow.
You're a little more like a Dark Knight now.
Shut up.
What happened to eating bones and all?
You really are a nitpicker, bugging
me about every single little thing.
Not about every single thing.
See, like I sad, every single little thing.
But, well...
...it turned out all right.
I got to accumulate my first Vice, too.
What can you do if you accumulate a Vice?
I can summon a daemon.
And what can that daemon do?
It whispers and tells me if an enemy is near.
And sometimes it explodes a Daemon Joke.
Th-That's all?!
What do you mean "that's all"?
It'd be a perfect partner for me.
Indeed.
It'd be just right for you.
Right?
It's kind of ironic that we say it'd be a good fit for you,
when we don't even know what the daemon is good for.
Meow!
Wha?! Huh?
I-It's you?
Do you have a transformation skill like that?!
Of course not.
I was just thinking how pretty the sun
looked when it plopped onto my head.
Apologize.
Of course, I knew that.
Don't scare me like that.
You seem kind of flustered.
Shut up...
It really is beautiful...
The sunset.
Even though I pass by here everyday...
Maybe... I never had the time to notice.
Manato... you awake?
Yeah, I'm awake.
What is it?
I felt like I had a lot of things I wanted to ask Manato.
Like how we only made eighteen coppers a person today...
...and if we'll be okay from here on out.
But... when I tried to ask...
...the words didn't come out right.
No, uh...
Nevermind.
Oh? Okay, then.
Yeah.
Well, I guess today wasn't bad.
Nobody knows what will happen in the future.
Something even better might happen tomorrow.
So, it's good.
At least, for now it is.
Be back in a jiff.
Ranta, you're awake?
Where are you going?
The baths, of course!
The baths!
Huh?
You just took one!
Not to mention it's the girls time now.
What a numbskull.
You still don't get it?
Wait, are you...?!
I'm glad you're feeling better, but you
have got to draw the line somewhere.
Hm? I'm always feeling great.
Super great!
I'm burning so furiously that I can't hold back.
My passion is glistening!
Those are just carnal desires.
I thought you were studying the bath walls carefully.
Listen me carefully!
At this very moment, the girls are bare,
washing their hair and bodies, right?
Just imagine, eh?
There's only one thing a man should do!
You're shameless.
Call me Shameless-sama!
The great and noble Shameless King-sama!
You see?
Today we crossed a moral boundary.
Then it should be obvious.
Don't make me say it, it's embarrassing.
This and that has nothing to do with it.
Where are your morals?
Here I go!
Hey, wait!
Hey, Ranta!
Ranta-kun!
Ranta, you idiot! Sicko! Lecher! Pervert!
Get lost and never come back!
We ended up getting caught in the mess and apologizing.
Ranta, you idiot!
When I try touching
the dry air after a rain,
like a sprouting flower,
fragments of memories overflow.
The warmth you gave this hand
led me to a future I can treasure
always.
I chased your voice.
I wonder when you became so strong.
I will probably find what I searched the vast world for
at the end of this journey.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
Are Goblin Pouches Filled with Our Dreams?
Also
check
out!
Goblin's
Journey
Now
serialized
on the
official
anime
web
site.