Ergh, Haruhiro, you bastard!
Ranta, it's you?!
Watch where you're going!
You should, too!
Thanks!
There!
This is Yume's new skill, Star Strike.
I'm fine!
Go help that idiot Haruhiro.
Who are you calling "idiot"?!
Now! Spider!
Stay back!
What?!
Exhaust!
Come forth Dark Skullhell!
Cause limitless fear for those who don't obey!
Dread Terror!
This causes fear, making the opponent
unable to make clear decisions.
This is magic only a Dark Knight can cast.
This isn't what it's supposed to do!
Exhaust!
It does seem like it's confused.
Exhaust! Exhaust! Exhaust!
Anger! Exhaust! Avoid! Exhaust!
Need a hand?
Mind your own business!
He's my prey!
My rival!
Oh?
So it's his rival?
I just wanna call it that!
Hatred!
All right, c'mon!
Die!
Repeating a yesterday filled with scrapes,
We clear the path to a hopeful tomorrow.
I wonder what remains
in both these tiny hands?
The voice I raised upwards scattered into the air.
The reality I've gamed is hazy,
and even if I can't see ahead of me,
I can keep moving forward on this long road
if I'm with you.
Connecting a bond covered in dust,
We join back to back in the past and future.
Repeating an answer full of mistakes,
I will reach out my hands to seek the light, again and again.
That's a talisman.
A kobold's protective charm.
Every kobold has a talisman.
Ohhh...
But this doesn't look like it's worth much.
The ones in the first level of the
mine are ruffians among kobolds.
They're poorly dressed and weak.
That's why Volunteer Soldiers call them
low-class kobolds or lesser kobolds.
So the others will have better talismans?
Yes.
Well, no matter.
I'll be taking this.
What?
Nothing.
There's probably a nicer way of retrieving spoils from a fight.
But, well...
That's right...
To the kobolds, we're invaders.
Nothing changes even if we have pangs of guilt.
No matter if we take their nose rings off carefully
or tear them off violently, the end result is still the same.
The whole thing is still the same.
Ranta does it without hesitation,
but I'm trying to make up for that guilt.
That might be hypocritical of me...
...but...
...I don't plan to change how I do things.
No matter if they're an enemy or prey, I should
at least be paying my respects in this way.
Let's move.
The Cyrene Mine has more than ten levels.
Lesser kobolds, normal kobolds, and elder kobolds live here.
Only the elder kobolds can freely use the gondola.
The gondola?
There is a gondola installed in the
mineshaft from the third layer down.
We'll be mostly going up and down through the wells, though.
Is it because the gondola is heavily guarded?
Yes.
The elders are the leaders, the normal kobolds are workers,
and lesser kobolds don't hold any status.
The elders seem pretty stuck-up.
Normal kobolds dwell in the second level down,
so that's where things will get serious.
So the hard part is still to come, huh.
They're quite noisy.
They're always noisy at these times.
Sleeping kobolds only wake up
when there's something big going on.
Do you hear something?
Yeah.
Woah.
Is it... sleeping?
Should I get 'em?
Nice and quick.
What?!
It'd be some easy loot.
You—
Are you a demon or something?
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
I'm no demon.
I'm a Dark Knight.
Get it?
I serve the Dark God Skullhell-sama.
We believe that in death, all are equal.
The Vices that we value
are the antithesis of what you call in your
pretty little words "common sense" and "morals."
Antithesis.
It's an important concept, so I'll say it a third time.
Antithesis!
Eventually, you'll fall into death's embrace anyway,
so it's stupid to be bound by useless ideals.
We should be driven by things like
our desires, instincts, and impulses.
That's how it should be.
And at the end, we all die, just the same.
Get it?
I'm going.
Listen!
I'm listening, I'm listening.
No you're not!
Ohm, Rel, Ect, Nemun, Dash!
That's Shihoru's new skill, Shadow Bond.
The enemy can't move, as if their legs are stuck to the ground.
Just like Sleepy Shadow, it becomes less
effective the more worked up the opponent is.
Strong opponents can forcefully
break free from the spell, though.
C'mon!
Thanks!
It's here.
I know what to do.
I just need to follow it.
When I see the streak, I need to breathe calmly.
If I change my breathing patterns, it'll disappear.
I can't strain either.
There's no time to think that I can't miss this chance.
When I see the streak, my body is already moving.
That's how it should feel.
If not, it won't succeed.
Your new spell is amazing, Shihoru.
Th-Thanks.
These normal kobolds were nothing, too.
It won't be this easy from the third
layer down because of the elders.
They're armed and fight using tactics.
Why are you spacing out?
Aren't we going?
No.
Let's return to Ortana for now.
What?
It's not like we can't get back.
I'm afraid of getting used to this
place and becoming complacent.
What, that's boring.
Merry?
I'm fine.
I'm all right.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
I'm
Not Fit
to Be a
Leader
If we're talking about compatibility,
Ranta and I aren't very much so.
We were this close to starting a fight today.
He doesn't seem to be getting along
with Yume, Shihoru, or Merry either.
Can I just leave him as he is?
I guess I'm the leader, though.
What would Manato have done?
It's not like Manato really liked Ranta that much, either.
Maybe Manato didn't judge him
by whether he liked Ranta or not.
It didn't seem like Ranta was as defiant with Manato.
He was pretty shaken up when Manato died, too.
What's the difference between Manato and me?
Ranta?
What is it?
Can we... talk?
Maybe not here.
Want to go outside?
I guess.
I initiated this... but I don't know what to say.
I feel there are things we need to talk about, though.
How do you...
Well... how do you feel about things?
Like about our party.
Our party is our party.
Nothing more, nothing less.
What's that "nothing more, nothing less" mean?
What?
I feel I've been properly fulfilling my duties to the party.
You have?
Didn't you see?
Like today, I proved I could take
on an opponent single-handedly.
That?
That would've been over in an
instant if we had all surrounded it.
Can you guarantee that we'll always be able to do that?
Of course not.
If I can reliably take one on by myself,
we can what... broaden our tactics.
That doesn't mean—
No, I'm getting too worked up.
So he's been thinking about things in his own way.
I do think that Ranta functions as our secondary tank.
This is something that Yume and I can't do.
And of course we can't make Merry do it.
Manato died and Merry joined.
He's been thinking about his role in this party in his own way.
But that doesn't mean...
I wouldn't have known that unless you told me now.
It'd have been too late after the
fact if something were to happen.
So I have to consult with you for every single thing?
That's not what I mean, but I'm saying that there
are things I won't know unless you say them.
On top of everything, you're...
easily misunderstood, you know?
It's not like you think it's a misunderstanding.
Huh?
What you're really saying is that it's my fault.
What, because I'm misunderstood?
Then, whose fault is it?
Mine? Yume's?
Shihoru's fault? Moguzo's?
Or Merry's?!
What?!
We're working as a team...
...so don't we need teamwork?
And I'm not working as a team?
You think you are?
Hell, no.
You don't think so either?
Everybody has their strengths and weaknesses.
What about you, Haruhiro?
What are your weaknesses?
My...
...weaknesses?
I have those.
I almost don't think I have any strengths.
Why do I have to tell you?
So you won't say a word when it's about yourself?
Have I complained about your weaknesses?
Hm?
Listen up, Haruhiro.
It's because you happened to bring
this stuff up that I'm saying this.
If not, then I would've never brought it up myself.
I'm not interested in being all chummy with you guys.
You guys can go play pretend friends without me.
If you guys hate me, go ahead and hate me. I'm fine with it.
We're a party, so I'll fulfill my duty to the party.
That's what working as a team is about, right?
I'm off to bed.
Wow!
You use knives, too, right?
I'm not as good as you though.
Thanks... for the blanket.
You'll catch a cold sleeping out here.
I just kinda fell asleep.
I didn't know what kind of knife was good, you know.
And when I asked Master, he took me to the market, you see.
Oh?
And Master picked two for me.
And he said he would only buy one, so he bought one for me.
I was super happy.
I bought the other one myself, too!
Really?
That's great.
Yup!
O light, return to Lumiaris' divine protection. Blame!
This is Merry's new Light Magic.
It's short range and doesn't do a lot of damage,
but it numbs and slows down the opponent.
She wanted to increase the ways she could
support Moguzo and Ranta in the front.
Thanks!
Anger! Hatred!
Hatred!
You'll run out of breath if you keep shouting!
Shut it.
This is how I fight!
That was close!
Vice, Vice!
What if you hit me?!
If you died, I'd just get an extra Vice.
Congrats!
What the heck?
Right, if I remember that this is just how he is, I won't get angry.
No, I am angry.
I'm fuming.
Will I be able to let it go?
Here I go!
This is Moguzo's Fast Thrust.
It's a one-handed attack with a longer range.
He also learned Back Thrust, an attack
he can perform while backing away.
Let's all go for the elder!
Marc, Em, Parc!
Surround it!
We might be able to defeat him unscathed!
It's pretty different from the third level and above.
Is this... farmland?
Hey, hey, look here!
Those animals are pretty cute, huh!
Hm...
M-Maybe a little...
Hey.
Hm?
I was just trying it out.
I wouldn't really do anything.
How does "just trying it out" and "wouldn't
really do anything" make sense together?
It makes sense to me.
I see.
It makes total sense to me, get it?
I get it, I get it.
Then tell me what it means.
That it makes sense to you?
That's exactly what I said.
Shh!
Wouldn't it be faster for us to just kill 'em?
That's not a good idea.
From the fourth level down, we'll cause
a big commotion if we can't kill them instantly.
Now that they've been alerted,
it's better if we go down to the fifth level.
They have the advantage in open fields like this.
Merry?
Merry!
Well, what do you see?
It has white and black patches.
It's Death Spots.
You mean...
Death Spo—
Don't look!
When I try touching
the dry air after a rain,
like a sprouting flower,
fragments of memories overflow.
The warmth you gave this hand
led me to a future I can treasure
always.
I chased your voice.
I wonder when you became so strong.
I will probably find what I searched the vast world for
at the end of this journey.
Grimgar of
Fantasy and Ash
Between
Life and
Death
Also
check
out!
Goblin's
Journey
Now
serialized
on the
official
anime
web
site.