Why are we getting off?
Iwato Station Knights told us to.
The order came from Diamond Citadel.
They said they couldn't allow
the Hunters through.
How could they do that?
The Warlord fears Biba-sama.
Iwato's gate is the last fortress
before Diamond Citadel.
I suppose it wasn't going to be easy,
That is why we have prepared for this.
They told Biba-sama not to enter.
Does that mean we're going to be separated?
Now we'll be able to get away from them.
But...
Nameless...
Are you human or a Corpse?!
I'm neither!
I'm a Corpseless!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Corpseless of the Iron Fortress
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world
Chapter
Nine
Fang
of Ruin
Once we get past this,
the next stop is Diamond Citadel.
If the track maintenance doesn't delay us,
we'll make it in three days.
But without Biba-sama..
Is it true that there are Corpses
inside the Master Fortress?
Yes.
And not just one or two.
Probably over a hundred.
Then it's good that we have
distanced ourselves from them.
That's true, but...
Ikoma.
I agree that Nameless-san shouldn't
be there with them either.
She's...
I know.
I promise to bring her back.
Ayame-san.
It's time.
I am counting on you.
If this plan succeeds, everyone
is going to be able to be happy.
Indeed.
But we need your help
in order to do that.
Are you up for it?
Of course.
Lord Maeda has agreed to a meeting.
However...
...he will only allow women
and children to accompany you.
Just as I had predicted.
Get ready.
Okay.
Nameless...
That poor girl.
You lied to her, didn't you?
I did not lie.
Either way...
...it does not change
what has to be done.
What I have to do as well.
You decided to use me first because
Nameless has returned, didn't you?
Am I...
...going to die today?
Maeda-sama...
...I wanted to thank you for offering to
prepare the way to Diamond Citadel for us.
It is only natural for the Headquarters
to work for the people.
In any case...
...I'm sorry for stipulating that only women
and children would be allowed.
If I hadn't, they would not have
agreed to see Biba here.
You will be seeing Biba-sama?
He said he wanted to discuss
something about food provisions.
I'd like to accommodate him, but...
Maeda-sama is unfamiliar with the feud
between Biba and the Warlord.
He has put that behind him.
Otherwise, he wouldn't
have spent 10 years...
...fighting the Corpses for the Headquarters.
They're so stupid.
Did they think these men
would be able to stop us?
You must not be so overconfident, Nameless.
Those who underestimate their enemies
will not last long in this world.
Death comes swiftly and unexpectedly.
Don't worry.
That day won't come for us until we
bring my brother back to his home.
Ikoma!
They have arrived.
It is an honor to meet you.
I am the commander of the Hunters...
...Amatori Biba.
Nameless-san is here too?
It is an honor.
I finally get the chance
to meet the Great Liberator.
Please, have a seat.
Thank you.
Stop, Itagaki!
Biba-dono has come to talk!
He can still talk with a gun pointed at him.
Please sit down.
Brother!
I'd like to go to the toilet!
Toilet?
Hurry up, I can't hold it much longer.
Could I ask that someone take her?
Did you really see Nameless?!
Yeah!
She was with Biba!
Biba too?!
What is it?!
There!
It's Nameless!
It's almost time.
Yes.
They will be paid back in full.
If I'd kill them, Ikoma wouldn't shut up about it.
What?
Who authorized this?
It's not fair that they're only keeping us out.
I'm not letting them treat us that way.
Nameless!
What are you doing?!
I'm just letting the Master Fortress in!
After everything we've done
fighting the Corpses all this time...
...they won't let us in?
The Corpses?!
Why?
It's the Corpses!
The Corpses are coming!
Raise the bridge!
Get the explosives!
It's the Corpses!
The Corpses broke trough!
The tocsin?
Why are the Corpses here?!
Itagaki-sama!
Stop!
How brave.
I will stop her.
Yukina-san!
Did you deceive me...?
Did you deceive me, Biba?!
Your master is the one...
who deceived me first.
Why are the Corpses here?
Help!
No.
This can't be happening.
Nameless!
Get back here!
Ikoma, we can deal with her later!
We need to get back to everyone first.
Come on!
Yeah.
Get away from the door!
Hurry!
Don't break formation!
Hold back the Corpses!
Ikoma!
Has Ayame-sama returned?
Not yet.
Even if we returned to the Iron Fortress,
without the master key...
I will go.
Hold down the fort here.
This all...
...happened because I opened the gate?
Don't worry.
We're together.
Are you okay?!
Don't be afraid...
Wait!
What are you thinking,
doing something like this?
One needs fuel to accomplish anything.
Please come with us, Ayame-sama.
Allow me to treat my friend.
Ayame-sama!
Where has our lord gone?
You don't think he left us behind?
A  Railfort?
Who's operating it?
Who cares?
We're saved!
Don't get left behind!
This station is done for!
We have to get to Diamond Citadel!
Fire.
This is retribution...
...for the Headquarters's cowardice
over these last ten years.
Fireless.
Come.
Are you shaking?
I'm only scared...
because you're scared of me.
Me... scared?
You are always afraid.
What was that?
That's...
It's a Black Cloud!
"Chimera" is such an appropriate name.
A man-made hybrid colony
with a Corpseless at its heart.
This is so exciting.
How much will it be able to do?
I will liberate everything.
The land... the people...
...their fears as well.
Fireless.
Destroy the gate.
Fire!
Kajika-chan!
Don't worry, everyone will protect us.
Damn it!
Take the tank!
Okay!
Diamond Citadel, this is Iwato!
A Black Cloud has—!
Very nice.
We will be able to use that.
Diamond Citadel will not stand a chance!
Brother!
Nameless.
Good work.
Brother, wasn't the purpose of opening
the gate to let the Master Fortress in?
So why...?
Look, Nameless.
This is...
...the world of fairness and equality
that we've been striving for.
Fireless?
Is that Fireless?
This is sooner than I expected.
It seems the restraints
could not withstand the virus.
Soue-sama, we should give
the white blood to Fireless-dono.
It's no use!
There's no bringing her
back from this point—
Kurusu!
I have come to take back Ayame-sama!
Hey, out of my way!
Stop!
If you do not stop, I will throw this over!
Ayame-sama!
Quit that!
You don't even know what
that's worth, foolish gir!
Stop!
Kurusu!
F-Fireless... dono...?
Corpse...
F— Fire!
What the hell... is that?
Protect the commander!
Fireless, stop!
No...
What are you—!
Ikoma!
Do not resist.
We are interested in your blood.
Resist and we will simply kill you to get it.
Behold!
This is the world that has been
liberated from its cage!
I speak to all of you.
Abandon the stations...
...and join the fight!
There's no mistaking that you
have been bitten by a Corpse.
No way...!
Help me!
Stop!
I told you not to move.
Do it.
What are you doing?
What is it?! What is the meaning of this?!
Young master's orders.
To make sure you do not interfere.
It is here where...
...the cowards will die...
...and only the strong
will be able to survive.
That is the way of this world!
Biba!
Therefore, we...
...will destroy the very symbol
of mankind's cowardice...
...the Warlord's stronghold, Diamond Citadel,
and liberate us all!
Liberation!
Brother...
...is everything you told before...
...was a lie?
Even if the stars
That connect you make a sound
There are just dreams in the same rain
And lights are dried up
I am tired of getting answers
By mimicking others
Dawn without the sun
And broken morning
Smashed cry and dream
The ideal only has its doors
City is uplifted and drown in noise
I will still sing and stop turning the rudder
To hush silence