Oh, this is fun, isn't it?
Now try that "kapow-kapow."
What?
I'm not sure if I remember it.
When did you learn Kurusu's move?
The Corpseless are good at copying others.
How does it feel seeing his
swordsmanship be as good as yours?
What was that for?!
Do not flatter yourself
for copying one move.
Wow, that was so childish.
You're pretty closed minded, aren't you?
What?!
Ikoma, you steal that move too...
...and then use it right back on him!
Got it.
What?!
I see the station!
It's Shitori Station.
What's going to happen this time?
There are people!
Finally! A station with people in it!
Heeeey!
We can rest easy for a bit now.
Yeah.
Are you human or a Corpse?!
I'm neither!
I'm a Corpseless!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Corpseless of the Iron Fortress
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world
Chapter
Seven
Begging
the Heavens
We meet with the lord of the station.
I leave the Iron Fortress in your hands.
You can count on us.
You must attend to your duties.
Ayame-sama, we are out of daita-iron.
Daita-iron?
Material used for the jet bullets.
Its low evaporation point increases
the piercing capabilities.
Then could I ask you to get more?
Yes!
We need spare parts to repair
the Iron Fortress as well.
You're right.
Clothes and medicine would be nice too.
We have been asked to leave by the 8th.
Isn't the 8th is tomorrow?!
Then today is Tanabata, huh?
We've got better things to do
than hang our wishes on bamboo.
What is he talking about?
You don't know about Tanabata?
You write your wish on a card
and hang it from a bamboo tree.
I want to do that!
I'm not sure we have the time to.
We don't even know if we have
enough money to buy supplies.
Let's celebrate Tanabata.
Please use this for money.
Ayame-sama, that's...!
Can I ask you to handle it?
Yes!
Ready and...!
Did you hear?
It's Tanabata today!
I completely forgot!
The shopping team is
going to bring back bamboo.
Then we'd better write down our wishes.
Oh, the bamboo leaves are so very smooth.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Come on, stand still.
Honestly!
It's so pretty!
Look at those beautiful colors.
I can't wait to buy new clothes.
It'd be nice to be able to get
into some new clothes.
You're right.
And you're always practically naked.
It's not because I want to!
Let's split up here.
We will head towards the repair shop.
Okay.
Ready?
Yeah.
Nameless-chan, could you come with us?
But I don't know anything about shopping.
They won't try to treat us fairly without men.
Please, Master Bodyguard?
Okay.
Too expensive!
Way too expensive!
Come on, it's bruised here!
Give us a deal!
You don't have anything thicker?
Something this thin won't last three days!
I'll buy all this, so give me
a 50-percent discount!
You're charging 10 mon
for this skinny bean?
You've got to be joking!
I guess Kajika goes out
and fights battles too.
What's that?
Oh, those are fireworks.
In Shitori, we set off fireworks for Tanabata.
If you have fireworks,
you must have burst charges.
Would you be able to spare some?
Sure, but what do you need them for?
I thought I could use them as
a combustion agent for jet bullets.
Jet bullets?
Oh, jet bullets are—
Hey.
The barrel is acting up.
It's urgent.
One moment please.
I will get right to it after
I finish with this customer.
Huh?!
We were here first.
A lowly steam smith
would oppose a Warrior?
He was talking to me before you got here!
You damn outsider!
What have you done?!
Damn it.
Leave the screws!
Fix my gun first!
Pick it up.
What?
Didn't your mother ever teach you
to pick up after yourself?!
How dare you!
Terrible form!
I will be back to pick it up by evening!
You'd better have it fixed by then!
The Warriors have nothing on the Corpses!
Oh, right.
So jet bullets are...
Would you mind just hearing him out?
I'm sorry about this.
Hey, are you from the Iron Fortress?
My dad's on a Railfort too.
Really?
I guess that makes him one of us.
Yeah. It's called the Tree Fortress.
I'm sorry, I don't hear a lot
about other Railforts—
The Tree Fortress got
overrun by the Corpses.
Sukari!
Everyone on it got turned into Corpses...
...before it rammed into Aragane Station.
That's where we've escaped from.
Why are you telling him this?!
It's more cruel to have him wait for
a father that's never coming back.
I wish someone had
told me with my father.
You're lying!
You're lying...!
My dad's not...!
I mean...
...he promised... he'd come back...
Sorry.
I didn't mean to make you cry.
But... the real fight begins
when the tears dry up.
He's late.
We are unwelcomed guests after all.
Food is precious everywhere.
But not even granting us
an opportunity to negotiate...?
He's fighting the wrong enemy.
You sound like Ikoma.
Let me go talk to her.
Ayame-sama!
Ku-Kurusu!
This... isn't...
M-My apologies.
We should wait a little longer.
Are you sure?
Don't we need too—
Just a little longer.
What is this?
It is an honor to meet you.
I am Ayame of the Yomokawa Family.
I am Yamazaki the minister.
More importantly...
A gift for Shitori-sama.
They are jet bullets invented
by one of our young steam smiths.
Please, allow us to give you
a demonstration for your benefit.
Kurusu.
Yes.
Ready.
What amazing power!
This could pierce through
the Corpse's heart cage.
If you are interested, we can
include the blueprints as well.
My!
It is only natural to help
each other in a time of need.
I understand.
I will promise you your food provisions.
Could we ask if you could take in
our sick and injured as well?
Yes, of course.
Minister!
I am keeping the heir of Yomokawa waiting.
I ask that we keep this short.
I am Kogenta, representing the Headquarters.
This man is the former Ear of the Liberator...
I am Enoku.
What business do the Hunters have?
He is working for us now.
The Liberator will arrive here
in Shitori Station soon.
Leave us out of it!
Shitori has nothing to do
with your power conflict!
At the very least, you are
not altogether uninvolved.
Not after that day ten years ago.
I'm back.
Look at everything we bought!
Whoa, that's awesome!
Thank you.
I can take him now.
He falls right to sleep when
you carry him, Nameless.
Oh, and this.
What is it?
I had Kajika buy it for us!
Let's go home now.
We have this lovely bamboo now.
So that's what we need for Tanabata?
That's right.
You write down your wish on a card...
...and hang them up like this.
Well, let's go then!
We need to get back and decorate!
Why don't we grab a bite to eat in town?
Hey, good idea!
What's wrong?
Where's Nameless?
She was just here.
She didn't take her lunch with her.
Honestly!
Lunch?
He means this.
Oh.
There you are.
I looked everywhere for you!
What's with you?
You... forgot your lunch.
Oh.
Thanks.
You'd better say "Thanks"
before you drink it.
Thanks for the meal...
You know, I...
...have actually celebrated Tanabata before.
I just forgot about it.
But I remembered after
seeing the bamboo leaves.
Is that so?
My mom...
...was putting up decorations.
"Hozumi, we'll be able to see
the Milky Way tonight" she said.
Hozumi?
That's my name.
Before I met my brother.
I wonder how it's written...
Probably...
I'm sure your mother gave that name in hopes
that you can eat as much rice as you could.
Why are you laughing?
Because you're acting so serious.
I'm sure I'm right!
Then my mother was stupid.
Nobody's been able to make any rice in ages.
And that's not what we eat anyway.
We're talking like this now,
but we might turn into Corpses tomorrow.
Or maybe today.
It's something I always think about when I sleep.
When I wake up in the morning...
...will I still be me?
My mind might just be gone.
Then everyone would get bitten
by me in the morning!
What a way to start the day, right?
Stop it.
You should be human again.
Stop fighting the Corpses.
There's no need for you to fight
the Corpses if that's how you feel.
I've decided.
I'm going to turn you human again.
Then I'm going to fill your belly with rice,
just like your mother wanted.
Wait... uh... what are you talking about?!
You don't even know how
to turn me human again.
Besides, you'll need to rebuild
the rice paddies to grow the rice first.
You can't do that unless
the Corpses are gone.
I'm saying I'm going to do all of that.
That's impossible!
I'd be hard enough doing just one of them!
No, I've decided!
I'm turning you human again!
But if I'm not a Corpseless...
...I won't be able to fight anymore.
You won't have to.
There won't be any Corpses left.
Oh, right.
You're right.
We're back!
Oh, daita-iron!
Fantastic!
Wow, you're so good!
This is not what my sword
should be used for...!
What did you write?!
Hey, don't look!
Let's see now.
"I hope I can live through this and survive."
What else are we going to be wishing for?
Alright, I wrote mine too!
My wish is to...
...destroy the Corpses...
...and take back all our paddies and stations!
Don't you think you're asking for too much?
Then you're fine with just being alive?!
Not me!
I want more than just being alive!
I want more!
I have written mine as well.
My wish is...
...to reopen Aragane Station!
Was that a strange thing to wish for?
No.
I'm sure your father would be proud.
I thought so too!
They're right.
We should dream big!
Precisely because times are hard!
Alright!
I want to get rich and have
three beautiful wives!
Three?!
Dream big, right?
I want to become a teacher!
What did you write, Yukina-san?
I wished for my own Railfort.
Could I ride on it too?
Nope.
What?
What did you write, Kurusu?
Ayame-sama, you can't!
It will not come true
if it's seen by others.
Is that true?
I showed mine to everyone already.
No...!
That is...!
What did you write, Nameless-chan?
I wished to eat a belly full of rice.
Brother...
...it's okay...
...everyone's nice here...
Your brother was the one...
...who made you abandon the name "Hozumi"...
...and taught you that the weak
were only here to die?
If that's the case...
I...
It's the Hunters!
Long live the Liberator!
Who are those people?
The Hunters.
They're an independent force
created to exterminate the Corpses.
They have a long history
of defeating the Corpses.
They rid the land of the Corpses...
...and return it to the people.
It's Biba-sama!
He is so beautiful!
As expected of the Warlord's son!
Brother!
Nameless!
I finally made it back to you!
You're safe?
"Brother"?
Nameless-chan's brother is...
...Biba-sama?!
Are you alone?
Where is Shimon?
Aragane Station was
attacked by the Corpses...
But he died honorably.
I see...
May karma smile upon him.
But I am glad you are alright.
I have so much to tell you, brother!
The Iron Fortress has...
I have...
... to find out something.
That's...
...whether he's a true hero or not.
Even if the stars
That connect you make a sound
There are just dreams in the same rain
And lights are dried up
I am tired of getting answers
By mimicking others
Dawn without the sun
And broken morning
Smashed cry and dream
The ideal only has its doors
City is uplifted and drown in noise
I will still sing and stop turning the rudder
To hush silence