Don't drop the pressure!
If we stop, it's all over!
Yes, sir.
Make the announcement.
We're passing through the abandoned station.
Please brace for impact.
Damn it!
Get out of here!
Stay back!
What you need to survive...
It's not some tool that will
keep you hidden and safe.
It's the power to fight the Corpses without fear.
Shingo!
Are you okay?!
Yeah.
I owe you.
You...!
Twenty years ago...
...the people of Japan...
...have locked themselves in fortified stations out of fear of the Corpses.
They abandoned their pride and fellow man...
...and run away.
Use it.
Use it!
The suicide bag!
Hurry up!
Show us what you're made of!
Don't be a disgrace!
What are you doing?!
Pull it! Pull it!!!
Can we really be proud of our survival...
that's predicated on sacrificed our own?
And we lose not only the lives of our friends.
That's why...
...I...
Mother...
Damn it!
I want the power to defeat the Corpses.
I'm... so close!
You're awake?
The Warriors held them off.
You can go back to sleep.
For now.
Did...
...another station get overrun?
Chapter
One
Frightened
Corpse
Hey, did you hear?
They said the supplies are late.
I guess the front line fell back again.
How long is this place going to last?
Stop it, don't say that!
What if a Warriors heard you?!
Hey there, hero!
Running late?
Watch your calculation.
Plate 3 needs more adhesive.
Heeeey, Ikoma!
How did yesterday go?
No good.
It should have plenty of pressure, but...
What's wrong with using
normal lead shots again?
Because then it'd be the same
as the Warrior's steam guns.
It will just get repelled by
the Corpse's heart cage.
That's why we need jet bullets.
We need more penetrating power!
And you're going to use that to fight
the Corpses instead of the Warriors?
You must be insane or something...
Did you up the explosives?
Come on, because you just increased
the cavity in the last tune-up.
That's it, Takumi!
Why did I skip a step?
Where are you going?
I'm going home to start over.
Hey, hey!
At least finish your work here first...
Hey, it's Ayame-sama.
From the Yomokawa family?
I like to check everything myself.
Oh, isn't it Ayame-sama.
How can we help you?
It's my father's steam gun.
It's having some problems, so I was
hoping someone could take a look.
We would be happy to.
Ayame-sama.
She is beautiful.
She is the Warriors princess.
Ikoma!
Come here and help Ayame-sama!
Here's your chance, hero.
Allow me to take that.
Do you want to become a hero?
I just don't like having to run away.
Ayame-sama...
...where will you be pointing this?
The west gate is opening!
The Iron Fortress is coming!
The Iron Fortress should be coming tomorrow.
Let's go.
The Iron Fortress?
The Tree Fortress is supposed to come tonight.
Two Railforts in one day...?
Father, wasn't the Iron Fortress supposed to arrive tomorrow?
Hayatani Station has been lost.
With less stops to make,
of course it would arrive earlier.
No way...
Get the inspection box!
I wonder if anyone's been bitten.
That's what they're about to find out.
They search for bite marks to determine
if they have been infected by a Corpse.
If they find one, they throw them in jail.
It's what the authorities always do.
Well of course they do.
That one might be infected.
All right, start the maintenance!
Hey, look!
Just the carotid artery is thicker.
So the virus really does pass through here.
Hey!
It's rare to find this good of a specimen.
You're breaking the rules!
This isn't some curse.
We both know it!
What?
Some kid of a bigwig?
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
Hey!
You there, kid!
The exit is the other way.
Even children have to go through inspect—
Only a fool would judge a book by its cover.
It's what my brother always
told me, Mustache-san.
Wh-What did you say?!
Enough.
She is my guest.
My lord!
Are you the boss here?
I am Kensho, head of
the Yomokawa Family.
Yomokawa-dono, thank you
for your hospitality.
Shimon-sama, I presume?
I have read your letter.
We would like to take you
to our mansion first.
They're not going to be inspected?
What is going on?
Who are they?
No idea...
It's a Corpse!
He has a wound!
Don't let him get away!
A Corpse?
Stop right there!
No! I'm not a Corpse!
Stop!
Kill him!
Surround and kill him!
I swear, it's not a bite!
Please help me!
Stop!
Who the hell are you?!
He's saying he's not a Corpse!
Like we can trust him!
Stop, you coward!
Those suspected of being a Corpse
are to be locked up for three
days and kept under watch!
You're the ones who made the rule!
Shut up!
This matter doesn't concern a lowly steam smith!
I'm trying to tell you that you're pointing
your guns at the wrong targets!
Father!
Corpse's...?
Disgusting!
Why does he have them?
Answer me!
Why do you have something like that?!
He's getting away!
Don't!
He's died...
Which means...
He wasn't a Corpse?
Y-You aren't even ashamed?
Being so afraid of everything?!
For losing your sanity?!
Those are some lofty words.
A privilege afforded to you because of the
guaranteed safety the Warriors provide.
You're wrong!
I will fight too!
Kurusu!
Yes, sir.
I'm close to finishing the steam g—
Throw him in jail.
He may be a Corpse.
Father!
Let's go.
Ayame.
Defending order is also a Warrior's duty.
The order...
...is it?
I see.
You're both headed to Diamond Citadel?
Then, the Warlord-sama is...?
No, not yet.
That is why the two of us are going alone.
It's June.
Almost time, brother.
I knew it!
It's the corpse gatherer.
You're...
Nameless.
"Nameless"?
Is that a name?
Nice, isn't it?
My brother gave it to me.
Hey, did you know that the guy
from before, wasn't a Corpse?
No...
But I couldn't just ignore it.
Normally, you would.
Then there's something
wrong with being normal.
You're interesting.
What is it?
I mean, it's normal to be
scared of the Corpses, right?
People are generally frightened cowards.
They can do nothing about it.
Yes, they can.
They can do nothing
but kill others out of fear?
That's unthinkable to me.
You cannot lose your humanity to fear.
Ikoma is a dumbass.
Getting all worked up like that.
What a self-righteous idiot.
But...
...it's something I couldn't do even if I tried.
Talking back to a Warriors like that.
That's what makes him stupid!
It's here! It's the Tree Fortress!
It's right on time this time.
It's going too fast!
Slow down!
Damn it! Raise the bridge!
Hurry up!
It's too late!
What?!
It's the Corpses!
Out of the way!
That's...
...the tocsin?
Don't tell me...!
The Corpses are here?!
I have to go.
I need to get my piercing gun!
Hurry up!
I'm taking these too.
Nameless.
They have broken through the west gate.
This whole place is lost.
But—
We're going to the Iron Fortress.
Come.
Father, where are you going?
To the Iron Fortress.
You're not...?
Are you abandoning this station?!
I will give the signal when the
Iron Fortress has been secured.
Come when you see it.
The Corpses react to blood.
Damn it, that hurts!
Stop!
Take off your clothes immediately!
Are you kidding me?!
The Corpse are coming!
That's why you have to show that
you don't have wounds on your body!
What's going to happen to us?
Where's Ikoma?!
He took the bait!
I won't fail this time!
I've increased the explosives this time!
I did it!
My piercing gun...
...bore right through its heart!
My!
I did it!
I see it!
It's the Iron Fortress.
Nameless-dono.
You will have to continue on alone.
Go to Diamond Citadel...
...and please await the
Young Master's orders.
I leave the rest...
...in your hands.
May karma smile upon you.
It's not a curse.
I just need to make sure the virus doesn't reach my brain!
Five years...
It's been five years!
For whose sake I was working...
...to be able to fight the Corpses...?!
I'm...
...not the same as I was then!
I...
...will never run away...
...again!
This time...
I...
I will become someone I can be proud of!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Corpseless of the Iron Fortress
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world