"Corpseless"...?
Yes, something between a Corpse and a human.
You're... the same as me, then?
Either way, it means you're not human!
If you're saying you're my enemy...
...I'll kill you.
Corpses are the enemy of humanity.
Stop, Kurusu!
If not for these two...
...we would all be dead.
That does not mean we can have
the Corpses accompany us!
I feel the same way.
I'm a Corpse.
I will turn everyone here into Corpses.
Wh-What are—?
You're a Corpseless, not a Corpse.
Your body may be a Corpse,
but your mind's still human.
You want me to believe—?!
Ayame-san.
This Iron Fortress goes to Daimond Citadel, doesn't it?
Yes...
It does according to its schedule.
"Daimond Citadel"?
You don't know?
It's the Warlord's greatest stronghold.
Ayame-sama, if we are heading to Daimond Citadel—
Can you take me there?
If you do, we promise we'll stay in this car.
Hey, I'm trying to talk—
Although I'm not leaving this train
whether you agree to it or not.
Are you human or a Corpse?!
I'm neither!
I'm a Corpseless!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world
Chapter
Three
Prayer
Offer
Suzuki-san, that's too dangerous!
I have to look at it from the side.
I can't believe this.
Don't just open the window!
It's one per person.
We'll be back this evening with more food.
Like this is going to be enough.
Here you go.
Thank you.
And this is for your unborn baby.
There isn't enough food and water for
the number of people that are onboard.
Are we going to make it?
We still have to try.
It's the last safe place we can go to.
But what if Daimond Citadel doesn't take us in?
I have food rations.
The current elder is Ayame-sama's uncle.
We will not be turned away.
Stop!
You have oil all over your hands!
It's my body!
A body mother gave you!
Your body's healed, hasn't it?
It's because your body is a Corpse's.
You should be able to move around fine now.
You said you were going to Daimond Citadel.
I promised my brother.
I can't tell you what, but I'm on an important mission.
Are you interested in Daimond Citadel too?
They're at the forefront of Corpses research.
They might be able to do something...
about this Corpseless condition.
Didn't you want to get off?
It's not that I fully believe...
your "Corpseless" story.
But... if I'm trapped inside
this boiler car for three days...
...it will show that my mind will remain human.
Then it's decided.
Decided?
You'll ride the Iron Fortress with me.
And you will be my shield.
Shield?
When I fight for too long, I fall asleep.
That's why I need a living shield.
It's not like you have to worry about
getting bit by a Corpse, right?
Don't be ridi—
You're going to Daimond Citadel, right?
Then stand up.
We're going to start.
Start what?
Training, obviously.
You're not much of a shield right now!
Hold on!
Your motions are too big.
Your feet are dragging.
Wait!
How could you let the Corpse onto the train?
It's still not too late.
We should throw the Corpses off!
They promised they would remain in the rear car.
Like a Corpse knows how to keep a promise?!
Do the Six Chiefs not have
any sense of gratitude?
And that man has tried to do the right
thing even before becoming a Corpse.
Y-You cannot just barge in here!
They demand we stop the Iron Fortress.
They won't listen.
Please stop the train.
We want to hold a funeral.
We want to pray for our family.
Our prayers will not reach them if we go too far.
Do you want our grandchildren unable to pass on?!
You're hopeless, how many times do I have to tell you?
You spin around and boom, boom, bam.
You're not even close.
Ju— Just because you can do it...
...your explanation is terrible!
Get it together already.
You're already getting overpowered
when I haven't even removed my restraint.
What is that thing around your neck for?
Probably the same as yours.
It's just that if I remove mine,
I can fight at my full potential.
But after a while, the curse spreads and I get tired.
It's strange...
Corpse?
What is it?
H-Hey!
Nameless!
What are you doing?!
Please stop.
I saw it!
You have got two!
It's the Corpse!
The Corpse!
She's not supposed to come out!
It's the Corpse!
The Corpse are loose!
If definitely felt it.
Come back, Nameless!
You promised you were going
to stay in the boiler car.
Stay out of my way!
Don't move!
So much for "Corpseless."
I knew not to trust you.
Stop!
I'm taking Nameless back with me right now.
I'll make sure she cooperates
until we reach Daimond Citadel!
You think you can make me?
Nameless-san!
What is the meaning of this?
Why did you come out?
You promised me...
You wouldn't understand even if I told you.
Hey!
We never should have let Corpses onboard!
Let's remove them from the train now.
I'd like to see you try.
Stop it!
I've got bad news, Captain.
Seems like the water tank we
patched together is busted.
No way it's making it to the next station.
Are we stopping?
They're gathering water.
Check and see if the pressure's rising.
Yes, that's it.
There are no Corpses in sight.
How long do we need in order to repair the water tank?
We might be done by morning.
By morning...
We can have the lookouts rotate in shifts.
Good idea.
Then let us hold a vigil since
the Iron Fortress is stopped.
For those elderly people?
I would like to pray as well.
For my father.
Understood.
Please have mercy. Please have mercy.
What?
Is that true?
Yeah.
And pretending to be human.
Unforgivable.
Are you kidding me?
Hey, get back to work.
It's not like praying is going
to bring them back to life.
I'll do it.
You are the worst.
Did you lose someone too?
My teacher.
Were you particularly close with your teacher?
Scumbag.
That's just the kind of man I am.
You're not going to pray?
I lost my family years ago.
Oh.
Just like me.
It's a pretty common story.
Losing your family to the Corpses.
What's that in your right hand?
It hurts when I get hit by it.
Just a rock you can find around any river.
I found two of these pretty rocks with my sister.
I told her she could have both...
...but she said we should both
keep one as good luck charms.
I never planned on keeping it as a memento.
Five years ago...
...the Corpses broke through our station.
The adults fled in fear.
We were left behind.
And my sister was caught by the Corpse.
It's a pretty common story, isn't it?
But what do you think her stupid brother did?
He ran away.
I made an excuse about calling for help...
...and I ran from there.
I tried to rely on someone else.
By the time I returned...
...my sister was lying on the ground,
already beginning to change.
The cowardly brother cried and apologized.
"I'm sorry. I'm sorry."
But it was already too late.
My sister was gone.
Even if it meant dying with her...
...I should have overcome my fear and fought.
No matter how much I hate
myself for running away...
...my sister is never coming back.
Yeah, that's a pretty common story.
The weak die...
...and the strong survive.
That's all it is.
Do we do it?
Let me do it.
What are you planning on doing?
They are not our enemies.
They saved us.
The Corpses are our enemy!
What if they attack us first?
Please allow us to do this, Ayame-sama!
You people...
Ayame-sama?
Um...
Your friends are awful jumpy.
That's...
Fine with me.
If you want war, I am happy to oblige!
Hey!
Stop trying to act brave when you're weak.
Nameless, don't provoke them!
They're the ones doing the provoking.
Look! I knew the Corpseless were our enemy!
Don't back down!
We have to protect our families!
Purification!
Stop!
It's dangerous, please come down.
Please don't, Ayame-sama.
I can't?
I'm sorry.
Mother... won't be able to have you.
Shino-san?
It's the Corpseless!
Why are you here?!
These guys are jumpy too.
I didn't come to fight.
Hey, can you do me a favor?
Wh-What is it?
What's the matter?
Do you need to go potty?
Are you not feeling well?
He's laughing!
I got him to laugh!
Ikoma, you told my father...
...not to point our guns at the wrong targets.
Then!
Are the Corpseless our enemy?
Or are you our allies?
A-Ayame-sama!
Please don't!
As the one left in charge of the Iron Fortress...
...I have to ascertain...
...who our enemies are, and who our allies are!
Why aren't you using your right arm?!
Why don't you just grab and bite me?!
I can't!
Why not?!
Because I made a vow!
I won't run away anymore.
Even if it would save me.
I am not sacrificing any more lives!
It's the Corpses who are our enemy.
My purpose in life...
...is to destroy the Corpses!
Are you...
...satisfied now?
Those who still believe he is our enemy...
...you are welcome to come up here.
I shall give you the opportunity
to check for yourself.
I am sorry for testing you like that.
It's okay.
But why did you take the blade directly?
You could have grabbed my arm.
No... um... my strength...
It hasn't been long since I became like this, so...
...I was afraid I might have hurt you.
Oh, my.
You do not need to be so concerned.
Please worry more about yourself.
Okay.
Ikoma?
What happened?
Seriously! Stop!
That's so funny!
All that laughing made me hungry.
We have some dumpling soup.
I'll get you a bowl.
Thanks.
But I don't need that.
Just give me blood.
Blood?
It's red.
The stuff that comes out when you cut someone.
But you're...
A Corpseless.
I'm half-Corpse, after all.
It must be because of your bleeding.
Please hold on.
Are you kidding me?!
Are you telling us to become Corpse too?!
Get back, Kajika!
She's just a monster after all!
It's not my fault, I got hungry.
It's a Corpse!
Shino-san?!
Wait!
She's...!
She's... pregnant...
Ikoma?!
You are...!
Even if the stars
That connect you make a sound
There are just dreams in the same rain
And lights are dried up
I am tired of getting answers
By mimicking others
Dawn without the sun
And broken morning
Smashed cry and dream
The ideal only has its doors
City is uplifted and drown in noise
I will still sing and stop turning the rudder
To hush silence