Biba-sama!
Lord Liberator!
Long live Biba!
You know what, brother...
...there's another Corpseless
besides me on the Iron Fortress.
He said he did the operation himself.
Weird guy, right?
He did it himself?
That's impressive.
Biba Amatori-sama, I presume.
I am Ayame, heir to the Yomokawa family.
Yomokawa?
Then you are the elder's...
Elder Dogen Makino is my uncle.
They're all going to
Diamond Citadel too, brother.
We owe Nameless-san a great deal.
I had no idea she was your sister.
Oh, she is not my sister.
Huh?
He just lets me call him brother.
Ikoma!
Brother, this is the guy.
He's my shield.
So you are the Iron Fortress's Corpseless.
I am—
I know who you are.
You are the one who taught Nameless...
that the weak are expected to die.
Hey, Ikoma!
Nameless, why don't you
visit the Sickbay?
Have your body inspected.
Okay.
It is a bit loud here.
Would you like to talk inside?
Ikoma-kun, you as well.
Are you human or a Corpse?!
I'm neither!
I'm a Corpseless!
I will remember that day
Losing myself
In steam
Countless mistakes are made
When I can't see anything ahead
You said
"Ask your own burning blood"
Answer my beat
Corpseless of the Iron Fortress
Stand up
And slam everything onto the ground
My soul is devoted to my friend
Burn your life
Change the world
Chapter
Eight
The
Silent
Hunter
I am humbled.
To have the Warlord's son
guide us himself...
I have already been disowned.
I am no longer my father's son.
Oh, but...
Stay back.
What is it?
Biba-sama.
Well, there is a leak, and we're
unable to build pressure.
We have been fighting
constantly after all...
I'm sure it must have come loose.
Do you have a wrench?
No, you mustn't, you will get dirty.
Fighting Corpses is dirty work.
Udo, you shovel the coal.
Yes, sir.
Fireless, please go on
ahead with Ayame-sama.
Yes, sir.
This way, please.
Shall I help?
You might need filler.
I have some on me.
Yes, I'd appreciate it.
Please wait here.
Okay.
What's this?
This is no place for a princess.
I'll take your sword.
We have been invited by your lord.
I have no reason to
hand over my sword.
I wasn't going to need it for long.
What?
What is the meaning of this?!
Don't get me wrong.
Let's all be friends here.
Friends.
Ikoma-kun...
...to answer your earlier question...
The strong survive and the weak die.
Do you not believe that
this is how the world works?
But...
...I can't agree if you're saying that
the weak don't have the right to live.
I fully understand that.
However...
...I'm not talking about
casting anyone away.
I'm talking about saving them.
Nameless saved herself
by choosing to fight.
What do you mean?!
What is important for survival...
...isn't the ability to hide
and protect yourself.
It is to stand up and
fight the Corpses.
Am I wrong, Ikoma-kun?
Look at those numbers...
Can we really stop... all of them?!
They brought the Corpses here
on purpose to put our people in danger...
Do not worry.
The Beaters will
take care of the Corpses.
I'm sure the Liberator
himself will join the battle.
And when he does...
The west gate!
Hurry!
What will you do, Ikoma-kun?
I will fight!
I see.
Then I shall see you
out on the battlefield.
Yes!
So they've come.
How many?
Seven hordes.
They have spread out
in front of the wall.
There's no danger of
a hybrid colony here.
Fifteen minutes is all we need.
Just enough for one canister.
We will deploy with light arms.
After you slow them with
cannon fire, we will clean them up.
Understood.
Forge by fire, prove in combat!
We can't use the Guardian Cannon
because they're too close!
Be careful!
I will!
In the end...
...I guess this is all we can do.
That's Biba's Railfort!
Incendiary bomb!
Fire!
All hands... charge!
Amazing...
They went to face them
outside the walls...!
That's right.
If you wantto defeat the Corpses...
...you have to get close!
A stray Corpseless?
My guess would be that he
has a high pain threshold.
Take care of everyone...
Brother, let me!
Okay, take care of it Nameless.
Fireless, give her a hand.
Yes, sir.
Another Corpseless?!
Enoku, huh?
It's begun.
You do not know...
...just how many people
are after your life.
I am here after having met
some of them face-to-face.
I am to kill you at the first opportunity!
I see.
I can tell you where they are.
All you must do... is ask it of me.
Give me the order here...
and I shall do as you bid!
I have no need of you.
Be gone.
Is that...
...your...
...answer?!
H-Help me!
You lied to me.
You already decided you would betray me.
You are weak.
Stop!
Why... did you kill him?!
He asked for help!
Ikoma!
Leave it to the commander.
Is this man your blood?
Perhaps a long-lost brother?
No!
Then why are you so upset
over a man you barely know?
Because he was asking for help!
Stop it, you idiot!
Biba-sama was the one in danger!
I'm so sorry.
I promise I will talk to him.
I would also like to offer my apologies.
It is just as we feared!
If Biba could be killed
by some assassin...!
Who goes there?!
Please come with me.
I'm sure he only felt sympathy for him.
Please forgive him.
Very well.
In any case, it seems
there is still much danger.
If you would like, we could accompany
your Iron Fortress to Diamond Citadel.
We can rest easy knowing
Biba-sama will protect us.
Yes.
We've all but made it
to Diamond Citadel.
Is it really that easy?
Did I make the right decision?
It will reduce the Corpses threat.
Is there something that bothering you?
No.
So, what's bothering you so much?
He taught Nameless that
the weak are expected to die!
He's not exactly wrong.
And Nameless said that she's never
been bitten by a Corpse before!
Doesn't that mean...
...that she was made into a Corpseless?!
Let's talk outside.
Fight.
If you want to live...
...you'll have to save yourself!
That's right.
Your mother...
...would have lived if she were not weak.
Live on your own.
Do not rely on others.
You no longer need a name
for people to call you with.
From this day forth
you will be Nameless.
Indeed the bruise is quite large...
...but it should not be a problem.
Are you afraid?
No, I'm fine.
We're so close to getting
you back to your home.
You're strong, Nameless.
Perhaps I could ask you
to do one thing for me then.
What did you say, brother?
Get the Iron Fortress's master key for me.
But Ayame-san has the master key!
Is this Ayame-san...
...stronger than you, Nameless?
No.
She's not, but...
Then... there shouldn't be an issue.
L-Lord Biba!
What is this place?!
What are you going to do with us?!
I have not forgotten what I've done.
That is why you tried to kill me.
I only have one thing to ask you.
Who left us on that
battlefield 10 years ago...
...to die at the hands of the Corpses?
You were... in charge of supplies
at that time, so you should know.
Stop!
Do not lay a hand on Hirotsuka-sa—
Would you like...
...a new hole in your head as well?
I-It wasn't me!
It was the Warlord!
Don't kill me!
What is it?
It's the Corpses!
The Corpses are here!
Over there!
On the Master Fortress?!
There are a lot of them!
What are they doing...
...transporting Corpses?
Nameless-san?
Do you need something?
Yes.
Give me...
...the Iron Fortress's master key.
What?
The master key.
The one you have.
Why do you need the master key?
Are you not going to give it to me?
Are you going to use it?
Or did someone ask you
to get it for them?
Enough questions, just hand it over!
Nameless-san...!
You won't be able to
beat me... Ayame-san.
So just...
...give me...!
I have the master key here.
What?
I was using it for some
coupling work I was doing.
May I hand it to her?
What? Yes...
Thank you.
Yukina-san, what did you hand her?
The key to the boiler room.
In any case, why would
she need the master key?
I can't imagine it was
Nameless-san's idea...
Ayame-sama!
Please come with me!
It's Ikoma!
Huh? A fake?
This key is to the boiler room.
That can't be!
Because—!
They lied to you.
Unfortunately...
...it seems that they do not trust us yet.
Commander.
The Corpseless man is at the freight car.
Open this!
Is nobody here?!
Ikoma?
Nameless.
If he forces his way in here...
...we will have to kill him.
I know.
I'll turn him away.
Why are you here?
Nameless... you have to come back
to the Iron Fortress with me.
I have to ask you something!
There he is!
Let's trust him.
Biba is hiding a horde of Corpses
on the Master Fortress!
You must have heard it too.
You mean the Sickbay?
You knew about it?!
It's because we have
to know our enemy.
Did they use that technology...
...to turn you into a Corpseless?!
That's right.
I asked my brother to
turn me into a Corpseless.
Why would you do that?!
It's because brother told me...
...not to be weak like my mother!
To become strong!
It was the only way for a child
like me to become strong...
Do you still want to talk about this?
It's not like you'd ever understand.
No!
You shouldn't be in a place like this!
Stop!
I am staying with my brother!
Why does he use his power to kill people?!
It's... something a coward
who's scared of dying does!
You don't know anything about my brother!
So watch what you say!
Nameless!
Trying to protect yourself
is not being a coward.
There won't be any more reason
to be sad if we all just become strong.
What my brother says is right.
Not that I expect liars
like you to understand!
Wait, Nameless!
Don't go!
Biba...
He's no hero.
At that time...
...he was smiling.
Even if the stars
That connect you make a sound
There are just dreams in the same rain
And lights are dried up
I am tired of getting answers
By mimicking others
Dawn without the sun
And broken morning
Smashed cry and dream
The ideal only has its doors
City is uplifted and drown in noise
I will still sing and stop turning the rudder
To hush silence