Recollection
Stop
Hachikuji Mayoi
Cut number 22
Hachikuji!
It's been so long!
You're so damn cute!
Let me touch you! Let me hug you!
Ooh, I'm gonna see your panties!
Transparent view
Enlargement
Oww!
The hell are you doing!?
Don't worry, I'm not an enemy!
Calm down! Take a deep breath!
You breathe like a Terminator.
Araragi's heartbeat / Murmur
Cut number 47
It's me! Me! Take a good look!
Muraragi
Cut number 52
Oh, it's Muraragi.
Don't call people things that sound so unsatisfying.
Sorry, I stuttered.
No, you did it on purpose.
I bit my tongue!
It wasn't on purpose!?
God is with us.
Koyomi
Mayoi
What miracle happened to you!?
Red
Unnumbered cut
Black
So you've been studying for your exams?
Well, I can get help from the valedictorian and the 7th-best.
Honestly, I'm invincible.
White
Unnumbered cut
Hanekawa's the one with braids that I met, right?
Yeah.
And Senjogahara's your girlfriend.
Got a problem with that?
I figured you'd go for Hanekawa between the two of them.
It seems kind of weird that you'd pick Senjogahara.
Why I'd...
I don't think of Hanekawa like that.
I owe her too much, and she'd probably shoot me down anyway.
Plus, I'm into-
Well, if you say you'd rather Senjogahara,
I guess that's right. It takes all kinds.
Cut number 77
I guess.
Cut number 78
It's "everyone has a type", isn't it?
Back
on
topic
Cut number 79
By the way, Araragi.
About that vampiress.
Um... She's going by Oshino Shinobu now, right?
Looks about eight, blonde, with a helmet and goggles?
What about her?
I wasn't able to get close so I can't be sure,
but I think I saw her around yesterday.
At around five at night,
at the donut shop by the highway.
Donuts, huh.
Would Oshino really let her go out alone like that?
Yeah, I thought the same thing.
I thought I should tell you, so I waited for you here.
Really? Why didn't you say so sooner?
I'm sorry.
Some pedo came up to me and started groping me.
I was so shocked that I forgot all about it.
Oh, really? Sorry I gave you the wrong idea.
I'm just glad I could help you out.
Anyway, do you have the time?
Oh, right.
Later, Hachikuji.
Sure. I know we'll meet again.
Cat ears.
Cat ears had
sprouted from
Hanekawa's cute
little head.
I stayed silent and bit my lip.
Hard enough
to draw blood.
Don't laugh...
I have to be serious.
Can't laugh.
Saying something so solemnly to someone,
then having them break down laughing
is like a gag from a comic.
Above all, I can't do that.
I told her I wouldn't.
But, those ears
They fit so well
with her
neatly-trimmed
bangs, it's like they
were made for her.
I thought so during Golden Week too.
She's the kind of
woman who was born
to wear cat ears.
On the other hand.
During the nightmare
of Golden Week she didn't
have them when
she was Hanekawa.
So this just blows me away.
Body
Right, right now, her ears
and their fur
are black, like her hair.
Yellow
Unnumbered cut
Episode 13
Tsubasa Cat part 3
Font used in video:  HGP Mincho B
New mail
Hanekawa Tsubasa
1 message
Oh my.
Where are you going, Araragi?
Not far.
What are you going to do?
Volunteering.
I see.
Very well. Go ahead, Araragi.
I'll take pity on you and answer roll call for you.
Do it for me?
I'll say it in your voice, so it should be fine.
Leave it to me.
Voice actress / Saito Chiwa
(I'm enterprise)
Cut number 125
Born in Saitama, does both strong and weak female,
enthusiastic girl and boy roles.
Sometimes also plays animals or nonhumans or roles calling for an eccentrically deep voice.
Is cast as many different types of character.
My voice actress is excellent.
Voice actress!?
What is this, an anime!?
You're so beautiful, Hitagi.
The woman I've always dreamed of. I love you.
How was it? Pretty good?
Not even close! I'd been looking forward to it, but it doesn't even match what I imagined!
I haven't even said anything like that yet!
"Yet". So you plan on it in the future?
Yeah!
Rohaku Park
Bike parking
Hey, Hanekawa!
Araragi!
You're not supposed to ride your bike in the park.
There's parking for it.
This is no time to worry about that!
We're skipping school, quit worrying about biking.
They're completely different problems.
Just hurry up and stop.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Sorry to make you skip school, Araragi.
No problem.
Did you think I was angry? I wasn't trying to be sarcastic.
Don't worry, I planned it all out.
You won't have any trouble being absent from today's classes.
An unpleasant
plan
Cut number 157
But what's going to happen to the preparations for the arts festival with the class pres and VP gone?
I'm having Senjogahara take care of things after school.
Isn't that a mistake?
She took yesterday off.
So it's only fair.
Black
Unnumbered cut
These have gotta be her pajamas.
Hey, Hanekawa.
What?
No, Miss  Hanekawa.
Miss?
Let me take your shirt.
Araragi.
Yes?
You're making me angry.
Sorry.
Okay, I'm done joking around.
What's wrong, Hanekawa?
Headache
Cut number 177
Those headaches again?
Headache
Cut number 179
No, I'm feeling better now.
Araragi... About Golden Week...
I remembered something.
Oh.
No, it's not that.
I feel like I'm remembering something I forgot.
I see.
A kitty.
It's a kitty.
Recollection
I remembered that.
The kitty we buried together.
I remembered it.
But you didn't just call me out here because you remembered it.
Yeah.
Oddity
Cut number 194
An oddity, huh...
Yeah.
So I'd like you to show me how to get to Oshino's place.
Can you show me the way?
Of course.
... Of course. But can I ask you a couple questions first?
I guess. Why?
I've been leaning too hard on Oshino to fix oddities for me.
Even if I end up making it his problem,
I want to have a handle on it first.
Okay.
Fine, go ahead and ask.
You said you've had lots of headaches lately. When exactly did they start?
Around a month ago.
Yesterday and the day before were both when I was with you,
and I've had them pretty bad at the bookstore and in front of school too.
You should have told me then!
Sorry.
I didn't want to make you worry.
Oh well, don't worry about it.
So, after Golden Week,
has anything happened to you involving cats?
Cut number 207
Something involving cats?
Even just a black cat crossing your path.
From the
program
broadcast
on 5/27
Cut number 155
On May 27th,
Listener mail
Cut number
the radio show I listen to at night read a letter from someone named "Big Bear Cat".
Do you think that's related?
No, I don't.
Speaking of which, this is what it said.
People in comics and anime seem to have it really easy,
but being a maid must be incredibly stressful work.
They don't have any time to rest.
I heard this at a mixer recently, and it's right on the money.
You don't need to go into that much detail.
By the way, Araragi. Don't you think there was something funny about that letter?
I can't quite put my finger on it, though.
Um... He heard that maids never have any spare time,
from someone he met at a relaxed mixer.
That's funny.
Why did you even need to tell me about that letter!?
Oh, I see. I didn't quite get it the first time.
Big Bear Cat
Cut number 209
Plus, if you think hard about it, a "Big Bear Cat" isn't a cat, it's a panda!
Big Bear
Cat
Panda
Cut number 209
Oh, you're right.
Anything else?
Anything?
Well... On the same show, there was a guy named "the Posturing Waggler".
Listener mail
Cut
number
"Lately, when I've played Asshole with my friends,"
"after someone deals, one of them keeps saying things."
"Things like 'when I was in middle school, 4 was the highest card'."
What's funny about this?
When I asked whether there was anything else, I didn't mean any more hard-to-understand letters.
Plus, about that letter, in Asshole there's all sorts of weird rules
like "8s go out of turn" or "anyone who's no longer President becomes the Asshole".
The joke is that they pick the best rules for the hand they've drawn.
Oh, I see! I knew you'd get it.
You thanking me for this doesn't make me happy.
suburiwosurusoburi
Cut number 225
Also, about the pen name "the Posturing Waggler",
the Posturing Waggler
Cut number 225
"Posturing" and "Waggler" are written with the same kanji, so it's a bad pun.
But not all the letters to the show are that hard to understand.
Listener mail
Cut
number
Someone named "Walk toward the apple" wrote.
"Yesterday a friend and I went to a video rental place."
"We wanted to rent the DVDs of a certain serial drama,"
"but someone else had volume 8 out,"
"so we were only able to run up to volume 7."
"My friend said 'volume 7 makes it seem like it ends in 8.'"
"'The person who has volume 8 out now must be chuckling.'"
"I think the person who rented volume 8 is playing Sevens."
That's pretty funny, but quit talking about the radio!
Anyway.
Next question, Hanekawa.
Will you take off your hat?
That...  That's not a question, Araragi.
Really?
Really.
Miss  Hanekawa, let me take your hat.
Araragi.
Yes?
You're making me angry.
Then be angry.
If you want to be angry, go right ahead.
I care more about my debt to you than our friendship.
What do you mean, your debt to me?
Spring break.
That... But that's...
Didn't you just save yourself?
No.
Oshino may say so,
but I think you saved me.
I owe you my life.
I want to do something for you in return.
If I do, even if you get angry or hate me, I can take it.
Take it, huh.
That's pretty saucy.
Really?
Coming from you, it's saucy.
That's something a bully would say.
I didn't expect to hear it from a star pupil.
Yeah.
Don't laugh.
Are you done yet?
This week's password
Cat            ears
Ah, yeah.
Thanks
Cut number 280
Thanks.
Why are you thanking me?
Well... Okay, yeah.
It feels like Golden Week again.
If it's that, we can deal with it.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's go to Oshino's.
Don't tell me you're going to complain that doubling up on a bike is against the law?
I kind of want to, but I'll let it slide.
I made you skip school, so it's fair.
Isn't calling that a fair trade kind of weird?
They're both
because
of you
Cut number 287
Red
Unnumbered cut
All right, get on.
Let's go.
Her
two
breasts
Cut number 295
They're soft.
And big!
Araragi.
There's something we need to talk about after we get off the bike.
Red
Unnumbered cut
All right, let's get going.
Even still, it must be so much trouble for you.
You have to take care of so many people.
So many people?
Like Senjogahara, and Mayoi, and Kanbaru,
and Sengoku yesterday.
They're all girls, huh.
Shut up.
And always with oddities, now that I think of it.
It seems like you're not done yet.
That's right.
There's no way Senjogahara really recovered that quickly.
It started when you were attacked by a vampire over spring break.
That's when it all began.
The oddities themselves were always there.
It's not like they just showed up one day.
Did you know, Araragi?
Know what?
One of the special powers of vampires.
They captivate humans with their charm.
Captivate?
It's like hypnotism.
One gaze into those eyes can captivate someone for life.
So what?
Nothing, just a thought I had.
Maybe it has something to do
with why you're so popular with the girls all of a sudden.
Sorry, I'm just teasing.
Don't worry.
If anything, it helps me understand.
Charm, huh.
You know everything.
I don't know everything.
I don't know anything...
I don't
know anything...
Cut number 321
Black
Unnumbered cut
Hey, it's Araragi.
And the class prez, right?
Her hair's different, but with those glasses it's gotta be her.
Long time no see, Prez.
Araragi, I saw you yesterday.
What, can't you say "I've been waiting" or "I stayed up waiting"?
Nothing like that today?
Black
Unnumbered cut
Huh? Really?
What's up, Prez?
You have today off?
I don't really think he's trying to sabotage you.
Oh, that's it?
Must be the Foundation Day I've heard about.
Well, no.
A cap?
That cap looks good on you.
Thanks.
So that's what you're up to, Araragi?
You really can't even take three steps without getting in trouble.
Anyway, come on in.
To be honest, I'm really busy right now, Araragi.
I'm so busy I don't have any spare time.
I see.
Oh well, I don't mind.
You're you, but I've gotta be a bit accomodating if Prez comes to me with a problem.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Cut number 348
A blocat.
It has to be considered one of the three legendary cat spirits.
You're you, but I don't even need to tell this to Prez, do I?
Hey, stop it with the "You're you, but" when you mention Hanekawa.
It's starting to get to me.
I'm not doing it on purpose.
I just can't tell a lie.
You'd better keep your eyes open at night.
Don't worry. I'm a night owl.
Cats are night owls, too.
Hanekawa!?
Don't get worked up, Araragi.
Feels good.
Isn't it a good thing?
Getting to see Prez's cat ears,
getting to see her in her pajamas,
Don't judge me like that!
You're misunderstanding!
It's not a misunderstanding, is it?
If anything, you should thank me for giving you an excuse to bike the whole way here
with Prez's arms wrapped around you.
You've already scouted out the situation, haven't you.
What happened with the shyguy the day before yesterday must have woken you up.
So Sengoku's a shyguy?
Anyway, what's happening?
With what you've learned, I don't really have anything to do.
I'm gonna skip a step here.
Skip a step?
There's no time, right?
And it's quicker to ask her herself than bother Prez.
Herself?
But...
Yeah.
Here she comes, Araragi.
Here comes the sex kitten.
So we meet again, human. I'm amazed.
And it looks like you haven't been punished for lusting after Mistress's boobs.
You're always such a bad boy.
Do you want to be eaten up?
Bakemonogatari
Cat
Tsubasa Cat part 3
Continued next episode
Preview
Dialog
Nisioisin
Cartoon
Haritama Hiroki
I'm Karen!
I'm Tsukihi!
Hey, about baseball.
About baseball?
We went to advertise in Akihabara
We went
DVD On sale
You can't question the ump, can you?
You can't.
The ump's judgments are absolute!
We got lost
But you can try to fast-talk him.
Fast-talk him?
Heyhehehehey ump don't pretend, you had to have seen that was an out.
Let's ask that girl
Let's
Sometimes it works!
Cunning!
If you do it at the wrong time, you get ejected!
Get outta here, you bum!
Preview quiz!
We went to advertise in Akihabara
We went
DVD On sale
Quiz!
Preview squeeze!
Squeeze?
Squeeze means bunting!
Bunting?
What's a safety squeze? I don't get it!
We got lost
I don't get it at all! What's safe about a sacrifice bunt?
It's sacrificial! That's a paradox, make up your mind!
Let's ask that girl
Let's
Being so vague makes it confusing! What's with a bunt that makes you safe by sacrificing you!?
That wasn't a quiz, that was qust a complaint!
Next time, Tsubasa Cat part 4!
Next episode
Tsubasa Cat part 3
A bunt to advance the runner!
We're completely lost
Canned
oden
Shinobu
A failed bunt.