Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
as the war rages on
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
That blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
Both "Shao Pai Long," the fantasy kung-fu
movie made aboard the Macross,
and footage from the collapse of
the Omni-Directional Barrier
have been sent to the Zentradi's
main Bodol fleet.
Seeing these things sends
a shock through Bodolzaa.
Shao Pai Long!
To save a diseased city, he has returned
Evil's slayer! Slayer! Slayer...
These are the miclones?
And they possess weapons this powerful?!
I don't believe it.
If this is true, they are beings to be feared!
LOVE CONCERT
Zero-g love, zero-g love!
With him after school, on my way home
At the corner of that same old intersection
This is called "song"?
It feels good!
But is it true that the real one
is aboard the Macross?
He made sure no one else was around
It's true.
And watching the real one sing in person
makes you feel even better!
Then without warning, he kissed me
Wow, "song" sure is great.
And I was so angry, I led him to think,
What are you doing?
You're gonna break it!
Just watch.
If you push this down,
it will play another song.
ANOTHER song?
You mean there's more than one song?!
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
My boyfriend is a pilot
Shining, making a rapid descent
Then BOOM! he...
"Song"?
What's that?
If you listen to it, it makes
you feel really great!
I've never felt so good before!
Well, where is it?
Warera Nantes has it.
Come on!
A disturbance aboard Britai's ship?
Yeah, those three spies he
sent aboard the Macross
brought a bunch of strange
things back with them,
and it's causing a lot of commotion
among the men.
So that's all this is about?
Not just that.
Some of these guys are saying they'd like
to surrender and live on the Macross.
Surrender?
To the enemy?!
And it's not just one or two of them either.
Unacceptable!
I will not tolerate talk of surrender!
Why are they saying this?!
I don't know really know
the details...
Do our superiors know about this?
Dunno.
This damn Macross!
It's gotten everybody running scared!
At this rate, I'll have to destroy
the Macross myself!
A miclone...
You want us to capture a miclone, sir?
I have reviewed all the materials
you sent me.
My order is in response to that.
I'm almost certain that these people
are the Protoculture.
That means they pose an
extreme danger to us.
You must capture a miclone and
once again study it in detail.
Once this is complete, we will
move to the final stage.
Final stage?
What would that be, sir?
Contact with beings who possess culture has
always had a negative effect on our soldiers.
To avoid that, we must gather all the data
we can and then annihilate the miclones!
Understood, sir.
We will capture a miclone at once.
On the Macross, a girl the size of this photo
lets other miclones listen to her songs.
Let me see!
No, let me!
We are about to attack the Macross.
All personnel, report to your battle stations.
I repeat, we are about to attack the Macross.
We're going to attack the Macross?
Hey, what do we do?!
If we attack the Macross, we'll kill this girl!
We won't get to hear her songs anymore!
It's not just songs.
They have all sorts of things that we don't.
And all of it will be gone...
Let's surrender!
We can surrender and live on that ship!
But how?
If we try thinking this through,
we'll never do it!
During the attack, if we see a chance to
run to the Macross, we take it!
All right, I'm in.
And me.
If we're discovered, they'll
execute us for desertion!
We'll worry about that once it actually happens.
Take me with you!
To the Macross, and all the stuff we don't have!
Okay, I'll go too!
Me too!
And me!
All right, we'll all go!
But first we'll have to become miclones.
Do you guys know how to work that machine?
No.
Then how are...
Don't worry.
Someone in this group knows how.
Torakajiide!
I can't!
If I operate the machinery without
authorization, I'll be...
If we're discovered,
we'll all be facing that!
You want to hear a real song, don't you?!
I do, but...
Then help us!
I'll give you this!
And the doll and everything!
Everything?
Come with us!
There's a whole lot of culture
that'll make you feel good!
And she's not the only woman
there, you know!
All right!
What am I doing here?
The only thing that's here
is a meaningless war.
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
My boyfriend is a pilot
Shining, making a rapid descent
Then BOOM! he makes a sudden climb
Minmay...
Leaving a long trail of vapor
He traces two big hearts
A love sign in the big, blue sky
"I love you, you love me?"
But he's head over heels
For his plane instead of me
Of course. Minmay!
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
I can fight to protect Minmay.
My boyfriend is a pilot
That's enough. That's enough...
If I can't get away from here, then
fighting for her sake is enough.
Thank you, everyone.
And now, I'll sing "Love Drifts Away."
Please enjoy it.
Beautiful...
She looks especially lovely today.
Time drifts away,
love drifts away.
Standing before me, a sad look on your face,
It'll be nice if the enemy doesn't
come today, huh?
I know you're going off to war.
I want to feel a passionate love
like in the song too!
Silly girl!
Hey! Hey!
All the men, together, as if possessed,
With mouths pulled tight, with eyes burning,
They march in step.
I know I'll be left behind,
She must be thinking about Major Focker.
This song must be really hard on her.
All for war,
She acts happy, but you can't forget
a love like that so easily.
Huh?
All for pride
Time drifts away,
love drifts away.
And I rot away...
L-O-V-E! Lovely Minmay!
L-O-V-E!
Lovely Minmay!
L-O-V-E! Lovely Minmay!
L-O-V-E!
Lovely Minmay!
We lure them into launching a
Daedalus Attack on our ship?!
Yes, sir.
It's a little crude, but if we use their
Daedalus Attack against them,
we should be able to insert a Reguld
squadron aboard their ship.
Then we can capture not just a miclone,
but the Macross itself.
They pierce our flesh but we
break their bones, eh?
Precisely. However, we cannot let them
choose which area to attack.
Only one section will
do: the ship's bow.
Even with the bow ruptured, we will be able
to hold out for 4 or even 5 adenors.
Well planned.
It was developed by analyzing data
brought back by our spies
regarding the Macross's attack patterns.
Excellent.
None of us were discovered.
Our plan's a success!
It's too soon to relax.
Until we see our chance,
we lie low and keep quiet.
All Reguld and Noujadeul-Ger forces:
Move to the ship's bow at once!
Once in position, stand by for further orders.
The bow?
That's not what we usually do!
Yeah...
Don't panic.
We know we're attacking the Macross.
Our chance will come.
All right, men! Your orders are when the
Macross closes and launches its fighters,
we attack them in waves!
Sir!
And with permission from above.
Well, it's my pleasure to serve.
Number of ships is approximately thirty.
Thirty?!
They're headed straight for us!
This is just a fraction of their main force.
And we can't expect any help
from our own forces, either.
But we can't let them destroy us here!
Send the order to scramble
Valkyrie squadrons!
Yes, sir!
Enemy fighters have been deployed and
are closing in from 12 o'clock!
Roger!
They're not acting normally.
Be careful.
You don't have to remind me.
Minmay, I'll protect you.
Let's go!
So far, they've kept to the
usual pattern.
This is tactical leader Grundkol.
All units are in position.
Good, head toward the Macross.
This ship will take the lead.
Roger.
Remind the other ships that our objective
is to capture the Macross,
and that this ship will be
damaged in the process.
Roger.
Their fleet's up to something!
Captain!
Lure them in as close as possible,
then launch a Daedalus Attack!
To save the Macross, we'll have to take
them out one ship at a time!
Yes, sir!
Prepare to launch a
Daedalus Attack on my mark.
Roger!
Did you hear that just now?
Our mission is to storm the Macross!
Here's our chance!
What luck!
We just have to get inside and
then we've won!
Or if we get inside and our luck
runs out, we all die.
Let's just lie low for as long as we can.
Right, I'll tell the others.
Minmay, keep going!
Keep singing!
Huh?
Everyone, the concert will continue as planned!
Let's get out of here!
We can't let this barbaric war
get the better of us!
Singing mustn't be defeated by
weapons of destruction!
Come on, everyone!
Let's keep this concert going!
Sing, Minmay!
Sing!
Sing as loud as you can!
Sing...?
Come on, be brave.
Go on, sing!
Whoosh, whoosh...
Louder than that!
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
My boyfriend is a pilot
Shining, making a rapid descent
That's it!
That's the way!
Then BOOM! he makes a sudden climb
Leaving a long trail of vapor
He traces two big hearts
A love sign in the big, blue sky...
Captain! That large ship is
headed straight for us!
They want to ram us?!
Evasive maneuvers!
It's no good!
The surrounding ships have blocked us in!
Execute Daedalus Attack!
Target the large ship and open up
an escape route!
Yes, sir!
Daedalus Attack, stand by!
Now!
Go!
Hurry!
They WHAT?!
What's wrong?
Battle pods have broken in through
the starboard side!
We've been boarded?!
There!
Run this way!
Battle pods have broken in?
50 or 60 of them are shooting up
the interior right now!
Return at once!
Is the concert hall okay?!
We still don't have any details.
Lieutenant Ichijo, just hurry!
Max, battle pods have
boarded the Macross!
Back to the ship!
Minmay...
Get back here!
Ten battle pods sighted
on Suzuran Street!
We are exchanging gunfire!
Defense forces!
The enemy has destroyed an
entire section of the base!
We are now at 10th Street
in front of the base gate!
We have engaged the enemy!
Please send a Destroid platoon at once!
He must be at the concert hall too.
Ichijo, please save him!
Remember!
Dancing in the sky, the silver wings
Shao Pai Long...
"Shao Pai Long!"
Sing for the audience!
Sing!
"Remember!"
The eyes of fire splitting the darkness
Shao Pai Long!
Sing louder!
"Shao Pai Long!"
Look out!
Kaifun!
I'm okay.
Huh?
What's going on here?
No doubt about it:
it's him!
Does it hurt?
Here...
You're so sweaty!
Minmay!
Next Episode
Preview
The Zentradi infiltration of the Macross
has allowed the three spies
and other defectors
to board the Macross.
Troubled by the request for asylum
from these 23 deserters,
Global decides to summon those who
have had contact with the Zentradi:
namely, Hikaru, Misa, and Max.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
DROP OUT
"DROP OUT"
I won't follow it anymore
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running to the end
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away