Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
will set out on their journey
as the war rages on
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness, they fly toward
that blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
It is the year 2009.
The alien spacecraft that fell
to Earth ten years before
has been reborn as the
gigantic battleship "Macross."
However, on the day that the Macross
was scheduled to be launched,
its automatic defense system of alien
origin suddenly activated itself,
firing the main cannon and destroying
an unidentified warship.
Humanity was plunged into
unavoidable conflict.
Meanwhile, Lynn Minmay, a young girl
attending the launch ceremony,
...and Hikaru Ichijo, a civilian pilot,
have also found themselves
in the midst of the battle.
SPACE FOLD
At this moment, the Macross is
making its way into space.
Hikaru!
I guess the shock was
a little too much for him.
This is Skull Leader.
I left something on South Ataria Island,
and I'm going back to get it.
Have some other squadron fly
escort for the Macross.
What are you picking up?
Well... Valkyrie VT-102
and its pilot.
VT-102?
Now that you mention it, there was
something strange about that pilot.
You think so, too, huh?
Well, it's not so surprising...
...after all, he is a civilian.
A civilian?!
Oh, no!
No way!
This isn't something I'd want
a girl to have to see...
What's wrong?
You look like you're shaking.
What?
What is it?
Don't look!
What?
Why not?
Just don't look!
Hey, Hikaru!
How long do you plan on
staying here goofing off?
Aliens have the hots for you, huh?
Talk about bad luck!
It can do that, too?
What's going on?
Handy, huh?
This is control.
We are now engaging main thrusters.
Prepare for retrieval of Valkyrie squadrons.
All units, move into landing positions.
This is Mountain Three.
Following landing line.
You're cleared to land.
Hayase, is the Valkyrie
retrieval completed?
Just a moment, sir.
All that's left is Major Focker and
the civilian pilot in VT-102.
Knowing Focker, there's nothing
to worry about.
Vanessa, where are ARMD-I and ARMD-II?
They're nearly at the rendezvous point
and currently decelerating.
I estimate contact in 20 minutes.
Very good.
Claudia, how are we doing?
Right on schedule, sir.
But it's strange, isn't it, Captain?
If the enemy fleet can launch that
kind of attack from orbit,
then why aren't they firing on us now?
So, that's bothering you too?
Yes, sir.
They may be toying with us.
You can't be serious!
Toying with us?!
It's just a feeling.
Pay it no mind.
You've got to be kidding!
I'm not going to go to the Macross!
Idiot! If you take her back to
the island, you'll be risking her life!
And you call yourself a man?!
Um, my aunt and uncle are on
the island in the shelter.
If they're in the shelter, they'll be fine!
Even if this does turn into an all-out war.
But I really would like to go
back to the island...
Once the fighting's over,
I'll take you back personally.
That is what really
worries me!
Well, what he means is...
This is Skull Leader!
Did you find what you'd left behind?
Yeah, the enemy had him scared so bad,
he was falling over himself!
I was not!
So, this is the civilian?
That would explain why he
didn't know anything.
Hey, what's with the old lady?
"Old lady"?!
She's the flight control
officer of the Macross.
So, even Hikaru thinks she
looks like an old lady?
Major Focker!
I will expect a thorough explanation
as to why you let a civilian
board VT-102.
Ooh, scary!
And you, Mr. Ichijo!
This isn't over for you by a long shot!
What's her problem?
Maybe you should just apologize.
People like her can be pretty scary.
I'm comin' in!
Requesting instructions
...old lady!
Roger. We'd appreciate it if you didn't
kill yourself when you land.
Retrieval of Reguld platoons
is now in progress.
Only half of them are unharmed?
Yes, sir.
What's the enemy ship doing?
It's currently ascending through the
planet's upper atmosphere.
They appear be trying to rendezvous
with the space fleet from earlier.
Orders, sir?
It would be simple to shoot them down,
but that ship interests me.
If they enter orbit, there's a possibility
they will execute a fold and escape.
Yes, I know.
We'll have to launch a containment attack
before they can join up with the others.
All ships, prepare to fire!
But why do you have to kill each other?
That's what war is.
I just can't understand the military...
You did some shooting yourself,
though, didn't you?
I never imagined something
like that could be inside.
Something like that...
Huh?
Something like what?
What?
Hang on!
Well, here we are.
Sempai!
What's wrong with you?!
Thank you, Sempai!
Well, I mean, if we left something
like this on the battlefield,
it would just get in the way.
So I, uh, had it stashed away.
This is the plane from the air show
this morning, isn't it?
Rendezvous with ARMD-I and
ARMD-II is complete.
Now moving into docking position.
All hands to emergency stations.
Well, I've got work to do.
You two, stay right here. If you start
wandering around, you'll get lost.
This ship is massive.
Now moving into docking alignment.
The enemy fleet appears to be regrouping.
Very well.
Fire a barrage between the fleet and the battleship!
I don't care about the smaller ships,
but do NOT hit that battleship.
Understood!
Firing will now commence!
Target the enemy fleet!
Aim wide of the battleship!
An attack?!
Yes, sir. It's coming from the same orbit
as before. Range: 12,000 km.
ARMD-I has been destroyed, along with
the Miranda and the Akishima.
Three ships at once?
How much damage did we take?
We've taken no direct hits.
All sections show green.
What's our position?
Sir. We've almost completed
a single orbit.
South Ataria Island is 800km ahead.
Our current altitude is 120km.
Claudia, make it look like we're going
to land at South Ataria,
then initiate a sub-space transfer.
You mean the Fold System, sir?
But, we haven't tested it yet!
It's definitely a risk.
But, if we just sit
here, we'll be destroyed.
But sir, it's an alien system!
We can't just give up without trying!
Put the sub-space transfer,
I mean, the Fold System on standby!
Our target will be the far side of the Moon!
Check coordinates, then execute fold
directly above the island.
You mean, near the surface?
The enemy won't see it coming.
But, shouldn't we get authorization
from UN High Command?
This is an emergency. We'll contact them
after we've reached the Moon.
But, sir!
Enough!
That's an order!
Yes, sir!
Fold System, stand by.
All hands to emergency stations.
Power system check shows all green.
Focusing power.
All hands to emergency stations!
This is not a drill.
The ship will execute a fold in five minutes.
It sure has gotten quiet, hasn't it?
I wonder if it's all over.
That's some ruckus,
wouldn't you say?
This sure turned into one hell
of a launch ceremony...
I have no idea how much damage we took.
I wonder if our shops are all right.
Who knows...
What happened to Minmay?
She hasn't come back yet.
There are plenty of other places
she could've escaped to.
There's nothing to worry about.
That girl's pretty sharp about some things,
you know?
You're really leaving?
You want to go back, too, don't you?
But...
Look, I won't force you or anything.
Ship is ready for fold.
T-minus three minutes to fold.
I wonder what that means.
Dunno. Anyway, we're leaving,
so it's got nothing to do with us.
This is just a one-seater, isn't it?
We'll be fine.
Go on, hop in.
Put this on.
Okay.
Can't you even put on
a helmet straight?
Hold on tight.
To what?
I can't see my instruments!
Sorry!
You shouldn't let a little something
like this scare you!
See?
Yeah, you're right.
T-minus ten seconds to fold.
Nine... Eight...
Seven... Six...
Five... Four...
Three... Two...
One... Zero!
Initiate fold!
What's going on?!
Wh...What?!
They're executing a fold near the surface?!
Is that even possible?
I do not know.
Locate their de-fold point at once!
Yes, sir!
What happened?
Switching to backup systems.
Captain, I'm picking up an object
below the ship.
Of course you are.
We're at the far side of the Moon.
It's much smaller than that, sir.
I'll put it on screen.
The object is closing in!
What?
No, the ship is moving toward it.
Claudia, full reverse!
Hurry!
I'm trying, but there's no response!
This is an emergency!
All hands, brace for impact!
We're floating!
It's so pretty!
Wow!
Oh, man.
The propeller's useless.
It's no use.
We must really be in outer space.
Is this space?
Is that what it looks like to you?
Huh?
What's that?
Well, it's not an alarm clock,
that's for sure.
I can't tell her that we're leaking air.
Let's go back.
Hey, don't get so worked up.
I sure hope the booster works.
Here we go.
Okay.
We're moving.
I think this'll work!
Now then, where's the Macross?
All right!
Here goes!
Oh, no!
We can't get in!
What?!
Perfect!
The remaining enemy forces appear
to have been destroyed.
What's the status on the
evacuees in the shelter?
They're being brought on board.
Fortunately, there don't seem to be
many dead or wounded.
That's good to hear. Hayase!
Sir.
Have you been able to contact
UN High Command?
Shammy?
I've called and called, but...
No response, huh?
And it's not a malfunction?
No. Um, sir?
About our current location...
You've pinpointed our location?
Where are we?
We're just inside the orbit
of Pluto.
What?!
Pluto? It can't be!
I said we shouldn't have tried to fold.
Captain...
Captain!
Now, now, hold on.
There's no need to worry.
If we made it this far out, we can
just fold again and go back.
Really, sir?
What is it?
But...!
Fine.
I'm on my way.
Captain?
It looks like the Fold System has
completely disappeared.
Disappeared?
You can't be serious!
It's gone?
But why?!
But that means we can't go back!
It looks like we're in for a long trip.
Hikaru and Minmay's joy at being
saved is short-lived.
Ironically, the section of the Macross
that they have flown into
has been sealed off from the
rest of the giant ship.
Not a single person knows where they are.
With no means of escaping their
forced confinement,
Hikaru and Minmay must watch
as time ticks cruelly away.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"LYNN MINMAY"
I won't follow it anymore,
the shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end,
but we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
the light that shines so far away