Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
as the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
that blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
It has been almost a year since the
Macross began its voyage,
GLOBAL REPORT
and we have amassed a sizable amount
of valuable data.
I will now report all we've learned
to the UN Forces High Command.
From the space battleship
SDF-1 Macross, UN Forces,
this is Captain Bruno J. Global.
For those on Earth, I think it's hard
to know just what befell
the Macross and its surroundings on
the day of the launch ceremony,
and what happened once it and
the island both disappeared.
It all began with a sudden roar
from the Macross's main gun.
W...What's going on?
What is it?
Look! The ship's original systems have
just activated themselves!
Huh?
Oh, no!
It's entered firing mode!
What is going on?!
The main cannon is activating!
We are currently engaged in
hostilities with alien forces.
This is not a drill!
I repeat, this is not a drill!
The directive from the previous day's defense
council that we were not to fire first
in the event of an alien encounter had
been thoroughly broken.
From what we could gather of the situation,
the alien's enemies had left the Macross
behind as a clever trap,
a booby trap.
As a result of our battle with
the enemy's land forces,
we confirmed that they were giants, five or
six times the size of human beings.
This matches earlier estimates made
by UN Forces High Command
based on the size of
the interior of the Macross.
We also gained valuable data on the
effectiveness of the Battroids,
which had been designed to combat
such a threat.
Meanwhile, we attempted to launch the ship
using the gravity control system...
but we failed.
What in the world is happening?!
I don't know, sir!
Captain!
The bow!
What is it?
What are those?!
They appear to be the gravity control systems.
The gravity control systems?!
That's impossible!
An analysis by our technical crew concluded
that the unexpected firing of the main gun
had affected all of the ship's components,
including the Fold System.
After transporting the Macross and
the nearby island to Pluto's orbit,
the Fold System vanished, forcing us
to make a long voyage home.
We quickly docked the Macross
with the aircraft carrier Prometheus
and the assault ship Daedalus,
then brought the base and various
facilities from the island,
as well as 50,000-plus refugees we found in the
shelters, into the ship itself.
The civilians used materials from
the island to rebuild their city
inside the ship's residential areas
and went about their daily lives.
I believe this will provide valuable data
for future deep-space voyages.
On a related note, we learned that the
disappearance of the Fold System
cut the energy lines to the main gun,
rendering it unusable.
For that reason, the ship had to undergo
a Transformation.
Valkyrie squadrons, all units, scramble!
I repeat, Valkyrie squadrons,
all units, scramble!
We're going to initiate
the ship-wide Transformation!
I regret that the Transformation affected
the citizens so badly,
but it allowed us to strike back at our enemy.
Following that, we were able
to modify the process
to minimize the damage caused
by future Transformations.
Also, for our first counterattack
in the rings of Saturn,
we used residual energy from the Fold System
to create the Pinpoint Barrier.
Furthermore, by concentrating the Barrier
at the bow of the Daedalus,
we developed the Daedalus Attack, which has
proven effective against the giant enemy ships.
Oh, no!
I'll never make it!
Agh, not that way!
Currently, I am hastening development of a
barrier that can cover the entire ship.
In the eighth month of our voyage,
in need of supplies,
we touched down at Mars Base Salla,
where we were trapped by hidden gravity mines
that had been planted by the enemy.
Destroid groups 6, 8, and 17
are destroyed.
The rest are heavily damaged.
Hold on. We may be able to disable
that trap after all.
But how, if it's underground?
The reactor! Salla's reactor is located
deep beneath the base!
If we can blow it up...
One moment, please.
It looks like it could work.
All right, begin the operation at once!
Have Hayase activate the reactor!
Yes, sir!
Reactor is overloading!
Danger! Danger!
Safety systems are disengaged. Status red!
Reactor entering critical cascade!
Fifteen minutes until detonation!
All personnel, evacuate!
By causing the reactor located
beneath the base to overload,
1st Lt. Hayase enabled us to escape.
The enemy's objective seems to be the capture of
our ship rather than its destruction.
I believe this is what allowed the Macross to run
for so long from an overwhelming enemy force.
To celebrate the launch of MBS,
the Macross Broadcast System,
we present the Miss Macross Contest.
Ship-wide civilian broadcasts began,
and the Miss Macross contest was
held to mark the occasion.
Who will make it to the finals
and win the crown?
The Miss Macross Contest!
Our queen will be chosen by you!
A young girl named Lynn Minmay
was crowned Miss Macross.
With the Earth in sight, a fleet of enemy ships
surrounded us, forcing us to a stalemate.
It was at this time that the enemy
subtly changed its tactics.
The jamming that had blocked
our communications ceased,
and we immediately reported our
situation to headquarters.
However, directly following this...
I'm getting a signal from someplace
that isn't High Command.
Put it on the speaker.
Yes, sir!
...name of the Zentradi, we order you
to surrender your vessel.
The recent attack was merely a show of force.
If... do not wish to be destroyed,
you will surrender immediately.
It's from the enemy fleet?
...receive this demand for surrender...
Enough.
The enemy's deciphering abilities
are exceptional.
We mustn't be careless with
our communications.
When our radar was destroyed,
1st Lt. Misa Hayase went out on a
recon patrol in a Cat's Eye.
1st Lt. Hayase, along with 2nd Lt. Ichijo
and Corporals Kakizaki and Jenius,
were captured and taken all the way to the
main Zentradi base for questioning.
After that, they miraculously escaped and
were able to tell us the shocking truth.
I'll let them explain it in their own words.
I am Bodolzaa, Supreme Commander of
the Zentradi 118th main fleet.
There are some things I wish to ask you.
They know our language!
What's going on here?
My Lord, the translation device appears
to be working properly.
Good. When did you people make contact
with the Supervision Army?
"Supervision Army"?
You ever heard of that army, Leader?
I just joined the military myself,
so I don't really know.
Just joined the military?
What in the world did you do before that?
What do you mean? We were civilians.
"Ci-vil-ians"?
What does "civilian" mean?
Someone who doesn't fight in wars.
Doesn't fight in wars?!
P... Preposterous!
The universe overflows with conflict, and
it is in battle that one finds life!
It's in battle that one finds life...
It seems that we need to change
our line of questioning.
Are there really people aboard
your ship who do not fight?
And how can your men and
women live together?
Men and women together? What are you...
Kakizaki!
I don't intend to answer any
more questions!
You must be their commander.
None of you appreciate the
situation you're in.
We have enough power to destroy your
ship and your world in an instant.
Take a look at that planet.
What have you done?!
Do you want the same thing to
happen to your homeworld?
That's...
What is it?
Something's strange. They have
that kind of power,
so why haven't they launched an all-out
attack on the Macross and the Earth?
I will ask you once more:
Do these "civilians" really exist?
And how can men and women
coexist on the same ship?
Civilians... Men and women...
Maybe we have something that they don't.
If you don't answer, I'll destroy
your ship and your planet!
If you really think you can,
then go ahead and try!
What did you say?
Lieutenant!
Let me handle this.
We have powers you know nothing about!
Silence!
Lieutenant!
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Stay where you are.
How soft.
To think that fragile miclones
like this dare to defy us.
Tell me, why did you go through the
trouble of becoming a miclone?
If you don't tell me why you became
a miclone, I'll kill you.
Stop it!
We were born with these bodies!
Born with them?
And just where were you "born" from?
From our mothers, of course!
"Mothers"?
Our female parents!
From a woman?
You're saying you were born from a woman?
But how?
How? You don't even know that?
A man and a woman make love,
and together they make a baby.
"Make love"? How is this done?
Well, they kiss and hold each other, and...
And that is how miclones are "born"?
You two, show me this "kissing."
Give me a break! Two guys
can't do that!
If you don't, then I'll crush you too!
Wait!
I'll do it.
You? Very well.
2nd Lieutenant Ichijo, kiss me.
This is our chance to see
how the enemy reacts!
Then do it with Kakizaki!
I'd rather it was you.
Still, you can't just say something like that and...
Do it now!
That's an order! Hurry!
Okay, fine!
Here goes.
I'm sorry, Minmay.
Protoculture...!
"Protoculture"?
What's going on?
Someone! Take these things
away immediately!
What could the Zentradi have feared so much?
Their giant bodies are so strong that they
can survive for short periods in the vacuum of space,
and they have an unbelievably powerful
fleet as well. All that strength and yet...
Enter.
I brought you some coffee.
Thank you. You're very considerate.
Not at all, sir...
It's this late already, is it?
It's beautiful.
I never thought I'd see this sight again.
To be honest, neither did I.
Strange to say now, but
I had a bad feeling when
I was given this ship.
A feeling that by launching the Macross,
something would happen that
would change our...
No, that would change humanity forever.
Your premonition came true
in a way, didn't it?
What will the Macross mean for us in the end?
Next Episode
Preview
Captain Global and Misa travel to
UN Forces High Command in Alaska.
Meanwhile, Hikaru and Minmay leave the
Macross and journey to Yokohama.
For both parties, unexpected situations await
them at their respective destinations.
Next time, on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"CHINA TOWN"
CHINA TOWN
I won't follow it anymore,
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away