Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
as the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
that blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
1st Lt. Hikaru Ichijo, Vermilion Team,
Valkyrie Fighter Group.
Wounded at Torishimaoki while
defending the Macross.
Lacerations across entire body.
Currently in recovery.
Irregular brainwave activity detected, the
result of contusions to the head area.
PHANTASM
Ladies and gentlemen,
we thank you for your patience.
Miss Lynn Minmay's first concert
will now begin!
First up is her debut song,
"My Boyfriend is a Pilot."
Enjoy!
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
Min...
May!
My boyfriend is a pilot
L-O-V-E! Happy Minmay!
Shining, making a rapid descent
then BOOM! he makes a sudden climb
Leaving a long trail of vapor
He traces two big hearts
A love sign in the big, blue sky
Help me!
Hikaru, help me!
Minmay! I'm coming to save you!
Seated and ready to take off.
Let's go!
VT-102! Respond!
I'm not reading your transponder signal.
What's the matter?
Signal?
How would I know anything
about that, you old lady?!
Old lady, huh? Don't tell me you...
You're a civilian!
This is the bridge.
At approximately 2:00 this afternoon,
civilian Hikaru Ichijo
hijacked a Valkyrie variable fighter,
but due to his inexperience
he failed to escape
and was shot down.
I blew it, huh?
"Please, Hikaru!"
"Come save me! Hurry!"
"Please!"
Oh, well. I guess I'd better ask
Sempai for some advice.
You want to become a military pilot
so you can go rescue Minmay, huh?
That's right.
Well, what the heck.
It's probably better than being a civilian who
swipes military planes and gets shot down.
Right!
What's with you, Hikaru?
You'd better salute!
O...Oh, right.
I'm Hikaru Ichijo.
Misa Hayase. Hikaru Ichijo?
I've heard that name somewhere.
You're that civilian!
And you're that old lady!
What?!
Uh...excuse me!
I can't believe these two!
That's the guy who got shot down
a while ago!
What? What is it?
He's that civilian.
Huh? No way!
If you pass your aptitude tests, she'll be
your operator and your superior officer.
Y...Yessir!
This one? Pass the aptitude tests?
I hear you hijacked that plane
to rescue your girlfriend,
but make sure you don't crash
and burn on your tests too.
Moron!
Way to go, Hikaru! You passed!
That means you're now a full-fledged soldier.
Be sure to do your best and
rescue Minmay now!
You bet, Sempai!
Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
That does it!
I've launched in an Armored Valkyrie.
1st Lt. Ichijo!
I thought you were going to behave
and not run off on your own again.
Um... Right.
You want to try to save Minmay
again, don't you?
Why do you keep running off like this?
Why do you keep chasing after that girl?
I love her! So I've got no choice!
See if I care if
you get shot down again!
I'm not gonna get taken out this time!
Go!
The Armored Valkyrie has been
heavily damaged.
Lt. Ichijo says he's returning to base.
Shot down again?!
I'm impressed.
Hey, do you think he's gonna go out again?
I bet he'll go out over and
over for that girl!
Maybe he'll even go on all fours!
He wouldn't!
No way...!
I could see it though.
I get shot down every time
I'm in a Valkyrie
but I might have a chance on
this special bike!
Wait for me, Minmay!
This is the bridge.
Early this morning, 1st Lt. Ichijo Hikaru,
also known as the Crash King,
tried unsuccessfully to pedal his
bicycle into outer space.
Such behavior is extremely
dangerous,
so we ask that you please don't
attempt it at home.
Ichijo, if it's all right with you,
we'd like to help you rescue Minmay!
C'mon, you should've just asked, Leader!
Leave everything to us!
Well?
Guys!
I can't believe you and the others
offered to help me, Captain.
In return, once we get back,
you'll have to do as you're told.
A second wave is coming in from above!
Let me handle them!
He's incredible.
Ichijo!
Come on, let's sneak aboard the enemy ship.
How will we look for Minmay
once we're aboard?
Well, why not disguise yourself
as one of the giants?
A disguise, huh?
Roger!
I don't think it will take long
for someone to spot us.
We'll worry about that when it happens.
Here goes!
Muetema!
We've been spotted!
Sorry about the bumpy ride!
No problem!
It's no use! It won't move at all!
Understood. What should we do?
We'll just have to make
a break for it!
Roger!
The love between us...
Singing?
This way!
Right!
Is like a raging wind...
We made it!
Yes!
Minmay's okay!
And she has such a nice voice.
It never leads to...
I'm jealous.
Well, we'd better hurry up and rescue her.
Where you'd expect
Captain Hayase, please let me do this alone.
You're right. That would be best.
I will go forward loving you the way I do now
All right, here I go!
Good luck!
Minmay!
Two hearts beating as one
Minmay! I'm here to rescue you,
just like I promised!
That just won't do!
Won't do? But why not?
Sorry, Hikaru. Kaifun says I
can't go out with soldiers.
He said that?!
But why would Kaifun...?
Because I hate soldiers!
I'll never give Minmay to you!
What the...
Well, you heard what he said.
Fine! Then I'll give up being a soldier!
What?!
Hikaru!
Zero-g love, zero-g love!
Quick, hop on!
But...
Zero-g love, zero-g love!
Hurry! Missiles are coming!
With him after school, on my way home
At the corner of that same old intersection
Are you okay? I'm taking us up!
He made sure no one else was around
Then without warning, he kissed me
Minmay!
And I was so angry, I led him to think,
But, but, but
My head was dizzy
And my heart was fluttering
Zero-g love, zero-g love!
Four, three, two, one,
Zero-g love!
My body floats up and I fly away on the wind
It's still dangerous here!
We'll be saved if I transform the ship!
Transform...?
Perfect!
Here...
Hey, does it look brighter down there to you?
You're right!
We did it!
It looks like we can climb up over there!
Yeah...
An airlock for giants, huh?
What's wrong?!
That...
Those are all spaceships?
Such a huge fleet!
What's that?
A skirmish?
No, the closer we get, you can
see the scale is huge.
It's big enough to swallow the Earth!
What's the matter, Hikaru?
I think I was having a bad dream or something.
Darn it, Hikaru!
You were peeking!
Sorry.
It's been a long time since we were
alone together like this.
It sure has. About a year, since you were
picked Miss Macross and became a star.
Has it really been a year?
It sounds long, but it just flew by.
What's gonna happen to us now?
Who knows?
Hey, are you sure
that's a good idea?
There'll be trouble if somebody
sees you here.
What was that light just now?
Maybe some paparazzi got
some pictures of you.
Oh, no!
If those pictures get out,
the whole town will be talking!
She's so cute.
I finally rescued you.
But what's gonna happen to us now?
When the midnight bell tolled,
the magic spell wore off.
Down the staircase she rushed,
as if trying to outrun it.
And at the top of the stairs,
a single glass slipper...
Is that a new song?
No, it's an old one I wrote
myself, called "Cinderella."
I wonder if it'll be a hit?
Yeah, I'm sure it will.
You and I are getting further
and further apart, huh?
No, that won't happen!
We'll always be friends, Hikaru!
Say, Minmay, what would you want to be
if you couldn't become a singer?
Me? I'm not sure...
A bride, I guess.
A bride?
I see, I bet you'd make a great bride.
Thanks.
But it's all over for us anyway.
That's not true!
There's nothing that says we're
going to just die here!
It's okay, Hikaru. But I wish I could have worn
a wedding dress just once before I die.
What do you say we have
a wedding ceremony?
You're right. That would be nice.
I... Are you sure you're okay
with someone like me?
Say, Hikaru...
When we wake up from this dream...
Let's get married for real!
Are you serious, Minmay?
Let's be together.
That's easy enough to say, but won't
you just change your mind later?
You've always been fickle like that.
How can you say that?
You were the one who said we should
have a wedding ceremony!
You never meant it! You liar!
I don't mean to have doubts. It's just...
I...
I live in a different world from you.
But I...
I still... I'm sorry.
If that's all it is, then...
There's nothing to worry about, Hikaru.
Hikaru...
Hikaru!
Protoculture!
Why did Minmay turn into
Captain Hayase?
In the end,
you're a soldier too.
A dream?
It sure was a bad one...
Next Episode
Preview
Hikaru Ichijo is still unable
to return to duty.
Meanwhile, a Queadluun-Rau team led
by Milia launches its attack.
But Milia's target isn't the Macross;
it's Max.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"PINEAPPLE SALAD"
PINEAPPLE SALAD
I won't follow it anymore
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away