Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
will set out on their journey
as the war rages on
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness, they fly toward
that blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
To evade the sudden alien attack,
the space battleship Macross
executed a hyperspace fold,
catapulting the surrounding city, the island
and even some of the nearby ocean
far into space, to arrive near
the orbit of Pluto.
The rescued civilians
aboard the Macross,
have recovered from
their initial shock.
While unable to completely
shake free of their anxiety,
the refugees slowly began to
pick up the pieces,
and the city has begun
to regain its balance.
TRANSFORMATION
We waited in line all that time,
and this is what they give us?!
Yeah...
Oh!
Welcome back!
Minmay.
Should you be out of bed so soon?
Sure.
I'm fine now, Auntie.
Well, that's good to hear.
By the way, where's Hikaru?
I don't know.
Isn't he still asleep?
I wouldn't be surprised.
After all, he had to take care of
you for more than a week!
I guess you're right.
Anyway, Auntie...
Once we get things straightened up, are
we going to reopen the restaurant?
Reopen the restaurant?!
Sure!
I mean, look at everything we've salvaged!
Yeah, but the only food rations
they gave us were these.
That's all?
But, the restaurant stayed open
during the Unification Wars, right?
Well, the military did give us special
wartime ration status, but...
Besides, we're on a spaceship.
That's not the point.
If you say you're reopening the restaurant,
I'm sure they'll give you more rations.
Please, Uncle?
Auntie?
Well, why not?
We can't keep loafin' around here forever.
You're right. Maybe re-opening the restaurant
would be a nice way to keep ourselves busy.
Okay!
We'll be the first to give it a try!
Great!
It's settled, then!
I'll go get changed!
Typical Minmay...
We'd better get busy, too.
You're right.
Careful, Minmay!
Okay!
There we go...
This is good, right?
Yup.
What are you up to?
Indeed!
Oh, Mr. Mayor.
We're reopening the restaurant, of course!
Reopening the restaurant?!
Are you serious?
On a battleship out at the edge of space?!
Oh, come on, Mr. Mayor!
Even if we are far away from the Earth
and inside a spaceship,
this is still our town, isn't it?
We should do things the
way we always have!
Y'know, you're absolutely right!
Huh?
Check it out!
Hey, is this restaurant really open?
Welcome! As of today, the Nyan-Nyan
Chinese restaurant is open for business!
I'm so happy! You soldiers are the first patrons
of our Chinese restaurant in space!
Well, we're honored.
Say, you're that Minmay girl
everyone's talking about, right?
They say you had
quite an adventure.
That's right!
It was really rough!
I hear you were all alone with
some guy for nearly two weeks.
So, what did you two do?
"Do"?
C'mon, don't play dumb!
You know what we mean!
Oh, that's enough!
You really didn't do anything?
Not a thing!
Hey, yeah. I hear the guy's stayin'
in a room upstairs here.
And...?
What's your point?
So, you two fell for each other and
now you're a couple, right?
I swear, you're making me angry!
It's nothing like that!
He's just a friend!
Now, are you going to order or not?
Right, right.
I'll have some ramen.
Yeah, ramen sounds good.
Well, I'll have ramen, too!
Okay, that's three orders of ramen.
Just a friend, huh?
"If we're going to die anyway,"
"let's get it over with and throw
ourselves out into space!"
"Let's die together!"
And the very next day,
I'm "just a friend," huh?
Well? Does it look like we
can use the main gun?
Sir!
Please, take a look at this.
This is the main reactor.
And this is the energy converter
for the main gun.
They were initially connected to the
Fold System via energy conduits, but...
The connection was broken when the
fold system disappeared, eh?
We don't have the resources to
repair that amount of conduit.
What can we do?
Sir. We exploit the modular block
structure of the Macross.
In short, we replace this "block"
with this one.
I see.
However, the problem is that the
main gun simply will not fire
unless we first carry out
this transformation.
Transformation?
Yes.
The ship will undergo structural changes
internally and externally,
causing major disruptions in the process.
And, there's no other way
to use the main gun?
Correct. I'm afraid that the
transformation is our only option.
We can't do it.
To throw the city into chaos again just as
we're getting it quieted down...
I just can't do that.
Hey, there! We'd like two orders of
chashumen and fried rice!
Coming up!
Hikaru, where are you going?
Hikaru...
How terrible...
Hikaru!
I finally found you!
Sempai!
You little cockroach!
Huh?
No matter what happens, you always
survive, just like a cockroach!
That's just mean! Don't go putting me
in the same category as you!
Yeah, maybe so!
I'm glad you're all right.
What's with this scrap heap here?
Scrap?
Sempai, this racer was the second most
important thing to me, right after my own life!
And, you call it scrap?!
But, it's wrecked and that's a fact.
What's done is done.
Jeez...
What do you say Hikaru?
You up for a walk?
Just look at that gloomy face of yours.
It's not like you!
Sempai! Those fighters can
fly in space, too!
Uh-huh. The Valkyries have
thermo-nuclear reaction engines.
With that much thrust, they can
fly just about anywhere.
It's incredible!
Sempai?
How about it, Hikaru?
Don't you feel like trying to
fly one of those again?
You mean join the military?
Well, it's pointless to just hang
around here and do nothing.
What is it, Hikaru?
Sempai...
I...
Can a girl change in a single day?
What?!
Can a girl be completely different today
from how she was yesterday?
You don't have to laugh at me!
You've fallen for her, haven't you?
Huh?!
N...No, that's not...
Relax, Hikaru.
Minmay was the one who said
you were feeling down,
and that I should come check on you.
So, cheer up and go on back
and show her you're smiling.
The thing is, girls like her
are pretty fickle.
Make sure you don't lose
her to another man!
Sempai...
What? You have data on
the alien homeworld?
Yes, we were able to capture some images.
Please observe.
These were taken by a reconnaissance Reguld.
Wh...What?!
So, these aliens are miclones?
Yes, sir. I also realized as much
upon viewing this.
There is an ancient legend in
the old Zentradi military records...
What is it?
Sir. It says, "Avoid the worlds
of the miclones."
Avoid the worlds of the miclones, eh?
I believe we should not have any
further contact with this world.
Instead, we should concentrate on
pursuing the target battleship.
Understood. Fold at once
and initiate pursuit!
Yes, sir.
Once we've de-folded, send a
detachment of ships to investigate.
I want to probe
their capabilities.
Oh, Hikaru.
You're back.
Did you want something?
Uh, it's nothing really.
It's all right.
Come in.
Please.
Oh, would you open the window for me?
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Isn't that...
Didn't I smash this when I
was in the Battroid?
Don't worry about it.
And what's this?
It's something I forgot and
decided to go back for.
You ended up saving me
while I was getting it.
I'll bet it's a letter from
a boyfriend, right?
No way!
You can read it if you like.
This says you passed the preliminary
round for a singing audition!
You mean...?
Uh-huh!
Well, no wonder you sing so well!
Thank you.
Not that it matters now.
We're not on Earth anymore.
C'mon, don't talk like that!
When we get back to Earth, you can
get another audition, right?
If we get back.
Say, Hikaru.
Do you have a dream?
A dream?
Yeah.
A dream...
I had one, but it broke.
Now, it's just scrap.
You mean your airplane?
Yeah.
Now I don't have any dreams.
Really...
A de-fold reaction has been
detected at six o'clock!
We have a report from the radar room.
Unidentified objects have appeared
behind us and are closing fast.
Enemy ships!
So they've come.
Hayase!
Take us to battle stations, now!
Aye, sir!
Enemy attack!
Valkyrie squadrons, all units, scramble!
I repeat, Valkyrie squadrons,
all units, scramble!
Wow!
The town looks so nice, doesn't it?
Yeah...
Air-raid alert!
Will we be all right?
Relax. Sempai and the others
will take care of it.
It's always "Sempai, Sempai"
with you, isn't it?
You're as good a pilot
as he is, you know.
Dammit! They're a lot more slippery
here than they were on the ground.
This is gonna take some work.
Our lead detachment has moved
into firing range.
Strange.
They're not firing their main gun.
Damned miclones.
What are they up to?
Why not provoke them a little more
and see how they react?
Yes.
That is acceptable.
Authorize the lead detachment to open fire.
Enough to get the enemy
ship to return fire.
What was that?!
The enemy ships are firing on us!
A section of the sub-control
systems has been damaged!
However, it looks like we'll be
able to manage somehow.
I'm counting on you.
Captain!
We've lost auxiliary
gun turrets Numbers 2 and 5.
Immediate repair is impossible.
Section 4 has been
heavily damaged.
Sub-control systems report heavy damage
and several casualties!
That's it! Send a message to all sections:
Prepare to fire the main gun!
We're going to initiate
the ship-wide transformation!
But, if we do that, the city will be...!
Th...That's right!
Just do it!
We don't have much time!
Attention all sections!
Take positions for firing
the main gun!
Transformation will commence
in three minutes!
Huh?
Did she say transformation?!
No way!
That's just nuts!
T-minus two minutes, thirty seconds!
Oh hell!
Attention all civilians.
Our ship is to make a
transformation in 60 seconds.
For your safety, please hold tightly
onto anything within reach.
Transformation?
What's that?
Beats me...
I bet Mr. Focker and the others
are in battle right now, huh?
Are you saying, I should join the military?
That's not exactly what I mean, but...
...well, airplanes are your dream, right?
I guess.
But, if I join the military, you and I won't
get to see each other very much.
Don't be silly!
We're on the same ship, aren't we?
And, we can see each other
whenever you have time off.
If I survive, that is.
But, it's the same for all the soldiers
who come to the restaurant.
All the same, huh?
To you, I guess I'm no different
from any of them.
T-minus ten seconds.
Problems in any of the sections?
G block and D block are a little
behind, but they should be able to manage.
Good.
T-minus five seconds.
Three.
Two.
One.
Zero.
Initiate ship-wide transformation!
J, K and L blocks, initiate transformation!
Please increase output to the No. 7 reactor.
Transformation is underway in section 78.
There's insufficient power in J block.
Ship-wide transformation is underway.
Maybe I'd be happier if the city
and everything else
was blasted to space dust.
What?! How can you say
something so selfish?
I hate you!
Fine by me!
Me too, I...
Minmay!
Hikaru!
Three minutes have elapsed since the
order to begin transformation.
Reconfiguration is now 11.5% complete.
What the...?!
Transformation of the starboard
section is 75% complete.
Transformation of the port
section is 80% complete.
Main gun system is nominal!
So, that's the Macross's...
...transformation.
Transformation is complete!
The enemy ships have launched 40 or 50
smaller units, closing rapidly.
Never mind them!
Fire the main gun!
Yes, sir!
Wh...What?!
What is this?
The enemy ships have been destroyed.
All right!
We did it!
Thank goodness!
Get me a ship-wide damage report at once.
Attention all civilians.
Our sincerest apologies, but
thanks to your cooperation,
we were able to fire the main gun
and destroy the enemy.
If you were injured or your
home was damaged,
please inform your nearest branch office
or police substation.
Well, you said you wanted
the city to be destroyed.
Well, but... I didn't think that
something like THIS would happen.
I wonder if the restaurant was destroyed.
I'm going to do it, Minmay!
Huh?
I'm going to join the military!
Hikaru!
I can't just keep standing around
doing nothing, can I?
Valkyrie squadrons, return to base!
Next Episode
Preview
The Macross, newly fitted with a
temporary defense system
dubbed the Pinpoint Barrier, moves
to strike back for the first time.
Captain Global decides that the place for their
counterattack will be the planet Saturn,
and Focker takes Hikaru into his first
battle, inside the planet's rings.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"DAEDALUS ATTACK"
DAEDALUS ATTACK
I won't follow it anymore,
the shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end,
but we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away