Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
as the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
That blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
The Macross has been practically
banished from Earth.
However, the morale of the civilians
onboard was high enough
to permit the completion
of the kung-fu movie, Shao Pai Long.
Tonight, a party is being held on
the eve of the film's premiere.
MICRO COSMOS
Hikaru, what are you doing these days?
I haven't seen you for ages.
And what is the star of tonight's
party doing out here all alone?
And what is my manager doing
drinking too much vodka?
You can't call this "too much."
Too much is when I see two of you,
which would make me extremely,
outrageously happy!
Because I'd be twice as pretty?
Nah, no way.
Because I could schedule you
for twice as much!
I'm joking, I'm joking.
Now come inside before you catch a cold.
I'm so tired.
Tired? Well, no more getting sick.
That last time was bad enough!
No, I meant tired of all this.
Aah, you're just feeling blue
because the movie's done
and your schedule's wound down a bit.
That's not quite it.
I know! Can I get a seat reserved
for the premiere?
But that's tomorrow!
And it's already so late...
You really can't?
I'll figure something out.
Just wait, I'll get you that seat!
See you!
A seat reserved for the premiere.
A great idea if I say so myself!
Ah, Miss Minmay, our big star.
It is I, Jamis the villain.
I'm so sorry! I almost ruined your
lovely dress, didn't I?
No, it's...
But it was quite expensive, wasn't it?
Not as expensive as mine, but...
Oh, Jamis, dear!
C'mon, Jamis! Let's go!
Yes, I'm coming, Mr. Company President!
Oh, is that Minmay?
Oh, let's leave the child alone.
Adults should keep the company of adults, yes?
That's another thing that's making me tired.
Minmay! I got a message from your manager.
He got you a VIP seat, A-5.
Oh, that's great! Thank you!
Thank your manager.
Come on, we have to make an early day
of it tomorrow. Time for bed.
Okay.
I'll walk you to your room.
Hello. Military barracks, men's residence.
Umm, is 1st Lt. Ichijo there, please?
Lt. Ichijo? One moment, please.
Ah, the Lieutenant is flying escort
for a recon plane right now.
When will he be back?
I couldn't tell you that, miss.
Oh, I see. Could you please tell him he has seat A-5 waiting for him at the premiere of Shao Pai Long?
Seat A-5. And your name, please?
Just tell him it was "Nyan-Nyan."
He'll understand if I tell him that?
Yes! Well, thanks for your help.
Sure, my pleasure.
Where could he have gone to?
And after I got him a reserved seat too.
I'm back.
Good evening, sir.
Oh, Lieutenant! Lieutenant Ichijo!
Yes, what?
You got a phone call a little while ago.
From who?
A young lady. Said you'd know who
if I said "Nyan-Nyan."
Huh? Really?! All right!
Ah! And she said that seat A-5 was...
He's gone. Oh, well.
Hello? Is Miss Minmay there?
Oh...
Well, can you connect me with
the hotel switchboard?
Hurry up, pick up the phone.
I don't care if it was "just for fun," you can't go
wandering around dressed like that, can you?!
Now go to bed. Goodnight.
Goodnight.
What was that phone call about?
Minmay never calls me anymore.
Oh wait. Shao Pai Long
premieres tomorrow.
Warriors!
The one who shot me down
could be among them.
Hey! This way!
What is this crowd here for?
Stop pushing! Move back!
Hey, it's Minmay!
Wow, Minmay sure is popular, huh?
Yeah, good thing we got in line
first thing this morning.
I'm so grateful to all of you for
showing up so early today.
Thanks to the full cooperation of the
military, Shao Pai Long has finally been completed.
And now, let me present the film's stars.
I'm pleased to introduce Lynn Kaifun
and Lynn Minmay!
So, Minmay, how was your
first starring role?
Really hard. You scolded me
every day, Mr. Director.
Hey, hey! Was I really that bad?
Sorry about that.
You were actually very kind to me.
If anything, I was
a bother to the staff.
But I really worked on this
as hard as I could.
I hope you all enjoy the film.
Thank you, Minmay.
Just a little longer and then you
can rest up backstage.
And Kaifun, do you have anything
you'd like to add?
Yes, I do. It was an honor for a novice like me
to have been involved in such a big production.
Y'know, I heard that Minmay and Kaifun are going out!
Your warm support is what made this possible.
No way! Really?
Really!
That's a lie! You've got a lot of nerve saying
that in front of the Minmay Fan Club!
Shut up, you guys! I can't hear!
Well, enough opening remarks.
Minmay, would you be so kind?
Okay!
I hope you like this. It's the theme
song to Shao Pai Long.
Remember!
Dancing in the sky, the silver wings
Shao Pai Long!
Remember!
The eyes of fire splitting the darkness
Shao Pai Long!
To save a diseased city, he has returned
Evil's slayer! Slayer! Slayer!
Shao...
Image enhancement is complete, sir.
Very good. Onscreen.
...splitting the darkness
Shao Pai Long!
It seems to be a visual combat record.
Such a primitive combat!
Why would they be so eager to view
a combat record like this?
To save a diseased city, he has returned
Well, I have no idea, sir.
Evil's slayer! Slayer! Slayer!
That unique fighting style...
Could he be the one who defeated me?
Shao Pai Long!
Is a very messiah!
The light of hope, a messiah!
Hey, that's Minmay!
Moving! Speaking!
Guys, Minmay's a lot cuter in person.
Shao Pai Long!
We got to see the real Minmay, in the flesh!
We're Minmay's friends, you know!
Hey, look!
What was that just now?
Could it be?! Is it the legendary power?
What? They have abilities like that?!
It would explain that energy barrier
we encountered previously!
I suppose we should inform
Lord Bodolzaa of this.
Ow!
Sorry...
You're blockin' my view!
What is... this feeling?
My heart's gotten all warm.
This "culture" stuff gives you feelings
like that all the time!
Is "culture" really that incredible?
It's fantastic.
Did you... Did you all do stuff
like this with Minmay?!
Uh, yeah!
We sure did.
And not just once or twice either!
Gah! I'm sorry!
1st Lt. Ichijo!
Captain Hayase! I'm sorry.
I sort of tripped, and...
And I just happened to be there, is that it?
Of course.
Who'd touch your butt
unless it was by accident?
I beg your pardon!
You tell him, sister!
Call the cops on that pervert!
Come with me! No one respects
the military anymore!
I've never been so embarrassed!
What were you doing there, anyway?
I just went to see the movie...
And you had to leave in the middle, too?
An enemy attack!
Transformation initiated.
All civilians, please get to your shelters.
They're transforming already?
Captain, do you know where the
shelter for this area is?
We're about to be attacked!
We'll have to run back to the base!
Hurry! The shelter's this way!
Minmay!
Are you all right, Minmay?
You okay? You're not hurt?
You must have been scared. You're safe now.
Can't the military even give us
enough time to evacuate?
This is a safe location. Please remain calm.
Jeez, and it was almost over, too.
I have to find that man.
I think we'll be all right if we go this way.
You just had to take us around that corner!
What else could we do?
If a path takes a turn, you turn with it!
Besides, if we hadn't, we would
have been crushed.
What we should have done is
head to a shelter...
Is that any way to talk to
a superior officer?!
Could you not pull rank at a time like this?
It looks like the attack has begun.
I wonder if Shammy's okay?
No, no! Phalanx Pearl Battery goes to, uh...
C-4 block, not B block!
Please make your orders clearer!
I'm sorry.
Oh, Captain Hayase, come back soon!
Come on, stop pouting and say something.
Lt. Ichijo, say something!
Please, say something.
Even if it's just to badmouth me.
I get lonely when people don't talk.
I never thought I'd hear
you admit that YOU get lonely!
Well, excuse me!
There you go. That's the Captain I know.
So was the one you just heard...
To be honest, I was getting
a little lonely too.
I was wondering...
Hey, listen...
Go ahead.
Well, I was wondering why they
transformed so quickly.
When I'm not around, 2nd Lt. Shammy is the
one who gives tactical orders.
Oh, that explains it.
She's been specially trained
for it, you know.
Say, I wonder if Max is doing okay?
Relax, he's a genius, remember?
Yeah, he's a better pilot than I am.
He's a genius. His combat awareness
and piloting skills are top notch.
Just please don't say that in front of him.
Why not?
Well... Not that I think he's the type, but the thing
to be most afraid of when going into battle is overconfidence.
You actually sound like a real commander!
I guess.
Somebody must be talking about me.
Being like this reminds me of
when we were captured.
Yeah, that time was...
It was rather difficult, wasn't it?
But things aren't nearly as desperate
now as they were then.
After all, we're still on board the Macross.
That's right. We're not on some enemy ship!
Still, we're cut off.
We'll be out soon, as soon as
the enemy attack lets up.
But after this one ends,
there will be another.
They just don't give up, do they?
But why do you think they
keep letting us live?
They have all that power, but...
That's right.
You may have already heard this, but the enemy
seems to have split into two factions.
One faction thinks that we're "Protoculture,"
which they fear so much they want
to prevent any contact with us.
And then there are the guys
who want us dead.
That's right. As a result, their chain
of command is in chaos,
which could be why we only
get these sporadic attacks.
But how long can this situation last?
And if they get things under control,
what happens to us?
Do we get to live?
Or will they kill us all?
Purple Battery, the main enemy force
has shifted toward you.
Phalanx Ruby Battery, please provide
support for Purple Battery.
Looks like she's gotten the hang
of giving orders, huh?
Well, she's still got
a lot to learn...
Please! No chatter during combat!
Aye, aye. Understood.
Are you getting thirsty?
Cola!
Ichijo, what's wrong? Are you all right?
Cola! Cola!
Cola!
Hey! Cola!
Ahh, dammit!
Forget it, Ichijo. Sit down.
By the way, what were you doing at the
movie theater, Captain Hayase?
What brought that up?
Nothing. I just thought of it
so I figured I'd ask.
Is there a reason you don't
want to talk about it?
It's not like that! I just went to see
the movie, same as you.
You were watching the movie,
were you? Really?
Yes, I was! I even heard Kaifun
and Minmay's intro.
Oh? I never took you for
the movie-going type.
What's wrong with that?!
I'm a normal girl too, you know!
Girl? Yeah, right. Old lady, maybe.
That's uncalled for!
'Cause a "girl" is more...
Wait a minute.
A woman like you wouldn't have gone
to see the film for Minmay.
That's it! You were there for Kaifun!
That's not true!
I'm right! I'm right, aren't I?!
Captain Hayase, you went to see
that movie for Kaifun!
So, Miss Hayase, what is it about
Kaifun that you find attractive?
Stop making fun of me!
So things are just great between
you and Minmay, are they?
Minmay...
It feels like it was ten years ago.
Come on... Come on...
Don't let what I said get to you.
Don't take it so seriously.
Did you walk out of that theater
for the same reason I did?
But how can you like a guy
who hates the military?
He... looks a lot like someone
I used to care for.
Someone who died before
I could tell him anything.
Thanks...
Still, seeing you act like this seems
almost like a put-on.
I'm sorry. The memories got
a little too strong there.
It's all right.
The kind of life we're living, we all
need someone to love.
I guess so.
The enemy is retreating.
It's finally over.
Shammy, can you hurry up and
take us off of battle alert?
I have a date I'd like to keep.
That's up to the Captain.
What do you think we should do?
Live each day to the fullest.
That's all we can do, isn't it?
Only that?
Only that.
They're switching back to normal mode.
That's right. I guess we've been saved, huh?
Want a cola?
Treating a superior officer?
Maybe in ten years.
Well, bottoms up.
What are you doing?
Quiet!
What's wrong?
No, Captain, you don't need to see this.
Well, what did we expect?
It's okay. Kaifun is her cousin, right?
Besides, Minmay is friendly with everybody.
But those two look like more
than just "friends."
Well, I'm gonna check out things
on the Prometheus, so...
You can check the hangar later, can't you?
Couldn't you stay with me a little longer?
Sure...all right.
Next Episode
Preview
Britai is used by his own superior as a decoy
in a final plan to drive out the Macross.
Onboard the Macross,
Minmay's concert gets underway.
And in a successful surprise attack,
enemy battle pods storm the Macross.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
LOVE CONCERT
"LOVE CONCERT"
I won't follow it anymore
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away