Piercing through the Macro sky,
A thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind
The Light struck.
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
And fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
As the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
That blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
All hands, level-one battle stations!
Love Drifts Away
Yes, sir!
All hands, level-one battle stations!
We'll go to the bridge. This way, please.
I repeat, all hands, level-one battle stations!
Very well.
Shall we go, Milia?
Of course, Max.
We'll be going now, "Sempai."
Don't get yourselves killed!
Understood. Let's go, Milia!
Wait for me, Max!
Minmay...
Hikaru!
I may never see you again,
so I'll just say it.
I...loved you.
What?!
It's so sudden...
Be happy with Kaifun.
Hikaru!
Where are you going?
Please let me go!
Minmay!
Work teams, switch payloads to reaction
warheads on the double!
4th Tomahawk Battery, remain on standby
once the Sentinels deploy.
Squad, move out!
Monster-01, stand by for launch!
Reactor output climbing.
Balancers normal.
All systems green!
Launch!
How is the changeover to reaction
warheads progressing?
We're currently at 70%.
And on your end?
About 20% of the Valkyries still
need to be loaded out.
Have them work faster!
Roger!
Reaction weaponry, eh?
I always thought that we'd be using
our reaction weapons against your fleet.
But not like this.
Ironic indeed, yes?
De-fold signatures are increasing.
Hurry up and get everybody into
the maintenance block!
The gravity controller is at level 8.9.
The enemy fleet is now over
four million ships!
Station Liberty reports that...
The Grand Cannon will reach
critical in 300 seconds.
Silos 7 and 9 are now open!
A fleet of four million ships?
Can we really beat them with
the Grand Cannon?
Are we able to communicate with
the enemy fleet yet?
I've tried several times, but
there's still no response.
So we have no choice but to fight.
3rd Valkyrie interceptor units,
climb to 30,000 meters and...
18th and 27th combat squadrons,
deploy to Area A-4 at once!
Roger!
Come in.
Hikaru?
Minmay!
I only thought of you as a friend.
As a friend, so I...
All ships have de-folded!
Very well. We'll strike the enemy planet first.
All ships, prepare for barrage!
I'm sorry, Hikaru, but I...
I guess I like Kaifun.
It's not your fault. I should have
made my feelings clear.
But...
It's okay, Minmay.
I'm a fighter pilot and you're a big star.
It wouldn't have worked out.
But...
It's funny, isn't it?
Even on a ship as small as the Macross, we're
living in two totally different worlds.
Total annihilation?
Impossible!
Annihilated? The Earth?
It's been wiped out?!
It can't be!
No way!
What is it?
The Earth!
Is it done for?
Probably.
No!
Dad... Mom!
Captain Hayase...
An ocean filled with stardust
Reflects the warm sun back
A little oasis
Our home, the green Earth
One day we shall...
It's all over! First the Earth, and then us!
It's not over yet.
There's something I'd like to ask of you:
Could you sing? Sing for us all?
Sing?
Yeah, I have an idea.
Damage ratio for all sections is 30%.
Is the Grand Cannon secure?
We should be able to fire it.
Very well. Recommence countdown at once.
Roger.
Power generators are online.
Energy levels are climbing.
T-minus 2 minutes to firing.
Commander Britai, I want your fleet to do a
simultaneous translation of Lynn Minmay's song
and transmit it on all military frequencies.
I can do that, but why?
The soldiers of the Bodol Main Fleet are unaware
of the essence of Protoculture.
If we broadcast the female's songs, they will
experience a momentary culture shock,
allowing us to disrupt their
chain of command.
And you'll use that disruption
to attack the Bodol flagship?
This isn't a foe we can beat
in a head-on attack.
Very well.
Broadcasting those songs will likely boost
the morale of our own men as well.
Captain Global...
Ah, Miss Minmay!
I've been in contact with 1st Lt. Ichijo.
We're working on a plan based on his idea.
You will sing for us, won't you?
Yes, I'll do whatever I can to help.
I have one more favor to ask.
Could you perform a "kiss" with that
man who was in your movie?
I'm sorry. But why a kiss?
That is the most effective method of delivering
a psychological shock to us Zentradi.
I'm asking you as well.
All right.
Energy converter is online!
Power is exceeding ignition threshold!
T-minus 20 seconds to firing!
A high-level energy signature is
building on the enemy planet!
What?!
I'm picking up a high-level energy
signature coming from the Arctic!
A section of the enemy fleet
is being eradicated.
Eradicated?
Displaying maximum magnification.
That's... That's the Grand Cannon!
The Grand Cannon?
Alaska Base is still there!
Give it your best, Minmay.
We'll be rooting for you.
Thank you, all of you.
Minmay, stand by to start the operation!
Okay!
Attention, all soldiers of the Macross
and the Britai Adoclas Fleet.
We will now advance through the sector
cleared by the Grand Cannon.
All ships other than our fighters and those
relaying Lynn Minmay's songs are hostiles!
Gentlemen, I expect you to
show me a good fight!
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
My boyfriend is a pilot
Shining, making a rapid descent
Then BOOM! he makes a sudden climb
Simultaneous translation is proceeding well.
Leaving a long trail of vapor
Good.
All ships, launch!
He traces two big hearts
A love sign in the big, blue sky
"I love you, you love me?"
But he's head over heels
What are these visuals?!
I don't know.
It's being broadcast over
our entire communications spectrum!
For his plane instead of me
We are now within firing range.
The enemy is not attacking.
It's working!
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
All ships, open fire!
My boyfriend is a pilot
Minmay...
Farewell, Hikaru.
What is this?!
It's a man...
And a woman!
ATTACK!
Remember...
Dancing in the sky, the silver wings
Shao Pai Long!
Remember...
The eyes of fire splitting the darkness
Shao Pai Long!
To save a diseased city, he has returned
Evil's slayer! Slayer! Slayer!
Shao Pai Long
is a very messiah!
A battleship, huh?
Okay, I'll use reaction missiles.
The light of hope, a messiah!
Shao Pai Long!
I got him!
Area A-4, please respond! Area A-4!
Area A-4!
Misa! You're still there?
What about you, Admiral?
It's a lost cause here.
Get out of here and save yourself!
I can't!
Maybe you were right after all.
Father! Father!
...the fragrance of Turkish coffee fills the air
Along with a listless tango rhythm
I'm alone and lonely, but if I dance
A breeze will blow through my heart
The atmosphere?
I guess I can't make it back.
If you don't show up
I wonder who I'll be dancing with tonight?
Silver Moon
Red Moon
You're so cold, Shanghai dandy
The smoke from the Gitanes gets in my eyes
"So you'll sing? You'll sing for us all?"
"Just for today, I'll do it only for you."
Farewell, Minmay.
The surface has been destroyed...
Please respond!
This is High Command.
If anyone is still alive, please respond!
Captain! Captain Hayase!
That voice! It can't be! Is that you, Ichijo?
You're all right?!
Yes, but it looks like I'm the
only one who survived.
Just you...?
Then I'm coming in to get you.
Give me your current location.
No, it will just put you in danger!
You know I've never obeyed
orders like that.
Ichijo, you... You...
Time drifts away
Love drifts away
Standing before me, a sad look on your face
What should we do?
Boss!
That's a nice song.
We're heading out, too.
I know you're going off to war
But sir! We'd be fighting our allies!
Idiot! I'm Kamujin the Ally Killer!
All the men, together, as if possessed
With mouths pulled tight, with eyes burning
Keep up the barrage!
Britai, don't fall behind!
They march in step
I know I'll be left behind
All for war
All for pride
Time drifts away
Love drifts away
Is this the place?
And I rot away...
Captain!
Ichijo!
Time drifts away
Love drifts away
Standing before you, a helpless look on my face
I'm certain I'll always hate war
All the women, together, will recover
Approaching target!
All reaction weaponry is standing by!
All escort squadrons, deploy at once!
Focus the pinpoint barriers on the bow!
With teeth clenched, with spines firm
It's finally time, yes?
Macross, attack!
For the sake of the children
I know you're going to return
Stop the war, all for the cause of living
Time drifts away
Love drifts away
Damn you, Protoculture!
Before I rot away...
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
But...I guess I disobeyed
orders again, huh?
That's okay.
To tell you the truth, I thought you
might come for me again.
Captain...
I guess it's over.
Yeah...
Do you think everyone's okay?
I don't know.
We might be the only two people
left alive on Earth.
That's not so bad, is it?
'Cause we're not alone.
Ichijo...
A little oasis
That voice!
Our home, the green Earth
Minmay!
The Macross! They made it!
One day, we shall return
Where are they?!
There!
So until then, please don't change
Macross...
"Beautiful place in my heart"
Come on, let's go.
Okay!
Next Episode
Preview
The hellish battle that reduced
the Earth to ashes has ended.
Those few who survived will descend
onto an unrecognizable world and begin working to restore it.
However, new problems begin to arise.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
MY ALBUM
"MY ALBUM"
I won't follow it anymore
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away