Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
will set out on their journey
as the war rages on
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness, they fly toward
that blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
BOOBY TRAP
The year was AD 1999.
The object that had suddenly
crashed into the earth
was a gigantic space battleship
over 1,200 meters in length.
The ship's technology was far in
advance of mankind's own,
and while no trace of alien beings
could be found aboard,
it was clear that extraterrestrial civilizations
did indeed exist beyond our planet
and that they had made the
stars their battlefield.
This prompted both the founding of the
Earth United Nations Government,
which would take precedence over the
interests of the individual nations,
and a concerted effort to restore
the hulking spacecraft.
But the road to establishing the Earth UN
Government wasn't an easy one,
and brush-fire wars
sprang up across the world.
Despite this, restoration of the
battleship progressed steadily.
Finally, the long and painful
"Unification Wars" came to an end,
and the Earth was once again at peace.
In time, this wrecked craft of alien design
was rebuilt by humanity,
and was reborn as the giant
battleship "Macross."
It is now ten years since the Macross
crash-landed on Earth.
What's the matter, Mr. Mayor?
I was just thinking...
Today may be the last day
we'll get to see the Macross.
I'll miss its constant presence.
Still, I wonder if that
monstrosity will even fly?
And I wonder what will happen
to our local businesses?
Now, there's a VIP...
someone who invested a lot in the Macross.
He's probably headed for the launch
ceremony, don't you think?
What's with you, Captain Global?
Got a hangover?
The citizens are out here to celebrate
the launch of your ship.
Why aren't you showing some appreciation?
Huh?
Oh, yes...
Oh!
1st Lieutenant Hayase!
It looks like the captain has
arrived at the stage.
We have fifteen minutes until
the ceremony starts.
We might just make it.
I wonder what the captain has
been doing this whole time?
Probably out partying,
don't you think?
He left last night saying something about
the Earth Defense Council...
That sly old fox!
Not that you would do anything like...
Oh? Whatever do you mean?
You and Major Focker came home
together this morning.
He's quite the celebrity around here.
Staying out all night won't affect my performance.
You may be fine, but the major has to
fly escort for the Macross later!
Oh, that man can drink all night
and not feel it a bit.
He always brags about shooting down five
fighters in the Unification Wars while hung over.
Even so, if something were to happen...
He'll be fine! I guarantee it!
Or perhaps you'd like to take him off my hands?
You can have him! He's all yours!
Wow! Even OUR 1st Lieutenant
is interested in men?!
I had no idea!
That's a terrible thing to say!
To think, 1st Lieutenant Hayase, the top
graduate from the academy, is...
Why, you!
Look at the screen!
Small craft approaching on heading 1057,
please state your affiliation, over.
This is Hikaru Ichijo, invitation
number 1021. Over.
Confirmed.
You were invited by Major Focker, I see.
Please proceed along vector 1069, over.
Roger!
We will now present an aerobatics
demonstration performed by
our newest, most powerful fighter:
the Valkyrie!
Commentary will be provided by the Ace of the
Unification Wars...Major Roy Focker!
Please keep your eyes on planes 2 and 4.
They will pass each other at 950 km/h,
only 20 meters above the ground!
What's more, the two planes will be
just a few meters apart!
Hikaru!
It's you, isn't it!
I know that voice...
Sempai!
It's been a while!
How have you been?
"How have you been?!"
What a moron!
Hikaru! What the hell are you doing,
puttering around up there?!
Huh? That's pretty cold, considering you were
the one who sent me the invitation!
Nobody asked you to come buzzing in
here in a prop plane!
I'm perfectly safe.
Safe my ass! Besides, you could never keep
up with me, so don't go talking all big!
I won't always be in your shadow, Sempai.
Say what?
That idiot!
Dammit!
Sempai!
When did you get so g...
I mean, what the hell was that
little stunt just now?!
It was just a boost to an inverted climb.
You taught me that yourself, remember?
Of course, those military pilots were
pretty good too.
Look, kid, don't get cocky
just because you won
...the Amateur Pilot Competition
two or three times.
What about the other
four or so times?
Seven times?
Big deal!
In the Unification Wars, I shot
down more than 180 planes!
Murderer!
"M...Murderer"?
Look, it's not like I had a choice!
I was just doing my job.
But you made a promise to
my dad, didn't you?
That you'd come back to the team
once the war was over.
I know I let your dad down,
and I'm sorry.
But once you start flying fighters...
Well, if you ever do,
you'll understand.
You sure have changed, Sempai.
Cola!
I wanna have a cola!
No!
I'm not going to buy you any!
You just had some juice a while ago!
Cola! Cola!
It'll make you want to use the restroom! No!
I gotta pee!
You see?
Here we go already!
I'm gonna pee my pants!
Oh, dear!
Well, that's one thing about you
that sure hasn't changed!
Their de-fold signature was tracked
here, to this planet?
That is correct, sir.
Any sign of a re-fold?
No, we have detected no indications
of a second hyperspace jump.
But they should've been withdrawing
from this region eight taarms ago...
Perhaps the signature is from some
other ship that was shot down.
We don't have enough information
to make a determination.
Send out a recon ship to investigate!
This is one of those new fighters,
like the ones from before!
Hikaru, wanna take this baby up?
Can I really?
I'll be in the back seat with you.
Well? This is one of those fighter
planes you hate so much.
It all depends on who's using it!
You never shut up, do you?
The Macross has ushered in vast
improvements in individual welfare
and has profoundly contributed to
the development of humankind.
Once the Macross is launched, Earth's
defenses will finally be complete...
Captain Global.
We've just received a message
from Space Carrier ARMD-I.
They've detected anomalies in
the gravitational field
and luminescent phenomena
originating in lunar orbit.
Gravitational anomalies and
luminescent phenomena?
Just like ten years ago...
...when the Macross arrived.
Let's go to the bridge.
Now, let me introduce the commander
of the Macross, Captain Global!
Where are you going, Captain? Captain!
W...What's going on?
What is it?
Look! The ship's original systems have
just activated themselves!
Huh?
Oh, no!
It's entered firing mode!
Shut down all systems!
I can't! They're not responding!
What is going on?!
The main cannon is activating!
So, it was hiding on the planet after all.
Attention all ships!
Advance into the strike zone!
The... The ship's systems are back
under our control, Captain.
Now that was one flashy salute!
Something's not right...
I'll go check things out.
Hikaru, you stay right here!
Sempai!
This is a Star-class code.
The beam from the main cannon has
destroyed what appears to have been
a spaceship in lunar orbit,
at a range of 280,000 km.
Multiple additional spacecraft detected
and they're closing in rapidly!
Captain?!
We fell for it!
It was a booby trap!
"A booby trap"?
German troops often used them
during the Second World War.
They would hide explosives in things
that would get attention,
like pens or guns, and then they'd retreat,
leaving those things behind.
When somebody picked the object up...
BOOM!
I'll bet the aliens that crashed
this ship planted a program
that controlled an
automatic defense system.
Captain!
No smoking is allowed on the bridge!
Oh, brother...
Shammy!
I...I know that!
I was just keeping it in my mouth!
All hands, Level One combat alert!
What... Just what were
those weapons?!
Well, perhaps...
Out with it!
But no, it couldn't be.
Two enemy vessels approaching!
We believe they are the craft that
launched the weapons!
Crush them!
They don't seem to be part of
the Supervision Army.
Plow through them!
Message from ARMD-II.
ARMD-I is out of commission, and ARMD-II
has sustained minor damage.
The enemy fleet has broken through
the space defense perimeter
and is headed straight for us!
At the Earth Defense Council yesterday,
it was decided that if the Macross
launched into space today
and were to eventually encounter
an alien race
under no circumstances were
we to initiate hostilities.
How ironic this is...
Launch all fighters!
Roger!
All fighters, launch!
We are currently engaged in
hostilities with alien forces.
This is not a drill!
I repeat, this is not a drill!
Another war, huh?
It's been two years!
Ghost Squadrons, launch complete!
Major Focker!
Launch the Valkyrie Squadrons!
Roger!
What?
They're completely disorganized!
This must surely be a primitive species.
So they DID find the Supervision Army ship.
What's this?
This type of vessel is not in my records.
Not in your records?
But you're the Chief Archivist!
What's more, it seems to resemble
the weapons of this planet.
You can't mean that they
found this ship and...
Restored it.
Yes, it's quite possible.
Preposterous!
I can't believe that such a primitive species
could possibly possess the lost technology!
It fits the facts.
It would also explain the missiles we saw earlier.
The long-lost...
Reaction weaponry.
And if that's the case, we cannot
justify destroying them.
J'nerl target pinpointed.
Now launching!
VT-102!
VT-102 on the display grounds!
Why haven't you taken off yet?
VT-102?
Huh?
Stop fooling around!
Take off at once!
We're in the middle of a battle!
Take off?!
But the runway's a mess!
Oh, well...
Here goes nothing!
This is Skull Leader.
Attention, all fighters in
Sepia and Mountain Teams:
scatter and take down the
enemy in zone 428!
Sempai!
Focker-Sempai!
Where are you?!
Is that you, Hikaru?
When did you become a fighter pilot?
You're joking!
Like I'd ever become a fighter.
Hey! What's going on?!
Hikaru!
You okay?
I think so.
Calm down, Hikaru. What happened to that
hotshot attitude you had earlier?
Say, Hikaru. Flying in formation like this
feels just like the old days, don't it?
How can you be so laid-back
at a time like this?!
I was always in front, and you'd be
puttering around behind me, right?
I told you before, didn't I?
I'm not gonna be in your shadow forever!
That's the spirit.
Follow me!
Hikaru!
Damn!
Damn it!
I swore that when I died, it'd be during
a stunt, just like Dad.
VT-102!
You're on a collision course with us!
Veer off at once!
It's no good!
It's no good at all!
The rudders and spoilers are fried,
and nothing else is responding!
Why don't you just change to Configuration B?
Configuration B?
You don't know what that is?!
But that would mean...
Okay, pull the "B" lever on the left of
your console and engage ACS!
Understood!
Huh?
I'm saved.
Still not clear what's happening around him,
Ichijo finds himself drawn into the conflict.
Amidst the flames of battle awaits a
fateful encounter: Lynn Minmay.
Hikaru has no way of knowing
just how important...
...this beautiful young girl will become.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"COUNT DOWN"
I won't follow it anymore,
the shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end,
but we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
the light that shines so far away