Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
as the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
That blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
The conflict between Max and Milia
has ended in marriage.
This, however, has plunged
Britai's fleet into chaos.
MESSENGER
A single enemy ship is approaching.
Move the main cannon into firing position.
Target the approaching enemy ship!
Yes, sir!
Main cannon, lock on target!
The main cannon is standing by to fire!
Target lock acquired!
Maybe they want to settle this one-on-one!
Don't be stupid.
Why would they do something like that?
Hey, it happens in comic books all the time!
Idiot.
Why do you have to call me
an idiot all the time?!
Please delay firing the main cannon!
I'm getting a transmission from the enemy vessel.
They request a cease-fire.
What?
Shall I put it on the speaker?
The approaching vessel does not intend
to attack. We request a cease-fire.
Enemy fighters closing in fast!
What are they up to?
What the hell are you doing?!
You're interfering with our negotiations.
Just stay out of the way and watch.
We can beat them!
Why do we need a cease-fire?!
If we don't negotiate a cease-fire,
the fleet will tear itself apart.
Preposterous!
You think so?
A peace envoy?
Culture shock may have hit them
harder than we thought.
Leader! It sure feels strange escorting
an enemy pod, doesn't it?
You got that right.
I wonder who's inside?
Hey there!
What are you doing?
I can't climb down by myself!
Ah, forgive me, sir!
I didn't mean to...
These miclone bodies are
so weak and powerless.
So this is how we look to them, eh?
Welcome aboard. I'm Colonel Maistroff,
UN Forces, Strategic Space Command.
I beg your pardon?
It's a sign of friendship.
I am Exsedol, Zentradi Zem
1st Class, Chief Archivist.
Archivist, you say?
Indeed.
Please, if you'll follow me.
Archivist Exsedol, I would ask that
this gentleman remain here.
You wait here!
Yes, sir!
Be good hosts and get him something to eat.
"Be good hosts and get him something to eat"...?
How much could this guy put away?
Don't ask me! Anyway, let's bring him
a container or something to sit on.
And what might that be?
They sell electronic goods there.
And use "money" to conduct "business," correct?
You're certainly well-informed!
What in the world is that?!
It gave me quite a shock!
Well, that would take a lot of explaining,
so perhaps some other time...
Ah, a military secret, eh?
I see, I see.
And what is that translucent uniform?
Uh, umm... that's a
military secret too!
The ambassador has entered
the conference room.
Understood. I'll be right there.
What about the enemy ship?
No change whatsoever.
Maintain our current status.
Claudia!
Yes, sir.
I'm counting on you.
If they make any hostile moves...
then shoot.
Yes, sir!
Here you are, sir.
This is delicious!
Then please have another.
Thank you, thank you!
The concerned parties still aren't here yet?
No, sir. After all, they were on
combat duty when we called them.
Milia!
1st Flight Commander Milia!
Archivist Exsedol!
Excellency!
That wedding business caused a
rather astonishing commotion.
Sir!
Even I had no idea
that things would turn out like this.
Or that I would be here either, I'll bet.
Sir.
And this is the male
you've mated with?
Yes, sir.
That's right.
"Mated with"?
Reporting for duty.
Max, what's with that face?!
Oh!
Being micloned, I didn't recognize you at first
but you're one of the prisoners
from the main fleet!
You're that...!
Our positions are much different now.
How did you escape us?
Was it the power of Protoculture?
I don't know how to answer...
Another military secret, eh?
I'm Warera Nantes.
Conda Bromco...
Loli Dosel...
Lord Exsedol!
I see the masterminds behind our
Protoculture-shock are all here.
We, that is...
That is to say...
To say we, uh, well...
Relax, nothing's going to
happen to you.
Now then, Archivist Exsedol,
would you please tell us the reason
for this meeting?
Two vitally important people
are not yet present.
They are the reason that things
have come to this:
The superhuman Shao Pai Long,
and the woman who is at the core
of your psychological attacks.
"Shao Pai Long"?
He means that movie!
It looks like they thought those
were real super powers!
That's quite a misunderstanding!
But what about this "psychological attack"?
I don't know of anyone who could be at
"the core of a psychological attack."
Could you perhaps be more specific?
A person of that magnitude isn't
considered important?
It must be Protoculture, all right.
Hey!
Could he mean...
Her?
What I mean is:
"Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!"
"My boyfriend is a pilot"
Minmay!
We knew it!
Lynn Minmay!
"Shining, making a rapid descent"
"Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh!"
"Then BOOM! he makes a sudden climb"
I thought as much.
"Leaving a long..."
Who would've thought that a song
could have such an effect?
"Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!"
Make arrangements at once.
"Plane..."
Minmay...
Excuse me, what were we called here for?
It's just another example of
military being self-centered!
They never think about us civilians!
I will not...
Mr. Lynn Kaifun!
We are in the middle of negotiations.
This is not the place for you to
be giving your speeches.
Furthermore, you are not to repeat
what you see or hear here.
Understood?
Yes!
You might be able to accomplish
what you've always wanted.
We should cooperate with them.
Everyone you requested is now here.
Very good.
I certainly hope we can negotiate
with the Zentradi, but...
Have you gotten the hang of
things here, Captain Hayase?
Yes, sir, but...
They say the Macross has entered into
a cease-fire with the Zentradi.
So it would seem.
If it holds, we might not have to
use the Grand Cannon.
I doubt that will be the case.
The report says that the cease-fire is only with
that part of the fleet that's already here.
In the end, we'll
probably use it.
I'll be in the central core.
If you need anything, come see me.
Lynn Kaifun, what is your rank?
I'm a civilian.
A civilian?! You, a warrior with
such superhuman abilities?
I have no superhuman abilities!
What?
I'll be honest with you.
You'll find out eventually anyway.
We do not possess the supernatural
powers you've attributed to us.
But that man's...
That was a form of entertainment
we call a "movie."
But what about the destructive power
of the Macross's energy field?
I assume you mean the barrier and
the explosion that occurred.
That was purely
technological in nature.
But...
How can this be?
But you cannot deny the
power of that song!
The power of that song?
Excellency!
That's the real thing!
We've been deeply moved by the
power of the songs!
Long ago, those who encountered
the Protoculture
were drained of their will
to fight by song.
They awakened to culture and
they were destroyed.
What did you just say?
To us Zentradi, warfare is life and our
history is one of battle after battle.
But once again we have met with culture,
and the shock of this has made our
soldiers begin to reject warfare.
So as to avoid the mistakes
of our predecessors,
Lord Bodolzaa, supreme commander
of the main fleet,
has ordered that ours is the only
fleet to have contact with you.
However, if he learns of these results,
the main fleet will most likely
launch an all-out attack.
To wipe out Earth's
culture, you see.
The main fleet?
The large fleet mentioned in your report?
Yes, sir.
Britai, what is the meaning
of this cease-fire?
Do you think our fleet can fight the
Macross in the shape we're in?
In any case, this will all be settled
once the main fleet arrives.
The main fleet?
Damn you, Lap'Lamiz, you didn't!
I have reported everything to Lord Bodolzaa.
He decided to mobilize the main fleet.
So he has determined that the people
of Earth are the Protoculture?
That's right.
In that case...
This fleet will be destroyed
along with the Earth.
Preposterous!
Why?
Because we've been contaminated
by the Protoculture.
What?!
What was that, Lord?
Is that true?
Yes, yes...
Then our fleet will be...
Understood.
I wonder, would the Macross alone
choose to flee the Earth?
You want us to abandon the Earth?!
Correct.
We could never agree to that!
The Macross is a warship, part of the
Earth UN Forces, and...
Yes, that is the answer I expected.
As it would prove rather difficult
for our fleet to escape,
it seems that we will be facing
a common enemy.
What?!
What do you mean?
I have just received word that the main
fleet is headed for this star system.
The main fleet?
The Bodol main fleet, which consists
of 4,790,122 warships,
has finally been mobilized.
It looks like we need to prepare ourselves.
We may have to trust to fate whether
or not the Earth will survive, but...
We'll do everything we can.
You must be joking!
Five million ships?!
It's over.
This is hopeless.
Milia, we may die.
Max, nothing would be greater than
dying together in combat.
Together...
This is not the end!
What?
The Macross has fought us off
single-handedly, has it not?
There is no guarantee of victory,
but we have a way to fight them.
I hear they've even called in the reserves!
Man, there goes my leave!
The Zentradi have a pretty big fleet, don't they?
So what?
We got the Grand Cannon!
Oh, I see.
Admiral!
Misa!
Very well, this way.
What's the matter?
What will happen to the Macross?
It probably won't survive.
Before long, we'll have to use it to
divert the enemy's attention.
But that's...
It may be cruel, but there's no other way.
Father, I have something to ask of you.
What is it?
Please send me back to the Macross.
What are you saying?
I want to stand with my comrades.
We've fought this far side by side!
You ought to be able
to do it, Father!
You want to go that badly?
Yes!
So you'll...
I can't let you go!
Father...
I can't let you go.
I cannot send my only beloved
daughter to certain death!
There's no way I could let you go!
I am a soldier.
So am I.
Then transfer me!
Listen, I'm also a father.
I'll throw you in
the brig if I have to!
What do you two intend to do?
I...
Lord Bodolzaa probably intends to
destroy our fleet as well.
There's no other choice.
It seems I must walk the same path as you.
Lap'Lamiz...
Do not die in vain.
You either, Britai.
What about you, Kamujin?
Count me out.
There's no way you can win.
Besides, I can't stomach the thought
of helping the Macross.
Very well, I wasn't counting
on your help anyway.
Huh?
Oh, is that so?!
Let's go.
Where to?
Anywhere.
Set whatever coordinates you want.
Kamujin...
What?
Are you sure about this?
Damn right.
Let's go!
Lord Bodolzaa, I will show you how
Britai Kridanik fights his last battle.
In many cases, branch fleets are ordered to
retreat should their flagship be destroyed.
There's one more thing.
One more thing?!
Within the branch fleets, only
Belnar-class flagships,
that is, ships occupying one of
the top three ranks,
are informed of the position
of the rest of the fleet.
I see, so we "crush the head of
the snake," is that it?
That's still more than 2,000
heavy warships to deal with.
So, will the Earth join our thousand ships
to fight an enemy of 4.8 million?
Archivist Exsedol...
Such is the consensus of our
Protoculture-contaminated fleet.
Miss Minmay, your songs have
shaken us to our very core.
Well, I...
Soon we will face the main fleet in
a battle that is both unavoidable
and in all probability quite ferocious.
We may never again be able to listen to
and be moved by your songs.
Miss Minmay, would you sing for us here?
Sure!
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
My boyfriend is a pilot
Shining, making a rapid descent
Then BOOM! he makes a sudden climb
Leaving a long trail of vapor
He traces two big hearts
A love sign in the big, blue sky
"I love you, you love me?"
But he's head over heels
For his plane instead of me
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
My boyfriend is a pilot
Multiple de-fold signatures detected!
I have to go.
Detecting suspected de-folds:
Multiple gravitational anomalies
and luminescent phenomena!
What?!
The signatures are increasing in number!
The readings are too strong.
We're unable to calculate!
De-fold readings are off the scale!
The main fleet!
Next Episode
Preview
Nearly five million ships under
Bodolzaa's command
have completely encircled the Earth.
All peaceful avenues of resolution
have been closed.
Hikaru bids Minmay farewell and
heads off for the final battle.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
Love Drifts Away
"Love Drifts Away"
I won't follow it anymore
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running to the end
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away