Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
will set out on their journey
as the war rages on
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness, they fly toward
that blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
Two months have passed since the Macross,
just prior to its launch ceremony,
executed a sudden space fold and was instantly
transported inside the orbit of Pluto.
The Macross is currently
headed back to Earth.
It fended off a Zentradi attack by
making a transformation,
but the change in the ship's structure
caused a great deal of casualties
among the refugees on board.
However, the people have
since rebuilt their city,
DAEDALUS ATTACK
and for the moment, things are
peaceful once again.
Meanwhile, having volunteered
for military service,
Hikaru Ichijo has been undergoing the
rigorous training of a new recruit.
Then, at last, came the day
of his first leave.
Here, let me carry that.
No, I've got it!
But, it looks bad.
Makes no difference to me.
Sorry...
Wow, they're so pretty!
Hang on a second!
Would you come look at them with me?
Huh?
You want me to go in THAT store?!
Well, do what you like.
No choice, huh?
No peeking.
Come right in!
Thanks, we will.
Um, where's your lingerie corner?
Right this way, please.
For crying out loud...
Huh?
Wow, this is cute!
What do you think?
It looks great!
Let's come back some other time.
Come back any time!
What do you think, Hikaru?
What are you doing?
Oh!
I think it really suits you.
This is it?
That abnormal energy reaction you mentioned?
Yes, Captain.
It's a phenomenon we haven't seen before.
This is where the Fold System
used to be, isn't it?
Could there be some connection
between the two?
Sir. It's possible that the disappearance
of the Fold System resulted in
a distortion of the space-time continuum.
Well?
Is it interfering with any of the ship's systems?
Not at the moment, no.
Very well.
Continue with your analysis.
Captain.
If we can harness this energy, I believe
we could create some kind of barrier.
Is that possible?
Yes, sir.
Very well.
Get started on it immediately.
Aye, sir!
Well?
Do you have an explanation?
I've analyzed it
from every angle,
but I just can't see the necessity
of adopting this configuration.
However...
taking this shape would compromise
their gravity control system,
greatly limiting their speed.
Continue playback, sir?
No, that's enough.
Return to the original image.
Yes, sir!
What planet is that?
The fifth planet in
this star system, sir.
I believe they'll try to lose
us in its vicinity.
That is a possibility.
If they activate their ECM
within those rings,
it will be impossible for us
to pinpoint their location.
That plan is almost too obvious.
Your opinion, sir?
Let them attempt to carry out their plan.
When they run to the planet, we'll
have them like vermin in a hole.
Uncle!
Auntie!
What's wrong, Minmay?
Look!
Hikaru's back!
It's been about a month, hasn't it?
Maybe it's my imagination,
but you look so grown up now!
Training you pretty hard, huh?
Come on, sit down. And you guys, too.
Hikaru isn't on display, you know.
It looks like business is good.
Ah, it's nothing really.
Anyway, eat up while they're still hot.
Hikaru!
There you are!
You're about to get the order to sortie.
Get back to the barracks.
I... I'm gonna sortie already?!
Yeah!
The orders just came down.
Five recruits were formally assigned
to combat duty.
And you're one of 'em.
Huh?!
Wow!
Congratulations, Hikaru!
M-Me...?
Don't just sit there.
Come on!
Well, see you all later!
Good luck!
As of today, you're a real soldier.
You'll even be moving from your communal
room in the barracks to a private one.
However, just because you
have your own room
doesn't mean you can do any stupid thing you want.
You got that?
Sempai, I'm not like you.
Aren't you...?
Oh, you know 1st Lt. Hayase?
Um, well, kinda...
Oh, man!
It's that guy!
Ooh!
Mr. Lingerie!
What are you talking about?
Well, we were in this lingerie shop, and...
What? No way!
So, Major Focker, is THIS the "fine recruit"
you've taken under your wing?
That's correct.
Hikaru Ichijo, ma'am!
I'm Misa Hayase.
Hikaru Ichijo?
Where have I heard that
name before...?
"So, this is the civilian?"
"That would explain why he
didn't know anything."
"Hey, what's with the old lady?"
"'Old lady'?!"
"So, even Hikaru thinks she
looks like an old lady?"
You're that civilian!
And you're that old lady!
Ulp!
Excuse me, ma'am!
Well, she's your superior now,
so you'd better watch what you say.
Aye, aye!
I look forward to working with
you in the future.
By the way, I don't know
what you're into,
but it doesn't look good for a man
to be going into those kinds of shops.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Pervert!
Captain, electronic counter-measures
are now active.
I don't think they'll be able
to track us for a while.
What next, sir?
We launch a surprise attack.
A surprise attack?
A surprise attack, sir?
Captain...
Once we leave Saturn, they'll
be after us again.
I want to launch a sudden attack,
and then disengage.
But, captain...!
I'm fully aware that it's a risk.
Yes, sir.
We'll reduce speed and begin
preparations for the attack.
Ow...!
Tomorrow, we will be luring the enemy
force into Saturn's rings
and then hit them with a surprise attack.
That's all I can say at this point,
but beyond that:
I expect you to show me your
hearts as true pilots.
That is all.
If there's anyone you want to see,
say your goodbyes to them tonight!
Dismissed!
I'm sorry!
Waiting long?
Not really.
So, what's the big emergency?
I'm going into battle tomorrow morning.
Wow, really?
Your first day as a soldier, huh?
Minmay...
You're a wonderful pilot.
I'm sure you'll do great.
I mean, everyone's already
says that about you.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Hey, Hikaru.
Look.
Wow, you look so lady-like.
After I went and wore the
dress we bought together!
I'm sorry.
It really looks good on you.
You mean it?
Yeah.
I'm so glad!
Why don't we get a picture
to remember this by?
Oh, but I never look good in photos...
That's not true at all.
Come stand over here.
Camera!
Okay, get ready.
Not too bad.
It did a good job.
Well, I'd better be getting back.
If I'm out alone with a guy for too long,
my aunt and uncle get worried.
Oh...
Yeah. Well, be careful out there.
I wish we could talk longer, but
good luck tomorrow.
See you.
Bye-bye!
Bye.
Tomorrow...
...I could be dead, Minmay.
Captain, we can now activate
the barrier system.
Oh, really?
However, the energy field simply
can't completely cover the Macross.
I see. The Macross is too big.
The system has its limits.
Captain, this isn't an ideal solution, but...
Please observe.
If the enemy attacks, we can
raise the barrier like this.
Then, should an attack approach
one of our vulnerable points,
we can move the barrier
to intercept, like so.
I see.
The positioning is controlled
by the barrier system team.
We're calling the device
the Pinpoint Barrier.
Well done.
What a measly barrier, huh?
Come in.
I figured you'd still be up.
Sempai.
You'll be up early tomorrow.
But...
I know how nervous you are,
but count sheep or something
and just go to sleep!
His first mission.
I'm not surprised.
The hours just before a battle
are the worst of all.
Minmay, I can't sleep.
Attention Valkyrie squadrons.
The surprise attack will take place
in the Cassini Divide.
Squadrons will assemble into seven groups
and stand by in the ice rings.
Repeat, the surprise attack will
take place in the Cassini Divide.
Sleep well?
Yeah, sort of.
I was the same way before my first mission.
Well, one night without sleep won't kill you.
Sempai.
All Valkyrie squadrons, report to the
Prometheus and confirm personnel.
Valkyrie Skull Squadron, launch!
Valkyrie...
Valkyrie Skull Squadron No. 23,
Hikaru Ichijo, now launching.
Roger.
Orange, Purple, and Rose Valkyrie teams:
advance into the rings...
...and proceed to point R-18
in the Cassini Divide.
Lure the enemy ships into range
of the main cannon.
Why's everyone flying so dangerously?
Skull 23!
Why are you playing around like that?
Weren't you paying attention
at the briefing?!
That kind of fancy flying will give
you away to the enemy!
This isn't an aerobatics show!
But the others were all flying
really dangerously, so I...
Be quiet and follow
your orders!
Okay, I got it!
Is that any way to talk to a superior?!
Take a look around you, Mister!
You're the only one who's goofing off!
Roger, roger...
This is going to be
tougher than I thought.
Skull Leader to all units.
We'll soon be heading into the
planet's shadow zone.
Watch out for ice.
And keep your eyes on your instruments!
So, that's the shadow zone, huh?
Skull 23.
Your speed's dropping.
Easy for you to say.
I can't see a thing out here!
Oh, dear. What happened to all that
confidence you had earlier?
How come I have to get bossed
around by some old lady
who's sitting somewhere nice and safe?
I do hope he'll stop insulting
his superior officers
by the time the attack starts.
It's all right.
It doesn't bother me.
Hayase, how long until the Valkyrie
squadrons reach their targets?
About five more minutes, sir.
Good. Once the enemy ship
enters the rings, we'll fire the main gun.
Sound firing stations.
Yes, sir.
You called me, Commander Britai?
Captain Zeril, I want you to approach the
sixth planet and capture the enemy vessel.
Sir!
Preferably undamaged.
Understood.
Here it comes!
Commence attack!
As weak as they are,
they dare to attack us?!
Their grasp of battle tactics is laughable!
They haven't realized we're holding back
in order to capture their vessel.
It's time we show them how terrifying
we can be!
The enemy vessel is approaching,
within the main gun's starboard firing arc.
We have a lock!
Good!
Raise the ship and fire the main gun!
It's the enemy ship!
Firing main cannon.
What's wrong?!
We can't fire the main gun!
The Pinpoint Barrier system seems
to be preventing it from operating somehow!
I don't believe it.
Incoming missiles!
Activate the Pinpoint Barrier!
Aye!
Oh, no!
I'll never make it!
No, don't attack from the side!
Come from the front!
What IS that?
Make a fool of me, will you?!
Agh, not that way!
We're completely surrounded.
Captain, Valkyrie Teams Green and
Brown have been wiped out!
Rose Team is under heavy attack.
Then it's all up to Skull Squadron.
Thanks, Hikaru!
Sempai, why isn't the Macross
firing the main gun?
We can't take much more.
Captain, would it be possible to
concentrate all the energy
from the Pinpoint Barrier to
the front of the Daedalus?
I think we could, but...
Please do it!
I have an idea!
Very well.
I leave it to you.
Kim, Shammy. Assemble all the Destroids
at the bow of the Daedalus!
Right!
Claudia! Send the Macross straight
toward the enemy ship!
Understood!
Ow...!
An airlock...
The enemy ship is closing in!
Fire!
Blast them to pieces!
Daedalus Attack!
What is that?!
Wha...
What's going on?!
It worked!
Yeah.
That was great!
The Daedalus Attack!
I could really become a fan of yours!
We may need to call in reinforcements.
Y...Yes, sir.
With the destruction of the mother ship, the battle pod
pilots lost their will to fight,
and were soon defeated.
Of course, it goes without saying that
Focker, Hikaru, and the others
also played an important role
in the enemy's defeat.
However, try as he might,
Hikaru could not erase the image of the
terrified soldier's face from his mind.
At that moment, when faced with
a flesh-and-blood person,
Hikaru had found himself unable
to pull the trigger.
Focker-Sempai told him that
he was no different at first.
Now able unflinchingly to pull
the trigger against enemy ships,
Hikaru felt that somewhere in his heart,
he was losing touch with his emotions.
Next Episode
Preview
Mars: home to an abandoned base
from the Unification Wars.
The Macross sets course for Mars
in search of supplies.
But for Misa, the planet brings
back heartbreaking memories.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"BYE-BYE MARS"
BYE-BYE MARS
I won't follow it anymore,
the shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end,
but we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
the light that shines so far away