Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
as the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
That blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
Claudia has told Misa of her
early days with Roy Focker,
and in those memories, Misa finds
reflections of Hikaru and herself.
PRIVATE TIME
Maybe I should have used a little more mustard...
Yahoo!
Huh, the phone?
Hello, Ichijo speaking.
Hikaru? It's me!
Who am I speaking with?
Me! Can't you tell?
Minmay? Is that you, Minmay?
Have you been doing okay, Hikaru?
You bet!
Thank you for before.
If you hadn't saved me, I would've...
Hey, it's all over now.
Anyway, are you free today?
Well, I...
I'd love to see you. Can you come to
Highlander City right away?
Right away?
Is that a problem?
Well, I sort of made plans...
"It's a promise!"
Come on, just change them!
You're meeting someone who lives
in Macross City, right?
Yeah...
Then you can see them anytime!
I guess you're right.
So c'mon!
"This is Skull One.
Nothing unusual to report on patrol."
"Now returning to base."
"Roger. Good work, Ichijo."
"Thanks. Say, do you have any plans
for your day off tomorrow?"
"Eh? No, nothing at all."
"I'm flying over the forest zone right now."
"If you want, how about coming to see
it tomorrow? It's really beautiful."
"Really?"
"Really. It's a promise, then.
We'll work out the details when I get back."
"Roger! Thanks, that will be wonderful!"
I can see them anytime, huh?
Okay! If I just explain things,
I'm sure they'll understand.
So you'll come then, right?
Yeah!
I'll be waiting. Hurry on over!
I guess I am a little early.
Hikaru!
Over here!
Minmay?
Thanks for coming!
I didn't recognize you at first in that outfit.
It's a disguise. Anyway, hurry up
and come over here!
I'm sorry for calling you on such short notice.
Was the person you made plans with angry?
No, they understood.
Anyway, is it all right for us to be so close?
What if some gossip columnist spots us?
So long as I'm with you, I don't care.
Huh?
With this disguise, no one's
going to know it's me.
Even you didn't recognize me at first.
Yeah, but still...
Turn this way.
Your tie's crooked.
Thanks.
So you've got some proper clothes after all.
Talk about a surprise!
They look good on you.
I don't know...
Come on, let's go!
A friend of my producer owns this place.
A lot of celebrities come here.
I guess you're a full-fledged celebrity now, huh?
I have been for a while, thank you.
So where's your manager today?
He's out setting up some work for me.
I wonder what's wrong? He sure is late.
Hikaru? What's wrong?
Nothing.
Here.
It's not much, but I wanted to
thank you for saving me.
No, you don't have to thank me.
Don't say anything and just take it.
Really?
Go ahead, open it.
Are you sure?
Uh-huh!
Hey! Is it true that Major Hayase and
Captain Ichijo are out on a date?
It sure looks that way.
I bet the two of them are spending
a romantic day off right now!
Must be nice...
Come on, stop being so insensitive!
It's none of your business what
Major Hayase is doing.
Unbelievable!
The less popular the girls,
the more insensitive they are.
WHAT?!
Wow, thanks!
Do you like it?
I do, I do!
Thank you! I'll take good care of it.
It goes great with your outfit.
You think so?
But isn't it just a little long?
That extra bit's for me.
How inconsiderate! You could have
brought those a little later.
But you young people always seem
to be in such a hurry.
To our reunion! Cheers!
Cheers!
How many years has it been since
we were alone like this?
The last time was just after
that mission, so...
Let's see...
I think it's been around two years.
Two years... It seems short but
it's actually a long time, huh?
It's better to think of it as a short
time that just seems long.
But you don't feel the same
way you did then, do you?
Huh?
"I may never see you again,
so I'll just say it."
"I...loved you."
You can't just drop something
like that out of the blue...
Oh, man...
I'm sorry, today we're...
Ah! Mr. Kaifun!
I thought you'd be here.
I found a job, but it's
right now. Let's go.
No!
What are you saying?!
You're a professional, aren't you?
Is that any way to act?
Minmay, if this is a bad time,
I can come back later.
You just sit right there!
Come on.
That hurts! Let go!
Enough already! You're acting
like a spoiled child!
Well, now I'm all tipsy.
There's no way I could work!
That'll sober you up.
Enough with your games.
Minmay!
Sorry, Ichijo.
I guess I've ruined your little date.
I'll apologize properly later, but for now
don't worry about the bill.
If you'll excuse us.
Farewell, Minmay.
Bartender, another scotch and water.
You should call it quits.
You've already had too much.
If he's not at home either,
then where could he be?
If there was a scramble, they
would've called me in too.
Watch where you're going, you
dumb jerk!
Shut up, moron!
Maybe he was in an accident!
No, that's not it.
Good afternoon, military command center!
Machizaki? It's me, Hayase.
Major Hayase! How can I help you?
It's nothing important.
Actually, it's just a personal matter.
Yes, ma'am?
Do you know where Captain Ichijo is?
Captain Ichijo, ma'am?
Surely you have a much better idea of where
Captain Ichijo is than I would, Major!
Talk about insensitive!
Be quiet!
With a personality like that,
no woman will ever fall for you!
They wouldn't even go out with you!
Oh, yeah?! I don't see anybody
going out with you!
Never mind!
Of all the...
I bet Misa's already gone home by now.
From here on out it's off limits.
Then could you tell me another way
to get to the airport?
There are some Zentradi on the rampage
at the airport right now!
What did you say?!
Now you know, so just go on back.
Hey!
You can't go in there!
Wait! Come back here!
Misa...
I hope I'm not too late.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
What do you think of that?!
Smash some more stuff!
I can't land in this situation!
What on earth could he be doing?
Captain Ichijo! I hope you realize what
we had to do.
Authorizing you to take command of this
operation is a very special case!
I appreciate your kindness!
I expect to see that reflected
in your work out there.
Ichijo, moving out!
You're completely surrounded.
Resistance will get you nowhere!
Shut up!
There's our answer!
Damn them all!
This is Ichijo!
Commence Operation A!
They got us! It's hopeless!
Hang in there, you idiot!
They're just tear-gas shells!
What?
Damn Earth people!
All right! Now!
Hey! Do you have things
wrapped up over there?
Yes, sir, Captain.
Oh, man... It's finally over.
Captain Ichijo, what should we
do with these guys?
Lock them up in a hangar or something.
Headquarters will deal with them later.
If I don't apologize to her today,
she'll never speak to me again.
I'm such an idiot...
Are you alone, too?
Hey, I know!
Just a second.
You can smell what's in there, can't you?
Okay, okay. Here you go.
Shane! Shane, where are you?
Come back, Shane!
Oh!
Alone again, huh?
Hey!
I'm really sorry about today!
I can't believe you're still here.
The forest park is closed by now
but why don't we go someplace
and eat these sandwiches?
Sure. Something came up
all of a sudden, and...
That's okay, but I wish you
had at least called me.
I kept calling, but...
It's all right.
What's the matter?
You're wrapping that around the wrong person.
Huh?
No! You've got it all wrong!
Misa!
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen
of South Coast City!
Congratulations on receiving the
right of self-government
from the New UN Government.
Today, to celebrate your first
step toward autonomy,
Miss Lynn Minmay has rushed all the
way here to South Coast City!
Let Minmay's singing embody our hopes for the
future and let's all give her a warm welcome.
Here's her old favorite,
"My Boyfriend is a Pilot!"
Huh?
Minmay?
What's going on?
What's happening?
Hey, she's not singing.
What's going on?
Minmay! Minmay!
Minmay! Minmay! Minmay! Minmay!
Go on, Minmay! Sing!
I'm sorry, everyone.
I...
I don't want to sing today!
Hey!
Minmay!
What the hell?!
But why?
It's because of you.
Ever since you showed up, Hikaru
and I have grown farther apart.
You haven't changed at all,
not since we were kids.
You only think of yourself.
How did your audience feel as they
were going home just now?
Did you think about that?
Your songs don't belong to you alone.
It's easy to say that, but...
When your songs have a kindness
that projects concern for people's feelings...
then you'll be a real singer.
These past two years, I've worked in my own
way to hear those real songs of yours.
But all that ended today.
I'm leaving again. I probably won't
see you for a long time.
One of these days, let me hear a song
that's filled with kindness.
Take care of yourself.
Next Episode
Preview
It's Christmas time, and news has spread
of Minmay's disappearance.
Meanwhile, Kamujin and his men
have attacked Onogi City.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
ROMANESQUE
"ROMANESQUE"
I won't follow it anymore
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running to the end
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away