Piercing through the Macro sky,
A thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind
The Light struck.
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
And fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
As the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
That blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
The appearance of defectors
aboard the Macross
has raised the possibility of coexistence
with the Zentradi.
Seeing a glimmer of hope, Misa
resolves to travel to Earth
to persuade those at UN High Command.
GOODBYE GIRL
Hey! Pull yourself together, Misa.
You think you'll be able to convince
them looking like that?
Right, that's better.
Did you tell Lieutenant Ichijo
that you're going to Earth?
He'll find out eventually.
The shuttle is ready for launch.
It is scheduled to depart in fifteen minutes.
What about Zentradi movements?
No movement detected from
point A-4 onward, sir.
No change, eh?
I just hope they don't launch another attack.
The Captain's pretty restless, huh?
There's someone here who's
even more restless.
Look, look.
Valkyrie Violet Squadron!
Prepare to begin your landing sequence!
How's everything going, Shammy?
Captain! Excuse me, but please don't
talk to me while I'm giving orders!
Oh. Sorry.
No kidding. She even forgot to say,
"No smoking on the bridge!"
Escort squadron, prepare to launch
in three minutes.
Hmm. Captain Hayase's stand-in is Shammy, huh?
Can that kid handle it?
The rumor is she's kind of a screw-up.
They mounted FAST Packs?
I guess I'm going now.
Hang in there.
Right...
Is this the communicator?
Yes, ma'am.
Can it connect to the ship's internal phone line?
Yes, if you don't mind voice-only.
This is Ichijo.
Your call is being connected.
Hello?
It's Hayase.
Captain? Um, I've got the day off, you know.
This isn't about work.
What's going on?
I just wanted to say goodbye.
Goodbye?
I'm about to leave for Earth.
I'm taking all the data we've acquired
to try to persuade High Command
to end the war with the Zentradi.
What? No one told me about this!
If it got out that I was heading back to Earth,
it could cause unrest among
the civilians on board.
Soldiers using special
authority to return to Earth.
That's how they'd see it.
So this had to be top-secret.
Captain, where are you right now?!
Once I go back, I may not be able
to return to the Macross.
That's why I wanted to at least
say goodbye to you.
Captain, where are you calling from?!
Lt. Ichijo, please look after
our Zentradi defectors.
There are still a lot of people who
don't understand them.
Please help them.
I have to go now.
Captain?
Hello? Captain Hayase!
Shuttle escort squadron is now launching.
That must be her.
Captain! An enemy detachment has
suddenly moved into action!
It looks like they've detected the shuttle!
Have the shuttle change course!
Evade the enemy forces!
Yes, sir!
Enemy attack! We are changing course!
Enemy fighters are approaching
from 1 o'clock!
Units 4, 5, and 6, break off
and delay the enemy!
Roger!
Sir! An enemy formation has altered course!
It worked. All right, men... Attack!
Enemy pods have appeared at 2 o'clock high.
They're closing on the shuttle, fast!
Units 5 and 6, head to point Lambda 0-3-4
and rejoin the main shuttle group!
Those first ones were decoys!
Reinforcements for the escort
squadron are en route!
The shuttle is surrounded!
Approximately sixty enemy pods!
How long until those reinforcements get there?
At maximum thrust, twenty minutes, sir.
Shammy! Deploy the Booby Duck!
Booby...?
The mechanics will know what it means.
Now hurry!
And have Lieutenant Ichijo pilot it!
Yes, sir!
Come on, step on it! At this rate,
I'm not gonna make it!
Yes, sir!
First Lieutenant Ichijo, your target
is point Lambda 0-3-2!
I've never heard of that location!
Where the hell is it?!
Didn't you tell him the new codes?
Well, I never thought he'd have to
sortie on his day off, so...
I'm sorry.
Lieutenant Ichijo, I'll use
the old code system.
Please head to point A3-102 immediately!
Roger!
Finally, that's thirty down, huh?
There they are!
Go!
Incoming message from escort squadron:
"The enemy pods have been destroyed.
We're returning to base."
"Lt. Ichijo is staying behind
to escort the shuttle."
I'm beat!
I've just about had enough of standing in
for Captain Hayase!
Well, you certainly appear to have recovered
from your little code mistake.
It was a good lesson for Shammy to learn.
Why don't we give her a break this time?
The Captain has spoken.
Right...
You have an incoming transmission
from First Lieutenant Ichijo.
It looks like you got hit pretty hard.
Are you okay?
Thank you, Ichijo. You saved us.
You said before that you might not
come back to the Macross.
I'm a living witness, someone who knows
the truth about the Zentradi.
High Command may not let me
go so quickly.
Even though your father's an
admiral in the UN Forces?
I don't want any special treatment just
because of who my father is.
The atmosphere...
Thanks for the escort.
I should be thanking you instead.
This whole time, you've helped us all so much.
I know all I've done is complain about you,
but you're a great controller.
We're about to begin reentry.
See you.
He's signaling.
"I hope... you complete... your mission..."
"and can... safely... return... to the... Macross."
"Hikaru... Ichijo"
Admiral, are you ready to greet the shuttle?
I'll be awaiting you at Elevator 4.
Thank you.
Admiral! The shuttle is twenty
minutes behind schedule.
Would you care to return to the control tower?
It's all right. I'll wait here.
Talk about gloomy.
You'd think he was at a wake.
First Lieutenant Ichijo, it's too soon
to start getting depressed.
I'm sure Captain Hayase will make it back.
I'm not thinking about the captain.
And I'm not depressed either!
Anyway, at times like this, it's best
to go someplace fun.
Come on, let's go!
This place is fun?
At least with you, I'll have a
decent opponent. Come on.
No, thanks. I don't think I could beat you today.
So we'll find you a one-player game. Okay?
Misa...
UN Forces Captain Misa Hayase.
By order of Captain Bruno J. Global,
I stand ready with my report, sir!
Well done.
"Mr. Thief! Mr. Thief! Mr. Thief! Mr. Thief!"
Wow!
All right! Gotcha!
Lots of fun! Right, Leader?
I guess.
There we go.
Boss, machines 16 and 7 are
about to get cleaned out!
I never shoulda opened an arcade
on the Macross!
So we and the Zentradi have almost
identical genetic makeup.
If this report is true, we may have to change
our attitude toward the enemy.
Then you'll persuade the military to
enter into peaceful negotiations?
I'll try.
With a little practice, I'm sure you'll
be able to do better, sir.
Just my type!
Could I try a game against you?
It looks like you've just about cleaned out
your machine too.
If you bet all that.
Done!
Can we start at Level B?
Very well.
He's good!
Wow! Level A!
Looks like a good match is going down!
Boss, I'm gonna put machine 7's game up.
Ah, whatever!
Got you!
This is...!
Damn you! You...!
"But let me tell you something:"
"the Macross has an ace pilot of its own!"
Could this man be the one?
Beautiful...
Bust of about 85 cm. She's the type
to keep 'em wrapped up, though.
I lost.
This "game" has been my way of life, but I lost!
Wow, leave it to the genius pilot!
That was an excellent win!
No, not at all. She had me
sweating for a while there.
Umm, Miss? Could I get your name
and phone number?
My name is Milia. I have no phone.
Would you meet me in Happiness Forest
Park tomorrow night at 9:00?
Accepted.
Way to go, Lieutenant!
That's a real beauty you got a date with!
Admiral, what did they say?
They've begun considering how to
open peace negotiations.
Thank goodness.
Father, what's wrong?
You've been staring at me for a while now.
I was just thinking how much you
look like your late mother.
So, is there a man in your life yet?
I see.
Anyway, what is it you wanted to show me?
Look at it, Misa.
Once we've used the Grand Cannon,
our negotiations will proceed smoothly.
This can instantly destroy a fleet
of tens of thousands of ships.
When the Zentradi see its power, they'll have
no choice but to begin negotiations.
Father, using this is pointless!
Compared to a Zentradi carrier, the
Grand Cannon isn't even a child's toy!
This weapon will only make the war worse!
It won't serve any purpose!
I'm sure the Zentradi will negotiate
without us having to use this.
So now a born soldier like you is going
to start talking so idealistically?
Do you think the ones who attacked your
shuttle are interested in your "peace"?
Their blood and genes may be the same
as ours, but they're still aliens.
Reaching an understanding
with them won't be easy.
Father!
Misa, how many thousands of years did
humans fight among themselves
before the formation of the
Earth UN Government?
The day has been set for the
firing of the Grand Cannon.
Negotiations will start after that.
So, is it true you haven't left his side
for over a week, Miss Minmay?
Uh, yes...
There are rumors the two of you
are going to get married.
We haven't even considered that!
Miss Minmay, what about your old boyfriend?
Old boyfriend...?
You're good at feigning ignorance!
Would you know who I mean if I mention
a certain First Lieutenant?
You mean Hikaru?!
He's just a good friend!
A friend...
Anyway, you and Kaifun have been rather close.
It's strange that you've never
considered marriage.
Loli, sir, what is this "marriage"?
Well, marriage...
It's incredible! They do things even
more amazing than kissing!
More amazing than kissing!?
Like what?!
Kaifun, you really haven't proposed to her?
Correct.
I don't buy it. Quit hiding the truth and fess up!
We aren't getting married, however...
However?
Personally, I would not be adverse to the idea.
What?
Oh, stop! You're always joking!
I thought something was up!
What a scoop!
Look over here! Over here!
A picture, please!
Look this way!
Come in.
Sir, I need your opinion.
Does this tie look good on me?
I was thinking of wearing it
on my date tomorrow!
"You mean Hikaru?!"
"He's just a good friend!"
So, what are you doing brooding
in a place like this?
Claudia...
You saw Minmay on TV?
Yeah, pretty much.
Still, I envy you.
Huh?
You've already got someone who's a
better match for you than that girl.
I don't have anyone like that!
Oh, really?
Couldn't it be that you just haven't noticed yet?
Lots of times, people don't see
what's too close to them.
They can get into selfish fights with each other,
but deep in their hearts it's a different story.
That's how it was with Roy and me.
You don't find someone like that very often.
That's all I wanted to say to you.
And if you spend all your time here,
you'll catch a cold.
Next Episode
Preview
Max and Milia move closer
to their third battle.
Milia appears before Max at the appointed
place and pulls out a dagger.
And reflected in her eyes,
there is burning hatred for an enemy
that has already defeated her twice.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"VIRGIN ROAD"
VIRGIN ROAD
I won't follow it anymore
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running to the end
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away