Piercing through the Macro sky,
A thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind
The Light struck.
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
And fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
As the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
That blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
A series of television signals originating
from within the Macross
piqued Britai's curiosity, and he sent
a recon vessel to investigate.
The three soldiers aboard the
recon ship were astonished
by the television broadcast of
the Miss Macross Contest.
Though their ship was destroyed by Hikaru Ichijo,
the soldiers now carry word of their shocking
discovery back to Britai.
BLIND GAME
So... there, uh, wasn't much cloth...
It was so thin and wispy...
How can I put this?
It kind of makes you feel hot, like
something shooting through your heart.
I think it may be a new enemy weapon.
No, it's nothing as simple as a new weapon.
Well, what is it then?
It's...
Enough! I have no idea what
they're talking about.
It's most unfortunate that the
recorder was destroyed.
Should we send out another recon unit?
As Archivist, I believe it may be more
effective to collect samples.
Captives?
Yes, sir.
That's not it at all!
What the...?!
There's no way that was a new weapon!
That's the only thing it could have been!
Liar!
What?!
Stop that, you fools!
But Conda was...
That bastard Warera started it all!
It had to have been a new, secret weapon!
Stop spouting garbage!
Look who's talking.
What?!
Stop this! Your work here is finished, so get out!
Yes, sir.
If we don't address this, and quickly,
it could affect the ship's morale.
Do you have something in mind?
It may entail treating our enemy a little roughly.
Roughly, eh? This sounds interesting.
Exsedol, I'll hear more of this idea
of yours in my quarters.
Captain Global, having given up on trying
to elude the pursuing Zentradi fleet,
decides to lift radio silence.
With their transmissions no longer
being jammed by the enemy,
the crew of the Macross successfully
contacts UN Forces High Command.
I've received a signal from
UN Forces High Command!
From High Command?
Hayase, put it on the speaker.
Yes, sir.
High Command, you are connected
to the Macross. Go ahead.
Global, we must assume the enemy
is listening in, so unfortunately,
I can't reveal how we're planning to assist you.
All I can say is we're scrambling
to get to combat readiness.
Fortunately... Well, not so fortunately for you,
the enemy fleet is only pursuing
the Macross for some reason.
Based on how long you've been able
to elude them, we've determined
that their combat abilities are not as
superior as you've suggested.
That's why you are ordered to wear them
down as much as you can.
That is all.
What?! It's like they don't understand a damn...
I'm sorry, Captain.
Don't worry about it. You're right.
So they want us to buy them some time...
Captain, why do you suppose the enemy
didn't jam our signal this time?
I mean, why now, after they've
been doing it all this time...?
They probably want to get a little
information about us.
Information about us?
Dammit!
That's one down!
Kakizaki, Max, we're teaming up
with Skull Squadron.
Kakizaki! You got hit?
Nah, it's nothing.
Gunsight One, this is Vermillion Leader.
We're heading back to base.
This is Gunsight One.
Vermillion Team, you aren't
scheduled to return yet.
One of our planes has sustained damage.
Damage? Is it so bad that you can't
complete the mission?
If possible, I'd like you to stick to the rotation.
Look, Leader, it really isn't a big...
Quiet!
Juggling the rotation is part of your job, right?
Permit us to return to base.
Oh, so you're disobeying orders?
Lieutenant Hayase, didn't you learn
anything in the academy?
There's no atmosphere out here.
The slightest amount of damage means
the chances of us dying skyrocket!
You're always someplace safe and warm,
so you have no idea how rough
it is out here, do you?
You're lecturing me now?
When did you get promoted?
Let it go, Lt. Hayase. This time,
Lt. Ichijo's decision is correct.
Vermillion Team, I'm ordering you back to base.
And Ichijo? You went too far!
Roger.
A shot across their bow?
Interesting... Let's do it.
I bet it was that Exsedol's idea.
Who knows what that walking
skeleton is thinking?
Isn't there a...
We have an old-timer on board who's just about to retire?
Yes, sir, Baklorela.
You know, Oigur, when old-timers
try to shoot something,
a lot of times their aim isn't so good, right?
I mean, if he tried to fire a warning shot,
it could end up scoring
a direct hit on the enemy ship.
But if he really hit them dead on, it could
do more than just intimidate them...
A shot like that is the
best kind of threat.
Race ya!
Is that the necktie I gave you?
It sure is. Thanks for the great present!
I'm so happy!
She's late.
Who are you waiting for?
"Who"?
A-ha! Are you on a date?
Yeah, something like that.
Get stood up?
No! I just got here!
Hey, is she pretty?
I guess so, yeah.
Is she prettier than we are?
A...About the same, I guess.
So she's really pretty then!
Jeez!
What? That includes you, too!
Mr. Hikaru Ichijo! Mr. Hikaru Ichijo!
Is there a Mr. Hikaru Ichijo here?
Are you Mr. Hikaru Ichijo?
Hey! Over here!
Yeah...
Hello, Ichijo speaking.
Hikaru, I'm so sorry!
Minmay! What's going on?
We were supposed to meet at 1:00!
Hey, haven't I seen her somewhere before?
It's her! The girl who won the
Miss Macross Contest!
My singing lesson is running late,
so I don't think I can make it.
Singing lesson? Man...
You have one today, too?
Shammy!
You sure have been busy since you
became Miss Macross, huh?
Because they suddenly decided
they wanted to make a record!
Kent the composer wrote
a song for me!
I guess you're finally going to be
a professional singer, huh?
Minmay! Let's get started!
Okay! Well, see you later! Bye!
Kamujin's squadron has assembled
at the designated position.
Firing will commence in twenty sperig.
Countdown start!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Commence firing!
Asteroid Pamir has been destroyed!
It seems to be an enemy military operation!
Set the ship to Condition B!
Yes, sir! Setting ship to Condition B!
Asteroid fragments are inbound
at 2 o'clock, 40 degrees!
A powerful energy signature is
inbound on the same bearing!
Focus the Pinpoint Barrier to starboard!
It's an enemy barrage!
Set output to maximum!
Close the emergency shutters!
Armored shutters are now closed!
A second volley is coming in fast!
Oigur! The old timer!
Baklorela, stand by to fire the main cannon!
Baklorela is targeting along the central axis!
What?!
Captain! An enemy ship seems to be
deliberately changing its aim.
They're bluffing. It's just a feint.
Fire!
Baklorela has opened fire!
It's headed right at us!
What?!
It's going to hit us!
The Barrier can't take any more!
Is it over?
Captain! The asteroid fragments!
Captain, I have a report from the
observation team.
They say it will take five hours for the fragments
to move away from the Macross.
Hmm... Vanessa, switch over
to wide-area radar.
Yes, sir!
Captain! The wide-area radar is off-line!
What?
It must have been damaged
during the attack.
What does the radar control room report?
I can't raise them, sir.
The lines seem to be down.
It seems they were able to weather the attack.
It was rather close, wouldn't you say?
That fool Kamujin took it upon himself to...
It's all right. This will make our
next move that much easier.
True enough, I suppose.
Now that they're without radar, will they
stumble their way toward us?
Captain, I have a report from
the engineering team.
They say it will take ten hours to
repair the wide-area radar.
Also, the radar control room personnel
have all been killed.
Commencing launch!
Noshiran team, ETA to point three is seven mil!
Halmesta Team, ETA to point four is ten mil!
All teams will be in position in twelve mil!
How is that decoding coming along?
It's finished, sir!
We can transmit at any time.
Broadcast once all Reguld teams are in position.
Understood, sir.
What is the Captain thinking?
We could use the short-range radar
if we just changed our location.
Maybe it's because we don't know
where the enemy is hiding,
so we shouldn't go moving around blindly.
But what if they attack again?
If we fight here, their radar will
also be useless, so we'll be on even terms.
Oh, I hadn't thought of that.
I guess our captain has actually picked up
a few tricks over the years!
What is it?
"It's fine for you! You just sit someplace
safe and order other people around!"
"We're out here in a vacuum!"
"The chances of us dying are much
higher than in an atmosphere!"
Misa? Misa!
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine. I'm just a little down, that's all.
It's just like he said.
Um... Do we have a code like this?
Hey, Kim, I'm getting a really strange
transmission from someplace.
So patch it through to the Captain.
It's just going to be High Command
calling to tell him something.
But the signal doesn't look
like it came from Earth.
What's going on?
I'm getting a signal from someplace
that isn't High Command.
Put it on the speaker.
Yes, sir!
...name of the Zentradi, we order
you to surrender your vessel.
The recent attack was merely a show of force.
If... do not wish to be destroyed,
you will surrender immediately.
It's from the enemy fleet?
...receive this demand for surrender...
Enough. Turn it off.
We repeat...
Still, I'm impressed.
We lifted radio silence
for just a few hours,
yet they've already deciphered our language.
Captain, how shall we respond?
Ignore them. There's no need for
us to bother answering.
What do you plan to do, sir?
The enemy has clearly hatched some new plan.
It's dangerous, but I'm thinking
of sending out a Cat's Eye.
Captain!
Still, I can't believe we were
assigned to fly escort for you, Lieutenant.
Indeed. Maybe it's fate.
They're heading for the flagship!
They fell for it.
Make for their predicted destination.
Damn! It's a sneak attack!
Kakizaki, do not pursue!
But, Leader!
Our orders are to fly escort!
Yes, sir...
Leader! Four enemy pods at 9 o'clock!
Okay. Kakizaki, you stay here
and guard the lieutenant.
Max and I will take on the pods.
Don't do that to me, Leader!
We'll be fine here.
Go take care of those pods.
And have you fly without an escort?
Are you crazy?
We can take care of ourselves.
Stop wasting time and get going!
Listen, that's an order!
Yes, ma'am! Max and Kakizaki, let's go!
Captain, the Cat's Eye has begun scanning.
What's the enemy's status?
It's hard to tell with all the rock fragments.
We're going to have to move a bit further
out, if we want good readings.
Change course to 10 o'clock.
Roger.
Leader! They've launched a recon unit!
And they aren't putting their
usual effort into this.
Max! Kakizaki! We're heading
back to the Cat's Eye!
It looks like we're finally clear of them.
It's too big to be a rock fragment.
Lieutenant Hayase! The enemy is behind us!
Be careful!
The enemy recon unit seems
to have had an accident.
Retrieve any survivors!
You must not kill them!
Cat's Eye, respond. This is Vermillion Leader.
Cat's Eye, come in! Lt. Hayase!
Lt. Hayase, please respond!
The retrieval team has found a survivor.
They are now landing in the lower hangar.
Lt. Ichijo, forget about me.
You won't make it in time.
Max! Kakizaki! We're going in!
Let's hurry up, Leader!
I don't have much reserve ammunition!
I don't have any at all!
I can't believe you're all
blatantly disobeying orders!
This is hardly the time to talk about that!
Watch your head!
Enemy troops have infiltrated the lower hangar!
They've probably come to rescue the captive!
Lord Britai!
Sir, I'm out of ammo.
Same here!
All right, it's time to get out of here!
Lieutenant Hayase, get away quick!
This guy's so strong!
Kakizaki, fire a missile at the bulkhead!
Wh... What for?
Just do it! Now!
What do we do now, Leader?
Cut through the airlock with your lasers!
Hurry, before more enemy soldiers come!
That's good thinking.
You can thank me later. Now would you
mind please putting me down?
Oh! Sorry about that!
Looks like our Leader is helpless when
he's around the Lieutenant.
Absolutely!
Sir, I'm about to overheat.
Okay, switch places with Kakizaki.
I hope we're able to make it out of here.
Next Episode
Preview
Hikaru, Misa, Max, and Kakizaki have
been captured by the enemy,
and are taken out of our solar system
into the depths of space.
There, they learn the shocking true
nature of the Zentradi Army.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"FIRST CONTACT"
FIRST CONTACT
I won't follow it anymore,
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end...
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away