Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
as the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
that blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
PINEAPPLE SALAD
Talk about pathetic.
Jeez...
Huh?
Nothing.
The doctor said your wounds aren't serious.
But given their location,
he wants to keep you in the hospital until
we get more detailed results back.
In the hospital?
With head wounds,
it's not uncommon for people to feel fine
at first but suddenly drop dead.
Stop trying to scare me.
It's just for four or five days.
Well, I'll see you in four hours.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
It's my fault that you were hurt.
Do I have something on my face?
It's just... You've never said,
"I'm sorry" to me before, Captain.
Anyway, it's clear that my orders are
to blame for what happened.
Stop saying that.
If I were a better pilot, then I wouldn't get
hurt no matter what orders you gave.
It's not your fault, Captain.
I feel like I've lost my confidence.
What's the matter?
This isn't like you at all.
I can't leave the bridge unattended,
so I'll be going now.
Get well soon, okay?
Thanks.
So you do know the word "thanks."
Stop moping around.
The boy's injuries weren't serious, right?
The same thing happened to
me once, you know.
The first time I met Focker, my heart
kind of went "twang..."
Even at work, my head was full of him.
And no matter what I did,
I just couldn't focus.
I had it pretty bad.
You?
Don't make it sound like I'm
a robot or something!
That's not what I meant.
Enough about that.
How'd it go?
Did you tell the boy how you feel?
Boy?
Don't worry that he's younger than you.
Just come out and say it!
Um... It's not like that at all.
Sure, whatever.
Just stop moping, got it?
Oh, Captain!
With as many people as we have on board,
supplies can be a problem.
How long will we be staying here, sir?
Until we've finished taking on supplies.
Understood.
Oh, and I gave Captain Hayase
a stern lecture
about not letting her personal feelings
interfere with her work.
Considering what I saw when I came in,
it might have been a little too stern.
Zero-g love, zero-g love!
Minmay...
With him after school, on my way home
She's a big star.
And she's getting farther and
farther away...
How depressing.
No matter what I try, she...
At the corner of that same old intersection
Hey, Hikaru!
Sempai!
He made sure no one else was around
Why so glum?
Here's a get-well present.
Nice! You've even got Minmay
singing to you in here!
Then without warning, he...
Leader?
You came to pay me a visit, right?
Yeah, but... C'mon, don't look at me
all scary like that!
I'm just glad you weren't hurt too badly.
Now take your mind off of things
and just get some rest.
That's the last thing I feel like doing.
You've gotta get it together, Leader.
I mean, getting hurt in an attack
like that is just...
I'm sorry, sir.
It's all over for me when my
own men talk to me like that.
Hang in there, Leader!
After all, we're gunnin' to
become leaders ourselves!
What is it with you?!
You'll be in here forever if
these two stay.
We'll be leaving now.
I've seen you're alive, so I guess I can relax now.
Those are some lovely flowers.
Ah! Minmay must have been here.
Like she'd ever show up.
She's a big star now.
She doesn't have the time.
Yeah, you have a point!
Hurry up.
Excuse us!
Then they must be from Capt. Hayase, right?
Excuse me.
He seemed worse off mentally than physically.
It might be serious.
There's only one specific medicine
that'll cheer him up at this point.
Specific medicine?
So, is this business or pleasure?
If I had to say, it's a bit of both.
Whatever.
I checked out Minmay's schedule, and today
she's on the set filming her first movie.
The set, huh?
Okay, then!
Sorry to ask you to run errands
for me like this.
Don't mention it.
Now then, can I tell you what
I want in return?
Go ahead.
I've just learned how to make
a pineapple salad.
Well?
Would you like to try it?
Of course.
I'll drop by once I'm off duty.
All right, then.
You're going already?
I'm after a busy lady.
If she goes someplace else,
I won't be able to find her.
Thanks again!
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
My boyfriend is a pilot
Get your brand-new Minmay dolls right here!
Buy one now before they're sold out!
Shining, making a rapid descent
then BOOM! he makes a sudden climb
Leaving a long trail of vapor
What an amazing device!
Oh, wow... I've got to have one.
He traces two big hearts
A Minmay doll... I want one!
No! Don't push!
Don't push!
Dammit!
My stock's all over the place!
That disco's nice, but it's always
the same guys there.
And they're all posers, anyway.
The guys there are all idiots.
No way!
Huh?
We got away!
That worked great!
The old man didn't even notice.
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
And now for the spoils of war!
My boyfriend is a pilot
That's a Minmay doll you're hiding, isn't it?
Shining, making a rapid descent
Um... Uh...
then BOOM! he makes a sudden climb
Damn!
They saw right through us!
You're bad people! You took that
from some child, didn't you?
No, not at all!
This is mine.
No way!
You're into high school girls?!
High school girls?
Don't play dumb!
I'm gonna poke you!
I haven't seen you guys around here before.
No, we've been around.
We, uh, well, we work over there.
Really?
At the disco?
No way!
That's the disco we always go to!
What's a "disco"?
Talk about convenient!
Let's go together!
We were on our way there
ourselves. Let's go!
Perfect, it's three on three.
Come on, hurry!
Fever! Fever!
Wait!
Speaking to women without permission
is a court-martial offense!
This is for our mission.
It can't be helped.
Okay!
Damn it! What gives you the
right to lecture me?!
I'm just saying you should feel
ashamed to be a warrior.
Don't get cocky! You came strolling up to the
front line after we had already done all the work!
Have you forgotten? The only reason
you can mouth off now
is because we were there to
haul you out of the ocean.
Silence!
You seem to enjoy bragging about how
you've never been defeated,
but let me tell you something:
the Macross has an ace pilot of its own!
An ace pilot on the Macross?
Interesting.
I'll take him on.
Hey there!
Major Focker!
We're making a kung fu movie!
I'm the star!
You look so cute!
You came to cheer me on, right?
Where's Hikaru?
Actually, I came here about Hikaru,
and to ask a favor.
Is Hikaru all right?
He was injured in combat.
He's in the hospital right now.
I was wondering if you could
stop by and see him.
Is he badly hurt?
It's not serious, but he's really
down in the dumps.
I figured seeing your face
might cheer him up.
Oh, so that's why you...
I know you're busy, but if you could
just pop in for a second.
Sure! I don't know how long
I can stay, though.
I'll go talk to my manager!
Thanks very much.
I'm glad I came.
They bring it on themselves.
Soldiers fight because they like it, so when
they get hurt, they brought it on themselves.
Say wh...
Miss Minmay!
We're starting the test for scene 12!
Coming!
See you later!
Bye!
I hope this'll cheer him up a little.
Major!
Major Focker!
Focker here.
A single enemy ship is closing in at high speed.
Captain Global has ordered a scramble.
Please return immediately.
Roger!
Oh, hey, don't tell Hikaru about this.
Knowing him, he might push his luck
and try to launch too.
Understood.
And tell Kakizaki and Max to
stick with my team.
Roger.
Captain, are you sure we
shouldn't lift off?
We haven't finished loading the supplies yet.
We'll just see how things go
for the time being.
But don't let them get near the Macross!
Yes, sir.
Understood? Once the enemy I indicate
has appeared,
you are not to engage him under
any circumstances.
Just make sure that he and l
can face off, one-on-one.
Understood.
Leave it to us.
Vermilion Two and Three, launch!
Roger!
Windsor Squadron, get ready to launch next!
Roger.
You're getting back to normal.
Just relax.
Your engines are up and running.
Thanks!
This is Skull Leader, ready to launch!
Major, try to keep the enemy
away from the Macross.
Roger that! I'm looking forward
to some pineapple salad!
Captain? What is "pineapple salad" code for?
Pineapple salad?
Major!
Where did you run off to?
Here and there...
Anyway, listen up! Your boss isn't here,
so you'd better stay sharp!
Yes, sir.
Understood.
Not to worry!
Here they come!
ATTACK!
Go!
All right, which one of these
is their ace pilot?
Him?
All right...
Impossible!
He dodged my attack.
The enemy's acting strangely.
That's just what I was thinking.
Don't you think they should be sending
craft toward the Macross?
I don't want them to,
but you're exactly right.
It's as if they're only targeting
Vermilion Three.
Tell Lt. Max to clear out.
Clear out?
If their command ship moves to pursue
then you may well be right.
The enemy's after Max?
Why?!
We don't know. But based on our observations,
that's what we think.
Okay!
We'll find out soon enough.
Max!
Retreat!
Retreat?
It looks like the enemy's after you.
Roger.
You were right.
Minmay!
You're looking better than I'd imagined.
Lying around in bed.
I'm jealous!
This isn't a bad room at all.
Oh, yeah. Sorry, but I slipped out in-between
setups so I couldn't buy you anything.
Oh, don't worry about that.
Anyway, how'd you know I was in the hospital?
The Major told me.
Sempai did?
He's a thoughtful man.
Can I sit down for a minute?
This feels great.
Haven't you been sleeping?
About two hours a day.
That's it?
It wouldn't be so hard if it
were just the movie,
but there are press interviews, and
I'm called out to all sorts of parties.
I feel like there isn't enough
of me to go around.
Say, is Kaifun in your kung fu movie too?
That's right.
Kaifun's an expert at Chinese
martial arts, right?
That's why the director took a liking to him...
Oh.
Move it, move it!
Damn!
Oh, no!
It's headed right for us!
Seal all entrances into the Macross!
Damn!
An enemy unit has entered the ship!
Anyone outside, please take shelter
in the nearest building!
Max?!
I'm losing?
Impossible!
"But let me tell you something:
the Macross has an ace pilot of its own!"
Open all ship's hatches!
Chase him out of there!
Vermilion Three! The enemy has
lost interest in fighting.
Halt pursuit!
Roger.
Someday I will redeem myself of
this disgrace. Count on it.
Okay!
They've had enough!
Major, you're nosing down.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
What about Max?
He almost took out their command unit.
Really...
Returning to base.
Roger.
Ah!
Here she is!
Minmay!
Wake up!
Manager?
Don't "Manager" me!
You didn't come back on time, and now
the whole shoot's off schedule!
Huh?
Did you see a man in here?
A man?
What are you saying?!
What if some weird rumors got started
about you sleeping in here?
Come on!
Hurry!
That hurts!
Fine, I'm coming!
He got shot up bad this time!
Same here.
This thing is really messed up.
Hey...
Hikaru sure is lucky.
He's got a real ace on his team.
Did you say something?
It's nothing.
The pineapple salad will be ready in a minute.
Why don't you have a drink while you're waiting?
I already have one.
All done!
Sorry for the...
Huh?
You drunk already?
Roy!
He's dead.
Major Focker is...
Dead...?
Just now...
In this same hospital.
He's dead?
Sempai...
Next Episode
Preview
Captain Global is contacted by a government
willing to take in the refugees,
and orders the Macross to set
a course for North America.
But when the Macross comes under attack by
Kamujin just prior to reaching its destination,
it responds by setting the Omni-Directional
Barrier to full power.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"BURST POINT"
BURST POINT
I won't follow it anymore
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away