Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
as the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
that blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
With special permission from Captain Global,
Hikaru and Minmay fly out to visit
Minmay's parents in Japan.
There, Minmay is reunited with her cousin
Kaifun, who has long been out of touch.
Meanwhile, at UN Forces High Command,
Misa and Captain Global
presented their information on
the Zentradi forces,
but their lack of evidence caused
them to be met with disbelief.
What's more, they were refused to allow the
civilians aboard the Macross to disembark.
KUNG-FU DANDY
It's not fair! How can they not
let us off the ship?!
That's just typical of those people
at High Command!
They're nothing but a bunch
of hard-headed idiots!
You're not going to agree to this, are you?
Captain!
You'll fight this, right?!
All of you, just carry out your assigned duties.
I'm trying to figure out how to
break this news to the civilians.
You can understand that, right?
Ah, Captain!
He won't even listen!
Vanessa, the captain strongly
objected to this at High Command.
Objected?
As a soldier... Right?
High Command is nothing
but a bunch of thugs!
You said it.
Hey, let's go into town and
blow off some steam!
No objections here!
Welc...
Ka...
Kaifun!
I'm home, Mother.
I'm not...
I'm not dreaming, am I?
It's not a dream, Mom.
You're home...
You're finally home!
Now you're making me cry, too!
Oh, my! Hikaru, you must be feeling
awkward seeing this.
No, it's all right.
You're looking well, Father.
Dear!
It's all right, Mom.
He's always been like that.
That damn fool kid...
Do you think we can eat this?
It sure smells good.
I could eat anything!
We haven't had any food since the
rations we brought ran out!
Anyway, how do we get it out?
There doesn't seem to be an
access port anywhere.
It can't be helped. Loli, do it!
Me?!
Fine!
Huh?
Hey!
What are you people doing?!
That's not food!
If you're trying to eat that, you
must really be starving.
All right!
Inside, all of you!
I'll give you something to eat.
C'mon!
Yeah!
Wait for me!
Huh?
What's all the excitement about?
Hey!
Over here!
Hi!
It's 1st Lt. Ichijo!
C'mon, let's go over there!
Well, this is rare, Max.
You hanging out with Captain Hayase.
I was just wandering around town and
they sort of made me join them.
1st Lt. Ichijo, what's all this about?
Minmay's cousin, I mean her uncle's son,
left home a long time ago, but now he's back.
So all his friends in the neighborhood
decided to have a get-together.
Wow!
He's cute!
Lieutenant Riber...!
Uh-oh, Kim's drooling.
Yeah, well your eyes are practically sparkling!
1st Lt. Ichijo!
What's his name?
Lynn Kaifun.
Ooh, what a cool name!
Minmay's aunt looks so happy.
Li'l Hikaru!
Are these friends of yours?
Talk about a bunch of nice-lookin' ladies!
Hey, Kaifun!
You got some more guests!
I'm glad you all could come.
How do you do?
Nice to meet you.
See, Kaifun? You may hate the military,
but it's got some real cuties in it, right?
Huh?
Did I say something wrong?
Well, I'll leave you kids to yourselves.
See ya 'round.
You dislike the military?
That's right.
I don't believe in fighting.
Fighting accomplishes nothing.
All war ever leads to is destruction.
"All war ever leads to is destruction..."?
It's not like I joined because I like fighting.
What's wrong, everyone?
We're celebrating Kaifun's homecoming!
Oh, that's right! My TV show's coming up!
Could someone turn on the TV?
Sure thing!
And at the top of the charts,
Miss Lynn Minmay!
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
My boyfriend is a pilot
Yeah!
Minmay!
Shining, making a rapid desce-
We interrupt this song to bring
you a special report.
What?
What the hell?!
What's goin' on?
According to a statement from Captain Global,
the Macross will be undergoing
quarantine procedures,
meaning that no civilians will be
allowed to leave the ship.
What did he just say?!
This is, of course, a temporary measure.
Citizens are asked to remain calm and
go about their normal business.
We finally get back to Earth and
they won't let us off the ship?!
What are they quarantining us for?!
Damn it, I want an explanation!
We now return to the song,
already in progress.
...boyfriend is a pilot
Are they kidding?!
What's going on here?
He could've come up with
a better way of telling them.
No wonder these people are angry.
You think they're just going to accept it?
Hey, that's right!
We've got some soldiers in here!
Let's have them explain what's going on!
Yeah, let's do it!
Well? You gonna explain
this to us or what?!
Look, I don't know what's going on either.
Stop it!
Is this how law-abiding citizens act?
Just calm down.
Calm down? You think we can take
something like this calmly?!
Look, it's your fault we lost our homes!
We finally get back to Earth, and...
We get back, but...!
You won't let us off the ship!
But it's just a temporary measure...
That's the same thing the military always says!
"You'll be back on Earth real soon."
"You'll be off the ship real soon."
We're sick of you people lying to us!
Yeah!
Let's hold 'em hostage and make
the military let us off the ship!
Let's go.
Hold it!
What are you doing?!
Shut up!
That's enough!
Do you know what will happen if you do this?!
I said SHUT UP!
Uh-oh.
Bastard!
You bastard!
Damn it!
I said stop!
Are you all right?!
That guy...
Kaifun...you, too?
Damn you!
Ow...
Kaifun, you were great!
That was Chinese kung-fu, huh?
Yeah, and he only used defensive
techniques too.
So that's Chinese-style kung-fu?
I've never seen it before.
You're pretty tough for a guy
who claims to hate fighting.
I don't use it to hurt people.
Ri... Mr. Kaifun, here.
Forgive me. I'd accept it if you
weren't a soldier, but...
That's right.
Kaifun hates military people!
Here!
Ow, not so hard.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What's with Minmay?
What?!
Kamujin went out in an assault craft?
Aye!
Oh, that foolish child...!
Perhaps I should punish him a little bit.
Captain, an unidentified flying object
is headed this way.
What?!
Altitude 12,000... 11,000...
On its current trajectory, it will land
12 km away at 1 o'clock.
Take us to alert condition B at once.
And recall Captain Hayase here!
Yes, sir!
Enemy vessel descending!
It looks like it will splash down
at point K-32, R-56.
The enemy, huh?
Well, fire interceptor missiles!
Yes, sir!
They're after the Macross, eh?
I swear, the Macross is a burden that
the Earth just can't handle.
Ten minutes until it reaches estimated
landing coordinates.
"All war ever leads to is destruction."
Misa?
Misa!
Misa, why are you so distracted?
You finally found a boyfriend worth
daydreaming about?
There's no one like that!
Incoming message from
UN Forces High Command.
They have launched interceptor missiles.
Not killing us...
But not letting us live either.
Captain!
Aren't we going to respond?
We're not allowed to touch
this planet, remember?!
So the planet isn't our target?
That's right.
Valkyrie teams, first wave: launch!
The enemy ship has launched flying battle pods!
We have to light a fire under their ass
somehow, and get them back into space!
A large number of battle pods are headed for us.
It's turning into a close-quarters fight.
Move the Spartan teams out onto the deck!
Yes, sir!
That stupid Minmay. What's so
good about that guy?
Spartan teams, stand by in blocks 7, 9, and 16.
Vermillion Team, provide support to block 3!
How many do we have to shoot down before
they stop coming, Capt. Hayase?
A hundred thousand?
A million?!
I thought she would bite my head
off for that one.
Vermillion Team, launching!
Vermillion Team, provide support
for block 7 at once!
Roger!
What is that?
A second enemy wave is approaching
at high speed!
Your objective is to stop Kamujin's
unauthorized attack!
Under no circumstances are you
to attack the enemy.
We're not to attack the enemy?
That's going to be a little difficult...
See? We've already disobeyed the order.
Kamujin, do you read me?
Cease your attack at once!
This is a clear violation of your orders!
A violation of my orders?!
I'm just attacking the enemy vessel.
I haven't laid a single finger on the planet.
Do you honestly think arguing over
semantics will work with me?
Return at once!
All right, fine!
I'll come back!
Assault force, retreat at once!
Roger!
We're quittin' so soon?
I have no choice!
Commander Lap'Lamiz gave us a direct order.
Oh, but don't forget to leave
them our souvenir.
Souvenir?
Ah, like I could forget that!
The enemy vessel is on a collision course!
A suicide run, eh?
Prepare a Daedalus Attack at once!
Hurry!
Yes, sir.
Attention, all stations!
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
I wasn't too close to the blast.
Didn't even touch me!
Vermillion Team, attack the approaching
enemy ships at once!
Roger!
They've got some fast ones on their side.
We'll handle things here.
You go after that other one, Leader!
All right, I'm counting on you!
There!
Co... Commence Daedalus Attack in twenty seconds.
Persistent little...
Daedalus Attack in eight seconds.
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Attack!
M...Misa!
Daedalus Attack!
Damn!
It punched through!
Launching missiles!
I'm hit!
Daedalus Attack, phase two was a success!
The enemy ship has been obliterated!
Damn it!
They blew up my assault craft!
Kamujin, it seems your present didn't reach them.
I sent down a recovery craft to pick
you up, though.
All right, retreat!
The enemy forces are retreating.
Should we pursue them, sir?
No, no pursuit.
The battle's over.
But maintain alert for the time being.
Yes, sir!
Oh, and Captain Hayase...
Report to your quarters at once.
You're taking some time off.
Yes, sir.
"Fighting accomplishes nothing."
"How many do we have to shoot down
before they stop coming?"
I don't know!
I don't know anything,
except that Kaifun is not Riber.
Preview
Next Episode
Zentradi forces ace pilot, Milia,
engaged in heated aerial combat.
Hikaru is in serious condition
after having been shot down
He is taken to the operating room,
and in a half-conscious state,
he is tormented by nightmares.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"PHANTASM"
PHANTASM
I won't follow it anymore,
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away