Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
will set out on their journey,
as the war rages on
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness, they fly toward
that blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
It is the year 2009.
The alien spacecraft that fell
to Earth 10 years before
has been reborn as the
gigantic battleship "Macross."
However, on the day that the Macross
was scheduled to be launched,
its automatic defense system of alien
origin suddenly activated itself,
firing the main cannon and destroying
an unidentified warship.
Humanity was plunged into
unavoidable conflict.
Meanwhile, air-racer Hikaru Ichijo,
a pilot invited to the launch ceremony
by Major Roy Focker,
was accidentally ordered to fly
a Valkyrie fighter
by 1st Lt. Misa Hayase, a Macross
defense systems operator.
However, overwhelmed by his
first taste of combat,
Hikaru was shot down by beams
fired from an enemy pod.
As the alien forces begin their ground
descent, the fighting enters a brief lull.
Twenty-four unidentified objects are
currently on a descent course.
You weren't able to detect them until now?
No, sir.
Radar is useless due to the use of reaction
weaponry during the first attack wave.
So the first wave was a decoy. Whoever
they are, they're good.
Hayase, can't you recall
Major Focker?
No, sir. He's still fighting off
the first wave and can't break away.
I see...
The 24 targets appear to have splashed
down in the sea 30 km ahead of us.
Ask the Prometheus to send out
some patrol helicopters.
They should be arriving in five minutes, sir.
That was quick thinking.
Thank you.
COUNT DOWN
What is that thing?
An alien robot?
You've gotta be kidding!
It looks like it's stopped.
Yeah...
Hey, Minmay!
Be careful, Yot-chan!
What if that thing had stepped on you?!
Goodness...
Hey!
Let's go take a look at the robot!
Go?
Go where?
The third floor!
Your room!
Wait!
I'm coming, too!
Come right back, you hear?
Okay!
This is patrol helicopter PHP-202.
We are currently over the ocean.
Roger. Be careful.
They've opened fire!
Turn back!
Hurry!
The patrol helicopters have been shot down.
It looks like they're trying to
surround the island.
We have to stay alert!
Yes, sir.
Well, well, well.
I must say, it's always a pleasure to
be on this splendid bridge.
Sir.
So, Global, my friend...
Just when do you plan on
launching the Macross?
Launching it, sir?
The ship still hasn't been
properly outfitted.
We've put a great deal of money into
repairing this spaceship.
We'd hate to see it destroyed
sitting on the ground.
I understand, sir, but...
That's your response for everything,
isn't it Global?!
Say, Kim, are we going into space?
ARMD-II is still combat-ready; launch
and dock with it immediately!
It sure looks that way.
Why have you just been sitting
here this whole time?!
Oh, no!
What do you mean, "Oh, no"?
Up until yesterday, you were so excited
about going up into space!
What can the Macross accomplish by
staying here and not launching?
Yeah... I was, but...
But we have reports that
the enemy forces have warships even
bigger than the Macross, and...
It's not about size, is it?!
It's about having the ambition
to get the job done!
But, sir...
Or are you telling me, Global,
that the Macross will be defeated
without even putting up a fight?
N...No, sir.
Then launch, why don't you?
Yes, sir.
Very good.
You just leave the negotiations with
these aliens to us politicians.
You all do your best, too, all right?
In other words, we're just buying time...
It's huge!
Yot-chan!
It's moving!
Hey, it's moving!
Its head split open!
Yeah...
No one's inside?
Strange, huh?
It's moving again!
What the heck is going on here?
Um, excuse me!
What does this look like to you?
What does it look like?
Well, obviously, it's a big...
Yeah, obviously.
That's what I thought.
I don't believe it!
The plane turned into a damn robot!
The plane turned into a robot?!
How is that possible?
That's what I wanna know!
Jeez...
What?
But you're the pilot, aren't you?
Just because I'm a pilot doesn't
mean I'm a soldier, you know!
What?!
Then why are you...
How can I put this?
He's a thief!
Yot-chan!
You little...!
Anyway, it's gotten pretty banged up...
But wasn't it expensive?
Er...very.
Hey, buddy!
How about gettin' off the road?
I'm tryin' to evacuate to the shelter!
Yes, sir!
I'll get right to it!
Well,then...bye!
Take care, okay?
Sure.
I sure hope I can get this thing to work...
All right, here we go!
Look out!
Help!
Yot-chan, are you okay?
Yeah.
Are you all right, miss?!
I think so.
That's a relief!
Gravity control systems 1 through 48,
are you showing green?
No. 4, green.
Roger.
No. 16, preparations complete.
GH block 24, prepare for launch.
No. 16, are you clear?
AF 74 through 140, please complete
preparations on the double!
No.34, are you clear?
Roger.
Block 25, prepare for launch ASAP!
Incoming transmission from
UN Forces High Command.
Space carriers ARMD-I and ARMD-II
have completed fighter retrieval...
...and are now proceeding to
the rendezvous point.
Claudia, what's our reactor status?
We can launch at any time, sir.
Very well.
All hands, commence liftoff!
Initiating transfer of main reactor output
to gravity control systems.
T-minus ten seconds to liftoff.
Nine... Eight...
Seven... Six...
Five... Four...
Three... Two...
One... Zero!
Liftoff!
Good.
So far so good...
What in the world is happening?!
I don't know, sir!
Captain!
The bow!
What is it?
What are those?!
They appear to be the
gravity control systems.
The gravity control systems?!
That's impossible!
Is everyone all right?
Yes, sir.
Kim, Shammy, get me a damage report!
Roger.
What a terrible ship!
That's what we get for trying to
use salvaged parts, sir.
That's for sure.
Okay!
Stop, stop!
Stop!
Skull Leader to Gunsight One.
We've sent the enemy air forces
back where they came from.
We are heading back to the ship.
Roger that, Major.
How many did you get?
Only ten.
Adequate, I suppose.
Well, I haven't seen any action in two years!
Anyway, do you know the
location of the VT-102?
VT-102 made an emergency landing
in the city a while ago.
Really?
That's good news!
Is there something the matter
with the VT-102?
I'll explain later.
That's it, over and out!
Skull Leader to all units.
You guys head back to the Prometheus.
I've gotta make a quick stop first.
Roger.
Okay, now...
Where'd that idiot get to?
Over there, huh?
VT-102, come in.
102! Hikaru!
Do you read me?
Sempai!
You don't give up, do you?
Yeah. Sorry to disappoint you,
but I'm still alive.
Wow, that's some change!
It turned into a robot!
It sure did...
Well, Hikaru?
How was your first time getting shot down?
Not very good, obviously!
And what's with these fighter planes
turning into robots?
I can't really get into that right now.
What, is it some military secret?
Exactly.
So why don't you join up?
You're dreaming! And would you
please do something about this?!
Calm down.
I'll have you fixed up in five minutes.
All right, that should do it.
Put both feet on the pedals
and press slowly.
Okay. Like this?
Good job.
Is it fixed?
Yes.
Thank you for your help.
Minmay, let's go.
Okay!
Well, see you!
Sure thing.
Be careful!
Auntie, wait!
It looks like we're the last ones.
Right.
We'd better hurry up and evacuate.
Hey, Hikaru!
You take after me more and more
every day! You dog!
It's not like that at all!
Hey, take it easy!
Jeez...
Reguld platoons have made landfall.
Understood.
All ships, prepare for barrage.
Provide support for ground units.
Roger!
Well, I guess we should get going, too.
That's easy for you to say.
I don't know how to pilot a robot!
Oh, right. Okay, change to Gerwalk mode.
It's the lever marked "G" on your left.
This one?
The controls for this aren't that much
different from a fighter plane's.
Really?
You okay?
Oh, no!
I left something at the house, Auntie!
I'm going to go back for it!
No, Minmay.
It's too dangerous.
I'll be fine.
I'll be right back!
Be careful!
All ships have completed
preparations for barrage!
Good. Begin firing, and have the
Reguld platoons move in.
Capture the enemy battleship!
What was that?!
I'm not sure, but I think it
was an enemy attack.
It looks like the city got hit
pretty hard, huh?
I'm worried about that girl and her family.
Wanna go take a look?
Okay.
Details on the attack?
It came from orbit!
They're attacking us from above?
Captain! Multiple enemy units are
closing in. It's a ground assault!
What?!
Gunsight One to all Valkyrie units.
Assume B-mode and destroy
enemy ground units!
Brown Squadron, roger!
Cerulean Squadron, roger!
Hikaru!
Take care of the girl!
How am I supposed to do that?!
Aah, quit whining!
I'll draw off the enemy fire!
C'mon, move it!
Grab on!
Hurry!
Hey, you're that guy.
Just do it!
All right...
Get out of here!
Everything all right?
I guess I'm okay.
Not you!
The girl!
She's okay... For the
time being.
Good! I don't care if YOU die,
just be sure that she stays safe.
So that's how it is, huh?
Yup, that's how it is.
Well, see you later.
Oh no, I forgot that this plane
is a two-seater!
Are you all right?
Y...Yes.
Thank you.
Whew, that's a relief!
Huh? Oh, no!
My hair's a mess!
Which is more important,
your hair or your life?
Huh?
My hair, of course!
I knew it!
It... It can't be!
So now you know.
The Battroids were built to
fight these giants.
That's impossible!
Still, I had no idea they looked
just like humans.
Rocket engines are standing by
and ready to begin liftoff.
Civilian evacuation status?
All the island's civilians have
evacuated to the shelters.
Very well. Fire main rockets.
Take us up at once!
I wonder if it will work this time.
Don't worry.
This propulsion system was made on Earth.
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Skull Leader, provide escort for the Macross.
Roger that.
Let's go, Hikaru!
What's the matter, Hikaru?
Take off!
Are you coming or not?!
Hikaru!
Through the sudden appearance
of the giant alien,...
and the sight of it being killed
before his very eyes,
Hikaru came to know the
meaning of true terror.
Major Focker's calls went unheard
as Hikaru sat, lost in thought.
Faced with the overwhelming power
of the enemy forces,
Captain Global decides to
execute a space fold.
However, neither the enemy forces
nor Captain Global
could have known the effects that
this first fold would have.
The Macross will find itself facing an
altogether new kind of battle.
Next time on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"SPACE FOLD"
I won't follow it anymore,
the shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end,
but we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
the light that shines so far away