Piercing through the Macro sky,
A thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind
The Light struck.
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
And fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
As the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
That blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
Hikaru, Misa, Max, and Kakizaki were
captured by the Zentradi
and taken to their distant main fleet.
However, their determination to
return to the Macross
gave rise to a miracle beyond imagination.
BLUE WIND
We're so close now...
When do you think we'll be able to go home?
Why don't you ask the Zentradi
fleet surrounding us?
Now then...
Let the brass worry about this.
Our enemy won't cut you any slack just
because you're the alternate watch.
Yes, ma'am!
Meanwhile, three micloned Zentradi spies
have infiltrated the Macross.
I know we don't have that much
intel on them, but this is cruel!
There's no way we can walk
around looking like this.
I just can't relax unless I'm in uniform.
Oh, stop complaining.
So where are we going?
I don't know.
C'mon, what are we gonna do?
Let's hit the disco!
We can't go dressed like this.
Let's change in the locker room over there.
Good idea!
How exciting!
Yeah, it's been a while!
"Disco"...?
No idea. That word wasn't in
our immersion training.
I'll make a note of it.
Fever! Fever!
You see that?
It looks like you have to change uniforms
depending on where you go.
What a pain!
Warera, take note of that!
But if they changed uniforms
in there, then...
There are more uniforms!
Right!
Warera, aren't you ready yet?!
I'm having trouble getting this on!
Hurry up!
Well?
It's fine. All right, now our
mission really begins!
So it looked like this?
No, I recall seeing ship silhouettes
stretching even farther out.
I agree.
Not counting the smaller ships,
we estimate there to be between
four and five million of them.
Im... Impossible!
I don't believe it!
Wait! Let's hear more of what they have to say.
Misa, Hikaru, and the others explain that
Zentradi society is completely military,
with no concept of civilians.
Also, because Zentradi history
is one of continuous warfare,
they theorize that the Zentradi used artificial
means to turn themselves into a race of giants.
And that they can shrink themselves through
a process called "micloning."
They also describe the enemy's fear that humans
have something called "Protoculture,"
and relate in detail everything they
observed on the enemy ship.
This is just absurd.
Are you sure they weren't just brainwashed?
No, physical and mental evaluations
both came back normal.
Just what is this "Protoculture?"
It seems to refer to the ancestors of the giants.
They think that Protoculture has the power
to destroy their society.
Phew! That'll make it easy!
Gentlemen, that's enough!
If this is true, it would explain why despite their
power they have yet to attack the Earth,
and it would explain the inconsistency in the
attacks launched against the Macross.
Lt. Hayase, anything to add?
No, sir, that's all.
She sure remembered a lot, huh?
Her brain's on a whole different
level from yours.
The question now is, how do
we respond to this?
We have to get this information
to Earth, no matter what.
We'll send a coded message at once!
No.
We're going to try to break through
the enemy blockade.
It's too dangerous!
The Earth is two days away at maximum thrust.
We'll have to get back eventually,
so why not now?
But...
We can do it.
If we're the Protoculture, that is.
You all are on shipboard leave.
There's no need for you to involve
yourselves in the fight so soon.
Besides, there's a welcome-back reception
for you that's about to start.
All right! I'm gonna stuff myself
on some fine food!
Well done.
Hayase...
Sir?
Personally, I believe you. However...
I understand, Captain Global.
All right, let's get this strategy
meeting underway.
It looks like they didn't really believe us.
I can't blame them. I saw it with my own
eyes and even I don't believe it.
If only we had that video pack...
Hey, we all got promoted, so they're
at least giving us some credit.
Our Leader made 1st Lieutenant, and Max
and I made 2nd Lieutenant.
I wish I could be as cheerful as you, Kakizaki.
So many amazing machines.
And so many people!
This must be an important section of the ship.
We have nothing like this on our ship.
Something's strange though.
It just doesn't...
What do you think you're doing?! PERVERT!
What was that all about?
Look over there!
Males and females are interacting!
Impossible! But it looks like we've
already passed a lot of them already!
Their uniforms are so mixed-up
that I didn't even realize!
Is this sort of thing allowed?
Look at how close they are to one other!
It... It's hideous!
No, it may hold some significance for them.
Gangway!
Are you all right?
This is no time to be fainting!
What's that guy's problem?
Hey, we seem to be attracting attention.
Oh, no, are our uniforms not on properly?
They don't seem any different from
how the others wear them.
Still, this uniform doesn't feel quite right.
It's so breezy around the legs.
Warera, it's you!
You're wearing a female uniform!
We'd better get out of sight.
Huh?! Women go in that side!
Pervert!
This is what they call "culture"?
Isn't this where they held the
Miss Macross contest?
Your memory works fine for
things like that, doesn't it?
Oh, be quiet.
Here they are, the four heroes who
miraculously made it back alive!
Captain Misa Hayase, the most
heroic woman in space!
1st Lieutenant Hikaru Ichijo,
the young hero who flies through the heavens
on heavenly wings!
Joining them are Hayao Kakizaki and
Maximilian Jenius! Well done!
Well done, all of you!
And now, our very own Miss Macross
and latest singing sensation,
Lynn Minmay, will present them
all with bouquets.
M... Minmay?
Jeez, who is this reception for anyway?
Er... although I do like Minmay...
I don't really like these flashy
sorts of events either.
Still, this doesn't happen very often,
so where's the harm?
Congratulations on your return!
Thank you.
Looks like we both got famous, huh?
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, what the hell?!
It's a riot!
No, stay calm. I don't think so.
Oh, I think I'm gonna faint.
You call yourself a soldier?!
And now, in honor of our heroes,
I'd like to sing my debut song, "My Boyfriend is a Pilot."
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
Min...
May!
My boyfriend is a pilot
L-O-V-E! Happy Minmay!
Shining, making a rapid descent
Then BOOM! he makes a sudden climb
It's them! How did they escape?
Leaving a long trail of vapor
The power of Protoculture?
You know, my body's starting to feel hot.
Now that you mention it...
He traces two big hearts
I don't know why, but...
A love sign in the big, blue sky
"I love you, you love me?"
You!
Me!
But he's head over heels
For his plane instead of me
What's wrong?
Nothing, the lights are just a little bright.
Whoosh, whoosh! Whoosh, whoosh!
Min...
May!
My boyfriend is a pilot
L-O-V-E! Happy Minmay!
Misa! Welcome back!
Please!
I heard you're a captain now.
Congratulations, Captain Hayase!
Th...Thanks.
Well? How's it feel to be back home?
Well...
Why do you always
have to be so serious?
You'll never enjoy life that way!
Just be happy.
"Ooh, wow! Is this where I work?"
Is that how you want me to act?
Here you are.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Cheers!
This tastes great. Thank you.
Misa, don't you have special leave?
This is where I feel most comfortable.
It's her!
She's back!
You're right!
Welcome back!
Hey, Hikaru!
Sempai!
You haven't come to see me at all!
How heartless!
Heartless?
Where do you all think you're going?
Didn't you hear the announcement, sir?
We're to report to section B5.
Your orders were to remain on
the ship on standby, weren't you?!
But Captain Hayase is...
Idiot! There's a difference between
being inside and outside!
Now head back to the barracks
and get some sleep!
But this is an emergency.
Shut the hell up! Or do you wanna
go to the brig instead?!
Understood, sir! Going back, sir!
Good! Just so long as you
understand! See ya.
The Macross has begun to accelerate.
Range to target increasing.
What shall we do?
Lord Bodolzaa did not order its destruction.
So we'll follow it and observe.
We are at maximum thrust
and maintaining speed.
Any reaction from the enemy fleet?
They've begun to match our speed and
are maintaining their envelopment.
As I expected. They're following,
but not taking direct action.  It looks like your theory was correct.
I hope so, sir.
We are now passing into the Moon's orbit.
And the enemy fleet?
No change, sir.
Valkyrie and Ghost squadrons have
assembled in section B5.
The Macross is here and we're here.
At full speed, their range
is increasing.
This blockade of ours is useless!
They're going to escape.
If we sit by and do nothing, it will bring
shame to the Kamujin Clan!
Right, Oigur?!
It seems that way, sir.
Destroy the damned thing!
It's the only way I'll be satisfied!
All right, increase speed and prepare to fire!
Part of the enemy fleet has changed course
and is advancing toward us.
Approximately ten ships.
Deploy all defense forces!
Yes, sir!
Valkyrie and Ghost squadrons,
launch all units!
Begin Transformation and activate the Pinpoint Barrier!
We're breaking through!
Civilian evacuation of all blocks is complete!
Beginning Transformation in all blocks.
Everyone vanished after that
"transformation" announcement.
Mm. Very well-organized.
Perhaps civilians are
part of their military.
What...? Why is it moving?!
This may be "culture," too!
The artificial gravity!
Macross Transformation in the starboard
section is 75% complete.
Transformation in the port section
is 80% complete.
Connecting energy-conduit system.
That group from the enemy fleet
is headed straight at us!
Fire the main gun!
Yes, sir!
Don't fall back! Fire! Fire!
Secondary starboard thrusters have been hit!
E block engineering section has been hit!
Section 27 has been destroyed!
If my theory is wrong, then...
Misa, no second guessing yourself here.
Right...
What a mess. Damn that Kamujin!
What shall we do? Lord Bodolzaa has
not ordered us to destroy them.
Move the fleet in front of Kamujin
and force him back!
But that will break
up our formation.
We have no choice.
Damn you, Kamujin!
The main fleet is moving to join the
group already attacking us!
The Barrier won't hold up!
Oh, no!
Huh? What's going on?
What the hell are they doing?!
Kamujin! Lord Bodolzaa has not ordered
the destruction of the Macross!
As the direct commander of this fleet,
I will carry out the Supreme Commander's orders
until I am told otherwise.
Abort this unauthorized attack or you
will be fighting the entire fleet.
Captain Kamujin, I don't think she's bluffing.
Damn it! Why does something always
stop me from cutting loose?!
Damn that Lap'Lamiz, always flaunting her rank!
Don't assume I'll let
this insult pass!
What happened? They shielded us
from their own attack!
Worry about that later!
We're re-entering the atmosphere!
Yes, sir!
Are the Valkyries keeping up with us?
Yes, sir, and losses are minimal.
Set course for UN Forces
High Command in Alaska.
It's those damaged starboard thrusters.
We just lost the Number 7
gravity control system.
We can't maintain altitude!
All hands, prepare for impact!
Blue skies!
We're home!
That's right! We're home, aren't we?
I'm so happy!
The ship has touched down
in the Pacific Ocean!
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you
for all your cooperation.
The ocean!
It's so beautiful...
The smell of the sea!
Earth! It's Earth!
Leader, we've finally made it
back to Earth, haven't we?
Yeah, this warm sunlight...
It really is like a dream.
Valkyrie squadrons! Hey!
Hey!
The Macross had at last returned to Earth.
However, the Zentradi menace now
threatens both it and the Earth.
Next Episode
Preview
The Macross has finally made it back to Earth.
But for Captain Global, an even more
fearsome opponent lies in wait:
the Earth UN Government and
the Military High Command.
Will they accept the difficult-to-believe
truth about the Zentradi threat?
Next time, on Super Dimension
Fortress Macross:
"GLOBAL REPORT"
GLOBAL REPORT
I won't follow it anymore,
The shadow you cast as you run away
We all keep running until the end...
But we still can't see the goal
What awaits us after today?
What awaits us beyond tomorrow?
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away