Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
To awaken us, the young mankind,
the Light struck
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
and fight to protect their loved ones
Will set out on their journey
as the war rages on.
Will you love me tomorrow?
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
That blue planet that shines in the distance
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
Farewell to Tenderness
Maybe I'll quit.
You still haven't decided, have you?
Huh? No.
But why? If you quit the military, I wouldn't
care if I quit being a singer.
Don't say something like that so lightly.
But there's no reason for you to go on killing!
It's not as if I do it because I enjoy it.
I still remember
the way we were when we first met.
You weren't a soldier yet and I was just
an ordinary girl, not a singer.
When we were trapped onboard the Macross
and we thought we were going to die,
that's when you asked me...
"What do you say we have
a wedding ceremony?"
Let's go back to how things used to be!
Minmay...
Reaction core status?
Reaction core connections are nominal.
Energy levels are increasing.
We did it, Kamujin!
Yeah...
Now we can run wild again,
just like the old days!
We start with the Macross!
Once we've smashed it, we'll
head back into space!
Sir!
So this is where you've been.
I've been looking all over for you.
Commander-in-Chief Global wants to
see you on the old bridge.
The Commander-in-Chief? On the old bridge?
Have you been crying?
What? Of course not!
Claudia, thank you for everything, I...
Don't tell me you're going to resign.
You can't go doing something like that.
Or don't you care if Minmay
steals him away from you?
There's nothing I can do.
I mean, as a woman, even I have to
admit that Minmay is cute.
And how do I compare?
I'm older than Ichijo, I'm uptight...
And I'm a soldier!
This is why you're resigning?
I can't bear to stay in the military,
having to see him every day.
Oh...
Major Hayase reporting!
Yes...
Everything's just as it was
back then, isn't it?
Hmm? That it is...
I want to talk to you about
your new assignment.
New assignment? But Captain...
I'm sorry, Commander-in-Chief.
Being here brings back some old habits.
It's all right, Hayase.
Actually, I want YOU to be the captain
of a ship of your own.
You'll be captaining a ship that's
being constructed.
Me? A captain?
You'll accept, won't you?
I'm sorry, Commander, but I'm thinking
of quitting the military.
Isn't that a bit drastic?
Captain Ichijo is the cause of this, I assume?
How did you...
When a female officer suddenly wants
to quit, that's always the cause.
Take a look at this scenery, Hayase.
It's so pretty.
The Earth is truly a beautiful place.
Yes...
But we can't stay on this world forever, Hayase.
Out there in that vast galaxy the Zentradi
and the Supervision Army
are at this very moment locked in battle.
If they come to attack the Earth again,
our chances of survival are
less than one in a million.
Is that why you captured the Factory Satellite
and have been strengthening
our battle readiness?
Exactly.
But consider: If we had the military
might to resist such an armada,
the Earth would become a world
that existed only for warfare,
just like the once-great Protoculture
who in creating their giant Zentradi
soldiers destroyed themselves.
I want us to spread out to the stars, so that
Earth's culture will never disappear.
Space emigration?
Yes, as quickly as possible and to
as many planets as possible.
Captain...
At this rate, we'll be able to reach the
Macross without being detected!
Yes, sir!
"If you quit the military, I wouldn't
care if I quit being a singer."
"There's no reason for you to go on killing!"
"Let's go back to how things used to be!"
"Let's go back... to how things used to be."
Who could that be?
I'll get it.
Major!
Miss Hayase!
Hello, Ichijo.
I came here to say goodbye.
I'd planned to quit the military today
and go someplace far away.
But I changed my mind when I was picked
to take command of the first ship
in the Space Emigration Project.
Space emigration?
Yes, even if humanity is able
to live here indefinitely,
the Earth could one day very well
be destroyed by aliens.
For the sake of the children yet to be born,
to preserve our culture for others
thousands of years in the future,
I believe we need to fly out to
every planet in the galaxy.
But not to kill: to spread culture
among the stars.
Not to kill...
Right. Minmay, I love your songs.
I can't create culture the way you can
but I might be able to protect it.
Miss Hayase...
Now... Right now, I can come
right out and say this.
Ichijo, I love you.
Minmay?
Take good care of your songs.
That's all I wanted to say.
M... Major!
Hikaru!
Don't go!
Please!
Minmay...
Get down!
Major!
Hikaru!
Major! Major!
Major!
Ichijo...
Are you okay?
Yes...
What in the world?
An attack, a large-scale one!
Why didn't we spot them?
I don't know, but they're
going all out today.
I'm going back to the Macross!
Major Hayase! I'm going out too.
Please be safe.
You, too.
Hikaru!
Why?!
Minmay!
Why do you have to keep fighting?
Minmay, who is it that you sing for?
For yourself? Or...
It's not for the people who love your songs.
We fight for the same reason
that you sing your songs.
But that's...
Hurry! You need to get to a shelter!
No! If I'm going to evacuate,
you're coming too!
Don't be stupid!
I'm a soldier! I have to
protect you... and the city!
No! No! Then take me with you!
Don't leave me alone!
Minmay, I'm sorry. But you're not alone.
I have to go. You have your songs, don't you?
Hikaru...
Hikaru... Hikaru... Hikaru...
Hikaru!
What's the enemy's status?
One gunboat, closing in at high speed!
Range: 50 km at one o'clock. Altitude: 300.
Roger.
The enemy ship has entered the
main cannon's line of fire.
All right! All hands, prepare to fire!
After the main cannon has fired,
launch all aerial battle pods!
The enemy ship has entered the F Line
and is still closing in!
I'm picking up a high-level energy
signature that's building quickly!
What?
It's headed straight for us!
Ma... Macross!
Major! Respond!
Major! Major!
Major Hayase!
Damn it!
Sub-systems 1 and 2 are not responding!
How about you?
I'm not getting anything either.
All control systems are offline.
What should we do, Major?
At this rate, the Macross will...
"Just like old times, isn't it, Captain?"
We're going to the bridge!
Everyone, hurry!
What took you all so long?
Claudia!
But how?
Man your stations at once, people.
Captain!
We're launching the Macross.
So it can still fly?!
Yes, but not for very long.
Captain!
All hands, stand by for launch.
Fire the main cannon at once.
We'll take them out with one blast.
Yes, sir!
Auxiliary reaction-core output is climbing!
All personnel, brace for liftoff!
Gravity control systems are nominal.
Five seconds to launch.
Three, two, one...
Launch!
Hey! Look at that!
The Macross! The Macross is lifting off!
The Macross...
The Macross is flying!
Piercing through the Macro sky,
a thunderbolt strikes the Earth
Output in the main cannon's firing
system is still climbing.
One minute to firing.
To awaken us, the young mankind,
Attention, all pilots engaged in combat!
The Macross is preparing to
fire its main cannon.
the Light struck
Get clear of the enemy ship at once!
Macross! Macross!
The brave youths who arise
I repeat, get clear of the enemy ship at once!
Major?! You're alive!
and fight to protect their loved ones
Yes! Now firing the main cannon!
Will set out on their journey
as the war rages on.
Get clear of the enemy ship now!
Roger!
Will you love me tomorrow?
Understood.
Slicing through the darkness they fly toward
Roger!
That blue planet that shines in the distance
Fire!
Macross! Macross!
Macross!
Damn! Oigur, we'll plow straight into them!
Oigur!
Dammit! Let's do it, Lap'Lamiz.
Right! Don't die, Kamujin!
Same to you. We'll do some
culture afterwards!
Let's go!
Captain, the enemy ship's not changing
course! It's going to ram us!
Damn! Are they crazy?
All batteries, open fire!
Drive off the enemy ship!
Auxiliary reaction core has failed!
The Macross is inoperative!
Enemy distance: 300 meters!
We're unable to evade!
MISA!
Lap'Lamiz!
Kamujin!
You're all right, Minmay!
Thanks to you. Good work.
Thank you, Minmay.
I'm going to go to a city
I've never been to before.
And when I'm there, I'll try singing again.
I'll never think about giving up singing again.
That sounds good, Minmay.
Miss Hayase?
I don't know when this might be,
but when I'm finally able to sing my
true songs, when that happens...
When that happens?
Would you let me come onboard your ship?
I'd be glad to.
And we'll let your songs echo
through the galaxy.
Thank you.
Until then, take care, Hikaru.
You too, Minmay.
Well, I'd better get going.
See you again!
She's gone.
Didn't you want to try to
keep her from leaving?
No, a girl like Minmay can't get
tied down to a guy like me.
Oh...
Anyway, can't you hear that?
I took your tenderness for granted
Minmay's song...
Her song?
But I want to try to shine someday
Yes, I can hear it, Hikaru.
So for now, farewell.
I won't lose it anymore,
My own path that I'm walking.
We all keep running to the end
But we still are far from the goal.
In the days that leave behind today,
I'll be glad when comes tomorrow.
Even now, I keep running toward
The light that shines so far away