neiki yori sotto yoake ga kuru
Dawn comes softer than a sleeping breath
寝息よりそっと　夜明けが来る
kimi no yume wa ima mori wo kakeru
Your dream runs through the forest now
君の夢は今　森を駆ける
mezamete akari wo sagasu shigusa
You wake up and stir to find the light
目覚めて　灯りを探すしぐさ
nakushita nara mitsuketeageyou
If you've lost it, I'll find it for you
なくしたなら　見つけてあげよう
kimi to boku no mirai ni kakureteiru
It's hidden in our future
君と僕の　未来に隠れている
saa koko he te wo tsunaidara
Now if we joined hands
さあここへ　手をつないだら
hodokenai yo kimi to tooku he
we would go far away without letting go
ほどけないよ　君と遠くへ
haruka na hi no kioku ni saita
In the memory of a far off day
遥かな日の　記憶に咲いた
aoi kuni no miru story
the story of the blue country bloomed
青い国を　見るストーリー
kagayaku hitomi
Shining eyes
輝く瞳
sono utagoe
Your singing voice
その歌声
tsutaeyou
Let's share it
伝えよう
Wolf and Playful Days
This is nice.
You're awake?
This is too nice.
I think I'll get by without freezing like this.
You can talk.
I'm cold, after all.
I need to be heated.
Jeez.
Burnt rice!
That looks like burnt rice you see floating in stews!
You said Renose has lots of different kinds of strong liquor, right?
Yeah,
we'll probably be fine even if we get held up by a blizzard.
I hope one comes.
Hey hey.
Just so you know...
Renose is famous for its lumber and furs.
Right.
Don't get upset if you see wolves pelts among those furs.
"I get eaten by wolves,"
"but mice get eaten by me."
In our world, it's normal to hunt and be hunted.
I won't complain.
And even though you say that, humans are even more shocking.
You buy and sell each other, right?
You mean the slave trade?
It's profitable and a necessary business.
In the same way you calmly talk about trading people,
we have no feelings for those who are hunted.
Though, when I was being hunted by another man, you got pretty worked up, didn't you?
Yes I got worked up.
Really worked up.
Don't speak in monotone!
It's only natural.
Why?
Because it's embarrassing.
It really is.
Right?
They're fellow merchants.
It looks like it'll take a while to enter the town.
Is this like a temple courtyard?
Those are in front of churches.
It's odd that they're setting up right in front of the town walls.
It doesn't look like they're doing any business either.
The gates aren't closed,
so it doesn't appear to be a revolt.
You're expecting another battle here, aren't you?
I don't particularly want one.
What's with that face?
It's true that ever since you met me you've been caught up in a number of disputes.
But there hasn't been a single time where I directly caused one!
The first one...
Well, that may have been partially my fault.
But it was more because you were greedy.
The next one happened entirely because you got greedy and failed.
And the last one was because you got all worked up on your own.
Am I wrong?
Well, I do see where you're coming from,
but I have trouble accepting it.
Though it's true you weren't the cause of all the trouble.
It's natural for you to find it hard to accept.
Why's that?
You always measure me against your own standards,
so you feel you're being manipulated by me.
That's not true.
So stubborn.
Why you!
You're finally being honest with yourself?
Not good, not good.
How boring.
Stew would be nice.
Oh, dinner?
It is pretty cold.
It depends on the price,
but it'd be nice to have something with a flour and butter base rather than one with cream.
That does sound good.
There are times when the scent of milk beats wine.
The vegetables at this time of year are still especially good.
Vegetables?
Don't you know the taste of black, tender chunks of beef floating in a milky white broth?
Well, they do say that good things are poison to the eyes and tongue.
That's not very fair for me, considering I wasn't able to have a meal for several hundred years.
Well, I'll consult my purse first.
This is an identification plaque that shows you're a traveling merchant.
The townsfolk won't do business with outsiders unless they display this,
so make sure you don't lose it.
Oh what,
it's just a cheap wolf pelt.
It's not like I think it's the best thing in the whole world.
But that's a matter of the differences between species, not the quality of my tail!
That's true.
Between something that's at the lower end of a superior scale,
and something that's at the upper end of an inferior scale,
you'd definitely commend the second one!
That's true.
No,
between a steward from a noble house with no fame, fortune or personality, and an ordinary citizen with all three,
no matter which way you look at it, you'd commend the latter.
Room or luggage?
I need a room for two.
Would you prefer a warm room or a bright one?
Is there a choice besides the warm room?
Okay, I'll take the horse to the stables.
If you talk to the maste...
the old man, he'll get a room for you.
Okay.
Behave yourself now.
Third floor, by the window.
Okay, third floor...
By the window.
I think it's a splendid tail.
It's a good, warm fur.
Well then, I'll go dry your clothes.
When that's done, we'll get onto the stew!
Traveling merchant identity plaque, huh?
Strange things they've got here.
Oh crap!
S-Sorry.
What's wrong?
Aren't you eating?
I'm going to go maintain the furs.
I need to make sure they fetch a good price.
You're already too expensive.
So much that you won't find any buyers.
Has anyone bought you at this point?
Oh come on.
Good morning.
Right.
So, what are you going to do?
Gathering stories about you comes first.
Stories about me, and about Yoitsu.
Let's find a chronicler first like I did in Kumerson.
I'll leave that to you.
You know the right channels.
Something wrong?
No.
I know how to go about it.
So what do you know?
There's a saying that goes:
"The man who knows the way does the work."
"The man who knows why that man works becomes his employer."
I see.
Now I know why you work so gallantly.
They used to say that a long time ago.
So if I'm your employer, I have to reward you somehow.
Reward?
Yes.
In other words,
isn't there something you want?
Nothing in particular.
As long as you're in a good mood, I'm happy.
Are you treating me like a spoiled child?
At least children listen when you scold them.
Well, first let's go talk to the old man.
He doesn't look it, but he is the owner.
You're coming, right?
Yep.
Even if you smack away my hand.
If I clap my hands now, will the magic spell disappear?
Why, what have I been doing?
Ah yes,
this is the town of lumber and fur, Renose!
I must stock up on furs and be off to the next town!
Are you a traveling, traveling merchant?
I can judge the quality of furs.
Why, you do have good eyes.
But what about judging the quality of people?
I do not know.
I am under an evil spell.
Then we mustn't clap out hands, so as to keep it intact.
But they've already been clapped once.
Are you saying it's already disappearing?
Yes.
So could you recast it before the magic fades?
Like this?
Come now. We're going.
You...
It wasn't surprising enough to make you so clumsy, was—
Your spell was too strong,
you fool.
So when are you going to start running amok?
I wonder.
Maybe when you stop doing things like this?
You've developed quite a sharp wit.
Haven't I?
You really have become a smooth talker.
Did you get someone to teach you?
No.
It just came to me at the moment.
At the moment?
That makes me even happier.
When I stop doing things, you said?
Something the matter?
I see.
You wanted me to care that much.
You really are adorable.
A chronicler?
Yes.
Or just someone who knows the legends of the town.
There was a man called Rigolo who was a chronicler,
but unfortunately, he's currently in a fifty-man meeting.
He won't meet with anyone.
Fifty-man meeting?
Did you see the town entrance?
I saw it.
Merchant-like people were gathered there.
Does that have something to do with this fifty-man meeting?
Are you saying there's some kind of problem in town?
The furs, I guess.
Furs?
Rigolo is the scribe for the meeting.
For legends, old lady Bolter the tanner knows quite a bit.
Any others?
Others?
Ah,
the old geezer at the Latton company.
No.
In the heat of the summer year before last...
My God.
I see.
The legends of the town will only be found in books.
Then,
we'll have to have Rigolo show us the records.
That's how it goes.
The years weather even stone towers.
And even the memories of men...
It's frightening.
Hey.
Want something to eat?
You should build more vocabulary.
Excuse me.
She was surprised when she saw me.
Don't tell me, another animal?
I didn't get that feeling,
but maybe that girl was taken aback by my beauty.
Not likely.
Wait.
Girl?
Yes.
That was a woman?
What kind of mutt are you, looking around at other women when I'm right beside you?
You shouldn't say things like that.
It's much cuter if you show it with your behavior.
You're a fool, so you wouldn't know if I didn't say it.
So?
What should we do?
Will it be difficult to meet this whatsisname man?
He said his name was Rigolo.
If he's in a meeting, then talking to him will be difficult.
Well, it does depend on his role at the meeting.
That face says you want to know the subject of this meeting.
No, not at all.
In that case, you'll be wandering around until the meeting is over with absolutely no interest in what's happening?
I can't fool the eyes of the sage wolf Horo, after all.
I want to know what's happening in town so badly, I can't help myself.
And maybe—
"if possible, make a profit."
It's enough to require these wooden plaques.
Something interesting is happening.
But you know...
Don't go too far.
I know.
I wonder about that.
First, how about the sights of this town,
dear princess?
That will do.
It's an honor.
So?
What shall we do?
I don't remember whether I really came here or not.
It's changed a lot since then, I'm sure.
Let's go to the port.
The port?
It seems that ships have become quite common recently.
It's quite a sight.
Ships, you say?
Yes.
soshite koi suru bokutachi wa
The two of us who fell for each other
そして恋する僕たちは
ai no temae de surechigau
missed each other just before love
愛の手前ですれちがう
tsutaetai noni damarikomu
I want to tell you but I keep quiet
伝えたいのに黙り込む
Take me, take me
to the perfect world
sakamichi wo sora he noboreba
If you climb the hill towards the sky
坂道を空へのぼれば
wakareyuku suisei no mizuumi
there flows the comet river
わかれゆく彗星の湖
mikansei na bokutachi dakara
Because we're incomplete
未完成な僕たちだから
kizutsukezu ni irarenai
we can't avoid hurting each other
傷つけずにいられない
dakishimetekuretara
If you will embrace me
抱きしめてくれたら
fureaeru ki ga suru
I feel like we'll touch
触れ合える気がする
dakishimeaetara
If you can embrace me
抱きしめ合えたら
ai suru hito ha kitto soba ni iru
Your beloved will surely be by your side
恋する人はきっとそばにいる
taisetsu na mono wa itsumo soba ni aru
Those important to you will always be by your side
大切なものはいつもそばにある
Next episode: Wolf and Enticing Traveler
Wolf and Enticing Traveler