douka please can you keep my secret?
Please, please can you keep my secret?
kira kira to kagayaku miraa
The mirror, shining so brilliantly.
watashi wa donna fuu ni utsutteiru no
I wonder how do I look in it.
hora hora to temaneku mirai
The future, beckoning me forward.
kore kara donna koto ga okoru no
What will happen from now, I wonder?
me ni mieteiru mono ga subete dewa nai kara
Because what we see is not everything.
mugamuchuu da that's all right
I'm losing myself but that's all right.
mayowanaide I wanna try
I will now try not to waver.
jibun no kimochi ni massugu de itai
I want to be true to my heart.
dakedo hitotsu ya futatsu gurai
But even I have a secret or two.
dare ni mo baretakunai
That I want to keep to myself.
naishotte aru mono dakara
mune ga chotto itamu my secret
That's why my secret makes my heart aches slightly.
Continuing from last episode, we're still at Yumesaki High's Cultural Festival.
This place is especially crowded; let's go somewhere else.
A-Alright...
I came here because I was worried about Sakura.
We got separated, but it'll be pointless if I go back now.
Maybe someone from our school is here as well!
I guess so...
Signs: Usui , Misaki
I guess I'll kill time with Usui 'til the live performance is over.
The grilled squid was delicious!
Yeah!
What shall we try next?
The fried stuff!
OK! Let's go!
It's really crowded here.
Yeah.
How did you manage to get all those?!
Exhausted
from escaping
the crowd
For some reason, the passersby gave them to me.
They told me to try them out.
What do you mean by 'some reason'?! That's weird!
Maybe it's that?
I made their flowers bloom.
Damn, I'm getting surrounded again. Let's run!
Where is that hot guy?
Where is he?
I don't know what's happening, but...
Don't make their flowers bloom again. What kind of magic did you pull?
I don't think that's the right word...
What's the point of doing that?!
Uhh... to spark off jealousy?
Between who?!
Hey, cool down. Why not try some food here?
I'm fine. I'm not really hungry...
Here.
It's rather tasty.
How is it?
Good.
This feels strange... It's just like...
...a date, right?
It looks good on you!
Did you read into my mind again?!
You perverted alien! What's with that superhuman power?!
Just what exactly are you?!
What? Why are you laughing?!
Sorry. Ayuzawa...
You're thinking of the same things as I am, eh?
Where are you going?
A-Anywhere! I can't be sitting here idly in a festival!
You're right.
You're really sly Ayuzawa, Usui you idiot!
I tried most of the food here already.
Same here!
Let's try out the events next!
What's this 'Old Mansion' thingy?
Let's see how 'ancient' the designs are!
Let's go!
Did you win the game console that you wanted?
I won it with only a single postcard!
Wow!
There's no lucky draw club here, I guess.
It is an unusual club, after all.
Let's eat some steamed buns.
Kanou, let's get some fried stuff!
Sure.
Froggy~
It's Mr. Froggy~
Damn, I'm still feeling hot.
We've got an event just right for the both of you!
Try our "Love Trial"!
Test out the strength of your relationship!
We're not a couple-
The rule is simple:
Follow the designated course and clear the challenges along the way.
3-1
Ramen
shop
Speed-eating
Card game
3-2
Game Lounge
3-3
Table Tennis Cafe
You'll be eliminated if you fail even once!
If you manage to succeed, the prize is this:
Super Premium Ticket
A super premium ticket to the post-festival event!
Woah! Amazing!
However!
You mustn't let go of your partner's hand during the game.
Well then, will you be able to overcome the trials ahead together?
Dare to take up the challenge?
I'll do it.
Hey you-
I want to see for myself if a romance between us is really impossible.
A romance between the two of you cannot happen.
You're still thinking about that-
Let's face this obstacle together, 'kay?
Thank you for participating!
Geez, this is such a waste of money.
We can enjoy a lot of things just for 500 yen! It's a bargain, you know?
Maybe, but still...
Oh yeah, take off your ribbon.
This is the proof of participation and it has to be kept visible at all times.
I'm supposed to wear that?
Well, it looks good on you.
They say it's fine to bring it back with you.
It's not such a waste after all, is it?
It's fine to enjoy yourself once in a while.
You'll get that frown embedded on your face if you always have it on.
Shall we go?
You idiot!
I-
I know.
You hate me, right?
That's not for you to say, idiot.
Can we go back now?
Shizuko!
Next up is Kamiyama and Oono's comedic skit.
Kamiyama here!
I'm Oono.
We're the comedic duo!
It's boring!
Is that supposed to be my fault?!
When will UxMishi come out?!
Uh, 2 hours later?
I have 2 hours to lecture you then.
Shizuko...
Why are you willing to wait so long for this?
I'd rather be with Misaki and go back first.
I'm sorry.
What's with this course of events?
Why am I holding hands with Usui in this game?
Just like a date, right?
It's not! I'm supposed to be with Sakura and Shizuko!
How did it turn out like this?!
Are you ready?
Your Love Trial starts now!
What's wrong? We have to clear this within 10 minutes.
Don't hinder me, Prez.
Who will?!
Your face is pissing me off!
You aren't supposed to run on the corridors, right?
Shut up! I'm just walking quickly!
This is walking quickly.
That looks creepy!
I'm surprised we didn't meet anyone we know.
Yeah...
What is this sound I'm hearing...?
Here, this is my proof of participation.
Man, we took 3 minutes.
I'd have taken only a minute to get here.
What the hell? I'd have done it in 30 seconds!
Please explain the game to us.
Listen to me!
Finish this within 10 minutes!
It'll be simple for two people.
Only one of you will do the eating.
I'm feeling some hostility from behind...
The other couples barely cleared this stage!
Good luck, for the sake of your girl!
Let's decide using rock, paper, scissors.
What, you think that I'm unable to finish this?
Shouldn't the
guy eat instead...?
Huh? Why would I? Let's get this on.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Lost
Fine, I'll finish everything right to the last drop of soup!
Huh~?
Huh...?
Sorry, can I let go of his hand for this game?
Right hand
Right-hander
You'll be disqualified.
I'll have to eat with my left then.
This is where I come in.
I'll feed you, so just enjoy the food.
There's no need! I'll manage this alone!
Please signal the start.
Alright, ready, go!
Ramen, ramen, for your man!
The game starts now!
Here, ahh~
Hurry up, or you won't be able to finish within 10 minutes.
Grip
It's the girl who's doing the eating!
Do your best!
Want me to blow on it?
No! It's fine as it is!
It'll be just what he wants if I feel embarrassed here!
You suck, Prez. Come on, it's here~
Here, come take it~
Hey, it's getting crazy over there!
You mean Class 3-1's ramen house? That extra large servings challenge?
Yeah! A couple's duking it out at godly speed!
Hey, that couple did something amazing again!
The next game was Class 3-2's card game, right?
Toran, who was unbeatable in speed games,
lost to them at the speed of light!
They're devils! Devils, I tell you!
It got even crazier next!
3-3's doing table tennis, right?
Usually it'll be hard to win using the hand you're not used to.
What the-?!
She's not a left-hander?!
I've won, but I can't seem to control my strength...
Trying to give an excuse since you're naturally a right-hander?
No! I'm just not in top form!
They're no ordinary couple!  They're...
Don't drag me
down in the
next event, okay?
You're having
fun all
the while,
aren't you?!
...a superhuman tag team!
Quiz
Balloon
Challenge
Welcome to the balloon quiz!
First, find a balloon marked with the word "Lucky".
Then, burst it, and answer the questions on the paper that's inside it.
There! It's those two!
You have 5 minutes. Start!
We're attracting quite a lot of attention...
We stood out too much, I guess.
Maybe it's about time to tell her straight...
What did you say?
Nothing.
Let's race to see who finds the balloon first.
Interesting. I'll take you on!
See? I found it...
...already...
Why are you spacing out? There's a time limit, you know?!
Indeed.
Let's burst it.
Sakura, listen.
I'm against him from the start.
He's arrogant, and his looks are outrageous as well.
Just what do you see in him?!
I'm getting more and more annoyed waiting in this crowd!
Under extreme stress
Shizuko...
Sorry, I got loud there.
Shizuko's getting unstable...
I should've put it in a nicer way.
I'm really sorry.
I can't explain it well, too.
Uh, let's see...  He's cool, and I admire him for how he chases after his dreams.
We should move now
Okay
But that's not all. I just can't describe it.
The feeling of 'love' overflows from somewhere else.
Even if people are against it and you know you can't make the cut,
once you realize this feeling, it's unstoppable.
Super Premium Ticket
Congratulations
You've cleared it superbly! Congratulations!
This is a special invitation for tonight's post-festival event.
Please enjoy it to the end!
How nice...
In Maid Latte
Why is Misa-chan taking the day off?
No idea... Don't ask me.
She has something on?
She should have asked me to go along with her.
There's no way that'll happen, you perv.
My, my, I see you're relaxing comfortably here.
Yeah, to the point of becoming blobs.
You can't distinguish between us now.
We aren't even humans anymore.
I'm glad that you're relaxing that much over here.
Please take your time and enjoy yourselves.
Okay~
Thank you for waiting. Here is your cream soda.
Yay~!
It's here!
I'm sorry for being late, Manager.
Me too, I had some unfinished business to attend to.
It's fine, I'm glad you both came to help.
Hey, how are we going to drink this?
We can't drink in this form...
How do we transform back?
Ah, it was rather fun.
You were having fun teasing me, weren't you?
Huh? Was I the only one having fun?
No...
Well, I had fun as well.
Go retrieve your bag.
U x Mishi
kimi o mitsuketa
I found you
ameagari no houkago
When the rain stopped after school
fui ni me ga ai
Our eyes met by coincidence
boku no sekai ga hora irozuiteku
Look, my world is getting stained
sou kimi iro somatteyuku
Yes, it's stained with your color
sotto yasashii hikari ga kimi o tsutsunda
A warm light embraces you gently
sou mizutamari ja hontou
Just like the puddle after the rain
It started!
Seems like it started.
It got delayed quite a while.
How did you know?
It's written here.
yume no hana o sakasemashou
Let the flowers of your dream bloom
zutto
Because I'll always be at your side
kimi no soba ni iru kara
hana o
Let the flowers bloom
sakasemashou
kono omoi kanjite
Feel my emotions
yume no hana wa sakimidarete
The flowers of my dream are all blooming
zutto
Because you'll always be at my side
boku no soba ni iru kara
The nearer it is to the stage, the more crowded it is.
hana wa
The flowers are all blooming
sakimidarete
kono omoi kanjite
Feel my emotions
That's why we should meet up with them after it ends.
zutto
Forever and ever
I thought it'd be better to get closer to them.
Usu-
Are you alright? Could it be that you almost got separated from me?
Do you want to hold my hand, just like before?
No thanks!
akaneiroshita sora ga ochite
As the sky turns madder red
mou soro soro kanashii kisetsu da ne
It's time for that sad season again
sonna hi no gogo
On such an afternoon
kimi to deatta hajimari kara kimi to boku
I want to go back
omoide ano toki o modoshite
to the time when I first met you
kuruoshii hodo ni mune no oku ga
My heart is beating so madly
ima mo tsuyoku shimetsukerareteru
Even now, it's still tightening up
mou wakatta no ni
I knew that since then
She's gripping me tightly!
tada itsu made mo kono kioku o
I don't want to lose this precious memory
nakushitaku wa nai kara
mou nidoto sayonara
I don't wanna say goodbye for a second time
Hello, Sakura?
The live ended already, right?
Huh? You can't meet up with us?
Geez, I'll do the explaining!
We're going to stroll around the festival grounds with UxMishi.
What? UxMishi?
Guy from UxMishi
Geez, I thought some girls chased after me again.
Kuuga called just now.
They wanted to take a look around without being noticed, so they asked us along.
I see... Got it.
I'll call you back later.
What's wrong, glaring at me like that?
Don't worry, I'm not the least bit interested in you.
I don't want to get scolded like that again.
What is your intention?
About what? Sakura?
Is it wrong for me to invite her for a stroll?
You know she wouldn't refuse, so you're just using her, right?
You're scary, as usual.
To tell you the truth, I don't trust you at all.
But Sakura told me you've changed, so I came here to see for myself.
Changed... eh....
Stop using that glare on me!
I'm sorry, but this is just how I look.
I'm staring hard to spot where you might have changed.
You won't get it.
Kuuga, I brought these for you today!
She's the only one who sees me for who I am.
You're serious about Sakura-
Stop right there!
You're being overprotective!
Just go play along with your boyfriend and leave us alone!
Boyfriend?!
Whose!?
That stalker guy you mentioned.
Just
another
stalker
N-No! He's just a perverted alien stalker!
Wait, don't tell me he's still enduring it?
What are you-
You're not only clueless, but strict and violent as well.
I'd ditch you already if I were him.
I wouldn't want to be with you either!
How scary~  Catch ya later~
What did he mean by 'enduring'?
Sorry for the wait.
It was packed with people, so I had to wait.
What's the matter?
You want
some juice?
I-It's nothing...
Well, I've completed what I came here to do... I think.
Huh, you're not acting like your usual self.
It's not up to me to decide anyway.
Well, since we're done already, shall we head back?
W-Wait! Since we're here already...
I wanna stay on til' it ends...
Usui, are you still free?
This is very unexpected indeed.
What's wrong?! I just felt like inviting you!
Fine! I'll just go there alone!
Alright.
We cleared the trial and got this special invitation anyway.
Super Premium Ticket
Congratulations
So this is what they meant by special service...
You look perfect in that!
Create your own special memories in this special uniform on this special night!
These costumes
are precious,
so be careful
not to get
them dirty
Please enjoy yourself!
Ladies' changing room
Guys do not enter!!
Romeo's waiting for you!
Hey.
You look good, Juliet.
Stop it! It's embarrassing!
Heard they're going to have fireworks in this event.
The
campfire's
starting
soon!
Is that so?
Oh!
I'm
going!
Since we're here already, let's watch that.
Yeah.
Good, this place seems to have the best view of the fireworks.
Is it fine to enter just like this?
It's fine as long as we don't mess it up.
What's wrong...
...Ayuzawa?
N-Nothing's w-wrong...
Is it? Fine then.
Let's change places. Watching it from the campfire site might be better.
A-Are you enduring this?
You mean the fireworks? Not really-
That's not what I meant...
Are you... enduring a lot of things just for me?
Why do you think so?
I... just felt that way...
Ehh... So you knew about it.
So I was right? What were you-
How cruel of you, Ayuzawa.
Do you want me to say it out?
I'll tell you if you answer my question.
What do you...
Why are you that bothered by me?
There's no reason-
I don't know it myself, even if you ask me.
You don't know, eh...
Do you know?
You always lie at times like this.
W-What are you saying?!
Why are you blushing so hard now?
I'm not blushing-!
Are you nervous?
I'm... I'm not!
Are you enduring as well?
Sorry, I crossed the line.
I am.
I've been enduring!
Why must it be you?! I don't get it at all!
You're a pervert who annoys me all the time.
You're always running ahead of me and teasing me.
Ayuzawa!
It's your fault!
Calm down!  What are you saying-
I wouldn't have realized it if not for that game!
I wanted to join hands with you since a long time ago!
One moment you're sexually harassing me, and then gone the next...
Just what are you thinking?
Why is my heart beating so fast?
Why do I feel lonely when you leave me?
Why are you...
...the only one causing me so much confusion?
You idiot, why do you always tease me?
You're really sly, Ayuzawa.
Just how much more are you gonna make me endure?
I wanted to see your interesting expressions, that's why I teased you.
Your sudden smiles always surprise me.
They're interesting, but dangerous enough to make my heart race.
I have been enduring a lot of things, and I can't phrase it short.
Even now...
This is what's on my mind right now.
I love you, Ayuzawa.
I...
... hate you.
You're really sly, Ayuzawa.
Usui, you idiot...
kitto mata aeru
We'll surely meet again
sono me ni utsuru mono subete
Everything that's reflected by your eyes,
maboroshi ni wa miemasenka
is it all just an illusion?
karami aitoketeyuku naka
I wonder how you feel,
kimi wa nani o kanjiteru no darou
as you melt away in this entangling love
mite goran doko made mo
Take a look at the reason we're joined together
tsunagatta sono riyuu o
kanashii kara sugarou
Let's cling on to each other from our sadness
-And so, on a certain day-
Ah
I forgot we need aprons for today's lesson!
sonna mono de ii ja nai ka
Isn't it fine just like that?
Don't worry!
kazaranai mama ukabu utsukushisa yo
It'll be an unadorned beauty
Here's an apron I won from a postcard draw!
Hair band
Included
Someone will be happy if you wear this!
Who will?!
I wonder who~
itsu no hi ni ka wakarou
Let's understand this, someday...
Preparing
Please wait~
tatoe doko ni ita toshitemo
That no matter where we are,
It's the quiet tea time before opening hours~
kitto mata aeru
we'll surely meet again
Satsuki, I got thrown out again so I'll be counting on you!
Oh my~
I need to be manlier!
He's my rival, after all!
It's Usui, you know?
I'll definitely make her look at me!
Be prepared for it, Misaki-chan!
Morning, Misaki-chan!
Thank you for your support     -    FFFPeeps
Don't eat bread crusts on your way to school!
I love you, Misa-chan~
Misaki!
It's too heavy for you, Yukimura.
This is interesting.
Misa-chan, moe!