douka please can you keep my secret?
Please, please can you keep my secret?
kira kira to kagayaku miraa
The mirror, shining so brilliantly.
watashi wa donna fuu ni utsutteiru no
I wonder how do I look in it.
hora hora to temaneku mirai
The future, beckoning me forward.
kore kara donna koto ga okoru no
What will happen from now, I wonder?
me ni mieteiru mono ga subete dewa nai kara
Because what we see is not everything.
mugamuchuu da that's all right
I'm losing myself but that's all right.
mayowanaide I wanna try
I will now try not to waver.
jibun no kimochi ni massugu de itai
I want to be true to my heart.
dakedo hitotsu ya futatsu gurai
But even I have a secret or two.
dare ni mo baretakunai
That I want to keep to myself.
naishotte aru mono dakara
mune ga chotto itamu my secret
That's why my secret makes my heart aches slightly.
Geez... Why did you tell everyone that you didn't want them to come?
You look so depressed now.
You actually wanted them to see you off, didn't you?
Geez, you're so helpless.
Here, take this.
Don't make that face anymore!
Cheer up, okay?
You-kun!
Hinata, Misaki And Usui
Morning arrives, and school's over in a blink of an eye.
She's as scary as always.
Oh, that devil Prez? That's because he was having lunch in class before break.
She even scolded him before the teacher could do so.
Shintani, why are you having lunch now?!  And it's only first period!
Hinata, aren't you afraid of getting scolded by her?
Not really, 'cause she's Misaki!
Did the sports clubs make this mess?  I told them many times not to track mud inside...
Sports Clubs Members
Hide!
See!
What the guys saw
She's communicating with the devil!
Through Hinata's filters
This is back-breaking indeed...
Sheesh, cleaning this up sure is back-breaking!
Misaki-chan...
Run!
Run! She'll bring you to hell if you get caught!
Misaki-chan!
Why did you choose the Prez out of all the girls?
She might have been kinder back then, but look at her now.
The male students' image of Prez
Are there any bad boys lurking around?
She does talk a little differently compared to back then, but...
She's still as kind as she was!
I'm confiscating these bread crusts!
How?!
Eh? Don't tell me she treats me differently?
He's a masochist?
That's what I thought, too!
Anyway, she is still Misaki-chan.
My feelings for her won't change.
Hinata...
I realized a long time ago that she has to be the one for me.
Hey!
What are you doing up there?
You're gonna get your new uniform dirty!
What's wrong with you? Pouting like that...
Hey! You can't do that!
Nothing...
How's middle school going?
There are a lot of people in my class.
I hope you can make a lot of friends.
Time really flies! You're already in middle school...
Yeah. I'm glad he grew up well.
Thanks for the meal!
I worried about him everyday after he came here.
He was plump back then, but he slimmed down a lot.
That's 'cause you only gave me veggies!
Stop being ridiculous!  You were the one who didn't want the meat!
You said it's fine, though you didn't look fine.
I'm glad things turned out well.
Run! Come back to home base!
Safe!
You got faster, didn't you?
And you don't look all that muscular, either!
I do have them, see?
He's just so cute!
Hinata-kun!
Hinata's surprisingly popular.
Even the girls at the school we
played practice match with fell for him...
He's the ace, so of course he'd be popular.
Dammit! He's such an idiot!
I'm so jealous of him!
But I... actually...
Shintani
Today's Valentine's Day, eh...
Here, take this.
Cheer up, okay?  You-kun!
Autumn's Oil Festival
Please come this way!
Student Council Room
UxMishi's live performance?
Yeah! They're gonna perform in Yumesaki High's Cultural Festival!
Have you forgotten how awful he was to you?
Exactly! Please tell her she can't go, Misaki!
But he's different now!
He supposedly got injured in his last performance,
and changed his attitude when she visited him.
Wants to say
a lot of things...
Sorry!  But...
He has really changed, and I wanted you two to know...
Guess I have to go, then...
I want to go, too!
Usui!
I want to go Yumesaki High's Cultural Festival!
Why are you going?!
Just bring him along!
He's worried about you!
That can't be-
Misaki, you're blushing.
You're so warm!
Today Fortune-telling Day
Welcome back, masters!
Eri Kari... Eri Kalipso!
Now, tell me.
Okay!
Please, Lady Erika!
Will I...
No, will I!
be together with Misa-chan?!
Fine. Let the crystal ball reveal your future with her!
I can't wait to hear!
She's a fitting fortune-teller, but she still lacks some moe points.
But look at her. She's moves as if she's possessed by something.
I'm so anxious!
It has been revealed! This is-!
What did you see?!
I can't wait to hear!
I'm so excited!
Shh!
I can't see anything, since it's as cloudy as gray matter.
Meaning...?
What do you mean?
I can't see anything! That's everything you need to know! In other words-
I don't give a damn!
Which means it'll never happen for you guys!
That's what the crystal ball says.
You don't need to put it so bluntly!
Since fortune-telling is basically just observing people, Misa wouldn't be able to do it.
You don't even know about your own feelings.
Welcome back, master!
Misaki-chan- Oops, it's Misa-chan here.
I guess I don't come enough to remember to call you that. How embarrassing!
No, you're already a regular.
Oh yeah, I saw outside that there's fortune-telling today. Can I get one too?
Of course, master!
Please sit in front of the crystall ball, master!
Oh, how authentic!
Please tell me my future with Misa-chan!
Fine.
I can't wait!
I see it.
What did you see?!
A paper balloon...
And?
...that is deflated.
How sad for him.
His future with Misa-chan's like a deflated paper balloon, eh?
Must be worse than our cloudy prediction!
Look! The deflated balloon's inflating again!
My my!
Trying to hang on to your last thread, eh?
I don't see any holes in it.
I'm relieved. I can just inflate it again as long as there are no holes!
That's quite optimistic of him.
Here's something extra for you.
That optimism might just turn things around for you in the end.
Really?! Yay!
If that's the case, I'll get my future with Misa-chan told as well.
Is it me, or am I seeing dogs?
Then, I shall look into your future.
She's totally averting her eyes from the crystal ball!
And what's my fortune?
O-Oh yeah, r-right...
Just tell it to me straight.
You're right. Here goes...
The two of you...
...have no future together!
I see fire and water in the crystal ball.
You two are very incompatible, and a romance between the two of you cannot happen.
If you still wish to pursue this relationship, you will have to face a great obstacle.
There's more to our fortunes, right?
Aren't you going to tell us more?
Lady Erika, please tell us!
It's not our turn yet, eh? Let's retreat quietly.
Sorry to bother!
Good work!
You too, Misa-chan!
You were waiting for me?
I saw Mr. Third Rate hurrying off somewhere just now.
Does it really bother you that much?
Where did that come from?!
He might be waiting for his situation to turn around.
If Mr. Third Rate were to hit the comeback homerun...
I see... So we were that incompatible with each other eh...
Wait! You aren't that easily influenced by fortune-telling, are you?
So that's the reason why you're so cold towards only me...
No, that's 'cause you're a perverted alien-
I'm sure you're calling me that 'cause of our incompatibility, right?
Are you an idiot?!
We're not allowed to be together, huh...
So are you going to leave me just because of this?
N-No, umm...
Damn those guys from the sports clubs! I'll make them pay this time!
So are you going to leave me just because of this?
I'll help you, Misaki-chan!
Shintani!
This is a big mess.
Do your cleaning properly!
I am!
Don't lie!
W-What's so funny?
N-Nothing, you've just completely changed...
Thanks. You're a great help, Shintani.
R-r-really? I-I'm glad! I-I'll work hard!
Shintani, what's wrong?
N-Nothing!  I'll change the water!
Already?
She was so cute that I thought I'd die!
Misaki-chan!
Won't it be faster to use this?
Oh, the hose?  It might be long enough to get the whole entrance.
Press here, just like this, and it'll-
Idiot! Did you connect the hose properly?!
It's cold! Don't block the water with your hands! Turn off the tap!
Which direction should I turn it?!
Get off! Don't use your hands to block it!
S-Sorry, Misaki-chan.
What are you doing on this chilly day?
Usui, you again!
You're gonna catch a cold if you don't change.
I won't stop you if you insist on playing in the water, though.
Shut up.  Shintani, do you have clothes to change into?
I've got my jersey!
Change quickly and head back. You're gonna catch a cold.
What 'bout you?
I'll go to the infirmary and take care of this. See you later. Get moving.
Wait a moment, Prez.
You're going there like that?
Yeah, the corridors would get wet, so I'll walk around the building to the infirmary.
That's not what I mean.
It's fine, right? Not like you can see through my underwear.
Wears chemisole
Hmm... Why do you think that guy over there is blushing?
Just noticed that
Why are you feeling embarrassed?
It's not good to be so clueless, Prez.
I-It's fine! No big deal!
I'll strip completely if you don't wear it.
I mean, if you're fine with me dancing stark naked at the school gates...
Alright already. Just don't go stripping, you pervert!
Geez... I'm off!
Ruff!
Why did you bark?
Nothing, just felt like doing it.  Why don't you try meowing?
Huh?! What are you trying to pull?!
Ruff!
Boyfriend?
Yeah, she might have one already, don't you think?
Especially if she's as cute as you say.
Well, no worries if she's a fugly pig, though.
She's not! She's definitely cute!
Then she must have a boyfriend by now!
You honestly never thought about that possibility?
How naive! We're gonna be high schoolers soon, you know?
For the city girls, even for the middle schoolers, they must've...
To be a high school girl, I'm sure they have to have done this or that...
Done what?!
What's gotten into you?
Try reading this book I found in my big sister's room.
The high school girls were playing around with a guy's body, you know?
Misaki wouldn't do things like that!
She's a pure, cute, and kind person!
Hey, don't tease an idealistic middle school boy!
Still, don't you think that he needs to start seeing things more realistically?
Well, he does worry others sometimes.
He still has the candy wrapper that girl gave him, right?
How did you know that?!
Guys, you know?  He put that wrapper into the victory charm we bought together for the baseball team.
Victory
Given to all members
in the club
WHAT?!
So you were the reason we lost our second round in the summer league?!
Don't be ridiculous! It was the reason why we won our first round!
It doesn't really matter...
Hinata.
Are you really serious about finding her in high school?
You're gonna be disappointed if you expect too much from her.
Be prepared if you're gonna try to find her.
I was prepared, but...
It still hurts.
I'll worry about getting her annoyed when it happens, and just keep trying.
A few days later
A few days later... What a nice weather!
It's dangerous!
Kanou!
Were you waiting a long time for me?
Not really.
I heard Yumesaki High's Cultural Festival is amazing!
Sounds like it.
Aoi!
Good timing! I was just about to film the lakeside scene that we didn't get to do last time.
You guys are free, right?  Here, hold this.
We were all in the same boat, eh...
You're really gonna do that?
The fireworks have been going off non-stop, so we'll cover up the audio later. I'll leave this to you!
Yumesaki Festival
Whoa! This year's really amazing!
I heard rumors, but to think that it's this grand...
Seems like it's their school's tradition.
I heard they've spent half a year preparing for this.
It's really noisy over there.
Could it be?!
They've shown up eh? UxMishi, that is.
Sakura- She's not here!
Kuuga! Here's something for you!
Hey you're in the way!
Sakura!
Haven't I said it before? Be nice if you want me to like you.
Only those who can promise me that can follow me.
Sakura! Shizuko!
So both of you were swept up to the first few rows?
Which means...
Beyond this sea of people, right?
Seems like they were lining up for the performance,
I don't wanna move! I don't wanna!
and Sakura doesn't want to move now.
I don't wanna go further away from the stage!
I guess we won't be able to meet up with you guys,
Please stay here!
so go ahead and enjoy yourselves!
E-Eh? Shizuko-
Alright, catch you later.
You say that, but...
Kuuga's changed recently, right?
The band has a different feel about them, too!
They seem so tense. It feels like there's a gap between them and their fans.
But scandals involving the fans have faded away.
This is a good thing for their fans who are looking forward to their music.
Kuuga certainly seemed different, like Sakura said.
Although I'm still not sure if he's trustworthy.
I'm worried about her...  So worried...
But I guess a person's opinions differ when seen from different angles.
Still...
There's no use thinking about it now, huh?
Shall we go and enjoy the festival?
E-Enjoy?
kitto mata aeru
We'll surely meet again
sono me ni utsuru mono subete
Everything that's reflected by your eyes,
maboroshi ni wa miemasenka
is it all just an illusion?
karami aitoketeyuku naka
I wonder how you feel,
kimi wa nani o kanjiteru no darou
as you melt away in this entangling love
mite goran doko made mo
Take a look at the reason we're joined together
tsunagatta sono riyuu o
kanashii kara sugarou
Let's cling on to each other from our sadness
sonna mono de ii ja nai ka
Isn't it fine just like that?
kazaranai mama ukabu utsukushisa yo
It'll be an unadorned beauty
itsu no hi ni ka wakarou
Let's understand this, someday...
tatoe doko ni ita toshitemo
That no matter where we are,
kitto mata aeru
we'll surely meet again
Preview
I still feel like I'm being led around by Usui...
Never mind that, shall we enjoy ourselves?
It's exactly like that!  You always talk like that!
Let's enjoy Yumesaki's Festival, since we're already here!
Now you're switching to the spoilt brat tone!
You're annoying, so go be with Shizuko and Sakura!
When is KameMushi's live performance ending?!
It's UxMishi! I hope Kuuga will sing his new song!
Oh yeah, shouldn't you tell everyone that next episode's the last one?
I-Is it? Then I should do something befitting of the last episode.
You're really sly Ayuzawa, Usui you idiot!
I wanna see your true self.
Usui, you idiot!