Nothing lets you call the students of Seika "flies".
I demand an apology from you.
Ayuzawa Misaki-san.
Will you join us at Miyabigaoka's Student Council?
I will guarantee everything.
I'm serious.
Apparently that's what "dominant" is.
I've had enough of you playing around with me.
You're one of Miyabigaoka's...
I'm the Vice President of the Student Council, Maki.
Do you need something from me?
May I have a moment with you?
You guys.
Yes.
Please accept them.
They're gifts from President Igarashi.
No, I really can't accept these gifts.
President Igarashi strongly desires for you to transfer.
I don't have any intension of going to Miyabigaoka even if you do this for me.
I appreciate it, but please take these back.
It's a special cake I had my shop make for this day.
I'd be a waste to have it thrown away.
Please don't worry.  President Igarashi wouldn't intend for this gesture to leave you in his debt.
Please accept them.
President Igarashi simply wants you to help make Miyabigaoka a better school.
I'm home.
Welcome back, Suzuna.
Unfamiliar men.
Are they new students of the Ayuzawa School's?
No they're not.  Leave us alone.
Well, maybe I'll prepare some tea.
I'm sorry.  She's a little bit unique.
If you would come to Miyabigaoka, the president says he would offer your sister a generous deal, as well.
Now that's going overboard.
The Igarashi Foundation's influence on Miyabigaoka is extraordinary.
Please seriously consider this offer for your sister's sake, too.
We'll wait for another 3 days.
We await your favorable reply.
But...
President will be waiting at Miyabigaoka until you come.
What's wrong, Misaki?  You're spacing out.
Nothing.
Oh, is it about Tora?
"Tora"?
The son of the Igarashi Foundation.
Miyabigaoka's Student Council President.
That Igarashi Tora!
You wouldn't transfer to Miyabigaoka, would you, Misaki?
Of course I won't.
Don't ever forsake us!
You're the only one we can count on!
Sakura-san!  Watch what you say!
If we consider Misaki-san's future,
we shouldn't let emotion guide us.
It's not bad to graduate from a renowned school.
Misaki's future?
What if a love story starts between Misaki and Tora after her transfer?
Misaki might become Tora's wife?
She could become the Igarashi Foundation's celebrity madam!
I think it's better for the Prez to be over there.
After all, Miyabigaoka is a prestigious school.
Who would turn down this offer?
There's no reason not to accept.
If Prez leaves, then we'll be able to do what we want like we used to.
How can you guys say something like that?!
Ow.
What was that for?
When Prez went against Miyabigaoka, she trusted us and stood up for us.
Do you guys have any idea how much she thinks about us?
Yeah, we know.
But, if Prez says she wants to go...
Then we can't stop her.
I've been absent for a long time...
I've been ash for a while.
So I better take care of the work that's piled up.
Usui-san?!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Don't hang around the student council room when you don't have any business here.
Look.  You're frightening Yukimura.
I do have a business.
What are you going to do about Miyabigaoka?
I'm the Student Council President of Seika High School.
If I leave, Seika will...
It might be nice to be freed from a stalker like you.
Transfer to Miyabigaoka?  What is this about?
What happened while I was gone?
Hey, where's Mom?
I got a call from the hospital, she suddenly had to cover the night shift.
There she goes, when I always tell her not to work too hard.
She's raising two daughters by herself,
so there are times when she has to overwork.
I guess that's true, but...
Dinner's ready.
What's with this feast?!
Are the guys from Miyabigaoka hiding somewhere?
No.  I made it all.
Bean curd croquette, bean curd salad,
bean curd molded to look like king crab,
bean curd imitating the shape of a roast chicken, and bean curd imitating the shape of sashimi.
This is all bean curd?  Wow.
Bean curd is cheap and full of nutrition.
We're poor, so we need to be creative with our food like this.
I'm sorry for making you go through hard times, too.
It's not your fault, Sis.
It's our Dad's fault for disappearing on us.
Besides, cooking is fun.
Itadakimasu.
It's good.
Hey, Suzuna.  Would you want to go to Miyabigaoka?
What?  Isn't that a school for rich and smart people?
What if you could go?
If we had the money to go there,
I would buy a real king crab instead.
Why are you asking?
No real reason.
Anyways, they all taste like bean curd.
Desserts are the top-notch cakes brought by the students of the Ayuzawa School.
I said they're not from the Ayuzawa School.
Where did Misaki go?
I don't think Misaki-san would go to shows like that.
Honestly, I'd like to pass, too.
I swear!  If you see them once, you'll love them, too!
Look!
He's so hot!
Is that a girl?
U cross Mishi?
It's Umemishi.  Was that on purpose?
Seriously, I don't have any interest.
I guess I'll give her a ring.
Hey, Misaki?
Sakura?
Where are you?
I'm at Miyabigaoka.
Miyabigaoka?  Why?
Sakura... I'm sorry, but I'll call you back.
Hey, Misaki!
Misaki?
Then person you are trying to reach is unable to answer the phone.
What did Misaki-san say?
I can't get through to her.
She's at Miyabigaoka Academy, isn't she?
What is Misaki planning on doing?
Why is she making such an important decision alone?
Don't worry.
I'll figure it out.
It's not bad to graduate from a renowned school.
Misaki might become Tora's wife?
She could become the Igarashi Foundation's celebrity madam!
No fret.  Misaki-san will take care of him.
We've been relying on Misaki-san so much.
We didn't ask about her feelings at all.
We weren't discussing any of the important things.
Are you really all right even if Misaki goes to Miyabigaoka?
Wouldn't you be lonely?
Sakura-san.
If we are going to get Misaki-san back, we need to fight seriously, too.
Yeah.
How do you do?
How is your mother doing?
Where will you be going on the next vacation?
I didn't notice last time I was here, but this definitely is Miyabigaoka.
The atmosphere is completely different from our school.
Prez.  Seika High School's Ayuzawa Misaki is here.
Okay.
I'll give her a warm welcome.
She's the first woman that you've really been into.
Maki.  I bet you're thinking there are no women out there that will satisfy me, right?
I always thought so myself, too.
President Ayuzawa.  I had faith that you would come.
President Igarashi...
I assume you're here to accept our offer?
Regarding that...
Why isn't Misa-chan here today?!
So much for-
-today being Shiroyan's birthday!
I wanted her to celebrate it!
Ikkun.  Kurotatsu.  My life just ended.
Shiroyan.
Lift your head up.
Hey, Shiroyan.
Masters.
We can't replace Misa-chan,
But can we celebrate?
We have a cake ready, too.
It's Maid Latte's special birthday cake.
Don't worry.  It's on the house for your continued patronage.
We're so happy.
But, it says "Moron Trio" on it.
Yeah, it's hard to be really happy.
Who cares, it's free.
Excuse us.
I'm sorry for Shizuko's intrusion.
Will anyone here go to Miyabigaoka with us?
Misaki-san has gone to Miyabigaoka by herself.
Prez did?
If Prez ends up going to Miyabigaoka,
then it's partly our fault for not stopping her!
This could just be us being selfish, but I want Misaki to be at Seika.
Isn't it the same for all of you?
I can't imagine anyone else
other than her being the President!
Let's go get Prez!
Yeah, that's right. Let's go get her.
Count us in.
Yeah.
Let us go, everyone!
Yeah!
As expected from the rich school.
A shower room attached to the Student Council Room is just unreal.
More like, why am I doing this?
It's gone!  I'm sure I put it here.
Was it another locker?
It's not even this.
There it is!
This is...
Ayuzawa-san, are you all right?
Um, I can't seem to find my uniform.
Ah. I asked a girl to take it to the dry cleaning so it doesn't get stained.
Um, then what am I supposed to wear?
There's something there for you, isn't there?
You're telling me to wear this?
Is there something wrong, Ayuzawa-san?
Well, it exposes a little too much.
Did you perhaps burn yourself in the shower?
Huh?
And, perhaps you're trying to cover the burn with your clothes in order to be considerate to us?
No, nothing like that...
Or maybe you slipped and fell?
No, I didn't do that, either.
Are you sure that you didn't injure yourself?
Really, like I said-
I'm coming in, okay?
Hold just a second!
I'm all right.
I'm not hurt at all.
You sound very agitated.
It's the clothes!  They're embarrassing!
Why would you lie like that?
I'm not lying!
Then let me confirm that you're fine.
I'll get changed, so give me ten seconds!
Ten is all you need?
Ten
Nine
Eight
Seven
Six
Five
Four
He's serious with his countdown!
Three
What's wrong with him?
Two
One
Zero.
Give me back my uniform!
See?  It's weird! I look weird, don't I?
See what I mean?
I was thinking, despite what you said,
you're wearing it perfectly.
Force of habit.
Anyways, I don't mind it being dirty, so please give me back my uniform.
What a waste that would be.
You look really good in that.
Wouldn't you think so, too?
You like things like this, doncha?
That's...
A girl like you chose a job like this, but acts totally different at school.
You're way too interesting.
You're not going anywhere.
I've got a bunch of people outside.
Anyways, come over here.
So that's your true face.
I couldn't see through it at all.
I knew you were thickheaded from the first time I met you.
He's horrible.
But honestly, you disappoint me.
I didn't think you'd fall for this so easily.
I thought you'd put up a better fight.
You work as a maid and student council president, and I look forward to seeing what you'll accomplish at Miyabigaoka, too.
Wait.  You're misunderstanding something.
Fine.
Isn't this enough?
If this isn't enough, then entertain me more.
Entertain?
Since I'm the next heir of the Igarashi Foundation,
that's enough to attract all the women in the world.
I'm bored with obedient women.
I had some hope in you.
You came here lured by the money.
In the end, you're no different from the others.
Just another worthless woman.
I pity you.
Have you been looking down on people like that all your life?
If you say those around you are worthless, then that's your fault.
There is not a single person in this world that is worthless.
The reason I came here today is to decline your offer.
That's all I came for!
I have no intention of quitting being Seika's President!
Man, you are...
So interesting.
Forget it.  You've got aikido, but I've got judo.
I'm best on the mat.
Hey, stop it.
U...sui...
Stop right there.
What happened to the guys outside?
They wouldn't let me in, so I misbehaved a bit.
Sorry.
But, you're misbehaving more than I am, aren't you, perv bro?
You've got some guts.
In any case, could you go find another person to do this with?
She's not someone people can touch so nonchalantly.
You're one to talk!
That's all I've got to say.
Let's go, Prez.
Hey, wait.
President Igarashi.
If you want to speak to me in my role as President of Seika High School, you're welcome anytime.
Excuse us.
Usui, why are you here?
I can't believe you were fooled by him.
Besides...
You called me, right?
W-What are you saying?
Don't be ridiculous.  I never called out for you.
I have no intention of quitting being Seika's President!
But well, good job.
Oh, I figured.
Usui.
T-Thank... you...
Oh, I did get your clothes back.
I have the refined Miyabigaoka uniform that uses the finest thread and the clothes you always wear.
Which would you like?
Give them back to me already!
Of course.
Prez!
Master!
You guys...
Misaki-san.
Misaki!
I turned down the transfer offer, so don't worry, everyone.
Welcome back!
We were so worried!
Why is Usui here?
She really is an interesting woman.
Prez, in that situation,
you'd only call out my name, right?
You're annoying, Usui!
I said I didn't call out your name.
Well I definitely heard it.
Where were you?
There's no way you could
have heard such a soft voice.
See?
Huh?  Why are Sakura
and Yukimura dressed like that?
Looks like more great weather.
Look, Granny.
A big peach is drifting down.
I love peaches.
I live in this neighborhood.
Do you want to eat the peach, too?
If it's Oni busting, I better
take subordinates with me.