so ra no wo to
The brilliant glow of this sky, does it carry right into your heart?
The melody you heard in your dream, it plays like the silence
Even if your hands are still far from that dream,
Come now and remember that kindly voice,
Someone was there singing for you, singing those chords of happiness
Sound of the sky, echo on high, break through that overwhelming sadness
Everything that shines in your eyes
Is part of the real world
Even your tears can't leave you here to stay forever
In this light pouring down onto you, play tomorrow's song
Are you ready, my little ones?
Standby to advance!
Forward!
Advancing!
Where are our reinforcements?
Left, forty degrees! Main armament, standby!
Distance, 400.
Load shell. Incendiary round.
Check.
Olga!
Leave it to me!
I've been canned in this thing for three days! I'm not dying until I get a shower!
Target locked!
Fire!
Direct hit!
Anna, signal the forces to our rear.
Have destroyed enemy unit. Take up our rear.
Roger!
Filicia, cover her.
Y- Yes.
It's flashing out there, but there's no thunder. Just relax.
I know!
Three o'clock!
No...
Lieutenant Anna!
Paper!
Bamboo!
Chirping Crickets - Floating Lights on the River
Come on, Noël!
It won't get clean if you don't scrub harder!
It's so hot!
This building gets way too cold in the winter, but thank God it's cool in the summer.
Oh? Weren't Filicia and Rio in charge of the laundry today?
They said they were busy so they asked us to do it for them.
Whose is that?
Filicia's.
She said she wasn't hungry, so we could have them.
Then this one's mine!
What are you doing? Are you starting on dinner?
Ouch. What are you making? You shouldn't play with your food.
I'm not playing!
It's almost time for Obon, right?
What? What's this Obon?
Fiesta des Lumières.
Fi?
Fiesta des Lumières is an event specific to the southern part of Helvetia.
It originated in a local belief that
for a short period during the summer, the souls of the dead would return to the world of the living.
Paper lanterns are floated down the river as a symbol of their return to the afterlife.
In some regions, the festival is called Obon.
Right. Here you are.
Thank you.
Oh? So it's the same thing?
Souls returning?
Wait, wait! What does that mean? Does that mean ghosts come back?
In one sense.
Paper lanterns? That sounds so wonderful!
We used to hold bonfires back in my village, but-
No! Dead people go to Heaven and stay there forever!
Only the evil spirits wander around on earth!
What? That's not true!
But the Church...
We're home!
Hey! Mind lending us a hand?
When did you two go shopping?
Oh, aren't those...
They looked delicious, so we bought them.
And these too.
Is it like this?
No, Father. I told you, it's like this.
I'm done!
Your mom and dad?
Oh, you did a really good job!
What? Even the Church approves of it?
That Fi-whatever?
Yeah.
The central diocese would start a riot,
but this is the middle of nowhere.
That's not much of a reason...
In my village, we would make horses and cows out of cucumbers and eggplants for our ancestors to ride.
And to console our ancestors, we would all dance together.
Are you two making them too?
Yeah. Last year we only watched, but...
Maintaining smooth cultural relations with the local residents is also part of our job.
If you don't get into details, it's just another festival.
Right, Filicia?
Sound of the Skies
Filicia!
Are you okay? Does it hurt?
No, I'm fine.
I just made a little mistake.
But it's pretty rare for you to make a mistake like that, Commander.
I mean, you're not Kanata.
Well, it's been pretty hot these last few days.
I haven't slept very well.
I'll go get a little rest.
Filicia...
The Commander's acting a bit weird today.
She didn't eat her lunch, and then she buys watermelons without checking our food budget?
I'm sure even she has her reasons.
I think I'll talk to her...
Don't!
Everyone has a part of themselves they don't want anyone to know about.
Just leave her alone.
Noël?
Do you know what happened, Rio?
I read the files.
I was there when it happened.
So...
Filicia...
Put your elbow into it. Good.
There, there, now.
And then a ghost that looked just like the Commander
There used to be millions of things living in this ocean.
It's hard to believe that now.
Did anyone ever tell you?
They say the world is slowly dying,
and eventually, all humanity will fall completely into ruin.
Those are just...
people talking.
But if it were true,
then what are we fighting for?
I'm...
Still alive?
Ideographs?
I'm sorry.
I wish I could read your final words.
This equipment...
Could you be a soldier from-
Commander...
Lieutenant Olga...
Marlina...
Anna...
Why
only me?
are you crying?
I see.
So there are still people alive in this world.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Why
are you apologizing?
Because...
we lost.
Against them.
We couldn't protect you.
I'm truly sorry.
The world is already dead.
No...
You are just the dregs.
The last few bubbles in the bowl.
Humanity...
The world will never shine as it did before.
Don't decide that for us!
But that is the truth.
So just end it.
Living pathos in the dregs of the world, in this despair? It's far too desolate.
No. I won't.
Why not?
Does remaining in this world have any meaning?
There...
Save me...
I am here! I am alive!
Please! Save me!
You...
I'm sorry.
If only my corps had arrived half a day sooner,
it wouldn't have turned out this way.
Your Highness, Princess Iria.
But I was surprised.
About what?
You completely ignored the Fiesta des Lumières last year.
Why the change of faith?
Well...
Isn't it a pretty color?
Treize is famous for these. I bought them at the flea market.
They're amazing! They're so wonderful!
Aren't they?
Yes!
I know.
She used to mean everything to me.
I thought I wanted to protect my country, my people, like she did.
But sometimes, I think...
Is there any meaning in it?
So if she really did come back...
I wanted her to tell me.
But what about you?
They're worried about you.
You're right. I may have made them worry a little.
I've failed as a Commander.
They aren't the only ones!
Even I'm... Um...
Um?
It doesn't matter! Just don't try to shoulder it all yourself!
Even I can listen to what you have to say!
Thank you, Rio.
Then I'll take your offer and tell you.
What?
Actually...
I've put on some weight this summer!
What?
If I don't lose it, I might not fit into my winter uniform.
I heard that if you only eat watermelon for a while, you can lose weight, so I thought I would try it.
What's wrong, Rio?
Will you stop playing dumb?
You were in the front lines at the battle at Vingt-et-Un and-
Oh.
So you thought I was remembering that?
Y- You weren't?
It's so pretty.
Should we head down too?
So you made one too, Kureha?
It's not like I believe in souls or anything.
It's part of my duties.
Excuse me...
Who are you sending, Filicia?
My old friends,
and a soldier whose name I don't know.
The ones who helped me realize the most important thing.
Are those the people...
Filicia...
If you're worried about anything, I...
I might not be able to help, but...
But...
It looks like I made you worry about me.
I'm sorry.
But I'm okay.
You're making me sad.
I want to worry about you!
The way you always worry about me, Filicia!
Because I make you worry. I want to worry about you!
Because I love you, Filicia!
I love you too, Kanata.
Always stay the way you are now.
Please.
Filicia...
You're always trying to tell me
not to fear putting my feelings into words.
I think it's a wonderful thing.
Commander...
Filicia...
Me too...
Oh, you three...
I love you all...
Until next year then, ancestors.
Dad. Mom.
Mother.
Sister.
That girl...
Rio, you were just asking if there were any meaning in this world, right?
Yeah.
Ever since I survived the battle alone, I've pondered the same question.
Why did I, alone, survive?
Was there any meaning in it?
Listen up. You can't just space out like that.
And then I realized.
There can't possibly be any meaning in this world.
But isn't that wonderful in its own right?
Because if there isn't any, we can find our own.
And I found mine.
My meaning in being alive.
And so even the priest joined in!
And then? And then?
Well, he was really bad at it, so Sister Yumina...
I don't want them to suffer the way I did.
Neither do I.
Love and friendship - put these feelings together
And sing of how important they are
I was so happy that I cried
It hurt so bad that I laughed
But that all just goes to show that I'm alive
Let's just walk it slowly
Everybody singing!
Just tell me a bit of what you think
You're just my friend!
Love and friendship - even though they might waver
I know, you know, little happy
I want us to echo on forever
Can you hear my precious note?
All these words that there are can't even describe it.
Our harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony
Next time: Telephone Duty - Declare a State of Emergency