so ra no wo to
The brilliant glow of this sky, does it carry right into your heart?
The melody you heard in your dream, it plays like the silence
Even if your hands are still far from that dream,
Come now and remember that kindly voice,
Someone was there singing for you, singing those chords of happiness
Sound of the sky, echo on high, break through that overwhelming sadness
Everything that shines in your eyes
Is part of the real world
Even your tears can't leave you here to stay forever
In this light pouring down onto you, play tomorrow's song
Just what am I doing wrong?
Really.
Noel?
The Rainy Sky - A Glass Rainbow
Do you have your wallet?
Yes, sir!
And your dog tag?
Handkerchief?
Yes, sir!
Tissues?
Map?
Yes, sir!
Compass?
Emergency rations?
Yes, sir!
Helmet?
Handgun?
Hand grenades?
She's kidding, Kanata.
Come on, you scared me!
If you thought about it for a second, you would have known.
That wasn't funny, Rio.
Those two have been getting along really well recently.
Rio is just like an anxious mother.
Here's the list for today.
Listen up.
Your mission is to enter town and purchase the items on that list.
Understood?
Yes, sir!
Well then, drive safely.
Commencing operation.
Hurry back now!
We're having pot-au-feu for dinner!
Come straight home, okay!
Just like a mother.
This the first time we've gone into town together, isn't it, Noel?
Though...
This is basically my first time going to town...
Wow!
Oh! What's that?
It was completely different during the festival.
Now it's a calm, quiet town.
Ouch...
The first thing was a Nue. It's a roof ornament regional to Trois.
It's supposed to ward off evil spirits.
Second was a water fountain. It was modeled after the twelfth Helvetian Archduke, Akira Arcadia II.
We've arrived.
Oh! Those things?
Orders were to drive safely.
Thank you! I understand!
You really do know everything, Noel!
Hey, girls.
Are you coming in or not? Would you make up your mind?
You're blocking the store.
Oh, you're the lady I met during the festival!
Young lady.
Coercion. No.
You're as stiff-necked as ever, aren't you?
Then at least call me Naomi, okay?
Miss Naomi?
So the next shipment is next month?
And does that girl know?
Strange as ever, you girls.
I mean you're soldiers.
Excuse me!
What do you want?
That...
You've were obsessed with it when you first got here, too.
You like it?
Excuse me, but... Can I touch it?
A-flat.
This is a fish, isn't it? What kind is it?
Oh, what was it-
It's not a fish.
But...
That's a dolphin. An animal more like humans than fish.
A type of sea mammal from when the ocean still had animals.
The ocean? They lived in the ocean?
How wonderful.
That old gaffer's good at making stuff like that.
He's as much of a romantic as his face isn't.
You know the person who made this?
There's a factory a bit from town. That's where I get all this glassware.
I want to see them make it.
Don't worry.
About what?
We're heading there right now.
Oh, that's why. You had the factory make parts for the Takemikadzuchi.
Right. We also had Naomi collect old parts for us.
But you're just amazing, Noel.
You're fixing that complicated machine just like that.
Just like that?
I'm having a hard time just trying to remember the bugle signals.
It's not really that difficult.
Because machines won't cross you.
Noel-
Here you are! Your change is ¥2,750,000
What? Do we get that much?
No. Our change is ¥2.75.
Sharp as always, Noel.
Here's your change.
It really is.
You've been playing the morning bugle lately, right?
Yes. Sorry I'm still bad at it...
Not at all!
I like it!
How should I put it... I wake up completely.
No, I was just thinking that I need to learn so I don't cause problems for the townspeople.
No fair, Seiya!
Come and get me then!
I don't think-
Ow... Oh, sor-
Ha! You ran into someone!
I'm so very sorry!
Oh, you!
The girl at the festival!
That clumsy girl!
Thank goodness.
It looks like you're back to health.
You murderer!
Seiya, these two had nothing to do with your parents!
They're all the same! Soldiers disgust me!
Just get out of town already! Blowing that crappy bugle every single morning - you suck already!
Hey! Seiya!
I'm so very sorry.
That was so rude...
Not at all.
That boy was orphaned during the war.
That may be why, but when he sees soldiers, he just...
Noel...
I'm okay.
We are soldiers. That is the truth.
So...
Noel...
Sound of the Skies
You're right. We are soldiers.
When I enlisted, I took the Oath of Paradores.
I thought I knew what it meant, but...
Oh, what am I saying?
I knew it right from the start! I can't start doubting myself now!
That's right! I need to put time into it and get better!
It would be chaos without bugle signals!
You can see it.
Is that the glass factory?
It's amazing, Noel! I've never seen a building that big before!
So this one's no good either?
Is it some aberration?
The refraction should be just right.
I'm Kanata Sorami, a new recruit!
Pleased to meet you!
Ah.
And, um, I'm...
So about what time does it throw the error?
The seek time is about the same.
The distortion in the peripheral regions was far less,
but compared to last time the...
Sorry about that.
Once he gets down to something about work, he just won't care about anything else.
But that gaffer Carl is just amazing.
He's one of only five artisans in our nation with the title Meister.
He even won a competition in the capital and presented his work to the Archduke.
Maria! If you're talking, you're not working!
Right!
Sorry there, boss!
I don't even deserve the title, anyway.
I can't make anything like this.
What is that?
The lens for the Takemikadzuchi's optical sensor.
That's the original.
To restore the Takemikadzuchi,
I need two exactly like it. So I requested a duplicate here.
But it's not going well.
Even though they're this pretty?
This lens isn't just silicon oxide.
It's infused with sodium oxide and magnesium oxide.
This corrects chromatic and peripheral aberrations.
In other words, it corrects distortion in the refracted image.
But we don't know the distribution.
It's almost like a magic item from an ancient past, this thing.
I thought glass was just pretty,
but it's hard to make, isn't it?
In Seize, there are high-quality silica deposits,
so it always had small workshops where artisans produced their goods.
This used to be one of them.
But as the war grew more violent,
the need for glass for military uses increased.
So this workshop expanded during the war.
Kanata.
I like machines.
Yes.
But sometimes machines can hurt people.
In the past, the Takemikadzuchi probably
killed hundreds of people.
I think machines for killing people
really are scary.
Yes.
But,
maybe what's really scary isn't the machines,
but the people who used them.
I mean, look at this bugle.
It sounds like that when I play it,
but when Rio plays it, it sings beautifully.
Don't you think tanks are the same?
And a while ago,
Rio let me hear a song from the Takemikadzuchi.
It sang so beautifully.
I'm sure the Takemikadzuchi was a good tank.
Oh, right! Let's-
Noel...
Let her sleep.
She probably stayed up all night again.
Noel works so hard,
trying to fix the Takemikadzuchi.
I know.
This girl is a real artisan.
If she weren't, I would never have taken this crazy job.
Here. Put this on her.
Thank you very much!
By the way, you two went by Windmill, right?
How's Miss Naomi doing?
Yes.
She called the gaffer a wonderful romantic!
Or so it sounds. Isn't that nice, master gaffer?
Oh, shut up! Hurry and get back to work!
Whoa, he's mad! Back to work, back to work!
But is that old technology really that amazing?
It sure is.
But the boss always says,
"No matter how amazing it is, humans made this!"
"There is no reason why we can't make it!"
You think so too, right?
Yes...
I'd like to think so.
I see.
There sure is a huge difference between your bugling and Rio's trumpeting.
I'm always thinking about it. What should I do to bugle like Rio does?
I think I'm practicing as hard as I possibly can.
I mean, look at my lips, they're all swollen.
But...
No matter how much I try to play, the sound won't come out like Rio's.
Maybe I just don't have talent...
Young lady.
Yes!
Talent is the worst excuse for those who give up.
Hand that here.
I don't know anything about trumpets.
But there's one mistake the young ones always make.
Young lady,
are you trying to force the sound out?
I'm not trying to make it this shape.
The glass...
It wants to be like this.
Thank you very much, Meister Carl!
Let the sound echo the way it wants!
Morning.
Well.
Looks like the sun came out a bit earlier for her.
That young lady's quite an artisan too!
It's a good sound.
Sound?
The tone glass makes changes based on the type and amount of impurities infused into it.
Our ears can't hear the difference,
but someone with perfect pitch should.
Kanata can test each of the samples you've made
to find the one with the closest sound.
If she does, we might just...
Now then,
listen to their voices,
young lady!
Yes!
Noel has changed quite a bit since she came here.
You think?
Yes!
You did it! You did it Noel!
Thank you.
This is the first time I've seen Noel smile.
Love and friendship - put these feelings together
And sing of how important they are
I was so happy that I cried
It hurt so bad that I laughed
But that all just goes to show that I'm alive
Let's just take it easy
Everybody singing!
Can you tell me who you're asking to the dance?
You're just my friend!
Love and friendship - even though they might waver
I know, you know, we'll be happy
I want us to echo on forever
Can you count my precious hours?
All the usual words can't even describe it.
Our harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony
Next time: A Mountain Hike - The Ends of the Earth