We will now begin the second phase of the footman audition.
There is only one assignment in this second phase.
Please arrange the table nicely for afternoon tea.
Consider the occasion and mood, and arrange it accordingly.
Crap, I don't have a clue.
Aren't there supposed to be some guidelines?
It's important to understand how to set a table,
but use your taste to cover places you don't know.
How one little thing is placed could alter the appearance.
Being considerate and having good taste are important.
You have 10 minutes.
I will protect Maid Latte.
Please begin.
Which one should I choose?
Let's go, Usui!
Hold on.
What was that? Are you planning on killing me?
Who's the one that's going to enjoy the afternoon tea?
Huh?
Who are we setting the table for?
The person's going to be elegantly enjoying the tea at a British looking café, so...
It'll be a classy madam or rich girls!
Usui!
I went and got every cake out there.
This will be plenty, right?
Whee, so much.
It's almost like a cake buffet.
Not exactly elegant, huh?
How about using something like this?
Hey, that looks nice.
3 minutes remaining.
We have to set it up fast!
Mind if I choose?
I don't get why, but you look confident.
Put scones at the bottom rack of the cake stand.
Go find red jam and clotted cream for me.
Clotted?
Put packed sandwiches in the middle rack.
Packed?
And on the top rack, pick out small cakes from what you brought.
Which ones do you want?
Let's go with the tarts, then.
The choice of tea will be the light Earl Grey.
Why that out of all the possible choices?
It's a standard choice for afternoon tea.
30 seconds remaining.
As a final touch,
Arrange some small flowers.
It's all finished now.
It perfectly replicates British style afternoon tea time.
The knives are well polished, too.
The ladies will like the special touches.
It's a wonderful table.
Wow. Just how perfect are you?
What do you take me for?
A mysterious perverted alien from planet Pheromone.
Fine, I can live with that.
No, I mean, how do you-
We'll now have a short break.
Enjoy your moment of afternoon tea at your table.
Kanou-kun, we get to eat cake.
It's because you were so picky about the appearance!
I wanted to splurge more!
The appearance matters, so it was an obvious choice!
Hey, Usui. Why did you take part in this audition?
The famous net idol asked me to, so I had no choice.
You don't want to answer me seriously?
Because the masked suit looked interesting.
That actually doesn't sound like a lie.
You'll pay for making her sigh!
We won't forgive you for making Misa-
I'll go toss these two in the bushes.
An impressive performance,
considering his major handicap.
Pretty good, Usui.
There he is!
I knew it was Usui-san!
What a surprise to see you at a place like this.
You are who?
You're Usui-san, right?
Me name is Usui je Nye.
Study abroad student from England.
Kanou-kun, he's not Usui-san!
He's a totally different person!
We've got to tell Usui-san about him.
Yes...
It's a surprise, isn't it, Kanou-kun?
I'm totally shocked.
Let's head back now.
We had more cake at the table, right?
You're right. It's a waste to let them sit there.
Good grief, those guys.
Shiroyan!  Kurotatsu!
You took your time.
Yeah. I went to the bathroom. And because he was there, I went right into the men's room.
You look mad.
Are you angry that I said it's like a board?
Should I have said, "what magnificent pecs"?
No one's talking about that!
Then maybe you were nervous to be in the men's room and couldn't properly take care of yourself?
What kind of nonsense is that, you freak?!
What? Let go!
You're the mad one!
Maybe. Do you know why?
I think...
Okay.
Then let's make up.
If you overwork yourself, I'll be punishing you, Misaki.
We're not on some kind of show!
You made your point, too, Usui, so get off.
I'm glad you understood me, Misaki-kun.
Shut up! And I said you made your point, so get off of me!
Oh, good. They're still arguing, but looks like it didn't turn into a fight.
Stop smirking, you perv!
You're right.
We'll now begin phase three of the footman audition.
Usui... you know...
I'll do my best not to overdo it,
but I will still do my best until the end.
Aoi-chan! Subaru! Over here!
I'm sorry for the trouble you went through. Are you two okay?
Yes.
Aoi-chan! You're doing something like this again without telling me anything!
Yeah, yeah. I don't want to hear your lectures.
Gosh!
There's no way I'm going to sit around and watch Satsuki-san's place getting taken over
and replaced by something as uncute as a butler café.
Aoi-chan.
I'm supposed to make that place cuter in the future.
Aoi-chan... You plan on taking over my shop?
If you ask me, she's the one being reckless.
What is that girl thinking?
I'm glad. Those two made it back to where everyone is.
I know I'm being reckless.
Still, I can't turn back down now.
Not since I brought up the takeover.
Wow, I was really able to jam it in.
We're not here to play around, stupid Usui!
What is this paper for?
49?
Have you all received a paper with a number written on it?
The number I had each group draw is the order of audition.
The final phase is a customer relations simulation.
We will have you wait on the judges.
What we are looking for is elegance and loyalty, while handling tension.
How well can you improvise in a situation where you can't make mistakes.
This is the most important task.
Good luck, everyone.
Our pair switching reduced the number of pairs by one,
so we're dead last.
Usui je Nye-san, I'm all nervous. How are you?
Go away! He'll know it's me if he comes this close!
Usu...
...i...
Are they alright?
Is he conscious?
Wake up, both of you!
Usui.
Hey, Usui!
Usui! Usui!
Usui!
Usui...
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm fine, too, Misaki-kun.
You shouldn't move. You need to get first aid.
I'm fine.
Of course you're not.
Even for you, you fell while protecting me.
There's no way you're not hurt!
Misaki-kun.
The café's staff looks worried.
If you're fine, you should wave at them.
You...
Your arm's...
Are you really okay?
If not, I'll call a doctor.
That won't be necessary.
W-W-Welcome home, M-Ma-Mu-Mustard.
Next, number 49.
It's finally our turn.
That reaction earlier.
His left arm should be badly hurt.
And his right wrist, too.
Is it all right to let him go up those stairs like this?
But if I quit now...
We'll now begin your audition.
The customer and the judge will be me, Maki.
I look forward to your service.
Thank you.
It's started.
I knew that slit eye would come out.
This is the last thing they do, right?
Please. Let there be no more issues.
I hope they'll come back safe.
Welcome home, Master.
Let me take your bag for you.
Then your coat, too.
Let me take your coat, too.
Let me show you to your table.
That's right. I'll let Usui handle the guiding and talking.
I'll take on all the manual labor.
I can't increase Usui's burden when his arms are injured.
Did you need us, Master?
I'd like to order dinner now.
Yes, certainly!
Oh, and you.
I'd like to have something to read.
Can you bring about 10 books from over there?
Certainly.
Please enjoy, Master!
It's been bothering me for a while now, but are you covering for him?
There must be a reason.
Perhaps you don't want him to hold anything?
I'm sorry, it was not my place to inquire into your affairs.
But if he is incapable of working,
I shouldn't ask him to do anything, should I?
Crap...
Thank you for your kind thoughts, Master.
But we have no purpose without your commands.
Please ask for whatever you'd like.
I only drew attention to Usui...
But you have an issue, do you not?
For instance, an injury?
He is doing my work for me in order to leave me free to do other tasks.
I'd like to ask your permission for one thing.
So this "other task" is playing violin?
I never knew he could play.
But his wrist is...
Wow.
He's good.
I see. Well done.
It'll make the dinner taste even better.
I'll take the moment to enjoy the performance.
He's starting to show that he's in pain.
They're taking much longer than the others.
I hid my gender this long in order to protect the café.
I thought that this was the only way to handle the situation...
But...
That's enough.
Stop already!
Is something the matter?
I'm sorry! His hands are injured. He needs medical care.
You. Is that true?
Can't you tell from how pale he looks?
He hasn't admitted to it.
Which means, even if he is injured, he's showing his will to follow through with his work.
Just because he looks like he's in pain, you forced him to stop working in front of the Master?
You do want to support your coworker, don't you?
The "support" you speak of at your restaurant may be to watch your coworker collapse from fatigue.
But at our place, we "support" them so that they don't collapse.
Because when people support you, you want to support them, too.
Even if you trouble them, they will watch your back and allow you to concentrate on your work.
Because it's a shop like that, I can put my heart into my work, and be confident that the customers will enjoy it.
That's why I love that relaxing café.
Excuse me.
Misa-chan! Usui-kun!
I'm sorry! Could you call a taxi?!
We need to take him to the hospital now.
Okay. Hold on just one moment.
Look at how swollen his wrist is.
I'll go wet the handkerchief.
Chief!
I'm sorry.
Misa-chan. If Maid Latte moved and looked different from how it does today,
What would you do?
If you needed me,
Then I would go anywhere.
Thank you. I'm truly a fortunate manager.
What's making you stand in a place like this?
I told you not to be an idiot when you're in public.
I thought I knew what butlers and footmen should be like, so I never allowed them to compromise.
I was convinced that I could satisfy any customer if we perfectly recreated the British atmosphere.
Have you lost your vision because of what she said?
You're a real troublemaker.
Well, there are plenty of other locations.
Like the best one possible.
You don't mean that place that the Igarashi Foundation owns?
It's a place that was given to me.
There's no problem.
You'll probably learn a lot if you leave that place alone.
Thank you very much, President.
You do your best now.
Hey, that Trio is freaking me out more than usual.
What? She's zoning out too.
You have to forgive them, Aoi-chan.
We just overcame Maid Latte's greatest crisis.
Speaking of which, can you explain what happened?
Why did they suddenly decide not to purchase this place?
The Chief didn't tell you?
Maki-san's café is going to open elsewhere.
Then he shouldn't have brought up the takeover stuff in the first place.
Hey, where is she?
She?
You mean Misa-chan!
She's finally talking!
Misa-chan must be at-
What in the world is this place?
It's my house.
So it would seem.
What? You came to visit me?
Something like that.
Where's your family?
They aren't here. I live alone.
Excuse me.
You didn't just move in or anything like that, right?
I've been living here since I started going to high school.
Why did you come alone?
You don't mind me doing things to you?
I knew you had a fever!
So it's true that you forced them to let you leave the hospital!
Go to bed!
I'm going to borrow a towel, ice and so forth.
No, I'll do it.
You stay in bed!
Ayuzawa, really-
Please stay in bed, you idiot!
Please...
Let yourself heal.
You haven't called your family at all?
It's unnecessary.
Why did you leave the hospital so quickly?
It was boring.
Are you eating well?
You've overcooked it, the rice's turned into a white soup.
Prez, so you're-
Yes! I suck at cooking! You got a problem with that?!
If you don't want it, then don't eat! I'll eat it all myself!
I'll eat.
But I can't use my right hand, so feed me.
By the way, I'm sensitive to hot food, just like cats.
I'm speechless.
I never knew there was a way to totally kill the natural flavor of food.
Shut up and eat!
Hey, if you can eat all that,
then I guess I shouldn't have worried.
How can I leave leftovers?
It's the first time I've had Ayuzawa's home cooking.
You should get changed, you must be soaked with sweat.
Actually, you can't unbutton yourself with that hand, can you?
What are you looking at?!
You're like a punk that gets pissed at people who make eye contact.
Shut up! Look outside the window or something!
Yes, yes.
I owe him one again.
He's mean to me, sexually harasses me, and makes me think he's screwed up,
But he's always there for me when it counts.
On the other hand, I can't do anything.
I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm totally depending on you.
I've wanted to repay the favors you've done for me, but I can't at all.
In the end, this is all I can do.
I'm so hopeless.
You're so sly, Ayuzawa.
In what way?!
I'm actually relying on you quite a bit, too.
You're lying!
No, I'm not.
Someone like you is perfect for me.
"Perfect"? Who do you think you are?
Stupid Usui.
What's up with this?
You piss me off.
That wasn't fair, Prez.
What wasn't?
Don't blame me for everything.
Stop being ambiguous!
Kanou-kun! How come you passed the audition and I didn't?
I don't know.
We're a pair, so why did I fail?
Is that Usui-san standing over there?
Or is it Usui je Nye-san?
What's wrong, Yukimura-kun?
Oh, so it was Usui-san.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Yukimura, are you sure you want to ask this perv for a favor?
But I want to be a good brother,
for my sister's sake.
Ah ha ha ha! I'm Usui je Nye.
What? When did they switch?
Where did Usui-san go?
Help him out, Usui.
Next week will be about shooting a promotion video for Aoi-sama.
In other words, it's a double header
about Yukimura's sister and Aoi-chan.