so ra no wo to
The brilliant glow of this sky, does it carry right into your heart?
The melody you heard in your dream, it plays like the silence
Even if your hands are still far from that dream,
Come now and remember that kindly voice,
Someone was there singing for you, singing those chords of happiness
Sound of the sky, echo on high, break through that overwhelming sadness
Everything that shines in your eyes
Is part of the real world
Even your tears can't leave you here to stay forever
In this light pouring down onto you, play tomorrow's song
I'm going to wet myself...
Phone Duty - Declare a State of Emergency
Headquarters Hotline Wiring Maintenance Confirmation for Sudden High-Priority Emergency Contact and Direction Mission?
That's a really long name.
It's an extremely important mission.
If we fail, we'll all receive reprimands.
Depending on the situation, a level-one security alert may be issued,
and all forces in the area placed on emergency standby.
That's right. It's a heavy responsibility.
Wh- What kind of mission is it?
Well, you see...
Phone duty.
You know how this is the hotline connected to headquarters in the capital, right?
Has it ever rung?
No.
That's right. Thankfully.
So this mission...
Right. It's a good thing that the phone hasn't rung,
but it's not a good thing if it doesn't ring when necessary.
So once every six months, they test the line to see if it works.
And that's the?
Headquarters... Um...
Come on, at least remember these things.
Headquarters Confirmation High-Priority Emergency- Wait...
No, it's the Headquarters Hotline Wiring Confirmation Emergency for...
Headquarters Hotline Wiring Maintenance Confirmation for Sudden High-Priority Emergency Contact and Direction Mission.
There.
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Let me take care of this mission!
I've always wanted to try talking on a telephone!
Is it that exciting?
It works pretty much the same way as the intercom in the Takemicaduchi.
It's just that the other side is far away.
But that's the amazing part!
You can talk to people so far away!
It's wonderful!
Well, it is a strange feeling to talk to people you can't see.
But once you get used to it, it's no big deal.
The only problem is that we don't know when the call will come in.
Do you still want to do it?
Of course!
Alright.
Then you'll be stuck to the phone for the entire day.
This is Private Kanata Sorami of Platoon 1121 of the Army of the Republic of Helvetia.
And when the call is over, we put the phone back the way it was.
Alright.
Fil- Fili-
Oh, you're just so cute.
Filicia!
What are you doing? It hurts just to watch.
The train might leave before we get there.
The train?
We have some documents we need to rush to headquarters.
Klaus doesn't come until next week.
So we're taking them to the station.
Keep an eye on that phone now.
Yes!
If you don't answer, they might even think we've been attacked.
Keep both eyes on it.
Leave it to me!
Hey.
Yes, sir!
I wasn't sleeping!
Not a single wink of it!
Have you seen Noël around?
She wasn't in her room.
Um...
The hangar again, then.
Well, that's fine.
So Kanata, what do you want for lunch?
I- I- I'll take care of it.
Don't worry about it.
It's my turn to make it.
But...
Hey. Why do you and Kureha never let me cook whenever it's my turn?
I cooked all the time before you two got here.
Well, um...
It shouldn't taste bad.
Well, it doesn't taste as bad as it looks...
What was that?
No, it has a very distinct flavor! It's wonderful!
Isn't it?
Then I guess I'll put even more of my love into it today.
Hey! Anyone home?
Yes!
Rio, it's Miss Naomi.
I'm working.
But I need to stick to the phone.
Hey! You've got a customer here!
Fine. Guess I'll get it.
Yeah! I'll be right there!
I don't want to eat sandwiches with cutting board in them anymore...
Are these...
Go ahead and drink. It's apple cider.
It's handmade from the farm where we get our apple juice.
So it's like a cousin of the calvados we make?
What?
Oh, right. She found out.
Two should be enough for tonight, right?
What? Oh, yeah, sure.
Tonight?
There's a merchants' guild meeting tonight.
We always like to provide refreshments as thanks for everything they do.
Remember that.
Okay.
Oh, come on! They did everything they could to hide it from you too!
How'd you find out?
W- Well, um...
Well...
If I get the chance, maybe I can...
Miss Naomi, how would you like to have lunch with us?
What? You want me to attend it?
Look, everyone wants a proper explanation from the military for the news in this week's paper.
News?
About how the peace treaty conferences aren't going smoothly.
They aren't?
They're squabbling over paying reparations and drawing borders.
Everyone knows these things always take longer than they should.
It's more like those old geezers in the guild want to see you again.
Ever since you played the part of one of the Maidens of the Fire at the Water-Casting festival,
you've been gaining quite a fanbase.
What a bother. Seriously.
So, there. It looks like I'll have to attend the meeting.
I'm one of the Maidens of the Fortress now, heart and soul!
I will complete this mission by myself!
Understood. It's all yours.
Yes!
Kanata, I'd like to give you this.
Sorry they're not new, they were mine before.
Aren't these... trumpet-
Wonderful! Wonderful! Wonderful!
Thank you very much!
Your bugling's gotten a lot better recently, you know.
It's a reward for practicing so hard.
And with those, you won't fall asleep.
And...
This is C...
D...
E...
F...
G...
A.
I guess summer's just about over.
Iliya?
Maybe I drank too much.
Noël! Are you there?
It's raining! The laundry is getting wet!
The courtyard is within the field of operations!
Kanata!
Come out to play!
Coming!
Kanata!
Come out to play!
Help me!
Sound of the Skies
Thank you so much.
No, I'm glad that your laundry is fine.
So am- I mean-
Sorry to make you help me after you came all this way!
Oh, not at all. I'm sorry for the sudden visit.
I must return to Treize tomorrow, so I came to say goodbye.
It's an honor, Father...
Even though soldiers don't need goodbyes.
That's not true at all, Seiya.
I've heard that Seiya has been disrespectful to you in the past.
I thought I would apologize for that as well.
Are the others home?
They're all out at the moment.
Was it... Rio? And the black-haired one?
Yes.
I see.
I would have liked to pay my-
Oh, is this book... yours?
What is it?
It's a book for the trumpet.
Rio gave it to me.
I see. I thought so.
Oh, no. I'm sorry. I was just talking to myself.
Are you here alone?
That's right.
I'm on a...
Headquarters Hotline Wiring Maintenance Confirmation for Sudden High-Priority Emergency Contact and Direction Mission
right now.
In other words,
you're waiting for this to ring?
Yes.
But I've never used one before.
I'm kind of nervous.
Like whether I can speak properly.
Then would you like to practice?
So Sister Yumina is attending the guild meeting too?
Yes, she's gone to collect donations from the members of the guild.
Here you go. Drink up.
Yummy!
Isn't it? Drink up, Seiya.
Fine, I'll drink your stupid cider, but don't think I'll like you any more for it.
What are you making?
Do you two know?
A phone!
Is this really the same?
It is. It's a phone.
The kids love them, so sometimes I make them.
Go ahead, Seiya.
A phone...
Hello?
Amazing! Amazing, Seiya!
I can hear you!
No, when you pick up a phone, first you say, "Hello."
That's how you use a phone.
H- Hello?
Hello.
It's amazing! I can...
I really can hear his voice!
You can practice a bit with that.
Yes!
Um... This is-
It's "Hello."
H- Hello.
This is Private Kanata Sorami of Platoon 1121 of the Army of the Republic of Helvetia.
Yes. Very good.
It is an honor to receive a call from you at this time.
So, um...
Wait, little bird!
Mishio!
Mishio, don't-
What happened?
The phone!
Excuse me... Are our priest and our-
Yes?
My myriad gods...
And what is this?
You only paid a visit to thank them and say goodbye.
And instead, you played and made a mess!
No dinner tonight.
Yes, ma'am.
Me, too?
It's all clean now.
Thank you.
But your clothes are soaked.
That's okay. I have some right over-
Oh, I know what we can do!
This is...
Embarrassing...
Not at all!
Ah, how dazzling you are!
Thank you, Sister Yumina.
I'll wash them before I return them.
No, you can have them!
They're too big for the kids,
and I can't imagine anyone who would look so dazzling in them!
I'm sorry, Kanata.
Will you play with us again?
Yes.
Come back again soon, okay, Seiya?
I- I...
Maybe when I'm bored.
Then, please excuse us.
May the blessings of all be upon you.
Th- Thank you very much.
Now then, I need to clean up.
I forgot...
The bathroom...
I'm going to wet myself...
Someone... Please...
Please...
Seriously, those old geezers!
What happened to you, Kana-
Rio... Please...
Save me... Please...
What's wrong, Kanata?
I can't hold it...
I'm going to wet myself!
Hurry up and do it! You'll get sick!
Thank you very much!
She was holding it in this whole time?
She really does do whatever she's told.
What's wrong?
I'm okay!
Kanata!
No... I can't...
I can't move at all!
Seriously, these people have horrible timing.
Hello?
This is Master Sergeant Rio Kazumiya of Platoon 1121 of the Army of the Republic of Helvetia.
It's been a long time.
I heard we would be confirming your line, so I insisted -
Are you running away?
No!
I am not running away!
I know.
You simply haven't forgiven me.
After this long. What do you want now?
Please! I want you to save this country! To save Helvetia!
Good morning, Kanata.
Noël, have you been in there since morning?
Yes. I sleep well in the bathroom.
No...
We're ho- my, Kanata, what cute clothes you're wearing!
What are you two doing in the hallway?
Kanata fell down. Can't get up.
Is she hurt?
Then why don't you just stand up?
Guess we can't help it.
You're just so spoiled.
No... Don't...
One, two...
No!
Love and friendship - put these feelings together
And sing of how important they are
I was so happy that I cried
It hurt so bad that I laughed
But that all just goes to show that I'm alive
Let's just walk it slowly
Everybody singing!
Just tell me a bit of what you think
You're just my friend!
Love and friendship - even though they might waver
I know, you know, little happy
I want us to echo on forever
Can you hear my precious note?
All these words that there are can't even describe it.
Our harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony
Next time: After a Typhoon - Illusion and Reality.