neiki yori sotto yoake ga kuru
Dawn comes softer than a sleeping breath
寝息よりそっと　夜明けが来る
kimi no yume wa ima mori wo kakeru
Your dream runs through the forest now
君の夢は今　森を駆ける
mezamete akari wo sagasu shigusa
You wake up and stir to find the light
目覚めて　灯りを探すしぐさ
nakushita nara mitsuketeageyou
If you've lost it, I'll find it for you
なくしたなら　見つけてあげよう
kimi to boku no mirai ni kakureteiru
It's hidden in our future
君と僕の　未来に隠れている
saa koko he te wo tsunaidara
Now if we joined hands
さあここへ　手をつないだら
hodokenai yo kimi to tooku he
we would go far away without letting go
ほどけないよ　君と遠くへ
haruka na hi no kioku ni saita
In the memory of a far off day
遥かな日の　記憶に咲いた
aoi kuni no miru story
the story of the blue country bloomed
青い国を　見るストーリー
kagayaku hitomi
Shining eyes
輝く瞳
sono utagoe
Your singing voice
その歌声
tsutaeyou
Let's share it
伝えよう
Is Lawrence going to be alright?
Quite frankly, it'll probably be tough.
I doubt he'll be able to compete effectively with so little pyrite.
All we can do is pray that Deanna's assistant comes.
If he sells a superficial amount,
all it'll do is get people's hopes up that there's more to buy.
And if that happens, the price will just rise even higher.
Doesn't that mean Amarty can pretend he's about to sell in order to bait Lawrence?
Exactly.
You're pretty good.
Where's Horo?
He's a fool that gets agitated easily.
You can just relax.
Horo...
Amarty...
Don't be stupid!
Another buy!
Just how much will it rise?
Wolf and Trustworthy God
It's gone up that much?
I'm guessing it'll go up another 20% by this afternoon.
I wish I had bought more of it instead of giving up.
It's still slowly rising in value, isn't it?
If I remember right, Amarty currently has 800 silver worth of pyrite.
And when it goes up another 20%?
It would be 960 coins worth.
If that happens, he'll sell his assets on the spot,
scrape around for the remaining 40 coins,
and definitively seal the contract.
All before the poison of selling on credit takes effect.
The poison of selling on credit?
Still nothing?
Where's Deanna's assistant?
If she's been with Amarty this whole time, Horo may have attained quite a lot of information.
No way!
This is it!
To think it'd come this far.
No, it'll still go up!
This is bad...
The one who made a deal with Deanna must have been Amarty after all!
But...
even if Amarty wins, Lawrence gets paid, right?
That's right.
So as a merchant, it would be a win for him.
But it's also a huge loss.
Because no matter how much he pays, he'll never be able to buy it back.
Pyrite?
Are you after the alchemists' stockpile?
Didn't you make the contract after finding a buyer?
Unfortunately I didn't have the time.
Someone has already bought some.
I'll handle the negotiations.
Where will I be able to contact you tomorrow?
In front of the mineral merchant's stall at the marketplace.
No good, huh?
Another buy!
You're going to trade me for 1000 silver, right?
Say something!
He's looking for her as well?
A sale!
Is that Amarty?
Excuse me!
Let me through please!
U-Um...
It wasn't him?
Another buy!
It's going fast.
Are things going to start moving now?
Time to sell?
No, buying's still the way to go.
Horo!
Oh, it's you.
S-Sorry.
There's a patron at the store saying he'd like to pay for barley in stones.
How much?
250 coins worth.
Be as quick as possible.
Yes.
A sale!
No, I need this to rise more.
Amarty bought 500 coins worth of pyrite from Lawrence.
Not in real goods, but with a certificate.
The goods change hands this evening.
Do you know what that means?
If the price looks like it'll rise, the certificate will sell,
but if the price looks like it'll drop, it probably won't sell.
Exactly.
Nobody would deal in something so dangerous.
If the pyrite returns to its original value as a rock,
the 500 silver certificate becomes as worthless as garbage.
The person with the certificate at the end loses.
Right.
That's the poison of buying on credit.
Horo?
Hurry, Lanto.
Another purchase!
An ore purchase!
It's too high.
And there are fewer waiting to buy.
If I sold all I have now...
I'm selling!
If I had that 400 silver worth of pyrite from Deanna...
the winds would definitely blow my way.
If she came now...
Mr. Lawrence!
Sorry for taking so long.
250 silver of it.
Is something wrong?
Ah, no.
To be perfectly safe,
I should wait for Deanna's assistant...
But...
will she come?
That assistant.
That's right.
I'd only just given up on that chance.
If I'm going to take this gamble...
Now's my only chance!
What happened?
Someone placed an order.
The winds have changed.
I have no choice but to wait for Deanna's assistant now.
It's Amarty!
Did he discover the poison behind the credit?
She'll come.
I'm sure she'll come.
There's no time, regardless.
Please.
Quickly.
Are you Lawrence?
You are Lawrence, correct?
Ah, yes.
I bring a message from Deanna.
Let's hear it.
"Negotiations have failed."
"They weren't willing to sell after all."
That is Deanna's message.
She apologizes for not meeting your expectations.
Excuse me.
I've been looking for you, Horo.
...rence...
Lawrence.
Lawrence!
Lawrence!!
Oh, sorry.
Sorry about today.
I put you through a lot of hassle.
Could you pass this onto Mark?
Tell him the plan failed.
But, well...
I do get 1000 silver coins from Amarty.
As a merchant I should be delighted.
Now here's your share.
Lawrence!!!
Are you giving up?!
The master always tells me that merchants should never give up easily!
The god of wealth doesn't come to those who pray,
but to those who don't know when to give up!
I was told if I said this to you,
I'd be beaten to the ground.
But I'll say it!
I've felt it since I first saw her!
I LOVE HORO!
So...
You're right, I do want lay down a beating.
I really want to beat...
myself.
I'd forgotten.
People who don't give up are the kind who realize things that nobody else believes.
And I'm one of them.
Merchants make a plan, theorize an outcome, and compare it with reality when doing trade.
If I buy this, the outcome will be like this.
If I sell this, the outcome will be like that.
That kind of theory is important.
Frankly, there are any number of theories you could come up with.
That's why if you speculate too much, you'll soon become lost.
All types of trade will start to seem very risky.
So in order not to become lost, we keep a guidepost.
That is the one thing a merchant requires.
If that guidepost is trustworthy, we should take even the craziest ideas,
and maybe just believe in them.
Once I sell the stones, spread that rumor I asked you to please.
Y-Yes!
Do you believe in God?
You came again, eh?
I'm selling.
I'm selling too.
Fool.
Sorry.
Unlike someone I know, that woman was quite a mature beauty, wasn't she?
In the end, Amarty didn't make that much of a loss.
The mental blow was far greater.
This is your punishment for trying to steal someone else's woman.
That's what happened after.
I wanted to leave him in a poorer state than that.
I'll never forgive that guy for what he said.
Don't ask what it was.
That's fine by me.
So?
I hope you don't think that settles all of this, do you?
I'm sorry.
Do you really understand where you went wrong?
Yes.
I do.
...probably.
Taking matters into my own hands after Amarty made that contract with you was completely arrogant of me.
Wasn't it?
My biggest mistake was not trusting you.
Those white feathers were supposed to be a sign that you were the one who'd bought the pyrite from Deanna.
But in my panic, when I saw Amarty go talk to the vendor, I thought it was a trap you had laid for me.
What do you mean by that?
Well...
I thought you were maybe trying to get me to sell prematurely.
I really thought you had completely gone over to his side.
But... I guess I was wrong.
You were trying to tell me that Amarty already had enough, so I should sell quickly.
But I was confused and overthinking everything.
And before that, with the marriage certificate...
You signed your name on it,
but that was just to get me angry enough to confront you.
Right?
Back then I was waiting there on the second fl...
Never mind.
Continue.
You once said in Rubinhaigen,
"Don't beat around the bush."
"Come out with what you truly feel."
"Problems are solved much faster if you yell at each other."
I misunderstood you from the start.
When you got confused over Yoitsu,
the last thing you said...
I'm sorry.
I thought you were rejecting me.
But, in truth...
that was you coming to your senses.
Right?
You fool!
This is exactly what they mean when they say it's hard to tell a poor thinker from a sleeping one!
Not only did you ruin the plan I painstakingly put together,
but you also thought I was treating you as my enemy?
And on top of that, you just couldn't let go of the deal with that kid!
It's true that we only met recently.
Even so, I didn't think the bond we had was so shallow.
Is that just my wishful thinking?
Or do you really...
I want to continue traveling with you.
My life until now has been all about business.
And I intend to keep it that way.
That's why...
When it comes to life outside business, think of me as a bit of a slow guy.
Even so, I want to travel with you.
Then...
What am I to you?
I can't express it in words.
What kind of dry line is that?
You like dried jerky, right?
I hate it.
Tell me one thing.
How did you persuade Deanna to sell you the pyrite?
I more or less figured out your plan from everything Amarty told me.
Though I must say I was impressed by what you came up with.
So, you called her Deanna, right?
I actually went there for a different purpose.
For a different purpose?
It might be better to say for help.
I found her house from the scent on the letter.
Though, the place carried a strong stink like you'd find near hot springs.
I'll bet that was harsh for you.
I asked her to make up a story that Yoitsu is still around somewhere, and pass it onto you.
But all that woman did was get all the facts she could out of me and ignore my request.
That so?
Just as I'd finished embarrassing myself explaining the situation,
you showed up.
Is anyone in?
Afterwards, that damn woman...
She came up with her own plan.
She decided it would be a good idea to test your resolve, as if she knew it all.
So that's why she said that...
Do your best.
I also heard every word of your stupid question.
Are there any legends of pagan gods and humans becoming mates?
Plenty.
It seems there are a lot of these stories of humans and gods mating.
If that's how you feel, then I don't mind, but...
Will you be gentle to me?
Or not.
I'm not in the mood after talking to that woman.
Did you notice she isn't human?
Really?
There were lots of feathers scattered around the room, right?
Those are hers.
She's actually a bird bigger than you.
She fell for a traveling priest, and spent a long time with him working to build a church.
But the priest grew suspicious of her since she never grew old no matter how much time passed.
You can guess what happened afterwards.
I want to return to my homeland.
Even if it's no longer there.
What will you do when we arrive?
Humans do some amazing things.
Yeah, they do.
I wouldn't mind if you were as fiery as that doll.
I'll manage somehow when I get drunk.
Who's going to take care of me if you get drunk?
You fool!
soshite koi suru bokutachi wa
The two of us who fell for each other
そして恋する僕たちは
ai no temae de surechigau
missed each other just before love
愛の手前ですれちがう
tsutaetai noni damarikomu
I want to tell you but I keep quiet
伝えたいのに黙り込む
Take me, take me
to the perfect world
sakamichi wo sora he noboreba
If you climb the hill towards the sky
坂道を空へのぼれば
wakareyuku suisei no mizuumi
there flows the comet river
わかれゆく彗星の湖
mikansei na bokutachi dakara
Because we're incomplete
未完成な僕たちだから
kizutsukezu ni irarenai
we can't avoid hurting each other
傷つけずにいられない
dakishimetekuretara
If you will embrace me
抱きしめてくれたら
fureaeru ki ga suru
I feel like we'll touch
触れ合える気がする
dakishimeaetara
If you can embrace me
抱きしめ合えたら
ai suru hito ha kitto soba ni iru
Your beloved will surely be by your side
恋する人はきっとそばにいる
taisetsu na mono wa itsumo soba ni aru
Those important to you will always be by your side
大切なものはいつもそばにある
Next episode: Wolf and Playful Days
Wolf and Playful Days