douka please can you keep my secret?
Please, please can you keep my secret?
kira kira to kagayaku miraa
The mirror, shining so brilliantly.
watashi wa donna fuu ni utsutteiru no
I wonder how do I look in it.
hora hora to temaneku mirai
The future, beckoning me forward.
kore kara donna koto ga okoru no
What will happen from now, I wonder?
me ni mieteiru mono ga subete dewa nai kara
Because what we see is not everything.
mugamuchuu da that's all right
I'm losing myself but that's all right.
mayowanaide I wanna try
I will now try not to waver.
jibun no kimochi ni massugu de itai
I want to be true to my heart.
dakedo hitotsu ya futatsu gurai
But even I have a secret or two.
dare ni mo baretakunai
That I want to keep to myself.
naishotte aru mono dakara
mune ga chotto itamu my secret
That's why my secret makes my heart aches slightly.
Is last month's financial report done?
Also, confirm the location for the next major cleanup-
Misaki-chan!
What business do you have here?
Let's play!
This isn't an amusement park!
Why is Takumi here already?!
And you! How many times do I have to tell you?!
Well, it's relaxing here...
Go to the library if you want to read!
The student council room is not a place for fun!
I often see him hanging around her recently... Who is he?
Ah, you mean Shintani? I heard he was her childhood friend.
She took care of him when they were kids.
I thought I saw dogs glaring at each other just now...
What are you saying? Pets aren't allowed in school!
You're imagining things.
No, that's not what I mean...
As I thought, she's an amazing person!
Melting things away with Latte Magic
I'm hungry.
Hinata, do you still have any bread crusts?
Bread crusts taste surprisingly good!
Give me some, too!
So you guys finally realised how great bread crusts truly are?!
How many times must I tell you to abstain from eating in class?
Misaki-chan, do you want some, too?
No thanks!
Hey, what about that, have you told her?
Oh, the part time job?
P-Part time job?!
So Misaki-chan is Misa-chan?!
This is where you're working part time?!
What 'bout the part time job?
Oh, he started working at a petrol station.
Oh, that.
Don't worry. I'm not gonna tell anyone about your job.
What's the hush-hush over there?
It's nothing!
Ok, I need to leave for my job!
So, give us the dirt.
How's things between you two?
You guys didn't have much chance to converse properly at outdoor education.
Though, it seemed like you guys got closer after that!
Don't tell me... Did something happen between you and him?
Nothing happened! He's just my childhood friend!
Night arrives...
I'm back!
I'm so hungry!
To Hinata
Oh yeah, I forgot to call him
Hey grandpa! Hinata here-
HEY!
What were you thinking?! You didn't even call us, Hinata!
You don't need to be that angry...
Granny's worried sick, too!
I'm doing fine here! You don't need to worry about me!
I'm glad I came here!
Did you manage to find her?
Yeah. I found her almost immediately.
She's at the same school, even the same class, as me!
This... must be fate, right?
Magical Maids!
An anime-cosplay event?
Yeah! The producers gave us permission to do it after seeing our pictures!
Especially you! You're just perfect for Rose!
Magical Maids...
You haven't watched it yet? It's airing on Sunday mornings.
There's no one else that can play Mimosa but me!
You don't need to!
Anyway, take this!
I'll lend you these DVDs, so try to get into the role of your character.
There's this much?!
It's the 4th season already.
There's about 40 volumes in this season alone.
You don't need to watch them all. Just watch episode 1,
And episode 12 and 13.
Also, this volume's pretty popular as well, so I recommend this!
That aside, what happened after Hinata found out about your secret?
I don't know if I can answer that...
Did Usui become jealous?
Speaking of Usui, he's not here today. I didn't see him in the kitchen.
Doesn't matter!
He's just a perverted alien!
Thank you very much!
Shintani! You can leave now!
Okay!
Remember to tell me what shift you want next month!
Sorry but... I might need to attend supplementary classes...
What?! You're having problems with your studies?
You gave me a shoulder massage, so shall I tutor you?
It won't really help much.
What are you saying, you idiot?!
Need a ride back? I have an extra helmet.
It's fine, I need to make a stop today.
Strange...
I'm sure it was somewhere around here...
This persimmon looks yummy!
Wait! Be good and don't roll away!
Oh my!
I wanna dance in the summer!
Oh no! Master's been cursed with black magic and made to dance!
Let's go, Lily!
Got it!
Mop Missiles!
Kids shows nowadays are rather... amazing, aren't they?
Mop missiles, huh... There's also rag bombs...
Ah, Mom's back.
Ah, there's a man I've never seen before.
No, this is...
Maybe he'll be our new father?
Suzuna-chan!
You've gotten so big! You were so tiny back then!
Let's go, Hamburger-kun!
I was waiting for that, Cheese-chan!
Super Mega Cheese Hamburger!
What the hell was that?
It's a part from an anime we watched together!
I know that, but still...
This won't do. You don't look tasty at all.
You were much bigger and juicier last time.
Eh?! What should I do then?
We'll lose to Tsukimi Burger-kun like this, right, Sis?
What should I do, Misaki-chan?!
Don't ask me! Why are you here?!
He picked up some persimmons I dropped.
We met by pure coincidence.
Here, this too!
Thank you!
Wait, didn't this happen before...?
Thank you for the meal!
You've gotten a lot handsomer, Hinata.
Am I manlier, too?
Yes! You've grown sturdy.
You still have that habit of eating persimmons you've picked up, though.
Well, I didn't know it was you who dropped them!
So, what were you doing near my house?
Ah, I was looking for something.
You-kun, don't tell me that you still like Sis?
Suzuna! What was that for?!
W-What do you mean by that?!
You-kun's still as easy to read as he was back then.
Back then?!
No way! I was shy and kept a low profile!
No one should have known!
Yeah... You kept staring at Misaki-chan.
Even you knew about it?!
You were looking for our house, right?
You shouldn't stalk people, you know?
No, that's not it. I was looking for the cherry tree.
I thought it might still be there.
Cherry tree? You mean the one you fell from that one time?
Oh! You remembered?!
Hey! It's dangerous!
You-kun!
Are you okay?!
I'm fine.
Geez, you're such a troublemaker, You-kun!
Don't go climbing trees again, and make sure to follow me, okay?
I got it, Misaki-chan.  I promise.
I'll follow you for life, Misaki-chan!
You-kun!
That's not right! That part happened in the hospital, didn't it?
You remember it that well...
I got it, Misaki-chan.
I promise to follow you for life, Misaki-chan!
Also, that's not what I meant by follow me!
But, no matter where it happened, the promise was real!
This drink tastes rather nice.
Hot tea
I wonder if that cherry tree is still there...
Magical Girls Day
It's finally Sunday!
Of course, we'll spend our time here today!
I'm looking forward to today's event!
I've done my research since Ikkun told us about it!
Me too!
It was my first time watching early morning shoujo anime!
Welcome back, masters.
Get ready to be melted away by today's Latte Magic!
Oh no! Master's been cursed with black magic!
This is where Misa... No, Rose shows up!
Let's go, Lily!
Got it!
Kariron Popuron Instant Cure!
With this, you'll be fine!
Take your time and enjoy!
That was a perfect "Magical Maids" cosplay!
The similarity to the original is just amazing!
I only watched it once, but I liked it!
Especially the two main characters. It's just as you predicted!
But I didn't expect Misa-chan to do this much for us!
I thought she was gonna ignore us again...
That's fine by me, though.
That error you made when calling her name is unforgivable!
Do you know that?!
I got it...
We're going to make today's event a complete success!
Satsuki, I'm just perfect for Mimosa's character, aren't I?
No. You're a boy in middle school, Aoi-kun!
I won't let you go out to the floor.
Even when I'm this suitable for the role?
An extra order, a Witch Parfait!
No-nam-cha-ruru-tte!
Mam-pu-kan!
Why the diet spell? Though I answered you instinctively...
You even remembered the core spells that are never really used?
You didn't even know anything about this before...
I watched all of the DVDs.
All of them?
It took a lot of time, though.
I spent all of last night finishing them up.
You even pulled an all-nighter for this?!
Huh? He's coming today as a customer...
I thought he was already a part of the staff...
What are you gonna do? Are you gonna do the magic girl routine in front of him?
Welcome back, master.
Melt away with Latte Magic today!
He seems different today...
Normally, he would have replied smugly...
So he really is bothered by Hinata...
I don't really get it, but it's time for Mimosa to-
You stay here.
Sorry for the wait!
Sorry for the wait, miladies!
How was today's special, the Magical Miracle Parfait?
I enjoyed it. It was miraculous.
Do you really mean that?
The girls in the kitchen wanted to hear your opinion.
Use a pointed spoon when putting the quenelles on top.
I'm sure they'll get better with some practice.
Quenelles,
Spoon,
and um...
Quene- Pointed spoon, right?
For this parfait, the frills around the rose decoration was nicely done.
However, I think the sponge cake inside should be a little firmer...
That's quite a lot of opinions you have there...
Shall I write them down on a memo?
Really, just who are you, Usui?
You're not just another ordinary guy, that I know.
I'll take that as a compliment.
A certain someone has been calling me this,
so just think of me as another perverted alien.
Misaki-chan! I've come to play!
Shintani!
Why are you here?!
Rather, you knew about Misa-chan working here?!
Oh, you guys are here to see her as well?
You're wrong!!
It's not Misaki-chan, but Misa-chan!
That's the law here in Maid Latte!
You're here too, eh?
Today's event is not an all-you-can-eat. Are you fine with that?
So that is Hinata...
It's getting interesting, isn't it? It's all that dimwit's fault.
You two, chill out!
Oh yeah! Time to use the patch-up spell!
Ukinpa, Wakunpa, Let's be friends!
Huh?
That's not strong enough! They need some of Mimosa's Boys Love Spell-
You're not allowed to go out, Aoi.
Sorry for the wait!
It's the Magical Russian Roulette!
I've been waiting for this!
This is the special event today!
Okay, one of these contains a magical juice.
The one who drinks it has to put on a straight face, and I have to guess who drank it.
If you beat me, you can choose either a specially-made coaster, or a commemoration photo-
The photo, of course!
Okay, I got it.
I'll cast a spell right now. Don't hold back on me, 'kay?
Wait, what kind of spell?
A spell that renders you incapable of lying~
Dorinpa Dorunpa! Now you can't lie!
What's wrong?!
Get hold of yourself!
T-This juice is... no joke.
The one who drank the magical juice is Master Kurotatsu!
Never mind, give me some water...!
Kurotatsu!
Have a safe journey, masters!
Let's just pull back for today!
W-Water...
Kurotatsu!!
That looks interesting! I wanna try it, too!
What spell would you like, master?
How about... a spell to beat my rival?
It's pointless to beat me by magic.
He's got a point! You gotta win it by yourself!
Besides, the love spell is a double-edged sword.
Even if it succeeds, there will be a price to pay.
Stop! I don't like scary stories!
I'm shivering just from listening to the scary consequences!
No one said anything about them...
Thanks for the meal.
What's wrong?
No...
Have a safe trip, master.
Have a safe trip, master!
Misa-chan!
I've got a spell that I'd like you to cast on me.
A Seeking spell!
Seeking spell?
You know, that cherry tree!
Hurry, cast on me!
I'll cast it, then.
Derunpa Deronpa! You'll find it soon!
Aoi seems moody.
He's pouting about not being to get out to the floor.
I helped you with the outfits!
Yeah, yeah.
I even helped you with the acting!
I looked so cute as Mimosa, too!
You just butted in forcefully.
I wanted to show off on the floor!
Enough of that!
Anyway, why are you alone here on a holiday?
Go make some friends to play with!
Why do I have to be lectured by you?!
This place is not a playground.
Shut up! It doesn't matter to you whether I have friends or not!
I'm not the only one who's alone! Usui's alone all the time!
Don't say that!
I'm sure he doesn't have any friends at all!
That's not true, right, Misa?
Ah, his friends? Um...
Is Yukimura his friend? No, more like a pet.
Is Kanou his friend...?
How about you?
What are you to him?
Geez, isn't that obvious enough?
Just friends?
No... It doesn't feel like that...
Rivals?
I thought so at first, but I'm not sure he thinks we are...
"Thought"? You used past tense just now.
Let me change my question.
What is he to you now?
What is he to me now...?
W-Why are you here?!
Is that wrong?
Yes! It's suspicious to hang out around here at this hour!
You'd be taken as a pervert! What are you thinking, you idiot?!
W-Why are you laughing?
It's funny to see a magical girl taking out the trash. Isn't there a spell for that?
Try casting another spell, like just now!
Your face's really red, Ayuzawa.
Shut up!
Tonight's rather cold...
Don't you feel cold? Wear a coat if you're gonna be out at this hour!
You sure like to worry about others, eh?
Is that wrong?!
I planned to walk home just like this, but I felt like seeing you.
Don't you have friends?
Do I look that solitary to you?
Don't tell me you heard what we said just now-
Speaking of that, I'm curious.
About that last question- I want to know the answer.
Just what am I to you now?
Shut up!
I see. So this is what you do when you can't lie.
Really, you're not honest with yourself.
Shut up! It's embarrassing, you know?!
How terrible of you.
Just shut up already!
I'll show you what my feelings are, then.
What are you doing?! Let me go!
Stop it, you sexual harassing alien! If someone sees us like this-!
Dorinpa, Dorunpa
Now you can't lie.
I want you to tell me the truth.
You're not even a magical girl...
How can you use spells?
As I thought, Misaki-chan is...
No! It has nothing to do with him!
It's here! I found it!
I'm glad that it's still here. It's grown quite a bit, too.
This... must be fate.
kitto mata aeru
We'll surely meet again
sono me ni utsuru mono subete
Everything that's reflected by your eyes,
maboroshi ni wa miemasenka
is it all just an illusion?
karami aitoketeyuku naka
I wonder how you feel,
kimi wa nani o kanjiteru no darou
as you melt away in this entangling love
mite goran doko made mo
Take a look at the reason we're joined together
tsunagatta sono riyuu o
kanashii kara sugarou
Let's cling on to each other from our sadness
sonna mono de ii ja nai ka
Isn't it fine just like that?
kazaranai mama ukabu utsukushisa yo
It'll be an unadorned beauty
itsu no hi ni ka wakarou
Let's understand this, someday...
tatoe doko ni ita toshitemo
That no matter where we are,
kitto mata aeru
we'll surely meet again
Preview
The event in Maid Latte this time was a bang!
I was even knocked out by the magical juice!
This is truly a fearsome heart-shocking event! Heart Attack!
I don't know what you guys are saying, but never mind.
Misaki-chan!
Ah! Misaki Misaki!
Misaki!
Misa-chan!
What's wrong?! Why is everyone calling for me?!
I just wanted to circle around you!
There's a UxMishi live performance at the Cultural Festival!
Haven't you learnt your lesson yet?
I just wanted to call your name.
Hinata, Misaki and Usui
Just what do you want me to do?!