Did you wake up after finding something tasty to eat?
I was dreaming of Yoitsu.
My hometown.
Can I tell you how I truly feel?
Sure.
I'm hungry.
Wolf and the Sudden Crack
What is it?
Hurry up and put it back under the blanket.
Don't treat my tail like a hand warmer.
With fur as fine as that, I couldn't match it even if I had a pile of top-grade pelts.
Ah, that's right.
I'll give you a present in return.
Our next stop, Kumerson, is owned by the Furoania nobles, and there are a lot of heathens.
Religious symbols are banned.
It's an unspoken rule that even nuns and monks follow.
Everything works out well.
What?
You really though I had a present for you?
Don't underestimate my ears!
I was expecting more of a surprise.
Hey, hey!
This is payback!
Stop that!
I won't.
Are we still not at Kumerson?
We'll arrive today, right?
Yeah, not long now.
Not long, right!
So the next meal I'll be freed from hard bitter rye wheat bread and gruel made from it!
Yep.
And on top of that Kumerson is in the middle of a big town-wide festival.
I'm sure there will be all sorts of food, so look forward to it.
I see, but...
Will your pocket be okay?
There's enough to buy you food.
But won't the inn be shabby because of that?
I intend to stay somewhere decent.
As long as you aren't going to insist we each have our own fireplace or something.
I don't plan to be that picky.
But I don't want you to use buying food as an excuse.
Excuse?
"We don't have enough money so we have to share one bed" or something.
I don't want to hear that from someone who snores so noisily.
I don't snore!
Besides, you're not even my type.
Your ears can tell I'm not lying, right?
Basically—
Basically, you like me this way don't you?
Foolish men prefer weaker women right?
If I were the weak princess,
then you'd have to be the mighty knight.
But what is it in reality?
Wait, you did act the knight once.
I did?
What, you've forgotten?
You know,
when we got caught up in the silver coins affair, in the sewers.
Oh, that?
Being a knight isn't just about physical power.
That was the first time anyone had protected me.
Hey, stop that!
You'll also treat me well from now on, won't you?
Sorry...
about what I said earlier.
I like that part of you.
Thanks...
Well, I don't mind if the room only has one bed,
but then there has to be two meals.
I got it.
There's good fish in that crowded place over there.
Why don't we buy some first-rate fish and have it cooked for us?
Some fish?
Yes, could you sell me a few?
I'm terribly sorry.
All my fish have already been bought.
Pardon my rudeness, but might you be a traveling merchant?
Yes, I just came from Rubinhaigen.
In that case, if you follow that path for half a day, you'll reach a lake.
The carp today is very good.
If you get a good deal you'll be able to acquire a lot.
Oh, no,
I'm just looking for a few for dinner.
You look like you've come up with a new business idea.
Ah, that was embarrassing.
If you're looking for fish for dinner tonight,
does that mean you're staying in Kumerson tonight?
Yes.
We're here for the grand winter fair and the festival.
The Radora festival is very popular.
Have you already booked an inn to stay at?
The festival starts the day after tomorrow right?
Don't tell me everywhere's already fully booked?
Exactly.
In that case I'll try asking the trading firm.
You belong to a guild?
Pardon me, but which one?
The Rowen Trading Guild firm in Kumerson.
What a wonderful coincidence!
I also belong to the Rowen Trading Guild.
This must be God's guidance—
Saying that is taboo in this area, huh.
It's alright.
I'm also a believer from the south.
I'm Fermi Amati.
For business, I go by Amati.
Craft Lawrence.
Likewise, I go by Lawrence.
This is my traveling companion, Horo.
We're journeying together for various reasons, but we're not married.
Is there something on my face?
Ah... no...
Is Horo-san...
She's a nun on a pilgrimage,
basically.
Well, I suppose problems in life are God's way of testing us,
as arranging for two rooms will be difficult.
You mean...
If I ask my business acquaintances to help out, they should be able to spare a room.
Are you sure that's okay?
Of course.
I'd like you to enjoy plenty of good fish at trading partner's inn.
You look young but you have good business sense.
We'll leave it in your hands.
I'll arrange it.
Sorry for making you wait.
It's a nice spacious room.
I appreciate you introducing us to this place.
Do you like it?
But of course.
I'm so glad we met you.
Ah... uh...
Um...
You're a really pretty and wonderful person.
You're too different from how you were earlier.
I just know how to act in different situations.
The wine and fish here are truly delicious.
That kid has quite good senses.
While being so young, too.
The amount he was dealing in was above average too.
Compared to that, the stuff you were selling...
What was that?
Nails.
I know they were nails!
I mean you should deal in more interesting goods.
Were you hit that bad from failing in Rubinhaigen?
Well it is plain, but it should yield relatively good profit.
And I'm not just carrying boring things.
You're on the wagon too, right?
Huh?
You ordered another just a minute ago.
Well I guess that's about all you can handle.
It wouldn't hurt to be a little nicer to me, would it?
If you're nice to men, they get carried away.
I can't stand you expecting me to fall for the same flattery each time.
Understood, from now on I'll ...
Fool!
Men should be kind.
And if I act upset,
you'll want to be kind to me, right?
This is quite a pale wine.
It called 'burning wine'.
Hey, if you drink that much at once!
See, what did I say?
What a nostalgic flavor.
It's like the wine in Yoitsu.
I used to drink it a lot.
How nostalgic.
I wonder how everyone's doing.
I look forward to arriving at Yoitsu.
I can handle more!
Seriously...
Yoitsu's wine is the best after all.
So,
what happened to that Yoitsu village?
I see this face a lot.
I bought you some water and a bucket, just in case.
And about Radona festival.
The real events start tomorrow, so there's no need to be anxious.
Well, sleep there quietly for a while.
I'm off to see a business associate.
Mark!
Ré su pan dia milto.
Vant derji.
Piréji.
Bao.
Was I interrupting some business?
No,
he was just regaling me with tales of the god of Pitora mountain.
You saved me.
There's merit in being able to communicate using foreign languages.
Well, if I didn't go around talking everyone into deals, Adelle would scold me.
So?
You came here to talk business, didn't you?
Of course.
I've brought nails from Rubinhaigen.
Nails?
Hey, this is a wheat store you know.
But you get a lot of customers from the north right?
Nails are required goods to last through the long winter.
I guess there is a demand for them...
How many?
120 three-pattes,
Note: "pattes" are some form of measurement
200 four-pattes, 200 five-pattes.
I've got a letter of gauranteed quality from the Rubinhaigen Blacksmith's guild.
I'll take them for 10½ rumiones.
That's too cheap.
Haven't you heard about the crash in battle equipment?
The Northern military expedition was canceled this year,
so swords and armor are being sold dirt cheap.
Because of that the market for nails has fallen too.
Even 10 rumiones might be too expensive.
That's only true for the southern regions, isn't it?
It's true that raw materials availability has increased,
but melting metal into nails during the winter season would drive up the prices of firewood.
No one would be willing to incur the wrath of the townsfolk in doing that,
so the price of nails shouldn't be affected.
Good grief.
Could you not have gone elsewhere to sell nails?
If it were wheat, I could find ways to bargain,
but nails are outside my field.
Then how about 16 rumiones?
Too expensive.
13 rumiones.
15.
14 and two thirds.
Okay.
We'll go with that.
That's my buddy.
So, payment in cash?
Or do you want credit?
Credit please.
Appeciated.
Everyone's charging cash this time of year.
The scarcity of cash makes it difficult.
Lanto!
Yes, master!
You have an apprentice?
It's natural when you set up a store.
Load all these boxes onto my cart.
I'll be selling them at Hans' later.
That ironsmith person?
Just go move them!
Yes!
You'll be here until the end of the festival right?
Come over at least once for a drink.
I'll introduce you to Adelle.
Ah, sure.
What's wrong?
Are you taken in by my store's beauty?
Yeah...
It's a good store.
Oh come on.
Young people like you have much better ahead of them.
You're close to opening an even bigger store, aren't you?
Cheers!
The festival is only a day away now.
So we've got pre-festival celebration to do tonight.
You're just using it as an excuse to drink.
I'm really glad I met you.
If it'd been anyone less serious but brainless, I'm sure they wouldn't have put up with me.
Hey now...
It feels like a long time ago since we first met.
That's true.
Back then, you were much more embarrassed at my temptations.
It was cute.
And you only drank half as much as you do now.
And you wouldn't have answered back like that.
It's strange, isn't it.
It's definitely strange.
Normally it'd be much easier to get by in wolf form.
It's easier to chew meat,
and I still can't get used to these cheeks.
But, you know...
I think I'll be okay for a while like this.
You let down your guard when drinking in that form too.
You fool!
There's a fool here!
You damned...
fool!
Come now, drink up.
Forgiven.
So, there's something I want to ask before you pass out.
What's that?
About possible clues that could help us find your hometown.
Clues?
There isn't a predetermined path ahead of us, and we don't have a useful map.
Depending on the circumstances we might not be able to go straight there.
For example, don't you remember the name of any nearby towns?
That's it!
Niohira!
Niohira?!
Do you know it?
Yeah, it's famous for its hotsprings.
Even though it's full of heathens, I heard there are a lot of archbishops and royalty there.
Really?
Even these days?
The hotsprings were good for healing our wounds back then, so we went a lot.
So if this way was North and Niohira was here.
Where would Yoitsu be?
This way!
Southwest, huh?
How far?
It'd take me two days.
For people it'd take...
I don't know!
Two days, huh?
Two days at that speed would be quite a distance.
It'd take me a month.
Don't worry about it.
I'm fine as long as there's good food.
There's too wide an area to cover.
We can't assume you took the roads as a wolf.
If things don't go well it could take a year or two.
This wine is delicious!
Aren't you going to drink?
If we got to Niohira, wouldn't you be able to go back alone?
Th-That's true.
I'm sure I'd be able to go back alone if we got to Niohira.
I'll be fine.
Loneliness is a sickness that leads to death.
No!
I don't mean that, we still have traveling to do!
That'll be enough.
You'll take me as far as Niohira, right?
I still want to look around more towns.
Listen...
I want to do all I can to help.
What I just said...
Earlier I said men are measured by their kindness.
But I don't want to be...
too pampered.
I'm terrible, I'm always thinking in our scale of things.
The time you age is like the time it takes us to blink.
A year of that short lifespan is precious.
I just... forget that.
That may be true, but...
How can I put it...
I'll feel bad if you make faces like that.
Sorry.
I'm the one who didn't consider the obvious.
It's comfortable being by your side.
I just...
ended up depending on you.
Seems I'm drunk.
I'd better sleep soon, or who knows what I'll come up with next.
Next episode: Wolf and the Calm Before the Storm.
Wolf and the Calm Before the Storm