so ra no wo to
The brilliant glow of this sky, does it carry right into your heart?
The melody you heard in your dream, it plays like the silence
Even if your hands are still far from that dream,
Come now and remember that kindly voice,
Someone was there singing for you, the happiness they sang about
Sound of the sky, echo on high, break through that overwhelming sadness
Everything that shines in your eyes
Is part of the real world
Even your tears can't leave you here to stay forever
In this light pouring down onto you, play tomorrow's song
For the time being,
you'll be practicing with only the mouthpiece.
Is there a problem?
No, um...
But I would love to play tunes like you, Rio...
My way is Spartan.
Yes! Thank you, sir!
Next is breakfast.
That's the mess hall.
You go on ahead.
Yes!
Craggy, and rough.
I hope we can get along.
Good morning!
You really suck!
First Battle - Talk of a Chair
Actually, we prepared all this for your arrival last night.
A sort of welcome meal.
Thank you very much!
Oh, right, Rio.
Did you bring in the fish I was drying upstairs?
No, I didn't.
That's odd.
Come on, Noel!
At least eat breakfast before you sleep!
I'll try.
What happened to trying?
I'm trying.
That's Rio's...
Hurry and sit down.
The food's going to get cold.
Now then.
Let me reintroduce you to the members of Platoon 1121.
First, our commander.
Lieutenant Felicia Heidemann, tank commander.
Let's have fun while you're here.
Pleased to meet you.
And this is-
Come on, Noel.
Noel Kannagi.
Corporal Kannagi. Pilot.
She's our mechanic, too.
Pleased to meet you.
And finally.
Private Kureha Suminoya. Gunner.
Listen.
I might be younger than you, but I have seniority. You'd better listen to everyt-
Ran out of gas?
Keep up the good work, Noel.
Now then, how about breakfast?
But...
I was done.
Okay, then, let's eat.
Let's eat.
This is happiness.
I made the bacon myself.
Eat as much as you'd like.
Thank you!
Both soldiers and buglers are all about body strength.
Eat up and build it.
I will.
Kureha.
Yes, sir!
When breakfast is over, show her around the fortress.
Roger.
Attention!
I had work to do, but this was an order.
So I'm showing you around, under orders!
Yes. Thank you, Kureha.
Insubordination, Private Sorami!
I apologize, sir!
Private Suminoya!
Acceptable.
First: attention to the national and platoon flags!
Salute!
Tank Platoon 1121
currently consists of five members, by rank: one liutenant,
one sergeant, one corporal,
two privates. Total: five.
Understood, Private Suminoya.
It may be the minimum number for a platoon, but it does mean...
We're the few and the proud.
Understood!
Our platoon has been equipped with the following armaments:
One tank,
one heavy machine gun,
two light machine guns,
four rifles,
and five handguns.
Our assignment is to defend the national borders of Seize, Trois, with these arms.
Excuse me...
Private Suminoya! I have a question!
Acceptable.
Permission to speak granted, Private Sorami.
Isn-
If my memory serves me, then next to Seize is...
Yes, beyond the mountains is Nomansland.
But the borders of Helvetia only extend to this region, so this is the national border!
The front lines!
A strategic position!
We will not allow a pre-emptive strike.
We trade off watch duty through the night.
Sleeping is strictly forbidden.
And this is the only hotline connecting to the capital in this town.
In other words...
If it rings, something big is going on.
If it does, everyone is to be woken up
and immediately placed on full alert.
Understood?
Yes, Private Suminoya!
On the second floor are the commander's quarters and the operations room!
Entrance is strictly-
free.
But make sure you knock!
These are the latrines.
Readying the bath and cleaning are done in turn.
And...
The bathing order is by rank, right?
No.
Don't you think it's more fun if everyone bathes together?
Commander! What are you doing?
Cleaning the bathroom.
But today is Noel's turn!
But she looks tired today.
Commander, if you're like that, the recruit will never learn discipline!
I'll do it later, so be commander-like and stay firm!
Now then, take a good look!
This is the tank deployed for Platoon 1121's use.
Vector Zero Series Autonomous Walker Tank, the Takemikadzuchi.
It's so much bigger than the ones at training!
This is one of those zero-generation tanks.
There are less than ten still in operation in the country. A treasure from the past.
I've heard about them.
They're supposed to be really amazing.
But its legs...
It's undergoing repairs, but we don't have enough parts.
And we don't have the servicing manual and we can't find any parts for it,
but Noel is doing something about it, so don't worry.
It's not just decoration!
I'm sure that someday...
This tank... I'm sure...
Don't laugh at us.
We're lax.
Yeah, our unit is completely lax.
They even call us Seize's extra baggage or a decoration.
We've got pink epaulettes but we don't even have an operational tank.
But...
Kureha.
That's it for the tour!
Dismissed!
Looks like they're already getting along.
Are they?
Just like us when we had just met.
Aren't they.
But there's a bit of a problem.
After you sent Kanata to sleep last night...
Commander, why did we get communications personnel?
You said the new recruit would be a loader or a pilot!
I can't do anything.
Headquarters sent her to us.
You can't always get what you want.
But...
There, there now. It's okay.
Rio will take care of you the way she always has.
Just like she always has.
And I will, too.
She's young, but she has good intuition.
She might already know.
You think?
We have to do something.
It appeared.
What appeared?
Sound of the Skies
A ghost?
Don't be stupid.
You were seeing things half asleep.
I thought so.
What do you mean, you thought so?
I saw the ghost, too.
It's in the barracks, right?
Why are you going along with her?
But it's normal for ghosts to be around.
Why won't you stop playing along with her?
And Noel, I'm disappointed in you!
You're an engineer! You're supposed to investigate this scientifically before reporting!
No.
Why not?
Scary.
What are you saying?
There are no such things as ghosts.
No such things, no such things!
No possible way there are!
I agree with you completely.
Don't you?
Right. There are no such things as ghosts!
At all!
They can't exist!
Not a chance of a chance!
Exactly!
Inspect the area thoroughly!
In the event you encounter the enemy, blow your bugle!
We'll send you reinforcements!
Why?
Excuse me, Private.
What is it, Kana- Private?
Isn't this kind of...
exciting?
The thunder is like a marching beat.
This is a mission!
This is not a game!
Listen up, Kana-
Private Sorami! You go in the lead.
I'll cover you.
Yes, sir!
Commence charge!
This part was left the way it was before it was turned into a fort.
What was it before?
Like I would know? Just hurry up and go!
Ideographs...
I wonder what it says.
If you can't read it, there's no point staring at it.
It would be wonderful if I could read it.
It's probably just nonsense from a long time ago.
Let's just go.
Aren't you scared?
No.
How can't you be?
But ghosts are things that protect us.
In the village I was born, we had a festival every year to thank the ghosts that protect us.
What kind of village would do that?
Listen up. Ghosts possess people, drink blood, move corpses, and are just pure evil.
That was close.
Sometimes rats can carry diseases-
What? Well, aren't you sca-
Are they gone?
I think.
Kureha.
Private?
I was thinking...
Maybe this was a school.
There probably isn't a school this big, even in the capital.
But there used to be a lot more people, right?
So I'm sure that this building was filled with kids about our age,
and they would study together...
What? What? What is it?
They must have taught music here!
Outside the army?
Well, look.
They don't change.
Even if you can't read the words,
D-sharp.
Notes never change.
Why are you just smiling like that?
What?
Isn't it wonderful, Kureha?
What part?
All of it.
The town of Seize, this fortress, everyone in our platoon. All of it!
We're just a tiny little unit in the middle of nowhere that doesn't even matter.
Our tank is broken.
And they forget to send us supplies.
We're just soldiers in name.
We're completely lax.
But you still love it.
What?
What's-
What? What? What?
It appeared!
Wait, Kureha!
Kanata!
Amazing...
Of course!
This is the wonderful, ever so wonderful, Platoon 1121.
And I'm the gunner.
So this is our ghost?
Where's the "ghost" part?
Hey, you.
You look just like that thief from yesterday.
You...You're dinner!
Stop that, Rio.
Don't frighten her when she's hurt.
But...
She probably just doesn't have a place to go.
And what was our unit's symbol?
Making roasted owl is like roasting ourselves.
Isn't it, Shuko?
She gave it a name.
I think she's wonderful.
You know you nearly died yesterday because of this thing.
But I got to have an amazing adventure because of her.
Right, Kureha?
What are you saying?
That was the furthest thing from an adventure there could be!
Good grief. Maybe we should be democratic about this.
No.
Commander's orders.
But if she steals food again, then she'll be punished.
Okay?
So you played this morning, Rio?
The townspeople would complain if we let Kanata play it every day.
I'm really sorry.
That's your chair.
Kureha?
I just happened to find another one of these chairs.
I didn't do it for you or anything.
Thank you!
Cut it out, you two.
That's dangerous.
Cut it out, now.
Breakfast.
Love and friendship - put these feelings together
And sing of how important they are
I was so happy that I cried
It hurt so bad that I laughed
But that all just goes to show that I'm alive
Let's just take it easy
Everybody singing!
Can you tell me who you're asking to the dance?
You're just my friend!
Love and friendship - even though they might waver
I know, you know, we'll be happy
I want us to echo on forever
Can you count my precious hours?
All the usual words can't even describe it.
Our harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony
Next time: A Day in the Life - Rio Runs