so ra no wo to
The brilliant glow of this sky, does it carry right into your heart?
The melody you heard in your dream, it plays like the silence
Even if your hands are still far from that dream,
Come now and remember that kindly voice,
Someone was there singing for you, singing those chords of happiness
Sound of the sky, echo on high, break through that overwhelming sadness
Everything that shines in your eyes
Is part of the real world
Even your tears can't leave you here to stay forever
In this light pouring down onto you, play tomorrow's song
Standby to advance.
Forward!
Advancing.
Enemy unit spotted.
Main armament, standby.
Distance, 800.
Load shell. HE round.
Check.
Loading complete.
Standby.
Fire!
Boom!
Direct hit!
All right. Signal the forces to our rear.
Enemy unit destroyed. Take up our rear.
Roger!
Enemy unit destroyed?
Good job.
Not good enough.
Filicia, it's Klaus.
My. Then let's have tea.
Good work, everyone.
A Mountain Hike - The End of the World
You're back on your feet again, aren't you, Shuko?
She's completely healed, but she just won't leave.
Well, this place is just wonderful, after all.
Hey!
How can she run around like that when it's so hot out?
Really.
From headquarters.
Get the receipt.
Here you are.
And here's your mail.
Kanata.
Here!
Here! Here! Here!
This one is yours.
Thank you very much!
There.
It's from my mom!
And one for you, Noël. From the professor.
Professor?
His first name is Pro.
His last name is Fessor.
Common names in the Sept region.
So it's Mr. Fessor?
It's wonderful that you have friends from so far away!
Sorry.
It was a joke.
Oh, come on, Noël! I almost believed you for a second there!
Get Klaus something for the road.
Okay!
Rio.
You've got another.
Burn it.
So what are our orders?
Excuse me!
What is it, Kureha?
Major Klaus!
Have this!
This year's?
Yes!
Um... Thank you for everything every time!
Don't mention it.
Just doing my job.
Major.
Would you mind?
Got it. I'll take care of the place while you're gone.
Gone?
Good luck out there, Private.
Y- Yes, sir.
We're going on a field trip tomorrow.
Yay!
Did she say field trip?
Doesn't that sound great, Noël?
Isn't it exciting?
A field trip? Filicia?
Just walking would be a bit boring, so let's play a little game while we're at it.
A game?
As you know, all along the southern edges of Seize,
in other words, the border between Seize and Nomansland,
there are surveillance devices from the ancient past.
Of these, three are due for regular maintenance checks.
I'd like you to look at them during our field trip.
Isn't that...
The mission's not even disguised!
No, it's just your normal field trip.
We can't do anything even if they were broken.
Noctur-Type Surveillance Devices are a complete black box.
Analysis is impossible.
So it's a field trip.
So this is what he meant by "Good luck out there."
But just walking is putting time to waste.
And so, you three
will be carrying those on your backs!
You're just so weak.
Listen up. To carry something like this, you have to put your body weight forward and...
Amazing, amazing!
I... I can't move.
Botcher.
You're one to talk!
You're all such good children. You've met all of our expectations.
Listen up! When you're lifting a heavy pack, first you lie back,
then once the full weight of the pack is on your back,
Not very graceful.
'kit cha chappin'...
and do it!
Yes, sir!
Good. Now then. Filicia and I will go ahead to the goal point on your map and wait for you.
If at any point you don't think you can go on, blow your bugle.
We'll come looking for you,
got it?
And there are wild animals on this mountain. Should you encounter one, in order to handle the situation
I authorize the use of firearms,
got it?
Have fun now, you three!
Right, face!
Forward, march!
March!
Now then.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Roger.
Too heavy...
Too heavy! Too heavy! Too heavy!
Kureha, stop saying that.
It feels like it gets heavier every time.
Noël, how much farther?
Noël! Come on!
Hey, Kanata!
There it is!
Hooray!
It's amazing...
In working order. No abnormalities.
Oh come on. That was easy.
Let's keep this up.
Something wrong?
No, it's just that I thought about this machine protecting the town all alone, all this time.
Okay then, Noël, where's the next one?
Um...
We're here, so...
That mountain.
Th- Th- That mountain?
Sound of the Skies
Someone do something about these packs!
Heavy.
I knew it. The Commander and Rio both hate me.
I know it.
That's why they're...
Heavy.
Come on, say something, Kanata!
It's not like you to keep quiet!
Say something!
Shut up.
You shut up!
I hear you.
I hear you...
I hear you!
Hey, Kanata!
What happened to you?
Broken?
Yes...
Oh, how wonderful!
It's so refreshing! It's so pretty!
R&R!
I don't care what anyone says, we are getting R&R! Because I say so!
First!
No fair!
Oh, delicious!
Now you've done it!
Take that!
Everybody else was doing it.
Noël!
You... Take this!
Look, a fish!
Kureha, this is wonderful!
This is so much fun!
Yup!
I mean, no!
You're not taking this very seriously.
But it's a field trip. We have to make the most of it.
Did you forget about those stupidly-heavy sacks?
This is training!
But Filicia said-
Come on now, are you blind?
She's black-hearted!
Blacker than coal!
But her hair is blonde and her skin is so white and she's just wonderful.
Not like that!
Kureha doesn't get it.
Get what?
That's what's good about her.
Isn't it?
No! Wrong!
You two are talking about a different Filicia!
Come on! Someone do something about this pair of airheads!
Now, time for food! Time for food!
We're all soaked.
It'll dry soon with this sun.
What's this?
Our food is gone.
Maybe it was a boar?
What?
Back in my village, they dug up our fields pretty often.
But there's a lot of food during the summer, so they usually wouldn't come near.
We have a bigger problem.
What?
The compass is gone.
I wonder if it's okay to leave those sacks there.
Our first priority should be reaching the goal now.
Are we headed in the right direction?
The first device was here.
The river was here.
The second device is at the summit of the mountain we're on.
So we just need to head up.
Okay! No matter what-
Sounds like you're hungry.
I wonder if there's anything we can eat...
There we go!
Bayberries!
Are they edible?
Yup!
They're sweet, a little sour, and just delicious!
They're in harmony.
But we can't climb up that. It's dangerous.
You think so?
We should hurry.
They say Major Klaus once crossed a desert in a tank without food or water for three days and took down an enemy fortress.
This is nothing compared to that!
Did he really?
You didn't know?
They call him the Desert Wolf.
He's an amazing person...
Really? Klaus is?
So let's keep going!
But the bayberries...
No whining.
Here's number two!
A boar?
Just where is this thing?
It's gotten pretty dark.
We had to get our bearings after every turn, after all.
Is this really the right way?
Probably.
What do you mean by "probably"?
Without a compass, I can't be completely sure.
Then what? We walked all this way for nothing?
I didn't say that.
If the compass was that important, you should have kept it with you!
Wait!
Let's not start fighting now.
It's your fault for playing in the river.
That's right!
You're not taking this seriously!
This isn't a field trip!
You're always spacing out and smiling like an idiot! That's why we're in this mess!
Do you understand that?
Hey!
There it is!
Hooray!
Hold it! Kanata!
Good grief. Well, it looks like they'll be alright.
Goal!
We made it!
We made it, Kureha!
I got you! I got you, so get off me! I can't breathe!
Look.
Nomansland.
This is the end of the world we live in.
Good work.
Commander! I apologize! We were unable to complete the mission.
What mission are you talking about?
But...
I said it was a field trip.
But then...
All we wanted
was for you to see this.
These are the signatures of those who came before us.
Every girl who comes to the fortress has come here.
And has seen this. The end of the world.
It's our past, isn't it?
It is.
Can you walk just a little more?
There's one more thing they left us.
Took you long enough!
Rio?
What happened to you?
Here.
Bayberries!
Like coming back to life.
So, did you win?
Don't even ask.
But it was worth the trouble.
Love and friendship - put these feelings together
And sing of how important they are
I was so happy that I cried
It hurt so bad that I laughed
But that all just goes to show that I'm alive
Let's just walk it slowly
Everybody singing!
Just tell me a bit of what you think
You're just my friend!
Love and friendship - even though they might waver
I know, you know, little happy
I want us to echo on forever
Can you hear my precious note?
All these words that there are can't even describe it.
Our harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony
Next time: Kanata's Day Off - A Haircut