What's wrong?
Oh? So you're off to Mistral?
Hard stuff there.
But the food is good, and they say the women are lookers.
About half a year since the truce?
And with that. Happy I'm still alive.
See? Grim Bourlouge.
Oh please.
Can't beat that.
Oh come on.
Oh, dammit again.
Hey miss. Awake there?
Your share of the booty.
Caramel?
Such a fancy thing. It's too kind of you...
Sergeant!
Don't mention it. Being nice to the bugler means
you hear the retreat calls clearer, so they say.
With the draft gone and all,
it's rare to see new recruits.
You volunteer for this?
Yes!
I wanted to learn the trumpet-
What?
I mean...
Good! An honest one!
Good luck there, miss!
What's your name, private?
Kanata.
Kanata Sorami.
so ra no wo to
The brilliant glow of this sky, does it carry right into your heart?
The melody you heard in your dream, it plays like the silence
Even if your hands are still far from that dream,
Come now and remember that kindly voice
Someone was there singing for you, the happiness they sang about
Sound of the sky, echo on high, break through that overwhelming sadness
Everything that shines in your eyes
Is part of the real world
Even your tears can't leave you here to stay forever
In this light pouring down onto you, play tomorrow's song
Echoing Sound - Town at Daybreak
There's a festival in Seize today.
A festival?
So I'm leaving you here.
Look.
That's your assignment. They call it the "Time-Telling Fortress".
Set a course and walk.
Yes!
Appointment:
Private Kanata Sorami.
Seize, Trois region.
You are assigned to Platoon 1121.
General Headquarters of the Armed Forces of the Republic of Helvetia.
1320.
Mission complete.
Thank you, sir!
The town of lakes and glass,
Seize.
Wait, wait!
Assignment time is 1500.
I finally get to let you sing.
Bearing: confirmed.
Assignment time: confirmed.
Equipment: confirmed.
Forward march!
G-flat.
A beautiful sound.
Fish.
￥ 10.25.
What a pretty doll-
I'm sorry!
What is it, Rio?
A kitten, drunk in the merriment
was running full-speed into places it shouldn't be.
Well, you can't help that.
Kittens thrive on what they find in the streets.
Isn't that why they're cute?
Maybe for stray cats.
Unfortunately, it was a pet cat.
That was scary.
But I found another wonderful thing.
What is it?
Thank you!
Oh, a soldier!
One of the girls in the fortress?
Now here's something to celebrate!
For the fire!
Thank you!
Alright!
You sure did it!
Aim.
Fire!
Thank you.
Thank you!
Hey!
Are you an idiot? Getting completely caught up in the festivities.
Where are you going looking like that!
Gesundheit.
Thank y-
Come with me.
How's the water?
I'm happy!
That's good to hear.
It does look like you did quite a job.
You couldn't at least dodge it?
This dye goes away when it dries.
No need to worry.
That was the festival, wasn't it?
There's a legend here in Seize.
A legend? What kind?
The Maidens of Fire
protect the town.
Sorry for all the trouble.
I'll add it on. I finished repairing that thing.
And...
this, too.
Felicia?
That meddling...
Late.
Late, late, late!
We even came all the way out here for her!
Yes.
Let's stand at ease.
It was a present from your father, right?
It's a good one.
D-flat.
Thank you for letting me use your bath.
I tend to get lost on the road...
but I'm thankful that I was able to meet such a wonderful person!
You're welcome. But don't get lost up here.
You... know the sound?
It's a clear... somewhat familiar sound.
I don't mean like th-
Thief!
Idiot!
Thank you very much.
Honestly.
Were you going to die for that thing?
But that bell...
It's fine.
I'm sure...
this is how it should be.
Late.
Happiness.
Sound of the Skies
Excuse me...
I have some business to attend to.
Don't get lost again.
That bell...
It must be important to her.
What should I do?
Oh no!
Over there?
Forward march!
The Maidens of Fire?
A long time ago,
long before the world turned out this way...
a winged demon lived at the bottom of this town's valley.
The demon
spat fire,
shook the earth,
and caused the people suffering.
Finally, it carried off the maidens that lived in the fortress,
and held them in an underground labyrinth.
But
The Maidens lost no heart.
Calling to each other with golden horns,
granted to them by an angel,
they escaped the labyrinth.
With the aid of a giant spider,
they defeated the demon and took its head.
When they did, an intense fire sprung from the head.
If left alone, the town above would burn to the ground.
To keep the springing fire from the town, the Maidens,
each in turn,
held the head of the demon.
Every day, the townspeople cast water upon the flaming head
and upon the Maidens.
After one year, the fire had gone.
Since then, to console the spirits of the Maidens who saved the town,
they have celebrated the Water-Casting Festival.
She didn't come.
The new recruit.
Who cares about her?
Look, Commander! It's Rio!
It does look good on her.
Looks like I was right leaving it to her.
But we drew straws to de-
Looks like I got lost again...
I'm just hopeless...
There are times when it's fun to get lost,
but that's because you might meet someone new.
Being all alone...
isn't fun.
Lost?
I want to see my mom.
It's okay.
If you wish for it,
your wish will reach her.
Really?
Yes.
The sound will surely echo.
Surely echo...
and reach.
Maidens of Fire,
rest in peace.
Hold the demon, and silence its curse.
May you never need to wake again.
This is...
A golden horn?
The demon can't have...
Have they awakened?
Kureha!
Reach!
Someone! Hear my sound!
It reached.
The sound will echo,
and...
Hurry and wake up,
Private Kanata Sorami!
Huh?
Where am I?
How long does your brain plan on sleeping?
This is the Time-Telling Fortress.
The garrison for Platoon 1121.
Yesterday...
Um...
I'm sorry for causing you so much trouble!
Honestly.
I'm sorry!
But...
I'm kidding.
But no more of this nonsense.
For a bell like this?
Let me show you.
A trumpet!
Why this fortress is called the Time-Telling Fortress.
It's the sound of the sky!
Rio Kazumiya.
That's my name.
I will be your bugling mentor.
I place myself in your hands, Master Sergeant Rio!
Just Rio.
Felicia-
Our Commander's policy.
There are no ranks here.
Then, Rio!
Then let's start now.
The Reveille! Try playing it.
Today's girl isn't very good.
Love and friendship - put these feelings together
And sing of how important they are
I was so happy that I cried
It hurt so bad that I laughed
But that all just goes to show that I'm alive
Let's just take it easy
Everybody singing!
Can you tell me who you're asking to the dance?
You're just my friend!
Love and friendship - even though they might waver
I know, you know, we'll be happy
I want us to echo on forever
Can you count my precious hours?
All the usual words can't even describe it.
Our harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony
Next time: First Battle - Talk of a Chair