A large contingent of Roman forces has appeared on the border between Seize and Nomansland?
A'ishah!
What was that gunshot?
We have captured the Roman soldier.
Is she dead?
No. She is still alive.
Very good.
Our battalion will now join forces with the First and Third Divisions in transit to the border.
What are you doing?
Don't move.
If you move, I will shoot.
Commander!
Colonel.
Command your troops to leave the fortress immediately.
Echo Through the Blue Sky
What's going on here?
Treason!
Those girls in the fortress have taken our commanding officer hostage and barricaded themselves in!
What?
Fortunately, it didn't hit any of her major organs.
Her condition should stay stable.
Thank you, Sister Yumina.
Good work.
That girl was going to be a sacrifice to start the war.
Wouldn't be worth much dead.
What does that mean?
This last month,
we've been following Roman forces as they mobilized for an attack from a rear front.
Probably another bargaining chip in the peace conferences.
They took us lightly.
But the Archduke has cold feet - he specifically ordered us not to attack.
So we need one little push so they attack us first.
A little push, like a prisoner of war, executed by firing squad, crying and screaming.
You can't-
Peace is just a worthless play!
Rome must be thrown into ruin!
Don't you think so, Noël Kannagi?
Or should I say, our hero, the Witch of Helvetia?
Did you think I wouldn't know?
Enough! Noël was just used by you!
Miss Noël...
You really were involved with the Invisible Death?
The Invisible Death?
The greatest genius the Academy has known in over a hundred years - the Invisible Death -
the one who restored that ancient biological weapons plant
is the girl sitting before your eyes.
Your talent is wasted.
Come back to work under me.
Kureha.
Lock this man in the distillery downstairs.
Our compatriots are already in transit for battle with the Roman army.
One small tap and the scenario will play itself out.
And it's back to the battlefield for us.
Just when you think it's over.
We've got some bad luck.
The Colonel has been locked in the distillery.
Thank you, Kureha.
Go ahead and eat these.
They're sweets I stocked up on in Treize.
They're good.
Miss Naomi, you're still here?
I'll leave when it really gets bad.
This is all completely messed up!
The Maidens of the Fire protect the town.
We're throwing the town into the war!
About that...
When we were hiding,
I heard the legend of the Maidens of the Fire from Miss A'ishah.
She said that a completely different legend was passed down in Rome.
How does it go?
The Maidens of the Fire protect life.
What?
It's time for the shift change.
Don't need to. I can't leave you to do the job.
Do you think you can shoot a gun at someone?
If I think that it's the right thing to do, I might.
Are you sure?
I'm one of the Maidens of the Fortress.
Like the Maidens of the Fire before us.
What, do you actually believe that story? That fairy tale that Roman made up?
Yes. Something about it clicks with me.
The Maidens of the Fire protect life.
I think it must have been that way.
What is it?
I can hear it.
What do you hear?
Kanata!
No matter how good her ears are, she can't possibly hear it from here.
A cease-fire signal?
Yes. I heard it.
Did you really?
There is no mistake.
It's still too early to celebrate.
She might have just heard things. And even if it were, we don't know if the treaty has been signed.
Either way, we must inform Colonel Hopkins that-
Emergency! When I went to bring him food, the Colonel wasn't there!
It's good to see you alive.
Commence attack in ten minutes.
Colonel!
Do you think the Colonel will actually listen?
There's no point in not trying.
Understood.
He won't.
The Colonel laughed.
When he saw the people dead from the Death I resurrected.
He laughed.
He will kill.
Until there's no one left to kill.
And I helped him.
It's my fault.
If you think so, then save more lives than you took.
Miss Noël.
A'ishah!
Ceasefire? Don't make me laugh.
You can trust her ears.
That's right! We'll vouch for her!
She's easily amused, she forgets everything, she's just like a little kid, and she's not sexy at all!
She doesn't lie!
Arrest this old hag!
Do you want war that much?
War advances civilization and science.
I want to restore it.
Man's former glory.
What?
The Roman army is set to attack tomorrow morning!
Then there's no way to stop the war.
Miss Naomi was arrested.
Let's go.
You're crazy! We're up against the Demon of Binnenland!
But I want to deliver it!
Someone gave me this sound!
That's just what you want!
You are being selfish. You do not do things because you decide them.
We are soldiers.
Someone once said that the world was already dead.
But I love this world.
I love this town. I love everyone here.
I can't
just give up.
Kanata...
Please.
Stop the war.
A'ishah is begging you too.
But I...
As a soldier, I too have killed people,
just like you, Noël.
I...
You... Same...
You have suffered enough...
You have suffered enough.
So I will forgive you.
Even if no one else will.
So don't...
Will you forgive me?
Thank you, A'ishah.
If we go, there's no going back.
Are you prepared for that?
Yes.
Then I...
have no objections.
Do what you want.
Thank you, Kureha.
You've been objecting for us this whole time.
I don't...
want someone my age...
going through torture either! But Rio isn't here!
And Noël and Kanata are lax...
So I had to do it...
I'm sorry I'm such a bad commander.
Kureha.
Let's go, everyone.
Yes.
My myriad gods,
let your blessings be upon the Maidens of the Fire.
Primary converter reactor output rising.
FAP, FAC, DMR, and ECP all green.
Superconducting circuits, function stable.
Fire control system also good.
Primary and secondary armaments are operational.
Release all joint locks.
Weight-reduction system operational.
Factor of minus... about five.
Prepared to launch.
We do it just like we practiced.
Let's go, my little ones!
Yes, sir!
Main armament, standby!
Load shell! AP round!
Loading AP round!
Target locked!
Kanata, signal.
Yes, sir.
Commence attack?
Fire!
It's Kanata!
The Takemicaduchi.
They're in that!
To restore the pinnacle of ancient technology...
Signal all units! All possible measures to prevent escape!
Commence attack!
We won't let you through!
We've had enough of your war!
Don't get in their way!
If you want to get them, get us first!
That's right!
So what will you do?
Mister Demon of Binnenland.
Go around! Join with the forces at our rear!
The Maidens of the Fire protect life.
The rest is in your hands, Miss Kanata.
A long time ago,
long before the world turned out this way...
An angel that God sent to deliver divine retribution upon the world
was injured, and set her wings down to rest in a town at the Western end of the world.
It was the maidens that lived in the fortress that saved her,
the one sent to bring them ruin.
But the maidens took pity upon the angel.
With the aid of a giant spider,
they sheltered the angel in the valley below.
To stifle the blood springing from her, the maidens,
each in turn, held the head of the angel.
And in thanks, the angel granted them a golden horn.
But eventually, the people of the town learned of the angel's presence,
and set fire to the bottom of the valley.
The maidens were lost to the fire,
the angel's head taken,
and their suffering ended.
At that moment, the host of angels appeared, filling the sky above the town.
But then, a miracle happened.
The sound of the sky echoed on high,
and the angels departed.
With her last breath, the last maiden of the fortress sounded the golden horn
and saved the lives of the people.
Hey, you remember that young lady?
The one you gave the caramel to.
She's going to get thrown into this too, huh.
All units, prepare to charge!
Can't do anything about that. We're soldiers.
Charge!
What?
What's that?
It's an allied vehicle!
Under command of...
Platoon 1121!
A cease-fire signal!
Yes.
And that's a Roman signal!
Major General!
We can't pull back now! Main armament, standby!
No. They're not stopping.
Commander!
Kanata!
That young lady...
Hey! What are you doing?
I told you to commence attack!
Fire! You will fire!
Both sides, lay down your arms!
I am second in line to the throne of Helvetia,
daughter of the royal family of Helvetia, fiancée to the Emperor of the Holy Roman Empire,
Rio Kazumiya Arkadia!
I am here in the name of my father, the Archduke of Helvetia
and the name of the Roman Emperor, to announce:
We have peace! There will be no more fighting!
Both sides will disband immediately!
This is an imperial command!
Those who do not comply will be punished by the First Royal Guard of Helvetia under both names!
After all this...
Then we...
We don't need to fight anymore!
Miss!
Oh! Sergeant!
It sure feels like spring!
Oh right, Noël, what did A'ishah say in her letter?
My wounds are now healed. I am practicing the trumpet every day.
Translate it.
I am well. I am practicing the trumpet every day.
Really? That's great.
We even get letters from Rome,
but we still don't get any from the capital.
I'm sure she's just really busy.
Rio is a princess, after all!
But I mean, she was surrounded by the Royal Guard back there.
We couldn't even talk to her.
Oh, it's Klaus's bike!
Alright, alright!
Come on, new recruit!
We're going to beat-
As of today, I have been assigned to Platoon 1121.
I am Lieutenant Rio Kazumiya Arkadia.
Captain Filicia Heidemann, requesting permission to perform duties.
Permission granted.
There are no ranks here, Rio.
Um... Well, the Roman Emperor is actually a pretty reasonable guy and, well,
he told me he would grant me one wish as thanks for ending the war...
So...
Welcome home.
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Welcome home, Rio.