The heck is this?
Pickles, I guess?
Maybe she wanted to thank us for letting her stay the night.
I'll taste test it.
Well?
She might be our enemy, but she's good.
Why are the keys on the floor?
She probably opened the window on her way out
and threw in the keys after locking the front door.
No wonder she's a hero.
Such a nice girl.
What would you have done?
It should be obvious.
I would've locked the door
and taken the key with me.
You're a demon.
That I am. What about it?
Get out of your cage
Fly towards the sky
It all starts right here, right now
Let's picture what we can do
Unbelievable things might happen
But we can overcome them all
(For our dreams)
Our dreams are born from nothing
And take us (fly) to that shining sky
Spread your wings
I want to spread my wings
Now here I go, with the greatest smile on my face
Let's set out to an unknown world
(Go to another world)
We'll be the ones to choose and decide the future
Let's chase after our dreams
There will be times when we cry
But they will be precious memories
Don't fade away
I'm sure you'll be to meet your future self
Get out of your cage
Overlord at Work!
Fly towards the sky
I feel like I've been defiled.
The Overlord
Goes on a Date
with His Junior
in Shinjuku
More breaking news.
Shots were fired late last night at a residential area in Shinjuku.
Several of what appear to be bullet holes were found in the vicinity,
with some of them in a bicycle that was abandoned at the scene of the crime.
Shots fired in the city             No casualties
Wha—
Those guys!
The police are looking for its owner, believing them to be involved in the incident.
That idiot!
Well, I guess it's got nothing to do with me.
Multiple late-night robberies and muggings have been reported in the area recently.
The police are investigating if these are related to last night's shooting.
Wow, that's practically our neighborhood.
Isn't that close to where you work?
There was an earthquake in the Kantou region.
This isn't a joke.
I really feel like there's gonna
be another earthquake.
Um, if it's fine with you,
could we meet up
and talk about this?
This isn't a joke.
I really feel like there's gonna be another earthquake.
Um, if it's fine with you,
Maou
Need some advice
could we meet up and talk about this?
Maou
Re: Need some advice
Gotcha.
Is tomorrow evening okay?
I'm off work tomorrow anyway,
and you don't have a shift either,
right?
Gotcha.
Is tomorrow evening okay?
I'm off work tomorrow anyway,
and you don't have a shift either, right?
Do you have work today, Chiho?
Uh, no...
Today, I, uh...
I have plans!
You should be careful too.
O-O-O-O-O-Of what?
What are you talking about?
This area's been pretty dangerous lately.
Oh, that's what you meant.
What else would I be talking about?
Nah, never mind.
Chiho!
Hey, the shooting on the news this morning was pretty close to your place, wasn't it?
Nah, it happened three stations away.
Oh, really?
Anyway, what's goin' on for lunch?
Wanna go to that curry place we talked about the other day?
We might have to line up, though.
Oh, sorry.
I don't have the time to stand in line today.
I lost my purse.
What? Really?
I need to take care of a mountain of paperwork during lunch.
Thank you for calling.
This is Emi Yusa.
"Yusa"?
Sounds like you've totally gotten used to life in Japan,
Hero Emilia.
Could you state your name, please?
Someone who knows both the Hero and the Overlord.
And someone who's planning to destroy both of you in one fell swoop.
In that case,
were you the one who repeatedly tried to access the servers late last night?
I never thought the Hero and the Overlord would team up in a fight.
We are extremely ashamed of what has happened.
I thought as much.
Anyway, Overlord Satan, who traveled to another world,
shall be eliminated along with Hero Emilia.
This is Ente Isla's will.
What?!
I-I'm sorry, but we will not have an answer for you until it has been investigated on our end.
Investigate what? The fact that the Hero and Overlord both ran away with their tails between their legs?
I'd be very interested in the findings.
This vulgar voice sounds like it's echoing in darkness.
It must be a demon.
I'm pretty sure Alsiel was the only one who survived out of the four generals.
Just who are you, demon?
I can tell you want to provoke me by calling it Ente Isla's will and whatnot,
but a demon's rantings are of no importance to me.
That so?
It's too bad I can't get you to believe me.
I'll get in touch soon.
There are all sorts of people in this world, aren't there?
Let's grab some lunch.
The bank's probably jam-packed right now, anyway.
Hello?
Hello.
Is this Ms. Yusa Emi?
Yes, that's right.
This is the Yoyogi Police Department.
Huh?
The police?!
Man, who knew they'd sniff us out using just my bicycle?
Japanese cops aren't half bad!
It turned out we were right though, weren't we?
The Hero had indeed cooked up her age.
If I'm not mistaken, her real age is somewhere around seventeen or eighteen.
I told you so.
I knew she'd've registered herself to be over twenty.
Wait, don't people usually cook up a younger age?
How do you even "cook up" an age?
Who the hell cares?!
Why...
Why do I...
Why do I, the Hero, have to be the guarantor for the Overlord?!
W-We didn't have a choice.
Nobody else came to mind.
We didn't particularly want to rely on you for this either.
You think I was expecting to use my seal and ID for something like this?!
Well, we also could've asked my boss...
Yeah, but you don't want to cause problems for her, do you?
Oh, but you do for me?!
Well, duh.
What kind of Overlord doesn't cause problems for the Hero?
Still, why would you choose me?
Come on, I even gave you a place to sleep last night.
Calm down, Emilia.
You're acting more pathetic than heroic.
Like you're one to talk, Alsiel!
What the hell was up with that empty fridge?!
Why don't you plan your purchases out properly?
Some resourceful general you are!
But it's not...
It's not even my fault...
Now, listen up.
I just got a threatening phone call at work.
I'm being targeted, but Maou,
so are you.
What was that?
Don't say I didn't warn you.
But mark my words: I will be the one to kill you.
Keep that in mind.
You should keep in mind that you're in public right now.
A-Anyway,
make sure you don't let some no-name loser kill you before I take your head!
Targeting both of us?
Not to mention, they called her, huh?
But it's not even my fault...
Pull yourself together.
I've been managing our expenses perfectly...
Let's go home.
I have to go meet Chiho soon too.
I'm home!
Okay!
So, Milord...
When and where are you meeting this Sasaki person,
and when will you be getting home?
What are you, my mom?
I'm meeting her at the east entrance of Shinjuku Station at five.
You've still got some time.
Let's go, Milord.
Huh?
Where to?
Hmm...
This is pretty good.
Wait, where did we even get the money to buy these clothes?
I've got some secret savings for rainy days such as these.
You're exaggerating.
Yeah, we're meeting up, but I'm only going to get some coffee, talk to her, then leave.
I don't really need to dress up—
What are you saying?!
A young lady wouldn't tell anyone but her most trusted friends about her serious worries!
Not even her parents!
And yet, she told you about it!
I'm sure you know what that means, right?
Y-Yeah, totally.
Besides...
I can't let you go on a date wearing just Uniclo stuff.
Y-You...
Apologize to the number one brand in the fashion industry, Uniclo, and to me!
Oh!
Maou!
Huh?
Did you cut your hair, Chiho?
You can tell?
I got it trimmed a little.
How does it look?
Oh, it looks great.
Yessss!
You too, Maou.
I thought you'd be wearing Uniclo again, but...
Huh?
No, no, no!
There's nothing wrong with Uniclo!
Uniclo is fine too!
But you look cooler than usual today.
My roommate insisted I couldn't possibly wear Uniclo on a date.
So you consider this a date?
Huh?
Yeah, I guess...
Yessss!
So, what are we doing?
Let's go to Cafe Dotour.
It's cheap, and we can relax there.
I'm the one asking you for advice,
so I'll pick up the tab!
Don't look down on me. I'm an adult.
I can take care of this.
Shall we?
Ah...
M-Maou...
Yeah?
Um...
Er...
What's up?
Could we hold hands?
Oh, is that all?
Sure, why not?
Something wrong?
Huh?
Oh, n-nothing. Never mind.
Thanks!
Yeah, we might get separated if we don't.
There's a lot of people here.
Of course.
I kinda knew you were gonna say that.
What are you doing here?
#!$!@#%
Emilia?!
Stop calling me by my real name.
You're acting mighty suspicious right now.
Are you tailing someone?
That's none of your business!
Do you really think I, the Hero, would ignore you guys after seeing you act all suspicious?
Could you overlook this so I don't lose face?
That demonic face you had back in Ente Isla? I'd much rather you lost it.
Hey!
What?!
I'm so very sorry, Milord.
Alsi—
Ashiya!
What are you planning to do to that girl, you scumbag!?
You've got the wrong idea!
Milord hasn't a single evil intention in mind!
What kind of overlord doesn't have evil intentions?!
Please, just hear me out!
Oh, so that's what it was about.
So you understand.
The only thing I understand is that my archnemesis has fallen to an extremely pathetic state.
Still, why does he have to go on a date?
That's what I thought too.
However, it seems that Sasaki girl has considerable feelings for Milord.
I thought as much.
Hmm?
You don't have anything to say about that?
Does it bother you?
N-Not really.
I just found it extremely insolent that a mere human girl would even think about falling in love with Milord.
On the contrary,
I'm wondering why such a cute girl would fall for a good-for-nothing loser like him.
You dare insult Milord?
Well, I am the Hero, after all.
Anyway, there isn't a single woman out there that couldn't tell you what's going on at a glance.
She's wearing a dress that's all the rage this summer.
Her hair looks like she just came from the hairdresser's.
Those shoes are brand-new too.
Really?
But of course guys wouldn't get it.
The material gives off a fresh feeling of summer,
and with that fit, she's emphasizing her body shap—
Damn, they're huge.
What's huge?
N-Nothing!
Being big doesn't serve any purpose in battles.
Plus, the smaller you are, the cheaper plate armor is.
And it's easier to move around too!
What the hell are you talking about?
Nothing at all.
So, what's going on?
You guys think you can figure something out by talking to her?
No clue.
I'm just following them to make sure there aren't suspicious characters wandering around.
You're by far the most suspicious one here.
However, what she said about the earthquakes does bother me a little.
If her situation has anything at all to do with our world, then...
There's no point in standing guard here.
Let's go.
Go? Where?
To the cafe they're in, of course!
Say what?!
How could I possibly explain such a bold and audacious move to Milord later—
Hey!
Hold it right there!
So, could you give me the details one more time?
Oh, sure.
I told you about how my ears started ringing real bad around the time I started working at MgRonald's, right?
At first, I thought I was just tired because I was doing something I wasn't used to.
But last night...
Uh, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
Hello?
Can anyone hear me?
No use, huh?
I guess no one can hear me after all.
I can hear you!
Well, whatever.
Only a select few can receive this, anyway.
What's going on?
I'm sure some strange incidents are happening in your world.
There might be a big one
"A big one"?
in the near future, so be careful.
Huh?
We'll pick the right time
and travel there.
I'd never even heard that language before, but I understood what they were saying.
I didn't know what was going on.
So you reached the conclusion that they had to be talking about the earthquakes.
Yeah.
There's no mistaking it.
That was the communication technique used to synchronize
the minds of humans in different worlds to share ideas and concepts,
Idea Link.
An Idea Link is formed using a probe technique.
The probe, called a "Sonar", is released.
The Sonar causes a magic explosion once it reaches its destination,
which manifests as various kinds of phenomena.
In this case, it's pretty likely that it manifested as an earthquake.
If we consider the cause for these recent earthquakes around us
being Sonars sent out in order to investigate what we and Emilia were up to,
it makes perfect sense.
"There might be a big one in the near future", huh?
Looks like things are moving much faster than I anticip—
Are you okay?!
What's wrong?!
Why?
Why did Emi just walk in here with Ashiya?!
Maou?
It's all right.
I haven't done anything wrong.
Huh?
Sorry about that.
Anyway, judging by what you just said,
the ear-ringing and weird voices aren't really an issue.
What's important is whether a "big one" will really happen or not.
When it comes down to it,
I think just urging people around you to be careful can really change how things turn out.
I knew you were the right person to ask about this.
I feel like I got a lot off my chest.
How's that, Emi?
I haven't done anything wrong!
No matter which way you look at this, I'm being a wonderful colleague!
I couldn't tell my friends, parents, or anyone else about this.
But I thought you'd believe me.
You're a nice guy,
and... well...
Maou... um... I...
M-Maou, I—
Don't say another word.
Huh?
Nothing good will come out of getting involved with this man.
Emi?
He's nothing like what he seems to be.
He's wicked and cruel deep down.
D-Don't just show up and say such awful things!
Whad—
What are you to Maou, anyway?!
I'm this guy's enemy.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Getting involved with him will only bring you pain and sorrow.
Stop it, Emi!
Don't you dare tell me what to do.
You calm down too, Chiho.
Shut up, Maou.
I remember now.
You came to MgRonald's the other day, didn't you?
So what?
Are you Maou's ex-girlfriend or something?
What the hell are you saying?!
I knew it!
In that case, I can make my move on Maou however I want!
It's none of your business now!
Can you stop being so stupid?
We aren't like that!
Then why do you keep hanging around him?
Our relationship is too complicated to talk about!
Are you trying to say you're more intimate with him?
How can you even interpret it that way?!
There's no other way I could interpret it!
Just calm down, you two.
It's an earthquake!
It's a big one!
Maou!
What happened?
Oh, good. You came to.
You're...
This is bad.
We're trapped.
Where's Maou?
He's not here, at the very least.
That's not what I meant.
Oh?
You're worried he got crushed by the debris?
Well, there are a lot of people who'd rejoice if he died here,
but he's definitely alive.
And I'm going to be the one to kill him.
I will not let him die like this.
You're right.
I'm sure he's fine.
Yeah, so am I.
I'm Yusa Emi.
Just so you know,
there really is nothing between Maou and me.
I'm Sasaki Chiho.
I'll believe you for now.
Well? What do you even see in Maou?
Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you talking about?!
You picked a fight with me because you love him, right?
L-Love?! I don't... really...
Is it that easy to tell?
Anyone could tell just by looking at you.
How do you feel about Maou?
Me?
You call him your enemy,
but you seemed awfully close.
"Close" to him is the last thing I'd want to be.
Huh?
Well, we certainly do go way back.
But know this. You're bound to get hurt if you love him.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
I don't really get what you're saying.
You'll find out soon enough.
Actually, it might be better if you didn't.
Anyway, just take a little nap.
I know you're here somewhere.
I put Chiho to sleep.
Mind your own business!
Maou?!
Why do you look like that?
No clue.
By the time I noticed, I was already like this.
His powers have returned?
Good grief, how am I supposed to explain away how I look?
There's still time.
I can still use the last of my powers and summon my sacred sword to kill him.
Take care of Chiho.
We're getting outta here.
There are surprisingly few casualties,
but we can't just sit around and wait to be rescued.
I'll do something about this.
"Do something"?
All right.
Here we go.
Why?
Why is...
the Overlord saving people?!
1, 2, 3, 4
Where in this silent sky does the sun rise?
A promise I made while pretending to not see it
The moon that got ridiculed
Will disappear towards the past
Being a liar and a coward
If I was at fault for everything
Then our promise might only have been a fleeting dream
I managed to hide it in the shadow of the moonlight
But I was actually crying
My tears won't flow anymore
They've dried up
If I was able to let everything go
I might be able to cry again
But this world is full of things I want to protect
The Hero
Feels the
Warmth
of the Heart