Maou...
Chiho, I
have to go back to Ente Isla.
What?
No!
Don't leave me!
I'm sorry.
I cannot stay in this world any longer.
Then we'll go to Ente Isla together!
Take me with you!
I'm afraid I can't.
We're from two different worlds.
We weren't supposed to meet.
Chiho...
Forgive me.
Maou...
Maou!
That's the dream I had. Period.
A dream where I went back to Ente Isla, eh?
And? What happens to me after that?
Huh? Well...
That's, uh... Hehehe...
Well, whatever.
It's impossible for me now.
I don't have the kind of power required for that.
But man, yesterday sure was tiring.
I had to restore the destroyed buildings,
and let's not forget that I opened a gate and threw Sariel in.
That cost me all the power I had.
I see...
Chiho, where's Maou?
You called?
Kawacchi told me you ran off last night, mop in hand, and didn't come back.
Well, uh...
...it's a long story.
Why are you answering?
Sadao saved us.
Hello.
Looks like Crestia Bell's gone to Maou's place.
It's all well and good that you want to keep an eye on everyone,
but stop spying on people already—
Wait!
You put a transmitter on Emilia and Bell?!
How much did they cost?!
Hey, don't touch me with those soapy hands.
Pardon me. I'm Kamazuki Suzuno.
Last night, Chiho and I were on our way home
when a pervert started chasing us.
Sadao rushed to our aid.
That's right! Who knows what would've happened to us if Maou hadn't come to help?!
And all you took was a mop?
He was a tough opponent.
Oh, well, if that's what happened....
Excuse me!
Ms. Kisaki, we found a person in the freezer!
Oh.
Sariel...
Didn't you say you threw him into a gate?
Sadao, could it be that the bamboo decoration responded to your magic
and made the exit appear inside the store?
Have you come to?
Are you okay?
You're not dead, are you?
Beautiful...
Huh?
This must be fate.
I've met a goddess of beauty in another world!
O God,
I'm yearning for a forbidden love
and on my way to becoming a fallen angel!
What's with this retard?
Actually, he's Sentucky's—
Oh, my lovely lady!
You hail from House Mac and I from House SFC! Two organizations that'll never see eye-to-eye!
We are truly the Romeo and Juliet of the fast-food industry!
Did this guy hit his head or something?
I think we should call an ambulance.
Oh, such kind words.
You're worried about me, aren't you?
However, no medicine can cure my lovesickness!
Looks like I should call the cops instead!
So this is the temptation of corruption!
What an exquisite pain!
Get out of your cage
Fly toward the sky
It all starts right here, right now
Let's picture what we can do
Unbelievable things might happen
But we can overcome them all
Power of dreams
Our dreams are born from nothing
And take us to that shining sky
fly
Light blue wind
I want to spread my wings
Now here I go, with the greatest smile on my face
Let's set out to an unknown world
Go to another world
We'll be the ones to choose and decide the future
Let's chase after our dreams
There will be times when we cry
I have a really important wish
Don't fade away
I'm sure you'll be able to meet your future self
Get out of your cage
Overlord at Work!
Fly toward the sky
The Overlord
and
The Hero
Do a Proper Job
at Work
Certainly! Thank you very much.
You just spoke with Yusa.
What's going on?
This...
Finally, I have conquered Hatagaya!
Next up, Greenland!
What?
What an awful dream.
MgR turning into the Castle Overlord is a bit too far-fetched, I guess,
but I can't relax just yet.
Oh? You seem to be in high spirits, Emi.
I-I guess...
How about we get some dinner?
Sorry, not tonight.
What, you're gonna go see how Maou's doing again?
I'm not sure if I should call it that or "keeping an eye on him"...
Don't you think it's high time the two of you stopped with that kinda stuff?
Not a chance.
Huh?
It's kinda complicated!
I had my village destroyed and my father killed.
There's no way I could ever forgive him.
But still...
Anyway, I'm the hero, and he's the overlord!
Who knows when he'll bare his fangs again like he did in my dream?
Maou
Sadao
I'm coming in!
What are you doing?
Oh, Yusa.
Hey! What are you doing, Suzuno?!
Well, I tried my hand at some French cuisine.
Udon Confit et sa Sauce Américaine.
What the heck?
I said I'd make dinner, didn't I?!
And what's with you, Maou?! Why are you letting her do what she wants?!
Huh? Uh, y'know...
And aren't you supposed to be Maou's enemy anyway?!
Yet here you are, making him go, "Ah"! I'm so jealous!
Sasaki Chiho.
You're letting your true feelings show.
Quiet, Urushihara.
Which will you choose, Maou? My cooking or Suzuno's?
Uh...
It'd really help us financially if the two of you could take turns every day...
Nah, it's no big deal.
Sh-She's right!
This is the Overlord?
Milord.
Hey, Ashiya! Where have you been?
I need to talk to you.
Wh-Why so serious?
I'd like to take a vacation?
What? Alsiel's going home?
I don't think he's returned to Ente Isla, though.
But Alsiel himself said he'd like a vacation.
There are many different types of vacations.
Maybe he just got tired of living in that cramped Castle Overlord.
That's not at all what it seemed like.
A vacation? What do you mean?
It's a bit hard to talk about here.
Gotcha.
Sorry, but can I ask the three of you to leave?
Looks like Ashiya needs to talk to me about something.
Okay.
Understood.
I see.
Yeah, that does sound fishy.
So you couldn't figure anything out by talking to Emerada?
I asked her to see if there was anything suspicious happening in Ente Isla.
It's pouring.
Could it be that Maou's
really going back to Ente Isla?
That dream's gonna come true...
What dream?
Th-That's...
Come to think of it, I had a rather ominous dream too.
What? You too?
But it's okay.
As long as I'm here, I'll make sure that you don't have to go through anything sad.
That's a lot of stuff.
Did they buy all of that?
No, they don't have the money for that,
which means... Don't tell me...
Remember, I've had Eme send me stuff before.
Could they be importing something from Hell?
I had Albert check things out, but nothing strange's happening over here.
There've been no reports of any major incidents either.
Oh, but there has been just one problem!
What?
I've gained weight recently.
Who the hell cares?!
Huh?
Is that you, Emi?
What are you doing?
Oh, nothing. Just talking to myself!
What on earth is going through that midget manager's mind?
I'll surpass you
someday,
and then come to see you.
Sarue
Come in.
Ms. Kisaki.
I'm sorry to bring this up out of the blue,
but could you reschedule my shifts?
This is unusual.
There's something I really need to do.
Got it. I'll make some adjustments.
Thank you very much!
Tell me what days you need changed.
Yes, ma'am.
Raining again?
Are you really gonna go back to Ente Isla?
That's why you took that many days off, right?
Don't tell me you're never coming back—
Hang on!
I don't have enough power to go back.
Then why?
That's because...
Sorry. I can't tell you.
Maou...
Overlord at Work
Should we really be doing this?
Maybe we should trust Maou...
I'd like to, but considering all that stuff he got delivered the other day,
it's clear that he's plotting something.
We've gotta get to the bottom of this.
But—
Shh.
We're following him.
A construction site?
Is he planning to build a Castle Overlord here?
Surely not.
He's just working.
Why?
Huh?
What are you two up to?
We needed some money urgently to pay for the two transmitters.
Transmitters?!
Urushihara bought them.
He snuck them into your bag and Suzuno's footwear.
Say what?!
Hey, stop!
Don't use your sacred powers out here!
Come on, it was thanks to those things that I found out where Sariel took you guys.
Ahh, jeez!
Anyway, we're gonna get charged for them next week,
but we don't have enough money in our account,
and MgRonald's payday is still a ways off.
Ashiya came up with the idea of taking a temporary job that pays daily wages.
Is that why he asked for a vacation?
Yeah.
A request for everyone
And then I decided to take some days off at MgRonald's and work too.
Ashiya should be working someplace else right about now.
But then why'd you keep this from Chiho?
How should I put this...
I thought she'd feel responsible for this if I told her,
since we're trying to pay for transmitters that helped save her life.
Forgive me, Chiho!
I'm glad this wasn't about you going back to Ente Isla or anything.
What was with all that stuff you had delivered the other day, then?
Huh? What?
First I've heard of it.
Stuff?
Whatever are you talking about?
This shit was here before I moved in.
Pull the other one.
It wasn't.
Out of the way.
Down quilts...
Fire extinguishers...
Water purifiers...
And so many of them, too.
Urushihara.
What is this all about?
Serves me right for doing something I wasn't used to.
I looked it up afterward and found out that it was something called a "purchasing scam".
"Purchasing scam"?
They barge in saying they'll buy stuff you don't need anymore,
and trick you into buying stuff from them instead.
I sold them an external hard drive,
and then they made me buy all this—
How much?
Close, too close, way too close!
How much did it cost?
Um...
128,000 ye—
Looks like you got cheated by quite the evil merchant.
How naive can you be? Why didn't just send them away?!
But I'm unfit for society...
Yelling at Lucifer now isn't going to solve anything, Overlord.
This is the place.
Deluxe Life International Holdings...
What's with that meaningless name?
Why don't you give them a call?
Hello. This is Deluxe Life International Holdings.
How can I help you today?
We bought some down quilts, fire extinguishers, and water purifiers the other day,
but we don't need them, so we'd like to return everything.
I'm terribly sorry I have to say this,
but we test the water purifiers during installation, so it's difficult to classify them as unused,
and thus we can't take them back.
The two years' worth of filters that came with them are unused.
We charge a fixed price for the whole set, so we can't take just the filters back.
Also, regarding the fire extinguishers,
the Fire Services Act prohibits their uninstallation,
so we can't take them back even if they're unused.
What about the down quilts?
Oh, we'll take those back if they're completely unused.
It's a set of seven quilts, yes?
Nah, it should be five.
Our records say we sold seven.
Five's not enough, so we can't—
Screw it!
They had no intention of taking stuff back anyway.
What now?
Direct negotiations?
Direct negotiations!
This the place?
Coming!
Ashiya!
Milord!
And Emilia, too!
What happened?
You were working here?!
I thought that voice was familiar.
First things first. What on earth are you doing?
I was just following the manual in dealing with a customer making unreasonable claims—
Wait a second!
Why'd you buy seven quilts?!
Like I said, we got screwed!
Also, we got five. Not seven.
That's just a scam!
And what have I been saying this entire time?!
That means I was sent to a corrupt business
and was working as a pawn of the devil!
Says the Demon General.
However, now that I know the truth, I cannot stay in this company a second longer!
How noisy.
Oh, President.
Something wrong?
You the boss-man here?
How rude.
Let's talk things over in a calm manner.
I'm sure you heard this over the phone already.
but it's all mentioned in a clause in the contract.
Huh? First I've heard of it.
The heck's a clause?
But we handed it over to you.
Please don't be so irresponsible.
Listen to yourself!
This is just a scam!
It was a transaction made by mutual consent.
Mutual consent, my ass!
What kind of retard buys seven quilts for a rundown apartment?!
The one in yours.
You bastard...
Getting all cocky because you think we don't know a thing!
We didn't sell you any defective goods,
and the transaction was made by mutual consent.
If you're gonna keep making any more false accusations,
we could take matters into our own hands, you know?
I lost...
Maybe the best thing to do here would be to talk to the cops.
Can't rely on the cops.
They might've cheated, sure, but you signed a contract,
and there's no proof it was a scam.
Nothing we can do, huh?
Shit! Where are we gonna find 128,000 yen?!
I'm so sorry, Milord.
As his guardian, I was all too careless.
I am partly to blame as well.
"Guardian"?
Oh yeah, how old is Urushihara?
Not his Ente Isla age, but his Japanese one.
Oh, I think we put him down as 18 years old.
Then I have an idea.
What is it? Will it get us out of paying the 128,000 yen?
What's your idea?
It's called a cooling-off period.
For a minor to sign a contract exceeding the allowed amount,
they need their guardian's approval.
Mr. Maou, you'll be recognized as Mr. Urushihara's guardian,
so you can make use of the cooling-off period!
S   O   B   A
Good grief. We really got done in this time, didn't we?
Yeah. He may be human, but he acts worse than a demon.
But who'd've thought Emilia would be the one to save us?
I'm sure it's because she's used to people making complaints.
She'll be part of my legion someday.
Surely you jest.
Have you decided yet, milord?
Yeah, I'll take the same thing.
Excuse me! Two porkcut letbowls, please!
When I play my guitar, my fingers are like the waning moon
They're a faint light for the unruly days ahead
After the cold echoes have faded,
the nights are filled only with their sound
Faint smells lie on this moon-bound path
Haze drifts in the corners of my vision
I greatly underestimated everything
Was that the cause of my tears??
The world I admired is not quite how I had imagined it
My hands were full of the things I had, but once I held them out,
everything slipped through my fingers to make me who I am
Someone in their own little world
Are you stupid?
Emi.
What kind of Overlord stands in the rain without an umbrella, waiting for a signal to turn green?
Shut yer mouth.
Here.
Huh?
I told you I threw away the umbrella I borrowed from you, didn't I?
I'm giving you a new one in return, so accept it gratefully.
Huh?
Take it already.
Okay.
Um...
Thanks.
You're welcome.