So you're not confident, huh?
There's no way I'd be able to recover if I lost here.
Oh, come on...
Sure, the contents were totally out of place for this time of year,
but that lunch box had a lot of care put into it!
Not to mention...
Maou and the others might be in big trouble if it was poisoned.
If she's an assassin from Ente Isla,
it's probably too late for them anyway.
I guess.
Chiho...
Why don't you stop using us as an excuse
and go straight for him instead?
O-Okay...
Coming!
Oh?
Sadao, you have visitors.
Oh, hold on a second.
S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S—
Who is it?
The MHK?
S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S—
'Tis Emi and another lass.
Chiho?!
S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S—
Seriously?!
S-Sadao?!
Get out of your cage
Fly toward the sky
It all starts right here, right now
Let's picture what we can do
Unbelievable things might happen
But we can overcome them all
Power of dreams
Our dreams are born from nothing
And take us to that shining sky
fly
Light blue wind
I want to spread my wings
Now here I go, with the greatest smile on my face
Let's set out to an unknown world
Go to another world
We'll be the ones to choose and decide the future
Let's chase after our dreams
There will be times when we cry
I have a really important wish
Don't fade away
I'm sure you'll be able to meet your future self
Get out of your cage
Overlord at Work!
Fly toward the sky
The
Hero
Barges
into
a Fight
Huh?
You're cooking in place of Ashiya while he has heatstroke?!
Oh, so that's how it was.
Wow.
You've chopped the shiso up so finely. Looks great!
It's easy to do.
You just need to cut them in half, gather them together, and cut again.
And why's the red leaf lettuce so crisp?
I rinsed them thoroughly and then dried them.
Wow!
You're amazing, Suzuno!
Man, there's too many people here.
Do we really have enough chopsticks and fried rice for everyone?
Oh, don't worry. I brought some myself.
That so?
Guess it's time to tuck in.
Sorry for putting you through so much trouble, Kamazuki.
Oh.
Time for breakfast already?
Huh?
Where am I supposed to sit?
What the hell?
Why am I being treated worse than Emi?!
Guests get preferential treatment.
And aren't these the Sugiya containers from the other day?!
Thanks for the food!
Thanks for the food.
Hey!
I wish I was as good at cooking as Suzuno.
You'll improve in no time, Chiho.
Really?
It sounds all well and good that I'm "cooking for them",
but in truth, all I'm doing is getting them to help me finish off my food reserves.
I got these in order to minimize food expenditures until I got a job,
Huh? I thought I saw some fried chicken earlier.
but this is entirely too much to finish off in one summer.
Wasn't there chicken?
Hey, where'd it go?
By the way, what kind of job do you have in mind?
Did you finish it all off? Hey!
I'm not going to be as extravagant as to expect a full-time job.
Gimme some fried chicken.
I'd be satisfied if I found a service that at least covered my living expenses.
I'm positive I saw some earlier!
Where's the fried chicken?
"Service"? Who says that these days?
Huh?
Then why don't you come work with us?
We've got Chiho, so you can get your training done without any tension.
Oh, come on.
Aren't you forgetting that there'd be a different kind of tension in the air?
Plus, we could use a couple more hands since we often don't have enough people on shifts lately.
Normally, you'd notice how a high school girl feels!
Don't you agree, Chiho?
Huh?
Uh...
Y-Yeah...
He's useless.
Well, you don't have to be so hasty and decide right now.
Working with people you know has its pros and cons.
Thank you, Sadao.
I'll consider it as one of my options
and might end up deciding on it.
Sure.
I'll be in your care if it does come down to that, Chiho.
O-Okay.
A job is good and all,
but for the time being, why don't we help her out with shopping for clothes and personal effects?
The contents of my dresser are indeed meager.
And I don't possess any bags or much footwear either.
Don't tell me you've only got Japanese-style clothes on you.
I haven't any western clothes, no.
...
Is it odd?
No...
It's not really odd, per se...
You know where they sell this kinda stuff, don't you, Yusa?
Hey!
Don't casually touch my things!
They'll go from neat to deadbeat!
Like hell they will!
You do those things as casually as ever, I see.
What the heck?!
Why are you all treating me so coldly?!
Yusa,
why don't you take her to some boutiques and stuff?
I don't mind if it's after work.
I'll kill some time loitering until then.
Sounds good!
I think you're better off not sticking your nose where it doesn't belong, though.
My apologies for making you wait.
Uh...
Is that... supposed to be a change of clothes?
Indeed.
So she really doesn't have anything but Japanese clothes.
Something wrong?
Nah. Never mind.
Let's go.
Sorry for disturbing you first thing in the morning.
Take care of yourself, Ashiya.
Please don't mention it.
Thank you for treating us to something so nice.
Make sure you properly walk her home, Milord.
What are you, my mom?!
Your bicycle—
Dullahan.
It doesn't have a seat on the back.
Aren't city bikes all like that?
Too bad.
Riding double in the city gets you hit with a fine of up to 20,000 yen, you know?
I know, jeez.
But that's not the point...
Um...
Don't your parents have a a problem with you coming over to a guy's house?
Nah, they didn't say anything.
I told them where I was going and everything.
In other words, I have my mom's approval!
Wh-What about your father?
Dad was all like,
"Oh, so you found someone you want to cook for already?"
Suzuno went out today.
What are you gonna do about food?
Uh, well...
I don't really have anything in mind.
In that case,
is it okay if I made some for you and brought it along?
Well, yeah...
Ashiya'd be relieved to have me eat your homemade cooking instead of junk food all the time.
Guess I'll take you up on your offer.
Yay!
I have to keep nutrition balance in mind so he can get some peace of mind, then.
Chiho, y'know...
Doesn't it bother you? Us, I mean...
Are you talking about how you're demons from another world?
Y-Yeah...
Let's see...
I'd be lying if I said it didn't bother me.
Yusa and I text each other,
so I know a little about what you've done.
But I fell in love with you before I found out about that.
Don't look at me like that.
Is that the face of someone who wants to rule the world?
B-But y'know...
Yusa tried to stop me from falling for you and regretting it later,
but I fell for you out of my own free will.
So if I ever fall out of love, that'll be my own decision too.
Even if you only think of me as a colleague and nothing else,
I don't really mind.
That has nothing to do with my love for you.
Good grief. This is why humans are terrifying.
Yeah, that's right.
Especially girls.
Take them too lightly, and you'll get burned to a crisp.
I'll keep that in mind.
You sure are loved, Sadao.
S-S-S-Suzuno!
H-H-H-How long've you been there?!
From around the "But I fell in love with you" part.
You're so honest about your feelings, Chiho.
I find that extremely noble and adorable,
regardless of who the target of your affections is.
Chiho?!
Jeez.
I hope she doesn't get into an accident after dashing off like that.
Surprising.
Huh?
Is it that surprising that I worry about someone?
If I may be so blunt, yes, it is.
How do you feel about being the target of someone's affections?
Huh?
What're you interrogating me for?
No reason, really.
Well, let's see...
She was that straightforward about it,
so I don't want to sweep it under the rug either.
And although it's nice that Chiho likes me,
the fact that her parents, or rather, her mother trusts me
means I can't blow this off either.
Wait.
What's with that look?
N-Nothing.
Oh, right.
I'm keeping Emi waiting.
You're going to the station, right?
I'll walk you there.
Huh?
Wh-What?
Nothing...
Never mind.
Did you find your wallet?
Y-Yeah, I did.
Looks like I kept you waiting a while.
I apologize.
Don't worry about it.
Er...
Are we going to get on this "train" thing now?
Yeah.
Shinjuku's only one station away,
but it's too far to go there by foot.
Oh, about that...
I've never actually gotten on a train before.
Huh?
I hear they use some "smart gourd" things to pay for travelling expenses here in Tokyo.
Where may I procure one?
E-Er...
Hold on a sec.
Before that, can I ask you a question?
How exactly did you come here to Sasazuka?
I used the gate and came here directly.
Oh! So that's what—
Wait. Did you just say "gate"?
Did you come here from Ente Isla?
Huh?
I thought you'd realized that already.
Whaaat?!
Overlord at Work
You never once mentioned it!
You were the one who brought it up!
You asked me if I was after the Overlord.
And after that, you said stuff like,
"Getting close to him will only cause you sorrow."
And warned me to "stay away from him".
Huh?
And I replied, "I have gone through many battles in the past,
but I have no choice but to heed the Hero's words."
However, I had nowhere to go if I vacated that place at once, so I asked you for assistance.
And then you promised to help me and gave me your address, did you not?!
Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!
Did you not say that because you realized who I was?
How the hell am I supposed to realize who you are?!
Did you not find it odd?
An innocent girl like me, who just moved in,
Did you just call yourself innocent?!
would never barge into a house of men and take care of them!
Hearing that from you seriously pisses me off!
Then why'd you ask me if I was going after the Overlord?
Huh...
Uh...
Er...
What about you?
Why'd you ask me if I was in a close relationship with him?
Because I'd received information that you were teaming up with him!
Y-You've gotta be kidding me!
I only happened to suffer the misfortune of having to defeat a common enemy with him.
"Teaming up with him"? Don't be stupid!
Don't tell me you thought I was conspiring with the Overlord to get my revenge on the Church.
So it really was you at that convenience store skirmish last night!
Conveinience store sidedish?
FFFF—
I was attacked by someone from Ente Isla.
They had the ability to neutralize sacred powers,
so it wasn't a demon.
Which means it could only be you—
Huh?
There are no traces of you being hit with that paintball.
You don't reek of paint either.
I did nothing of the sort!
I know just how powerful you are, Hero Emilia.
Then who are you? Where are you from?
Why are you hanging around Castle Overlord?
My real name's Christia Bell.
Chief Interrogator for the Church's Investigation Commission.
If you still possess the will to kill the Overlord,
then, with us—
Hold on.
I don't want to be late to work,
so let's discuss this once we get to Shinjuku.
That's the kind of country Japan is.
Let me go!
I cannot afford to stop here!
So you insist on standing in my way?!
You saw a TV and went,
"Oh my god, there's a person inside!"
I never thought you'd actually do that.
Can we please stop talking about that?
What on earth did you use as a reference to study Japan?
Once I learned Japanese clothes were the tradition here,
I used "period dramas" to study the place because that's where these outfits show up most often.
What else? Oh, the longest-airing Showa era documentaries.
Now I get it.
The ones I liked most were "Ooarashi Monjirou" and "Lone Secretary and Child".
And also samurai stories such as "Three for the Mow"!
I didn't like "Mito the Vice-Shogun" or "The Short-Tempered Shogun" much, though.
Oh really?
Anyway, let's get back on track.
Why has the Chief Interrogator for the Church's Investigation Commission
moved in next door to Castle Overlord?
The only thing I figured out by following Olba Meyer's trail
was where and how the Overlord was living.
So I thought if I kept an eye on him...
...the Hero would show up sooner or later, huh?
Well? What do you want from me?
Before we get down to that, let me say just this one thing.
Regarding the injustice Olba Meyer heaped upon you,
there's nothing I can say with which to make amends.
Considering how you treated me, without knowing I was from Ente Isla,
it is clear that reports stating you have joined the Overlord were fraudulent.
His will is not the Church's consensus.
At the very least, I wish to be your ally.
I don't really care about that anymore.
Let's get down to business.
I want you to kill Overlord Satan with me
and return to Ente Isla.
Could you make your survival known
and talk the Church out of trying to cover up Olba's defection?
Don't wanna.
I'm saying I want you to restore your status and honor to how it should be!
I don't care about what the Church or the smaller nations think about me.
However...
There were loads of people in that underground tunnel.
And Olba made it collapse just to kill the Overlord and me.
You come from an organization where he was in charge,
so I can't trust you that easily.
You can understand that, right?
In order to kill me, Olba teamed up with Lucifer and caused a whole ton of problems for this country.
Emerada and Albert are well aware of that fact.
You can even ask Urushihara himself, if you like.
Most importantly,
I'm a Hero. Killing the Overlord is my duty.
Stay out of it.
Then you should co-operate—
Formerly known as the Inquisition, and now known as the Investigation Commission, was it?
I'd expect someone affiliated with that to understand what I'm saying here.
Also, I don't know why you're providing them with food,
but I'll warn you just in case.
Don't try any petty tricks on them.
They'll see through it immediately.
He's still the Overlord, you know.
Much obliged.
That said,
you have your own things to deal with, right?
I got this at the station earlier.
This one too.
If you're going to be staying here a while,
it'd do you good to learn a bit more about how this world works.
The way you dress and speak is way too old-fashioned.
Anyway, I need to head to work.
Let's pick this up after I get off work.
I'm so sorry!
A-About what?
I took your b-bicycle...
Oh, that?
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
Nah...
It's all right.
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
I said it's all right!
Man, we're really not getting many customers today.
The Sentucky across the street's taken them all from us.
Also, Kisaki has this craaaazy look on her face.
It ain't thriving.
We still have to make up for 80% of yesterday's costs.
Why do I have to go to HQ from today, of all days?!
I see...
One of my contemporaries got sent off to Greenland after losing a fierce battle with our rivals.
For real?!
You don't want to go to Greenland, right?
I don't!
You have my permission!
Use any means necessary!
Defeat Sentucky!
Yes, ma'am!
Man, this sucks.
This is my first day as assistant manager, too.
Welcome!
I'm sorry for coming at such a busy time.
Is the manager here?
I'm extremely sorry.
Manager Kisaki is not here today.
You can speak to me if you like, though.
Oh, so you're Maou Sadao.
I've heard quite a lot about you.
I've heard that you're diligent, sociable, and tolerant.
And also a very humane person.
I see.
Thank you very much.
Is this guy a weirdo?
Oh, my apologies.
This is who I am.
Oh, thank you.
Sentucky Fried Chicken's manager?!
I'm Sarue Mitsuki.
I apologize for my delayed greetings.
Things are extremely hectic, you know.
Hatagaya's a nice place.
It lies right between a residential and commercial area,
and hence, there's a lot of customers here.
The women are all beautiful, to boot.
That's right.
We're both operating in this market.
Let's do our best.
It's too bad I couldn't meet this incredibly beautiful manager of yours,
But!
Beautiful!
Please!
With those graceful hands of yours,
I want you to make a combo meal to go just for me,
Milady.
My bad, Chiho.
I should've stopped that wannabe playboy.
It's not your fault!
I'm just pissed off at that runt of a manager.
Stinky cologne and stupid sunglasses.
You can't be in hospitality and look like that!
I'm not gonna lose to him!
That's the spirit.
Huh?
We're gonna get our hands on some enemy intel soon.
I sent a spy.
Spy?
This is Milord's will.
I, Ashiya, will thoroughly investigate this Sentucky Fried Chicken place.
I'm starving!
Emi.
Emi, are you off duty at last?
So you went and bought more Japanese clothes in the end?
Did you have that much money on you?
I had on me some things that I could liquify,
so I got some "pawn shop" place to buy it off me.
I hope she didn't sell off something valuable for dirt cheap.
Look!
I bought this!
Uh...
Please insert the money.
If you need a receipt,
please press the receipt button.
Wh-What now?!
Good for you!
Is she your friend?
Uh... I guess?
I was waiting here, for I had a request to make of Emi.
What?
I want to go see Sadao's workplace.
Could you come with me?
H-Hey...
Sadao?
That name sounds familiar.
I understand you want me to stay away from him,
Hey!
but I cannot withdraw here.
Huh?
What's this?
Hey, what's this about?
Did you get into a fight over a man?!
See? Such a pain...
Okay, I know I'm being meddlesome here,
but usually, these things don't get resolved smoothly.
You need an outsider's help!
Come on, Rika.
It's not like that!
I have no choice.
I'll tag along!
So, where's this Sadao?
The MgRonald's at Hatagaya.
Huh? H-Hey!
What?! We'll be there in no time if we take the train!
I'm not going, okay?!
1, 2, 3, 4
Where in this silent sky does the sun rise?
A promise I made while pretending to not see it
The moon that got ridiculed
Will disappear towards the past
Being a liar and a coward
If I was at fault for everything
Then our promise might only have been a fleeting dream
I managed to hide it in the shadow of the moonlight
But I was actually crying
My tears won't flow anymore
They've dried up
If I was able to let everything go
I might be able to cry again
But this world is full of things I want to protect
The Hero
Experiences
a Fight