Oh man, what have I done?
Who knows how much this IV drip will cost?
Who cares if I recover thanks to this?
I can't face Milord now!
Oh. You're up, Mr. Ashiya?
Y-Yes...
Um, I'd just like to confirm this one more time.
National Health Insurance will cover this, right?
It will. Don't worry.
Well then, let's hook you up to another bag.
No, thank you!
What?
Uh... Are you okay?
A cop?
What's going on?
Olba!
Mr. Ashiya!
This is why I told you to stay in bed!
You're getting two more now!
That's absurd!
You're the absurd one here!
Does your tummy hurt?
Ashiya Shirou
Maou Sadao
Villa Rosa Sasazuka, eh?
That's not it...
It is!
Just you wait, Chiho!
Get out of your cage
Fly toward the sky
It all starts right here, right now
Let's picture what we can do
Unbelievable things might happen
But we can overcome them all
Power of dreams
Our dreams are born from nothing
And take us to that shining sky
fly
Light blue wind
I want to spread my wings
Now here I go, with the greatest smile on my face
Let's set out to an unknown world
Go to another world
We'll be the ones to choose and decide the future
Let's chase after our dreams
There will be times when we cry
I have a really important wish
Don't fade away
I'm sure you'll be able to meet your future self
Get out of your cage
Overlord at Work!
Fly toward the sky
The Overlord
Does
His
Job
Just give up already.
Surrender the sacred sword, Better Half.
What do you expect me to do? It refuses to materialize.
I'm sure it's the sword itself that's rejecting you here.
Humans are not meant to possess the sacred sword.
It must be returned to us.
This is Heaven's consensus.
More importantly, Chiho doesn't have anything to do with this, does she?
Let her go.
I'm afraid I cannot.
She's a valuable sample,
as a human from another world who knows who the Overlord really is
yet still has feelings for him.
We can use her as a research subject for how the Overlord's power affects human bodies.
You freak!
Watch your mouth, human!
How dare you speak to me, Archangel Sariel, in that manner?!
Ow!
Damn, a barrier?!
Can your body hold out any longer?
I consider myself chivalrous, you know? Don't force me to do any more.
A lady shouldn't scream like that.
Be more graceful.
Oh, looks like an insect has crawled its way over.
Ma...ou...
He's come this far. We should give him a warm welcome.
Don't you agree, Bell?
As he is now, even you can beat him by yourself.
You're okay with that?
The Overlord and I will perish in another world,
and Ente Isla will not change a bit from before you came here.
Are you really okay with that?
Why worry?
I'm the symbolic angel of the Investigation Commission,
and I guarantee the legitimacy of your actions.
Go forth.
Suzuno...
Why?
Why?!
Please!
Help me!
I don't wish to sacrifice anyone anymore!
What a pain.
Take that!
Ugh...
Huh?
Whoa!
What the hell?
Suzuno and...
D-D-D-D-Dullahan!
What have you done?!
What the hell do you have against Dullahan?!
Do you have any idea how much getting a new bike is gonna cost me?!
I demand compensation!
Wait! Hold on—
Quiet!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Stop!
Please, just wait!
I just need a minute!
Huh?!
Wh-What are you doing?!
All right!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What do you think you're doing?
You probably don't get it, since you don't work.
Listen up.
MgRonald's uniforms are lent to their employees.
If you damage them for reasons unrelated to work,
you'll have to pay for them.
Castle Overlord's treasury can't afford it!
Stop fooling around!
H-Huh?!
What are you doing in public, you deviant?!
You're the one who did this!
You bravely came all the way to Japan,
boldly stayed next door, and treated us to good food,
so I figured I'd overlook most things.
However, you're now getting in my way and hurting one of my staff!
As the assistant manager, I can't let you get away with this!
You'd realized who I was?
Of course.
In what universe would a lovely lady suddenly move in next door to a bunch of guys and take care of them?
Hm...
Oh?
There are still some leftovers from what Suzuno cooked.
It stinks of sacred powers, but food is food.
Looks like it affected Ashiya quite a bit, though.
That's really too bad.
I thought you could get along with Emi, and I had high hopes for you,
but in the end, you're no different from Olba, huh?
You may dress it up in pretty words,
but you don't care what you have to destroy for power, do you?
No!
If the end justifies any means,
then how exactly are you lot any different from us demons?
Shut up!
You went to Fushima Park with them. You helped with the flea market.
You'd finally gotten closer to Emi and Chiho, but you got them mixed up in this mess.
Are you not ashamed of yourself?
Shut up!
No way...
Wh-Why?
I used up most of my powers to break through that barrier.
What's wrong?
Not finishing me off?
I'll be on my way, then.
Can't keep Chiho waiting.
It's futile.
He's not someone you can beat as you are now.
What, you in cahoots with someone else?
Lord Sariel, the Archangel.
I see.
No wonder Emi couldn't beat him.
He gets stronger the closer he is to the moon.
You don't stand a one-in-a-million chance of beating him without your powers.
What do I do, then? Run away?
Why would you go that far?
Chiho's a colleague I should protect
and my precious employee.
I'm not shameless enough to abandon my employees and run away.
Besides, you're hoping for it too, aren't you?
Hoping for what?
Hoping I beat Sariel.
Huh?
That's why you didn't stop Chiho from calling me, right?
I...
Well, I don't really care either way.
You're a demon. Why do you say such things?
Why are you the Overlord?
If the Overlord speaks to me that way...
I won't be able to stay shameless now, will I?
What's Maou doing?
He's definitely gotten mixed up in some trouble.
What's he even doing at the Tokyo Government Office?
Huh? Maou?
Did he abandon Emilia and come back home?
How'd it go?
Did you have any problem—
Olba!
Long time no see, Lucifer.
So, you managed to escape.
You look well.
Well, yeah.
Nice life you're leading there.
Do you wish to return to the heavens?
Join me once more.
I'll grant that wish of yours.
Overlord at Work
If I can't retrieve the sacred sword even after doing all this,
I guess I have no choice but to extract it directly from inside you.
Directly?
H-Hey! What are you going to do?!
I'll take it directly from your body.
No! Don't!
I'm going to collect the heavenly silver that the sacred sword, Better Half, is made of.
What do you think you're doing to Yusa?!
You pervert!
"Pervert"? Rude.
In the first place, I'm not interested in modest women like her.
You're dead. You're so dead.
One could say you're more my type, actually.
I'll examine your entire body later, too. Every nook and cranny of it.
You're a fucking hopeless sleazebag!
Molester!
Scumbag!
Deviant!
Damn Peeping Tom!
Underwear thief!
I haven't done that!
Knock it off!
Just you try laying a finger on Chiho.
You'll regret it.
I appreciate that you're spirited,
but what can you do to stop me?
I'm not talking about myself.
Maou won't let you get away if you did anything to her.
The Overlord, you say?
Hero Emilia's gonna rely on the Overlord to save her?
It's not like that.
You set up shop opposite MgRonald's. Were you not aware?
What do you mean?
She's a MgRonald's employee,
and Maou's the assistant manager.
He's a shift supervisor.
It's a boss's job to protect his employees from danger.
Have you lost your mind, Emilia?
Do you seriously think the Overlord's bound to how this world works?
Shit!
Why
is the elevator
out
of order?!
He's not bound to it.
He's going along with it out of his own free will.
That's the kind of man A-ranked employee of MgRonald's Hatagaya Station branch,
and shift supervisor Maou Sadao is!
An Overlord who has the trust of the Hero? Classic!
Yo.
Maou!
Sorry I kept you waiting, Chiho.
Maou?!
Looks like Emi's in one piece, too.
Don't come any closer! Eyes anywhere but here!
What the hell?!
Who'd've thought you'd really come to save them?
I didn't expect the perfume-wearing midget manager to have the Radiance of the Fallen's Heinous Eyes, either.
I need to retrieve the sacred sword, you see.
Better Half is made out of the Heavenly Silver of Progress, which is Heaven's most prized asset.
We can't let the Hero hold on to it forever.
Honestly, I don't care.
What I find unforgivable is that you hurt one of my colleagues.
How dare you put Chiho through a harrowing experience!
Maou...
Chiho's a precious employee of mine.
As the Overlord, and the shift supervisor,
I'll protect my employees!
I figured.
What can you do with that frail body of yours?
Maou!
How much can you take with what little magic you have left?
Don't worry, Chiho.
I won't lose!
You're amazing, Overlord!
I wonder how long you can keep that up!
Dammit, I can't do shit without my powers.
What should I do?
I get stronger the closer I am to the moon.
You're in big trouble, Overlord.
What'cha gonna do?
O holy spirits that bind life and time.
May this world find itself beyond the stars.
If I destroy this place...
...people will panic?
Lucifer!
You thought he might be able to gather magic from people's fear and anger?
It's too late for that.
Take a look.
What is that?
What's going on? Who did this?
Marvelous!
I can almost touch the moon!
I'm overflowing with power!
Better get my act together!
Huh?
Whoa!
Damn you! Lemme go!
Resistance is futile.
No one can beat me now that I've gained this much power.
What's going on?!
Milord...
What? What's going on?!
Magic's gathering in one place.
Doesn't that mean things have gotten crazy down there?
Maou...
Well, isn't this nice?
I managed to replenish my powers thanks to that, too.
You'll be fine now.
Fool!
Huh?
Control those absurd powers of yours a little, will you?!
Do you want to kill Chiho?!
Oops! Sorry!
Are you seriously gonna fight like that?!
Relax.
This underwear's made with cutting-edge material that can handle anything!
Just how much do you trust your damn underwear?!
Hey, Suzuno.
Take care of them for me.
Understood.
Um...
Suzuno...
I'll give you
an explanation later.
Uh...
I'm sorry.
Suzuno!
Are you out of your mind, Bell?!
You're siding with the Overlord?!
Speak for yourself, Sariel.
Is burdening the populace with a false peace,
causing mayhem in a different world,
and betraying those that follow your faith
truly the justice that God exemplifies?!
As the chief investigator of the Commission,
I cannot turn a blind eye to that false brand of justice!
Investigator? Ha!
You're just the Inquisition's bloodthirsty reaper!
How dare you speak of justice?!
Shut up!
At the very least, the life the Overlord's—
No, the life Maou Sadao's leading here in Japan
does not oppose the concept of justice!
Say what you want.
There's still nobody out there who can beat me now that I've gained the power of this massive moon!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Now Lord Sariel will finish the Overlord off.
Hey,
can you give me Emilia's bag?
Sure.
What are you going to do with it?
Huh? I'll give it back to Emilia, obviously.
Huh?
She'll kill me if I don't.
Y-You...
D-Don't tell me...
You tricked me?!
Heaven is a place on Earth. It exists in a certain six tatami mat, second floor apartment.
Being a bum is the best.
It's all up to you now, Maou.
Th-The moon...
Hey, Sariel.
As a benevolent Overlord, I'll let you choose.
Choose what?
Will you run away with your tail between your legs?
Or will you pay for this by becoming my punching bag?
Choose your fate.
The answer's obvious.
I'll kill you and accomplish what I came here to do!
An Overlord who can only gain magic by doping on people's negative emotions is no Overlord at all!
Oh crap!
Friggin' mosquito.
This guy's insane!
Come this way, Sasaki Chi—
You okay?
Oh, come on...
What?
Well, whatever.
I don't have the energy for this today, thanks to that pervert tormenting me.
Just put me down already.
Hey, Emi.
What?
I can see your boobs.
That damn Overlord!
Once I get the sacred sword back, I'll have his head!
He's dead!
Give it up!
You may be invincible against those who use sacred powers,
but against me—
Just put me down already.
You may be invincible against those who use sacred powers,
but you should've picked who to fight more wisely.
You can have my unholy sword.
Go on, deviant angel.
Beg God for forgiveness.
O God,
save this lost little lamb...
Aww man, he went and destroyed a bunch of places.
I finally got my powers back, yet I'll have to burn it all to fix this shit again?!
It's your fault for taking your sweet time.
What?
You don't sound very grateful after I went out of my way to save you.
I never asked for that!
What'd you say? Ms. Washboard?
Y-H-W-H—
More importantly, Emilia...
What do you mean, "more importantly"?!
This is crucial!
This is a matter of life and death!
Please, calm down! Don't fight!
Milord.
I returned to base to don my mantle.
Sorry I'm late.
Damn straight! You're way too late!
What the hell are you even here for?!
It's all over now!
Just put on some clothes already!
I'm worthless!
Oh shit! I left my uniform downstairs!
Oh shit! I skipped out on work!
You can't go back like that, Maou!
I wanna die!
Is it over already?
Ah, I worked too hard.
I wanna eat some chicken.
1, 2, 3, 4
Where in this silent sky does the sun rise?
A promise I made while pretending to not see it
The moon that got ridiculed
Will disappear towards the past
Being a liar and a coward
If I was at fault for everything
Then our promise might only have been a fleeting dream
I managed to hide it in the shadow of the moonlight
But I was actually crying
My tears won't flow anymore
They've dried up
If I was able to let everything go
I might be able to cry again
But this world is full of things I want to protect
The Overlord
and
the Hero
Do a Proper Job
at Work