Huh?
Doesn't it seem more crowded than usual?
Apparently, a local festival called the Sasahata Tanabata starts today.
Now, then.
It's all well and good that we got to Hatagaya,
but it looks like there aren't many customers at our all-important MgRonald's.
This can't be good for them.
Bad place for a lovers' quarrel.
If the place isn't crowded, it could get really ugly if things go wrong.
Also, what if the man's in the right?
We could end up ruining things for him at work when it wasn't even his fault.
And...
Fortunately, there's a Sentucky right in front of us.
Let's have a strategy meeting there first!
Rika's definitely enjoying all this.
Get out of your cage
Fly toward the sky
It all starts right here, right now
Let's picture what we can do
Unbelievable things might happen
But we can overcome them all
Power of dreams
Our dreams are born from nothing
And take us to that shining sky
fly
Light blue wind
I want to spread my wings
Now here I go, with the greatest smile on my face
Let's set out to an unknown world
Go to another world
We'll be the ones to choose and decide the future
Let's chase after our dreams
There will be times when we cry
I have a really important wish
Don't fade away
I'm sure you'll be able to meet your future self
Get out of your cage
Overlord at Work!
Fly toward the sky
The
Hero
Experiences
a Fight
First, tell me everything there is to know about this Maou guy.
Maybe we can use that information to resolve this fight.
As long as I'm the Hero and he's the Overlord,
the only thing we can do is fight.
Still,
I wonder how she plans on clearing up the misunderstanding Rika has.
I'll have an iced coffee.
What about you two?
I'll have the maple biscuit and iced tea combo, then.
With milk, please.
Iced coffee for me too.
This one's on me, girls.
Oh, that'll be all.
Certainly.
If you like, please take this coupon we're giving away as part of our grand opening promotion.
Thanks.
We shall put all our heart into preparing your order.
I'm sure our items are simply thrilled to serve and be served to you lovely ladies.
Here's your change.
R-Right...
Here you go.
I have committed a grave sin in making a lady like you wait!
Here's your order.
Guys like that surprisingly suck at playing around
and cause all kinds of problems for themselves, right?
His perfume and shades are in bad taste too.
What're you talking about?
Oh.
It's nothing.
Let's go.
Now...
Let's hear how things ended up this way.
Maou Sadao, was it?
Let me hear it straight from the horses' mouths.
Hmm...
He's my new neighbor.
Well, he is a good neighbor...
This girl...
I want you to kill Overlord Satan with me
and return to Ente Isla.
That's what she said before,
but now he's a "good neighbor"? Wow.
And you, Emi?
He's someone I want to kill as soon as possible.
Divided opinions, I see.
But I know you're not being honest with yourself, Emi.
Hey, Rika.
Let me make this clear.
There's nothing going on between Maou and me.
I wanted to keep Suzuno away from him for a completely different reason.
It's not like we're fighting over him or anything!
See?
That's why I said you're not being honest with yourself.
Why do you even want to pair me and Maou up so badly?
Just thinking about it makes me mad.
That cruel, sneaky lump of avarice!
He's thick-skinned, broke as hell,
and the kind of absurd man who'd try to make someone feel indebted to him
by lending them an umbrella he just picked up somewhere!
I cannot let that slide, Yusa!
Ashiya?!
Why're you here?
Ashiya sure is taking his sweet time.
You want me to go and stuff myself with Sentucky's fried chicken?
Well you don't have to stuff yourself...
Telling me to go to the supermarket in front of the station
and stuff myself with the 88¥ per 100g bargain buckets of fried chicken would be one thing,
but we don't have the financial leeway to fill the coffers of Sentucky, a potential enemy!
Just hear me out.
We need to do this because they could end up being our enemy.
"To defeat the enemy, you must first know the enemy."
You're my strategist. You couldn't possibly have forgotten these words, right?
Milord...
Your job isn't just to eat.
You must eat as much as possible.
Learn their strengths, weaknesses, and everything in between.
This is the price we must pay to climb the corporate ladder.
Please.
If you insist,
then I cannot disobey.
However!
I, Ashiya Shirou, will keep expenses to a minimum as I thoroughly investigate them.
Ashiya!
Milord!
Leave things to me!
Ashiya!
I'm surrounded by retards.
Milord!
Ashiya!
Okay, I did say to learn everything, but you're taking way too long!
Maou...
Oh, Chiho. What's up?
So, we're done with our usual jobs.
Oh...
Yeah, I guess.
Everyone's lost their vigor,
but I suppose that's only natural.
Things outside have gotten pretty lively thanks to the festival.
However, compared to our enemy, Sentucky,
our place is a graveyard.
What now?
We can't afford to keep sitting on our asses.
Um...
Maybe we should stand outside and try to attract customers?
Attracting customers.
There's an idea,
but it'd be best to wait until Ashiya makes his report.
What would we even attract them with? Until he gets here, my hands are tied.
Should I just make a move now?
But wait...
If I made my move now...
I don't see it!
I can't see it at all!
I can't predict what'll happen on this fast-food battlefront!
I never knew it'd be this deep!
Maou, bro, you all right?
I know you're the shift supervisor, but you don't have to do everything yourself.
That's right!
I'm the commander of this army!
Me panicking here will only cause anxiety among my subordinates!
This isn't the time to make our move.
The flow of battle may be in the enemy's favor right now,
but gentlemen, our time fast approaches!
We need only bide our time!
So in the meantime,
wash the windows!
Roger!
Please!
Get here soon!
What're you doing here?
Wait, where were you even hiding all this time?
I noticed you when you came in, but I wanted to stay out of trouble.
However, after hearing you slander Milord, I had no choice but to speak!
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, right.
This is a good opportunity, Ashiya.
Help me out here.
This is something that will affect your and Maou's honor.
What?
Why do I need to help you out?
I'm guessing you're here to research this place.
I'll treat you to whatever you want.
Oh, well, if you insist.
I didn't expect you to be this greedy.
Don't get the wrong idea.
What I need to prioritize most right now is our finances.
I'll endure any kind of humiliation to that end,
even if it means I must cover myself in dirt for it.
Lame.
Anyway, I couldn't research the dessert and salads because I'd've gone over my budget.
I'll just order that later.
Um...
I don't really get it, but...
Are you friends?
Absolutely not!
I don't know who you are, but let me say this:
If I must specify some kind of relationship with the people here,
then I'll say that I'm Kamazuki's neighbor.
My name is Ashiya Shirou.
Oh, hello.
I'm Suzuki Rika, Emi's colleague.
Wait, you said you were Suzuno's neighbor.
Does that mean you live with Maou?
Indeed.
Do you know Milord?
I want to ask you about him because I want to know him better.
"Want to know him better"?
Oh...
You don't have to be on guard. Seriously.
Basically,
there's a man Emi doesn't want another girl getting close to.
Yusa, what exactly is going on here?
That's what I want to know.
A man Yusa doesn't want another girl getting close to, huh?
It will affect our honor, huh?
This is what they call "letting the cat out of the bag", Yusa.
Let's see...
This will be the first Kamazuki hears of this too,
but Maou and I used to run a company in the past.
Huh? A company?!
A-Ashiya?
What on earth is he on about?
Wait, you don't look all that different from us.
Just how old are you?
Our company was primarily a real estate and personnel placement agency.
We also dabbled in construction sometimes.
Our company name was such:
Maou Inc.
Maou Inc.!
"Maou Inc."?
Personnel placement, my foot.
And Yusa
was our rival's employee!
Emi...
Your previous job was related to construction work?
Wait, how old are you, again?
W-Well, how should I put it...
If I remember correctly, weren't you a temp at the time?
Temp?!
Oh, I see.
So the Hero's just a temp.
Don't take him seriously!
Our operations were pretty large in scale,
but we were still small enough that we proprietors needed to take command out on the field.
Not only was Yusa talented, she also had backup from her firm.
We frequently fought over contracts.
We were all youngsters without much work experience.
I am so sorry!
We were smack-dab in the middle of a recession back then,
so if a bunch of big contracts were taken away
from a firm that was run by upstarts like us, it would crumble and fall.
And the last person we competed with over a contract
Thank you very much, sir!
was Yusa.
We lost the contract, and our company went bankrupt.
We drifted from place to place until we reached Sasazuka.
Roughly a year after we'd seen her last,
we ran into Yusa again by chance!
Octopus dumplings...
I guess Yusa had us, her ex-business rivals, on her mind.
She stops by from time to time to see how we're doing.
Oh, so that's...
However, Maou has not given up on being a successful businessman!
Right now, he's working his pants off at MgRonald's in order to learn about business administration
from the ground up.
In just a year, he's become a shift supervisor.
As for me,
I take care of things around the house.
How the mighty have fallen. I'm pathetic.
However!
We hope to run a business under Maou someday!
I want to support that with all I've got!
But business is just a gamble, so to speak.
If Yusa wants to keep Kamazuki away from us
so that she doesn't get mixed up in our gambles,
then I can't blame her.
I'm in far too deep to ever get out, though.
Maou's kind of stubborn too.
He still sees Yusa as his enemy and hates her.
I don't think things are like what you think they are.
Oh man, that's amazing.
You're not that much older than me.
I'm ashamed of myself for letting my imagination run wild and poking my nose into this.
Emi, you should've just said so from the start.
I did, but you paid no heed to me.
My family runs a small factory,
and whenever we were in real trouble, we all worked together to get through it.
You called yourself pathetic earlier,
but this Maou eats the food you make,
sleeps on the mattress you air out, and puts on underwear that you wash, right?
Yeah...
That means you're supporting everyone.
You should be more proud of yourself.
You guys are close enough to help each other out like that,
so I'm sure things'll go well for you!
You're the first person to say anything like that.
Thanks for the encouragement. I feel a little better now.
Rika?
Wh-What?!
That's what I wanna ask.
What's gotten into you?
N-Nothing! Nothing! Nothing! Nothing!
She said it four times...
But yeah...
I guess everyone has their own history.
Anyway, that cleared up your misunderstanding, right?
Let's go—
Now I kinda wanna see this Maou guy for personal reasons.
You what?
If he has real talent, then I should get to know him for the sake of my own future as well.
Hey, what are you—
You have your scouting report to make too, don't you?
How about we head over together?
Hey, Rika!
You're coming too, obviously.
Anyway, get me a maple biscuit and salad to go.
H-Hey—
I must thank Kamazuki for all she's done for us too.
I'll foot the bill.
Argh...
Why'd it end up like this?!
Things are getting worse and worse.
Now, now, miss.
Don't make that face.
It'll make your food taste most foul.
Thanks for the warning.
No matter how much one worries,
things will change with time, whether one likes it or not.
I hope you don't have any regrets when things don't go your way.
That's the first time a Sentucky employee has stuck his nose in my business.
My, that was very rude of me,
but allow me to say just this:
It is in a man's nature to take advantage of women when they're at their weakest.
Be very careful.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing in particular.
Thank you very much.
Please come again.
Opening sale coupons, huh?
Also, from what I've seen,
their main attraction, the fried chicken...
Well, it depends on the type,
but shockingly, you can even eat the bones!
Even the bones?!
Wait, who even wants to eat bones?
To top it all off,
they're using organic coffee!
Did you just say ogre-nic coffee?!
No, organic.
I'm talking about organic cultivation.
I see.
Ogre farmers, huh?
However, I don't think there's much of a difference otherwise.
The service was nothing out of the ordinary, either.
The only possibility left is that the passersby are getting distracted by the new place.
I see.
Anyway, we won't go down without a fight.
Good work.
Your words are wasted on me!
Trivial as it may be,
allow me to contribute to your sales.
Two Big Mag combo meals
with large drinks and fries, please.
Urushihara will probably bitch and whine,
but let's go with this for tonight's dinner.
If he whines about food,
you have my permission to knock his lights out.
Very well.
Also...
Have high hopes for them.
Okay...
I don't really get it, though.
Best of luck, Milord.
Wow.
Those guys are really tight-knit.
Also, his professional spirit is off the charts!
There are lots of capable people around you, Emi.
Oh, can I count myself in that number too?
Do whatever you want.
The chairs here are harder than Sentucky's.
Um...
May I have a word?
What do you want?
Could you take a seat after placing your order, please?
Okay, then get me a small iced coffee.
You can help yourself to that.
Then I'll order an apple pie too.
Be grateful and bring it here.
Ma'am—
You're Maou, right?
You're not as charismatic as I expected you to be.
This place is a ghost town during the shift you're supervising too.
And what do you think you're saying?
Who the hell do you think you are?!
Hey!
Where are your manners?
I'll send a complaint to your HQ about the terrible way you're treating me.
Shut yer mouth.
Even customers need to play by the restaurant's rules.
Who are you, anyway?
I'm Suzuki Rika.
Emi's colleague.
Maou Sadao.
I heard about you from these two and Ashiya.
From Ashiya?
When?
What did he tell you?
Let's just say Ashiya and Emi have very different views of you.
I had to see for myself what you're like.
I have no idea what you're saying,
but are you one of those busybodies?
Aw, jeez.
Customers aren't showing up, and now Emi's here...
You can't be like that, Maou.
Yusa's an important customer too.
Here you go! An iced coffee and a fresh apple pie!
Sorry, Chiho.
You had to do this because I was dealing with Maou.
No worries.
I don't mind.
Looks like you're working hard, Chiho.
Hello, Suzuno.
Are you a friend of Yusa's, ma'am?
That's right.
I'm Emi's colleague,
Suzuki Rika.
I'm Sakaki Chiho.
Yusa's been helping me out a lot.
Cute...
Pardon me?
Cute!
What's with this girl? She's so cute!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
You're surrounded by way too many amazing people!
Well-mannered, with the right outlook toward work...
And cute too!
This has to be against the rules!
What are you, a middle-aged drunk?!
Oh, all right.
Sorry, Chiho.
I got too excited.
It's okay...
I don't really know what happened, though...
Well?
What are you gonna do from now on?
Huh?
You went and told Ashiya that you "wouldn't go down without a fight".
Let me make this clear.
What I wanna see is how you work.
Seriously, what is with you?
Be it Ashiya or Chiho,
there are a bunch of talented people around Emi.
Following that, you can't be as dim as you look.
So I look dim, do I?
Wait, it's not just your looks, but your brain too?
Fine!
Sentucky has coupons? No big deal!
We'll take them on with flyers!
Would you like a hamburger at MgRonald's?
Come right in!
It's no good.
What?!
In that case, let's show off how our stuff is easy to eat since it's boneless!
Would you like a Big Mag?
It's boneless, so it's really easy to eat!
Why wouldn't a burger be boneless?
You sure say some funny things.
She's cute!
It's no good.
Figured.
Kawachi!
Now that it's come to this,
I think it's time we start letting people who aren't customers use the washroom too.
What'll that accomplish?!
This is hopeless.
Is Maou around?
Mr. Tawabe!
I've been waiting!
I'm only doin' this 'cause you asked.
Sorry I'm late.
Please, it's perfectly all right! You saved me!
Let me treat you to something.
Nah, I delivered what I had to,
and my wife made dinner for me, so I'll pass.
Until next time, then.
Tell Kisaki I said hi.
Wow, we got a great one!
Let's decorate it before the dinnertime rush!
Let's do it!
Here you go, Maou.
Do we have enough accessories?
Okay, then let's use the flyers.
Can we really use these as decorations?
I'm the shift supervisor. You have my permission.
What's going on?
Since the Sasahata Tanabata festival's going on,
Maou came up with the idea of letting people write their wishes on strips of paper
and do the Tanabata decorations themselves.
He asked the manager to get HQ to approve his idea of giving people
who made the decorations a small soda for free.
He met Mr. Watanabe, the old man from earlier, while doing community service
and asked him for some of his bamboo.
The Overlord did community service?
Of course, we don't know if this will get us anywhere,
but at least it's changed the mood here, right?
Hell, ain't he capable?
I'll admit he's enthusiastic about work.
Huh?
So pretty!
Is this the place with the cute and funny girl?
This way.
Wh-What's happening?!
Mom, I wanna put one up!
What?!
For real?!
How did this many people show up just because they put out some bamboo?!
What kinda feng shui is this?!
It's unbelievable!
All right!
Battle stations, everyone!
It's time for war!
Welcome!
Those who've decided on your orders,
please line up!
Welcome!
There are some empty seats over there.
Certainly.
Right this way, please.
1, 2, 3, 4
Where in this silent sky does the sun rise?
A promise I made while pretending to not see it
The moon that got ridiculed
Will disappear towards the past
Being a liar and a coward
If I was at fault for everything
Then our promise might only have been a fleeting dream
I managed to hide it in the shadow of the moonlight
But I was actually crying
My tears won't flow anymore
They've dried up
If I was able to let everything go
I might be able to cry again
But this world is full of things I want to protect
The Overlord
and Hero
Have an
Unusual Day