Ashiya, you okay?
I'm terribly sorry, Milord.
I can't even go shopping like this...
Just forget about all that and get some rest.
I'll take care of dinner.
Milord!
Such gracious words... for the likes of me...
Looks like we've still got some rice.
Guess I could make some egg fried rice.
Huh? Is that Emi again?
Delivery for you!
Damn you...
Don't tell me you bought something again—
I haven't.
If I had, I'd've made them deliver it when you weren't around.
Thank you!
Maou Sadao,
I found a bunch of  lovely stuff in Hawaii,
so could you put them up for sale
in the local association's
summer festival flea market?
Mikity
"I found a bunch of lovely stuff in Hawaii,
so could you put them up for sale in the local association's summer festival flea market?"
I'm not gonna help, you know.
Hey!
Do you wanna cough or complain? Pick one.
You're...
You're from the Church, right?
Death Scythe Bell, if I'm not mistaken.
Get out of your cage
Fly toward the sky
It all starts right here, right now
Let's picture what we can do
Unbelievable things might happen
But we can overcome them all
Power of dreams
Our dreams are born from nothing
And take us to that shining sky
fly
Light blue wind
I want to spread my wings
Now here I go, with the greatest smile on my face
Let's set out to an unknown world
Go to another world
We'll be the ones to choose and decide the future
Let's chase after our dreams
There will be times when we cry
I have a really important wish
Don't fade away
I'm sure you'll be able to meet your future self
Get out of your cage
Overlord at Work!
Fly toward the sky
The Hero
Sticks to
Her
Beliefs
Looks like Tom hasn't been opening his shop lately.
Is he sick or something?
Well, he'd been opposing the Church and all...
Seems like he was giving the Alliance's Order of Knights
preferential treatment when it came to foodstuffs and other goods.
Is he gonna be the target of an inquisition?!
Mind your voice, idiot!
What if they heard you?!
Reports say that Lucifer's army is invading Poleridge Village.
Wasn't one of the Church's knight squads stationed there?
Should we send reinforcements and do them a "favor"?
Nah. Judging from how large the opponent's force is,
sending reinforcements isn't going to achieve anything.
In this case, the best thing to do would be to pretend we don't know anything.
I get it.
So you want us in the Alliance to spread the word of the Church knights' failure to protect the village
and use that to take the initiative in the war against the Overlord, right?
Well, yeah. Sacrificing one tiny village won't affect us much.
Who goes there?!
H-Hey...
What's wrong?
Don't tell me the wine...
So you're from the Inquisition?
Shit!
Damn Church lapdog...
D-Don't...
Good work.
Great job as usual.
Well done.
Here, wipe the blood off.
The blame for the Church and Alliance Knights' inability to put up a united front against the Overlord's army
lies partly with the Church.
Why don't you try to cooperate?
That's none of your concern.
You need only carry out your Inquisition work.
Here's the next list of heretics.
In the end, it wasn't us who saved the world, but the Hero.
Huh? Fushima Park?!
Did you go with Maou?
Why would I?
Oh, you didn't?
Well, we did meet up over there,
but I went with Chiho and Suzuno, not him.
But despite what you say, you're interested in him, right?
If I had to choose, I'd say I was more interested in Suzuno, though.
Pardon me—
Oh, Chiho! I've been waiting for you.
Um, Maou...
What's this?
The landlady sent all this from Hawaii.
She asked me to put these up for sale in the shopping district's summer festival flea market.
I'm terribly sorry.
You've had to help us out because I haven't recover—
H-Hey!
Don't make a mess, dude!
I'm so sorry...
Are you okay, Ashiya?
Getting her to help is all well and good,
No need to worry, Sasaki.
but this place is too cramped to do it all here, don't you think?
Be careful, okay?
Looks like Emilia's here too.
Thank you.
Emi?
How can you tell?
I snuck one into her bag the other day.
You can't go to sleep now, Ashiya!
You can't! You can't! You can't!
A transmitter, that is.
Do you have a death wish?
You can't! You can't! You can't! You can't!
I'm awake, Sasaki!
Actually, what does she want now?!
You can stop now!
We're too damn busy!
Huh?
Oh, her?
Kamazuki
Why do I need to help you out?
I only dropped by to check on Suzuno!
And why must I be "checked on" by you?
Can I go back?
I'm a bum.
I'm trying not to set foot outside.
You're helping too.
You'll be fine inside this building.
Can someone tell me what the deal is with the landlady's tastes?
Who the hell would wear this swimsuit?
But this is kinda cute!
Yeah, maybe I should get one for myself.
The size—
Quiet, bum!
Oh, there's food.
Pineapples,
macadamia chocolate,
and canned meat?
This food and drink
is for everyone.
There's juice too!
This food and drink
is for everyone.
"This food and drink is for everyone," apparently.
Gu-a-va juice?
Wanna give it a shot?
I'll get some cups.
Do you know where they are?
I think so.
That's not gonna work.
You're clumsy as hell, so be careful.
Oops. My bad.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
Hey, wipe yourself off with this.
Huh?
What's wrong?
No, uh...
It's nothing.
Um... I'm sorry.
I only found five.
Urushihara doesn't get any, then.
Why?!
We have five cups for five people!
Me, Emi, Suzuno, Chiho,
and Ashiya.
You can just drink water or something.
Um, we've got Sugiya's containers, if you like...
Come on!
What the hell?!
What's with all of you?!
Why's it always me?!
I—
Thanks.
You were a big help.
That was fun!
It was kinda like the day before a cultural festival.
Yeah, the preparations are usually more fun than the festivals themselves.
Hm? What's up?
Oh, I was just thinking how I haven't had the time to enjoy a festival in years now.
Let's all have tons of fun this year, then!
With the preparations and the festival itself!
Anyway, I've got a shift tonight,
so I better go.
Okay. Do your best!
We'll handle the rest!
Jeez, Chiho. That idiot's just gonna take advantage of you.
Preparing for a festival? What do you think you're doing?
Just do what you came here to do
before the Overlord regains his powers.
But...
It's too late for doubt.
You've stained your hands with blood plenty of times before.
Damn St. Isle.
They're getting cocky the second things get peaceful.
They want to keep us away from the central continent's restoration work!
They'll show no hesitation in taking advantage of our shortcomings.
But who'd've thought they'd get their hands on the corpse of the noble we assassinated
and records of the bishops' meeting?
What was Bishop Bell doing?
Simply offering her, the head inquisitor, up isn't going to change anything, though.
We've carried out plenty of inquisitions that we can't properly explain, after all.
Then what should we do?
The Overlord army was defeated by Hero Emilia—a former knight of the church—
and High Priest Olba.
In other words, it was the Church that brought about this era of peace.
Hold on a second!
Don't forget that it was you who stepped up the severity of the inquisitions!
Somebody's got to take the fall for that.
"Fall"?
The person responsible for all this, High Priest Olba, has unfortunately gone missing.
We can't take responsibility even if we want to.
I see.
We must avoid the stagnation of heresy trials due to a missing leader.
Thus, we'll establish a new Investigation Commission under the leadership of Lord Robertio
and transfer the members of the Inquisition over.
The Inquisition shall be suspended until Lord Olba returns.
Under new leadership, we'll conduct fairer trials under a more open system.
The smaller nations should be satisfied with that.
These things never change.
These people never judge their own actions.
They fear pain.
They fear humiliation.
That's why they're only willing to reap the benefits without dirtying their hands.
I wasn't executing people because I wanted to!
I'll say it again.
Do your job.
Kill the Overlord.
Overlord at Work
Huh?
Oh, come on.
Go to the hospital if you're that sick!
I'll call an ambulance for you!
I can't let something like this affect me!
That so.
I'll just call a private ambulance service, then.
W-Wait!
Don't!
How much would that cost?!
Would National Health Insurance even cover that?!
There she is.
Suzuno!
What were you doing?
Something wrong?
Not at all.
I was just thinking about something.
Oh, yeah. Did you find a job yet, Suzuno?
If you haven't, why don't you come to MgRonald's like we talked about?
Maou's there too, so I'm sure you'll find it easy—
Chiho.
Yes?
You'd best not involve yourself with him anymore.
Hey, Suzuno?!
Don't say a word, Emilia.
Emilia?
Isn't that your real—
I'd considered the possibility,
but I see you really are aware of Overlord Satan.
Suzuno—
I know you've got your own plans, Emilia,
but the same goes for me.
He cannot be allowed to live any longer.
Suzuno?!
Where is this coming from?
Kill him? No way—
Chiho.
Do you remember how the number of visitors to MgRonald's showed a great increase
as soon as he put up that Tanabata bamboo decoration?
What do you think that means?
What that means?
He used magic.
Huh?
Bamboo trees are said to clear the air of malice.
In addition to that, people poured their wishes onto the strips of paper they decorated that tree with.
With those two elements acting as a medium,
the Overlord unwittingly activated his powers.
But he only did it because he wanted visitors!
Of course, that doesn't mean he should've cheated, but...
That's not a big deal in itself,
but there's no guarantee he won't use his powers for more dangerous purposes.
Maou wouldn't!
Remember, when crocodiles escaped into the pool—
Let's say he continues to get ahead in this world
and becomes a man of great trust and popularity.
What do you think would happen if he then betrayed the world?
That's not gonna happen.
What?
It's not really nice of me to say this,
but do you really think climbing the corporate ladder at MgRonald's will let him conquer the world?
Demons have a long lifespan.
Who knows what they're planning?
We need to kill him while we have the chance!
But—
This might be hard for you to take,
but at the end of the day, the two of you are from different worlds.
You weren't supposed to meet.
We'll wipe your memories
and all traces of Ente Isla from Japan!
Chiho?
What?
Wipe my memories?
I don't want that!
You can't!
I don't wanna forget.
I don't wanna forget Maou, Yusa,
Ashiya, or you.
Not even Urushihara.
We've become friends and had loads of fun times together.
You want me to forget all of that just for Ente Isla's sake?
That's just cruel!
Taking advantage of your feelings for him might be part of his plans too!
He could be trying to weaken our will to fight, thus preventing his death!
He's not that kind of person!
How can you be so cruel?
He's working honestly.
He's such a nice guy!
Why would you say that?
He's the Overlord!
The King of Demons that made tons of people suffer in Ente Isla!
Then let me ask you this: Did you ever meet Overlord Satan before he became Maou Sadao?!
I...
All you did was fight the Overlord's army.
You never met him in person.
What could you possible know about him?!
That doesn't matter!
The leader of an army takes full responsibility for its actions!
That's just obvious!
If Maou's really the sum of all evil,
then why'd he restore a messed up city to how it was?!
He did that for a reason!
His own reasons as the Overlord!
What other reason could he have other than being a nice guy?!
Isn't it only natural to apologize to people you cause trouble for?
Maou did the right thing. That's all.
He taught me how to do my job.
He took great care to teach me so many things,
got mad at me if I screwed up,
and supported me, a complete novice.
Even when he turned into Overlord Satan,
he kept his promise to teach me how to maintain the soft serve machine.
If a guy like that led demons into a war for world domination,
then he must've had his own reasons for that!
You want us to forget about everything and pardon him?!
You want us to let everything that's happened so far go?!
Calm down, both of you!
Crestia Bell.
Honestly speaking, I think you're right,
Then I—
but let me just say this:
The peace I sought was a world where everybody could have a smile on their face.
I didn't fight all my life for a peace where people could avert their eyes from the fact that they made a friend cry.
I don't intend to sacrifice anything to reach that goal.
Are you serious?
I am.
That's just a pipe dream.
A method like that couldn't possibly exist.
I'll find it.
There are sacrifices that must be made!
Even so, I'll have to find a way to avoid that,
for I am the hero.
Yusa...
So you have no intention to kill the Overlord?
Not yet, no.
I see.
Suzuno!
I went too far.
I know virtually nothing about Ente Isla,
and yet I said such horrible things to Suzuno.
Don't worry about it.
Love isn't logical in any way, shape, or form.
Yusa...
You're...
I said the same thing last time,
but attacking me in this conspicuous a place?
What's wrong with you?
I don't have much time.
Things are gonna get a bit rough!
Yusa!
I need to contact Maou!
Just who are you, exactly?
I told you, didn't I?
It's in a man's nature to take advantage of women when they're at their weakest.
You're...
Please answer, Maou!
Again?!
It's futile.
This is my ability,
Radiance of the Fallen's Heinous Eyes.
It overwhelms every user of sacred powers out there,
and it's an ability that I, and I alone, can use.
Fallen?
Does that mean you're...
Indeed.
I came to relieve you from your painful mission.
I'll have you return the sacred sword, Better Half.
Yusa!
Suzuno...
Do you feel that way too?
Do you feel like Olba did? Feel that Yusa's in your way?
This is absurd!
You people call Maou a demon,
but you're betraying Yusa, who fought to save the world! What does that make you?!
Chiho...
Forgive me.
1 Missed Call
Chiho
Huh? Chiho?
H-Hello?
This is Sasaki Chiho's mother speaking.
Thank you for always taking care of her.
P-Please don't mention it!
Um, Chiho's not home yet.
Is she with you?
Huh?
Sasaki Chiho?
No clue.
She hasn't come back here.
More importantly, I looked up that Sentucky outlet.
Something's fishy.
What do you mean?
Sarue Mitsuki was the manager, right?
The employee register doesn't actually list anybody by that name.
What?
Looks like the data's been messed with.
You said you put a transmitter on Emi, didn't you?
Do you know where she is right now?
Hold on.
What the heck?
She's moving in a straight line, right through a bunch of buildings and stuff.
Suzuno, though. Not Emilia.
Where's she headed?
Tokyo Government Office
The Tokyo Government Office, I think.
Hey, Maou! Where are you going?
Just wait for me, Chiho!
1, 2, 3, 4
Where in this silent sky does the sun rise?
A promise I made while pretending to not see it
The moon that got ridiculed
Will disappear towards the past
Being a liar and a coward
If I was at fault for everything
Then our promise might only have been a fleeting dream
I managed to hide it in the shadow of the moonlight
But I was actually crying
My tears won't flow anymore
They've dried up
If I was able to let everything go
I might be able to cry again
But this world is full of things I want to protect
The Overlord
Does
His
Job