Why, hello there, Overlord Satan.
Wait.
Should I call you Maou Sadao now?
And long time no see, Hero Emilia.
Lucifer?!
Emilia...
Wait for me.
Looks like...
things have taken a turn for the worse.
No kidding.
You've really gotten gate sick, huh?
S-Sorry.
Get it over with already.
Get out of your cage
Fly toward the sky
It all starts right here, right now
Let's picture what we can do
Unbelievable things might happen
But we can overcome them all
For our dreams
Our dreams are born from nothing
And take us to that shining sky
fly
Light blue wind
I want to spread my wings
Now here I go, with the greatest smile on my face
Let's set out to an unknown world
Go to another world
We'll be the ones to choose and decide the future
Let's chase after our dreams
There will be times when we cry
I have a really important wish
Don't fade away
I'm sure you'll be able to meet your future self
Get out of your cage
Overlord at Work!
Fly toward  the sky
How?
The Overlord
and the Hero
I was sure my sacred sword pierced you through the heart that time.
Save
Sasazuka
Good question.
How am I standing here?
Is it because of your new buddy lurking in the shadows over there?
Show yourself already,
one of the six High Priests of the Church,
Olba Meyer.
Olba?
You were the one following Emi when she entered the gate, right?
I pretty much knew this was gonna happen when I heard about that.
You're the only one who could set things up against both Emi and me.
I guess there's no point if you already know.
You look well, Emilia.
Olba...
This can't be happening.
Why are you on Lucifer's side?
Do you really want to know?
Very well. I'll tell you so you can at least rest in peace—
"We can't have the Hero brag about her exploits after she destroys the Overlord Army,
so let's kill her on the sly and seize all the power for ourselves!"
That's about it, right?
And you probably convinced Lucifer by promising to reinstate him, yeah?
H-How do you know?
Oh, come on.
That's so cliché.
"Rest in peace," in this day and age?
Even an amateur movie has better scripts than this,
you damned cueball!
Cueball?
Amateur?
Amateur?!
Hold on a second, Milord.
Did I just hear that right?
When exactly did you squander our money on something like a movie?
C'mon, it's just a movie.
I used my allowance for it.
Even I'd like a break from housekeeping every once in a while,
but I just suck it up!
I'm cutting down on your allowance, Milord!
Oh, is that how it's gonna be?
You sure about that?!
Knock it off already—
Ashiya!
This farce has gone on long enough.
It might be a bit sudden,
but this is curtains for you all.
M-Milord...
If you absolutely must watch them,
please only go when the tickets are on sale...
Save your breath, Ashiya.
That's not important right now.
I guess it's Emilia's turn now?
Or maybe the Overlord's?
Ah, screw it.
I'll go for a twofer.
Ah, I haven't tasted destruction since I lost to Hero Emilia!
Who'd've thought it'd be this delicious?
Lucifer!
Oh, keep your pants on.
They probably can't put up much of a fight, anyway.
This is embarrassing.
Are we just gonna run with our tails between our legs?!
Shut up!
We need to save Ashiya first!
Either way,
how is Lucifer using that much magic in this world?
He's been feeding on the negative emotions of humans.
What?
The recent string of robberies...
It's all their doing!
Huh? What's the point of doing that—
Despair, fear, sorrow.
They did it in order to absorb magic from the negative emotions of people driven to the edge.
A normal human would probably piss their pants if they were attacked by that demonic form, right?
That's where he's getting his magic from.
Oh, you'd realized that,
Overlord?
It's all thanks to you.
When I got caught up in the underground shopping center's collapse,
the fear and despair of humans flowed into my body, and that's when it hit me.
That's when I realized why I'd gone back to my demonic state.
Then why didn't you try to gain more magic?
If you just filled this world with fear and despair,
you could've even regained enough of your powers to return to Ente Isla.
I actually kinda like this world.
I may be a human now,
but I'm also having fun.
And I don't wanna cause problems for a world that's helped me out.
That's why I won't resort to such methods.
You've grown soft.
Way too soft, Overlord.
I'll take the lead, then.
I'll wring all the energy I can out of this girl's fear and despair.
Chiho!
What have you done to Chiho?!
Being young is such a sin.
Even the most trivial things can greatly increase a person's despair and sorrow.
Run!
Not to mention,
the negative emotions they feel toward a certain someone
is extremely easy to use.
Ouch!
Damn, human bodies are weak!
I knew it all along, but damn it!
What the hell are you whining about?!
You call yourself the Overlord?!
Maou?
Olba!
You're even using something like that?!
I need to preserve enough magic to control the gate for when we return, after all.
So weak.
Is he really the Overlord who once tried to conquer all of Ente Isla?
Hurry up.
Now's your chance to put both him and Emilia down for good.
Emi.
Don't let go.
Oh,
so he left himself enough power to teleport, did he?
However...
Whoa?!
Is this...
Koshukaido?!
We're in front of Sasazuka Station!
Why'd you teleport us to a place with so many people around?
Don't tell me you brought us here just because you wanted an ambulance!
Like hell I'd do that!
You can't escape me,
Overlord.
Lucifer!
Take too long and there'll be too many eyewitnesses!
You're such a killjoy, Olba.
If there are too many, we just need to get rid of some.
But first...
Maou?
Get a hold of yourself, Maou!
No way...
With this, he can't make a comeback like he did in Shinjuku!
Now that I've defeated the Overlord, I don't need this girl anymore.
Here, you can have her back.
Chiho!
Olba!
I will now carry out what was stipulated in our contract.
With the noise of destruction and screams of despair,
perform a beautiful orchestra for me, will you?
Stop it, Lucifer! Olba!
That's a nice scream.
Don't tell me...
Wha—
What's going on?
That's amateurs for you.
Just as planned.
You have my thanks, Lucifer.
I finally managed to regain this form.
Overlord...
...Satan?!
Is that...
Maou?
Chiho...
I see.
He came to this crowded area so that he could absorb magic from enough people.
Emi.
Hero Emilia.
Lucifer and Olba were a real handful already, and now this?!
Hey, Earth to Emi.
Damn it, Emi!
Huh?
M-Me?
Don't give me that crap!
What are you spacing out for?!
Hurry and find a way to take him out!
My powers have weakened,
and this thing's heavy!
I can't hold out much longer.
Do something about this.
Please!
Hurry up!
Are you retarded?
I've never seen an Overlord this screwed up!
I don't care!
Just do something already!
Help me out!
Huh?
No, wait.
Help me out, please!
I refuse.
I'm a Hero.
No way in hell am I helping an Overlord out!
Huh?
What the hell are you saying now of all times?!
So,
just hang in there a bit longer.
I'll finish things off in a flash.
Yusa?
You'll be safe in there, and it won't hurt.
I want you to know, Chiho.
For some reason.
I summon thee,
my powers,
to rend evil from this land!
Overlord at Work
I summon thee,
my powers,
to rend evil from this land!
Her sacred powers?
I am a hero.
The world I'm in may change,
but who I am never will!
Wow!
So cool!
Shut yer mouth!
Once I'm done with them,
I'll be coming after you!
You'd best be prepared!
As soon as possible, please.
Oh,
but first...
What'd you just do?
I put up a magical barrier.
With this, you can fight to your heart's content without causing anyone problems, right?
Well, well.
Looks like I have to go all out, too.
Whoops.
My bad.
What was that for, damn it?!
I'm not gonna let you get away with this, Lucifer!
You can't replenish your sacred powers,
so how exactly were you planning on beating me?
What's so funny?
I'd much rather not team up with a hero,
but I've sworn allegiance to Overlord Satan.
Alsiel!
That makes you my enemy,
Lucifer!
Wait, you were all right?
I was on the verge of death,
but Milord so kindly gave me enough magic to recover.
Then what were you doing all this while?
I went home to get my Demon General Cape!
I'm not going to thank you.
That wouldn't've even scratched me.
I'm impressed you can say that even though you're aware of how frail humans are.
You useless hack!
If you're one of the humans who drove the Overlord into a corner,
then show me you can fight!
I have no means to replenish my sacred powers!
If I use it all, we won't be able to return!
We won't be able to return if we lose here, anyway!
Y'know, right now,
I don't have the best role, nor am I looking too good, huh?
This isn't a movie, is it?
Yeah,
there's no way I can explain this away.
Flame Strike!
Lucifer!
Emilia,
have you lost your mind?
How could you team up with demons?
Like you're one to talk!
Look who's talking!
You're the last person I want to hear that from!
Cueball!
Damn, that was heavy!
Way too damn heavy!
But good job, me!
I set that shit down like a boss!
It's all good!
Overlord...
Guess I should get this over with quick.
I mean, we'll be late for work if we stick around any longer.
I promised to teach you how to maintain the soft serve machine today, after all.
Now then, you bastards.
You have some nerve to make me, the Overlord, a minor character.
I wonder how I should pay you back for that.
Huh?
Hey, Emi.
What do you think I should do with this guy?
Let's see.
How about starting with punishing him for messing up this city?
You're right.
By the way, Lucifer. It's gonna be all your fault if I don't make it in time for work.
What are you talking about?
What are you going to do if you end up screwing me out of my perfect attendance bonus?
Milord's talking about something we will never, ever understand.
You're a Demon General too.
Take it like a man!
Brace yourself!
Um...
I get the feeling it's a bit too late to ask this now, but
who are you guys?!
This is kinda embarrassing.
But yeah, I'm an overlord from another world.
Hey! You don't believe me, do you?!
That's not true!
I saw you do something amazing, after all.
Aww, it was nothing!
Milord.
I understand humility's valued highly here in Japan,
but I believe you can stand to be a little more proud here.
As for me, I'm human.
Well, I am half angel, though.
What?
You're half angel?!
Don't you think it's a bit too late for that,
stinkin' Overlord?
Hey, Chiho!
I'm sorry.
I've only ever thought of angels and demons as these crazy fictional beings.
Well, yeah.
What kind of Overlord works at MgRonald's?
I don't wanna hear that from a hero who works at a call center!
Huh?!
Actually, if you still had that much of your powers left,
why didn't you attack me this whole time?
You're the cowardly Overlord.
You could've been playing possum for all I knew. That's why.
Also, I needed to save up enough to control the gate so I could go back home.
So there's no way Maou and I are in some kind of special relationship, okay?
You don't have to worry.
Y-Yusa!
But what are you going to do?
You got your powers back and all,
so are you returning to Ente Isla?
Huh?
Nah.
I've got a lot of shifts at work this month.
Milord, what's more important to you?!
Conquering Ente Isla or working at MgRonald's?!
Say what?
But it's not even payday yet!
So...
What should I do?
Oh yeah, Lucifer.
Were you the one who called me at work?
That's right.
How'd you find me?
With this...
But!
Don't give me that!
My...
My wallet!
Lucifer.
Did you seriously look inside a woman's wallet you picked up?
You're the worst.
Brace yourself!
Huh? Why has time stopped at this place?
It's a magical barrier.
Emilia!
Emerada?!
Albert!
You guys are late.
Wait.
Are you Overlord Satan?!
And...
You're Alsiel?
Indeed!
Tremble in fear!
Anyway,
it wasn't just Olba.
The entire church was in on it.
But is it really okay
to leave the Overlord and his crony alone?
Well, they told us to go to Castle Overlord first,
so let's leave the rest to them.
Anyway, that's Castle Overlord.
Huh?
Emilia. This is...
I know what you want to say.
Well then.
Milord,
are you really not going to regret this?
Yeah.
We can't really leave things this way, can we?
Don't tell me...
Oh well.
This is Milord's decision.
What the hell's going on?
What happened to you two?
Who knows?
It's the boss's job to clean up after his subordinates.
Be it in Ente Isla or MgRonald's,
that doesn't change.
An overlord needs to take that responsibility.
This magic...
But still,
we caused a lot of problems
for this world too, huh?
We sent out Sonars
trying to find you and all.
Weren't there a lot of earthquakes?
Wait, was the voice that echoed in my head...
Did you hear it too?
What's this about?
I tuned
my Idea Link so that someone who was thinking about the Overlord all the time
would receive it.
Wow.
Looks like
the Overlord's quite a smooth criminal.
We're back.
We're good to go!
Good.
The church might run amok if we don't return soon.
It'd be great if you came back as soon as possible, too.
Sure.
That said, there were no deaths,
and the city's back to how it was before.
Nobody remembers what happened yesterday.
Amazing.
Is he really the Overlord?
Tell me more
Thank you very much!
Maou...
before dawn breaks
Yeah?
Are you... um...
gonna go back?
Nope. I'm not going anywhere.
More like I can't.
I believe I can flee this twilight city
I used up a lot of power restoring the city back to how it was.
now that I hold a world in the palm of my hand
I do still have a little saved up, though.
Hey, Chiho.
I could wipe your unpleasant memories with that—
The melody in my ear
is a peaceful lullaby only you are singing
Maou, you idiot!
I wish you'd never leave me
You laugh and say you won't
I reach for you to make sure,
and, convinced,
I hold you
If we can stay like this
for a little while longer before dawn breaks,
then tell me more,
here in this dream come true
The Overlord
Climbs the
Stairs
at School