Things got pretty crazy yesterday, didn't they?
Yeah,
but Sentucky might steal all our customers again if we take it easy.
You don't want to go to Greenland, right,
Assistant Manager Maou Sadao?
Maou...
Go over to Fushima Park tomorrow.
What?!
Why?!
I reached the sales target!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
The manager there asked me to lend them one of my talented employees.
Oh. You scared me there.
Apparently, there are some new attractions and even a fair,
so there's gonna be a lot of visitors tomorrow.
Of course, you'll be compensated for your travel expenses and all that.
How about it?
Will you go?
With pleasure!
I'll help too!
Nah, it's all right.
Maou alone is more than enough.
That so...
That's how it is,
so give it your best shot, my dear "talented employee".
Fushima Park, huh?
Yes, ma'am!
Get out of your cage
Fly toward the sky
It all starts right here, right now
Let's picture what we can do
Unbelievable things might happen
But we can overcome them all
Power of dreams
Our dreams are born from nothing
And take us to that shining sky
fly
Light blue wind
I want to spread my wings
Now here I go, with the greatest smile on my face
Let's set out to an unknown world
Go to another world
We'll be the ones to choose and decide the future
Let's chase after our dreams
There will be times when we cry
I have a really important wish
Don't fade away
I'm sure you'll be able to meet your future self
Get out of your cage
Overlord at Work!
Fly toward the sky
The Overlord
and Hero
Have an
Unusual Day
Hm? Tomorrow?
Yeah.
Wasabi
You're eating too much.
You haven't fully recovered yet, so don't push yourself.
But,
it's going to expire soon,
so we need to finish it all off by tomorrow.
Thank you very much for your concern, Milord.
Wow, it's true.
It says there's a new haunted house opening in Fushima Park tomorrow
and a Great Asian Reptile fair as well.
Stop fiddling around with the computer and eat already.
I can't clean up otherwise.
Whoa!
300 Species Gathering
Great Reptile Fair
It says here that 300 types of reptiles will be gathered there.
It's probably gonna draw quite a crowd.
Looks like you'll have to work hard tomorrow.
Yeah.
Oh.
Terrifying attraction
Haunted House
Welcome to Fushima Park
Terrifying attraction
Haunted House
Welcome to Fushima Park
The new haunted house is apparently scarier than "The Labyrinth of Silence",
which is considered the best in Japan.
Loads of people are gonna go to that terrifying thing.
Doesn't that mean a lot of fear could be gathered at that one place?
We might be able to harvest some magic.
In that case, I shall come along with you tomorrow
and put my flesh and bones to use for you, Milord.
So you're going too, Ashiya?
Yeah. I am.
You sit tight here in Castle Overlord.
What?
Money for food.
I'm gonna get pizza.
Like hell you are!
Udon's all you'll get!
You don't have to do anything.
I'll make it for you before I leave.
What? Come on.
That udon probably expired already.
Nah, it's still edible.
A Spirit of Wastefulness will show up if you don't eat it.
Dumbass.
Damn you!
Sorry.
Just hurry up and eat already.
We need to clean this shit up!
Chiho
Hello?
Oh, Chiho?
Yeah.
Huh?
Fushima Park?
Sure.
I'm free tomorrow.
Um, thank you!
I'm so glad you're coming along.
I didn't really want to go alone...
Yeah.
Let's meet up over there.
In truth, I wanted to go with Maou...
Hello?
The Overlord's planning on harvesting magic at Fushima Park tomorrow.
Huh?
But I heard he was going there to help out another restaurant.
So you've already heard?
Yeah, from Chiho.
She invited me to go, so I'm doing just that.
Besides, you said "harvesting", but it's just a recreational facility.
What are we supposed to do about that?
You're as naive as ever.
I want to see it with my own eyes.
Let me come along with you.
Got it.
I'll tell Chiho that you're coming too.
Why would Emilia...
I'm Maou Sadao from the Hatagaya Station branch.
Pleased to meet you.
I've heard about you from Kisaki.
She said you're rather capable.
I'll try my hardest to meet your expectations.
Well, things'll probably get very busy today,
so do your best, everyone!
Yes, ma'am!
Oh, Yusa!
Sorry. Did you wait long?
Not at all.
Hello, Suzuno.
I'll be in your care today, Chiho.
Considering this is my first visit to an amusement park and all,
I'd like it if you could teach me its ways.
You can count on me!
Thanks for waiting!
What?!
Here are your special one-pounders!
Wow!
You look so mature, Yusa!
Here are your MgTunas!
Chiho...
Yes?
You're 16 now... right?
That's right.
Damn it all!
What's wrong?
Huh?
Oh...
I was just thinking you were massive...ly cute!
Really?!
I wonder if Maou will feel the same way.
My apologies for the wait.
Shall we be on our way, then?
What's wrong, you two?
Thanks for waiting!
Right this way, please.
I need some MgNuggets.
One with barbecue sauce,
one with mustard!
One MgCafé Iced Caramel Latte,
and one MgCafé Mocha!
Two Big Mags!
One without pickles, please!
Thanks for waiting!
Way to go!
Right this way, please!
Oh, Chiho!
Hey, Maou.
I'll take three Big Mag combos.
That's three Big Mag combos?
Yeah.
Three Big Mag combos, please!
I came to hang out.
I see.
Do your best, Maou.
Thanks.
Um...
How is it?
How's what?
Oh.
Compared to our residential area branch,
things are way more hectic here.
There are loads of customers, so I'm sure I'll learn a lot about how to handle them.
Figured.
I'll have to report this to Kisaki once I get back.
I kinda knew you'd say something like that.
You have no tact at all.
Why are you guys here too?
I work my socks off every day.
I'm free to do whatever I want on my days off, don't you think?
Yeah, whatever.
I didn't just come here to play either.
I'm learning the ways of society.
Yeah, whatever.
You okay?
Too much udon for you?
This is nothing.
No big deal at all.
You should take some medicine.
Who needs medicine for a mere stomacha—
I'm worthless.
I was going to assist Milord with his magic harvesting.
This is pathetic!
Don't push yourself!
If you're gonna stay home,
just lock yourself up in there or go to sleep.
Hey, you okay?
There sure are a lot of people here.
Are they all here for the new attractions?
You mean the haunted house?
Yeah.
I've heard it's pretty awesome.
Shall we go check it out?
Yes, let's.
We might be able to harvest some magic.
It interests me in more ways than one.
Overlord at Work
Let's go.
Huh? Um...
Huh?
Chiho?!
Just how far did she run?
Seems like she went pretty far ahead.
Is that...
...Chiho?
Or not.
Hey, kid.
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
I can't find her.
Who?
My mom.
Did you get separated from her?
I can't find her!
I see.
Would you like to come with us?
I can't find Mom.
I can't.
I can't!
I can't find Mo—
I can't find—
Mom—
I can't find her.
Mo—
Ca—
I ca—
Hey...
Mo—
Oh.
Mom!
Who the hell came up with that?!
And here I thought I was resistant to such things...
Shall we go check that out next?
300 Species Gathering
Great Reptile Fair
Ch-Chiho?
It's still not too late to turn back, you know?
Nah, I'll go!
Really?
It's no big deal if you wanna go back. Really.
No.
I've come all this way, so I'm gonna go!
Really?
Could it be that you're scared, Emi?
Huh?!
Scared?!
I'm just not good with these things!
Me neither.
It sucks when they just show up out of nowhere, right?
Totally...
Can't deal with those things...
Great Reptile Fair
Anyway, it looks like there are various types on offer.
Will they have any edible ones?
Huh? Edible?
You've eaten them before?!
Indeed. Plenty of times.
Whaaat?!
Where?!
If I recall correctly,
that was when I made a journey to the south.
Okinawa?
My acquaintance there insisted that I'd regret it if I didn't sample the area's lizard cuisine.
Was there nothing else?
She was pretty persistent about it,
so even though I wasn't too keen on it at first...
...you ate it, didn't you?
That eatery prided itself on cooking lizards from head to tail.
And yes, the tail soup certainly was marvelous.
Oh...
The soup stock was peculiar, but tasty,
and its grotesque appearance didn't bother me at all.
I wanted all of Ente Is—
Why would you talk to Chiho about Ente Isla?!
What have I done?
Maou!
Yes?
Could you make a couple deliveries around the park once you're done with that?
Sure!
I'm so sorry.
No, it was all my fault.
Don't sweat it.
What?
You're so cute, Yusa.
Jeez...
I'm from MgRonald's.
Thanks for waiting.
Right on time!
Could you bring that inside?
Um...
This is the Big MgTuna.
This is amazing!
I never expected there to be so many types.
Totally.
Well?
Did you spot the one you ate?
No.
I'm trying not to see them that way.
Huh?
Is this monkey...
...lost?
He's dressed, though.
Come on out. There's nothing to be afraid of.
This monkey kinda pisses me off...
I'll be leaving, then. Please call us any time you like.
Huh?
Sadao!
Sadao?
Yeah, our monkey.
"Monkey"?
Sadao!
Where'd he run off to?
Where are you?
S-Sadao!
What should we do with him?
Leave him at lost and found?
Sadao!
Ya can't up'n run off by yerself!
I'm glad you found him.
Yeah.
Maou?
Oh, Chiho.
Thanks a bunch.
Is Sadao his name?
Yeah.
So you were lost, Sadao?
I'm glad you found your master, Sadao.
Sadao sure does love his women.
What do I even do with him?
Yeah...
And he especially likes the big ones.
"Big"?
Knock if off, you guys!
What?
Attention, please.
Crocodiles have escaped from the Reptile Fair.
Chiho?!
Please evacuate to a safe area.
Please don't panic while evacuating.
Don't get separated from your kids!
Are you okay, Chiho?
Yeah...
Suzuno?
Return to the depths of Hell, O blackened souls.
By my command, cowardly beings begone!
Is that... Maou?
Looks like it.
Why?
He could've used the chaos to harvest even more magic,
but instead, he used what little magic he did harvest to help humans!
What in the world are you thinking,
Overlord Satan?!
You were even better than what Kisaki told me.
Really?
Thank you very much.
Well, I've got cleaning up to do,
so I'll see you at work tomorrow, Chiho.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
Acting like he's busy, jeez...
Nah...
Just seeing Maou being all cool made me glad I came.
That so?
Besides, I got to have tons of fun with you two.
That's more than enough for me!
And I got to relax for the first time in a while.
Right?
Yeah, that's right.
Suzuno?
Huh?
Oh, right.
Did you manage to harvest any magic yesterday?
Yeah, kinda, but I guess I ended up using it all.
Huh?
I knew Urushihara's ramblings would be just that...
I apologize profusely for doing this while you're eating, Milord.
Man, it hurts to even look at you.
You needn't worry.
Yeah, he just overate.
Shut up!
Don't say another word.
Package for you!
Coming!
I'll go—
Crap! I can't put any strength into my legs!
Coming right away!
Hey, wai—
I said I'll go!
Package for Urushihara Hanzou.
Urushihara?
Jungle...
Uh, you see... this is...
What the hell is this?
Way too close!
Just go ahead and say it.
What did you do while I was living on the toile—
Wanna go to the hospital, Ashiya?
N-No, thanks!
Seriously, you okay?
Shaddup!
I don't want your concern!
1, 2, 3, 4
Where in this silent sky does the sun rise?
A promise I made while pretending to not see it
The moon that got ridiculed
Will disappear towards the past
Being a liar and a coward
If I was at fault for everything
Then our promise might only have been a fleeting dream
I managed to hide it in the shadow of the moonlight
But I was actually crying
My tears won't flow anymore
They've dried up
If I was able to let everything go
I might be able to cry again
But this world is full of things I want to protect
The Hero
Sticks to
Her
Beliefs
Belief