Who could it be this early in the morning?
Who knows?
It's a tad too early for newspaper salesmen to be visiting.
Greetings!
"Greetings"?
Milord, could it be...
...staircase girl from last night?
Probably.
Greetings!
Coming.
My apologies for disturbing you this early.
I'm Kamazuki Suzuno. I just moved in next door the other day.
I was quite rude when we first met last night
and undoubtedly inconvenienced you, so I'd like to apologize and show my gratitude.
G-Gratitude?
Oh, nice to meet you.
I'll introduce myself.
I'm Maou Sadao.
Here's a little something as my greeting and thanks.
It's not worth much,
but I've heard that noodles are among the best gifts to give out when you move in somewhere.
Oh, thank you
very much!
A-Are you okay, Milord?
Wh-What do you mean?
Uh... Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm Ashiya.
Maou and I go way back.
I've heard about you two.
I haven't met the landlord here,
but she said in her letter that I should rely on you if I ever need help.
I-I see...
That letter also contained a photograph...
Oh, that's definitely from the landlord.
Anyway, I feel much reassured to know I have neighbors I can rely on.
I'd be much obliged if you deigned to guide me in the ways of the apartment.
Pfft. "The ways of the apartment", she says.
Is someone else in there?
Yeah, a recent addition to the residents here.
I'm Urushihara.
Pleased to meet you!
He's also a total bum.
I'm not doing this because I want to!
Then why are you doing this again?
Well, that's...
I see. Say no more.
See what?!
Well, then. I shall take my leave.
I am in your care.
L-Likewise.
Get out of your cage
Fly toward the sky
It all starts right here, right now
Let's picture what we can do
Unbelievable things might happen
But we can overcome them all
Power of dreams
Our dreams are born from nothing
And take us to that shining sky
fly
Light blue wind
I want to spread my wings
Now here I go, with the greatest smile on my face
Let's set out to an unknown world
Go to another world
We'll be the ones to choose and decide the future
Let's chase after our dreams
There will be times when we cry
I have a really important wish
Don't fade away
I'm sure you'll be able to meet your future self
Get out of your cage
Overlord at Work!
Fly toward the sky
The
Overlord's
Neighbor
Helps Him
with His
Money
Issues
Hello!
This is Emerada Etouver.
I know already.
And this is Yusa—no, wait.
This is Emilia.
I just got your package.
What is this?
Oh, it arrived already!
Amazing! I only sent it yesterday!
That was so fast.
That box contains sacred powers.
What?
Sacred powers?
I had it manufactured in a form that you could store in Japan without having it stick out like a sore thumb.
Oh god...
"Holy Vitamin B"?
It's not B. It's Beta!
Whatever.
So what, drinking this will replenish my sacred powers?
Holy Vitamin
That's right!
But be careful with the dosage.
"Dosage"?
Is there a recommended amount or something?
There is.
Consider the limit to be two bottles per day.
Take one in the morning and one in the afternoon,
but don't drink two in the afternoon just because you forgot to take the morning dose or something.
Oh.
I kinda get it now.
Great!
Make sure you know the directions, the dosage, and how to use it properly!
Later!
Just where is she right now?
Well, it can't hurt to try it out.
Why is it so hot each and every day?
And those guys don't seem to be up to anything, either.
I get the feeling I'm just wasting my blood, sweat, and tears here...
It's all about perspective, girl!
So what if the Overlord faction's just working like normal folk every day in order to put food on the table?
Peace is a good thing!
Then again, from another perspective,
you could say I'm just stalking some veterans who are peacefully living out their days.
Good grief.
Do you know not how to even dry garments?
What?!
You really have no idea how to do any chores, do you, Hanzou?
Oh, shut up already.
It'll lose its shape if you put it out to dry all wrinkled up.
That'll just ruin the sides.
Huh? Who's that?
Oh, I am so sorry.
Aw, jeez.
It really feels like there's another Ashiya now.
What on earth is going on?
Is she another demon?!
Villa
Rosa
Sasazuka
This is a bit risky, but I don't have a choice here, do I?
You have to be more responsible now, Hanzou.
Come, listen here.
You chop up the spring onions and then churn it.
Then you dilute the paste with cold water.
With just this, your meal's ready as long as you boil the udon noodles.
And if you soak them in cold water once they're done boiling, voilà!
You have cold noodles.
Add some raw egg, and they'll be perfect.
What?
I gotta boil noodles in this heat?
You will be eating this for every meal, every day.
Would it not be prudent to spice things up a bit?
You tell him, Kamazuki.
The rest of us are white noise to him.
Come on, grate some ginger.
You know how to use a grater at least, don't you?
Sure.
Huh?
Are we out of ginger, Ashiya?
Come to think of it, I think we used it all up yesterday.
My apologies, Kamazuki.
Will spring onions do for today?
Urushihara, the fridge is not an air conditioner!
What the heck are these people doing?
I'll go get some ginger from my apartment.
Oh shit!
Do you have to fall down every flight of stairs you see?!
M-Maou!
You're a hero, so you should really stop doing that.
The hell are you two doing?
My apologies.
It was my fault for suddenly opening the door.
Nah, it's not.
I just lost my footing because I was careless.
Seriously.
And you call yourself a hero?
Yusa.
I grabbed everything I could find lying out there.
Oh, good job.
Leave it over there.
Stop ordering me around. It pisses me off.
Actually, what is this thing?
You have vitamin drinks?
Hey!
Keep drinking stuff like that you'll get heatstroke like Ashiya over there.
What?!
You got heatstroke?
Even I fall ill sometimes.
Apparently, my gift caused this.
I should've picked something more nutritious.
N-No...
It's not your fault, Kamazuki.
That reminds me. I haven't introduced myself yet.
I moved in next door last week.
My name is Kamazuki Suzuno.
I hail from an old-fashioned family in a faraway land,
so I'm still not accustomed to this place.
I'd be much obliged if you could teach me the ways of the city.
I guess we're about the same size...
Huh?
Nothing!
I'm Yusa Emi. Nice to meet you.
Thanks for the food.
Man, there's so much to do and learn.
It's wearing me out here.
But you've been working for ages now.
You may have been idling your days away,
but I've grown immensely as a human!
At what?
Hold it right there, did you really just call yourself human?
Did you forget, Emi?
From Sunday, the day after tomorrow,
I'm a shift supervisor at the Hatagaya Station MgRonald's!
I'm gonna be an assistant manager!
Yeah, yeah.
Hey! You don't believe me, do you?
A shift supervisor holds great responsibility, and the pay reflects that!
What I find most unbelievable is that you're seriously bragging to me about that.
Well, whatever.
In time, I'll reach heights that you can't even imagine!
You're an idiot.
Hey, Yusa!
How dare you speak like that to the master of this house?
You won't get away with it!
What's up?
Emi, are you perhaps in a close relationship with Sadao?
Huh?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Well...
Your conversation sounded very amiable...
You two seem very unreserved with each other.
Yeah, sure looks that way.
Don't poke your nose where it doesn't belong!
Sure, we're unreserved,
but we don't share any trust, friendship, or the least bit of positive feelings toward each other.
In fact, if he just dropped dead, it'd pretty much make my day,
so keep that in mind.
I-I see...
I get the feeling I've gone through this before...
I don't believe for one second that it's true,
but are you going after Maou too?!
Huh?
Wh-What's up?
Are you out of your mind? What if they heard you?!
Huh? Oh...
I'm sorry.
I didn't think it was really the case...
Th-That was quite impressive, though.
How could you tell?
"How"? Well...
I probably shouldn't tell her that this has happened once before.
I just had a feeling. That's all.
I see.
Your intuition's as good as ever.
At first, I thought she was an assassin from another world,
or perhaps another demon,
but it'd be weird for an assassin to not do anything for a whole week after moving in,
and she's too polite to me to be a demon.
I should probably warn her.
Hey, Suzuno...
You might think this is all a bit too complicated, but hear me out.
What?
You shouldn't get too close to him.
It'll only cause you sorrow.
What does that mean?
He's not a man that any normal person can deal with.
You should stay away from him if you can.
I-I might not look it, but I've overcome loads of battles in the past.
If you insist this much, however, I'll be careful.
I'm sure there's something behind all this that only you can understand.
That said, it's too late for me to leave this place.
I'm fully aware this is impudent of me, but please give me your assistance.
Sure. I'll do what I can.
Really?
That's a relief.
Oh yeah. Give me a sec.
I sure hope you didn't do anything weird while I wasn't around.
Don't worry. I'm not that much of a daredevil.
Here's my address, phone number, and my e-mail address.
Feel free to ask for help any time these guys do something to you.
Understood.
I'm in your debt.
Just what the hell do you think we are?
Blood-thirsty monsters that are worse than cockroaches, that's what.
I don't think you will,
but if you dare try something on Suzuno,
I'll chop off your head and leave it hanging to dry at that window over there.
What are you supposed to be, an evil magistrate?
Well, it's about time I leave.
You don't have to worry.
They might not look it, but they're law-abiding citizens.
See you.
It's all good.
I'm fine this time.
Really.
Was that a scream I just heard?
No, she managed to grab on to something halfway down.
So it seems.
Oww...
Overlord at Work
I'm off.
Best of luck, Milord.
You don't have to see me off. Just get some rest.
Man, dealing with Emi drains all my energy.
Sadao.
Oh, Kamazuki.
Sorry about earlier.
Did she do anything rude to you?
No, she did not.
Good.
I'm off to work, then.
Um... take this, if it pleases you.
Huh?
So, how is it?
Is the Holy Vitamin Beta working?
Well, I've been drinking it,
but I haven't had a chance to see its effects.
It's been a while since I've needed to fight.
Oh?
How's it going with the Overlord?
Nothing's changed.
We start arguing the moment we see each other,
and we're both busy with work, so we don't have time to get in each other's business.
You sound like the wife who complains about how she can't spend time with her husband because of work.
What the—
What are you saying, Eme?!
I'm a Hero of Ente Isle, and he's the Overlord!
He'll be my enemy until the end of time!
H-H-Husband and wife?!
Just thinking about it sends chills down my spine!
I kept watch on him this morning, and I'm still doing so!
You don't know what I've been through!
I do know!
But please,
don't do anything that would make me have to turn on you.
Relax.
I'm a Hero.
I swear on the names of my parents that I'll never do anything wrong.
Anyway,
how have things been over there recently?
Let's see...
None of the countries are showing any signs of movement on the surface.
"On the surface", huh?
Indeed.
I do hear all kinds of rumors,
but who knows if they're true?
Also...
Go on.
It seems the Church is trying to get to the bottom of Olba's disappearance.
There might even be people looking for you.
Either way,
please be careful.
Some of them could get hasty and cause problems in Japan.
A Hero's job is never done, huh?
That's true.
Anyway, I don't want to rack up a massive bill from talking too long,
so I'll hang up now.
Okay.
Later.
As you're aware,
tomorrow will see the opening of what will likely be a formidable opponent,
Sentucky Fried Chicken's new outlet.
I'll be gone in the afternoon,
so it's up to you to carry our business on your shoulders, Maou.
Yes, ma'am!
Of course, you can still contact me in case of an emergency,
but unless it's critical, you may make decisions on my behalf.
This will help you grow, too.
Understood.
We don't have many people on shift tonight, so stay alert.
You may consider that your job as shift supervisor has already begun.
Huh?
Anyway, take a break while you can.
You can go out to eat if you can get back by 6 PM.
Or would you rather get a staff meal here?
Nah, I brought food today.
Oh, Maou!
Taking a break?
Yeah.
Figured I'd grab a bite.
Maou... what's that?
This?
It's a packed lunch.
Lunch?
That's kind of a tasteful lunch box.
Did Ashiya splurge on this?
Nah, someone lent it to me.
Someone moved in next door recently, actually.
Next door?
In that building?
Yeah, it's a girl.
A-A girl?!
Don't just yell out of the blue!
A girl?
You borrowed a lunch box from her?
What's the meaning of this?!
Stop shaking me, Chiho!
D-Does that mean the girl next door gave you her...
Yeah, but please... stop shaking me!
Don't tell me...
This can't be...
This can't be, but...
Don't tell me it's handmade!
Yeah.
P-Probably.
Could you let m-m-m-me have a look?!
Got it.
I got it, so let me go!
Please!
A New Year's meal?
What?
Wanna take a look at what's underneath?
P-Please wait!
I'm not ready yet!
O-Okay.
I have a baaad feeling about this.
I ended up coming this far,
but if I can turn back here,
I probably should.
But...
But!
I've come this far!
I can't turn back!
Maou!
Open it up!
O-Okay.
Welllcome!
Another day, another stakeout.
I keep buying the same one every time.
Thank you very muuuuch!
Pleeeease come agaaaain.
Huh?
Wha' wazzat?
Are you okay, ma'am?
Look out!
Don't go outside!
Also, hurry up and call the cops!
I don't know if you're human or a demon,
but you've got some nerve to attack me in such a conspicuous location.
What do you think you're doing?
It'd be one thing if it was just me,
but if you're gonna cause problems for the other people here,
I'm not gonna show you any mercy!
Huh?
What's going on?
Hey, you!
Hey! Get back here!
Are you okay, ma'am?
What about you? Are you all right?
Sorry I pushed you like that.
I'm fine.
I just got a little scuff on my forehead.
Did you call the cops?
The alarm should've alerted the security firm and the police.
So, ma'am...
What?
I'm sorry, but our employee manual says to not let the customers leave when stuff like this happens.
The police are on their way, so could you please wait a while?
Seriously?
It worked.
The Better Half I summoned this time
contained a lot more power than it did during the battle against Lucifer two months ago.
I might even be able to call the Robe of the Vanquisher.
That purple beam completely has me stumped, though.
I've never met an enemy who could nullify the sacred sword and my powers.
'Scuse me, ma'am. Um, I believe this is yours.
Yeah. Thank you.
You'd never guess I like this kind of stuff.
That so?
Yusa!
Huh? Chiho?
Big trouble, Yusa!
What's wrong, Yusa?
Maou...
What happened to Maou?
He brought it!
B-Brought what?
A-A-A handmade lunch with a heart mark on it!
A girl gave him a two-layered box!
A two-layered box!
Huh?
1, 2, 3, 4
Where in this silent sky does the sun rise?
A promise I made while pretending to not see it
The moon that got ridiculed
Will disappear towards the past
Being a liar and a coward
If I was at fault for everything
Then our promise might only have been a fleeting dream
I managed to hide it in the shadow of the moonlight
But I was actually crying
My tears won't flow anymore
They've dried up
If I was able to let everything go
I might be able to cry again
But this world is full of things I want to protect
The Hero
Barges
into
a Fight