In the great ocean, Ignora, lies a conspicuously large landform.
It is surrounded by continents on all four cardinal directions in the shape of a cross.
This is the island protected by gods, Ente Isla.
All who live within these lands know of Satan, the Overlord.
He is the symbol of cruelty and fear, and the lord of all demons that stalk in the shadows.
Overlord Satan.
It is his life's work
to conquer the human world and bestow unto his subjects a modern-day Arcadia.
Beside him stand his four trusted generals,
Adramelech, Lucifer, Alsiel, and Malacoda.
The four take upon themselves each a continent to conquer.
In retaliation, a hero steps forward, sacred sword in hand.
Together with his allies, the hero decimates Lucifer's forces in the west.
Adramelech fell next, in the north.
Malacoda in the south soon followed.
Led by the hero, the Alliance's Order of Knights
charges toward the central continent and Castle Overlord that stands there.
Too slow!
You foolish humans!
Holy spirits, gather in the eternal land! Freeze time and cast him unto the flames of Hell!
What?!
Damn you!
Milord!
Begone!
I beg your forgiveness, milord.
Our troops are starting to be overpowered by the human army.
I believe it's only a matter of time before Castle Overlord falls as well.
Who could've guessed we'd be cornered like rats by one meager "Hero" or something?
Milord.
We should retreat for now and regrou—
Hear me, Humans!
I leave Ente Isla in your hands for now.
But mark my words: I will definitely return.
And when I do, you and all of Ente Isla will be mine!
The
Overlord
Finds Himself in
Sasazuka
Where are we?
Milord.
Are you all right?
Alsiel.
We must first find a place to nurse our wounds.
Milord, we seem to be in a rather noisy place.
Wh-What's with this world?!
Milord, your appearance!
What is this?!
Are these
human hands?!
Calm down, Alsiel.
Use not your magic without due cause.
Hey, you two.
Mind if we have a little chat?
Know your place, human!
Have you a death wish?
Whoops.
I think they might be foreigners.
Do you guys know Japanese?
Looks like you're hurt.
Did you get into a fight?
How can this be?! They should be able to tell we're demons,
even if they can't understand what we're sayi—
Alsiel.
Do not use your magic.
Not until we figure this world out, at least.
Aren't you guys hot in those outfits?
They're cosplaying.
We don't get to see them too often around these parts.
Patrol Leader Sasaki here.
Reporting an assault resulting in slight injuries.
The victims appear to be foreigners.
This seems to be a carriage,
but it doesn't need a horse...
Doesn't look like it's fueled by magic, either.
Could you get in the car, please?
If we don't see any problems—
Don't you dare put your hands on me!
You have quite the nerve, filthy human!
Let's take it easy, all right?
Uh...
This is a pork cutlet bowl.
Okay?
Pork cutlet bowl...
Yes, yes.
They took some meat and grains and soaked them in oil at a high temperature.
Then, they mashed some bird eggs and added them on top.
Finally, they heated it up one more time in an oven.
We're not actually supposed to serve you this.
However, you guys are the victims here, so just consider this my treat.
You will give me information regarding this world.
Huh?
Sure.
Answer my questions.
Alsiel.
Alsiel?
Milord!
Hey, you can't just walk in here!
Currently in use
Silence.
O-Okay.
Milord,
I'm glad you're all right.
I was able to attain some details regarding this world through hypnosis.
They call this world "Earth".
We are currently in Japan, an island country.
It seems this is Tokyo, Japan's capital,
and this building is called a police station.
The police are apparently members of a state-run organization and maintain the law and order of society.
I see.
And what is that on the table?
A "porkcut letbowl".
It is a common dish in this country.
Porkcut letbowl...
I see.
There is much power in that name.
Very interesting.
Huh?
No, this isn't that big a deal.
In this world, magic, sorcery, demons, and overlords
are all considered fictional concepts and do not exist.
Magic doesn't exist?!
Impossible!
I see.
Then the reason we could not maintain our demon forms was because of a lack of magic, right?
Right.
I never thought we'd look like this underneath, though.
Surprisingly enough, humans might be the foundation of all living beings.
Surely you jest.
It's probably an effect of this world or the gate through which we got here.
I still have a bit of my magic left.
However, it is rather difficult to stop it from leaking out.
What about you, Alsiel?
Milord, could it be that this...
No, I don't think your magic did that.
I see.
If we ration our magic, we should be able to make it last a while longer.
The problem is that we don't have the means to generate any more.
However, as long as the concepts of magic and sorcery exist, fictional as they may be,
there might be a way to recover our magic.
The only course of action left to us is to find that method and regenerate our magic.
Until we do, we have no choice but to live in this human world and abide by its rules.
Reality is a cruel mistress.
Indeed.
But in order to do that, we must first
obtain a family registry and a certificate of residence from the regional council.
Milord...
Huh?
Here you go...
Good.
Next, we need to create a bank account.
This is what we'll use to do that.
What is that paper?
It's the currency this country uses.
I borrowed it from that policeman.
We'll also be using this seal.
I made it on a whim earlier.
Impressive.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Mori Real Estate
TEL  (03–0000–0000)
Lastly, we'll obtain a base of operations from this realest ate agency.
We are looking for a house.
All right, what kind of house are you interested in?
They understood you!
C-Calm down, Alsiel!
Picking up a language like this is a piece of cake for me!
All right!
I've got this!
The landlord here is a very charitable person.
She says she'd gladly welcome tenants like you with uncertain backgrounds.
Th-This is...
Yeah, even I can tell what kind of place this is.
At least it has two floors.
It has six rooms too.
And here's Apartment 201.
What, just this one room?
We'll just have to consider ourselves lucky that it's not worn down.
This is a toilet compared to the old Ca—
Good day.
Is that... a person?
So you're the two who wish to move into this place.
It talked?!
This is the landlord.
She lives right next door.
I'm Shiba Miki.
Miki, written with the characters for "shining beauty".
Oh, but you can call me Mikity.
Yes, ma'am.
Milord.
Are you really okay with this place?
Apparently, in this world, they like to say that you must "work your butt off" to attain your objective.
I'm sure living in this kind of Castle Overlord is just one part of it.
Milord...
Let's start a new journey from here...
Milord.
Milord!
I had no idea this body required sustenance.
Well, it is a human body.
Also, why the hell did just one of IV drop things cost as much as one month's rent?!
This must be what they mean by "When it rains, it pours."
Things could've gotten a lot worse if that mysterious landlord hadn't saved us.
Apparently it's called National Health Insur—
Anyway,
money makes this human world go round.
We can't spare any more magic either.
That means there's only one thing we can do.
And what would that be?
Whoops, I screwed up.
Fool!
Resume forms aren't free, you know?!
Here we go... "Maou Sadao".
"Ashiya Shirou".
Isn't this name kind of strange?
It's too late for that.
We already got our family registry made.
Milord.
What's up?
Maybe you should spend our money a bit more wisely.
But I'm being plenty wise about it.
Summer's right around the corner, so we need a fridge.
A washing machine will cost less in the long run than using the laundromat.
I also need a bicycle to get to and from work.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm saying you could've paid in installments.
I hate loans.
Oh, come on!
You know installment payments come with an extra handling fee.
I don't want to pay for nothing.
Then let me ask you this, milord.
How are we supposed to survive until our next paycheck on just konjac, cucumbers, and milk?!
Well, that's...
I-It's not like we're penniless now.
There's still some money in our wallets.
Also, maybe we could get some staff meals where I work.
We're going to die.
Are we going to eat burgers and fries every meal until payday?
Supersize me, huh?
If we maintain a high-calorie, high-cholesterol diet from now on,
it'll be fun to see what we end up like in ten years' time.
It'd be nice if we didn't die due to living a terrible lifestyle before we got home.
The rate at which time passes is a lot different from when you're just looking back.
Ten years may seem like a second, but it is actually an extremely long time.
Maintaining your health over such a long time period is very difficult, you know?
Do you even understand that?
Oh, shut up!
I'm going to work!
Milord!
I'll listen to the rest of your lecture when I get back.
That's not what I mean!
You need an umbrella!
Let's go, Dullahan!
Guess I should get ready to go out as well.
Uh, here.
Huh?
You can have it.
But...
My workplace is right over there.
The MgRonald's in front of the station.
Well...
Go ahead and toss it out when you're done with it.
Whoa, it's cold!
This week will decide who in this district made the most promo item sales.
I'm sure I'm gonna set a new record for Black Pepper Fries orders!
Welcome!
What can I get for ya?
A cheeseburger and a small Coke.
Would you like some Black Pepper Fries with that?
No, thanks.
That's right.
I need to take this step by step as I make my way back to being the Overlord.
A thousand yen, so your change is...
So that's a Happy Meal with a MgChicken and an iced coffee.
730 yen, please!
Oh, would you like to use the microwave too?
Huh?
If you've got any baby food that can be microwaved,
we can heat it up along with your order.
Oh.
That would be great, thanks.
No problem.
Maou, you're really amazing!
You even realized that she'd be carrying some baby food around!
Oh, that?
Studying the seventeen points of customer service in your spare time
really pays off in the long run.
You're so cool!
It's like you're a full-fledged working adult!
Well,
I'm just a part-timer, though.
We lost our jobs again, Ashiya.
Call me Alsiel.
In the first place, our objective is to return to Ente Isla.
We are not here to earn a daily wage!
You're right.
You look for a method to get our magic back.
I'll get a job and earn some money.
I need you to use your brain.
The concepts of overlords and magic exist in this world.
If we can find their origins...
...we might be able to regain our powers!
Yeah.
And once we do, let's conquer not just Ente Isla,
but this world too!
Milord!
Call me Maou.
Your wish is my command.
I, Alsiel, will definitely find you a road to world domination!
Stand up, Alsiel.
We're in public.
That's what we agreed on, but...
Hey, I got a 200-yen raise!
The rookie who joined today is pretty talented!
Milord, you're acting like a total underling!
What's going to happen to me if even you act like that?!
Well, I haven't been doing too great either.
I can only make guesses with what I have now.
Oh, an earthquake.
It's an earthquake, Maou.
Oh yeah.
Chiho.
Yeah?
Everyone makes mistakes.
But this makes it six times this month that I dropped fries all over the floor!
Yep.
You do it once every two days.
I'm stuck cleaning while everyone else waits on customers.
The floor's going to turn into a potato farm if this keeps up!
Yo, you two kids on break.
Why so tense, Chiho?
What's up, boss?
It's Kisaki, damn it!
Anyway, it's starting to get crowded.
When your break is over, I want you to give me 110%.
This rush will be critical if we want to make the most sales.
I'm counting on you.
By the way, Sasaki,
let's try not to drop any more fries, 'kay?
Yes, ma'am.
Tuna burger combos are 10% off!
Would you like some Black Pepper Fries?
Welcome.
I'd like a smile, please.
W-Welcome!
I can do this if I keep this up!
I can get us the most orders in the district!
Huh?
They're not done yet?
Don't tell me it's broken!
Black pepper? More like broken pepper!
This isn't the time for jokes!
What should I do?
If this isn't fixed, we won't be able to get the most sales!
Should I use what little magic I have left?
Save your powers for when you really need them.
What's wrong?
It's all over.
It's not your fault.
They even said it could be fixed tonight.
Maou, we need to talk.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh shit, what now?
Is she going to blame me for us not making the most sales or something?
Wait, it's not like I broke that thing!
Was I acting too suspicious when I was going to use my powers?
Sorry I kept you waiting.
Relax.
It's not bad news.
I just got approval from the main office.
And?
Maou Sadao,
from today on, you're a full-time employee.
All
right!
I'm a full-time employee, Ashiya!
I'm getting a raise!
Hey.
Oh, you're the girl from this morning.
I went to your restaurant afterward.
What, really?
I didn't notice at all.
You should've said hi.
I was watching you from the bookstore across the street.
Huh?
It's just that you look so different, I thought I was mistaken.
You tried to use your magic, didn't you?
Magic?
You...
Are you...
Why are you working part-time at MgRonald's,
Overlord Satan?!
Hero Emilia?!
1, 2, 3, 4
Where in this silent sky does the sun rise?
A promise I made while pretending to not see it
The moon that got ridiculed
Will disappear towards the past
Being a liar and a coward
If I was at fault for everything
Then our promise might only have been a fleeting dream
I managed to hide it in the shadow of the moonlight
But I was actually crying
My tears won't flow anymore
They've dried up
If I was able to let everything go
I might be able to cry again
But this world is too full of things I want to protect
The Hero
Puts Work First
and Stays Over at the
Castle Overlord