Why?
Why is the Overlord saving people?
Get out of your cage
Fly towards the sky
It all starts right here, right now
Let's picture what we can do
Unbelievable things might happen
But we can overcome them all
For our dreams
Our dreams are born from nothing
And take us to that shining sky
Fly
Spread your wings
I want to spread my wings
Now here I go, with the greatest smile on my face
Let's set out to an unknown world
Go to another world
We'll be the ones to choose and decide the future
Let's chase after our dreams
There will be times when we cry
But they will be precious memories
Don't fade away
I'm sure you'll be able to meet your future self
Get out of your cage
Overlord at Work!
Fly towards the sky
We're right above the scene of the subway collapse in Shinjuku.
The Hero
Feels the
Warmth
of the Heart
Several emergency response teams have arrived,
and the situation looks very serious right now.
But surprisingly,
despite the scale of the accident,
no deaths have been reported.
I repeat,
we've received information that nobody has been killed in this disaster.
The police—
Daddy!
I brought lunch.
Thanks, Emilia.
Is it good?
You bet it is.
Hey there.
Nord. Emilia.
Oh?
Did you make this, Emilia?
That's right.
Looks great!
It is!
You can have some too!
Really?
Well, isn't that nice?
Did you hear?
Apparently, the Overlord's army has taken over the Eastern and Northern continents.
Rumor has it, the West won't last much longer either.
The Western continent is protected by the Church and the Royal Army. It's unassailable.
There's no need to worry.
Nah, man.
They have a snowball's chance in hell against Demon General Lucifer.
What's this world coming to?
Are the demons going to come here?
It'll be all right.
The Cardinal's prayers will protect us.
Don't worry.
Daddy's right!
He never lies!
Right, Daddy?
Yeah.
You're right.
I agree.
Are you the Cardinal?
Have you come to save us from the demons?
Daddy!
The Cardinal's come to save our village!
Emilia...
He's come to pick you up.
Huh? Why?
I have
protected and raised you all for this day.
Daddy?
You're the daughter of an angel.
You're the only human in all of Ente Isla
with the strength to defeat the Overlord.
What? But I can't be.
I'm your daughter.
You are,
but your mother was an angel, and you're her daughter too.
I don't get it.
You're not making any sense at all.
You'll come to understand someday.
What about you, Daddy?
You're coming too, right?
Forgive me.
I hope this world is freed from darkness
so that you may live a life overflowing with light.
Emilia, my dearest daughter...
I love you from the bottom of my heart.
That turned out to be the last time
I ever saw my father.
A few days after I was torn from him,
Demon General Lucifer led his army to our village
and razed it to the ground.
Stay strong, Emilia.
You're the daughter of one of the great angels, and you've inherited her powers.
Listen closely.
The sacred flame sword, Better Half,
may only be wielded by the progeny of a child of Man and a child of God.
You're the only human in all of Ente Isla with the strength to defeat the Overlord.
Then teach me how to wield it...
...so that I can kill the Overlord myself.
What the?!
Well, you looked like you were kinda spacing out,
so I was wondering if you were okay.
I'm fine!
I don't need you to worry about me.
And you look like a bum again.
Don't call me a bum!
Maou!
Chiho.
Um, I...
I'm just glad you're all right.
Thanks.
You guys over there.
It's dangerous there, so could you come this way—
Huh?
Are you Inspector Sasaki's daughter by any chance?
Y-Yeah.
My father is Sasaki Senichi from the West Shinjuku Station,
if that's who you mean.
Hm?
I knew it.
I'll go get him right away.
Oh?
Um, Maou...
Yeah, I know.
You don't want him finding out that you were caught up in all this because you were on a date with a guy,
even if you had nothing to feel guilty about, right?
More like I don't want him finding out about me.
Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I'll see you tomorrow, then.
Sure.
Thank you too, Yusa.
Sasaki from the West Shinjuku Station, eh?
So that wasn't just a coincidence.
The magic I used on him right after getting to this world
affected his daughter as well and made her hear voices.
What's your plan?
I'll go eat underground at different towns
and wait for them to collapse.
Are you retarded?
Shut yer mouth.
I'm tired, so I'm gonna go home and sleep.
Wait!
Nothing else is going to happen today.
The enemy's attack failed, after all.
Failed?
Yeah.
That was no natural disaster.
The fact that it happened at a place both you and I were in
means that someone caused it.
I don't know if they shot off a Sonar,
caused magical interference, or what,
but there's one thing I can say for sure:
We've been exposed.
And who's this "enemy"?
They were right there, close to us.
However, they didn't follow through.
I'm guessing it's because I was getting my powers back.
But in that case, who could it be?
Neither magic nor sacred powers can be replenished here in Japan,
so who is it that can afford to use this much power?
Emi!
Over here!
Rika!
Hey Emi, are you all right?
Looks like you do have a friend after all.
Emi!
What does that have to do with anything?!
Hey, Emi!
Hurry up and go to her.
Emi!
I know already!
Emiii!
Hurry up!
I'm so glad you're safe, Emi!
Later.
Milord!
What's with you?
I'm terribly sorry!
Not only did I allow Emilia to get close,
but I didn't even notice the enemy's approach!
And to top it all off, you had to save my life!
How could I possibly atone for my failure?
Quit your crying. It's time to go home.
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm fine.
And now you're being so considerate!
Milord!
Get off me!
Gross! Stop!
Oh. So your parents are overseas?
Yeah, something like that.
I'm sorry about all this.
I'm the one who should apologize for dragging you here.
That's not true.
Well...
How should I put this?
Speaking from experience,
when this kind of thing happens, I feel like it's better to have company.
Thanks for waiting.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
Nope.
I'm so hungry I might die of starvation instead.
All right, then. Eat up.
Milord...
Please punish me...
I told you it's okay already!
Could we have a moment?
Thanks for the food!
Well, if you've got that big an appetite,
I guess I have nothing to worry about.
Yup!
Sorry, give me a minute.
Hello?
Oh, you got it?
Well, it ain't that pricey,
and old gramps loves all kinds of shochu.
Today's incident?
Ya don't got ta worry 'bout that.
'Twas close ta where I work, but I'm hunky-dory.
Pass it along, will ya?
Talk to ya later!
'Twas from my mum!
Is that her?
Yeah.
That was the first time I heard you speak with a dialect.
I'm from Kobe, you see.
Well, it's a pain every time my hometown comes up in a conversation.
"A pain"?
People ask a bunch of questions oh so casually.
About the earthquake and stuff like that.
I was just a kid back then,
but I still can't forget what happened.
I was so, so scared.
A lot of things happened that I can't easily talk about even if people ask me.
"Can't easily talk about"...
What?
Where's this coming from?
You're the first.
You're the first person to show some tact and not ask me about the earthquake when you heard I was from Kobe.
When people lose the sense of values they've relied on all their lives,
there's no telling what path they'll take.
There are some who try to take advantage of the chaos and do bad things.
But on the other hand, there are some who desperately try to save other people,
even though they don't know how they're going to live from then on.
I really felt it back then.
Y'know, it's like that one cliché.
Like when you're conflicted, you get an angel and a demon on each shoulder, arguing over what you should do.
I really felt that if people truly wanted to, they could become angels or demons.
Angels
or demons?
You're theater actors, aren't you?
I used to wanna be an actor too, so I get it,
but you can't practice your lines on the streets.
Uh...
I'm sure you've got your own problems like selling your quota of tickets,
but do your best, okay?
Well, I should be the last person saying this, what with my broken dreams and all,
but it's all over if you give up.
I see.
Also, be careful.
There've been a lot of muggings recently.
Make sure you don't end up as suspects.
Overlord at Work
Go ahead and take a bath, Emi.
O-Okay.
Serial Muggings
Only one culprit?!
Seventh case this month
Robert Tashiro
Serial Muggings
Only one culprit?!
Seventh case this month
Robert Tashiro
Serial Muggings
Only one culprit?!
Seventh case this month
Robert Tashiro
An office worker had his bag stolen on the street.
What? Again?
The police commissioner says they're investigating potential connections between the recent string of incidents.
There's been a lot of them recently, hasn't there?
At times like these, you start wanting to have a bodyguard or something, right?
But I guess you've got one already.
Huh?
Y'know, the guy you were talking to back there.
He's just—
Oh-ho? So casual.
He seemed like a really nice guy, though.
I can't stop thinking about it.
He's—
That guy means nothing to me!
I'll leave your towel here.
Yeah, thanks.
I wonder what this is.
This warmth.
This feeling.
Is this what a human heart feels like?
Then what did he feel back there that made him save people?
What do want this early in the morning?
Relax.
There's no poison or sharp objects inside.
I don't think I've ever gotten anything safe from you, though.
Oh, really?
Does that mean I don't have to return the 1,000 yen you lent me the other day?
We're even with this.
Huh?
What about when you promised you'd leave us alone for a while?!
Null and void ever since I became your guarantor.
Damn you!
Was Alsiel all right last night?
He wasn't injured or anything.
Looks like he was wounded mentally, though.
Huh?
Milord!
Please forgive me!
He knew I got my demon form back for a bit,
but he was beating himself up all night over not being able to do anything when I was in trouble.
That's why he's out like a light now.
Jeez.
What about you?
Were you all right?
You used some of your powers to put Chiho to sleep, didn't you?
I-I've not fallen so far that I need my enemy to worry about me!
Maou
Sadao
Ashiya
Shirou
That so?
Well, whatever.
Leave if you're done here.
You don't have to tell me to!
First thing in the morning, man...
Huh?
Hey, Emi.
Be careful walking down these stairs with heels—
An enemy attack?!
Good grief.
Sure, this might only be your temporary form,
but you're still Hero Emilia, who drove Milord into a corner.
Why are you falling down staircases and hurting yourself all over?
This hurts Milord's reputation more than it does yours.
Oops.
We only have band-aids.
Didn't we buy gauze and stuff like that?
Oh.
It's a pain,
but could you go to the drugstore in front of the station and buy some gauze and bandages?
I don't want her to nitpick our shit again.
Certainly, Milord.
Could I borrow Dullahan for a while, then?
You have my permission.
Guess I should at least disinfect your wounds first.
First, use this—
Don't touch me!
I can do it myself!
Gotcha.
I'm so sorry.
Go ahead and do whatever.
Oww!
Does it sting?
It does not!
Whoa!
What the hell are you doing?!
Shut up!
Aren't you supposed to be the Overlord?!
Act like one and go cause the world pain and suffering!
Huh?
What are you even saying?
What the heck?!
You're broke, you cook for yourself,
you're highly valued at your workplace,
and you even seduced a high school girl!
I've never even heard of an overlord getting cocky just because a high school girl loves him!
Hey, one of them's not like the others.
I'm right on all counts!
Well, what about you?
I've never seen a Hero fall down stairs, cry, and get first-aid from demons before!
Why are you so nice to me?
Why are you so nice to me,
to people,
and to the entire world?!
How can you even be nice?
If you can be a nice guy, then why...
Why did you kill my dad?!
The Overlord I knew was supposed to be heartless!
He was supposed to think nothing of human lives!
He was supposed to like seeing the world painted red and filled with sorrow more than anything else!
I—
You burned down fields,
destroyed castles with lightning,
flooded towns,
and let your demons commit countless atrocities.
So Overlord Satan,
I will never forgive you even when I'm dead.
You took the home Daddy and I lived in,
Daddy's fields,
Daddy's life,
and my peaceful life away from me!
I cannot forgive you!
I've never thought about it too deeply myself,
but I'm sorry.
Back then,
I didn't understand humans too well.
Pardon my intrusion!
I met Sasaki over there, and she said she wanted to meet you, Milord, so—
Oh...
I knew it...
So the two of you were like that...
Ch-Chiho...
Ch-Chiho!
You've got the wrong idea!
I-I'm so sorry!
Chiho!
This is bad, isn't it?
A quarrel with your ex over another beautiful woman, I take it?
That's when the woman involved shows up
and finds out that your ex is still a part of your life.
Much like blood with high cholestrol levels,
this is one messy romantic drama.
Huh?
Really?
Hold it right there.
I'm Shiba Miki, the landlord.
You're Mr. Maou's girlfriend, are you not?
Wh-Who'd go out with a guy like him?!
What?!
Um, ma'am—
Non.
Call me Mikity.
R-Right...
I've decided to renovate this place.
I'm here to notify the tenants.
Things have been quite dangerous lately, what with the collapses and all.
I-Indeed.
Maybe something will happen today as well.
Wh-Who knows...
Anyway, it looks like that cute girl from earlier ran off toward the station in tears.
It shook?
Mr. Maou.
If you dragged her into this mess, you have to be the one to get her out of it.
Uh, what?
She took the brunt of a Sonar and formed an Idea Link.
I'm sure you've already realized that it was no mere coincidence.
Don't the three of you know better than anyone that thoughts and free will hold mighty power?
You'd better hurry up,
or it'll be too late to do anything.
Landlord?
Ugh.
I think I'm going to get gate sick.
Get a hold of yourself.
I don't think we'll have time to rest even when we get there.
Did you find something?
An unnatural magical reaction
that was on a whole different scale compared to Japan's magic reserves
that were calculated using Sonar readings.
Is Emilia in danger?
That's a possibility.
Might be a good idea to get ourselves ready for battle.
Understood.
I'll deal, so let's hurry up.
Very well.
Here we go!
Don't shake me so much!
Huh?
Why am I crying?
I guess I really do love Maou.
Oh...
I-I'm sorry.
Oh wow, you're worth devouring.
When I failed last time,
I took a chance and kept my eye on you.
I never expected you to fall into despair over them so easily.
Sasaki Chiho.
Huh?
I will feed on your despair and resentment toward the Overlord and Hero
and materialize them.
Don't just stand in the way—
Whoa!
Come now.
It is time for the hunt.
Today, I'll surpass the Overlord.
How terrible!
He's—
Who is it?
Did he do this?
Obviously.
I knew it.
No way!
Why, hello there, Overlord Satan.
Wait.
Should I call you Maou Sadao now?
What are you doing here,
Demon General Lucifer.
1, 2, 3, 4
Where in this silent sky does the sun rise?
A promise I made while pretending to not see it
The moon that got ridiculed
Will disappear towards the past
Being a liar and a coward
If I was at fault for everything
Then our promise might only have been a fleeting dream
I managed to hide it in the shadow of the moonlight
But I was actually crying
My tears won't flow anymore
They've dried up
If I was able to let everything go
I might be able to cry again
But this world is full of things I want to protect
The Overlord
and The
Hero Save
Sasazuka