Shinichirou has a cockroach under his shoe~♪
You're strong.
You really liked it, right?
But even so...
I'm sad.
Really, really sad.
Isurugi Noe...
Because... I lost my tears.
What I'm going to tell you is something I've never told anybody else.
I need you to trust me on this.
Trust-?
What is... what are tears?
Well, for example when you are sad...
That's not what I meant. What are tears?
Umm... In order to clear the eyes, the tear glands secrete... {was "Well... It's the secretion of the lacrimal gland as a result of the over-reaction of feelings."}
I have high expectations of you.
Eh?
I have a mission.
I have to go and retrieve my tears.
For that reason, I need the tears of someone special.{This line and the two before were misplaced. Corrected. The TL should be better too.}
Umm, could that be...
Although Raigou-maru died an unnatural death,
I still have a replacement.
This is a secret between the two of us, okay?
What would you do if I told somebody?
Come on, say something.
I thought that since it was you, you'd believe me.
Umm...
See you tomorrow at school!
Did I really believe that?
Seconds, please.
Okay.
Have some more, Shin-chan. The rice we used today is different from always.
So, have you decided yet?
Not yet...
When is the due date of your school's application?
I will make sure to do it next time.
I see...
Oh yeah, Shin-chan. You know, about yesterday...
Thank you for the meal.
Tea, please.
Coming.
I'm quite naive...
Especially since mom didn't go against that.
On top of that, my work didn't get selected.
So if I give my tears to that girl...
What'll happen to me?
Maybe I'll become incapable of crying?
Well, who cares about that anyway.
Come on, your lunch's old nowadays.
If you want to, I'll switch with you anytime.
You'd give your lunch away despite the fact it has motherly love written all over it?
But, I will take that banana of yours for dessert.
Just what the hell was my mom thinking when she put a banana in my lunch?
It means that she cares about you, right?
You know, that girl's kind of strange even at school... I mean, she asked you out in public.
You are incredible.
Idiots who eat tamago-yaki dropped on the ground are even more incredible.
Living under the same roof as Yuasa Hiromi,
On top of that, falling for Isurugi Noe.
Why are you the only one?
On top of that, someone who eats others' lunch.
What's up, pimp?
What is it?
I'm giving you these.
Giving it to me?
But... this is bird food.
You don't want them?
I don't want them.
I love looking at Shinichirou!
Since you seem like you're somewhere close to the sky.
So I really am taking Raigou-maru's place?
Oh?
What?
Is it really fine with you if he's taken away?
You thought it was perfectly safe since the two of you live together?
It's not like Shinichirou-kun and I have that kind of a relationship.
Woops, maybe I said too much.
I heard a racoon killed a chicken here the other day.
Is this grave the chicken's-
It's Raigou-maru's.
You know, there's still one in there, and yet you are making this a grave...
Bye.
Wow, Hiromi! You've already declared war with her?
It's not like that.
Rai...
Raigou-maru...
's grave?
Now, isn't this a cage?
On top of that, there's still one inside.
What do you want?
You brought something else for-
Shinichirou-kun, you know Isurugi Noe?
Have you heard of the strange rumors about her?
Yeah, I heard of them from Nobuse.
It's THAT, right?
Exchanging e-mails with someone who lives underground.
Just stupid, isn't it?
On top of that, I heard that she's hitting on a guy passing by while climbing trees?
I held the bottle towards the sun.
Staring at the sparkling liquid inside.
Suddenly, everything else became dark.
And, I opened my eyes.
Maybe I should trust her, since it's just exchanging emails with someone who lives underground.
And just forget about someone ever hitting on me like a chicken.
Good morning.
Good morning, Shin-chan.
Thank you for the meal.
Bye!
Shouldn't you hurry up and go as well?
I have a request.
Oh, we've been waiting!
Wh- What is it?
Suspicious...
Give me two of the white ones, please!
Right away!
Now, tell me about that request earlier.
Well you see, she wants me to introduce her to Isurugi Noe.
Huh?
How many times must I repeat myself?
Hiromi wants me... to introduce her... to Isurugi Noe.
Oh...
Why?
Well... maybe she wants to be friends with her?
If you don't eat it straight away, our delicious Imagawa-yaki here will become cold.
I think you should learn how to treat your customers.
But, think about it, maybe Yuasa-san has that kind of interest?
Interest? What do you mean by that?
Well... How do you put it...
Traditional, is it?
Well, seems like it's fun to stand by and watch this sort of erotic things happen...
Come on, tell me what do you mean by interest.
But well, it's great that my girlfriend has a keen eye.
Right, Ai-chan?
You fool.
You seem happy.
Well, I'm not really happy.
Especially since something sad happened.
But...
I saw a sparkling light, in front of the darkness of despair.
First I saw Isurugi Noe on the tree.
After that, the chickens were assulted by a racoon.
And then, I got these seeds.
What follows is Hiromi talking to me.
When I saw her this morning...
Cockroach...
"Shinichirou has a cockroach under his shoe~♪"
In the bottle exists a monster, disguised as an angel.
I am trapped.
As I see the other bottle nearby,
I see someone who is locked up, like me.
A girl that's crying.
That's right...
If she's going to take someone's tears,
It shouldn't be mine, but Hiromi's.
You seem to be pretty popular...
There's a girl that wants to make friends with you.
I'll introduce you. When is it okay? She's quite a nice girl.
I'm sure you'll like her.
Raigou-maru's grave... it's done!
Oh? So you get things done properly, after all.
Tomoyo!
Nice shoot!
I...
Hiromi, what are you doing?
Shinichirou-kun, where are you?
Don't leave me alone!
I... What do I want to do?
Hiromi, are you alright?
Are you alright?
Yeah...
Hiromi, are you alright?
You seem to be a little out of it today.
Perhaps you should take some rest.
Yes.
Are you okay, Hiromi?
Yeah... I'm sorry.
Alright then, everyone back into position. It's a 2-on-2.
Umm...
You made the grave, right?
Y- Yeah...
I think a grave should be properly made.
But maybe it was wrong of me to make that decision alone.
That's right, I did it the wrong way.
I- I didn't mean that your way of doing it was wrong...
I heard from Nakagami Shinichirou that you want to be friends with me.
I see... umm...
That's a lie, right?
You lied to Nakagami Shinichirou, right?
A lie? Why would you say that?
That's because you don't like me.
It's alright, I'm not mad.
What's wrong, Hiromi? Are you okay?
Hey you, hold on!
Forget it... it's my fault.
Are you done with your break yet?
That's bad...
Anyways, let's go back in first.
Sorry for the wait, we're coming back now!
I see you talked to Isurugi Noe.
About the details...
It's fine.
What do you mean it's fine?
Isurugi-san declined.
She told me she can't be friends with me.
That girl...
I am sorry.
Well...
I didn't actually want to make friends with her.
Huh?
I am sorry.
But... then why...
But... I think Isurugi-san is amazing.
Since she saw through me.
Huh? Isurugi Noe?
Someone came to pick her up on a bike?
Don't leave me alone...
Don't leave me alone, Shinichirou-kun.
Who?
How did it go? What we talked about the other day.