Inside of me... you've always been crying.
"I want to wipe your tears away" is what I think.
But... I do not know what your soft, warm face will look like after the tears are wiped away.
Argh, it didn't come out the way I wanted!
I really want to draw a more gentle smile...
What are you doing?
It seems that there weren't enough people to do this work.
I see...
You aren't going to eat?
Once I'm done with this.
Ah, I see.
"Ah, I see"... What am I saying?!
What am I doing trying to look cool?!
Umm, Bo-chan?
Err... I'm stretching, stretching...
Stretching.
Stretching... that's good.
Where's Dad?
Looks like he's still at work.
How's that girl?
Working on the records.
If she doesn't help me finish it, I won't have time to take care of the dishes.
Well, you shouldn't be saying that. After all, she's helping you with chores.
So you're also on her side.
That's not how it is.
I don't want to hear it.
Damn, what's with that?
"An angel exists somewhere..."
"Only if we could save up your tears,"
"And then, make a necklace out of them..."
"We could hang it on the tree."
"The tree of tears is shining..."
I'm leaving!
What's wrong? Is that all you can do?
Just who came up with pull-ups?
Woah! Hiromi, you're unbelievable!
You guys are slow! You're already a lap behind me.
Where did all that energy come from?
Well, we have different ways of working out.
You are insane!
I'm going on ahead!
Shinichirou, you damn pervert!
Stop it, Nobuse!
You look just like an old man
with your eyes focusing right at the girls' white legs.
Hiromi, you alright?
That's your fault. She's tripped over your eyesight, which was focused on her legs.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Yuasa-san sure is nice!
She really seems like a top-student, you know.
Well even so, she's not all that proud of herself.
Just perfect, isn't she?
Now ain't you an idiot? You're living with her.
If I were you,
I would take advantage of living with her, and peek at her changing.
And have her say "kya! pervert!"
I'll pass that to Ai-chan.
Well then, later.
What's with that? You're so cold...
Wait a minute...
Jeez...
Hey you, over there!
Don't look at me without permission.
I- I wasn't really...
Hey, you!
Is there something else you want?!
I can't get down.
So you were picking food for the chickens?
This food came from the sky.
From the... sky...
This child wants to fly into the sky.
But he's locked in such a place.
I pitied him.
So I got food for him from the highest places.
Huh?
A chicken that wants to fly into the sky?
Are you not letting that one eat?
That's because that one doesn't want to fly.
How do you know these things?
I just know.
And you are the one on that side.
Eh? Huh?
You don't want to fly.
Wait a minute! What do you know about someone like me, who has only talked to you once?
You spit, right?
Well, I think I know what's going on.
It seems like you might be able to fly.
Yes.
Since your head seems quite empty.
May bad fortune befall you!
Oh, that Isurugi Noe from Class A, huh?
Never seen her before.
She transferred in last year.
She's quite cute, but...
There are some scary rumors about her.
Scary...?
For example, it's said that she exchanges e-mails with a person who lives underground
Or that she can summon a pink elephant when she whistles.
That's nonsense.
No, wait. Since it's her...
Did something happen?
She cursed me.
Well, that's bad.
What?
If Isurugi Noe calls out her Secret special disaster move, you're no match for her!
After she said "I hope it shrinks" to someone, it turns out it really did!
Oh, Bo-chan.
Do you need the Chief for something?
Err, well, not really.
After someone dad knew died last year,
Their daughter, Hiromi, was adopted by my family.
We've been in the same class since elementary school.
I was surprised.
Hiromi has always been cheerful...
And because her smiling face interested me.
Because it interested me...
Welcome home.
I'm home.
"May bad fortune befall you"...
Come on,
If you keep sighing, you'll be hit with bad luck.
Even Ai-chan is cursing people...
Huh?
Not like I'm going to do the dance because I want to.
Everyone has high expectations of you!
About what? I'm really bad at the Mugiya dance. How could I be the main star?
TL Note: The Mugiya dance is a traditional dance performed in the Toyama prefecture.
Jeez...
I really don't want to be born in that kind of a family...
I think you're thinking too much about everything.
You're making it seem like you're so much better, even though you're just one year older.
One year is a long time,
A crawling baby could even learn to walk in that time.
Before you say that, remove that beer case under your feet.
I was worried about you, you know!
Aiko!
The store's closed, huh?
Oh, Shinichirou, so you were here!
Miyokichi, you're already done with the chores at home?
Yeah.
You need anything?
Whatever burns my throat, double!
Yeah, yeah... Cola, right?
What's with you, just give it to me.
What's wrong?
I'm heading home.
I feel bad about bothering you two.
Wait a minute! You're not bothering us!
Sorry about that.
Then, see you tomorrow.
Welcome back.
Shin-chan, give me your jacket.
It's fine.
How did it go?
Nothing special.
I- I'm sor-
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I'm the one that saw you...
I should be the one apologizing!
And yet... why did you...?
Sorry...
"Kya! pervert!"
She didn't react the way Nobuse said...
But that should be the natural reaction, right?
"Kya! pervert!"
My family is taking care of Hiromi.
But...
She has always tried to keep from standing out.
Good morning.
Shin-chan, what is this?
It says that it's a publisher from Tokyo.
Did you open it?!
Answer me first!
How can you hide something like this from your parents?!
Shin-chan, you...
Shin-chan!
Shin-chan...
So you opened it without permission.
Eh? Well, that's because...
It's just that I think it's inappropriate to open it without permission.
But...
Shin-chan is the Nakagami Family's...
Shinichirou is Shinichirou.
It has nothing to do with the Nakagami Family.
"May bad fortune befall you"...
Oi!
My name isn't "Oi".
Isurugi Noe!
I have something for you.
Something nice!
So, please take it back!
"It"?
The bad luck curse!
Come if you dare!
Wonderful! It's wonderful!
It's amazing!
To praise me like that...
You can fly, can't you?
I can fly?
That's right!
You can fly!
Good boy, good boy, good boy!
Let's go show it to Raigou-maru!
Raigou-maru?
It's the name of that chicken.
What about the one that can't fly?
Ground.
So you already named them, huh...
What about your name?
Nakagami Shinichirou.
Nakagami Shinichirou...
A raccoon, maybe?
Ground! What happened?
You saw it, right? Ground!
Hey...
He flew away.
Raigou-maru flew away.
Right? Isn't that right, Ground?
"May bad fortune befall you"
Cursing someone is a double-edged sword.
I am sorry, Raigou-maru...
It's all my fault...
To have made this happen to you...
Sorry...
She's crying...
Isurugi Noe's tears...
Let's go.
Shinichirou has a cockroach under his shoe~♪
You're strong.
You really liked it, right?
But even so...
I'm sad.
Really, really sad.
Isurugi Noe...
Because... I lost my tears.
I have a mission.
I need to reclaim my tears.
You're seriously trying to replace Raigou-maru with me?
I... What do I want to do?