It was great!
Here.
Let's go up to the roof.
I'm sorry...
Huh?
I'm sorry... I didn't stop her.
Sometimes snow isn't a bad thing at all.
Because of the snow, all she had is a broken bone.
Put that aside, it's beautiful.
She's really pretty.
Why couldn't she cry?
Perhaps she has a strong mind?
Is that all of it?
Go away.
I can never forgive you.
Are you awake?
Are you thristy, perhaps?
Oh yeah, I've some coffee...
I'm sorry.
I was wondering if I can do it too after I saw Shinichirou's dance.
Onii-chan worried about me again...
And I also hurted your feelings...
You didn't do anything wrong.
I was determined to do it, and you knew nothing about it.
It's wrong because I know nothing about it...
You were only hurt because I know nothing about it.
If I knew, then I could have avoided getting you hurt...
Did you see that yesterday?
Of course I did!
Hey, put that over there.
Got it!
It's all my fault...
Things are ought to be less troublesome if everybody thinks it's their fault.
It's fine, you have nothing to do with it.
I've nothing to do with it?
You don't like that?
Is that some trash from the festival?
Did you see it?
Nah, I was working.
You probably did, right?
Yup, it's was really spectacular.
I see...
I'm sorry...
It's fine.
Just as you said, I don't like you.
Not even a tiny bit.
Nakagami-kun, that was really cool!
That was awesome!
You're everybody's hero, Shinichirou-kun.
Shut up!
Can you stop by my apartment after school?
Hey!
Shinichirou-kun.
Here.
Huh, where's your coffee?
I broke one of the cups.
It's fine...
Fine...? What do you mean?
What's going on with you...
You seems strange today.
Don't hate me...
I'm not!
You liar...
Hiromi...
I'm sorry...
I'm a bit off my mind...
Sorry, but please go home.
It's a lie that my tears are beautiful.
Slowly... slowly...
I became someone that's hated.
I can see everything, Hiromi-san.
Nice shoot!
I'm home.
There's a call for you.
The phone.
Is it the publisher?
Yeah...
They want me to send in more.
Hey, dad...
When do you usually cry?
When my heart's trembling... Perhaps...
Thanks.
When my heart trembles...
Hey, what's wrong?
Yeah, I want to talk to Shinichirou-kun.
Hiromi.
Shin-chan, there's some cheese cake in the fridge that someone brought over.
Err... The Che-
Let's talk right here.
I think I am ashamed.
I hate how I am now.
So...
I never wanted to give up because I've always loved you.
But in turn, I don't want to give you any trouble.
So, I hope you can face all this,
No matter if it's me, or Isurugi-san,
I want Shinichirou-kun to face it, and make a proper decision.
I am going to accept it too.
You know,
Hiromi, you aren't bad.
You're pretty cool.
I'm an athelete, after all.
Shin-chan, you going out?
Yeah, I'm heading out for a second.
Hiromi-chan, too?
I...
If not, take a breather inside the living room.
Sure.
Then...
Oh yeah, what are you having for dinner tonight?
Ve- Veggie stew.
That's great.
I will come over for dinner, wait for me.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Sure, I'll wait...
Take a look at it.
No.
But I only drew it becaused Noe wanted it.
You got it wrong.
Even without me, Shinichirou can do fine.
You can still draw it without me.
Then, let's put it this way,
I only drew it because I want you to read it.
No.
If you aren't gonna, I'm throwing it away.
If you want to, go ahead.
I'm throwing it away.
Just go ahead, why are you even telling me?
Where are you throwing it to?
To the sea where Ground doesn't wish to fly to.
You saw it?
I did.
Noe.
Noe!
What are you doing, you idiot?!
Coming.
I've made a little bit too much fish, have some of it.
Err, thank you.
Please come in.
Don't worry about it.
No, I'll go get some tea.
Err...
Yeah.
Well, be sure to give me back my box.
Looks like they are delicious, obaa-san.
Really?
Thanks.
Waiting takes a lot of patience, doesn't it?
Thank you... Very much...
And I thought it's still useable.
I made it.
How is it?
The last page's gone.
It's fine, I will take a guess about what happened after Raigoumaru flies.
I...
I love Hiromi.
I know.
But, I drew the picture book for Noe...
And I only danced because of what Noe said...
Shinichirou thinks I can fly.
I do think that...
I...
I love Hiromi...
But...
Whenever I see you...
My heart trembles.
Shinichirou thinks I can fly,
That is what my wings are.
Let me carry you back to the hospital.
No.
But... I am worried about your leg.
So, please trust me.
It's tough...
Inside the pot by the side, there's a cockroach.
And it's painful...
But because I can't fly yet...
Shinichirou's shoe has a cockroach.
I'm walking.
Inside the pot by the side, there's a cockroach.
Shinichirou's shoe has a cockroach.
Inside Shinichirou's heart there is...
Yuasa Hiromi!
Inside the pot by the side, there's a cockroach...!
Shinichirou's... shoe has... cockroach...
Hiromi, are you there?
I'm coming in.
Just now...
I did a split.
A 180 degrees one.
It's the first time I've made it.
Did you let Isurugi-san see the picture book?
Yup.
I want to see it too.
Let's go out together.
No...
Let's go out together!
No!
You can see it whenever you want!
Since, from now on...
I'll be by your side forever...
By your side forever...?
What's that...
It's just like an engagement...
I still haven't agreed to go out with you...
I want to wipe your tears.
As I am right now,
I can do it.
It's snowing...
Nothing...
Good Morning!
Morning, Noe!
People can really obtain tears from people most important to them.
Noe, Granny probably is going to say that too.
If you really think about the people important to you,
Then the tears will flood out.
Hiromi!
Watch your side!
If you can understand these true tears,
Listen,
Don't just use your eyes.
Find the difference with your ears too.
Okay.
Come take a break.
Sure.
It's already time to open up!
Miyokichi,
Come on, you only came early by a tiny bit!
Let's go in.