Are you alright?
Yeah, looks like it.
Shinichirou's gone too?
Yeah...
Well... I don't think it's too big of a problem.
Have you called him yet?
Looks like he turned it off.
If... something happened...
Don't be so worried.
I'm going out to look for him.
Hold on! Looking for him without thinking first...
Your bike caught on fire.
Yeah...
What should I do... I still have loans remaining on it.
But, it looks kind of pretty.
And I bought a girl's bike for work...
Argh... damn it...
It didn't explode after the gas caught on fire.
Of course, it only happens in movies.
All it does is burn.
If it would just explode, it'd be easier to let go.
You've got any money to call for a taxi?
Yup, I do.
But...
But I wonder if we can even find a taxi.
Hiromi!
Shinichirou-kun...
Onii-chan!
We are alright.
You sure you two will be alright without calling an ambulance?
You sure you're alright?
Onii-chan!
I'm fine.
I don't think I'm hurt...
I...
Thank god...
I'm sorry...
Remember to file the report at the police tomorrow.
Yes...
Well, all that matters is that you two aren't hurt.
What are you doing, mom?
Wait!
It's alright.
It's better to leave the ladies to themselves.
Mom's just too strange though!
She's putting strange thoughts into Hiromi's head!
Yeah, well...
So it's true?
Hiromi and I really are siblings?!
Enough of this!
Calm down.
There's no way this could be true, right?
Thank god you aren't hurt.
Why don't you get a change of clothes?
I'll help you out.
No, it's alright.
I can do it myself...
That couldn't have happened, could it?
Mom! Hiromi! Where are you?
Are you in here?
You are in here, right? I'm coming in.
Mom, you know...
I...
I'm tired...
My clothes are all dirty now,
I need to change.
Th- Then... we'll talk later.
But... you're acting weird, Mom.
"Raigoumaru climbed up to the top of the hill."
"It was a huge embankment, reaching 10 meters tall."
"Looking from there, it seemed like the ground was the underworld."
"Ground, who was there pecking at the feed, looked so pitiful."
"Now, let's fly."
What's this? What's going on?
"Even if that's what Raigoumaru was thinking, his stomach suddenly started growling."
"So in the end, he decided to call it a day."
"Tomorrow, after filling his stomach, he'll try to fly to the sky again."
Seems like i can't fly after all...
Hiromi, what side dishes might you have today?
Taking others into consideration, how unlike Tomoe.
Is that so?
But, being the best friend of the main character in this school's shocking, big scandal can be devastating for a mere high school girl!
Sorry...
Idiot. What should I do about your worrying?
That's exactly why I feel inadequate. {"watashi no tachiba ga nai", could be translated "I have no place" etc etc, I think this is a fairly good translation of it.}
Thanks.
I'll at least pass on the latest gossip.
Right now, a staff meeting is taking place.
The subject is our school's prodigal basketball ace.{It's about one of the excels at the school, queen of the basketball team, beautiful, and pretty...}
She, who is called beautiful and handsome...
What's the matter?
Those mean the same thing.
What?
Elegant and handsome.
Oh, is that so?
Well, fine! Let's eat up.
Here, let's switch these for today.
You were at the site of Yuasa Hiromi's accident, right?
Yup.
That No. 4 was unharmed, too?
Meh, lucky bastard.
Hey, you know...
No, it's nothing.
Yo, Nakagami, why don't you tell us...
About what really happened.
Thanks.
Me and you... are friends, right?
I'm heading back to the classroom.
We can't help it, that's what the teachers said.
Captain Takaoka, when did you become such a rule-abiding person?
When you say she's suspended, you mean from tomorrow, right?
Alright then, please allow me to skip today's practice too.
I thought you'd say that.
Why don't you go hang out with Hiromi?
Yes, thank you very much!
Let's work hard for Hiromi and Tomoyo as well!
Yes!
Isn't... that...?
He said "I love Noe"... and he even wrote it down here...
Thanks for the food.
You're welcome.
I'm heading out.
There's a fight!
What are you doing?!
Noe...
Yo.
You scared me back there.
Onii-chan said he got a week off.
Of course, after that accident happened.
I'm sorry...
There's nothing for you to apologize for.
Does it hurt?
Were you fighting for Yuasa Hiromi?
Yeah...
Hey, how's it going, Ground?
I've got more of the picture book done.
I was thinking about showing it to you.
Hiromi is our child.
I will discipline her properly.
I understand.
You did well.
Raigoumaru can't seem to fly very well.
Raigoumaru eventually noticed it as well,
In fact, even if he'd fly from a ten-meter tall cliff,
he couldn't get anywhere.
But, he pretends he doesn't know.
Why won't Raigoumaru face the truth?
It must be because he's afraid...
Afraid?
He's afraid to face the truth that he's only a chicken.
In fact, Raigoumaru knew from the beginning he couldn't fly.
So that means, Shinichirou too?
What are you doing? That hurts!
Shinichirou, you can fly.
You just don't know it yourself.
But...
That's right...
This isn't the place where you take flight.
Umm...
Hey, Noe!
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Just now, I came back from school with oji-san and obaa-san.
You went to school?
Yup.
Ice... I bought ice cream with obaa-san on our way home.
I ate mine already,
Shinichirou-kun's is in the freezer.
I was just like an idiot.
I knew that nothing like that could have happened.
Something like you being my husband's child...
Was that story a lie?
I'm sorry...
I showed you my most shameful side.
So that story was a lie?
I've been treating you too harshly...
I knew from the start that obaa-san didn't like me.
That's right.
It's because there's affinity between people.
But this has nothing to do with that.
To tell you to forget about everything up until now,
might be asking for too much, right?
Is it okay if I stay here a bit longer?
Oh my.
I used to listen to that a lot in the old days.
Do you like it?
Yes.
I was such an idiot.
Thank you for worrying about me.
I've made up my mind.
That's what I am gonna do.
It's drawing together, more and more... {actually means fill/cover up something, but I feel like this is a more accurate translation. I might be totally off, though :P}{}{}
More... more...
Should I say thank you?
I will fix everything.