Was it last year?
When we were having a competition with Hotarugawa,
Isurugi-san... err... No. 4 and I were the head of each team.
After talking to him a bit... Well...
I thought he was kind of nice, and had a crush on him.
So you were...
This talkative...
But for someone like me...
It's probably impossible.
You are...
Not the person I know so well.
In my private world...
You were...
Without any decoration,
smiling like a flower.
Shin-chan?
Are you going out?
Good morning.
Oh... mornin'!
Have a safe trip!
Ah... I'm leaving.
What are you doing?
The old man that often comes to our store hurt his leg.
Oh.
I was delivering; one serving of red bean paste and two of cream.
Oh...
What's wrong?
It's all Ai-chan's fault.
What is?
It's because you surprised me.
Hey!
Come shopping with me!
Eh? I don't feel like it.
Come on, it'll help you relax!
Let's go! let's go!
Okay, okay!
I guess you're right...
At a time like this it would be nice to see Miyokichi's stupid face...
...Miyokichi?
You're not calling him?
Ah! He told me he had something to do today!
That's right!
In that case...
Let's go!
Come on, let's go! let's go!
Hey-
Ai-chan!
Hurry, hurry!
Hey, what about this one?
Ah, looks nice.
And this...?
Fits you.
And this one?
It might be nice!
Couldn't you pay more attention?
As far as I'm concerned, anything will do.
Eh? Something that normal?
Where are you going?
Toilet.
Excuse me, I want this one!
Tah-daah!
Come on, eat up! Eat up!
Today, it's all---on---me!
Is it okay?
Of course!
Since, you know...
I'm the one at fault.
It was my own misunderstanding.
Shinichirou...
The reason she wanted to be friends with Noe...
is to get closer to a guy that knows Noe.
A guy that's closer to Noe than me!
I see...
Well, come on, think about it,
Not like you could actually get back on your feet right after realizing that,
But that's what time is for!
Sometime, for sure...
Naturally...
The time will come when you'll naturally forget about it.
Cheer up!
You're just like a little brother to me, you know,
With a face looking like that,
Onee-chan will get worried!
You're so proud.
Who was it that found Miyokichi for you?
Nosy bastard!
I'll go buy some juice.
You really are nosy...
Welcome home.
I'm back.
Umm...
Umm... could it be...
...that you're avoiding me?
I'm sorry!
That I...
asked you for such a strange favor...
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I mustn't...
No, it's okay!
I was just a bit surprised.
I mustn't say this...
In order to get close to that No. 4...
You wanted to befriend his sister...
I never could've figured that out.
That wasn't the only reason-- I...
No! don't worry about it!
I guess I was just being stupid.
How I feel about you...
But you know, you could have just told me from the beginning.
It was a bit sly of you.
I...
Shin-chan?
I need to talk to you. Do you have time?
Shin-chan...
Those eyes...
They look just like your mother's.
I'm the worst...
Take a look, I switched to another gel. How is it? It's different from before.
I have a date with Ai-chan after school!
Ah, why won't they let us go home already?
It would've been great if you'd tagged along yesterday.
Not like you actually have anything important to do...
So, you could've come...
Here!
Today's share!
This one's brother...
Is there something on my face?
No.
Wait!
Why?
What are you...?
My reflection is there...
My nose looks bigger.
You are collecting tears, right?
Eh?
Right now I could make them.
Tears.
Because I feel like I might cry.
Why do you feel like crying?
I'm not telling.
You're mean for leading me on.
Yeah... that's because I am mean.
As you are now, your tears have no value.
Weak tears!
Gutter tears!
Slimy tears!
Puke tears!
"Puke"? You...!
I'll help you purify your tears!
Eh?
Okay, let's do this quickly.
Just like when you learned how to swim at the pool.
Did you even consider that there might be viruses or germs in there?!
There are more germs in Shinichirou.
We are killing off those germs with this.
Here!
Here.
Good work.
Is it warm?
Isn't it usually... the guy who does something like this?
Shinichirou is the one who's cold, right?
I guess so...
But, this...
Isn't it a bit too big for you?
It was my granny's.
Your grandmother?
Yeah. My beloved... my beloved granny!
My grandmother, who took my tears with her to the skies.
Your tears...
To the skies?
No way! No way! I want granny to come home with us!
Don't be so selfish, Noe!
No way!
Oh my, Noe is such a crybaby...
Granny will soon be going on a journey to the skies.
To the skies?
That's right! When that time comes, I'll bring Noe's tears along with me!
Noe's tears?
That's right. And then the crybaby Noe won't cry anymore.
That's a lie! You can't give or take tears from someone!
You can't take just anyone's...
A very...
A very important person's tears are the only ones you can take.
A very important...
Since then, I've been unable to cry.
It's because... granny took my tears with her.
Did her childhood memories really make her think that?
Eventually, I want to be able to cry.
But to do that, I have to first collect tears from someone.
But...
You couldn't take them from just anyone.
Yup.
It has to be the selected tears of someone that I care about.
It has to be the tears of someone elegant who's always looking up, towards where my granny is.
And that's me... and the one before me was Raigou-maru...
The tears of a chicken...
Do you get it?
That kind of gutter tears won't do.
I get it.
What do you want to do? Is it karaoke, after all?
Hmm... I don't really feel like it.
Then, let's go shopping!
I'm broke, though...
Don't worry! I helped out with cutting the crops,
so I have quite a lot to spend!
No thanks, that wouldn't feel right.
Oh, that's the rumored Isurugi Noe.
She's cute...
What's with that? Ai-chan is cute!
Thank you.
I'm sorry!
It's not that...
You surprised me.
I'm sorry, too.
Let's go.
You know...
It's fine if you want me to get along with her.
Yuasa Hiromi.
Since the cause of your worthless tears...
is probably her, right?
Is that your female intuition?
That's not it. It's just what I really think.
So that's it.
Why is she in pain,
what can you do to help her... you need to think about this sincerely.
Think about it... sincerely...
To me...
She...
I thought she always had such a pale and tormented face...
What if I could help her?
And yet...
After I found out she likes another guy...
It's fine with me to get along with her...
As long as Shinichirou cheers up.
I used to think she was a girl that I couldn't begin to understand...
But...
Then, could you also think sincerely about the food from the skies?
Eh?
You can't eat those!
Why?
Then, you try them!
Okay.
Why are you laughing?!
Because your face looked so funny!
You're terrible!
Hiromi...
Can I give up on her?
Right now I'm not sure.
But...
What are you doing?!
What are you guys doing?!
What am I doing!?
How's it going?
Eh?
The picture book.
Why don't you show it to me sometime?
What's troubling you?
Pumpkin or corn...
I wonder which one will grow closest to the sky...
Are you planning to cook?
Yes.
How rare, that you would do that.
This'll be the next food from the sky.
Is it for that back-carrying guy you told me about?
Back-carrying guy?
Sounds like a monster!
Take this one.
Sweet potato?
Yeah. It's close to the sky!
A lot of them grow at the top of the big tree.
Don't make fun of me!
And then, Shinichirou said my face looked funny!
Lift your head.
It was the first time someone told me that.
Granny always said how cute I am, but you know...
It's not like I'm angry.
Since everyone has different opinions.
Shinichirou's also unique in some ways...
There, let's go.
The red snow that the angel released...
Turned white, and piled up.
On the cracked ground...
On the muddy water...
It piled, and piled...
Until it became a snow-white field.
Everywhere...
White everywhere.
Alright!
Mornin'.
M-morning!
I'm sorry.
For the way I spoke before.
That's why... umm...
That one is...
Face-wash...
Cellphone!
Thank you!
Umm... why'd you take a photo?
Because it's common in manga and the like,
but it doesn't happen often in real life.
T-that doesn't mean you have to take one, does it?
Your smile was also quite bright!
T-that's because I was looking at the camera!
I can also...
It seems I can also make Hiromi smile.
Found you.
N-no. 4...
Wh-why are you here?
You sure are friendly in our first conversation...
Nice to meet you.
I'm Noe's brother, Isurugi Jun.
Nice to meet you! I'm Nakagami Shinichirou.
I know.
What's with this guy... just now he...
You really resemble your sister.
Not at all.
He's confusing me... no!
This won't do! I can't get caught up in his pace!
Eh... then... mind if I ask what business Isurugi Noe's brother would have at our residence?
I have a request.
Huh?
I want you to go out with her.
Go out with Noe.
What?!
Although I didn't say so clearly,
but I want the two of you to stop wandering around together.
Ah, you mean No. 6 on your team?
I came into your room because I wanted to tell you this.
I don't like nosy boys like you.