Cockroach...
Under Shinichirou's shoe, there is a cockroach, too.
In Shinichirou's hat, there is a cockroach, too.
Inside Shinichirou's heart, there is...
Yuasa Hiromi.
Fly.
Go on!
Stop it...
I knew it...
I knew it... it was useless...
If you can't make your own decisions,
You won't have fun...
You won't be happy...
and you won't be able to laugh...
As I thought, you can't cry if you don't decide to yourself.
I was only looking down on you, because I thought, like me, you can't fly...
But, that was wrong...
You only chose not to fly.
You hold up your head and look straight ahead.
That's the same as flying...
Yeah,
I think Noe will return home soon.
Yes.
It didn't seem like anything happened, so relax.
Pass it along to him, as well.
Yup.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Bye.
What was she talking about?
I was the one comparing myself to Ground.
I was the one not noticing how great Ground really is.
The one opposing everything, was me, I chose to escape from reality.
Ground chose not to fly,
but I didn't decide on anything myself.
The dance, the picture book...
Noe...
even Hiromi...
The reason I didn't want to do the dance wasn't because I'm bad at it!
It's because I didn't want to be compared to Dad!
The reason I didn't draw the picture book wasn't because I didn't feel like it!
It's because I was scared of learning my limits!
Welcome home, Noe.
I'm home.
Go on and wash your hands, it'll be ready soon.
You must be hungry, right?
Being out all night...
Hey, don't cling to me so hard.
The food will...
Thank you.
It's chilling cold... Let's head back in and get ourselves warmed up.
Enjoy.
Sorry for the trouble, ma'am.
Hey, where's the young master?
He should've gotten changed by now...
Hey...
I'll go have a look.
He should be getting ready in your room.
Alright.
Oh, you helping him change?
I'm envious!
Now now, don't talk such nonsense, have some more!
Take a look! Try some of our local wine!
The three consecutive year award winning, Namida Sankei!
It's so delicious it'll truly make you cry...
You need any help?
That looks good on you.
Thank you.
Shinichirou-kun too.
Alright, one bottle of Namida Sankei to bring with you!
Did you get any sleep after what happened?
Well, err...
That really scared me last night...
Sorry I called...
And you even practiced so hard for today...
That doesn't matter...
The reason I couldn't sleep was...
Ahh, well... the lack of sleep isn't a problem.
Since it'll make me more alert.
I wonder where I can see you best...
I was thinking that I'd like to watch Shinichirou-kun from the closest possible place during the Hounou dance.
Perhaps near the shrine office would be best?
When the festival comes, I will be at the front row looking at Shinichirou dancing!
I guess so...
Alright, it's done.
Thank you...
It'll be really crowded, so don't force yourself just to watch.
I'm not going to the festival...
I decided it by myself.
Alright, it's time!
YEAH!
Excuse me!
Coming through!
Sorry I'm late!
Oh, we're doing fine over here.
We have a lot of free time until the Hounou dance ends.
Sorry I had you do all the work!
Ai-chan, it's been a long time.
Wow! Hiromi-chan, you look really good in a kimono!
Huh?
I wonder if she came to see Shinichirou...
His girlfriend, huh?
I'm his girlfriend.
Well, I guess all these are things I wouldn't know about.
Isurugi-san!
Hold on!
Last night...
What did you say to Shinichirou-kun last night?
Shinichirou-kun told me yesterday...
Everything... He said he'll do everything properly.
I have always loved Shinichirou-kun.
I'm sure Shinichirou-kun feels the same about me.
I'm sorry...
I know I'm being selfish for what I've said,
But, we finally understand each other.
We can finally face each other honestly...
Sorry, but please leave us be.
We...
They're beautiful.
Your tears.
Ahh, I'm starving.
Hey, where you off to, master?
Oh, err, just some place.
Here, sorry for the wait!
Hey bro, the one just now wasn't completely cooked.
That's because we use only selected wheat!
Half cooked is just right.
Well said...
Alright, next custo-
Yo.
Ai-chan went to the community center, so I'm watching the store for her.
You're getting along well, aren't you?
Speaking of it, what are you doing?
What do you mean?
Should the star of the Mugiha dance really be loitering around here?
Really... What am I doing?
Huh?!
Shut up, Shinichirou!
Inside Shinichirou's butt, there is a cockroach, too!
Noe...
There was a call... from a printing company in Tokyo.
The boss went to watch the festival.
You can hang out here for a while.
Why did you decide that on your own?
You told me you were going to specialty school!
Why are you going to work, all of a sudden?
Because I promised Granny.
Remember that you locked yourself in your room after Granny died?
You didn't even come out to play with your friends.
I felt that I had to protect you...
Forever...
But... I am getting more and more confused.
I thought I only wanted to protect you, but I've done a lot of pointless stuff.
Onii-chan?
I love you.
I love Jun too.
But I think I love you a bit more than that.
It's strange to have such feelings,
that's why I asked him to take care of it.
Him?
I don't get it.
Is it really that strange to say you love me?
How is it wrong?
May I kiss you?
Didn't we kiss when we were kids?
Alright.
But, in return, you need to rethink about getting yourself a job.
Onii-chan...
That's probably the kind of kiss that I'd want.
I made many selfish decisions...
but being by your side... is too painful.
Inside Shinichirou's heart...
Inside my heart...
I didn't realize onii-chan's feelings...
Nor did I realize Yuasa Hiromi's feelings...
I didn't even realize how Shinichirou really feels.
Can tears really be shed...
...from my eyes which haven't seen anything?
Looks like this year's lead suddenly got better!
I'm pretty sure that's Nakagami's son.
Like father, like son.
But, why all of a sudden...
"When Raigoumaru came to,
"He's was tempted by the red seeds,
"And stood up on the cliff."
"'I want to fly!'"
"Is it because he wants to eat those red seeds?"
"Or is it because of this white snow?"
"That I do not know."
"But, that's what Raigoumaru was thinking deep within."
Yeah...
The only reason that I thought of drawing a picture book was...
because of those eyes... that believed I could fly.
You want to fly high in the sky.
Not for anyone else's sake,
Not for glory or history.
"And Raigoumaru spread his wings and flew."
The dance was great, wasn't it?
I know! I was totally into it!
I watched. It was really good.
Yeah...
Hiromi, I... need to...
Are you looking for Isurugi-san?
Huh?
I told her...
I told Isurugi-san not to interfere with us anymore.
Are you mad?
No, not really...
It's about time for me to go.
The festival is about to end.
Don't leave me alone...
I wonder how the view is from the sky...
My picture book... I finished it!
Can I see it too if I look from the sky?
I want you to see it!
I want to know what you think!
Really?
Thank you.
Let's go in.
I hate how I am now.
Shinichirou said I can fly.
Your tears