Thanks for the meal, I'm leaving now!
Hey.
I was just wondering if you were here...
I am now.
It doesn't really matter.
I didn't actually have anything to tell you...
Lunch.
Huh?
Wanna eat together?
Why do I have to eat together with you?!
Well, you know...
It's strange for a boy and a girl to eat together!
Why is it strange?
You see,
Because we're not dating...
What I'm saying is, you should eat together with your friends!
By the way...
Eh?
Did you hear anything from your brother?
About what?
Oh, nothing really.
After school...
Eh?
Why don't we go home together?
I can't! I have dance practice today!
For the Mugiha festival?
Y- Yeah...
Awesome! You're a dancer?!
Dancer...
Something lovely like that! Why'd you keep it a secret from me?
Not like I was actually hiding it...
Besides, I am not dancing because I like it.
Tomoyo, you're late.
Here.
Friends always exchange their side dishes with each other.
Sorry I'm late! There were lots of people at the snack bar!
Err, Isurugi Noe-san, this is Kurobe Tomoyo.
Are you going home?
We don't have club activities today.
I see...
Then...
Even though he told me he has practice...
Shin-!
It's going pretty well for him, I must say.
If it goes well, maybe the four of us could go out together next time.
Kind of like a group date...
Hey, where should we go?
Anywhere's fine.
What's with that?
Hey, isn't that a new sweater?
Yup, how observant of you.
Told you to leave it to me!
I know everything about Aiko, you see!
But... isn't that one just a bit plain?
Doesn't seem like Ai-chan's taste...
A change is nice, occasionally.
You could have told me, I would've gone shopping with you.
Didn't you buy that one over at that store?
What was that store that Ai-chan likes to go again?
Oh yeah, why don't you also buy yourself a sweater?
Since all you've been wearing is that one.
Sweater, huh?
"If I'm to get another one, it'd sure be nice if it was one that Ai-chan made..."
Or, that's what I want to say.
Sure.
Eh? Really?!
YES!!
Good day, bocchan!
I see things are getting pretty hot between you two!
Whoa! be careful!
Let's go to the seashore.
It's cold...
Here.
You're cold, right?
What about you?
I bet Shinichirou-kun's colder than me.
What do you mean by that?
Besides, it's usually guys who do this.
It's fine.
It's the second time already...
Well, I'm fine with it, anyways.
Nah, it's nothing.
You don't have dance practice today?
That's right.
Shinichirou-kun is the main lead, huh?
You know, if you'd like, next time...
Today...
At lunch, Isurugi Noe came to the bleachers at the field.
Oh, you mean where you eat?
She told me "Friends always exchange their side dishes with each other."
Huh? Did she give you any trouble?
Nope. Besides, it was me who asked Shinichirou-kun to introduce Isurugi Noe to me.
Let's go home.
Speaking of Isurugi Noe...
What?
Well, don't you think she's a strange girl?
Well, she's not a bad person, though.
Hmm?
Y- Yeah. That's right.
I didn't say it clearly, but...
I would like the two of you to stop walking around together outside.
But why?
Maybe you don't understand this,
But to begin with... you already live under the same roof, a boy and a girl...
I understand.
That's a lot.
Yup, but I can't eat with boys.
Oh, is that so...
They're all liars.
It's not actually red.
They probably added some dye.
Captain Takaoka...
Lunch practice?
Yup.
Just Hiromi?
Yup...
Don't you think that Hiromi's been pushing herself too hard recently?
Yup, let's do this.
Geez... How did you find out about this place?
You were just like Raigou-maru!
Looking cool, courageous, shining bright!
Is that so?
Later, bocchan!
Oh, thanks for coming!
Come on, over here.
Hey, Shinichirou.
It's fine if I eat with guys once in a while, right?
Oh, you can't eat that one.
You will only lie more if you eat food that rips people off.
Lie?
Sausages aren't actually red.
But you made this...
I nearly misunderstood Shinichirou...
But, I got it wrong. I can eat with Shinichirou!
Shinichirou's a person who can shed precious tears.
Tears, huh?
But, how are you going to turn my tears into yours?
There's still quite a lot to do.
But, granny did it on me this way.
"Following the windy night,"
"Is the moment when Raigou-maru wants to fly to the sky."
"It's a breezy afternoon with a clear sky,"
"Because of the wind the day before, broken straws and grass are everywhere, scattered across the ground."
"Even those worms, delicious and usually hard-to-find,"
"could be easily found."
Perhaps I can fly, too!
Isn't this exactly how she imagines it?
Yo.
So you really did come.
I told you, didn't I.
So, have you decided yet?
Now look here... don't go around trying to control how others feel.
It's not that big of a deal.
Then, in return for me dating Isurugi Noe,
You'd also need to go out with Hiromi, how about that?
Eh?
See, you need to think about it as well.
That's not what I meant,
Who's Hiromi?
It's Yuasa Hiromi! Don't tell me you don't know!
Oh, you mean No. 6 on your team?
That girl is quite cute.
Alright, then.
Hey, hold on!
Dammit, just what's with that guy?
Is he retarded or something?
He couldn't possibly be serious, right?
Same for Hiromi, I don't see any good in that guy.
I don't get it at all!
Just what the hell does he think other's feelings are?
How could he possibly propose to date with someone else as a return of favor?
But it was me who proposed that as a return favor.
If that guy's serious,
then wouldn't it be perfect for Hiromi?
So this is how you truly imagine?
Err...
I have something to tell you.
Well... there's no rush... we could talk about it at school tomorrow.
Come in.
It's the first time I've entered this room.
Isn't this the first time?
It's the first time that you've entered my room, ever since I moved here, right?
Eh? Is- Is that so?
Maybe you're right.
Yup.
Yeah, it's my first.
Hey, what's with this conversation?
So, what is it?
I just met No. 4 from Hotarugawa High.
He told me that he thinks you're cute.
Hmm...
Don't "hmm" me. Aren't you happy?
I don't like nosy boys like you.
You know, I didn't imagine you'd reply th-
What's that?
Well...
Is that the only reason you entered my room?
But didn't you let me in?
I told you, it's fine if we talk about it tomorrow.
We'll be in trouble if your mother finds out.
I have something to tell you.
Well... there's no rush... we could talk about it at school tomorrow.
Come in.
Isn't this the first time?
It's the first time that you've entered my room, ever since I moved here, right?
Eh? Is- Is that so?
Maybe you're right.
Yup.
Yeah, it's my first.
What am I talking about?
So, what about it?
About today...
I just met No. 4 from Hotarugawa High.
No way...
He told me that you are cute.
Hmm...
Don't "hmm" me. Aren't you happy?
I don't like nosy boys like you.
You know, I didn't imagine you'd reply th-
What's that?
Well...
Is that the only reason you entered my room?
But didn't you let me in?
I told you, it's fine if we talk about it tomorrow.
Are you only in here to talk about that?!
We'll be in trouble if your mother finds out.
He entered my room to say something like that...
Bocchan, it took me a long time to pack this up.
Old picture books from back when I was young truly are nostalgic.
I will help you out the next time you clean up the storage.
Wha-!
Isn't that an old photo album?
The photos are all laminated.
Oh! Dad was really young!
He looks just like bocchan.
You think?
Huh? Why is the face of the woman in this photo cut off?
Over here as well.
Hey!
Hey, let's meet up at Ai-chan's later.
I need to go home and finish up my stuff first.
I'll go on ahead.
Right!
Today, I'm late for the opening time.
Take a seat there.
Is Cola fine with you?
Sure.
Here, your Cola.
Hmm? What's this?
A sweater?
Eh? Ah, yeah...
For real? So even Ai-chan has a girl-like side!
Come on, no peeking.
How nice...
I bet Miyokichi is really happy.
Wh- What's wrong?
Shinichirou, isn't your size about the same as his?
Huh? Well, yeah, something like that.
Can I do some measurements?
Since I'm not confident enough.
Eh?
Why don't you just get him to do it?
Come on!
It itches.
Sit still!
Isn't it enough?
Not yet.
About last time...
Eh?
That...
What?
Hey, Aiko!
Don't open the door!
Eh...?
Isn't it tough when you can't tell your feelings to the one you like?
You!
There's nothing to forget!
Not a single moment...
What... kind of joke is this?