(yeah that's worded pretty much like a cliché, edit as you want)
I'm sorry.
But... then why...
But... I think Isurugi-san is amazing.
Since she saw through me.
What does she mean, "she saw through her"?
Chicken feed...
Yo, Shinichirou!
Yo!
Tomoyo, you're being weird!
Today, we are stopping by Ai-chan's as well!
Alright, let's go then.
Honestly...
Shinichirou, lend me your English dictionary.
Alright, it's in my locker.
Then I'm taking it.
Wa-Wait a second, Nobuse!
What the hell's this?
Hold it, Nobuse!
What's... wrong?
Well...
This example here is one of the basics of functions,
I'd hope that everyone here is able to solve these in a quick manner, so memorize them well.
Is it Isurugi Noe that gave you those red seeds?
Yeah.
That's what you call "love", right?
She's just showing how much she loves you with those red seeds!
I think I'm just cursed.
You're the cursed one!?
Oh! The roots of the curse.
You go first.
Oh, wonderful. A date after school is it?
Just a few words of complaint.
Be careful not to get eaten up!
Idiot!
What's wrong with her?
Isn't that Isurugi Noe?
He's picking her up on a bike...
He's so old...
Ai-chan!
Huh? Where's Shinichirou?
Oh, he said he will come over in a moment.
What are you doing here?
These are treats for the local community school.
Seems to me they are really delicious! Here!
What are you doing?
Come on, it's fine!
Why am I depressed?
I wonder...
What are you two doing?
He's just tasting.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Come closer...
Like this?
Delicious.
I'll go get you two some drinks...
You know, you really do like dropped food.
I will eat any food fallen on the ground, as long as it's made by Ai-chan!
Sooner or later you'll get a stomach ache!
I have no regrets from that since it's Ai-chan's cooking that I ate!
Isurugi Noe has a boyfriend?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Then why is she reaching out to you?
She's just using me as a replacement for Raigou-maru.
Raigou-maru?
A chicken in the school's backyard...
...which died.
So that means, those red seeds are...
Chicken feed.
That means she sees you as a chicken, huh?
She doesn't see me that way.
Shinichirou, it's time.
Oh crap! I've got to go home!
We'll take this shortcut since we're a bit late.
What's wrong?
How did it go? What we talked about the other day...
Eh?
You know, about Hiromi-chan.
Who did you hear that from?
I found it out myself!
Well...
She told me she wants to be a friend of Noe's.
But in truth, that's not the case, is it?
Seems so.
I seem to understand...
...the reason she said that...
But, I am not telling you.
Hey! What's up with that?
You're hurting me...
I-I'm sorry! Well...
That trunk's heavy, right? Let me take care of it.
A person...
One person can only get close to another person when she's in love with him, right?
What if, you want to get close to that person, but at the same time, that couldn't happen?
Since someone's already beside him...
Who are you talking about?
It must be a pain in the butt for the girls that fall in love with you.
Ow- Ow- Oww!
For example, if Hiromi fell in love with someone,
and close to that person is Noe...
Who would that be?
Let's see... Boys around Noe...
Could it be me?
Like that could happen.
But... there's no one else!
Is that how it is?
Wait, that can't be it.
But, perhaps...
Good evening!
Kid, lower your waist!
Understood!
Welcome back, bocchan! {Possible note: "Bocchan" is a way of referring to the young master of a household}
I'm home!
Huh?
What?
Seems like you're quite happy.
Oh... err... it's actually facial exercises.
I heard it improves your health by shifting it to the sides.
Facial exercises...
Facial exercises, huh? Oww!
I'm counting on you.
I need you to deliver this.
But you continue to behave rudely.
You understand, right?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Take care of it, okay?
Going somewhere?
It's urgent.
This is the sake for Amimoto-ojisan's celebration.
It's late already! We could deliver that tomorrow!
We promised that we would deliver it by today.
Then, I will...
Shinichirou!
Let's go.
Is something wrong?
Why did the two of them go out?
They're taking something over to Oji-san's.
Shin-chan doesn't have to go too...
Well, I think it's fine to let Shinichirou handle that.
Why must Shin-chan--
Why must Hiromi do it?
Hiromi's now a child of our household,
Just like Shinichirou.
She's not my kid!
Hey!
You didn't have to come with me...
This street is dark and dangerous.
Besides, the bottle is heavy.
You don't need to worry about it too much,
Since you're not a maid.
Right now, I am under the care of your family...
Oh yeah, we once walked this street, right?
Remember? You got lost on the day of the festival,
And you cried a lot!
I don't remember...
Is that so...
Hey, by the way, what did you mean yesterday with "Noe seeing through you"?
Thank you.
Actually, it's really scary to walk this street.
I-I see! I guess you're right!
Don't leave me alone...
Don't leave me alone, Shinichirou-kun...
It was all sealed...
When it was decided I was to live in this house.
"Don't leave me alone", huh?
What a shock that she doesn't remember...
After all, it was one step forward for us to walk together in the streets.
Wanting to hold your hand, I extended mine.
At that moment, snow started to fall.
It was red... red.
Mysterious snow.
COLD!
Good morning.
Is it already that late?
Nope, nope.
I'm just going to prepare for the basketball competitions.
Bye.
Err...
Well, err... when the time comes, I'll go cheer for you.
Good morning.
I'm going back to sleep for a little longer.
Is that Hotarugawa's basketball team?
What are you planning to do?
Well, since I have nothing else to do, I'll go take a look.
Hey, Nakagami-kun.
What are those?
That's yours, right?
Huh, what?
Ohh! These are...
What's-
That's fantastic! It's connected together!
T-H-A-T G-I-R-L...!
Good luck with that!
What is she thinking?!
What are these?
Who knows?
Isurugi Noe!
I told you, I don't want the red seeds!
That's not your choice to make.
You know, I don't have a clue what you want, but...
Wouldn't it be better if you didn't get too involved with me?
You have a boyfriend, right?
I saw you together with him!
Therefore... Stop doing this!{That's why, know your place! ( shouldn't it be "That's why, stop doing this!" Miku-chan) (Edit - Miku-chan is correct)}
Wait! I can't get down!
You climbed up yourself, get down by yourself.
Hey!
Oww...
Come on...
Come on, stand up.
What are you doing?!
Soon, there'll be a cockroach...
Soon, there'll be a cockroach on top of Shinichirou's head...
On Shinichirou's back there's a cockroach too...
You're... light.
That way!
You know what's over there?
Does your leg really hurt?
That guy is...
It's fine here.
Hey, your leg... What the hell?!
Dude, what the hell were you doing?
That's the one.
No. 4.
That guy's Noe's...
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan...
Huh?
Wait, her brother?!
Go for it!
Hoo-hoo... So you mistook her brother for her boyfriend! {I think "hoo hoo" could be translated to "I see", but this way it's a bit more obvious he's taunting him}
Well, not like it's unusual.
Right...
At least confirm it first next time!
It's not that big of a deal. Not like I care if she has a boyfriend or not.
That's true, but seems to me that this is one less trouble for you.
Don't say stupid things!
That's true...
Since you have Yuasa Hiromi in your hands.
Don't just decide on your own!
You better think of a reason real quick.
What do you mean?
Just now, when you were carrying Noe, she got a good look at you.
That will most likely end up as a misunderstanding.
Why must I find a reason?
Leave first.
Excuse me, can you pass me the ball?
Right away!
Did you see that just now?
What is that idiot thinking?
It's fine with me.
Really?
Hey, is that really fine with you?
Come on, Hiromi, seriously, don't you like Nakagami-kun?
Isurugi Noe's leg is hurt...
Nothing has happened between us...
She suddenly fell down from the tree...
What's this? Somehow I'm feeling like I was the one at fault here!
Screw this!
Screw this! Screw this! Screw this! Screw this!
You liar!
It's true.
I wouldn't lie to Tomoyo about that.
The person I like is Hotarugawa's No. 4.
Is that true?
I thought...
So, please don't mention Shinichirou-kun's name again.
You like chatting that much...
Um, could it be you're hiding from me?
Go out with Noe.
Hey, blink your eyes.