I'm heading out.
It's been a week since Hiromi moved out to live alone in an apartment.
After her suspension ended, Hiromi started going to school again.
As for me,
things aren't going very well.
I haven't seen Noe since that time.
Yes, thank you very much.
Yup, we will prepare three dozen right away.
Yes, thank you.
Boss, how many cases of Mugiha wine did we have again?
We have four cases.
Got it!
Doesn't it seem like demand is pretty good this year?
Yeah, we've made around 20% more sales compared to last year's festival.
What do you think? It's quite a nice room, right?
Yeah. It's close to my house too, isn't that nice?
Yup.
The festival's in three days.
Are you really going to have the inter-school match?
They said we should play a game to show the rookies.
The opponent is Hotarugawa, right?
Won't the boys' basket...
Yup, the boys' basketball team's gonna come cheer as well.
Then, that means he's going to come too.
Why didn't she mention this before?
Not like she had a reason to say it...
Eh? What?
Nah, it's nothing.
Here.
I like when it's snowing by the sea.
Let's go to the shore!
I'll head out first.
Hey!
Be sure to lock the door!
Wait... Hold on!
Because... I lost my tears.
It's going to start in three days, huh?
Have you practiced your dancing to perfection?
Yeah. Well, somewhat.
You were just like Raigoumaru!
Looking cool, courageous, shining bright!
I'm looking forward to see Shinichirou-kun dressed up.
Obaa-san told me that Oji-san once danced as the lead too.
Oh, so you knew that.
I will be at the front row, looking at Shinichirou!
Let's go home.
I have to go to Shinichirou-kun's home this afternoon.
If it's too busy over there, Oba-san might end up in a bad mood.
What the...
Want a nice, cheerful female friend?
You get all the coke and Imagawayaki you want if you become a friend of hers.
I...
Let's start over as friends again.
Making a sweater was impossible from the start.
We need to start over with something simpler.
But...
I'll be working hard so that one day, you'll make me a sweater.
I'll work to improve my knitting skills until then, too.
I'm home!
Sorry for intruding!
"The next day, it was raining."
"Beside him, Ground was eagerly and noisily flapping his wings, but..."
"Raigoumaru was resting peacefully."
Hiromi!
I'm fine...
That was obviously on purpose! How horrible!
Judge!
Hey, what's with you? Get off the court!
What was with that foul play?
I'll be listening if you have any explanations.
You! Get off the court!
Incredible...
Time out! Give us a time out!
Incredible! He confessed in front of everyone?
After doing something like that, she should fall for him instantly!
I...
Okay? We have to get our acts together!
Concentrate!
Yes!
Yo.
Yo...
Listen...
Could you tell Isurugi Noe that her curse didn't work?
It's fine. She'll get it when you tell her that.
Well, see ya.
I'm working part time at Ai-chan's today.
Hey, hold on!
"What's this? Isn't that Ground's upright silhouette, standing against the morning sun on top of the 10 meter-tall cliff?"
Master, spread wider.
I'm home.
I'm...
How are things over there?
Yes, everything's fine.
Hey, come here and take a look at this.
"I will wipe your tears properly"... What was with that?
Shinichirou, you can fly.
You just don't know it yourself.
I didn't do anything properly...
Not for anyone...
Isn't it cold tonight?
Yeah.
Oh, you're home?
I'm looking forward to the Mugiha dance.
Then, I'm going in first.
Yeah.
So, how's your picture book going?
It'll be finished soon.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
Well anyway, right now you should concentrate on leading the Mugiha dance.
Oh, Master, welcome home.
I'm looking forward to the Mugiha dance.
I'll do my best!
"Ground's shadow left the top of the cliff."
"Then, the stalled-in-flight Ground rapidly fell towards the earth."
"Raigoumaru watched it all, from beginning to end."
Hiromi?
Yeah. Thanks for today!
Today, Takaoka got a call from Hotarugawa's team saying that they apologize.
I see.
There was a big commotion about Number 4 being stolen away by a Mugiha girl!
How stupid.
But he was so incredible, that Number 4!
To say something like that in front of everyone!
Looks like he's serious about you, Hiromi, uh...
It's fine. I don't care about that anymore.
So how is it, living by yourself?
I'm eating a popsicle right now.
Ah, how unfair! It must be really nice, huh?
Yup, living alone is the best!
You could bring home all the guys you want!
Yup.
Eh?!
Oh, sorry. My mom's calling for me, I'll call you back later.
Yes?
I'm sorry about today.
We...
Huh?
I've been causing trouble for a lot of people.
I've caused many people to start feeling bad.
It's me who should be apologizing.
No...
I'm sorry.
And...
Thank you.
Can't we meet up?
Let's meet, please.
I prepared Yoshida-san's part as well.
I see.
That laundry of Shin-chan's over there...
Sorry, but could you bring it over to his room?
Ye- Yes.
Err...
"The Tale of Raigoumaru and Ground"...
Err... Obaa-san told me to bring your laundry.
I went to see the game yesterday.
I...
Shinichirou-kun, work hard at the Mugiha dance.
Hold on, Hiromi.
That guy's...
Yup.
At that park.
Thanks for coming.
No matter what, I wanted to apologize in person.
Yeah. I understand, so don't worry about it.
Besides, I was happy you did that for my sake.
Was that all you wanted to say?
Don't be so cold.
Want to get a cup of tea?
Then, it's my turn to talk now.
Let's not meet or call each other anymore.
At this rate, someone else will get dragged into this.
I wanted to tell you face-to-face when I met with you.
What, so it is bothering you after all.
But, like I said last time.
Our agreement is not over yet.
It's not me that you love.
To you, nothing matters but her.
Why don't you understand?
"It was the first flight of a chicken, and the one who held the glory for that failure...
was Ground."
"Raigoumaru was just a regular bird in the crowd of cowardly chickens."
"The end."
Who would read a bad ending like this one?
I wonder what Noe would say if she read it.
That's right...
I need to show this to Noe...
I've got nothing more to tell you...
Noe didn't come home.
Oh... I see...
Well, please call him.
Sure...
I'm sorry... were you asleep?
I'm drawing my picture book.
Hello? Hiromi?
"The Tale of Raigoumaru and Ground".
Eh?
No, it's nothing.
I see.
So, what's the matter? Calling this late...
Isurugi Noe didn't come home.
Eh?
Her brother wondered if Shinichirou-kun would know where she is.
I got it. I'll go look for her right now.
If anything happens over there, call me.
Shinichirou-kun?
Shinichirou-
It seems I can't understand how you feel, after all...
In this world, there are many painful and sad things.
I want to fly. To escape from everything, and spread my wings freely.
It would be simpler to wish for that, Ground.
Ground, I'll help you fly.
Ground...
Noe... did you take him with you?
That's right...
This isn't the place where you take flight.
That was... her way of breaking up...
...cockroach~
Under Shinichirou's shoe, there's a cockroach, too~
In Shinichirou's hat, there's a cockroach, too~
On Shinichirou's~
Butt there's a cockroach~
In Shinichirou's...
Inside Shinichirou's heart, there is...
Yuasa Hiromi.
They're beautiful.
Your tears...
Really, what was I doing?
May I kiss you?
From my eyes that can't see anything...