Granny, I've found him.
The person who's the most important to me.
Granny, I'm sure that my tears, through him...
What's wrong? Not turning on the lights...
Onii-chan,
Shinichirou told me that he likes me.
And he wants me to go out with him.
I see, isn't that great?
Right now... I want to cry.
I wonder why that is...
I'm not even sad, and yet...
I really, really want to cry.
It must be because I'm happy...
My birthday is later,
so Shinichirou-kun is my older brother.
I said it...
Look at me too...
Please...
Shinichirou...
It was soft...
What am I doing...
Thank you!
Why did I smile?
I'm sorry...
But I don't really have that kind of feelings towards Ai-chan.
To me you're a childhood friend, and Miyokichi's girlfriend.
I'll forget what happened just now.
Let's just pretend nothing's happened today.
Shinichirou, you going to Ai-chan's today?
Well, err... Today, I...
Come on, since all you do is slack around, let's go together!
Well, I...
Might be going on a date or something...
A date...?
With who?
Isurugi... Noe...
She's not around...
Well, it's not like I asked her in advance.
Noe...
What are you doing?
Ground looked like he was cold.
Huh? Are those two dating?
Seems like it...
Isurugi Noe, how surprising!
I've always thought that Nakagami-kun likes Hiromi.
Like that could happen.
Don't fall!
This feels great!
Shinichirou, you don't look very happy.
Sit down.
Crouch.
Wh- What?
Shinichirou looks like he's cold too.
Look.
What is it?
What do you see behind me?
The sky...
I want Shinichirou to always keep looking towards the sky.
I've never looked at the sky like this before.
"The first time Raigoumaru wanted to fly in the sky,"
"was after a stormy night."
"It was a breezy afternoon with a clear sky."
What's that?
A picture book I'm writing.
Eh?! Then what comes next?
What happens after that?!
"Because of the wind the day before, broken straws and grass are everywhere, scattering across the ground."
"Even those worms, delicious and usually hard-to-find,"
"Could be easily discovered."
What comes after that?
That's all I have now.
I want to hear what comes next!
Eh?
You'll continue writing it, right?
Hurry up and write it!
Y- Yes...
Here I go!
"Raigoumaru drifted into slumber, dreaming a dream where he decided upon the day of his first flight."
"Every single day,"
"Raigoumaru trained himself in order to fly,"
"To stand strong while facing the wind."
"Finally, the day comes when he'll fly in the sky..."
Let's stop here today.
I'm happy...
Because Shinichirou's writing about Raigoumaru,
And reviving Raigoumaru in the picture books!
I'm sure he'll be able to fly high!
Shinichirou could fly high as well.
This must be what's going to become the wings of Shinichirou!
Thank you.
Shinichirou's face is as red as a rooster's cockscomb.
Bu- But you suddenly...!
I will grow to like Shinichirou more and more!
Would you let me like you more?
Yeah.
Don't leave me alone...
I...
Master, your hair looks like a cockscomb!
This is... the shape of happiness!
Shape of happiness, huh?
Not like I could make it.
Good morning.
Seems you're getting along well.
Eh?
With Isurugi Noe.
Sure...
That's a weird hairstyle.
I'm going out.
Hiromi,
Is there anything troubling you at home?
If something happened, just tell me.
You're one of this family's children as well.
That stance...
Resembles your mother alot.
You're really the same, huh?
Acting all innocent,
And easily controlling men's hearts.
You even made the people in this house and Shinichirou your allies.
You're quite brilliant.
It's always snowing when we meet, huh?
Where do you want to go?
To a town where it doesn't snow.
There's a nice place.
The only thing that we have in common.
Let's play a game.
For every basket you score, the other must answer a question.
And you must tell the truth.
Three times each.
You can shoot here,
And I'll be shooting from here.
Nope.
You'll be shooting from here.
Didn't expect you to be this pushy.
It's fine if you don't want to.
Got it.
"When he woke up in the morning, he heard a cackling voice."
"Turns out that it was Ground, pecking feed off the ground."
"Raigoumaru wanted to say that it was his share, but he didn't."
"Because there was still a lot of food."
"Raigoumaru climbed up to the top of the hill."
"It was a huge embankment, reaching 10 meters tall."
"Looking from there, it seemed like the ground was the underworld."
"Now, let's fly!"
It's wonderful...
I just got the urge to go see Ground.
You got two baskets in, and I got zero.
So what are they? Your questions.
How many boys has Isurugi Noe dated?
What for?
Don't mind that.
Zero.
Perhaps you misunderstood Noe.
Because she's different, a lot of things were said.
Rumors spread, but Noe didn't do anything about it.
She's strong.
Way back, she was always crying.
But, after a certain event,
she stopped crying.
Since then, she grew strong.
But, in truth...
Siscon!
TL Note: Like "lolicon". Sister complex - somebody who is attracted to his sister in a more than familial way.
So even you can make that kind of face.
What's the next question?
Why are you going out with me?
It was Nakagami Shinichirou who asked me to go out with you.
As an exchange, he's going out with Noe.
What the hell's that?
That's how it is.
So that means,
If one side breaks up,
The other must break up as well, isn't that right?
That would be troublesome for me.
No matter what you ask for, I will hear you out, so...
It's my first time to come to school on a day off.
I like it.
To be at the school with Shinichirou when no one else's there.
Noe...
Onii-chan...
Looks like it's going well for you.
Same for you.
I've got a slightly better opinion of you now.
Since you are the first one who seriously got in a fight with me.
That's a cute smile.
You used that innocent face to grab a hold of Shinichirou's heart, right?
That's incredible.
I'm heading home.
Hey!
Do you think the words that slipped from my lips were my true feelings?
Eh?
I don't want to think that way, though...
Things like that happen often, don't they?
But if you could control your feelings freely,
I wonder how easy life would be.
I'm saying the exact same things...
What?
You surprised me, suddenly showing up there...
This was my mother, right?
Couldn't blame you.
I might have done the same thing if I were you.
But...
You know, that's actually...
Still, that was my mother!
Hiromi...
I shouldn't have come to this family.
It was a mistake coming here...
Sorry for being a bother till now!
Take me on a ride on your bike.
I've told you. No riding while there's snow.
I don't want to die just yet.
You told me you'd hear me out, no matter what it was, right?
Where do you want to go?
To a town where it doesn't snow.
During the festival, I'll be at the front row looking at Shinichirou dancing!
Well, despite all those expectations, my dancing isn't that nice.
Hey, promise me,
If you spot me in the crowd during the dance,
Fly high, like Raigoumaru!
I couldn't do that!
Besides, the choreography is already decided.
It's fine if you do something that only I would understand, right?
Well, sure...
Also, the picture book.
Finish it quickly.
Shinichirou in a dress as well as the picture book...
Before winter ends, I should be able to see it, right?
Yeah, I bet.
Riding a bike, even when there's snow...?
Hiromi!
Was that onii-chan?
No way...
I grew tired...
Could you stay here for a bit longer?
Mom, you're acting too strange.
All you've done is teaching Hiromi these strange ways of thinking.
Flying isn't easy...