I'm heading out.
Ah, bocchan, good morning!
Shoveling the snow...
Good morning.
You don't have to.
Since I'm not going to school, my body's been too idle.
So this is like a substitute for club activities.
I see...
Be careful.
We weren't siblings, after all...
Well then, let's keep working...
Hiromi-san, you must be tired, right?
No, I was just spacing out a bit.
Hey!
Thanks.
Were you calling your girlfriend?
Yeah, I guess...
You're quite popular with the girls, huh?
Ka-chan, time for a smoke!
TL Note: Ka-chan translates to "mom", but he's referring to his wife.
Yes!
That's not it...
This part is really important.
These problems will show up in the test, so remember them well!
Alright, now copy down this problem.
Making notes for Yuasa Hiromi?
What? There's nothing wrong with just taking notes, is there?
You've got it so good...
What is that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Well then, maybe I should go see Ai-chan's cute face again.
Go ahead, do it!
Well then, see ya.
It's being buried more and more... more... more...
The love message Shinichirou gave me...
I want to see you...
I want to see you!
Isurugi Noe.
What?
Why don't you curse me too?
Curse me so that I will never come to like anyone.
I did something horrible to Miyokichi... something really horrible.
Let's break up.
Isn't a guy considered cool if his heart isn't affected by anyone?
I want to become a guy exactly like that.
No.
I will never agree to that.
Miyokichi...
I thought we needed to talk about this thoroughly again.
I am fine now.
Isurugi Noe cursed me so that I will never come to love anyone.
All I want now is to see Aiko smile.
Because Aiko has the prettiest smile.
See ya.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Today's math.
I heard that it's gonna be on the test.
I asked Tomoyo for the notes.
I think that won't happen. Kurobe-san was sleeping like a sealed demon!
Then, I'll talk to Tomoyo about your help.
She was sleeping so deeply that not even the teacher was able to wake her.
Such bad handwriting.
"Now, let's fly."
"Even if that's what Raigoumaru was thinking,"
"his stomach suddenly started growling."
This isn't the place where you take flight.
Why would Noe say that?
Um... I'd like to talk to you.
There's been a lot going on...
I'm sorry for the trouble my wife has caused.
No, it's fine. It's already...
She went straight to the conclusion, thinking that with your mother, I...
Anyway, I understood what you wanted to say. I'll arrange it as soon as possible.
But, please don't forget this,
Hiromi, you are part of the family.
Right.
Um...
Do you really mean it?
Thank you very much.
Hey.
You didn't pick up my calls.
I was suspended, after all.
Aren't you still suspended, though?
I don't want to hear that from someone who's suspended and still needs to work.
Well, whatever.
So, what's the matter?
Why don't we end it? This pretend dating?
It's not that I hate you.
But a lot has happened, and I've done a lot of thinking.
I think I want to break free from all this at once, and sort out my feelings.
Oh, I will use my work money and pay your bike...
I've told you. Breaking up would be troublesome for me!
Because you'd break the contract?
I got an older bike from my boss.
I just need to exchange some parts and repair it, and it'll run.
Hey...
Listen to me!
I can't break our agreement.
Come on! For preventing injuries, running is the best!
The next match against Hotarugawa...
We have to win!
Yes!
What? You two broke up?
Yeah.
I see.
That's not something for you to be sad about!
Isurugi Noe is a pretty nice girl.
Just some helpful advice.
Well then, I'm leaving.
What? No way!
It's true! It's the first time I've heard about that!
Is it because of me?
Did you feed it those red seeds?
Yup.
What's the matter?
Well, a lot of things happened.
Why are you coming to me?
Eh?
Nah, it's nothing.
We have dance practice later, you want to come?
Can you dance for me today?
Yeah, sure.
Granny, just one more time.
This will be the last time I do it.
I made a lot today!
Eat as much as you'd like!
Good evening.
Good evening, bocchan!
There are lots of these left, so go ahead! Don't hold back.
Ai-chan's onigiri is always delicious.
Thanks.
I'll fetch you some tea.
Oh, this is my childhood friend Nobus...
Eh...
This is my childhood friend Ai-chan.
And this is my...
I know all about it. Isurugi Noe-chan, Shinichirou's first girlfriend.
It's about time to start.
Maybe I should say thank you.
Thanks to that curse you gave Miyokichi, I was saved.
I used to love Shinichirou...
What am I saying?
Things like curses don't exist.
If they did, I'd...
I'm leaving early!
I didn't tell my brother about this, so...
Good bye!
Oh... see ya...
You two broke up, didn't you?
So you heard about it from Miyokichi.
Yeah.
You are thinking that this is your fault, right?
No...
But in truth, that's exactly it.
It's all Shinichirou's fault!
Hey, that's heavy, right? Let me carry it.
I won't accept Shinichirou's help anymore.
I'm starting to outgrow you.
Shinichirou-kun.
There's something I'd like to talk about.
Come in for a bit.
Take a seat there.
I will be done soon.
I've decided to leave this house.
He told me when I first came here,
If I don't feel comfortable living here, I could stay at his acquaintance's apartment.
But, I wanted to come to this house.
Then there's no need for you to leave now.
It's a lot of trouble living alone.
Oh, you were drawing something like this?
Eh? Ah, that is...!
"The you inside me has always been crying..."
"I want to wipe off your tears."
Well, that's...
What a beautiful drawing.
So you can draw this well, Shinichirou-kun.
I don't think it's a good idea for you to live alone.
Even while living in the same house,
I never got to know Shinichirou very well, it seems.
Can't you reconsider?
I've already decided to.
I see...
"Now, let's fly."
"Even if that's what Raigoumaru was thinking,"
"his stomach suddenly started growling."
"So in the end, he decided to call it a day off."
"Tomorrow, after filling his stomach, he'll try to fly to the sky again."
Hiromi's leaving this home...
In the end, I couldn't do anything.
I even pulled everyone close to me into this,
and all it did was hurt them.
I never got to know how your soft cheeks would feel after the tears are wiped off.
I'm moving on Sunday.
How sudden.
Yeah.
A room just got vacant.
I'll help you move.
Is there anything else to carry?
Oh, that's all.
What's the matter?
I remembered what happened when I first moved here.
It was this empty in here that time, too.
It's not that happy of a memory, is it?
No, sometimes nice things happened as well.
We went to the festival when we were small, right?
After seeing I'd lost one of my sandals, Shinichirou-kun made do with only one sandal, too.
"I don't remember..."
You told me the other day that you don't remember that.
How could I possibly forget?
That memory...
The happiness of the festival,
then getting lost, feeling sad...
and lonely.
Then you found me,
and we walked together with one shoe.
I was so happy.
That's why I came to this house.
Even if I lost my parents and was alone...
But if I came here, I was sure Shinichirou-kun would help me find a way.
A way back from all that sadness.
But now, that's not something I can wish for anymore.
Hiromi, I...
I'm going.
Thank you for taking care of me all this time.
Don't act like a stranger, we're still just a stonethrow away.
Feel free to stop by and eat with us.
Sure.
I will also be waiting!
Yeah. Thank you.
If you want to come back, just tell me any time.
I will.
What's Shin-chan doing?
It's fine, we'll see each other at school.
"The you inside me has always been crying..."
"I want to wipe off your tears..."
I want to wipe off your tears!
I'm... a freaking idiot!
I could have done it! I could've wiped Hiromi's tears!
And still, why was I hesitating!?
I...
I...!
Err... The window...
You guys!
I'll properly wipe away your tears...
Properly wipe all of it away...
In the end, I couldn't understand your feelings.
It was definitvely on purpose! How terrible!
Wouldn't you like to meet?
The one you love is not me.