Hey, Aiko!
Don't open it!
Eh?
Why not?
Hey!
I'm opening now!
Still preparing?
Yeah.
I hurried cleaning up my house in order to see Ai-chan.
You don't need to force yourself to come...
Why do you say that?
Just be honest about how happy you are!
Here's something for ya.
Hey! Isn't that...
My sweater?
Y- Yeah...
Then let's check the size!
Come on, put it up against my shoulders,
I'm really looking forward to this.
Why must you act so spoiled?
I'm really busy!
I need to open up the store,
and you guys are keeping me!
Did you do something to make her angry?
I have no idea...
Hey, what were you doing during school breaks?
Huh?
I had to go pick out a sweater with her in your place,
it was a real pain.
Well, make sure you properly pay attention to her.
S- Sure.
Nothing but the sweets I like...
Why...
For someone like me...
My friend here is a really great guy!
Yo!
Welcome!
If you're Shinichirou's friend, then you're my friend, too!
Please go out with me!
Ai-chan, Miyokichi is a nice guy,
I guarantee it!
I know.
He's a good guy, right?
Sure.
Eh?
Awesome!
You did it!
A- Are you crying?!
I'm... such an idiot...
Huh?
Mom!
Oh, Shin-chan, you're back.
Have you seen the photo album in my room?
Oh, you mean that? I've thrown it away.
Eh? Why?
There's no point in keeping that.
That picture...
Did you call Ai-chan?
Nah, I leave her alone on days like that.
Ain't girls troublesome?
I like it even when they're being troublesome,
"I'm sorry, for being this selfish."
"Don't worry about it! Since you're so cute!"
Like that, after the storm, your love will grow!
Well!
You'll get it when you get yourself a girlfriend as well.
Girlfriend, eh?
So how's it going with Yuasa Hiromi?
Why that old story all of a sudden?
Haven't the two of you been getting along well recently?
Won't happen.
Why?
There's someone else she likes.
Eh?
And I've told him to go out with Hiromi.
Why did you do that?
Just going with the flow.
Is he retarded?
Hiromi, over there!
Hiromi, at the entrance...
Hey!
I came to see you.
I shall wait for you at the park after school.
Geez...
Incredible, Hiromi!
But that No. 4 seems like a delinquent!
He looks so cool, doesn't he?
Right?
Lay off, Hiromi's troubled.
Hey, is that fine with you?
If it's okay or not doesn't matter, does it?
Shinichirou?
Toilet.
Is that guy serious?
It's not like he really likes her.
My... all of my feelings until now...
But... Hiromi's feelings...
If I really think about it... this way should be best for Hiromi.
Shinichirou!
I... and her...
Shinichi... rou...?
Oh... did you want anything?
Here!
You should look happier when you eat something delicious!
Right now, I feel like a chicken in a cage.
Like, I can do nothing but just accept what's in front of me.
That's not it!
Like Raigou-maru, you are a special chicken aiming for the sky!
With a will of your own... a special chicken!
A will of my own?
That's right...
Then I'll be honest.
Right now, just looking at your face makes me feel anxious,
so could you leave me alone for a while?
For how long?
Shinichirou!
I met Nakagami Shinichirou the other day.
So, you like me?
Did Nakagami-kun say something?
Well, that's about it.
Want to go out with me?
Sunday at one o' clock, in front of the station's square.
Think about where you want to go.
Umm... please wait a second!
What is it?
It's nothing...
Seems like it's gonna snow.
Do you hate snow?
I won't be able to ride my bike.
What about you?
I once liked it, but now I hate it.
To start hating something you like... is hard, isn't it?
Eh?
Let me give you a lift.
You really ended up in this house.
Should I tell you...?
Ever since that day, I've hated snow.
I'm home.
Did something happen?
What did you say to No. 4?
Are you two going out?
For the time being, we have a date on Sunday.
I see, so he asked you out.
I see.
Well, isn't that great?
You nosy...
Shin-chan, you're back.
That girl came back with a boy.
I don't need you to tell me about that.
Granny,
Shinichirou told me not to bother him for a while.
Somehow I think it's just too boring.
What's with that belt?
It's Shinichirou's.
You... didn't...
I just borrowed it.
Did that guy say something to you?
Nope, why do you ask?
Nah, it's nothing.
You going out?
It's a date.
Really?!
You look cool, onii-chan!
Well, I'm leaving.
Hey, what kind of girl is she?
She's cute, right? Is she from your school?
She's from your school.
It's Yuasa Hiromi.
Remember I told you my dad gave me some money for helping out with the crops?
I'm gonna get you a sweater today, as a present.
Huh?
Is something wrong?
Well... it's my first time at the movies with a guy.
I've always just been here with Noe.
You two are really close, huh?
Our father and grandmother died,
and our mother goes out for work.
It's always just the two of us.
I understand her feelings as if I hold them in my hand.
Things she hasn't even realized herself.
It's fine... I'll feel bad...
It's just I want to buy one for ya.
7500 yen, please.
Alright, 7500 yen, eh?
There's no need.
We'll just get it next time.
Ai-chan?
I'm sorry.
Sorry about that.
You don't have to apologize.
I thought brighter colors would fit Ai-chan.
Since the one that Shinichirou picked is so plain.
You knew that we went shopping together?
That doesn't matter.
Just shopping...
That's not it...
Shinichirou didn't pick that sweater for me.
I decided to buy it after Shinichirou picked it up and looked at it.
Shinichirou liked that sweater... So, I...
What do you mean by that?
It's fine here.
Right.
Umm... As I thought, I...
Hey, I want you to pass a word onto Nakagami Shinichirou.
Tell him to be more serious about Noe.
The two of them are dating.
I- I gotta go.
Welcome home.
Is something wrong?
It- It's nothing.
But...
There's nothing wrong.
Oh, you're here?
I will be done soon.
Did you come back with another guy?
Eh?
People are watching, you need to be more careful.
And here, there is Shinichirou...
What do you think people would say about him living with such an easy girl?
Why...
Eh?
Why are you talking about this?
Just because I am mom's child...
Just because that happened...
Is that why you are calling me easy!?
You... still remember that story?
I've never forgotten about it.
Not for a single moment...
Anyway, be careful.
What the hell are you doing?
Shin-chan...
What the hell is "that story"?
It has nothing to do with Shin-chan.
I have always been wondering...
Mom, aren't you acting too strict towards Hiromi?!
Shinichirou-kun, stop it!
It's fine already!
It's not!
I said it's fine! Leave me alone!
Hiromi!
Mom, please! Take it easy!
What did mom say to you?
What is "that story"?
Want me to tell you a big secret?
My birthday is latter,
So Shinichirou-kun is my older brother.
Is that... some kind of joke?
Seriously... doesn't it seem like a joke?
Oba-san said that Shinichirou-kun's father might be my real father.
I said it...
What... should I do...?
"Left behind by the girl..."
"There, a small pond had formed."
"A pond formed from the girl's tears."
"For some reason..."
"It was really deep."
"Infinitely deep."
"I..."
"felt like I was dragged down into it."
Shinichirou has a cockroach on his head~♪
Shinichirou has a cockroach on his back~♪
Should I give up on Hiromi?
Apologize to Shinichirou.
Who's that girl?
Tell me properly, write it down here.