Siblings, she says?
That sort of twist... is impossible!
It seems so impossible that it's almost on the same level as a joke.
Besides, above all,
...we don't look alike.
What will make us look alike?
Like this?
I don't have a clue what Mom told her,
But something like that just isn't possible.
What will happen if it's true?
Will I give up on Hiromi?
How stupid... I was supposed to give up on her before that.
Got you! Got you!
Sorry, but I don't feel like eating.
Why don't you feel like eating?
"Why"?
You're still troubled, aren't you?
Let's think about it together!
What are you talking about?
Didn't you say you feel anxious when I'm around?
But I think that's wrong.
Huh?
You are troubled because you're alone.
Even if it's dark,
If someone is there by your side, you'll definitely feel much stronger.
You will surely find the answer!
I will help Shinichirou with that!
So, try telling me!
Impossible.
You won't understand.
I... won't understand?
Yeah...
Here, take this back.
Ground, today I'm giving you a huge sin as a present.
You understand, right, Ground?
I... don't understand.
Hey, Hiromi.
You aren't eating lunch today again?
Ho- Hold-!
A bento.
I'm sorry, but right now...
Eat it.
Crap...
It's delicious!
Eat it all up.
Here, potato.
Here's some fried meat.
Wait a bit!
I still haven't completely swallowed the potato.
Then apologize.
Apologize to Shinichirou.
Even if he could really fly, Shinichirou isn't looking at the sky.
He's avoiding looking at the sky.
I think that this is your fault.
I understand what's wrong after observing you.
You won't be able to fly,
ever.
Since you can't fly, it troubled Shinichirou, who can fly.
Just strange, isn't it?
What?
What the hell is that?
All you've done is talking,
but you don't understand anything!
That's unfair!
What is?
That I don't understand!
If you just explain it to me, would I not understand?!
Let go!
There are only mysteries revolving around you.
You won't even tell me about what's going on between you and Jun.
We aren't friends anymore if you don't tell me what's going on!
Since when were we friends anyway?!
They've started...
Hiromi!
Hey, is that a fight?
Damn, girls sure are scary.
Wha...
Hiromi!
Hiromi, wait!
Man...
this is troublesome.
What happened?
Hey, Noe...
Why won't the two of you tell me anything?
Why don't you just tell me what's wrong if I don't understand?
If not, we can't think about it together,
and then I can't be of any help to you, you know?
All I want is to understand you more!
It really hurts to see Shinichirou troubled!
It's really painful!
And yet, there's nothing I can do to help...
She... could it be that...
Could it be that...
you like me?
I do like you,
only you can continue Raigoumaru's will.
I don't mean that kind of like.
What do you mean by like?
Uh... well...
Like the kind where you go out together...
...what you'd classify as love.
Noe!
Noe likes me.
And, Hiromi likes Noe's brother.
Also, I like Hiromi.
But, Hiromi and I are...
like that's possible!
He's starting to get well on his posing.
Perhaps he's getting into it now.
Yeah.
Everyone's praising you back there.
You don't seem very happy...
Not really...
Hey, Shinichirou,
Um, remember when you helped me measure the sweater's size?
If you'd like... because...
I knit pretty fast, so...
I could make one for Shinichirou as well...
Who is this girl?
Aren't you going out with Noe?
Hey, what's he talking about?
Ai-chan, go on ahead.
Please.
Now then,
I've been dating Hiromi,
So why don't you hurry up and start going out with Noe?
I never promised that!
You're the one who proposed it, right?
Well...
If you don't keep your promise, it's over between me and Hiromi.
How long are you going to be this selfish?!
What's wrong?
Well...
At any rate, just keep your promise.
That's all.
Is Shinichirou dating?
But, I'm sure whoever Shinichirou likes, it's not that Noe girl.
But...
Oh no...
Shinichirou?
Whoa! Cold, cold, cold, cold, cold!
Don't you think it's getting extremely cold tonight?
Well, to be flirting in a cold place is kind of romantic, too...
You know...
Ah, yeah, how's that sweater coming?
Aah, I wan't to wear it soon!
It's a sweater made by my girlfriend, after all,
I never would have expected one!
I'm sorry...
I can't make you one, after all.
Eh? Why's that...?
We- Well! It's all right!
I bet Ai-chan's not skilled enough,
But that's also a part of you that I-
Stop being kind to me!
I don't deserve your kindness.
Ai-chan?
It was here, right?
This is where Shinichirou told me how you feel.
You know, I...
...actually...
...long before that happened...
Well, isn't it cold?
Let's go back to the store.
Hold on! I haven't said every-
I'm sorry, but I'm sure I don't want to hear what you were getting at.
Let's hold hands on our way back.
Hey...
All I have is Ai-chan.
There's only you...
About what happened yesterday...
You-
Could you fix what I told you to as soon as possible?
It's fine, right? I'm counting on you.
Is Mom making you work again?
Shinichirou.
Did Mom say something to you?
No... not really.
Nothing.
I've started thinking about Noe's feelings...
Because all I've been thinking of was Hiromi...
I never thought there can be any romantic feelings between us.
I like her, right?
Probably.
If I didn't like her, there's no way I'd let her push me around so much.
Yeah...
It's not just because of some promise...
I'm home.
Noe...
Stay away!
I've changed since yesterday.
It seems I've fallen in love.
Since a while back... different parts of my body feel hot...
My face, my chest, my ears...
Hey, what should I do, onii-chan?
I've changed...
I feel so embarrassed, I can't look at Shinichirou's face anymore!
It's fine.
There's nothing wrong with changing.
Really?
Yeah, it's fine.
No, in fact, you must change.
It's so cold!
We're going to another building, so we'll have to endure it.
In addition, if it's this cold it's definitively going to snow tonight!
Will we even make it through till evening?
Wanna bet?
Alright, then...
What's wrong?
What is it?
Snow...
Snow?!
What should we eat tonight?
Well, it's snowing, so why not udon?
Eh? Didn't we eat udon yesterday as well?
Then, what do you think about ramen?
Hey Miyokichi, it's time for lunch...
Sure, I agree.
Then, hold on for a second.
I don't feel like eating today.
Okay!
Are you feeling bad?
Nah, I just ate too much during breakfast.
Well then, I guess I'll go eat with someone else.
You're... cool, I guess.
I'm okay with it. If it's you...
You know, I think you really should go see a doctor.
Eh- hey!
That's not what I meant.
Noe!
Hey, don't you have lunch for me today?
There's none!
None, none!
I don't have any!
Hey! Noe!
Hey! Wait! Come on, wait!
Let go!
I bet you'll just run away if I let go.
I'm not running away...
See? You are running away.
Be- Because...
Because... of what?
Why are you mad?
I'm not mad.
What about you, why are you running away?
Then, why are you chasing me?
Well...
I have something to tell you!
What is it?
What? Hurry up and say it!
If there's nothing, then why should I stop?
Tell me, in three seconds, what do you want to say?
G-Go...
Go out with me!
"Go out"? What do you mean?
Are you saying you like me in a romantic way?
That's right...
Tell me properly.
Eh?
That you like me.
I like you, Noe.
Write it down here.
Eh?
Write it down?
I can't find anything more that will fit.
There aren't enough stones.
I need only two more...
No way...
They'll get dirty!
It's fine.
It's done.
Right now... I want to cry.
Why is that?
I'm not even sad...
But... I really, really want to cry.
Because I'm happy...
It must be because I'm happy.
She... really does like me.
Whoa... looks like it'll build up.
Huh?
Come on, what's wrong? What are you doing?!
Come on, you'll catch yourself a cold.
Hey, about last time...
Um, I've started going out with Noe.
I don't think I understand it clearly myself...
Ai-chan...
Wait!
Shinichirou!
Ai-chan...
Please...
Look at me too...
Shinichirou...
Is it okay if I fall in love with you even more?
With such a docile face, she was easily able to catch a man's heart.
It's a game.
A town where it doesn't snow...