Ah, yes, that way, please.
Be careful.
The Chicago-to-New York
transcontinental express, Flying Pussyfoot.
It's a mobile ornament, built by Nebula.
Its design is taken from the English royal train,
and these first-class cars,
which are usually in the rear,
are said to be up front because
the sculpting complements all the ornamentation.
Still, it does feel a little ostentatious, huh?
Let's not get on.
Why not?
Something not right is going to happen.
This train is cursed.
Hey, now, is this the same
sixth sense you always get?
Has it ever been wrong?
It's going to be terrible.
A lot of people are going to die.
The only ones who will survive
are those with fairly good luck, and...
And?
Probably...
...those who are not human, I'd say.
Hey, Isaac?
What, Miria?
What are we doing here?
We're digging for kin, Miria.
By kin, you mean, "gold," right?
Yeah, that's right, Miria.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime big job for us!
After all, we're stealing kin from the earth.
By "earth," you mean, this planet, right?
Yeah, that's right, Miria.
No one has ever tried to
steal from the earth before!
By which I mean, our names are
going to go down in history, Miria!
Incredible!
All right, let's go, Miria!
Let's go!
Ready, set...
Hey, Isaac?
What, Miria?
People usually take gold out of the river,
so why are we digging a hole?
That's something that hopeless
amateurs who don't know better do.
But then, when we tried to
pan out a little gold dust there,
some men made a lot of
noise about us being on their turf,
That was humiliating, huh?
However, I saw a centipede out
in front of this abandoned mine.
A huge one, that had
many hundreds of legs!
Word is that in the Orient,
centipedes are the gods of gold mining.
That's when I became convinced
that a whole bunch of
gold was coming out of here!
Wow! We haven't found
a single nugget yet, but
that's incredible!!
Oh, yeah, Isaac...
What, Miria?
We got a letter from Ennis.
Oh, and what does it say?
"Dear Isaac-san and Miria-san,
Almost a year has passed
since you left New York.
Everything is the same here,
but we sure do miss having
the lively pair of you around.
Why not knock off your
unsuccessful gold mining for now,
and come this way to visit us?
Isaac-san and Miria-san,
I feel like you two are
my own brother and sister.
The real brother and sister
that I never got to meet.
When I think of everyone
that was created before I was,
I feel very sorrowful,
but thanks to you, Isaac-san and
Miria-san, I am able to get past it."
Hey, Isaac?
What, Miria?
Does Ennis mean that
her older siblings are already dead?
No, no, you're wrong. You're wrong, Miria.
Um, "was made"? "Never got to meet"?
You see, what she means is...
Yeah, that's it!
She wants a younger brother!
So you mean, she's like a happy little
problem child, pestering her mother?
Yeah, that's right, Miria.
That's it. Ennis is happy, you see?
Well, Isaac, we're not Ennis's
mama, so we can't do anything, huh?
Nope. Unfortunately, you're right, Miria.
Instead, let's come up with some
amazing gift, and go to New York!
But Isaac, we don't have any money at all.
Well then, let's commit a train robbery.
Ah, fantastic!
By the way, a train robbery is where
you take the train to a destination,
do the robbery,
then get on the train again and flee,
isn't it?
That's right, Isaac!
All right! Then, like we've done before...
Let's steal some money from
the Mafia, who do bad things!
Strike! The count is 2-and-2.
Will the batter be able to
come from behind and deliver?
Yes, he'd certainly want to go for broke here.
The pitcher winds up... and throws!
Wham!
He hits it!
It's going... it's going...
it's gone! A home run!
Hold it--
The crowd is cheering wildly!
What do you think, Miria?!
It's incredible, Isaac!
We're champions of justice!
Wow, incredible!
J-Just a minute...
Look at that, Miria.
Oh, what's that?
Just to be safe, the orchestra will be riding
in the freight hold, if that's all right with you.
No, that's out of my hands--
We have received permission.
Ah, in that case, there is no problem.
Our instruments are delicate,
you understand.
Carry them in.
Miria! A symphony!
An orchestra! Mozart! Paul Dukas!
And Beethoven, huh?
Tony-san, nice work, there.
Nice work, yourself.
You're as energetic as ever, huh?
Yeah. I finally get to ride
aboard the Flying Pussyfoot, after all.
I just can't bring myself
to be fond of this train,
but maybe a youngster
like you will enjoy it more.
What are you talking about?
Tony-san, you're not through yet.
I'm retiring after this go-round.
I've already told the company so.
You mean it?
I'm old. This is your era now.
Tony-san...
I'm counting on you. This is a special train.
Right!
Oh, there's a fine woman!
Don't you think so? Huh? Huh?
What do I do? What do I do?
I heard there was going to be
some sort of lookout in the freight hold!
It's all right.
It looks like what we're after is
going to be loaded into another hold.
B-But...
T-Take it easy.
I'll take care of the lookout.
N-N-No, no, you can't!
Donny, if you do anything,
you'll die! No! No!
It'll be all right... probably...
P-Probably isn't good enough!
We've made a hidden room
in the freight hold.
As long as nothing
comes up, no one will find it.
What might come up?
An explosion, or something.
They're in black, huh, Isaac?
I wonder what kind of rich folk
there's going to be,
riding in first class aboard this thing.
Ah, first off, there's that
black-suited orchestra, huh?
They're all in white, Miria!
See?
Doesn't it feel great,
with them accentuating the contrast between us?
Hey, has anyone seen who
else is going to be aboard?
Over there.
Senator Beriam's wife and daughter.
I've seen them in the newspaper,
so I know I'm not wrong.
Oh... they must really be
enjoying their way in the world.
Riding in first class,
I'll bet they think they're
going to be in for quite a safe trip.
Okay, let's get going.
We're going to care for these poor
passengers like our own livestock.
We'll despise them...
...like maggots...
...lovingly...
...angrily... carefully... carefully...
What do you say? Let's grind them up!
Ladd!
Ta-da! I got us a conductor's uniform!
You're the best.
They're all in white, huh?
I wonder if they're having a wedding
on the train, or something.
A happy wedding, right? A big bash, right?
Yeah! This is indeed a train fit
for us to be doing our train robbery on!
Eh? We've already done it, and
we're running away on the train, right?
That's part of the train robbery, too!
They departed on schedule.
And the item?
It's safe. However...
Your wife and daughter are aboard.
You're certain?
I checked the list of names.
The item is in the last car,
furthest away from the first-class car.
If anything were to happen,
I believe they would be safe.
It is also possible to force the train to stop,
and get just the two of them off.
It doesn't matter. Stick to the plan.
But sir...
It's a matter of which is more important.
The item, or my family.
Senator Beriam...
If anything does happen,
such is my wife and daughter's fate.
I told you not to talk about that here.
But Youn, coming at night didn't do any good.
It's too risky.
They say this is a high-grade package.
It's supposed to be a new type of bomb.
Thanks for waiting.
B-Bomb?!
Thank you for waiting.
T-They just said it might be, right? Right?
They were certain of it.
O-oh, man... if it were
to explode or anything...
That would be neat, wouldn't it?
That's Nice for you.
Living up to her reputation as a bomb fiend.
Cut it out, would you? It's embarrassing.
A-Are we really able to steal it?
Are we? Are we?
With me along, it'll be all right.
B-But...
Knock on wood.
That's right, Miria!
Are they actors, or something?
They've been ordering nothing
but Chinese dishes for a while now.
And honey green tea.
W-Why?
Who knows?
Why don't you try talking to them?
Go on and talk to them.
We were right, Miria!
Incredible, Isaac!
Go on and talk to them.
It will be fun, won't it?
Incredible, Isaac!
B-But... I'm scared!
They could be movie stars.
It would be kind of cool
if you got chummy with them, wouldn't it?
You think so?
I sure do.
U-Um...
Stop teasing Jacuzzi so much, would you?
That's not what I'm doing, Youn-san. I just...
...want Jacuzzi to be a little more sociable.
I have to say, buddy,
that looks really cool!
I've never seen anyone
with a tattoo right on their face!
It's like culture shock, huh?
By any chance, are you a movie star?
Huh?! Incredible!
N-No, I-I'm not a movie star,
I make... and sell... liquor...
And? And?
No... that's not true...
I'm just a delinquent,
or whatever you'd call it.
And? And?
A-Anyhow, I'm just a normal person...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm not sure why,
but he's suddenly apologizing to us.
What do we do, Miria?
From a win-or-lose standpoint, we've won, huh?
Oh, we've won, have we, Miria?
It was a good match!
Buddy, wipe those tears away,
and come sit over here!
Come on, have some Chinese cooking with us!
It's all-you-can-eat!
O-Okay...
No, it isn't.
Cows are herbivores, right?
Mm-hmm!
Which means that when you eat beef,
it also means that you're
eating meat and grass together!
You're so smart, Isaac!
Aren't I?
If you eat something that's been eaten,
it means that you eat that, too!
And it's not just food, either!
If you pick up something
that something else is carrying...
...it all becomes yours!
If a person is carrying a bag full of money,
then they're carrying
both the money and the bag!
Yay! They're rich!
They have an expression
for this over in the Orient.
"And then I went..." um...
"...and ate you."
Yeah, that's it!
Oh, is that right? That's funny.
I haven't seen Jacuzzi have
this much fun in a long time.
It is funny, huh?
I haven't seen Jacuzzi have
this much fun in a long time.
Jacuzzi?
I'm sorry!
Um, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm perfectly fine.
Mary!
I'm terribly sorry
my daughter disturbed you.
Oh, no, I should be apologizing to you.
What for?
Are you taking a family trip?
Yes. My daughter and I
are going to see my husband.
I'm Natalie Beriam.
My daughter's name is Mary.
J-Jacuzzi Splot. T-This is Nice-
Isaac and Miria!
Good evening!
G-Good evening.
I'm... Czeslaw Meyer.
I'm on my way to see
my family in New York.
You're so cute!
Just like Jacuzzi was, way back!
I really am sorry.
Oh, it's all right.
It's not like you did anything wrong.
Yeah, yeah! You did do
something wrong, and now...
You're gonna get eaten by the Rail Tracer!
M-Me?
That's right! Gobbled right up!
W-What's the Rail Tracer?
Oh, Jacuzzi, you don't know?
The Rail Tracer is...
...a monster, that comes chasing after trains.
It is cloaked in the darkness
of night, and little by little,
it draws closer to the train.
And it can change its shape into many things.
What happens when it catches up?
The people, you see... they all disappear...
Starting with the rear of the train,
gradually, one at a time...
Until finally, everyone is gone...
And the very existence
of that train just vanishes...
Ha, that's ridiculous.
But what's even more frightening...
More frightening...
When you tell this story on a train,
it comes to that train, too.
The Rail Tracer!!
T-This is terrible! We're gonna get wiped out!
Take it easy, Jacuzzi.
There is one way
to keep the Rail Tracer from coming here.
Only one?
Yes. And that is...
Oh, just a minute. It's time.
It's time.
Split up into teams of three,
as planned, and get to work.
So, um, in order to be spared, you see...
I know of a similar sort of story.
And you want to swap ways to be saved, right?
Oh, it's a simple story.
A story about the ghosts they call "Lemures."
We no longer have any blood relatives.
All we have is our allegiance
to Master Huey Laforet.
Our earnest wish is to
transcend both life and death,
and ultimately become one with Huey,
who has obtained eternal life!
We are the Lemures.
I want you to consider once again what it means
to call yourselves ghosts.
We are no longer afraid of death,
because we have become ghosts
while still alive.
So, in order to be spared...
What are you supposed to do again, Miria?
I don't know.
This is the first time
I'm hearing about this, too.
O-o-oh, no!
I've heard the story.
R-Really?
Yeah.
From the young conductor
on this train, as I recall.
Isaac-san! I-I'm going to go ask him
right now how to be saved!
Sorry, he's a bit of a scaredy-cat.
Why did I give my real name out earlier?
Jacuzzi is a hell of a guy, huh, Miria?
Well, we'll have to let him win later.
Why did I give my real name out earlier?
Is there an immortal among them?
Yeah! Let's let him win a round!
It's scary, huh, Czes-kun?
Just one round, Isaac?
Huh? Oh, you're right.
Okay, two rounds?
There was a great leader among the ghosts.
But the United States
government arrested that man,
and is trying to keep it all hushed up.
This is a rite, to bring
our great teacher back to us again.
This train is our altar,
and the passengers are
no more than sacrifices.
Do not forget that.
Whoa.
What's the matter, Jacuzzi? What's the rush?
Oh, it's terrible!
This train just might vanish!
So I have to get to the conductor!
So then, the remaining ghosts had an idea.
They would take some passengers hostage,
including the family of a senator,
and demand that their leader be freed.
Our great teacher, Huey,
is going to be questioned by
the judiciary in New York tomorrow.
And so, this train has been chosen
to be a sacrifice for our teacher!
Have faith that our actions
will lead to the release and rescue of
our captive Master Huey!
Be right back.
Watch it, you little brat!
S-Sorry! Excuse me.
The train is in trouble!
T-That's why I have to get to
the conductor's compartment!
Anyhow, I'm sorry!
Wasn't that...
I'm sure of it.
Now then, as for
the all-important way to be spared...
Everyone who heard this story died right away.
They say there wasn't a single way
for any of them to be saved!
Looking up at the starry sky
that goes on forever, we sing
a melody of a dream
we have of our limited eternity
The water of adoration,
overflowing in our hearts
will reach someone in the distant future
I believe so
Running through time prolonged,
our voices calling out will
someday become a great song
We can go on spinning our love
though it may still be such a tiny light now
Hey, Miria, what do you do
to get ready for a party?
First, you get people together.
Then what?
Then you make a lot of noise!
Miria, that's not getting ready,
that's the actual party.
Oh. Then, what do you do?
What do you do?