Who's there?!
Gretto,
are you worried about your brother?
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Alchemists, summoning a devil?
Is something like that even allowed?
Eternal life, immortal youth...
does mankind really need that sort of thing?
I don't know about that.
But if it's a way to come near to
the secrets of the "grand panacea,"
then I don't think there's
anything we can do about--
I don't necessarily think that
eternal life would be a marvelous thing.
Even with just this limited life,
as long as I'm with you, Sylvie...
If I am granted eternal life,
then I won't be scared,
as long as I'm with you.
Sylvie...
You accept that man?!
Maiza-dono is outstanding.
It is patently heretical for
an alchemist to summon a devil!
This is unexpected,
for someone as inquisitive as you are.
The grand panacea is every alchemist's dream.
Even if it means devils,
if we are able to obtain it,
the history of mankind will be changed.
Obviously, it's a bunch of nonsense!
But what if it's true?
Maiza could be a great alchemist,
on the level of Synesius, or Zosimos.
Everyone, smile!
Smiling faces, smiling faces!
There is nothing to be afraid of.
Huey...
"That which is below is
like that which is above,
and that which is above
is like that which is below
to do the miracles of one only thing."
"And as all things have
been and arose from one
by the meditation of one
so all things have their birth
from this one thing by adaptation."
That is correct.
Everything is linked in one,
and the circle is closed.
The devil that we think of
may not necessarily be, in fact, evil.
When an alchemist tries his hand in
the realm of the black magician,
everything becomes linked in one.
Huey, you aren't worried?
Worried? No, I am just very interested.
About devils, the grand panacea,
how people will be changed
by them, and how they will live.
I'm just very interested in it all.
I look forward to it.
Would you bring everyone here?
Only his clothes were lying there.
There was no sign of Pierre.
Or Italo.
Italo is gone, too.
What's going on?
I don't know if what I am about to perform
is the right thing for me,
or for all of us together.
The one who passed this on to me was a man
who once undertook
the same school of alchemy that I have.
The man had not aged a day
since my grandfather's time.
This is because 300 years ago,
he successfully summoned a devil,
and was successful in
obtaining the "grand panacea."
That man is probably
surviving even now, somewhere.
Without having aged a day.
But coming near unto the "grand panacea"
is the earnest desire of
those of us who are alchemists.
I will now perform the devilkin summoning.
Believe that there is greater
worth in that which is gained by gaining
than that which is gained by losing!
Brethren, I ask you to see this
through with me to the end.
Denkuro, Gretto...
I summon thee to this place!
Thou art the heavens and the earth!
The night, and the day!
The darkness, and the light!
The good, and the wicked!
The one who sees, and who is seen!
The one who brings about creation,
and brings about destruction!
The one who loves man,
and despises man! Thou art--
Enough.
What happened?
I don't know! It's a monster!
There's something in there!
It's the devil! I'm sure that
the devil is raging in there!
What about Gretto?
Do you know what happened to Gretto?!
Your words of summoning
are nothing more than tedious.
I hear your words at all times,
and I know your thoughts, as well.
When you think about me,
I am already there in your midst.
Well, no matter.
There is no need to call me by name.
I am not at all content
with being called a devil.
But, no matter.
In any event, I know what you are thinking.
You want to know
all about immortal youth, right?
I will tell you, alone, how to make
what you call the "grand panacea."
Why only me?
Once you drink that,
you will become immortally young.
Now, drink.
If you wish to know all,
you must first drink.
Old man, you seem to not want an early death.
I'm just trying to put
a quick end to this charade.
I knew it, it's a sham, all right!
You won't believe unless I do this?
Well, old man? How does it
feel to be immortally ageless?
Calm down. Do not quarrel. I am generous.
There is enough "grand panacea"
for everyone here.
Brother...
Gretto...
There are a number of rules
we should establish.
What if you grow tired of immortality,
and want to die?
Do not hesitate to go to
one of your friends,
and have them devour you.
And when I say "devour, "
I do not mean by mouth.
By the right hand.
Have them place their right hand on your head,
and when they think to themselves,
"I want to eat, "
you will be absorbed into their right hand.
Your life will end.
Also, by doing so, the devourer will inherit
all of the knowledge and
experiences of the one being devoured.
Contrarily, when giving knowledge,
place your right hand on the person's head.
That is all that is required.
One other thing.
I will make it such that those who drank
cannot use false names.
You can only converse with fellow
immortals by using your real names.
Otherwise, you would never
be able to seek out another, for eternity.
Whoops, I forgot the most important thing.
If you wish to know how to prepare this elixir,
then you may ask the man who summoned me.
You want to contain this knowledge?
What are you thinking, Maiza?!
It's the conclusion I came to
after thinking about it overnight.
We had better keep everyone
but ourselves from drinking it.
It's too dangerous.
It's precisely because it's dangerous
that we need this information!
Szilard-san, I cannot trust mankind
as much as you do.
Are you being sarcastic?
No, that is my honest feeling.
Elderly sir, I kind of agree with Maiza.
Ultimately, I think that somehow
he's right about this.
What do you mean?
Here I am, having become
immortally young like this,
but I myself haven't changed at all.
I'm the same as I ever was.
I will go on living,
without ever dying or getting older,
but it seems to me that I'm no
different from those who won't.
On the one hand, I feel like
I'm going to become very sad,
and yet I feel that
I'm going to enjoy myself greatly.
Be that as it may,
it really does somehow seem like...
it somehow seems like he's right.
I think it's better for there not
to be too many people like us.
You're not making any sense!
I know. But elderly sir,
my intuition tells me that
what I'm saying isn't too far off the mark.
I stand with Elmer-dono. Hence,
I will abide by Maiza-dono's decision.
What?!
I support my brother's decision.
I will also follow Maiza-san.
It is always possible
to share this knowledge later.
It won't be too late to decide
after we see what the future brings us.
I will abide by Maiza's decision.
If Fermet says so, then so do I.
I'm following Maiza.
I'm with Maiza, too.
I will defer.
This is not a question that we can come
to a conclusion on by discussing it here.
Moreover, it's not something that
should be decided by majority vote.
My thinking is generally
the same as Elmer's and Fermet's,
but I can't express my opinion
in terms of "it somehow seems."
So I will ask to withhold my decision.
When will you draw your conclusion?
Who can say? A century, or two?
Whatever happens, no decision
will be too late for us any longer.
Thank you, brethren.
So then, for the time being,
I will ask that all knowledge
concerning the "grand panacea"
remain with me.
Gretto?
Gretto, I am having regrets.
Indeed, there is knowledge
that mankind ought not have.
This is dangerous.
This will cause discord not only
among those who hate each other,
but among those who love each other, as well.
Brother, what do you mean?
The truth is, right now, I am conflicted.
About whether or not
I should "devour" Szilard.
That man and I are not all that different.
Brother...
Still, Gretto...
if those who become
immortal are outstanding people,
people who will bring about
miracles and happiness in this world,
then this knowledge will be invaluable.
And so, Gretto, I'm thinking of
sharing half of this knowledge with you.
If you ever encounter anyone like that,
do not hesitate to come to me.
If I am no longer among you at the time,
then use this half of the knowledge
and your own ability
to seek out the secret of the elixir.
No... That responsibility
is too much for me to bear...
Gretto, you are the only one
aboard this ship that I sincerely trust.
You are the only one who
possesses true purity of heart.
I want you to accept this.
This is our fate.
Brother...
Thank you.
Don't do it, Maiza!
Elmer!
You can't. You can't do that.
In time, Szilard is going to do harm.
Before long, someone is
going to start the devouring.
But you can't be the one who starts it!
Elmer...
Smile, Maiza.
Even that old man might change.
What is this?
Who would have thought that I would end up
devouring a young girl in a place like this?
It was you.
My lust should have disappeared long ago,
but I hear a voice inside me that seeks you.
I see. That young man seemed to be
quite taken with you, huh?
What do you mean by that?
Stop!
Please, stop! I beg you!
Gretto, this is your punishment.
That man was wrong in trying to monopolize
such grand knowledge in the first place.
Help!
Sylvie, I'm so happy.
Everyone's own experiences,
everyone's own knowledge,
everyone's own desires...
There is no end to the useful
things one ought to know in life!
I still want to know more!
I still haven't eaten enough, Sylvie!
You're the one... You ate him, didn't you?
You can curse your fate for being born
that man's younger brother.
Do not worry. I will make
you one with me, inside me.
You ate him, didn't you?!
S-Sylvie!
Maiza, I...
Let's find Szilard.
Sylvie! You didn't drink!
Nile, why, you!
I am extremely angry with you
right now, but I'll go ahead
and put my feelings into words anyhow.
I'll kill you!
Maiza-san...
Sylvie, are you okay?
Come on, let's smile together.
I guess not. Well, I'm going to
go try to convince old man Szilard.
Convince him?
What can you convince that man of?
The possibility isn't zero.
Elmer-san!
Give up, Szilard-dono!
I have no reservations
any longer, Szilard-san.
Hey! Old man Szilard!
Listen to what I have to say!
Yow!
Elmer!
Maiza!
To think that you would try a stunt
like that to get the old man's attention...
You're an unusual man. Fascinating.
I will grant you one wish.
Almost like an Arabian genie.
Yes, but you only get one wish, not three.
All right, I've decided, devil.
Elmer-san!
Are you all right, Elmer-san?!
Where's old man Szilard?
He fell into the sea. I doubt he'll be
returning to the ship, in his condition.
I see. I thought
I had a chance at convincing him.
Sylvie...
I know you don't want to right now,
but you have to keep
a happy face. Smile, Sylvie.
Elmer-san...
I did believe that the possibility was zero.
So that's why...
I haven't given up yet, though.
Gretto...
I never imagined that it would start so soon.
It bothers me that it looks like I incited this,
but the human race is
thoroughly steeped in avarice.
Why are you speaking to me?
Because you were there.
As fellow onlookers, not getting involved,
let's try to get along with each other.
I'm just interested, that's all.
Birds of a feather. Well, all right.
I thought this was the time, for sure.
What do you mean?
Nothing much.
It was just a mild sentiment, you might say.
It almost sounds like you are
expecting something from us.
Don't be so hasty.
After all, we're going to
be together for a long time.
We'll have opportunity to
meet each other again, as well.
It's risky turning the Runoratas against us,
but you might say that
this man Gustavo is less than fearsome.
I see. Then, other than brushing
away the sparks that come at us,
you want us to not get involved, right?
I don't think there will be any problems.
Maiza, I can sense
the presence of Szilard right nearby.
Don't you sense anything?
Oh, well.
Looking up at the starry sky
that goes on forever, we sing
a melody of a dream
we have of our limited eternity
The water of adoration,
overflowing in our hearts
will reach someone in the distant future
I believe so
Running through time prolonged,
our voices calling out will
someday become a great song
We can go on spinning our love
though it may still be such a tiny light now
Miria, it says "Isaac and Miria
Unintentionally Spread Happiness Around Them!"
That's incredible, Isaac!
They've got the same names that we do!
Same first, same last!
We'll have to spread happiness, so we're not
shown up by this Isaac-san and Miria-san!
I'm not sure I get it, but it's incredible!