Instead, let's come up with some
amazing gift, and go to New York!
It's all-out war...
...with the Russo Family...
Incredible!
All right then, gentlemen,
allow me to introduce to you,
from the FBI, special investigators
Bill Sullivan, and Donald Brown.
It's a pleasure.
Yeah.
These two are pursuing suspects
in a string of robberies
that have taken place over several states.
They have struck more than 80 times now,
and I have pledged
the whole force's cooperation.
These are photos of the robbers.
Next.
Chief...
What is it?
Are you pulling our legs?
An understandable question,
but it's these two
who are doing the goofing around.
Chief...
What is it?
If they have turned up in all of these photos,
why hasn't anyone
been able to arrest them?
An understandable question,
but I will ask Mr. Sullivan to explain.
These are all photos that
local people happened to shoot of them
because of their eccentric outfits.
Generally, they did not realize
that they were robbers
until after the pictures were taken.
All of their crimes up to
now have been petty offenses,
not serious enough to get
them on our wanted lists.
Watches, chocolates, candy, and...
They once stole the door to an art museum.
In that case,
wouldn't it be quicker to have
their mamas chew them out?
I'm afraid we can't settle for just that.
The pair have made off
with the entire inheritance
of the New Jersey millionaire, Mr. Genoard.
Chief...
What is it?
What could have suddenly come over them?
An understandable question,
but if you ask me, I have no answer.
You can ask them yourselves.
Oh, crap!
Miria! We've forgotten
something awfully important!
What's that?
Ennis's... Ennis's...
W-W-What do we do?
What are we going to do?!
Isaac!
Miria!
--We forgot to buy a gift for Ennis!!
Hey, guys.
There's something up on the forward coupling.
Ready, set...
The Rail Tracer?
I don't see it anymore.
Let's go.
Maybe...
Let's go up and see.
Donny, you head up the aisle down there,
and wait for us one coupling ahead.
You can count on me.
Be especially careful about the black suits.
Yeah.
Let's go!
Boss, you get the feeling
that Jacuzzi is all worked up?
He hasn't been like this since
those eight were killed by the Russo Family.
He was amazing back then,
even as he was crying, huh?
I wonder how far he'll go this time.
I am Gustavo Baggetta, of the Runorata Family.
We may have been rough with you,
but relax, we have no plans to take your life.
Runorata... I've heard that name before.
Your granddad, father, and brother
were all good friends with our boss.
Why are you doing this?
We have business with your other brother.
With Big Brother Dallas?
Your Big Brother Dallas
has done something naughty.
We have to tell him off,
but we have no idea where he is.
So, we're going to hold you hostage.
It's our way of calling the bastard out.
You're going to stay with us
for a while, like it or not.
You scared?
You're scared, aren't you?
You're a strong-willed little lady.
You want me to tell you
what kind of mischief your brother got into?
He's blackmailing us.
He says that your father and brother...
...were killed by us!
Is that true? Did you really
kill my father and Geoffrey?!
I'm not telling.
Are you really related to
that good-for-nothing father
and good-for-nothing brother of yours?
If they'd had
the strength of will that you have,
they might have lived another five minutes.
Whoops, that just slipped out.
God is going to punish people like you.
God, huh?
The people with the power prevail.
Such is the law of this world.
That's not true!
Big Brother Dallas...
Hey, Miria...
What, Isaac?
She's crying.
She's crying, huh?
She's looking at the picture and crying.
Photography.
It must be her lover.
Romance.
They were lovey-dovey.
Lovey-dovey.
I wonder if they've been separated for life.
I'm sure it must have been
an incredibly sad farewell.
Or maybe, they've been separated by death.
How tragic.
Um...
How did you know?!
How could you tell?!
I could hear you.
What do we do, Miria?
She's a formidable opponent.
We are robbers!
Robbers!
She's laughing.
She's laughing, huh?
She was crying just a second ago.
It was an abrupt change, huh?
It's just, you two are so funny.
Then we have no choice.
No choice, huh?
Tell us all about your lover!
We'll be guidance counselors!
We'll give you good advice!
--We no tellum lie!
Well?
There were two lookouts.
Both of them had machine guns. And...
everyone who was
around us has disappeared.
Isaac-san, Miria-san,
Czes-kun, Mary-chan, Beriam-san...
They're all gone.
Oh, no...
They could have been taken somewhere.
We have to find them.
Nice, you and Nick take the roof
and head to the dining car.
Donny, you're with me.
Nice, I'll be coming back here for sure,
so don't overdo anything.
--Eh? Your brother?!
Yes.
My Big Brother Dallas is
really very kind at heart.
But lately, he's been acting a little violent,
and doesn't come home much.
She says he's been violent.
A juvenile delinquent, huh?
But why?
Our family, you see, is wealthy.
That's good, isn't it?
It is good!
No, it isn't.
Perhaps because my family
has been so blessed,
people only keep superficial company with us,
and what they say and what they think
are two separate things.
We saw a lot of things
that we didn't want to,
and that's probably why my brother...
That's a hard one, huh?
A real poser.
What should she do?
If that's the case,
what if you weren't rich anymore?
If that happened, you wouldn't
have to see that icky stuff anymore!
That was simple!
All right!
Excuse us a minute.
Excuse us.
--Keep excusing us.
What is the meaning of this, Miria?
It's a mystery, huh?
Is it the Rail Tracer?
It's a horror!
Where is Jacuzzi?
What do we do?
What if he's already been eaten?
I-It's all right, I tell you!
Since his body isn't here,
it could mean that he was
swallowed up by the monster.
That means he's still alive
inside its stomach.
He was swallowed whole, then?
Ah, thank goodness.
He was swallowed whole?!
Swallowed whole!
He's been gobbled up!
But, but, we don't know
where the guy who ate Jacuzzi is!
Yeah, that's okay.
As long as it's still aboard this train,
it means we're still together with Jacuzzi!
Mm-hmm... he still lives on in our hearts, huh?
Miria-san!
He really was a great guy... a great guy!
Are you all right?!
Jacuzzi, up in heaven, thank you.
Isaac-san!
Yeah, his voice, calling out to me like that...
is something I'll never be able to hear...
...again!
T-Thank goodness, you're both still safe!
W-We're glad you're safe, Jacuzzi!
You got out of its stomach, huh, Jacuzzi?
S-Stomach?
F-First thing we should do is
leave this room and go to the freight hold.
All right, let's go!
So that's it. I get you.
This train is now
"The Annals of the Three Kingdoms."
T-The Annals of the Three Kingdoms?
What are the Annals of the Three Kingdoms?
The Annals of the Three Kingdoms
is a famous history of China.
It's a story about these great samurai
who divide the land in three,
and feud with each other.
--Go on.
As I recall, they were
Cao Cao, Liu Bei, and Hokusai.
They are often likened to
the snake, the slug, and the frog, huh?
Slug?
So you see, Jacuzzi, you have to be Yoshitsune!
Be him!
M-Me, be someone that great?
You can do it!
I-I was planning to make sure
all the passengers are saved,
and to defeat the black suits
and the Russo guys.
But I'm not all that outstanding a person.
I make liquor,
and just yesterday, I killed three men.
--Killed?!
No! We're the ones who killed them!
It wasn't you, Jacuzzi!
It's the same difference.
We had eight of our friends
killed by the Russo Family.
--Killed?!
S-So I lost my temper, and
robbed 18 of the Russo Family's shops.
E-Eighteen?!
That must have taken all month!
N-No, one day!
--One day?!
Jacuzzi was ten times
more fearsome than usual.
And he also cried a hundred times
more than usual.
I was out to avenge them,
but it turned out...
...I overdid things, and
more people ended up killed.
So I'm not some outstanding person.
Don't let it bother you!
Cao Cao and Yoshitsune
killed thousands, millions,
billions, and trillions of people!
Even so, if those around them said
they were great guys,
then that makes them great guys!
Well, I mean, you know...
You've got to live in the moment!
That's right!
So you see, Jacuzzi, we're
telling you that you're a great guy.
Don't miss out on that wave!
Even if someone is against you,
you've just got to let
yourself go with the flow!
Still, still, in order to make those waves,
you need to have at least
one of the people around you
think that you're a great guy.
We know you are!
So, we're making waves for you!
--Okay?
Thanks.
--How.
We're going to take all of the unhappiness
out of your home for you.
Then, the whole family will enjoy tranquility.
I'm sure your brother
will regain his footing.
He'll be rehabilitated!
--Bye.
U-Um...
That's right. What's your name?
Eve...
Eve Genoard.
Eve, I'm sure that you will find happiness!
Happiness?
--Bye.
Where are you going?
Why, to look for the Rail Tracer, of course.
We're going to ask it to leave this train.
What if that doesn't work?
--We'll beat it up!
What if that still doesn't work?
--We'll run and hide!
Huh?
The monster is sure to be strong.
You'll be killed.
No problem!
If it comes down to it...
I'll use my hundred-shot pistols.
You don't even have
a single-shot gun, do you?
Indeed I don't.
But you know what
gunmen of old used to say...
Everyone has a gun in their heart.
Don't go dying, now!
--Bye.
What a couple of willful,
do-as-you-please folks.
Those two are
much bigger bad guys than I am.
Let's go do a little as we please.
If we're going to do this,
let's be the biggest bad guys on the train!
Yeah. Sounds like fun, Jacuzzi.
That's the end of that, huh?
The end of that.
You know, this car looks just like
the one that hit us, huh?
Just like it, huh?
Um, actually...
--Huh?
Nothing, never mind.
By the way, miss,
where are you taking these guys?
To the police.
I see. Well then, this is goodbye.
That's too bad.
Is something the matter?
The police might be a bit, you know...
They would arrest us, and all.
Well, if I had to say, we're kind of
on a journey to redeem ourselves.
We're doing good things,
to make up for all the bad things we've done.
I see. You two are strong, aren't you?
Oh, yes, I'm strong!
I'm strong!
I'm so afraid to face my sins, I can't stand it.
What do you mean, miss?
Have you done something bad?
I've...
I don't know what might have happened,
but you just got done saving us, right?!
So then, let's just call it even!
Mm-hmm! However many bad things
a bad person has done,
if they do one good thing,
everyone will think,
maybe they really are
a good person, after all!
--So, call it even!
--Okay?!
T-Thanks...
I have to go now.
Yeah, okay. Oh, I'm Isaac Dian.
I'm Miria Harvent.
I-I'm Ennis. No last name.
You don't say? No last name, huh?
That's unusual.
We'll remember it. Ennis. Ennis, right?
Bye, now, Ennis!
Bye, now!
Hey!
See you later!
We'll see you later!
Bye-bye!
See you later.
Eve...
Big Brother Dallas...
Sorry I've been away so long.
What do you say tonight,
I teach you some billiards or something,
for old time's sake?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, no!
We've been robbed!
I'll go see what it is.
Mm-hmm.
Stop that praying, will you?!
They say there's been a burglar.
I can't take this.
And here, I came home
for some spending money
because I'd inherited
something from Grandpa.
Big Brother...
You're a fool for believing in God!
Looking up at the starry sky
that goes on forever, we sing
a melody of a dream
we have of our limited eternity
The water of adoration,
overflowing in our hearts
will reach someone in the distant future
I believe so
Running through time prolonged,
our voices calling out will
someday become a great song
We can go on spinning our love
though it may still be such a tiny light now
Hey, Isaac, who is Claire?
What do you mean, Miria?
You don't even know that?
Let's see..."carries out the mission..."
What's the matter, Isaac?
Well, you know, with a name like
"Claire, " she must be a woman, right?
Incredible!