Late Night Show
Bones 10th anniversary project
Oh, hello.
I'm Shinigami-sama's son, Death the Kid, who'll be attending Shibusen starting today.
A healthy soul,
...resides in a healthy mind...
...and a healthy body.
I've folded the toilet paper.
Clean and perfect.
The picture frame is perfectly leveled with the ground.
The lengths of the right and left candles are the same.
Clean and perfect.
Perfect bilateral symmetry...
That is what I enjoy aesthetically.
It's time for school.
We're leaving. Liz, Patty.
Cut it out, Kid.
We're three hours late already.
This is a free fansub. Not for sale or rent.
Today is Kid's first day of school .
Will he be able to make a hundred friends?
No, I don't think...
That a hundred is possible...
And today's lesson is...
Some sort of a dissection experiment.
Again?
Excuse me...
But since Dr. Stein became our homeroom teacher, we've had nothing but dissection lessons...
I'm telling you...
We'll be investigating something different from the usual frogs and mice today.
This time, the thing you'll get to chop and crop up will be this:
Tokiko-san, a souvenir of the natural world.
"A souvenir of the natural world?!"
Excuse me...
...but that's an important bird on the brink of extinction...
It'd be a problem if it goes extinct before I dissect it.
This guy's impossible! He's completely crazy...
By the way, Soul and Black Star aren't present...
Did something happen?
They're slacking off, as usual.
Really, that combo of stupidity...
Sorry, Tsubaki, but I'll be Soul's Technician from now on.
If they want to be together so badly, they might as well become a team.
Right, Tsubaki-chan?
That is bad, Maka-chan!
Such a thing... never!!
What a shame...
I think everybody knows this already, but...
...there's a new student coming to class today.
The Rumored Freshman Makes His Appearance!
~Kid's
First Appearance At Shibusen,
An Experience To Remember?
The Rumored Freshman Makes His Appearance!
Kid's First Appearance At Shibusen, An Experience To Remember?
Today!
There is a guy that that my great self has to assassinate!
Right now, at Shibusen,
...there's one thing everyone's talking about!
Shinigami's son is going to enter it!
I can't forgive him for being more talked about than me!
Yeah, you're that kind of guy.
And when is that damn stray son going to get here?
We've been waiting for three hours!
Us sisters have always been brought up on the streets, but we're actually attending school now.
Isn't it great, Patty?
I'm so happy, you bastard!
Oh, it's wonderful.
Just what I expected of father's school.
It is perfectly symmetrical.
Are you guys the famous son's group?
Are you going to be the one to show us around?
You're new and already late and want me to show you around?
I guess it's pretty nice to have a father who shines like he had seven sources of light, huh?
What?
Seven light sources, you say?
It's not seven anymore! It's eight, eight!
Make it eight!
Huh?
Even if you cut the seven in two halves, it could never be symmetrical in the end!
But how about the eight?
If you cut it in halves or into quarters, it will always be perfectly symmetrical!
Just drop the seven.
Please, make it an eight.
I beg you.
Oi, oi, oi...
Oi, are you alright?
No, he's a lost case.
It doesn't matter who they are, I won't forgive anyone who tries to stand out more than me.
What is that? A monkey?
Shinigami's great son, I will assassinate you.
Oh... it really is a monkey.
And then tomorrow's rumors will be like this:
Oi, Kid, it looks like he's calling you.
"As I thought, Black Star... he is the star that surpassed God!"
Listen here!
Heaven's Wrath! I'm the superior ruler!
Tomorrow, a halo shall appear over me!
Seems like it couldn't handle my humungous existence.
It's no wonder my era has arrived.
How dare you wreck the symmetry...
Ah, now, now he's done it.
Bring it on!
Make sure to imprint my assassination techniques onto your eyes.
Assassination isn't supposed to be seen...
You disgust me!
If you fight with a Shinigami, I can't guarantee the safety of your soul.
Liz, Patty, transform.
Okay.
I haven't been in a fight since I lived on the streets.
If it's a fight you want, it's a fight you get. Let's go, Soul.
Man, you were the one who wanted a fight...
But...
If we're doing it, we won't lose.
Right!
It's the birth of the strongest combo!
The strength that managed to defeat Anubis.
The guts to stand out more than myself.
These two...
...were the ones that somehow managed to fight against Dr. Stein.
I can't let my guard down.
Let's go.
W-What?
Doctor! It seems Soul and Black Star are having a fight with someone.
Soul, you idiot, what are you doing?
Dr. Stein.
There's a rule that if two Technicians fight on school grounds, at least one staff member must be present.
I'm at the good part, but I guess I'll have to go.
Then, Soul and Black Star's partners, Maka and Tsubaki, please come with me.
The rest of you study by yourselves.
Damn it!
If we can't get close, this won't end!
Oh, you want a close range fight?
Fine by me!
Don't take me lightly!
W-What?
Crap!
Ah... for some reason, I don't want to stand up ever again.
Woah! It friggin' hurts!
We're different from normal guns that just shoot bullets.
We condense our Technician's soul wavelength and shoot that out.
Damn...
He's not fighting seriously.
Oh dear... Well, they chose the wrong guy to mess around with.
Dr. Stein, is the boy holding the guns the one everyone's been talking about?
Yes, Shinigami-sama's son, Death the Kid-kun.
He wanted to come here, so he joined this class.
But he is stronger than other people here.
Black Star...
Sorry, Tsubaki, but I'll be Soul's Technician from today on.
Tsubaki-chan?
Huh?
Is something wrong?
No, nothing at all.
Well then, Maka-san, who has been able to see souls since yesterday...
Y-Yes?
Shall I have you take a special lesson?
Eh, ok.
Hey, hey you don't have to worry so much, it's just a simple question.
Do the Kid-kun and Twin Demon guns over there fighting...
...have their soul wavelengths perfectly in sync?
Yes.
Usually, matching your soul wavelength with two weapons is an extremely difficult task,
...but they're very stable.
They respect each other...
No, that might be wrong.
Admiration? Is that it?
Wonderful, that is correct.
Twin Demon guns, the Thompson sisters.
Since they were brought up on the street, they admire a dignified soul like Kid-kun's.
And Kid-kun for his side, too.
He greatly admires the magnanimous and positive souls of the Thompson sisters that differ from his sensitive personality.
They're a very good team.
Aren't they?
If you compare that with that combo of stupidity on the other hand...
Let's do that, friend.
That, right?
"That?"
Listen and be amazed, see it and tremble!
Don't you mean laugh?
We'll show you the power of our friendship!
That's right.
An infinity of power that you'd never expect!
What?
Let's go.
Yeah.
Transform!
Cool!
Let's take this seriously, people.
Come! Soul!
Friendship!
Fusion!
What are you trying to do catching me with your head?!
Damn it!!
C'mon, get a grip!
What the hell is this?!
You're friggin' heavy!
I shouldn't be...
Maka swings me around fine.
This is a typical situation when your souls' wavelengths aren't in sync.
So it is.
You damn broken scythe bastard!
What are you trying to do, driving your soul wavelength into me?!
Ah, sorry...
That won't work.
It's almost as if they're not picking up on their enemy's wavelength.
That's because a Weapon Technician and his weapon,
...must face each other before fighting an enemy.
It's over for us... isn't it?
Eh?!
W-What do you mean, Soul?
If I keep staying by your side...
I think I'm gonna start to hate you.
Huh?
Oi... can I shoot?
Let's wait for them. It's interesting.
I see...
But we're...
Even if we're apart, we'll still be friends, right?
You idiot!
Of course we will be!
Soul!
Black Star!
They're complete idiots.
Ah, I'm sorry, my hand slipped.
However, it's a fight we've accepted!
Yeah!
We can't step back until we've won!
Come!
I'll end it for you with the next attack.
I'll drive my wavelength into you, too!!
Black Star, who's good in close combat, is being toyed with...
What could Soul, the weapon, do against a guy like that?
Your speed and cut moves are too easy.
You bastard!
What?!
The kick was a feint!
You're mine!
That brat... I really want to kill him.
This is completely hopeless.
I'll show you the power of a Shinigami.
Soul Resonance!
What? His soul just swelled up.
He's going seriously now.
Those who can see the souls
C'mon! We can take anything!!
I am what God is!
Those who can't see the souls
Execution mode complete.
Oi.
Doesn't that look dangerous?
You brat! You've got one ultimate wedgie waitin' for ya!!
Resonance rate stable.
Noise 0.3%.
Charging soul wavelength into the black needles complete.
Feed back in 4...
3...
2...
1!
We're ready.
Death Cannon!
Oi, this is bad! Real bad!
Are you kidding me?!
That sorta thing will never work on me!
Black Star!
Ah, what are they doing?
A complete loss.
However...
Should I say it's because he's Shinigami-sama's son...
The latent power he has is completely different from the power of other Technicians.
It's like he was showing us the difference in level.
Shinigami-sama's son...
Ah, I want to study him...
Oh dear...
He won't get over this one.
Is something wrong?
It seems like he was cut.
What was?
Hm, that was...
Hm?
You know Soul's last attack?
It seems like his hair was slightly cut when that happened.
And after the explosion Kid-kun realized this...
...and said something like the balance had been destroyed or the symmetry wasn't right,
...spat out blood and collapsed.
That would mean it's our rebounded victory.
That's right! I have finally surpassed God!
Oh, halo, you can appear over me!!
Black Star, are you all right?
How was I, Tsubaki? Me, who has surpassed God?
Uh... yeah, you're amazing.
Yo.
Hm?
Ah...
Don't fight so lamely.
Isn't that what you always say to me?
I guess I wasn't cool just there.
I'm begging you, don't push yourself.
There's nothing I need to push myself to do!
Why that? Because I'm the man who surpassed God!
I suppose Tsubaki-chan's the only one for Black Star.
Yeah, it seems so.
Hey.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Let's do this in a cool way!
Alright!
Hi! Hey! Hello!
Hello!
I'm here because it's my son's first day at school.
Unbelievable, Kid, you're quite a handful!
Now that I think about it...
I wonder what kind of soul Shinigami-sama's is.
Let's check it out.
Huh?
I can't see it!
Well then, everybody, I'll be taking Kid home for today.
Bye!
Okay, see you later!
What is the meaning of this?
His son, Kid-kun, has a soul and I could clearly see it.
Oi, Maka!
What are you doing, standing there dazing?
Let's go back.
Yeah.
Could Shinigami-sama really not have a soul?
Well, whatever.
Assassination, the essentials of.
Ann will teach you the Essentials of Assassination.
You're the main center of attention here?!
Start off with the body!
Take that, take that, take that!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
She's good. She focuses her attack on the body and attracts the opponent's attention below.
Take that, take that, take that!
Not only that, she's exactly hitting the vital from accurate angles.
Finish!
Assassination Complete
Kid, who the hell are you?!
The other side of love
How could you when you had me?!
You don't understand! It's not what you think-
No excuse!
Take that, take that, take that!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
It's not what you think, Ann! I'm the one at fault not him-
Take that, take that, take that!
Please Angela, listen to what I'm saying!
Take that, take that, take that, take that!
Please! The one I love is you, Ann!!
Finish!
Assassination Complete
Like who the hell are you?!
The Black Blood
of Terror
~There's a
weapon inside of Chrona?~
After Film Art Museum Number 5, "Director Igarashi."
Artist: Voice Actress (for Maka) Omigawa Chiaki.