A healthy soul...
...resides in a healthy mind...
...and in a healthy body.
I'll leave this to you.
Be careful, don't overdo it.
Yeah.
If it gets dangerous, call for me.
For any of my friends, I'd come to help.
Geez. I got it, so hurry up and go on!
Let's do it, Maka.
Yeah.
Tsubaki, we're catching up with Kid and the others.
Yes.
I won't let you...
Speed Star!
See ya, Devil Sword!
That's fine.
He was the easiest to hold down, physically.
Won't you die?
I won't let you!
You're in my way.
Try to finish it!
Rather than attacks that focus on her point of balance,
...a full powered attack is more effective!
For now, what I have to do is hold her down,
...and gather all my power into my left side!
Tough.
It feels like I'm punching lead.
Chrona, forget about the running boy!
Focus on the girl in front of us.
Get blown away, idiot!
This is absurd...
Suddenly, I'm a mess.
I don't know how to deal with that weak girl...
Kill her.
Yeah...
Even though we landed the first attack,
...she's getting more lively.
Do we have any prospects of victory?
I mean, of course there are some, right?
Nope.
Not really.
You've got some nice brains but you're really dumb, huh?
You're the best!
Really, you're a "cool" partner!
Well, it'll work out.
We've got to do it somehow, right?
Cut the crap!
There's no such as "doing it somehow!"
Have you forgotten?
You can't put a scratch on Chrona!
It's damn annoying!
Eating a small fry's soul like yours won't even leave a taste.
That star brat from before looked much more delicious!
How dare you, you insolent, lowly brat with no sex appeal...
I'm gonna torment you! That's all that's left to do!
I did it.
You finally acknowledged me, heh?
When we battled before, you saw me as no more than a meal, right?
Right now, you see me a person.
Hence, I've done it!
And as for the Technician...
You're always acting timid...
Face me properly!
Leave me alone!
I don't get it!
Even though you're so weak...
You'll get cut up again.
Why should I get serious about beating you up?
Cut it out...
If I'm looked at with such focused eyes,
...I can't make eye contact.
I may certainly be weaker than you...
But I have no intention to lose.
After all...
When it comes to souls I can't lose!
That's a bad joke at best!
A sore loser's voice doesn't reach anywhere.
What was that? Did I hit a nerve?
I am the Scythe Technician, Maka.
Your name?
Devil Sword user, Chrona.
It's a duel then, Chrona.
What... you can make such a nice expression.
Maka...
That is the name of the person standing in front of me?
Ah, no...
Uhm, no this is...
Does a woman need a reason for sneezing, you idiot?!
With that said, let's do it over.
Stein, this is...
Maka is ignoring her orders and fighting the Devil Sword.
What?
It seems your cute little daughter has chosen death...
My daughter isn't that weak.
Fool of a father...
Black Blood's Resonance War!
The Small Soul's Large Struggle To Oppose Fear?
Oi, Maka! What are you doing, firing up our opponent?
Right?
Here I go.
She's coming, Maka!
Bloody Slicer!
The hardened black blood has liquefied?
Bloody Needle!
She's really a troublesome one.
Ragnarok...
Shut it!
Scream Resonance.
Why? Why target the souls of innocent people and revive the Kishin?
Because I'm afraid...
If I become stronger, I'll know how to deal with a lot of things.
If I don't become a Kishin, Medusa-sama will abandon me.
If I don't become strong, everything will be full of scary things!
Screech Alpha!
Come at me with everything you got!
Even though I'm weak and scared, I'll crush it down!
Chrona!
One question.
You abducted Devil Sword kid from somewhere.
By using that Devil Sword you tried to create a Kishin, right?
But still, why are you trying to resurrect Kishin?
You're disappointed by a Devil Sword that shows no sign of turning into a Kishin.
That's why you're taking this huge risk by using the black blood and aiming to revive the Kishin.
Once she becomes of no use what do you intend to do with her?
Your experience was a failure.
That's the best news of this year!
What is it?
Did I say something funny?
Really, such a cheeky boy.
This might hit you as a failure, Dr. Stein,
...but my research lies entirely on the black blood.
One more thing...
You're wrong about one thing.
That child wasn't abducted.
Chrona is my legitimate child.
Parfait...
Even though you're better off not standing...
Why do you keep trying to hit me?
Even though you're this weak...
Cut it off.
I don't know how to deal with that.
She's using blood from her injury again.
Cutting her won't work.
Our cuts will turn into a disadvantage.
But there's one thing we can do.
Yeah, you're right...
Let's do this, Maka!
Soul Resonance!
Hey, Chrona!
Scream Resonance.
I'm gonna raise the resonance!
This resonance response...
So, it's started?
Witch Hunting!
Screech Gamma!
Oi, Stein! What's going on?
The black blood is on the move.
Soul Eater Episode 20.
"Namari" misspelled.
"Kishin" misspelled.
"Taikaku" misspelled, "kinryoku" misspelled.
"Maken" misspelled.
"Kiritsu" misspelled, "kid demon" wrong.
"Sendou" misspelled.
Hexagonal Hunting!
U-Shaped Hunting!
What... that's it?
Eh?
The Witch Hunting was blocked with magic?
With a such a weak body why does she have such strength?
This case has nothing to do with physical constitution.
The black blood flowing in her veins...
Ragnarok takes care of Chrona's moves supporting her with physical power.
Now it's my turn, right?
Screech Gamma!
Geez! No!
No! No! No!
No!
Geez! Die already, you weapon!
Soul!
Shut up! You just stay back!
But at this rate you'll...
Maka, don't get any dumb thoughts!
Keep guarding like that!
Soul, you should stop with the boring talk, too...
Cut the crap and leave it to us.
We'll make you stronger.
Are you alright, Soul?
Yeah.
How come...?
I was almost there.
I wasn't going to lose to the Devil Sword.
That's how I felt.
I thought I had gotten a hold on Chrona's wavelength but still...
This can't go on.
Dammit.
Are you afraid?
You look like him.
Even now, I still don't know how to deal with it.
You look like the little one from that time...
Now, kill it, Chrona.
I can't do it!
I don't know how to deal with it!
You disobedient girl, please stay out of my sight.
As punishment, I won't let you out of this room for a few days.
No!
This is too dark! I can't see anything!
And the two of us alone in this room is...
It's dark and I don't know how to deal with it...
Why you... Chrona! Dammit!
Ragnarok?
If you don't behave, I too will get locked!
No! Stop it!
Stop pulling my nose!
It hurts! It stings!
You're hurting my nose!
It's dark and I can't see and it hurts and it stings!
It's your fault!
Damn you! Damn you!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
It really...
Damn you! Damn you!
Stop! It hurts!
Now, come out.
It's horrible! Ragnarok beat me up!
It hurts! I hate it! Make him stop!
Now, come. We're continuing the other day's task.
You're going to kill it.
I can't...
I can't do something like that.
Vector Plate.
Stay out of my sight for a while longer.
Why you... Chrona! Dammit!
Damn you! Damn you!
Stop! It hurts!
Stop, stop, stop it!
With this, how many times has it been?
It's unproductive...
How many times do we have to repeat this until you're satisfied?
Look...
My blood is black.
Bye, bye, little one.
Soul.
Oi, Soul!
Maka...
If this goes on you'll be done for.
Just leave it to us...
Get rid of your reason.
We'll make you stronger.
Never.
Hand over the power.
But...
I won't give up my rationality.
What?
That way you can't win to the Devil Sword's power.
Just leave it to us.
If you think you can become stronger without losing your reason, you're way off!
We've never heard such a great story before.
I understand "fear," so I fight it.
I understand "order," so I follow it.
Even though I think this way, it's a fine power.
Besides, this isn't a problem of the weapon alone.
If we resonate any deeper it might influence Maka, right?
Stop messing around, damn brat!
Enough with giving too much attention to small things!
Suddenly trying to tap into the Sun, what's wrong with you?!
You want me to slap you once, eh?!
If you can't handle fear, then what of your life?!
You listening?!
Shut yer trap!
You're like the stuff I crap out!
Stop talking to me all the time, crap doesn't talk!
Right?!
You keep quiet and guide me!
Whether I follow your advice or not... is my own decision!!
How am I supposed to stay quiet and guide you?
Raise your finger or whatever, you crappy bastard.
Okay, okay.
Shall we cool down a little?
We want to move forward as much as you do.
If we keep talking like this, we'll both remain on a standstill.
Right?
Yeah.
There's someone we've invited here today.
Come on in!
Here?
Now, now, we're not going anywhere, so let democracy decide this.
Maka?
I heard most of it.
Why are you here?
Wasn't this like my exclusive session thing?
Right now you're both resonating...
...so having your hearts connected is pretty much a given, no?
Oi, demon!
Isn't this something you made that just looks like Maka?
What a mood wrecking guy...
This place pretty much works the way you want.
We can't go that far...
Maka... Chop!
It's Maka, alright.
Now then.
Let's wash away our fear.
Take the lead.
I don't know how to do this...
Do it however you want.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Why did you come here?
Did you hear the demon's voice, too?
I don't know...
But now that I think of it...
I might have heard it the time we fought the Devil Eye Wolf.
Yeah, we certainly entered you.
But we were erased right away.
Don't know why, though...
If so, you shouldn't be here.
And was just able to make him disappear.
This time it might not disappear...
Hey, if we're matching our wavelengths like this...
...you can understand what I'm thinking, right?
You...
Yes.
You can't mean...
Do you intend to use the black blood and fall into the same madness as Chrona?
I knew it, you're upset...
I thought this when Witch Hunting was shattered...
If I had the same power as the Devil Sword, I might be able to grasp something.
Chrona's...
I might be able to grasp Chrona's wavelength.
No way...
For a mere whim that's too dangerous!
You may not be able to get your reason back.
Yeah.
No, I'm sorry. This is my conviction!
There's no guarantee of you returning...
But it's worth the try, isn't it?
Ok, let's do it.
We'll do it the way you like.
No matter how messed up you become,
...as your weapon, I'll bring you back.
Ouch!
Ah, sorry.
Lead me properly, okay?
Yeah, leave it to me...
That's the way.
It sure flew!
She's being dragged into my madness.
Maka, I'll definitely won't let you go, okay?
The fools...
We are the ones taking the lead.
That's the end of this week's broadcast.
The late show that's becoming more and more arrogant...
Just where will we end up?
At the least, I have no idea.
Director, if you don't take some time off you'll get broken.
Next week, on Soul Eater's late show:
Maka's World Tour.
Don't say you won't promise to watch.
I'll take your soul!