Late Night Show
Bones 10th anniversary project
A healthy soul...
...resides in a healthy mind...
...and a healthy body.
The camellia flower...
...the flower with no scent.
Also, while you don't even pay attention... it quietly blossoms.
It also whithers in a miserable way...
...and it leaves an unpleasant feeling.
Tsubaki, what do you want to play?
"Kemari" was A type of football played by courtiers in ancient Japan.
I want to play Kemari.
"Tsubaki" is camellia in Japanese.
I am Tsubaki...
...the flower with no scent.
This is a free fansub. Not for sale or rent.
It's the Autumn of Art!...... Not!
There's about 3 months until Autumn...
This is sudden, but we'll do art!
Funny Haikus!
We'll hold a funny Haiku competition !
The Demon Blade Masamune...
At this rate, he too will become a Kishin...
Do you really want to do this?
It'll be a hard battle...
I will stop the Demon Blade Masamune with my own hands.
What about Black Star?
I haven't told him everything yet...
But, he said he'll put the fate of his soul in my hands.
Is that so?
You've got a good partner, don't you?
Yes!
Demon Blade
Masamune
~Break
through the dependent spirit.
A heart that sings to the rain?~
Demon Blade Masamune!
Break Through The Dependent Spirit.
A Heart That Sings To The Rain?
Something's come up
Class Canceled
Geez...
What is Dr. Stein doing?
He's not on strike, is he?
What's wrong with that?
It's been a while since we had a cool morning.
And the energetic idiot ain't here either.
You mean Black Star?
Now that you mention it, Tsubaki-chan, too...
Maka, haven't you heard?
Huh, what?
We heard it earlier at the teacher's lounge.
The teachers were saying...
...that Black Star and Tsubaki...
Working on it
...went to get a Demon Blade's soul.
A Demon Blade?
I wonder if it'll work out okay...
A Demon Blade... seems to be close to turning into a Kishin.
What's up with this village?
This is Hari, the Shin Village.
Why would a poor village like this become a Demon Blade's target?
I don't know.
It seems the Demon Blade only targets scared souls, so...
You know, Black Star...
There is something I haven't yet mentioned about the Demon Blade...
Huh?
Woah!
What's that?
Black Star!
Black Star, on stage!
Don't break it.
A star like me has come to this stinkin' hick town!
Now, Black Star!
Hey, punk!
Huh?
Stepping on this...
...village's guardian deity... what's the meaning of this?
Geezer, are you the Demon Blade?
Black Star...
Aiming for old men out of the blue?
City folk sure are scary...
Don't be violent to the elderly...
What the heck're ya sayin'?
Day or night, I'm still good at it!
There, you see? There's no doubt he's the one!
There's no mistake he's not the one...
What's up?
A guest of grandpa's?
Are you the Demon Blade?
It's not him either!
My... a friend of Ryoku's?
Could it be... you?
Don't pick fights with everyone!
What's up with that kid?
Doesn't she look suspicious?
If it has come to this,
...you'll be done in by the great me!
You can't do that, Black Star! Calm down!
What do you want from this village?
Have you come back to kill us?
That tattoo on your shoulder...
"Hoshizoku" can be translated to Star Clan.
Are you a survivor from the Hoshizoku?
Hoshizoku?
Did he say Hoshizoku?
Why did he come here?
Money?
You from Hoshizoku do anything for money, right?
Take that and leave right away!
This village, too?
Crap!
Dammit... it's started to pour.
Unlike Maka, I can't sense Soul Feedback...
If I'm to find the Demon Blade's presence, I can only rely on my five senses...
But in this rain, you know...
My senses are dull.
Are you wondering about earlier?
No...
It's not like that...
I don't like telling long stories.
Yes.
I'll stop looking like I want to hear about it.
It's already happened before, right?
An old man's attacked out of the blue when he saw this tattoo, right?
Yes.
My clan is called "Hoshizoku," ya know?
And apparently, it was...
...a well known mercenary clan that did anything for money.
They murdered loads of people...
Later on, seeking power, they even laid their hands on human souls.
I'm the last surviving member of the Hoshizoku clan.
I didn't know...
Now, that clan is?
Thirteen years ago, all their souls were taken... by Shibusen.
I was still a baby, so...
...I just got taken in by Shibusen.
And that's it!
Do you despise Shibusen, Black Star?
Not really...
We're talking about when I was still just a lil' star.
Both my mom and dad crossed the line...
...and got their souls taken.
That's all there's to it.
Still... being hated because of that...
I don't like it...
Are you an idiot?
Didn't I stand out because of that?
You know, Black Star...
...there's something I haven't talked about yet...
You don't have to push yourself.
I don't know what your relation with the Demon Blade is, but...
He's an enemy we have to defeat, right?
If that's so, I'll fight, too.
When you feel like telling it to me,
...then I'll listen.
Ok.
The rain's getting heavier.
I doth think.
Shalt I sleep? Shalt I play?
Nay.
I shalt eat!
Shinigami-sama!
Why did you let those two go?
C-C-C-Calm down!
Or rather, who called you?
The Academy of Shinigami Weapons Wielders...
School Regulations code 118:
..."Students may come in for emergency situations," is what it says.
Is that so?
The one called Demon Blade, what kind of guy is he, father?
Kid, you too?
Don't tell me he's a guy like that Devil Sword we met...
Devil Sword?
There's no witch controlling the Demon Blade.
On the contrary, because he's alone, he's become evil...
He uses the fear in a person's heart as a way in.
He lays hand on the souls for himself...
...manipulates the body...
...and eats its soul.
At this rate, he too will become a Kishin.
That Hoshizoku guy... what has he come here for?
With this sickle I won't be much of an opponent...
No... if it's now I can have my revenge.
Because of them, mom and dad...
I doth think...
In thou I shalt be...
Thou I shalt eat.
Who are you?
I doth believe... there's seemeth to be fear in you...
What are you saying all of a sudden?
It's not like I'm...
I wonder...
As long as you have power...
...your fear...
...will be wiped.
Do you want it?
Honorable
Mention
I am cowardly...
...but still was your average... prankster in the past.
...but still was your average... prankster in the past.
L
i
z
Brief review:
I think this
very well
conveys Liz's
position in Shibusen.
I am cowardly...
...but still was your average... prankster in the past.
The Chosen
If even a bit...
...of symmetry is lost, then... it becomes deadly.
...of symmetry is lost, then... it becomes deadly.
K
i
d
Brief review:
This is an
elegant piece that holds
balance and sings
in an avant-garde matter.
If even a bit...
...of symmetry is lost, then... it becomes deadly.
Oh, Ryoku, you've been here...
I brought things we can use as weapons for the other folks.
Hari was built twenty-three years ago and no thief has been able to sneak inside.
What? Don't worry about a thing...
I won't let it turn out like the past.
After all, I'm still good to go at it!
Isn't that a Japanese sword?
Why is there something like that in our village?
Ryoku, are you alright?
He's out!
Let's go!
Yes.
Ryoku, what's wrong?
Ryoku?
Nay!
I'm the Demon Blade Masamune.
Thy soul I shalt... eat!
Are you the Demon Blade?
What's that?
He's the damn brat from earlier, isn't he?
What the hell is this?
One of the Demon Blade's techniques... Soul Possession.
Soul Possession?
What's that?
Normally, both Technician and weapon synchronize their souls wavelengths, right?
However, the Demon Blade possesses its wielder, manipulates him...
...and finally... he eats its soul.
That's the Demon Blade...
...the blade that was once so beautiful...
...has such a dull color.
Oh, it's you?
Tsubaki, what should I do?
Even if it's the Demon Blade, he shouldn't be able to control two wavelengths.
If the boy were to receive Black Star's wavelength,
...the Demon Blade should release the boy.
I will take it up from there.
'Kay!
I just have to hit him with a soul wavelength, right?
Yes.
I entered Shibusen to hunt down the Demon Blade.
But, I might have been just using you, Black Star.
Tsubaki,
...I know very well... that you don't think that!
A weapon and a Technician...
...are supposed to help each other, right?
You can still...
...depend a great deal on me.
Yes.
Shadow Puppet.
Black Star!
What's that?
The shadow?
The Demon Blade can even control the person's shadow?
Go! Puppet!
Two versus one, huh?
We'll stir things up with speed Tsubaki!
Ninja Blade mode!
Yes!
Speed Star!
Hah, did you see that?
My speed!
Can't you see me?
You can't see me!
I'm the man who already went to the next era!
While you, if you even get a glimpse of my ass...
...you'll be very lucky!
Speed Star wasn't made for rainy days, when it's slippery.
If the era can't keep up with me...
Does this mean I was born too early?
Speed Star...
...is so deep, man...
Bastard!
I don't have time to avoid his attacks...
...and drive the wavelengths together.
I've gotta do something!
Playtime... is over!
That stance...
Be careful! A swift lunge is coming!
Die...
Puppet Strike!
I see it all.
Okay!
Branch Attack!
Not yet...
Dammit!
This ain't my era!
Come!
Come, my era!
Tsubaki, Chain-Scythe mode!
Yes!
Come!
Here it is!
Let's do it, Tsubaki!
Yes!
Soul Resonance!
Shield Star!
Cut my flesh and I will have your bones...
Getting impatient for a finishing blow, he carelessly dived right in...
...into Black Star's domain!
Shadow!
Your era is gone!
The air fight is my era for sure.
And its name is...
...My Time!
Now, Tsubaki!
Yes.
Thank you, Black Star.
I'm off.
Interesting...
You intend to come inside me?
From here on, it's my battle.
I will stop the Demon Blade.
What happened?
Tsubaki entered the Demon Blade.
Why Tsubaki-chan?
We have to stop them, right now!
Without a Technician, how's a weapon to fight?
You see...
...it's inside a soul, so whatever happens is not surprising.
Besides that,
...the only who can stop the Demon Sword is Tsubaki-chan.
Tsubaki...
...make sure you return.
This is inside the Demon Blade.
Where is he?
To perform a Soul Possession, he's supposed to aim for my soul.
Soul Possession?
Nay...
I shall kill and eat your soul as it is now.
Welcome...
...Tsubaki.
Big brother.
En guarde!
Golden Prize
I will let you taste...
...a piece of the Maka-chop... if you flip my skirt.
...a piece of the Maka-chop... if you flip my skirt.
M
a
k
Brief review:
She honestly expresses
her feelings in this piece.
We should all be
strong enough to overcome
hurdles in this
already stressful world.
I will let you taste...
...a piece of the Maka-chop... if you flip my skirt.
Announcing the first prize
winner after this!
...a piece of the Maka-chop... if you flip my skirt.
Big Prize
If you are a man...
...go to the noon cabaret, "Chupa Cabras."
...go to the noon cabaret, "Chupa Cabras."
Brief review:
A unanimously first
prize piece;
it's something
any man can dream of
......
If you are a man...
...go to the noon cabaret, "Chupa Cabras."
Wait, what's with this flow?!
Isn't that too
much of a
dirty joke?!
Oi, you guys...
Can't you come up with jokes that aren't dirty?
Great person, come out!
Close both of your eyes,
...and behold with your mind's eye... Blair taking a bath.
...and behold with your mind's eye... Blair taking a bath.
Close both your eyes,
Azuma.
Hey!
A TV member said a dirty joke, too...
The camellia
flower
~What lies
Beyond The Sadness?~
The Camellia Flower,
What Lies Beyond The Sadness?
The blood remains...
After-film art museum, number 9.
Black Star's pot?
By Shibata Aya, Bones Publicity Division.