Late Night Show
Bones 10th anniversary project
A healthy soul...
...resides in a healthy mind...
...and in a healthy body.
I've brought it.
With this, you'll be removing one of the snakes you left in my body, right?
That's right.
Well done, Eruka.
Finally...
Free, how's the Evil Eye?
It's perfect.
As it is, I'll be able to produce an Independent Cube.
Mabaa-sama's specialized on spatial magic.
Tonight, your Evil Eye will be necessary.
Eruka and I will give you magical support.
I'm counting on you.
Yeah...
Leave it to me...
Now... the time draws near...
I've longed for this day.
This is a free fansub. Not for sale or rent.
This is out of the blue but do you like Yakiniku?
Today is the Big Yakiniku Special.
Meat Meat Meat Meat Meat Vegetables.
It's the Yakiniku's Golden Ratio.
Chef!!
This is good meat!
If you don't hurry, it'll start without us...
You were the one who took so long to prepare, though.
Hey Soul, I'm gonna stuff myself full!
He's so sloppy.
Welcome!
Look at you... all dressed up and stuff...
Kid-kun, what's wrong? You don't seem well...
Oh, no. Excuse me.
I'm starving...
Sloppy, huh?
Anyway, everyone, it's good you came.
After all, tonight is to celebrate the founding of Shibusen.
The Nightmare Before
The Festival
~And So, The Curtain Rises?~
The Nightmare Before The Festival:
And So, The Curtain Rises?
Now, come inside...
There will be a greeting from father shortly.
I'm starving.
What father said... could it be true?
Something like that here in Shibusen?
Yo!
Hey! Greetz!
Thanks! Thanks! Hey!
Thanks for the support!
It's Shinigami-sama!
Shinigami-sama!
Well...
Having said this, my greeting is over.
It's really just a greeting, huh?
Father, it was too little casual...
Then I too thank you for...
...despite your tight schedules, finding the time to attend to this Shibusen founding party.
With your permission I, Shinigami-sama's son, Death The Kid, will give you a welcoming speech too.
He's doing it so neatly...
As it stands, Shibusen protects the peace of the world by...
It's me!
It's my highness!
It's the one and only Black Star!
All of this is... you see?
Make sure this sinks in:
The only one who can add "-sama" to his name is none other than me!
How should I put this?
It's annoying and lame!
What're you doing?
Being a nuisance while I'm speaking!
The nuisance is you!
Fool! Blockhead!
I wanted to do a proper greeting...
It's useless... Just let me die...
Geez...
Whose festival do you think this is?
At the very least, it isn't yours...
Well, it seems it's already becoming a party...
There's a band too, so don't hold back on the dancing.
Just be yourselves!
Yes!
He's so embarrassing...
Raise your legs to a 60 degree angle!
Do it diligently!
Aye!
Embarrassing...
This kind of stuff doesn't suit me well...
Soul...
Maka?
We don't get to eat this every day... aren't you going to try it?
Standing in lines for the food is a pain...
...and eating while standing isn't relaxing...
It's a waste!
And it's this delicious...
Then gimme that plate.
Nah!
Stingy...
Is Soul-kun still having those strange dreams about the demon?
He seemed a bit troubled, so...
Hey, Soul...
Is there anything troubling you?
Huh?
What's that, out of the blue?
He came begging me for advice.
If you'd like, I can give you some advice.
There's really nothing so...
What?
It may be annoying if I'm too persistent...
Am I really that unreliable as a partner?
What's up with that, now of all times?
What?! Stupid Soul! Idiot Soul!
Okay, want to dance?
No way... it's too troublesome...
Why not? You're good at this stuff, right?
Take the lead.
Dancing is like matching wavelengths, so it's okay.
Hold it right there!
Dance with papa!
No way.
Perfect, isn't it?
Fathers and daughters should be close.
Go on and dance!
W-Wait!
As Soul-kun said!
Now, Maka...
Soul, keep an eye on my food!
Keep an eye, heh?
She's a real glutton...
Huh?
Maka doesn't like raw fish...
So why did she bring salmon?
Weird girl...
Oh...
I see.
Silly, isn't she...
She didn't have to bother, but still...
Thanks...
...for the food.
Medusa,
...we've entered Death City.
What should we do?
Wait for my signal at the designated place with Free.
Also, did you get their support?
As planned.
Currently, Chrona, or should I say Ragnarok, went to get them.
Is that so...?
Good work.
Well hello there, Medusa-sensei.
Having fun?
Doctor Stein.
My...
Don't scare me.
This guy again?
Cheers! Cheers! How many ... are there?
Doctor Stein?
Ah, I'm completely drunk!
I drank too much champagne!
Is he for real? I can't read him...
How about it? Let's dance!
Since you dressed up and all!
Now, now!
You're kidding, right?
Maka, do you remember?
On your kindergarten graduation day, you stood on papa's feet and danced...
After that I danced with mama...
It was so much fun...
The one you danced with wasn't mama...
It was Sara-chan's mama right?
Crap!
Was that so?
As expected from Maka, remembering it so well...
Well anyway, now I'm dancing with you again.
It will be a good memory.
From now on, I'm going to become a great papa, right?
Impossible!
What am I doing?
I can't let Eruka and the others see this...
Medusa-sensei?
Sid-sensei hasn't returned...
Do you know anything about that?
Is everything alright?
I don't know anything...
Is that so?
He went off to someone's laboratory.
Uhm...
Whose laboratory was it again?
Right, right!
It was yours.
I have no clue about what you're talking about...
A dangerous witch such as yourself... what business could she have at Shibusen?
You seem a bit drunk... should we get you some water?
I'm not drunk...
From the beginning.
You seem to be interested in Kishin.
I don't believe you infiltrated Shibusen just to investigate weapons and Technicians...
You know about it right?
Witch Medusa...
That below Shibusen, a Kishin sleeps...
Youngster...
If Shinigami weren't here, I'd kill you on the spot.
I wanna dissect you!
No need to hold back.
How about releasing the Protect?
That's right...
My aim is the resurrection of Kishin.
And for that, the black blood...
But why?
Kishin's power surpasses human comprehension...
Even evolution itself, so to speak.
Both Shinigami and Shibusen kept an eye on and protected the Earth through force...
Maintaining the status quo...
That would be the best description of Shibusen's work.
But, the times are changing.
Given that, heading towards unheard progress is obvious, right?
That's only natural...
Doctor Stein...
Whether you do or you don't, everything's the same...
This revolving world... is that what you long for?
Being a researcher like me, you know what I mean...
So?
Won't you join me?
Stein!
Hurry!
Get everyone out of here!
Sid-sensei?
Oi?
Are you alright?
Yeah, somehow...
There was a surprise attack from the enemy.
I dove underground when the explosion took place but...
It's as you see...
Crap!
Anyway, get away from here!
It's a trap.
Today, Shinigami-sama left the mirror and everybody at Shibusen gathered here...
They've waited for this day!
Medusa!
Free! The Barrier!
Trap them all in!
Got it.
Soul Protect... release!
This response...
Wolf, wolves...
Wolf, wolves!
Interference will not be allowed.
Once inside this magic box...
...none shall leave!
Eruka, we're maintaining the place where the box will materialize.
Ribbit, ribbit.
Subtraction magic... Magic Calculation!
T-This is...
So it's started...
Nygus, you can do it, right?
Soul Resonance...
Yeah!
At least you guys...
Casting location confirmed.
Spatial Magic!
Independent Cube!
What's this?
The room...
Materializing the key!
Please make it in time!
Set!
What's going on?
What the hell is going on?
The space is distorting.
This is bad...
We're being trapped in!
Let's do it!
Compulsive Burial!
Graves appearing from the floor?
Lock!
Sid!
I'm counting on you...
Protect Shibusen.
The time limit is one hour.
It won't last any longer...
Okay...
Until Shinigami leaves...
We've got no time to loiter around!
Where's Chrona?
I've brought them.
The Mizune family...
Mizune!
I lied and said that the witch Mizune was killed by Shibusen to get their cooperation...
...it breaks my heart.
I'm sorry, Mizune.
Mizune, that's the spirit!
I leave the rest to you.
Destroy Death City.
Eruka, my case...
Leave it to me.
We're close.
We'll revive Kishin.
Ouch!
We're the only group of Technicians left?
That's just not right...
Witches souls' responses...
One... two...
Eight of them?
And even the Devil Sword.
What's going on in Death City?
It's an emergency situation.
Everyone, calm down and listen.
Below Shibusen, the source of madness, the first Kishin lies asleep.
And as we speak, the one who infiltrated Shibusen as a nurse...
...the witch Medusa...
Is trying to revive the Kishin.
This must be stopped no matter what.
Medusa-sensei was a witch?
No way...
There's something like that sleeping below Shibusen?
That's for certain.
I heard it from father too.
And in order to hold that Kishin, father can't leave this place...
What?
The Shinigami master can't leave this place?
I thought he was just a hikikomori...
Anyway...
We can't waste Sid-kun's quick wittedness.
I will guide you to the entrance of the basement.
Everyone, please come along.
It won't even budge...
My, what a bind... what a bind...
We're weakened like this...
Shinigami-sama!
At least you escape from here, please!
A mirror?
I'm sorry but it's no use...
This space is isolated from the rest of the world, you see?
But this level of magic will hold at most for an hour.
Until then we're stuck...
I-Is that so?
I'm sorry...
Dammit.
We're Death City so everyone just let their guard down...
Now, now...
Why not be careless?
Let us be even more careless!
That only means that the world is at peace, right?
And that's exactly why, we cannot allow this peace to be trifled with, right?
As for the rest, we can only rely on them...
This is the entrance to the basement.
The enemy is strong...
From here on, half-assed resolve will lead you to your deaths.
If you're considering running... you should.
If you're ready to fight fear...
If you will or will not come with me...
That's for your souls to decide.
We will go!
That so...?
Special Talk
The meat was good, but...
Robot
__ Katou Takuji
Hey sensei, could you not say it so casually?
This stuff's cheap.
Well, the meat's good, but...
Thanks to you, even us assistants were made to appear on the omake, weren't we?
Bird__ Rokooshima Kamome
I've never heard a thing, seriously.
Well, the meat's good, but...
Usher
_ Oukubo Atsushi
Hey sensei, don't say it, leave it to Akkun.
The meat's good.
Excuse me, does anyone want lemon over it? The meat's good, but...
Cat_ Yakuyama Tomou
Bamboo Sword
_ Yamaguchi Mikoto
Isn't that fine?
Doing it so sluggishly, isn't there any publicity for Soul Eater or Gangan publishers?
The meat's good, but...
It's fine, having yakiniku for the omake. The meat's good.
Oi, that one looks good... wait it's overcooked!
Ah, the meat's good.
Right?
Well it's good but, why are we eating meat here?
Is the end soon?
Well, the meat's good, but...
Well, it's like a deal... while eating meat.
Ah, maybe instead of an omake they're doing it for our manga's publicity... on TV?
Eh? For real?
The meat's good, but...
Well, it might be like that.
The meat's good, right?
Hey, what's with this piece that won't come off?
The meat's good, but...
Excuse me, pass over a piece!
Well, the truth is, my old man was watching the late night broadcast the other day...
Your old man?
The meat's good, but...
Well, it's something like that.
I'll tell you the details after.
After?
Fin
The final proposal for Art Gallery Number 13.
Yakiniku?
Artist, Creator Oukubo Atsushi's  papa.