Late Night Show
Bones 10th anniversary project
A healthy soul...
...resides in a healthy mind...
...and a healthy body.
Where... am I?
It's dark...
I can't even see my own body.
It's painful.
Which way is up? Which way is down?
Which way should I go...?
Help me...
A light?
An exit?
No! Stop!
A voice... Maka.
That's Maka's voice!
Wait! I'm coming!
Soul!
What's wrong?
Medusa-sensei, Soul is...
Soul?
It's all right.
I'm fine.
It was only a nightmare.
Thank goodness...
But if something happens, call me right away, ok?
The black blood of Ragnarok has blended with Soul Eater.
It appears that this child will become a great research subject.
This is a free fansub. Not for sale or rent.
Finally, the time has come!!
Excalibur
's arrived!!
Please enjoy it, everyone. ♥
Now, let's get started.
My legend began in the 12th Century!!
Now then,
...I'm going home for today, ok?
Ah, are you thirsty?
Want me to get you something before I go home?
Nah... It's okay.
If I drink it, I leak it, right?
I don't feel like going to the pot. It won't help.
I see...
Aside from a change of clothes, is there anything you want me to bring?
Hm... not really.
I see...
You know...
It's my fault that I ended up this way.
You shouldn't feel guilty, 'kay?
Sorry...
Crap! I screwed up!
It ended up making her even more depressed.
I'm so stupid.
What am I doing making Soul worried about me like that?
Papa?
Wanna come to the roof?
There's a lovely sunset.
So...
What did you want me to do?
Clean up! Clean up the library.
Huh? No way! What a pain in the ass!
Ya know...
You didn't retrieve a single soul in the last extra curricular class either.
And I have to make up for it, right?
I already know that's the reason.
I don't want these lame pseudo-assignments.
Cleaning up...? Ugh!
How do you get under the spotlight doing that?
Do it yourself!
Can't I do something else?
Like when I fought with the professor.
Ya know, Black Star...
Your strength is ranked pretty high in class.
But you still haven't got a single star.
Tsubaki's working so hard. Don't you feel sorry for her?
What you need now is to be punished!
If you don't wanna do this, change your ways.
You can help, if you want.
I don't spoil the students.
That's the man I used to be.
What am I supposed to do with this?
Charisma Justice rules!
This is the second biggest guy after myself!
I never knew they had manga at the library!
I'm gonna skip Doc's class tomorrow and come again.
Hey, you! No talking in the library!
Ah! Sorry...
Kid?
What's up? You got punished, too?
I came to borrow a book.
I came for an amazing work of art.
Can I take the book you have under your ass?
Oh, this?
What's that?
E-Ex... ca... libur?
Excalibur.
What's that?
From what I know, it's a legendary holy sword.
Whoever pulled the sword from the stone would be the hero of the land.
That person would be worshiped for all time.
In the distant past, there was even someone who became King thanks to the Excalibur.
It must be a beautiful symmetrical sword...
Wonderful!
Hero? King? That's me all right!
Huh, Excalibur, right?
What's up? Did you get detention too, Doctor?
What are you talking about?
Do you know anything about the Holy Blade?
The Holy Blade Excalibur?
Even I couldn't do it...
What? You tried to pull it out?
Even Doctor couldn't remove it...
The Holy Blade Excalibur...
It's getting really interesting!
The Legend of
the Sacred Sword
~The
Adventure of Kid and Black Star?~
The Legend of The Sacred Sword:
The Adventure of Kid and Black Star?
Look, look! Look at that, Maka!
Look at the the stupid face he's making while he tries not to fall asleep.
Yeah.
This is bad! Really bad!
I finally have a chance to talk to Maka. And I don't know what to say!
Agh! Maka's annoyed and she's reading a book.
I have to say something...
Something really intelligent...
Quickly! Quickly! Quickly!
Hey, read your books in a bright place.
Oh, crap! Why am I lecturing her?
Say, papa?
Yes?
How do you feel about mama?
I can't ruin the mood now.
I love her, of course.
Then why were you always cheating on her?
Crap! I've taken too long to answer!
Now anything I say won't be the least bit convincing!
I gotta think!
All fathers in the country are on my side.
Don't run away!
Stand up to your daughter.
Don't run away! Don't run away! Don't run away!
Don't run away!!
It's pretty cold, huh? Shouldn't we go back soon?
Why? We just came...
I couldn't run away!
The way you put pressure on others! You're just like your mama...
Maka-chan,
...I love you and your mama more than anything!
Really!
It's really true!
It's here, then?
So the Holy Blade is on top of the waterfall?
Yeah.
To be precise, we climb up, and there's a cave.
Hey, that's cheap!
Crap! Pretty boy's got some good stuff, huh?
I'm not gonna lose!
Huh?
Where did Kid go?
Inside the cave?
Black Star.
I can't step in that water below.
I'll get my trousers wet.
What the hell are you doing?
Carry me.
You moron! You can just stay there for the rest of your life.
I never expected to find all these obstacles.
The path to the Holy Blade is not an easy one.
You're completely useless...
I'll take care of the water dripping from above.
You take care of the one below.
This is a road where one can't walk alone. One is assailed from above and below.
This is true hardship.
You are really useless.
Huh?
Whoah! It's a fairy!
What's it doing here?
This is where the Holy Blade lies.
Fairies being here is nothing unusual.
Is Excalibur further ahead?
What's up with the creepy mood?
This seems to be a dead end, right?
Oi! Is that it?
Yes. Undoubtedly.
The Holy Blade Excalibur.
Awesome!
I can feel the air vibrating.
It seems that the legends were true. Whoever obtains the sword will become a hero and gain eternal glory.
And look...
Look at the detailed writing on the hilt.
There isn't a single scratch to be found.
This is fit to be called a Holy Blade.
The Holy Blade which only the Chosen One can remove.
I-I want it!
Yay! I'm the hero!
What a-
There must be some mistake!
I'm the hero! The hero's me!
You don't deserve to be praised as a hero!
Let's try again.
What? That's not fair!
Go ahead. It won't make a difference.
Let me do it this time.
You'll never pull it out! Never!
The Holy Blade chose the awesome me.
The big me!
You never know who's touched it...
Just do it!
It came out!
Huh? What's up with that?
It probably wasn't inserted properly.
I'm glad you came, young ones.
The Holy Blade is...
Sorry for taking so long to introduce myself.
I am Excalibur!!
W-Whoa...
W-Woah...
Lame.
News Flash!
I understand now.
You have returned.
That man (?) has returned!
Show me!
Show me your true power!
With even more power, he's going wild,
...screaming that the screen's too small.
Now, his hidden truth finally unfolds!
Is this...
...the truth we have been seeking all along?
Youth?!
You're young.
Reasoning?!
I'm more reliable than I look.
Adult's Love?!
The Legend has already begun!
I'll show it to you.
This is a true legend!
Fools!
July 28th 2008, 6pm
TV Tokyo first time ON AIR!
Holy Sword Legend 2
~Drink, Hit, Buy, Virtue?~
Say, papa.
About that Devil Sword, the Ragnarok...
In ancient times, alongside Shinigami-sama,
...Technicians and living weapons worked to protect the world.
Neither were permitted to take a human soul no matter what.
That was the accepted morality.
The life force of a human soul can give a weapon great power.
But by gaining that power, the weapon loses its heart as a human.
However,
...a Technician broke that rule.
In the midst of a battle, that Technician was overcome with fear of death...
...and recurred to the help of a human soul.
He went into hiding, and kept feeding human souls to his weapon.
And as a result... a Kishin was born.
The Academy of Shinigami Weapons Wielders...
...was founded to cleanse and release souls that have railed off the path of humans and turned into Kishin egg,
...and also to train and educate Technicians and weapons from a young age.
All, so that the world wouldn't plunge into the depths of fear, engulfing people into a swirl of madness...
...and in order to prevent the rebirth of the Kishin.
Then, was that Devil Sword also...
Yes.
There's the witch involved.
And how she melted the weapon and planted it into the Technician as black blood.
At this moment, there's no doubt that they're the closest thing to a Kishin in this world.
And it's not only the Devil Sword.
There are still others who can also turn into Kishin.
To make matters worse,
...there's Soul with his bloodstream invaded by black blood.
Now then...
Is Black Star doing it properly?
Oh! You can do it if you try!
Ah, Sid-sensei.
I just have to put this book back and I'm done.
Tsubaki? That bloody brat!
He made Tsubaki do all this. Where'd he go?
I hate kids like him!
That's the kind of guy I was!
Oh, no! I don't mind!
I love cleaning.
If you're looking for Black Star, he's head out
with Kid to get the Holy Blade.
Something wrong with that?
The Holy Blade... that  Holy Blade?
Yes... Excalibur...
The legendary sword that can cut the sky in two and raise the earth?
I bet you know what's gonna happen.
Yeah... but in a way, it's the worst punishment, ain't it?
I forget about bad things right away. That's the man I was.
Well, I've got tests to look over...
You're the Holy Blade?
But you look so...
So lame...
Then, let me ask you something.
You, in that appearance, who are you?
Me?
I'm Black S-
My legend started in the 12th century.
You look like Technicians to me.
Where are you from?
Stop pointing that at me! It's annoying.
We're Shibusen stude-
I know!
I'll show you something good!
Are you even listening?
What's with that guy?
If you're gonna wear clothes, wear pants, too!
What is he going to show us?
Do you want to know about my legend?
Don't point that cane at me!
Would you like to hear stories about my bravery?
Move the cane, you bastard.
Where are you from?
Like we said, we're from Shibusen!
What's your favorite number from one to twelve?
Huh? From one to twelve?
Number one, of course! I'm not satisfied with anything less than first place.
I'm eight, eight for me. I like the symmetry.
Fools!
You don't have the right to choose!
My legend started in the 12th century.
You said to pick our favorite number!
Do you want to know about my legend?
Stop doing that, you bastard...
My legend started in the 12th century.
I begin the day with a cup of coffee.
My afternoon begins with afternoon tea.
And at night...
It's probably sake, right?
You're just an old man.
Fools!
Naturally, I wear pajamas at night.
That's got nothing to do with it!
This has nothing to do with the legend. Besides, at night pajamas-
Fools!
Do you know anything about my hat?
Huh?
I'm asking if you know anything about my hat.
As if I'd know something like that!
If you're asking about the silk hat, then I know.
Fools!
It looks like I'll have to teach you.
The longer the cook's hat, the more important that cook is.
So you're basically blowing your own horn-
Fools!
Who ever said I was a cook?
You're not making any sense!
This is why I can't stand country bumpkins.
You bastard!!
You really piss me off!!
Calm down, Black Star.
Don't let him get you riled up.
What's so legendary about the Holy Blade?
What's wrong with this book?
It's completely useless!
Who wrote it?
Who's the author? The author?
Ex... cali... bur?
Excalibur.
You wrote this book?!
I don't do autographs.
Excuse me, Doctor Stein.
What kind of weapon is the Holy Blade?
Uh... that, right?
Its wielder will obtain wings of light...
...and gain the ability to teleport.
And a swing of the sword will split the Heavens.
Among all the weapons in this world, it's undoubtedly the ultimate weapon.
But unless you're the chosen one, it can't match your soul's wavelength, right?
Well, not necessarily...
Believe it or not, anyone can do it.
To become my Technician...
...there are one thousand tasks you must complete.
Read them carefully!
He even wrote on the back...
Item 452:
I'd like both of you to take part in the five hour reading out loud meeting.
Now then!
You have been chosen.
And thus, you'll obtain the Heavens!
Victory and glory!
Victory and...
...glory...
Now, let us go!
Together!
You moron! Who'd want to be with you?
You disgust me!
Now matter how well the wavelengths match,
...there's not a single person on this world
who can put up with Excalibur.
Wait!
Please wait!
Alright, I got it!
You don't have to do a thousand. Eight hundred will be fine.
But I'd still like you to come to my reading meeting no matter what.
You'd have to be a hero to put up with him.
He disgusts me!
Oh!
Did you meet Excalibur?
I guess you did...
We both have great partners, don't we?
Yeah.
Yo! Everyone's here.
Soul!
Feeling better already?
It's no fun without you around.
Yeah. Thank you!
Oi, Black Star.
They've been laughing for a while.
Huh?
Those two?
They did it?
That's right.
Hey, Black Star, Kid-kun.
Come to the classroom, quickly.
I'll be always waiting for you
You've gotta be kidding me...
What the hell is this?
Pretty harsh, huh?
No kidding.
This disgusts me.
My legend began in the 12th century.
Yes. I was still young back then.
The towns were quiet, people had lost their hope.
They were just living with no purpose.
In those towns...
...young ones spent their times fighting.
I was no exception.
Shut up!
Demon Blade
Masamune
~Break
through the dependent spirit.
A heart that sings to the rain?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Say, that wasn't even a preview!
After-film art museum number 8, "Excalibur?"
Bones Manager, Mr. Tanaka Itsuka.