Late Night Show
Bones 10th anniversary project
A healthy soul,
...resides in a healthy mind...
...and a healthy body.
For our extra curricular class, Soul and I came to Italy.
We safely completed our assignment.
But then I sensed the presence of a strange soul...
I had a feeling that I shouldn't have opened those doors.
The domain that the weapon and the Technicians must not enter,
...the domain of the Kishin, that is beyond humans.
And we...
...were careless.
This is a free fansub. Not for sale or rent.
My sincere apologies, I was a bit cocky last week.
We got scolded so we'll take this seriously this week.
Medusa the Witch arrives, and then...
Excalibur
appears in...
...just one week! (No sign of repentance).
Soul?
Soul!
Now, Chrona... Finish them off.
Medusa the Witch:
~The one with
an overwhelming evil soul?~
Medusa the Witch:
The One With An Overwhelming Evil Soul?
Kill them and eat their souls.
Clearly understood.
No way... Soul?
Idiot!
Hurry up... run!
Well then...
Soul,
...I'm sorry, it's my fault.
What is this?
My body is...
Dr. Stein!
Then, that blade is...
Papa at the scene!
How was that, Maka?
Burn this bright figure of papa into your eyes.
Dr. Stein, is Soul...
This looks very serious. He'll be in danger if we don't provide him with proper treatment.
You didn't see me?
Still... That was over faster than I thought it would be.
I hardened the blood at the wound to stop the bleeding.
Oi, don't I get thanked?
Thank you...
"...very much?"
You little...
V-Very much.
Eh?
Ouch! Ouch!
Dr. Stein.
What is that... what are they...
I've never seen something like that.
They're the reason why Shibusen was founded.
The reason Shibusen was founded?
Then, he's... a Kishin?
To be precise, it's the stage before that.
With Death Scythe-kun, stop the Kishin before the Devil Sword awakens.
Of course.
That's why I was pulled back into Shibusen.
Please, leave it to me.
We can't ever allow another Kishin to be born.
Please do it, Stein-kun.
Now then.
Shall we get on with it?
Right.
Chrona!
What do you think you're doing?
If you don't wrap this up, I'll wake you up in one hour intervals tonight.
No way! Stop it!
I'll have shadows under my eyes again!
I don't know how to deal with the shadows.
Shibusen's strongest Technician and Death Scythe...
How far can Chrona go?
This will be a good experiment.
Do it, Chrona.
Senpai, can you block that Devil Sword?
Who do you think I am?
I'm a papa for God's sake.
How many years has it been since we've been a team?
We're not as young as we used to be, are we?
Don't say that!
Hey, hurry up and do it!
It's the first time I've seen a person with a screw in his head.
How am I supposed to go about it with him?
Eat him! Eat him to the core!
Purge him!
He's inserted his soul wavelength!
It's damaging the inside of the body directly.
One more...
What?
The blood from back then...
Bloody Needle!
Doctor!
Every drop of blood becomes a weapon, huh?
What the hell is that ability?
The Devil Sword's made from destroying souls.
If I don't stop him here, he's sure to become a Kishin.
And the souls of the Technician and the weapon...
It's as if the kid's passive personality is being suppressed by the bullying weapon's.
It's only fine now because the bullied one is revolting against the bully.
But it'll be bad once he gets completely swallowed up.
Plus...
...what's that snake coiling around him?
Hey there, if you get hit with that again, I'll put thumbtacks in your shoes.
No way...
If I don't know how to deal with shoes with thumbtacks,
...I can't go outside.
This is Dr. Stein's hand-to-hand combat style.
He guards with papa and after that...
...with his left hand...
Purge!
Wow.
Dammit. I can't dodge this.
Go to hell, you screw-headed four-eyes!
Doctor!
I'm gonna dissect you!
This is it for you! Damn screw-head!
Senpai!
Yeah!
Experimental Body!
Crap! I can't get him like this!
Huh?
That damn screw-head's gone!
Where'd he go?
Where'd he... crap!
Dammit! I will never forgive you for this!
Hurry! Snap out of it!
We don't want another different soul wavelength in you!
Ugh!
I'm seeing stars!
How do I deal with stars?
How to deal with stars... Just protect nature.
So hurry up and... Open your eyes!
Double Soul Purge...
...Twin Lance!
The needles are coming again!
Nope... It's over.
It's sad but it's the finishing blow...
My, that's it?
I need to experiment more.
What's up with that?
He's being rejected...
The resonance they were in is now completely out of sync.
This is its limit, huh?
Soul Protect... disable.
Since when...
Suddenly, there's a response for another soul.
This response... a witch?
Emergency Special Plot!
PUNCH!
Compilation
Emergency Special Plot!
PUNCH!
Compilation
Shinigami-sama
Punch
number
one
Maka punch number one
Two
In a row
Shinigami chop
One more time!
And yet again!
Over the fence punch!
Three weeks till  full recovery.
Pile of corpses...
If you look at these images...
Even if I'd said something else,
...I think I still would've
...been punched.
Then let's try it out.
"Tsukkomi" may be used to mean both "punch" and "stuff something into something
else". In this context, it's intended as a pun. They mean they've just finished "punching the rice" into the omelete, and that's the end of it.
Since we've punched the rice into
the omelet too, that's all folks!
A witch?
Plus, that soul... is overwhelming.
Is she the one who... changed the kid into a weapon?
That's a witch's soul?
But why...?
A second ago, I couldn't feel...
...that powerful soul at all.
Soul Protect.
Soul Protect?
An advanced type of magic that a certain group of witches uses.
By sheltering the soul with magic,
...it can completely nullify your soul wavelength's signal...
...and it can also make it seem like it's the wavelength of a normal human.
That's a real witch?
Mama beat something like that...
...and changed papa into a Death Scythe?
Jeez, Chrona turned out to be a mess.
I'm disciplining you when we get home.
Nake, Snake, Cobra, Cobabara...
But first of all, you guys shall be...
...disciplined.
Vector Arrow!
Soul Resonance!
Witch Hunt!
You're just as I thought.
I only came here because I had some business to attend to.
But I never expected to meet Shibusen's strongest Technician and Death Scythe.
I really wanted to play a bit more but...
For today, you'll have to excuse me.
Hold it right there!
No. Leave them.
Let's forget about chasing them.
I'm worried about Soul.
Soul...
Papa...
Now... let's go home.
Is that so?
And how's Soul-kun doing?
Right now, Stein's operating on him.
I think he'll be all right.
Devil Sword...
And a Technician that's fused to the Devil Sword.
And the one pulling the strings was... a witch?
This turned out to be a friggin' complicated thing.
You don't seem to be gravely concerned, Shinigami-sama...
Really?
How did you do on your extra curricular class?
Hmm... it went pretty well.
Really?
I have extra classes tomorrow.
You're a lot better off that way.
Did you hear?
It seems that Soul Eater, who's a One Star,
...has been brought in with a huge injury.
No way. That's really bad.
Huh? Soul-kun has been what?
Doctor Stein?
Huh, you've been waiting all this time?
You should've at least taken a shower.
How is he? Soul?
The surgery was a big success.
If he rests, he should be fine.
Thank goodness.
Thank you very much!
Uhm...
May I go take a look at Soul's face?
Sure, go right ahead.
Thank you.
Stop making that stupid face.
So, how is Soul really doing?
His wound... is definitely fine with the surgery.
There's just one thing that's bothering me.
One thing that's bothering you?
I guess I could call it a curse.
Curse?
What do you mean?
Is he okay?
The black blood of Ragnarok has invaded Soul's bloodstream.
From where we stand, what will come to be, is still a mystery.
Soul...
I won't let you lay a hand on my Technician!
Live
long
Ponkan
Vitamin
I'm sorry...
I'm resolute to die if it's for the Technician.
For my sake...
Just wait, okay?
I too will become strong like you.
Soul! You alright?
Hold it together!
The great me has arrived!
Open your eyes!
My great smile will get you back up in no time!
BLACK STAR!!
S-Sorry, Maka-chan.
Maka-chan?
Oh my, you broke down the door.
Pretty lively, aren't we?
Medusa-sensei.
Good day.
Oh, you've come to see Soul too, sensei?
Umm... Maka-chan.
Yes.
What is it?
Could you make your dad, let go of my leg?
Ooh! My angel in white lab coat!
Treat me with your medical love today, for once.
Anyway, how horrible for Soul-kun to be like this.
Yes. I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Cheer up.
I'm sure that you will become much stronger.
Yes.
Special News
That man...
...is finally coming!
Where's Excalibur?
Don't try to hide him!
It all started with one book.
We'll be raiding in now!
The ultimate weapon.
I repeat!
We'll be raiding in now!
The legend started in the 12th century.
Hey!
Excalibur launches in just five minutes!
But confirm the location of the satellite before that!
His name is...
We've finally got you...
Excalibur!
The Legend of
the Sacred Sword
~The
Adventure of Kid and Black Star?~
After-film art museum number 7.
"Sound Director Wakabayashi-san?"
...by Voice Actor (for Soul) Uchiyama Kouki.
Bring it on!