Late Night Show
Bones 10th anniversary project
A healthy soul,
...resides in a healthy mind...
...and a healthy body.
The Academy of Shinigami Weapons Wielders.
In other words, Shibusen.
To prevent the rebirth of the Kishin,
the beings that nearly destroyed everything,
plunging the world into the depths of fear and
engulfing people into a swirl of madness,
this training facility for weapons created by Shinigami...
...and the wielders of those weapons was founded.
Well, quite simply,
...it's an organization that enforces peace, you see.
I wonder why it's an Academy.
Shinigami-sama
Oh well.
So, if you think you're prepared, let's have a go at it!
This is a free fansub. Not for sale or rent.
Commemorative production for 10 whole years of Bones!!
Bones will also broadcast many other productions, but...
Those on air are...
...only Soul Eater?
And so, to celebrate, we present Episode 2.
Watch away!
I am the Star!
Has the
"BIGGEST" man arrived?
I am the Star!
Has the "BIGGEST" man arrived?
Exterminate all the trash who oppose me.
You know?
Tsubaki...
Are they our target this time?
Yeah, Al Capone and his friends, numbering up to roughly a hundred.
sake
Two vs. a hundred, huh?
Fair enough.
Black Star...
We'll retrieve all the empty souls that have
become Kishin soul eggs.
Law of the assassin, number 1.
Conceal yourself in darkness... quiet your breath...
...seek a path to your target.
Law of the assassin, number 2.
Know your target.
Be able to foresee his thoughts, his movements!
Law of the assassin, number 3.
Defeat your target before he becomes aware of your existence.
Let's go.
I am the great Black Star!!
I've come to assassinate you!!
I've nailed it.
Hey!
I'm not a microphone!!
I'm a weapon!
A Chain-Scythe!
Do you even understand what an assassination is?!
Who the hell are you guys?
Die!
Let's retreat as soon as possible, Tsubaki!!
Man, this again?
Smoke Bomb mode!!
Right!
Break time!
Were they Japanese ninjas?
Don Al Capone.
What now?
We've discovered the whereabouts of the witch.
Once we get our hands on the power of a witch, the family will be unstoppable!
You know?
That was a great stage today! I was really big!
I can't believe I haven't retrieved a single Kishin egg yet...
I'm gonna start losing faith in everything thanks to him.
Are you playing on the words "Kishin" and "Gishin"?
"Gishin" is doubtful or unfaithful in Japanese.
A lame joke like that will never make it big!
Really? Sorry.
But hey, no lame comedian could compete with a big guy like me!
They're all too naïve!
Do you know the difference between them and me?
"They suck so bad it's really sad!!"
Just try to beat a joke like that!
That wasn't even a joke...
How'd you like that? Did your eyes shrivel up in surprise?
Totally! I was so surprised!
The rate we're going, I can't face Shinigami-sama...
Hm, isn't there anything worthwhile here?
What are you saying? Luck just wasn't on our side when it came to finishing off Al Capone and friends.
But if we carry on failing our missions like we're doing now,
...it'd be better to look for something easier...
Yo.
Was yesterday's mission a failure, too?
What're you saying?
Yesterday was my greatest performance on stage!
You just weren't able to cleanse and release the Kishin souls.
Well, that's exactly what happened.
And how did it go for the two of you?
Please, don't ask.
I become depressed just thinking about it.
Attention, the Crescent Pair, Black Star-kun and Tsubaki-san,
...please proceed to the Death Room.
What?
I repeat.
Well, well, well. Hello, hello.
I heard you were unable to kill Al Capone?
S-Sorry.
No worries, sir!
I'll be sure to turn Tsubaki into a Death Scythe and make her Shinigama-sama's weapon.
For you, Sir
In the meantime, I'll let you have my signature.
How's that?
You don't need a weapon anymore, right?
I'm terribly sorry.
You two possess the skills, but I get the feeling you're having it a bit too hard.
Yes...
I would personally like to keep you at your own pace, but we have a few problems to solve.
Problems?
Al Capone's gang is after a witch and they
have begun to make their move.
What?!
The name of the witch they're after is Angela.
Angela apparently has an outstanding bodyguard,
...but if Al Capone's gang were to get its hands on the witch's power, it'd be truly problematic.
Then, if we defeat Al Capone's gang and the witch...
Ninety-nine souls plus one witch soul...
She'd become a Death Scythe in an instant!
You know what they say, "Make hay while the sun shines!"
Black Star!
There's just a slight problem with this witch, Angela, by the way...
Hey, you!
They aren't listening...
Wait up, Black Star!
What is it?
How could we possibly fight a witch if we can't even accomplish the basic missions?
What was that?
Anyway, we can't just blindly barge in this time,
...we have to come up with a strategy, or else...
I do believe Tsubaki-chan would be much better off with any other partner, really.
He might be a fool, but he's got guts.
Tsubaki's probably aware that he's not just all talk.
Yeah.
She probably is.
Well then, shall we get going, too?
The path to gather up ninety-nine Kishin souls is a long one.
Yes.
We heard the witch lives in this castle.
With the power of a witch, my family will become the strongest!
You know?
Don Al Capone.
Al Capone...
What business does the king of the underworld have here?
Depending on your answer, you may die.
What a joker.
Waste him!
How could we possibly fight a witch...
...if we can't even accomplish the basic missions?
That Tsubaki... what's impossible?
Hiding my presence is as easy as blinking for me.
I'll catch Tsubaki by surprise and prove that to her.
Law of the assassin, number 1.
Conceal yourself in darkness... quiet your breath...
...seek a path to your target.
Oi, Maka.
Huh?
We got almost no screen time at all.
You're too loud.
Everyone can see you...
If you're an assassin, then at least mask your presence properly!
What a thing...
And now I'm dying... no presence... ok?
Ok.
Off to our goal: To the witch's castle!
Just a minute, Black Star...
Did you come up with any sort of strategy?
Yeah, of course! First, my big entrance scene...
Yes, yes, no plan. I should've known that by now...
But you know, Tsubaki,
...I'll definitely make you a Death Scythe.
Leave it to me!
Yup! I know!
What's this?
Today's looking rather noisy.
The Kishin souls in the form of Kishin eggs
that are floating around here...
...were all destroyed by you?
Did you come here after the witch's power, too?
Are you strong?
Very well.
I'll allow you to be a stepping stone for me to get big!
Have a fight with me!
My name is Mifune and I'm the bodyguard of the witch, Angela.
I am Black Star, the man who'll surpass God!
I dislike meaningless battles.
Move away from Angela and leave this place.
Tsubaki.
Right.
You're... a Weapon Technician.
Don't you feel small about yourself when you're facing someone as big as me?
I can understand that feeling.
Before, I used to get kind of freaked out by how big I was when I saw myself in the mirror.
The Infinite One Sword Style...
This is...
Be careful, Black Star!
You won't fall back no matter what?
I'll kill you!
If you want to kill me, go make a sword out of a Buddha!
I'll be taking that one!
Your weapon saved you...
A normal chain would've been broken by now.
This is your last chance.
Leave this place.
I can't sleep well when I have to kill kids.
What did you say, punk? Are you calling me a kid?!
A kid would equal small...
That's the complete opposite of big!
Tsubaki! Dark Tool mode Shuriken!!
Yes!
If you become one fourth of what you are now...
...you'd be smaller than me!
Tsubaki, Smoke Bomb mode!
Got it!
Gotcha!!
Idiot, you're shouting again! And this was your best chance!!
Black Star!
Fool.
No...
It can't be...
Mifune, you bastard! You're being cocky.
A blunt-strike is something done by people who're as great as me.
Don't you think you're being rude to that lady?
The fact that you haven't been defeated until now is thanks to the quality of that weapon.
No matter how amazing the weapon, it's worthless if the hand that wields it is weak.
You are just a small fry, are you not?
You've got it all wrong!
Black Star's just kind of silly, that's all.
He can actually do it if he tries!
Mifune, what are your reasons?
I'm just a bodyguard that protects Angela.
That's not it! That's wrong!
I get it now.
I get it now, Mifune!
You're trying to keep all the attention on yourself by calling me a small fry!
THAT, I will never forgive!!
Heaven's Wrath!
I'm the superior ruler! The main character is ME!
Right?
Whatever the reason, he's become more serious...
Tsubaki, Ninja Blade mode!
Yes, sir!
Mifune, a fair fight. No tricks, just swords.
It won't be a blunt strike this time.
Law of the assassin, number 1.
Conceal yourself in darkness... quiet your breath...
...seek a path to your target.
Law of the assassin, number 2.
Know your target, be able to foresee his thoughts, his movements.
What's going on?
Is this even the same kid?
Law of the assassin, number 3.
Impossible! It's as if I can't feel his presence at all.
No... that's wrong.
I'm able to feel a faint presence.
But it's clearly a different person's presence.
Before your target becomes aware of your existence,
It can't be... you?!
Defeat him.
Dummy Star mode.
What?
Killing Blow! Black Star Big Wave!!
I am what God is.
A fair fight. No tricks, just swords.
That's the assassin's way.
I lost...
You tried to stand out more than me.
You're a million years too early to win against me!
Tsubaki!
Yes!
Where is the witch?
STOP!!
Don't bully Mifune!!
Angela.
Mifune's just protecting me from humans because I'm not good at magic, yet!
So, don't bully Mifune!!
This is Angela?
Black Star,
...we have Al Capone gang souls everywhere and a powerless witch.
There won't be another chance like this.
Yeah, but...
Meanie, meanie, meanie, meanie, meanie, meanie, meanie,
Meanie!
NOOOOOOO!!!
I'm going to kill you, you damn brat!!
If you want my life, I'll give it to you.
But, if you try to kill Angela...
...I shall defend her with this sword until I die!
What are we going to do?
A bodyguard who protects a half pint witch?
You're too lame.
Let's go, Tsubaki.
Okay!
Besides, I can't sleep well when I kill kids.
Is it really fine?
Yeah, it's not like it was me who did them in.
It's odd coming from me, but...
...you should've just deceived me.
Such a thing wouldn't suit someone as big as me.
Right, Tsubaki?
Sure.
Law of the assassin, number 1!
Conceal yourself in darkness... quiet your breath...
...seek a path to your target.
Mask your presence already, dammit.
The future's not looking so bright.
Death the Kid.
He's the Shinigami-sama's son.
A perfect boy makes for a perfect ending.
It's the end, Lupin.
Lupin, the thief.
Your soul, which turned into a Kishin's egg...
...we'll be releasing it!
He's so much of a perfectionist that...
Oi, Patty! You're standing a bit more to the right!
Oh my.
Sorry.
...it even applies to useless things.
Chupa Cabras
What do you do for a living, Mr Customer?
I deliver newspapers.
Oh, so you wake up early every day?
No, that was a lie just now.
I'm actually in the underwear making business.
Eh? Really?
Really, really.
Are your underwear the proper size?
This old man will take a look for you...
I'll report you, you bastard.
Sorry.
It looks like it's finally our turn!
Liz, Patty, are you ready?
We know!
We'll nail it for sure!
We, the clumsy girls, and the Shinigami-sama's son will go wild in the next episode!
Look forward to it!
Wait a sec!
The Boy of Perfection
Death
the Kid's Magnificent Mission?
Only the parts of me getting beaten up are being aired!
You call this a preview?!
The final proposal for Art gallery Number 2, "Maka?"
Artist, the Director, Igarashi Takuya.