Late Night Show
Bones 10th anniversary project
A healthy soul...
...resides in a healthy mind...
...and in a healthy body.
With the threat of the Demon Blade turning into a Kishin,
Black Star and Tsubaki-chan went to the Shin village.
The Demon Blade possesses its owners, even controlling their shadows.
And, in the end, it eats their souls.
For the two who had obtained a total of zero souls,
...they had a reason to fight such a reckless battle.
Tsubaki.
Big brother.
Only she can stop the Demon Blade.
This is a free fansub. Not for sale or rent.
Last week's Late Show had omitted something, hadn't it?
We've received this postcard rebuking us for this.
And so, this week, a Special Drama...
... out-take is included.
It's my new production!!
Its title is... that fun will be in the end.
You went inside the Demon Blade, Tsubaki?
Ryoku.
You've been done in.
How terrible...
Because of that member of the Hoshizoku, Ryoku has...
It's terrible...
Get out of this village!
Tsubaki...
Are you ignoring me?
Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave!
Leave! Leave!
Leave!!
You better come back...
The camellia
flower
~What lies
Beyond The Sadness?~
The Camellia Flower:
What Lies Beyond The Sadness?
Powerless...
What's wrong, Tsubaki?
Don't tell me you came this far just to fool around...
You're just as your name states...
...same as the camellia flower...
...the flower with no scent.
Quietly blooming without being payed attention to...
It also whithers in a miserable way and leaves an unpleasant feeling.
A half-assed flower...
I doth think.
Should this be the outside world, you would've already died...
Your soul is shaking...
Are you scared... of dying?
I'll stop you even if I die.
I will...
Stop it!
Those eyes...
You drove me this way!
You drove me...
...onto the path of the Demon Blade.
Leave!
You damned Hoshizoku!
Leave! Leave!
Leave!
Black Star's consideration is amazing, isn't it?
To think the Demon Blade and Tsubaki were siblings...
But Black Star doesn't know about it yet, right?
Yup...
...that boy trusts her, you know?
Tsubaki's not moving... is she alright?
What's going on inside the Demon Blade?
Hmm, well, about that...
Oi?
While having lunch
We've brought drinks!
Hey wait, how serious are you about this?
Well, let's see...
In simple terms, there's a tug of war with her and the Demon Blade Masamune's souls.
On one hand, the Demon Blade is trying to take over her soul with his "Soul Possession" skill.
On the other hand, Tsubaki's trying to absorb him.
To take the mummy or to become one...
Still, does Tsubaki stand a chance?
It'll be tough... for her.
They're fighting inside him, so he has the upper hand in the tug of war of souls.
The probability of Tsubaki winning is low.
A fight to the death between siblings...
I can't even imagine my life without Patty!
There, there...
The path to becoming a Kishin is chosen by weakness of heart.
The Kishin sought power to escape the fear from death.
Why does the Demon Blade Masamune seek power?
How did he end up on this path?
Shuriken, Smoke Bomb, Dummy Star, Ninja Blade...
Why do you only use the Chain-Scythe?
Are you holding back on me?
Nay!
Is it compassion?
The Nakatsukasa, who raised both Demon Blade Masamune and Tsubaki,
...were a weapon family who passed on their special techniques through the generations.
Masamune, as the eldest son, was supposed to inherit his ancestors' power.
However...
You inherited all the other powers...
What I inherited... was nothing but the Japanese sword.
For some reason, Tsubaki ended up with all the powers.
I was raised in an overprotective environment.
I didn't know...
...that people could be kind to incapable trash.
The one who taught me that...
...was you.
Don't look at me with those eyes...
Don't pity me!
You've always tucked away your feelings and never looked out for me.
I hated that.
Tsubaki,
...I will kill you... and become a Kishin!
And... I will master the way of the sword!
Puppet Rain.
Black... Star...
Tsubaki...
Do you remember my big on-stage performance...
...at the Shibusen welcoming ceremony?
I remember!
All of you, remember this!
I am Black Star!
I will surpass God!
No! I've already caught up with him!
What?
Idiot.
Has he got a fever?
Don't be sorry, commoners!
I am just too awesome!
Heaven's Wrath
Heaven's Wrath! I'm the superior ruler!
I'm the superior ruler
Tomorrow, a halo shall appear over me!
Silence...
Huh... It seems I'm ahead of this era.
Uhm...
I-It was nice.
Oh?
You're the first one to recognize my great talent.
Congratulations.
Your name?
Yes.
Tsubaki.
I'm a weapon.
I'm Black Star!
A Technician.
That time...
...you watched my performance until the very end.
This time I'll be watching yours.
This woman hasn't moved for a while...
You should also get out of this village!
Oi, brat!
If you mess with Tsubaki's stage,
...I'll kill you!
Shut it and look over there.
Shut up, Hoshizoku!
Is there anything left for you?
In the end, you're just a scentless flower...
Will you remain silent until the very end?
Tsubaki, what do you want to play?
What about you, brother?
Geez, Tsubaki...
I'd like to play what you want.
Then...
I want to play Kemari.
Your soul...
...is mine.
Fighting the Demon Blade alone...
It's reckless!
It's true that Tsubaki's a powerful transmutative weapon...
However, the opponent is too strong for her.
As I thought, I should've gone instead.
She's not alone.
Isn't he there? Black Star.
Tsubaki's fighting because he's there.
Yup!
What's really important is right here.
Tsubaki-chan may have transmutative powers and be a very special weapon,
...but her strength doesn't lie there...
...it's in her soul.
Tsubaki, pay attention and pick it up, this time.
Okay.
There!
Did you really want to play Kemari?
Yes.
Actually, I wanted to play "house."
If I said it, would we have stayed together playing all this time?
I am Tsubaki...
I am scentless...
...and I also whither in a miserable way leaving an unpleasant feeling.
What do you want to say?
Do you pity me? Scorn me?
I bet it feels good...
...playing superior to everyone.
You remain silent, but you get excited just looking at people.
Can you deny that?
You don't think that way...
...and I know it very well.
No!
No! No! No!
I won't hold back anymore.
I will stop you, big brother.
Please, feel it with your soul, big brother.
The real me.
Nonsense!
Just like that?
You're just a half-assed flower, in the end!
You're wrong!
I won't let you say things like "half-assed."
There's someone who taught me better!
Even Tsubaki...
Even for a camellia flower...
...there's a scent!
Tsubaki!
Tsubaki went inside the Demon Blade?
You're kidding, right?
Tsubaki has...
...lost?
Tsubaki-chan!
It's no good, I can't bear to watch.
Geezer, lend me that stick!
Oi, Tsubaki!
Come out, dammit!
Don't you lose!
Your stage isn't like this, right?
Encore!
Encore! Encore!
Your feelings...
...I saw them.
Camellia flower.
The scentless flower?
Nay!
I saw your trembling soul.
Big brother...
It has a nice scent...
Encore!
Encore! Encore!
Ouch!
I'm back, Black Star.
Tsubaki...
I've met my brother.
Is that so? Welcome back.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Are you really okay?
Yes. I'm fine.
C'mon, get over here!
Black Star will give you a hug!
I'm sorry!
Black Star, you're bleeding!
Are you alright?
Don't worry about me.
You...
Lil' boy!
Ryoku!
You're still alive... good for you.
Hoshizoku are the worst!
Aren't you satisfied?
Get lost!
The losers from this village are so persistent and annoying!
Shut yer trap!
You're even scared of an imaginary enemy...
Lame!
I couldn't care less about the past!
I'm a star because I always move forward!
Stop joking around!
Get lost!
Don't come again!
If only you hadn't been born...
Crap!
Who'd want to come to this lame village?
You idiots!
I'm so sorry!
He's a good boy, really!
He's not a Hoshizoku, but I still don't like him...
Hey, Tsubaki...
You've defeated the Demon Blade and made amends with your past, but...
...you still want to continue as my weapon, right?
Huh?
Yes!
Aye!
Welcome home!
You guys...
I've made you worry...
Yo! Nice job!
You two were great!
You finally got a soul.
For a repeat student, you've changed, haven't you?
You kept us waiting for quite a while.
I told you, I'm an era ahead!
You did it, Tsubaki-chan!
This one was crying.
That was you, sis.
Shinigami-sama,
...it seems I underestimated them.
That's because they're all still growing youngsters, you see...
Attention, everyone!
I'm going to show all of you something awesome!
When did he...
Oi?
Would you believe it, Tsubaki's attained a new mode!
Wow~!!
Let's go, Tsubaki!
Yes!
Demon Blade mode!
Black Star!
My soul's wavelength suddenly got drained...
It seems Black Star can't use it yet.
But I was surprised!
She earned her brother's power, too.
Uh uh...
I guess I was born ahead of my time...
This age is already behind me...
Let's take our time moving forward.
Together.
Television Drama Series
Shadow Family
Voices:
Dad --- Kid
Mom --- Patty
Kid --- Liz
Scenario: Yamatoya Akatsuki
Continuity: Igarashi Takuya
Chappy
Film Production:
Original Pictures: Oyabu Yoshihiro
Oh, I'm so busy, I'm so busy.
Mommy, I'm hungry.
I'm so busy, I'm so busy.
Hey, mom...
Mom, are you even listening?
I'm so busy, I'm so busy.
I'm hungry...
Hey hey, your mom said she was busy didn't she?
Dad, I'm starved.
What? Does that mean you want to say you're hungry?
I'm telling you, I'm starving. Do I need to say it in a clearer way?
Wait, calm down. Everything's fine.
Now, in this moment, I'll think of a way.
This is hard so-
Dad, I'm hungry.
Geez...
I am hungry.
Why you!
You think you can eat without having a mouth?
Fin
Mom, what will next week be about?
I'm so busy, I'm so busy.
Hey, mom...
I know you're busy but could you do things a bit more seriously...
I'm so busy, I'm so busy.
Mom?
Hey now, we only have a bit more...
The Courage
to beat fear
~Maka
Albarn's big resolution?~
Next time in Soul Eater episode 12,
The Courage to Beat Fear: Maka Albarn's Big Resolution?
Mom...
I'm so busy, I'm so busy.
We apologize.
We'll do it properly next week!
Taken After Photo Gallery, Number 2.
Where Soul was born?
Director Igarashi, you've worked hard. ♥
Photographing, Cameraman Tsumura Yoneki.