A healthy soul...
...resides in a healthy mind...
...and in a healthy body.
Run!
It's the Black Dragon!
The Black Dragon has come!
This is a free fansub. Not for sale or rent.
Life's rough due to many reasons these days.
The cost-of-living has increased, business is decreasing, and global warming is also a serious matter.
This week, God is going...
...to slice up that kind of world!
What exactly will he be butchering?
That's for you to find out.
What's wrong?
Would you row properly?
Why did you ask for a rowboat?
Couldn't you have gotten us a chartered ship or a cruise ship or something with an engine?!
Stop complaining.
Besides, we've already reached our destination.
Destination?
Looks like a pretty good village.
It's pretty calm...
I wonder about that...
What do you mean?
Look there...
What's that?
A few days ago, something ate this city and its souls.
The whole town?
Don't tell me that our investigation is...
Let's go...
We need to ask around.
What happened in this village?
F-Fog...
Fog?
What happened with the fog?
N-No!
Calm down.
It's alright.
We came from Shibusen to solve this situation.
Shibusen?
Yes.
That being...
Let us talk calmly and clearly.
B-Black Dragon...
The Black Dragon... The Black Dragon appeared...
Black Dragon, you said?
The Black Dragon
That Eats Souls!
~Cowardly
Liz and Her Pleasant Companions?~
The Black Dragon That Eats Souls!
Cowardly Liz and Her Pleasant Companions?
Elephant.
Chimpanzee.
Dog.
Cat!
You know...
You should grow up a little.
Yeah, yeah...
A dove, right?
A pig, right?
Oi, Kid!
Enough of this moldy place already...
I'm gonna suffocate here.
Suck it up.
Preliminary investigations are important for this stuff.
Or so I'd like to say but,
...I've finished reading most of these.
We're done here.
So, where are we headed next?
What's wrong?
Can't you row any faster?
Why are we back to the sea in this rowboat?
You better know what you're doing!
Of course.
Or else I wouldn't have come out to the sea.
Acting all high and mighty...
So, what is that Black Dragon thing?
The Baltic Sea was the center of maritime transportation.
In the archaic days of the Vikings, people set out to this vast sea.
What's that got to do with it?
In other words, this is a place where lots of ships passed through and also,
...where many ships sunk.
You can't mean... that there'll be...
And out of all the sunken ships...
This is...
A cloud!
It's fog!
F-Fog?
It's close, stay sharp.
Yes?!
I can feel the presence of numerous souls nearby.
S-So, you mean...
That's it, the Black Dragon.
What the heck is that?
Look, there.
Ni-d-hogg?
Nidhogg is the name of the Black Dragon in Norse mythology.
And in this area,
...the legend of the being known as Nidhogg was passed down as if it were true.
And thus the pieces come together.
Alright.
Liz, Patty, we're boarding it.
No! No! No! No!
It's a ghost ship!
Ghosts will definitely come out!
Wait, Patty!
Wait! Wait!! Wait!! WAIT!!
Are you kidding me?
I told you to wait.
Woopzie.
If you're going to crash into a ship, do it right in the center!
That is what you're angry about?
Do it over!
'Kay!
Good...
Let's board.
You must be stupid.
Too stupid...
This stupidity is stupid right?
It's stupid isn't it?
Crap!
I got carried away by their stupidity and carelessly boarded the ship!
It seems the souls are inside the ship.
We're going in.
'Kay.
Oi, oi, let's stop...
They'll come out, I'm sure.
What if they eat us?
Hey, are you listening?
Hello?
Let's go, Liz.
Some lively souls came on their own.
It's through this door.
Gathering all these human souls...
What do they intend to do?
Can I take all these souls?
Fool!
Do you want to become a Kishin?
As a soul caretaker I can't allow this.
I will take them into custody.
How's that brat? You a Shinigami?
Liz, Patty!
Huh...
Yes!
Nidhogg!
Liz!
She fell! She fell!
It's your sister, right?!
It's no laughing matter!
This ship and I are one and the same.
All that's left is digesting her.
Are you an evil spirit?
What are you planning to do, gathering all these souls?
Because of a Shinigami, I've become extremely bewildered.
That's why I'm offering them to Kishin-sama...
...all these human souls!
Kishin?
Are you talking about Ragnarok?
That rookie's of no importance.
The Kishin-sama that's right next to you.
For that person's sake.
What?
Right next to us, you said?
It's better for children not to know.
This ship will surely get me something.
From the far off depths, humans are waiting for the Kishin song.
Everyone craves for power no matter what sort it may be.
But in certain times, that alone is not quite enough.
Humans are waiting for the Kishin.
These souls are a gift to Kishin-sama.
I won't hand them over!
Kid-kun, I'll transform into a gun, okay?
No.
I can't...
I can't! I can't! I can't! I can't!
It's no use!
Patty... Kid...
But I wonder if those two will be okay?
If Kid only has Patty to use, he can't be symmetrical.
He can't fight...
In any case, I've got to return to them.
Come on...
I'm not scared of this ghost ship!
I was once feared as Brooklin's Demon.
One of the Thompson sisters who'd even stop a child's tears!
There's nothing I fear.
Why am I in such a place?
My luck ran out when I got high and mighty, mugging a shinigami...
At any rate, is this the right way?
That's it... this way...
I appreciate the kindness.
Who's there?
Mishearing... mishearing...
That's it.
Like that, straight ahead.
Death the Kid's
Complaints about the World!
Cup ramen are too expensive, and I can't feel like I'd want to buy one!
Soba stores all over the world should serve cold tempura batter udon even in the winter!
Death the Kid's
Complaints about the World!
Make sure you're aware of global warming!
I can't look! I can't look!
It's definitely there! It's definitely there! It's definitely there!
No! No! No! No! No! No!
That's it. Like that, straight ahead.
I was eaten by this ship.
I'm the ghost of a poor girl.
Y-Y-You were eaten?
T-T-Then, you intend to eat me too?
The one who eats is the Kishin.
I only want to show you the way to your friends.
That's a lie!
You're just planning to eat my nice body!
I wouldn't eat you.
Believe me.
It's big but it's not tasty!
Believe...
Like I said, I'm not good for eating!
...me.
Shut yer trap!
Quit jabberin' and get a move on, damn it!
I'll beat your ass!
I will gladly follow.
As long as you understand...
Now, move it.
Geez...
If I'd lived as long as you have, I'd have a nice body and everyone would say I'm sexy.
I'm sure they would...
Patty, sis is in a pinch.
Running is useless...
I didn't want things to turn out this way,
...so I made these symmetrical guys my partners.
But now...
...where's my reason that I strongly refused...
...all the suggestions father had made?
My...
...hard sought effort for...
...the most important thing to me...
For symmetry...
Effort due to symmetry.
Effort for the sake of symmetry!
Where would it go?
Wouldn't everything... go to waste?
Damn it!
Where'd Liz go?
Miss...
This way...
Shut it!
No!
I don't want to be guided like this!
What's wrong Shinigami?
Is that all there is to a God's power?
I haven't done anything yet!
Then show me the power of a Shinigami.
I'm an evil spirit following Kishin, reaping innocent souls.
Show me how you judge your so-called "evil."
I don't deny evil.
I don't know a human completely without evil.
Everything is in balance.
If good and evil were perfectly balanced there wouldn't be a problem.
If there was perfect balance...
I don't care about God's ideals!
Don't think all humans seek the same!
Like I care about that!
I won't feel satisfied until I've created a neat, tidy and perfect world.
So you'll take our freedom?
You're disgusting!
I'm a Shinigami.
I will never give others the freedom to kill.
This way...
This is it.
M-Much appreciated.
Wait!
It's the deck...
No one's here though...
So you were lying! You'll eat me!
You're going to eat me, aren't you?
You're going to boil me in a pot!
They're coming now, so shush it!
I'll curse you!
Sis!
Hey, Liz! You fool!
Because of you I couldn't use Patty!
That's more your fault!
Sis!
Patty!
I missed you!
You won't escape!
Whatever... since we're all back together again.
Liz, Patty, transform.
Let's go!
'Kay!
Brace yourself!
He's...
The Devil Sword?
Ragnarok...
Scream Resonance.
What?
The souls of the ship...
Goodbye, Miss Scaredy-Cat.
What a thing to do...
It ate all the souls.
A pretty big feast, huh?
Bastard...
That's the Devil Sword's true form?
You're completely black!
Is he... supposed to be human, like us?
In this Baltic Sea,
...there was a legend of a ghost ship that was known as the Black Dragon.
However...
As I see it...
That  is...
...the true Black Dragon.
Hey, did you know?
My blood is black.
Judgement!
Death God martial art...
Stance of Sin.
I'll exectute you.
Death the Kid's
Complaints about the World!
Attention to all the people of the industry!
Be wary of gout and diabetes!
Next up is the preview!
And that's the end of "Kid's Complaints of the World."
I don't need ask how it was.
I'll also be kicking ass next week.
Next time on Soul Eater episode 16:
Kid's Complaints about the Industries!
Battle On the
Ghost Ship!
~The Hell Inside My Head?~
Look forward to it.
Final proposal for Photo Gallery Number 3
"Miwa - cold tempura batter udon from Kiku-Ya."
It's good. :)
Photo by Tsumura Yoneki of Bones Literature.