Late Night Show
Vons 10th anniversary project
A healthy soul,
...resides in a healthy mind...
...and a healthy body.
The Academy of Shinigami Weapons Wielders.
In other words, Shibusen.
Plunging the world into the depths of fear,
...engulfing people into a swirl of madness.
"Kishin" are demon gods in Soul Eater.
Those beings that nearly destroyed everything: The Kishin.
And to prevent their rebirth...
This is the training facility for weapons created by Shinigami...
...and the wielders of those weapons.
Well, quite simply,
...it's an organization that enforces peace, you see.
I wonder why it's an Academy.
Shinigami-sama
Shinigami = Death God.
Oh well.
So, if you think you're prepared, let's have a go at it!
Give me more power...
More... power!
Soul Eater, that guy...
Yes, Maka, there's no doubt. That guy's soul is already like the egg of a Kishin.
It ain't human.
Souls that have railed off the path of humans,
...have a high risk of becoming Kishins.
In the name of Shinigami-sama, cleanse and release that soul.
What's wrong, Maka?
The same way he's not human, I'm a weapon...
...just so happens that I have a human form normally.
How the shape looks like doesn't matter...
What matters is the soul!
I understand.
To the mass murderer, Jack the Ripper.
I'm here... to take your soul.
The weapon and the owner are two in one.
Let's go, Soul.
Yeah.
This'll make it ninety-nine souls!
Thanks for the meal.
Job completed.
We've finally collected ninety-nine pre-Kishin souls.
Just one left!
If I can eat a witch's soul, I can become a Death Scythe, the weapon of Shinigami-sama!
Not to mention, my coolness level would go up big time!
I'm gonna go report to Shinigami-sama.
Hm, Death Room's number is...
42-42-564.
Hello, hello, Shinigami-sama?
This is Scythe Technician, Maka.
Ooh!
Maka-chan! Is everything alright? What's going on?
We just collected the ninety-ninth soul, so now all that's left is the witch's soul.
Good job! Maka-chan, you're an excellent Scythe Technician, just like your mom.
Hey, Soul Eater!
Don't lay a hand on Maka...
...or else I'll take care of you as a Death Scythe... no...
I shall kick the lights of of you as a father, you moron!
Shut up!
There's no way a cool guy like me'd go for a girl with such small breasts.
Why you...
Are you saying my Maka has no sex appeal?
Just cop 'em a feel. And you call yourself a man?
What the hell are you saying?
Maka, I love you!
Forget it.
I don't think of you as a father of mine, papa.
Well, leaving that topic aside,
...by collecting ninety-nine deserted souls, in other words the souls that have become Kishin eggs,
...and one witch's soul, you obtain the right to becoming a Death Scythe.
But the problem is the witch's soul.
I've seen countless Soul Technicians die in battles against the witches.
Be careful, Maka-chan.
Scary, scary...
Make yourself a great scythe that won't lose to the Death Scythe your mother made.
Yes!
And finally, to clarify things...
The last soul is that of a witch.
If you get it wrong, you'll be stripped of all the Kishin souls you've collected up to this point.
I know.
Just wait, Shinigami-sama!
And that's how it is.
Maka... Maka...
Hey, you're getting a bit on my nerves...
Maka!
You're annoying! Don't make me do a "Direct Noggin Shinigami Chop" on you!
Tell me that before you do it...
The Resonance
of Souls
Will Soul
Eater become a Death Scythe?
The Resonance of Souls:
Will Soul Eater become a Death Scythe?
I am a cute and lovely lady...
Now the back.
But you know,
...the thing I love is pumpkins, see?
Pum-pum-pumpkin, that's magic to me...
So that's where the Blair witch lives?
A pumpkin?
That's cool.
Looks tasty. This sneaking around isn't manly.
I'm gonna go in and meet them face-to-face.
Hold on, you can't do that! This is different!
Let's go!
Hey, wait-
N-Naked?!
Oh my, what's wrong, boy?
Someone cool like me is used to women in nude.
The nosebleed says otherwise...
Besides, we're here for your sou-
You idiot!!
Sorry for improvising like this, but we're here for your soul!
Are you ok?
Wha-?
Hey, hurry up and turn into a scythe.
I got it.
Witch, let me eat your soul.
Witch?
Neat! He turned into a scythe!
I'll take your soul and turn Soul into a Death Scythe,
...the ultimate weapon, surpassing papa!
I like it.
Can I have that scythe?
Pum-Pumpkin, pumpkin, Halloween Cannon!
Oh, Death Scythe-sama, you're so naughty...
Chupa Cabras
Now that I think about it, Death Scythe-sama, you have a daughter, don't you?
What's she like?
Oh, don't mention that to him.
Huh? Why not?
Death Scythe-sama isn't exactly good with women.
And because of that, he hasn't been getting along with his wife.
It has even come down to divorce negotiations...
Even his daughter, Maka-chan, turned to him and said "I hate you, papa."
So it's pretty complicated.
MAKA!!
No, Maka!!
Papa... Papa... Papa loves Maka and mama the most!!
That's the truth!! I swear!
Thank you very much.
Death Scythe-sama!
Come back soon.
Yeah...
Well then!
The...
...next...
...day
The next day
Damnit! How dare she seduce the cool me with her sexiness.
Well, she is a witch, after all.
But you won't be able to become a Death Scythe if you can't even cope with that level of sexiness.
Shut up, flat chest.
It's her!
What should we do?
What we should do...?
Oh, lil' Scythe boy...
On...
...the day...
...after that
On the day
after that
Today, I filled up this paper with strategies.
What the hell... we're not making a "menu" here.
What could a single sheet of paper do, anyways?
Well, how do you plan on beating Blair, then?!
Dunno. With willpower, maybe.
What was that?! Damnit!
We can't do this if we don't cooperate!
You can't be a Death Scythe otherwise! Are you listening to me, Soul?!
I got it. Cut it out.
Pum-Pum-Pumpkin...
Why are all men like this?
Pumpkin...
Halloween Cannon!
The...
...next...
...day...
The 4th round
You'll never beat Blair.
What do you think you're doing?!
Quiet!
It's all because you do nothing but get nosebleeds.
Huh?!
You men are worthless!
I bet you jumped in on Blair that time because you knew she was taking a bath, right?
How could I have possibly known that?!
How can women say completely illogical stuff with such complete confidence?!
Women's intuition.
Damnit, you make no sense.
Hey, lil' Scythe boy.
If you two are gonna fight, why not just belong to me?
I'd forgive every little thing you do.
Hold it!
I'm Soul's partner.
So why don't you talk to its owner instead?!
Hm, I see.
Then I'll kill you and take him with me.
Not here?!
Pum-Pumpkin, Pumpkin...
Smashing Pumpkin!!
What shall we do, Soul? Nothing seems to be working...
Soul?
Hey, Soul! What's wrong?
Why not just be mine?
Rejoice, rejoice! Shinigami here!
I have a cheerful face but...
...under the mask I have a second face! Hahaha!
Really, cabaret clubs are so much fun!
Man, what do you do when your daughter's in trouble?
Eh?
Has something happened to Maka?!
She's in a critical situation fighting against the witch. She'll die that way.
What?!
Hang on, Maka!
Hold it!
Indeed, if we step in, we could finish off a witch of that level with a single attack... no...
...with a single direct hit of the "Direct Noggin Shinigami Chop."
However, that's not the issue here, is it?
Being that girl's father, you should be aware of it...
Maka...
But that witch is a bit strange, isn't she?
Say, Soul, why won't you answer me?
Maka...
Soul?
I don't care anymore.
Huh?
Hey, what was that for?!
I'm tired of this troublesome crap.
I...
I'm gonna be Sis' Blair's Scythe.
Huh?!
Oh, goddie! Really?
Yeah, you're on the right path! Ditch Maka, you idiot!!
Heh?
Is this the time to be saying something like that?
Blair!
You've used magic to mess with Soul's emotions, haven't you?
You're such an idiot.
Any man'd go for an older babe with a nice body over a kid like you, with a flat chest.
Oh!! That's definitely what a fully grown woman should be!
You keep quiet!
What's wrong with you?
Men are horrible.
All they do is cheat and mess around.
But...
...when I thought I'd finally found someone I could trust...
I don't believe this.
All of you can just go to hell!
Hey, Soul,
...you said earlier that women blab out completely illogical things, right?
Do men have any logic behind their cheating, you jerk?!
How would I know something like that?
'Cause cool men don't cheat.
Nya?
Maka!
Ok!
We did it, Maka.
Yes.
Thank you, Soul.
The form or the shape doesn't matter...
What matters is the soul, right?
If you eat this...
Yeah, I'll become a Death Scythe, too.
The power! The surge of power...
Isn't there...
Huh?
Blech.
Eww.
You... can't possibly be...
Blair never said she was a witch, you humans did.
I'm just a kitty with strong magic.
Eeeh?
The form or the shape doesn't matter, right?
Ouch, I knew it...
Cats work, too!
That's it! I'll become your catnip!
Does this mean that...
...I've eaten ninety-nine Kishin's souls and one cat soul?
Now that you mention it...
The last soul is that of a witch.
If you get it wrong, you'll be stripped of all the souls you've collected up to this point.
Stripped of all... stripped of all...
Does this mean... we've failed?!
Damnit!
Damn! Crap!
I've failed as a Soul Technician, and I have to start all over again.
And I thought I could become the perfect cool guy!
Besides, how are you still alive after we took your soul?
Don't you know how many souls a cat has?
Anyway, Soul-kun, why not be mine?
Hey, Blair! Stop following us!!
Hey, Soul-kun...
This ain't cool at all.
I present to you... Black Star,
...the assassin who resides and moves with the dark.
Tsubaki, those guys are the next target?
Yes.
Alkaponen and his friends, numbering up to roughly a hundred.
Two Vs. a hundred, huh?
Fair enough.
Black Star...
We'll retrieve all the deserted souls who've become eggs of Kishin souls.
The one who wields Tsubaki.
He had a huge problem, however.
Let's go.
So, there you have it, Soul Eater's finally begun. What did you all think?
Every week Soul Eater will be like this.
Action... Gags... Surprises!
But also this kind of stuff...
It will all take place in a very exciting stage.
Including, of course, the "Direct Noggin Shinigami Chop!"
The final proposal for the Art Gallery Number 1, "Soul?"
The representative director from Bones , Planning, Minami Masahiko.