Thanks to the idiot hero, we now have to join the Princess Recovery Battle.
General Godwin and Lady d'Arquien began their fight in the fortress
Even Yuki and Rico are involved in this crazy ordeal.
And I've got my hands full with Genoise!
Hero, you'd better save my princess!
Log on to www.ruri-subs.com or visit us at #ruri@irc.rizon.net
Fansubbed by Ruri Subs
「Fierce Battle! Myon Castle!」
The princess is coming with me!
If you're good enough!
Take this!
What...
The side.
Vert.
Okay!
Prince Gaul's Imperial Guard Army, Genoise.
Basically, these three are just idiots.
But, once they're in battle, they're strong!
Not bad. You're good enough for me to treat you as a guest.
But it's time to show you the real deal!
The purpose of our wars is for others to watch.
Power, magnificence, and straightforwardness
are the qualities of a knight and warrior.
To make these powers prevail,
we have Ki Power!
Ki Power unleash!
Lion King's Claws!
Heaven Lightning!
Blast Blade!
How did my Lion King's Thunder Blast combo feel?
It's the legendary Ki Power supreme attack.
Looks like it's over.
Don't end it yet, damn it!
H-Huh?!
No way! Normally it would've ended already!
Why are you still able to stand? You're a monster?!
Are you a monster?!
This guy was able to put up that sort of defense within a split second.
Hey, it did work!
A-Ah! Y-You idiot!
Aren't you injured?
Since you're not from here,
I guess you can't turn into a pet ball.
You'd better not try anything beyond your...
No thank you. Your worry is unnecessary.
I think I somehow got it.
Ki Power is this kind of feeling!
If I don't hurry, we won't make it in time for the concert!
Everyone's waiting for the princess's song!
Huh? C-Concert?
Here I come!
No, wait, wait, Hero!
What concert?!
My lady!
Bad news!
The enemy's reinforcements have arrived!
How many?
Well...
Only one!
Princess Leo is here on her own!
Open the city gates!
Yes, ma'am!
Your Excellency!
Greetings, Princess Leo.
It's been a while, Lady d'Arquien.
But don't call me princess.
I'm now a leader.
Pardon me.
Y-Your Excellency...
This is...
Move aside, d'Arquien.
I have some business with Gaul.
My sincere apologies. This is a battlefield.
Hence, as a rear unit guardian of the youngsters...
Does this mean that I have to force my way through?
Correct.
Do not think I am still who I was before.
Now... Not even you can stand in my way!
So, I shall face you.
It seems that the war at the fortress is still going.
Oh my, I wonder if the princess can still make it on time.
We won't be able to hear the princess sing?
Well, the knights and the hero are trying their very best right now.
Let's wait patiently.
Okay!
By the way, Your Excellency,
I've heard you're continuously attacking our country?
What about it?
It's just a routine war activity for us, the Galette.
Because of Your Excellency's attacks,
the diligent Leader of the Knights in my country is stressed out.
Not to mention my princess's concert and usual activities are unable to proceed.
So what?!
Besides, it's your doggie princess's problem!
She organized a sweet potato digging competition!
And some random water sport competition!
How are those going help exercise the youngster's bodies?!
Well, they do seem kind of happy.
I didn't say anything about being unhappy.
What I mean is that not everything can be settled so simply.
Well, our princess does have her weak points.
However, as she matures and gathers more experience,
I'm sure she'll be able to be an even
more outstanding leader in the future.
That is what I truly believe.
So, for now, please just...
How nice if... that was possible...
Princess Leo...
That's enough talk!
I don't care what others say! I will do it my way!
That was superb. I surrender.
Come, Godwin!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Th-That was really amazing, Your Excellency.
You only needed one strike to finish off that knight.
Nonsense.
She barely used twenty percent of her power.
She let us through on purpose.
R-Really?
To be fair, I used no more than thirty percent myself.
No, make that around twenty percent as well.
Wait! So, is there really gonna be a concert after this?
You serious?!
Didn't I already say so?!
Damn. Those Genoise idiots!
They got me into trouble again.
What are you mumbling about?!
Gaul!
And the quack hero of Biscotti!
Sister!
Q-Quack?!
You meddling kids!
Why the hell are you playing on the battlefield?!
Okay! Sorry!
Your Excellency, my apologies!
I didn't think it'd turn out like this.
Don't bother. It's the fault of the two idiots over there.
Excuse me!
Your Excellency? Um, it's been so long...
I'm sorry, Princess Millhiore.
I apologize for disturbing the
winning country's celebratory party.
I apologize on behalf of my ill-mannered brother for bringing you here by force.
No, it's okay. Prince Gaul didn't know that-
I'll consider other ways to compensate for this incident.
Please return immediately.
Your Excellency.
Rouge, do take care of the rest.
Ah, understood!
Can we still make it on time?
We have twenty minutes before
the princess is to appear on stage.
It'll take an hour just to get to the hall from here.
What have I done?! What have I done?!
Um, please don't worry about it.
But what should we do? What should we do now?!
Listen, we'll definitely get spanked if we wake up now.
Let's just pretend to be unconscious.
Just pretend to be unconscious... Unconscious...
Pretend...
Um!
Allow me to send you back, Princess!
You send her back?
How?
Of course, I will...
...use my Hero's Special Delivery!
So, Prince...
I'm sorry. What was your name again?
Remember it already! It's Gaul!
I remembered how you used your Ki Power, Gaul.
I should be able to do it!
Shall we get going, Princess?
Yes, Sir Hero!
One, two...
Off we go!
Sir Hero, you're amazing!
You're already familiar with Ki Power and Crest power.
I've memorized most of it. I'll memorize all of it soon!
Oh, is that so?
Lady d'Arquien!
Brioche, I haven't seen you for so long!
Princess, and the hero!
I'm sending the princess back!
Bye bye!
Princess, it's been a while!
Yukikaze!
Yup!
Nice to meet you, Sir Hero.
I'm one of the Knights of Biscotti, leader of the Omitsu Squad,
Yukikaze Panettone.
Nice to meet you! I've seen how dynamic you are.
Thanks for the compliment.
I'm quite confident in my legs, you know?
If you don't mind, we can take turns carrying the princess.
I appreciate the offer, but that won't be necessary.
I've just thought of a way to increase my speed.
I'll release Ki Power by using the crest,
by following the level I imagine,
then transforming it into the actual pattern and power. Is that right?
Right.
That's right.
Then I can probably do this too.
It's a success!
Whoa! That was cool!
Well, Miss Yukikaze...
Drop the "Miss"!
Well then, Yukikaze, I'll go ahead first!
Ahead?
Hold on tight, Princess!
Boost Rider...
Go!
Princess, it's okay now.
Um, Sir Hero...
Please don't overwork yourself.
If you overuse Ki Power, there'll be terrible consequences.
No problem. This is much easier than running.
Sir Hero, you know...
Yeah?
I have something I've wanted to tell you.
I became the leader of Biscotti just recently.
All the members of the Knight Army were from my father's generation.
As a leader, I'm a complete novice. I can't seem to do anything right.
That's why I've made so much trouble for Sir Hero.
Not at all! There was no trouble at all!
It's only been a day since I was summoned,
yet I've already had so many extraordinary experiences!
And I was able to meet a cute princess!
Besides, isn't it good to be a novice?
I'm also a novice in terms of being a hero. A novice hero!
Even a novice can fly if he tries.
So long as you give your best every day, you'll become someone great someday!
This is what my teacher taught me.
We're gonna land.
There'll be an impact, so hold on tight!
All right!
Sorry for being late. Millhiore has arrived!
Ten minutes 'til show time.
Makeup artist, costume artist, please take your places.
Yes, ma'am!
I'll lecture you later.
Do you remember the flow?
Yes, Amelita. It won't be a problem.
Thank you for waiting!
Let's welcome Princess Millhiore Frianno Biscotti on stage!
During the war today, the hero who came to Biscotti,
and all the knights who have been fighting for our country the entire time,
have brought us victory!
For today's victory,
and to provide a better tomorrow for everyone,
I'll sing my heart out!
"This Must Be Love"
I watched over your strong and gentle character
itsumo yasashikute, chuyoku massugu no
all this while from a distance.
anata wo tooku kara mimamotteita
I had a dream.
yume ni mita keshiki wa
The two of us together looked up at the sky.
futari de miageru sora
Sitting side by side, our eyes eventually met.
tonari ni narande, hitomi awase
Right now, there's still a little distance between the two of us.
ima wa mada sukoshi, tooi futari no kyouri
But one day, I'm sure
dakedo itsuka kitto ne
I'll be walking with you.
issho ni arukitai
Whenever I think of you, I cry gentle tiny teardrops.
anata wo omou to, yasashi sasa namida
My heart wavers, but I'm sure it's because I'm in love.
kokoro wo yurashite yuku, koi wo shiteru kitto
I'm relieved she made it.
Yeah.
Is the hero okay?
He used his Ki Power so recklessly.
Hm, yeah. He's totally burned out now.
I'm not surprised.
We'll take care of the rest.
All of you just come back.
We need to have a second celebratory party!
All right!
What a wonderful song.
I love you!
anata ga suki desu!
I fell for your gentle eyes.
yasashi hitomi ni de
I'm sure that this is love!
kitto koi wo shitteiru!
I just want to embrace you softly.
dakishimetai soutto
I just want to embrace you more and more!
dakishimetai motto!
Yay, Princess!
She's so cute!
Awesome...
The world's number one!
The Star Reading Princess
I'm so embarrassed.
Yay...