Eat it!
Why would you do that to me?!
There's no way I can eat human flesh!
I'm human! I'm not like you monsters!
Well? If I'm a monster,
what does that make you?
I'm begging you, please, tell me...
What am I supposed to do?
Everything has sucked since that day!
Sucked, huh? I wish
you'd tell me something.
What does cake really taste like?
It's so nasty, it makes me
want to puke, so I can't tell,
but it's something that
humans enjoy eating, isn't it?
What was it like, living a peaceful life?
One where you didn't need to
live in fear of CCG and other ghouls?
Everything has sucked? Come off it.
Does that mean that everything
since I was born has sucked?
Well, buddy? Tell me!
Tell me, oh tell me, the way it works
Who is that inside of me?
Here in this broken-down,
broken-down world,
you laugh, without seeing a thing
I'm just so damaged,
I hold my breath and freeze
Breakable, unbreakable;
shakable, unshakable
When I found you, it shook me
In this twisted world, I'm gradually
growing transparent and vanishing
Don't look for me; don't look at me
I don't wish to hurt you in a world
of someone else's imagining
Remember who I am
I'm...
I'm human!
You're not a ghoul, that's for sure.
But you're not human, either.
There's no place left for a
half-and-half like you anywhere now.
If you want to be human so badly,
why don't you see
how long you can starve?
I'll tell you right now,
starvation for a ghoul is utter hell.
Toka, I think that's quite enough.
It must be hard on you,
huh? Come with me.
But sir, why?
Toka...
it's our policy to help out our fellow ghouls.
Thank you for waiting.
Here you go.
Do you not like coffee?
It's not that, but...
Kaneki, take a good look at this coffee.
What do you think?
It looks quite delicious.
It's regular coffee.
It's delicious. This is delicious!
But no matter what I eat, it tastes awful...
Through the ages, coffee is the only thing
that ghouls have been able
to enjoy, the way humans do.
However, we cannot satisfy
our hunger by drinking it alone.
Which is why...
What is it?
When you need more, come
on back. You need not hesitate.
Sir, why did you help that guy?
Toka,
a little while ago,
there was a story about an organ
transplant on the news, remember?
Some steel beams fell, and two
students were crushed beneath them.
The doctor took it upon
himself to transplant the organs
from the deceased girl into
the surviving young man's body.
But the girl that
died in that accident was...
It was Rize.
Then, you don't mean...
Yes. He is that young man.
He has had ghoul organs
transplanted into him.
That's preposterous.
It's the first time I've seen this happen,
but his body may be becoming like ours.
Flesh... Flesh... Flesh... Flesh...
Flesh... Flesh... Flesh...
You're neither a ghoul, nor a human.
There's no place left for a
half-and-half like you anywhere now.
Who cares if you're a half-and-half?
Neither a human, nor a ghoul...
You're still you.
Enjoy being a half-and-half.
That delicious flesh is waiting for you.
It's so delicious, it's tantalizing.
Once you start eating it,
you won't be able to stop.
It will put any steak to shame.
Now, go on. Wolf it down.
It's prepared extra-specially rare.
"New message" "Hide"
"Sub: You're gonna die alone"
"Missing you a bunch in Asian History..."
"You need my notes?"
Hide...
Have you ever been to the
sweets shop in front of the station?
That place has the tastiest stuff, huh?
Hey, you, Kaneki! How long
are you gonna skip class, you jerk?!
Put yourself in my shoes!
When rabbits get lonely, they can die!
Hide, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
And what's up with the
eye patch? You styling it up?
While you were gone, I was
so bored that before I knew it,
--I'm sorry? Huh? When was it?
--I'd joined the school
festival planning committee...
Seems like this happened before once...
Hey, Kaneki! How long
are you gonna stay home?!
Do you know how hard it is for
me when you stay home like this?!
Hey, are you listening to me, Kaneki?
Oh, sorry. What'd you say?
Anyhow, I've got to go see that
upperclassman with the sharp tongue
to borrow some material
from him. Care to join me?
Mm-hmm.
Kaneki, are you eating right?
Huh?
You're looking pale. You've
gotta eat, or you'll ruin your health.
He's always been like that.
Hide is sharp witted in some odd ways.
He's overly aware of the
sentiments of others, so instead,
he pretends not to notice
anything, out of concern for me.
If I were to stop being human,
would we never be
able to walk together again?
I've been wanting to
introduce him to you, Kaneki.
Is this Mr. Nishio?
Yeah.
I don't know whether to describe
him as toxic, or bad-mouthing,
or just as someone I feel uneasy around...
No!
This is it. Pardon the intrusion!
Hide, at least knock.
Nagachika, can't you knock first?
Mr. Nishio, I'm sorry.
Nothing pisses me off more
than having my territory violated.
Yeah... Oh, this is Kaneki,
the good friend I mentioned before.
You don't say. Nishio Nishiki,
second year, School of Pharmacy.
Good to meet you, Kaneki.
You wanted last year's material?
Yes, I wanted to see the retail data.
Oh, where did I put that?
Aw, it might be at home.
You're serious?
Nagachika, why don't you
come with me to grab it right now?
You mean, to your house?
Yeah.
Hmm, well, okay.
Kaneki, sorry, but I have
to stop by Mr. Nishio's place,
so head on out without me.
Hide...
Um, is it okay if I go, too?
Huh?
What's come over you?
Yeah, that's okay.
Huh?
It's not like I'm planning on letting him in.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Before we go, I have to smooth this over.
What's with you, all of a sudden?
Nothing.
Hmm...
Nagachika...
Hmm? What?
How much did you see earlier?
--Huh? Oh, just her shoulders.
--Why are there ghouls
popping up around me?
--Just your shoulders.
--Why are there ghouls
popping up around me?
They were very pretty.
No, that's not true. They were
there before this all started.
I'm the one who wandered into this.
Want one?
Oh, how nice.
Yes, step right up. These are freshly made.
Here.
Ugh, I feel nauseous.
--Here.
--Thanks so much.
Kaneki, are you in any clubs?
Oh, I don't do that
well around large groups.
Hmm. The exact
opposite of Nagachika, huh?
Can a ghoul eat something like this?
Mm, what a superb taste.
Nice and crispy, too, huh?
Huh? Kaneki, aren't you eating yours?
Later.
He really does blend in to human society
like a normal college
student. It's kind of amazing.
I'm sure nobody suspects that he's a ghoul.
It would mean trouble if anyone saw this.
Hide!
Who'd have guessed there'd be
another ghoul on the same campus?
You reek. You stink
just like a female ghoul!
You were planning to
eat Nagachika, weren't you?
There's nothing better to whet the appetite
than that moment you turn on
some idiot who completely trusts you,
and that look of anguish
that crosses their face
when the foolish human
gives up hope, is there, Kaneki?!
I'm not like you...
Oh, yeah?
Having a kid younger than me
talk back to me really pisses me off.
You know what?
Your body is awfully fragile.
I thought it might be tofu.
Aw, how disgusting.
Geez, how can humans eat that stuff?
It feels like eating horse crap.
Sorry about that, Kaneki.
I've befouled your meal, here.
You've known this guy a long time,
right? You're best friends, right?
Just when were you going to eat him?
Come on, tell me, Kaneki.
What were you going to eat first?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Hide is not food. Move your foot.
What foot?
Stop that!
Seriously? Attacking with
your bag? What are you, a woman?!
You know, you just don't get it, do you?
Humans are nothing but things to eat,
the way that cows and
pigs are to them, right?
Are you having fun,
playing like you're friends
with what amounts to livestock?
I'm not playing...
I see. Then again,
I think Nagachika is risky.
The guy is no idiot.
Even you have to be
aware that having someone
as shrewd as he is by your
side is going to be dangerous.
And this...
You can't even control your own eyes.
Come on, get up.
Or should I kill Nagachika first?
Whoa, what's this? Here, avoid this!
I guess I've toyed
with you more than enough.
And I could have taken no
time at all by releasing my kagune.
There's no way... I can
beat someone like him... Hide...
Hide...!
Oh? Very good. That's more like it.
Hurry up, before I crush him.
He's unconscious?
You've helped me again, have you?
Later, Nagachika.
No... No...
Hey, you. You're always reading
books by yourself at school, huh?
I-Is that wrong?
I don't mean that. I just moved
here, so I don't have any friends.
So would you be my friend?
Mm-hmm, sure.
All right! I'm Nagachika Hideyoshi.
Call me Hide. Nice to meet you.
Mm-hmm. Nice to meet you, Hide.
Even then, when I didn't
get along well in class,
Hide was concerned,
and reached out to me.
No...
I don't want Hide...
to die!
I won't... I won't let that happen!
Damn you!
Stop it! Stop it, you dumbass!
I'm dying, dying, dying, dying,
dying, dying, dying, dying, dying!
That was... Rize's...
Damn it...
Hide...
Mm, he sure looks tasty.
What a savory aroma.
It's making me hungry.
Here, you see? Look closely.
Doesn't he look delicious?
Stop it! Hide is not for eating!
Are you sure about that? Take a good look.
See? You can tell, right?
Mm-hmm, I can tell.
He does look good!
Stop! Stop that!
What are you talking about?
You want him so bad
you can't stand it, right?
You don't have to put up with it.
You're not doing anything wrong.
Come on, quickly. You can do as you like.
As I like?
He's all yours.
All?
Go on.
You're right. This is
my special treat, isn't it?
I... I have to eat him...
Hide is my...
friend!
Yes! He is my friend, so I have to eat him!
You're becoming so much
more like us, huh, half-ass?
Your sense of reason has
given way to hunger, hasn't it?
Move!
You don't give a damn
about your own friend's life now.
You know what? After you
gobble this guy up, you'll regret it.
In a sea of blood and entrails.
Such is a ghoul's hunger, and our destiny.
You really are tedious.
I'll be understanding this one time.
So go down nice and easy!
Toka brought you back here.
Where's Hide?!
Come with me.
Hide!
I've been... stricken with
this hunger this whole time.
At that moment especially,
I was so hungry, I thought I might die.
I didn't even realize what I was doing.
And then, I went after Hide...
But right now, that's completely gone.
That blood that was in my mouth--
Please, answer me truthfully.
What did you do while I was asleep?
There is only one way
to satisfy a ghoul's hunger.
You know what that is, right?
The way you were going,
you would have set upon your friend.
You have to know what you are.
I... don't want to hurt my friend.
Which means, I can't
be around Hide anymore.
But I can't enter the world of ghouls, either.
I, who am neither
human nor ghoul, am all alone.
There isn't a place for me anywhere now...!
That's not true.
You are both ghoul and human.
You are the one and only person
who has a place in both worlds.
Come over to Anteiku. I'm
sure it will lead you to the path
in which you can keep your own place.
I also want you to understand us better.
To see whether or not
we are just ravenous beasts.
How about it? What do you say
you start by learning how to
make a delicious cup of coffee?
Well, um...
do you think even I can do it?
Nice rain, huh? Rain
makes their senses duller.
This is perfect weather
for us to work in, isn't it?
According to the 20th Ward Branch's report,
three months ago,
there was a predatory incident
by what they believe was a
binge eater here in this building,
and there were eyewitness reports
of a Jason sighting at that time.
Binge eater and Jason, huh?
Interaction between two S-rated subjects?
Who can say? I doubt they
were cordially sharing a meal, though.
Mr. Mado?
Mr. Mado!
Amon!
You see? I knew it!
If I had to offer one drawback to this rain,
it would be that I can't hear
the scumbags' throes of death!
It feels like eating horse crap.
Mr. Nishio, you know
what horse manure tastes like?
What are you, an idiot,
Kaneki?! Of course not.
It's a simile! A figure of speech!
Oh, yeah?
"Grin"
What?! Mr. Nishio has eaten horse crap?!
Cow manure, too?
And every other kind of feces, it seems.
For real?
K-Kaneki!
Hey, Nishiki! How's that poo taste?
"Next time: 'Dove'"
Nishiki, you smell like poo!
You're a disgrace as a ghoul.