I can't afford to let it all end here.
What... am I even doing here?
Tell me, oh tell me, the way it works
Who is that inside of me?
Here in this broken-down,
broken-down world,
you laugh, without seeing a thing
I'm just so damaged,
I hold my breath and freeze
Breakable, unbreakable;
shakable, unshakable
When I found you, it shook me.
In this twisted world, I'm gradually
growing transparent and vanishing
Don't look for me; don't look at me
I don't wish to hurt you in a world
of someone else's imagining
Remember who I am
I'm against this! He doesn't
have any desire to help Kaneki!
With him along, it increases
our chances of rescuing Kaneki.
It's more encouraging having him as an ally.
Why are you even still alive?
"Eat yourself." I followed
the advice you gave me.
As a result, look, you see?
And in what came as an
unexpected surprise, I taste pretty good.
In any event, I'm against it!
He's planning to eat Kaneki!
You need not worry about that.
I'll look after him.
I won't let him pull anything.
Yomo, any movement from CCG?
Once the civilians are evacuated,
they appear ready to mount an attack.
Anteiku will rescue Kaneki under
the cover of CCG's all-out attack.
Any objections?
Kaneki...
You... awake?
This is my room. Isn't it nice?
Mr. Tatara said he doesn't need you...
so I ended up claiming you.
I'm glad.
I've wanted to invite you over...
from the moment we met.
No...
Since even before we met, maybe. So please,
do not disappoint me.
RC inhibition fluid...
When this enters a ghoul's body,
their kagune activity is suppressed.
Once that happens,
their body becomes non-resistant,
and my scalpel can slice right through.
Just... like a human.
Hypodermic needles...
don't work on ghoul bodies.
But there is one place where
the needle will pass through.
And that... is the mucosa!
Here is our current status:
It has been two months since
the shopping mall was occupied.
There are five hundred ghouls inside,
as far as we can identify.
They have increased their forces
substantially in the last week.
--Here, at the main entrance...
--Mr. Mado...
Here.
What is this?
Mado asked me.
He said you were to use it.
--Take it.
--Once the first mission starts
rendezvous with Team A.
--Teams B and C will proceed
as scheduled to the annex.
--I will cherish using it.
--Teams B and C will proceed
as scheduled to the annex.
Move in at your own discretion once
you verify the conditions on the ground.
Civilian evacuation has been completed.
Let's go, men!
Yes, sir!
CCG and the police are waiting
to charge into the 11th Ward
with a joint force
of over a thousand men.
The leader on the scene is
Special Investigator Marude Itsuki,
the man who pinpointed
the location of the ghouls' base.
"Breaking News"
We will stake our lives to protect
the citizen population's safety
up to ninety-nine percent. The last one percent
will come from everyone's joint cooperation.
Let us all work together,
to take back the peace in the 11th Ward!
That was Special Investigator Marude.
--Kaneki...
--Now, back to the studio.
How many was that, again?
Five hundred and fifty-nine...
--I'll be back after you recover.
--Five hundred and fifty-two...
--Five hundred and fourty-five...
--Clean that up.
--Yes, sir.
--Five hundred and fourty-five...
Kaneki...
Mr. Banjo?
I swear, I'll find an opening
to get you out of here.
Just hang in there for a while.
Why... me...?
I heard that Miss Rize is dead.
You didn't tell me in order
to spare my feelings, right?
You're a good guy.
Shu and Haru, who will be
taking over for me, are my friends.
If anything comes up, you tell them.
Kaneki, hang in there.
Is everything ready?
Mr. Uta! You're coming with us?
Yes, I am. Kaneki is one of
my valued customers, after all.
That's everyone, right?
Let's go.
Is something the matter?
Hmm? Oh...
Amon, what did you
think after fighting this guy?
He's not like any other ghoul before him.
I got a peculiar vibe from him.
Hmm. This was before
they started calling him Jason.
He was arrested by CCG and sent
to Cochlea Ghoul Internment Center.
While there, there was a--how shall I say?
A problem investigator posted there, you see.
Five hundred and fifty-nine...
Five hundred and fifty-two...
--Five hundred and fourty-five...
--Let me take more!
Let me take... even more from you!
While being subjected to intense torture,
he created another personality within himself.
In order to protect himself.
And then...
he broke out.
Ever since, he came to
favor acting in a brutal manner.
Making use of the torture
that he underwent himself.
It was after that when he
started going by "Jason," as well.
That was sooner than we thought, huh?
Yeah.
Bin Brothers, you're in the main building.
Right.
Kirishima, the annex.
Let's get going, Eto.
You take it from here, Noro.
Where's Yamori?
Beats me. Who knows
where he could have gone.
That bastard. Now, of all times!
The weak are trampled upon,
attacked, violated, and afflicted.
N-No... D-Don't...
It's unusually quiet, huh?
Two hundred and twenty-three...
Two hundred...
How is CCG being outgunned?
The enemy is using
kagune shields and scopes!
Former soldier ghouls, huh?
Damn it! You've gotta be kidding me!
Give me that!
Men! Take out that insidious
sniper nest immediately!
Here.
Awesome...
What's that?
Oh, Mr. Marude, that's your motorcycle.
Hold up! What are you
planning to do with my bike?!
I'm just borrowing it.
Hold it!
Hey... Hey, now, come on,
h-h-hold it! W-W-Wait!
Yahoo!
Good eve--
ning!
Move in!
Hey, which team are you with?!
Anteiku.
Incoming at three o'clock.
Ten of them!
Hitting them with the Emerio!
Ten of them at nine o'clock!
Hirako!
South entrance block secured!
Keep watch on our perimeter!
This is Shinohara.
We've taken control of the main
building, second-floor entrance.
Awaiting instructions.
Divide into three units and
take control of the interior
and the parking lot from below.
You should be able to
rendezvous on the top floor.
Copy. Also, I don't see Suzuya around.
I can't let him die until he
reimburses me for my bike.
Somebody go and snag him.
Copy.
Hang in there! Hang in there,
hang in there, hang in there!
Hang in there!
Don't die now.
It's so cruel.
Thank... you...
Mr. Kaneki, Mr. Banjo asked
us to bring you a message.
"I swear we'll rescue you, so don't give up."
All right, Mr. Kaneki, we'll be back later.
We'll definitely...
definitely get you out of here.
Kaneki, where are you?
Is that...?!
Hold it!
What are you doing here, rabbit?!
Is he that guy from before?
Mr. Mado!
Fire! Fire!
What?!
Up there!
It's no use!
It's not working!
They're closing in harder than I thought.
Their footsteps are... It's all right.
It sounds like they all got in successfully.
Miss Irimi, that's amazing.
Hinami, I'm sure you'll be able to do it, too.
Kaya, how is CCG moving?
They've split into three forces.
CCG has the upper hand.
Hmm...
Then there's little choice.
We'll need to buy them a little time.
Kaya, look after Hinami.
Right.
You...! You, at last...!
Is he really this strong?
What's pushing him this far?
Is it because of me?
I don't have time to deal with him right now.
You won't get away!
Who was that other one just now?
Hey...
That was a number three combo.
He's a tough human.
The S-rated... Bin Brothers...
What... are you?
I follow the strongest scent,
and I end up sharing a table with you,
Mister High C.
Keep your guard up.
Apparently, this is no ordinary ghoul.
What a charming mouth.
Allow me to give you a passionate baiser.
Let's go!
Taking on an S-rated alone?
Can I do it, too, Mr. Mado?!
Amon, how do you suppose a
human of inferior physical capabilities
can prevail in a fight against a ghoul?
Certainly, the building up of
their muscles and stamina is vital.
Hmm... That is true.
But fighting head-on against a ghoul,
you'll never be able to overpower them.
So, do you know what you can
do to close that gap and prevail?
No.
Number one combo!
Right!
Being wily, Amon.
As long as it's for the right cause,
any dirty tricks can be overlooked.
I have a quinque named
Kura among my collection.
It's suited to you.
If I ever die...
Amon, you should use it.
Mr. Mado!
I can't afford to let it all end here.
Not until I have avenged you.
Kaneki...
Don't go being so careless,
you damn bonehead!
Nishiki!
Yo, my dumb sister!
What are you doing here?
Ayato...
Team one has taken control of
the annex's third-floor north exit.
Team two has taken control of the
main building second-floor west exit.
Shinohara, how are you coming?
We've taken control of the
fifth floor and parking level.
We're heading for the roof.
Copy that.
This reminds me of the good old days, huh?
Yeah.
They were all good men.
This is Shinohara. We've arrived at the roof.
There are no Aogiri here.
Something's not right.
Mr. Shinohara!
Amon! Are you all right?
Mr. Shinohara, actually...
Hmm? What's happening?
Maru, it's him.
The one-eyed owl.
Shinohara, leave only those distinguished men
who you don't mind dying with you.
If you guys can't handle him, then nobody can.
Merely dying for no reason
won't even buy any time.
Challenge him with as few men as possible.
That is all.
Though the city sleeps,
its buildings are always
under construction
Urban planning carries on
Its belt lines morphing, snakes interlocking,
stirring up endorphins,
and off you go, go, go
Souls ascend up into the night sky
Their procession and
their faith both resembling
an aberrant riddle
Our as-yet-empty tomorrows
are an all but black shade of gray
Without any possibilities
an all but black shade of gray
Ah, tonight, you're the one I want
Saints
Ah, I want you to signal the end
Even when I'm depressed,
riding you clears my mind in no time.
On days when my
good-for-nothing subordinates,
or pressure from above brings me down,
riding you like this invigorates me completely!
You're the best partner ever!
"Following 11th Ward charge --"
Hmm? My keys...
Yahoo!
Impossible!
"One minute later --"
"Next time: 'Ghoul'"
"Layout: Katsuya Yamada"