The status of one who can't see the effort
of someone trying to protect something...
...is lower than this watchtower!
I have arrested the
viscount due to his interference.
Standing by at the watchtower.
The assistant was injured...
Show me your injury.
I wasn't going to hide it from you.
'Cause you'd get mad if I did.
Idiot...
Th-This just now was...
Sorry, I did it without permission!
Shirayuki.
The next time I touch you,
I will tell you before I do.
At that time, please tell me how you feel.
Can you hear me, Shirayuki?
Well, shall we head back?
It'll be dark soon, so we should hurry.
A girl like that...
To leave a girl like that around
with no social status to speak of...
It's trickery...
Kiki, Zen will bring that girl with us.
Yeah.
Everyone, are you ready?
Yes, sir!
Her hands... are hot...
Zen's voice that had called
my name over and over
was tinged with warmth, and lit
a fire in a color I hadn't seen before...
"Episode 11: Encountering...
A Color for the First Time"
What should I do, Shirayuki?
For the prince's party to
accompany just me to the island...
You won't last if you're that nervous.
But Shirayuki, it's the prince! The prince!
Kihal!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Are you ready to leave?
Y-Yes, your highness!
I think the fastest way from here to Yuris island
would be to go through this mountain pass
and come out along the coast.
Calmly...
Calmly... So no one will
think anything is strange...
Yes, I think that will be fine.
Shirayuki, are you here to see Kihal off?
Y-Y-Yeah, th-that's right...
How's your injury?
Oh, it's fine. Ryu's treating it.
I see.
Don't you think Shirayuki's been
strange since the bird handler test?
Yeah. But Zen looks the same as usual.
That's the strange part.
Zen said or did something, I'm sure.
Wh-What did he--?!
I don't know.
Hey, what are you all gathered around for?
We're leaving!
Yes, sir!
Aw man, I wanted to go, too.
Leaving that aside...
Hey, Miss, when you and the master
were alone together at the watchtower...
...did he scold you harshly?
Huh?
N-No, he didn't.
Of course not. That's not what it was, was it?
H-Huh...?
Oh, I have to get to work. See you later!
Huh? Wait... Hey!
Jeez, it's hard to get anything out of her.
Wh-What's wrong with me?
It's been three days already,
so I thought I'd have calmed down by now,
but when I saw Zen's face,
I got flustered again...
Please tell me how you feel.
This is different from everything
I've told Zen up until now.
Zen, what should I tell you...?
You want to use the birds as a means
of communication for the kingdom?
Yes. Kihal took the test as
a representative bird handler.
As a result, we decided to implement the system.
Of course, we will acquiesce
with your demand to protect the birds.
However, we would like some of your
people to come to the castle with the birds
to train the soldiers in how to handle them.
Is that...
...true?
For you, who have been
clashing with the hunters,
I believe it will be hard for you to accept
the proposition of the kingdom, though...
Will you show us something
to make us trust your sincerity?
The apology of Lord Brecker,
and ten million dil in acquiescence money.
This is what we request.
H-Hey...
That is what he says. Your highness?
I'll do what I can to obtain
the viscount's apology,
but ten million dil, huh?
What do you think, Kiki?
Let's see...
Then, if we prepare twice that,
does that mean you will agree to the terms?
If we use money to buy authority
and make you obey,
we will be no different from the viscount.
I do not believe that the sincerity
you desire will come from that.
Huh?
I have spoken disrespectfully, your highness.
Please allow us to work with you!
Yeah, we're counting on you on our end, too.
Yay! All right!
Prince!
Are you a real prince?
S-Stop, you little--
Yup, I'm the real thing.
Wow! A prince! Wow!
Hey, what's the castle like?
--When are you going back?
--Do you wanna eat some, Prince?
Kids, you can have an audience
with the prince one at a time.
--His retainer!
--The real thing!
Oh, a sword! A sword!
What do they mean by "the real thing"...?
He did a fine job of seeing through us.
I thought all nobility
and royalty were the same,
but he appears to be completely
different from the viscount.
Yeah.
Taking a walk, your highness?
May I join you?
You can stop talking like that now.
You got it.
Where's Kiki?
I invited her, but she left it to me.
Left what to you?
Zen, did something happen
between you and Shirayuki?
Something happened, right?
A kiss... I kissed her.
Huh?
What?!
Really? It wasn't a dream or anything?!
I wouldn't dream that!
And? What did Shirayuki say?
She didn't say anything...
Nothing?
She didn't respond?
She looked surprised and turned red.
That girl did?!
What? It wasn't a dream
or an illusion or anything!
She turned red...
I have had feelings
for Shirayuki for a long time.
When I touched her... I became sure of that...
I want to tell her that as a prince of Clarines.
Zen, I'm sure she...
Hm?
Never mind.
Wh-What?
I don't serve you just because
you're Prince Zen of Clarines, you know.
I know.
I've cooked the riko fruit.
Okay, then grind it.
I'll weigh the rudra leaves.
Okay!
What are you doing, Miss, Ryu?
We're preparing a medicinal tea.
The chief herbalist has had consecutive
all-nighters, so her stamina is at its limit.
Because of that, she's in a bad mood.
But if we give her
delicious tea, she'll be nicer.
You're making it? Not just giving her tea?
Since we make medicines here,
we're going to make medicinal tea.
It's done!
It's bitter and sour!
What if we dissolved
julia flowers and rock sugar in it?
It'll lose half its efficacy if we do that.
We have to mix in something
that produces similar effects...
What about roka?
Hm?
It smells similar, and it's sweet, right?
I've never steeped it
in hot water before, but...
I have to do work...
Were you able to sleep a little?
Hm?
Chief herbalist, here's some roka tea!
Roka tea...?
It smells good!
It's delicious!
This would be good to steep in
anti-inflammatory medicines for kids.
It's the perfect sweetness for
cutting the bitterness of medicine.
I see. Are there are a lot of
kids who don't like medicine?
Even so, I can't believe you
guys thought to make roka tea.
Obi thought of it.
Huh?!
Really?
Now that you mention it, you went to the
roka garden with Shirayuki and Ryu, right?
Oh, it was nothing.
Just a thought from an amateur.
I don't think Shirayuki and Ryu would've been
able to make this roka tea by themselves.
You're a good influence on each other, huh?
Make sure you keep close the things
that can widen your perspective, everyone.
Shirayuki, once you're
done with that, you can go.
What, already?
Yeah, we've done more
than enough for today already.
B-But... um, if I don't
concentrate on something...
...it'll be bad... I mean...
What will?
Huh? S-Something will...
Shirayuki, if you're worried about something...
...you should write it down.
I even made Ryu worry. It's no good.
I can't let things continue like this...
I need...
I need some time to think by myself...
The forest...
Hm? You want to go?
Yeah, if I can.
If it's not being used for training,
it should be okay to go in...
Shall I take you?
Even though it's on the
castle grounds, it's still far...
Hmm... She's not talking at all anymore.
Shirayuki!
Oh, Master, and everyone! You're back early.
No, we're right on schedule.
What about you guys?
What're you doing all the way out here?
Shirayuki...?
C'mon, Miss. Why are you hiding?
I-It was so sudden... I was surprised...
What?
All right! Miss, run away!
Huh?
--What?
--It's fine, just hurry! Run to the forest!
Wh-What?
She ran away, huh?
Because you told her to!
Me? Oh, no.
You're the one who made her
want to run, didn't you, Master?
Mitsuhide, Kiki, Obi. I'll be back.
Wait at the castle.
Yes, Prince Zen.
Hang in there, Miss.
Wh... What should I do...?
I ran without thinking...
Why did I do something so pointless...?
Shirayuki!
Shirayuki, wait!
I... I can't face you right now, Zen!
Shirayuki!
I won't chase you, so please stop.
S-Sorry...
Why are you apologizing?
Besides, normally, I'd be the
one that can't face you right now.
Huh? No, that surprised me, but...
Was it the part where I said
to tell me how you feel next time?
The first time we met was in a forest, too, huh?
Shirayuki, why don't we stay
here together for a little bit?
Okay.
Oh, right. The talks with
the bird handlers went well.
Really? I'm glad.
We're going to form the squad after this,
so Kihal will probably come to the castle.
The wind that blows through
over there feels the best.
Zen, do you come to this forest often?
Hm? In the past I did, to take a break.
But after I started coming in
and out to practice riding,
it stopped being a place where I could relax...
Now, I don't come that much anymore.
I like the forest outside better.
I see.
Right now, you're here,
so it's different, though.
Just that is enough.
That's a nice sound...
Yeah.
It was then that I realized...
After meeting Zen and spending time with him...
In the feelings that
I continuously faced Zen with...
There were still emotions that I hadn't found...
Zen...
I love you, Zen...
You're so dear to me, and I respect you,
and I want to be your strength, but...
Now, I realize that I'm in love with you, too...
So...
I don't know if it's okay to want to look
at you the same way as I have until now...
I want that, too.
Shirayuki, the royal title I hold
may not be able to protect you.
I don't know how much I will be able to
give back in return for what I get from you.
But even so, I want to be with you from now on.
I wish for you to be by my side.
I swear, upon our meeting...
I will protect the desires
of us both with my body.
In order to do so, it might be
strange to ask you to help me,
but you certainly give me strength.
Therefore...
Will you take this hand, Shirayuki?
Yes, Prince Zen.
There's something
I've thought about for a long time.
Ever since I found out that my own
social status sometimes constrains others,
I couldn't help but think about it.
Hey, Mitsuhide.
Yes?
What if someday...
I found a person dear to my heart
and wanted to be with them...
When that person responds to my feelings,
do you think I can believe
that it's a response from their heart...?
That it's not something they are
saying because they cannot disobey me...?
Will I be able to believe that?
Do you think I will ever be able to
meet someone who I can believe needs me?
Thank you, Shirayuki.
Zen's voice that called
my name was tinged with warmth
and lit a fire in my heart...
Shirayuki's eyes trembled kindly
From now on, I'm sure time after time...
...time after time, the warmth of this day...
...the memory of this day...
...will give me courage.
Open Castle Day?
Zen...
I-I'm not use to stuff like this...
Do your best. We're here, too.
Here it comes! The climax of today's play!
"Episode 12: Goodbye to the Beginning"