Mom... Mom...
Miss Rize...
Long time no see, Kaneki.
What happened? You've been
through the wringer, haven't you?
That's hilarious.
The master is here.
How far did you count?
Five hundred... fifty... nine...
--Five hundred... fifty... two...
--I want to fill this bucket.
--Five hundred... thirty...
--Yamori ordered me to count out loud
backward by sevens from one thousand.
--eight...
--This instruction, which I
didn't understand at first,
--is something I now realize was
to keep me as sane as possible.
--Five hundred... thirty... one...
--is something I now realize was
to keep me as sane as possible.
--I was clinging to these numbers.
--Five hundred...
--twenty... four...
--Meanwhile, Yamori took my hands and feet...
again and again, and again, and again,
and again, and again, and again,
and AGAIN...
--Five hundred...
--and again...
--ten...
--Every time my
fingers and toes grew back in,
--Five hundred...
--I knew that I had become a monster.
--three...
Good morning.
Miss Rize? You're alive?
It doesn't really matter, does it?
Tell me, Kaneki, what kind
of person was your mother?
You said "Mom" a moment ago.
Is that her?
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Is that you, Kaneki?
Hey, Mom...
--You're adorable,
aren't you? What are you doing?
--How do you read this word?
--You're adorable,
aren't you? What are you doing?
She would always take
each kanji that I couldn't read,
and carefully write down the
pronunciation next to it for me.
Where is your mother going?
To work.
Where is this?
My dad's reading room.
What was he like?
I don't know. He died
before I can remember.
I just know that I came to
love reading because of the books
that my dad left behind.
Weren't you lonesome, all by yourself?
Mm-mm. I had my dad's books,
and my mom was very nice to me.
She really was a terrific person.
She went to work, and did all the housework,
and never once scowled,
or caused anyone any trouble,
and treated everyone equally kindly.
My mom was my pride.
Ken... it's okay to feel loss.
Nice boys like you can
be happy with just that.
Mm-hmm.
It's better to be hurt than to hurt others.
Nice people can be happy with just that.
That's what she taught me.
She was very nice and wonderful, huh?
Which is why you're going through all this.
Kaneki, you're a fine one.
Do you know why I'm
so particular... toward you?
I don't know if you realize this or not,
but your regenerative
powers are extraordinary.
All thanks to Kanou's experiment.
He made you a ghoul using Rize.
One eye. Rize's scent.
I'm talking about you, Kaneki.
Do you know about the
Chinese red-headed centipede?
I want to put this in your ear.
You don't mind, do you?
N-No... Don't... Please...
I beg you... No...! No...!
Don't! Don't!
Oh, no! How fascinating!
I want to kill you! I want to eat you!
Wanna kill you!
Wanna kill you! Wanna kill you!
Is it okay if I kill
you now? Can I eat you now?
You want me to kill you?!
You want me to eat you?!
Kill me... Kill me... Please, kill me...
It's better to be hurt than to hurt others.
Have you really lived your life believing that?
That's what my mom taught me. So I...
You obeyed what she
told you to do. What is that?
How dull.
Don't you want him to go to hell?
Are you sure your mother was
as nice and wonderful as you think?
What's that, there?
An allowance.
To whom?
My mom's sister.
She would always say
she's struggling financially,
and ask my mom for money.
Part-time work during the day,
garbage collection by night,
and work at home during her
free time. Mom never stopped working.
Mom? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
And then?
And then...
She overworked herself.
I was all alone after that.
I had no place to live anymore.
Hey, Kaneki! How long
are you gonna stay home?!
--Do you know how hard it is for
me when you stay home like this?!
--Oh, yeah... There was just one...
...place where I could go...
Kaneki, if you were a ghoul,
would you eat Yoshikawa in Class 2?
The one you like so much?
N-No, I wouldn't!
And I don't like her that much.
Hide was the only moral support I had.
He's a dear friend, isn't he?
But you're going to lose
your dear friend, too, huh?
Huh?
And it's all your fault.
All of the disadvantage in this world
stems from a person's lack of ability.
The person who told me these
words was a real sack of crap,
but right now, I'm grateful to him.
Kaneki, I've come to understand
something well these last few days.
Never mind your body,
your mind is surprisingly tough, too.
So I devised a little plan.
A man and woman...
who love each other...!
You will choose which one I kill!
I let these two look after you until now.
Tell me, you were holding out
hope that help was coming, right?
You saw these two as your saviors, right?
So, which one?
If you don't choose, I'll kill them both.
How about I rephrase that?
Which one do you want to save?
Why... me...?
Why do I have to be the one to choose?
Come on, hurry up and choose.
I can't choose something like that!
It would be like I'm the one
doing the killing, wouldn't it?!
Pick one! Pick one! Pick one! Pick one!
The man? The woman?
The right one? The left one?
Pick one!
There's no way I can pick one!
If you have to kill someone, kill me!
All right. Very well.
Watch closely, now.
This one? How about this one?! No?!
Come on! Pick one! Pick one, I say!
She's gonna die! Well, Kaneki?
Come on! Come on! Pick one! Pick one!
Well?! Well?!
Well?!
Pick me, Mr. Kaneki!
Haru is... Haru is going to die!
Pick me! Me! Pick me, Kaneki!
She broke, didn't she?
It's all your fault.
N-Not me...
No... it's... it's my fault...
How are you just now getting it?
You'll just sit there blaming yourself,
and keep blaming yourself,
but going on blaming
yourself won't change anything.
You don't try to change. It's all your fault.
That much is obvious, isn't it?
Whose fault is it that
things ended up like this?
Coincidence? Accident? Fate?
There's no such thing as fate.
It's simply a combination of
one circumstance with another.
And who is it that
creates those circumstances?
Who is it?
It's you.
All of the disadvantage in this world
stems from a person's lack of ability.
He's right, isn't he?
This whole thing started
because you're such a fool
to the ways of the world.
You were a fool, and I tricked you.
The doctor did some tweaking,
and we got turned into a monster.
It's all because of you.
It's better to be hurt than to hurt others.
Which is why you're going through all this.
If you had been strong and killed Yamori,
those two would have been spared.
If you had chosen the man,
the woman might have been spared.
If only you had been strong at that moment.
Mrs. Ryoko...
S-Stop--Stop!
Then there's what's to come...
Touka...
Hinami...
The one you hold most dear...
Hide!
You're a monster.
N-No... I'm...
Why didn't you open up to me?
Once again, you failed to choose. And so...
this... happens...
You see? This is the
way of life that you chose.
This is the future that you chose.
Why are you crying? Why are you sobbing?
You choose to be hurt
rather than to hurt others, right?
You're nice and wonderful.
But while it seems like you're choosing both,
you're really forsaking both.
Your mother was the same way.
If she had turned aside her
intolerable sister's requests,
she wouldn't have died from overwork.
Shut up.
What a foolish mother, huh? If she loved you,
she should have abandoned her foolish sister.
Stop it.
--That's what you really
wanted her to do, wasn't it?
--Stop talking.
--That's what you really
wanted her to do, wasn't it?
Mom...
Why...? Why did you leave me all alone...?
I missed you... I hate being alone...
I wish... I wish you would have chosen me...!
I wish you would have lived... for me!
Even if it meant forsaking your aunt?
Even if it meant that!
Even if it meant hurting someone?
Even if it meant taking her life?
Even if it meant that!
Good boy.
That's right, Kaneki.
There are times when you
have to give up on one thing
to preserve the other.
Your mother couldn't do that.
That isn't kindness. That's just being weak.
She didn't have the strength--
the resolve to turn her back.
Can you still remain
on the side of being hurt?
Can you abide someone like Yamori?
No... I can't!
If Aogiri gets much stronger,
they'll soon do a lot of damage
to the 20th Ward, as well.
I won't allow that to happen.
Your precious Hide,
and your friends at Anteiku
might also go through what just happened.
Anyone who tries to take my
place from me will get no mercy.
Do you have that kind of strength?
Yes.
Are you saying you accept me?
No. I'm not saying that.
I can always surpass you.
Even if that is the wrong choice?
I'm not the one who's wrong.
What's wrong... is the world!
That will do...
Kaneki.
To live is to devour others.
Eat.
I am... a ghoul.
Kaneki...
our special fun time has come to an end.
The doves are closing in on this place.
It's my job to take them on, you see.
Aogiri's goal is to
eliminate anyone in their way.
That includes humans,
of course, but ghouls, as well.
The ghouls who stand
opposed to Aogiri's cause--
the ones where you were
working--"Anteiku," was it?
They are also one of Aogiri's...
targets for elimination.
Kaneki! Let me take from you!
Here at the end, let me devour all of you!
Hilarious.
You really are an inconsequential man.
You truly are fantastic, all right!
Let me take from you!
Devour this.
Tell me, oh tell me, the way it works
Who is that inside of me?
That's foul.
Wha--? Y-You...
bit me?
Here in this broken-down,
broken-down world,
Almost like the intestines of
a fish on the verge of spoiling.
you laugh, without seeing a thing
I'm not letting go!
You think that after everything
else, something like that hurts?
I'm just so damaged, I hold my breath
Kill you... I'll kill you!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
I'll eat you! I'll make a sloppy mess of you!
Not even the truth, no not even the truth
I'll kill you!
can be unraveled now
I'll chomp you to death!
Freeze
Breakable, unbreakable;
shakable, unshakable
When I found you, it shook me
In this twisted world, I'm gradually
growing transparent and vanishing
Kaneki!
Don't look for me; don't look at me
I don't wish to hurt you in a world
of someone else's imagining
Remember who I am
My full, vivid self
Now...
Entangled in the loneliness
that fans out endlessly,
it's my turn.
stung by the memory
of smiling so innocently
I can't move, I can't move,
I can't move, I can't move!
Unraveling the world
Kaneki!
I've completely changed;
I couldn't change back
The two entwine; the couple penshes
Breakable, unbreakable;
shakable, unshakable
I won't defile you
In this shook-up, twisted world, I'm gradually
growing transparent and vanishing
What's one thousand minus seven?
Don't look for me; don't look at me
Before the future comes completely undone
I'll ask again.
caught in a pit of solitude
somebody set for me,
What's one thousand minus seven?
think back on who I am
What is one thousand minus seven?
My full, vivid self
Don't forget me, don't forget me
N-N-Nine hundred... ninety-three...
don't forget me, don't forget me
N-Nine hundred... eighty...
The change over me has me paralyzed
in an immutable object paradise
six...
Nine hundred... seventy...
Remember who I am
Nine hundred seventy-two...
Tell me, tell me,
--Nine hundred sixty... five...
--You tried to devour me.
So you have no room to complain...
is there someone inside of me?
if I eat you, do you?
"Layout: Katsuya Yamada"