CCG Base to 203,
trespassers reported in the
20th Ward at the Aqua Building.
Trespassers are believed
to be ghouls-- repeat, ghouls.
Proceed to location immediately.
Ah...
More! More!
Delicious!
It looks like they weren't kidding
when they called you a binge eater.
I hate being interrupted when I'm eating.
You don't know me, do you?
Yes, I do. You're a joyless
fellow that enjoys bothering others.
I've got orders from above.
I'm supposed to take you alive.
But then, before I do,
I can take a finger or two,
an arm or two, a leg or two...
You don't mind, do you?
A small toy for such a big body.
I'll bet you like playing house.
How adorable.
Let me...
take them from you.
Give them back. They're mine.
Give them back!
I'm not going to play with you.
Early this morning,
several unidentified male bodies
were discovered in the Aqua Building,
a commercial facility in Tokyo's 20th Ward.
What is believed to be
saliva belonging to ghouls
was retrieved from the bodies,
"Multiple Unidentified Bodies Found"
and the incident is being
investigated as a ghoul crime.
It's not that funny, is it?
I'm just saying, you can't have
a first date at a bookstore, right?
Why not? She might be thrilled, you know!
I'll state for the record, that
won't happen. Case dismissed.
Huh? Then first, I'll take her
out to Big Girl, just the two of us,
and we'll get a burger.
I'm giving you a serious answer.
No, it's great! It's great, just like you!
But as a date, it'll be a flop.
What, is everything I do wrong?
Hide, what would you do?
"Anteiku"
What, is everything I do wrong?
Hide, what would you do?
"Anteiku"
Listen up. You have to choose a place
where the girl will be
pleased when making a date.
"Anteiku"
Such as?
Huh? S-Such as...
"Anteiku"
Hide, you don't even know.
If I knew,
--I wouldn't be here spending
my afternoon off like this
--These last few days have seen a string
--out having a date with you.
--of predatory ghoul
attacks in the 20th Ward,
--I guess that's true.
--of predatory ghoul
attacks in the 20th Ward,
"Being Investigated as Ghoul Predation"
and according to CCG's 20th Ward Branch,
they are investigating the
possibility that the incidents
--That's pretty close, huh?
--are the result of the
same culprit. In other news...
So? So, so, so?
Who is she? The cute girl you mentioned?
--Oh, that's her, right?
--Yes, indeed.
--No it isn't.
Sure, she's cute, too...
Excuse me!
One cappuccino, please! And you, Kaneki?
--I'm not done with this, yet.
--One cappuccino.
And also, what's your name?
Hide!
It's Kirishima Toka.
Miss Toka! Are you seeing anyone?!
Stop that, you idiot!
Hmm, how lovely.
If I get kicked out
of here, then what do I do?!
This shop is the one
place where she and I both--
She's... the one.
Give it up.
Huh?
You and her would be Beauty and whatever.
The Beast!
Well then...
Now that I've seen you lovelorn,
"Egg of the Black Goat"
Well then...
Now that I've seen you lovelorn,
"Egg of the Black Goat"
I think I'll be off.
Wait, Hide...
See you later, Miss Toka.
Good luck, delusional Kaneki!
"Egg of the Black Goat"
I guess sometimes you get lucky.
Yeah. Imagine, liking
the same novelist that I do!
Yeah, who was it again? Takasaki Sen?
No, Takatsuki Sen!
We're going to go to the
bookstore together this coming Sunday.
Oh, yeah? I'm not sure how
good a bookstore date is gonna be,
but have a good time.
Yeah.
I have to say, this is getting ugly.
Word is that eating one person
is supposed to last them a month,
but these binge eaters are something else.
Write them off as animals,
and they'd eat any
number of people, wouldn't they?
Ghouls as animals, huh?
They're worse than livestock,
since they're not good for anything.
That's true.
Mr. Kaneki, what's your
favorite work by Takatsuki?
It would have to be his debut book.
It was a breakout hit, after all.
The delicacy amidst all
the extremeness, you might say.
Y-Yes, exactly. To have
that much talent in writing,
and still be in his teens when it came out--
Are you all right?
I-I'm fine...
Er, I mean... that is...
Miss Rize, you don't eat much, do you?
Huh? Oh... Actually,
um, I'm on a dietary regimen...
Excuse me, I need the restroom.
She's a girl...
Thank you very much for today.
No, thank you. It-It's been fun.
The truth is, I... live near where
these recent incidents have been...
Oh, the ghouls?
I'm awfully bad at handling this.
Just thinking about it even
now, I can't stop from trembling.
That's all right.
Please, rest assured. I'll see you home.
Yes, so then Hide asked me, "Which
do you like better, me or novels?"
He sounds like a funny person.
Yes.
Was there something that
served to turn you on to books?
My dad left us a lot of books in our house.
Ah...
I lost my dad before I can even
remember. I liked the books he left,
and while my mom was out
working, I spent the time reading them.
Then, ever since my mom died...
You know, Hide is the
only one I've ever told this to.
Is that right? Ah...
It's this way.
Oh, okay.
Toka, is something wrong?
Mm-mm, not really.
Well, I'm right over here, so...
Miss Rize...
Um, if you wouldn't
mind, can I see you again?
We do have a similar taste
in books, and we're the same age...
There's a lot we have in common, huh?
Mr. Kaneki...
Y- Yes?
The truth is, I noticed you.
The way you were looking at me.
Huh? Then, you mean, you, too...
Yes.
I, too...
happen to be interested...
in you.
Ah, delicious!
Mr. Kaneki,
there's something I like even
more than reading. Know what it is?
It's pulling out all the organs of someone
who isn't trying to run away from me.
That expression! It's fantastic!
Would you let me...
thrill myself even more?!
No way! No way! No way!
No way! No way! No way! No way!
I caught you!
Mr. Kaneki!
I'm going to gently scramble
up your insides for you now, okay?
Uh-oh, did you die?
That's too bad. I really did like you.
There's just the right amount of fat on you;
you look nice and soft, and easy to eat.
How...
could... this...
His abdominal organs are ruptured.
--What is this?
--We'll begin operating immediately.
Where is this place?
I thought I was on a date with Miss Rize...
Prepare for organ transplant.
Without the consent of the next of kin?
Organ? Next of kin?
What exactly are they talking about?
Dr. Kano!
I will accept full responsibility!
Transfer her organs into him!
It's warm...
Is this...?
That's strange. What's going on here?
Mr. Kaneki!
Is this all you're going to eat?
Oh, right. Your friend came by again today.
Ah, Dr. Kano...
How are we feeling, Kaneki?
I hear you haven't eaten
anything since you were admitted,
but there doesn't particularly
seem to be anything wrong.
Um...
my sense of taste... isn't right...
Sense of taste?
It's like everything tastes icky...
That could be psychological in nature.
It was a pretty serious accident, after all.
There's no rush.
Take all the time you need to heal.
I'll be by again later.
Nothing particularly wrong?
It almost seems like the events
of that whole day with Miss Rize
were something that never really happened.
But one thing is for sure...
Ever since then, something has been...
something has been strange.
"Kaneki!
Congratulations on your discharge!
Presenting some leftover
high-quality ingredients from my place,
along with your favorite hamburger.
I hope you appreciate it! Wah-ha-ha!
P.S. When you're up to
it, come on back to school.
It's rough here on my own."
Hide...
Thanks.
But I'm sorry.
A ghoul doesn't have
any need to eat this much
in this short amount
of time in the first place.
One dead body will allow
them to survive for a month or two.
Mr. Ogura, can't ghouls be satisfied
by eating the same food as humans do?
No, ghouls are only able to
derive their nutrition from people.
Not to mention that their
tongues work differently than ours do.
"Ogura Hisashi, Ghoul Expert"
Not to mention that their
tongues work differently than ours do.
When they eat human food,
it tastes incredibly awful to them.
Their tongues work
differently than ours do...
It tastes incredibly awful to them...
Oh, no...
Presenting your favorite hamburger.
Hide...
Did you go out and buy this just for me?
This can't be real.
"Hide"
Friend of yours?
Yes.
He was supposed to
get out of the hospital today,
but I can't reach him.
I went to see him several times, too,
but I got turned away.
Hmm... If it were me I'd cut
off ties with anyone as rude as that.
Kaneki and I have been
best friends since we were kids.
Best friends, huh?
Hello? Kaneki? How are you
feeling? I was just at the bookstore
in front of the station,
and Akatsuki what's-his-name
is doing a book signing,
so I thought I'd tell you.
Anyhow, give me a call
when you're feeling better.
"The Akatsuki Sen book signing is now over."
People... People...
Children...
--Woman...
--Flesh...
--Girl...
--Man...
--Flesh...
--Family...
--Children... Boy... Woman...
--Flesh... Flesh... Flesh...
--Child... Boy...
--Flesh... Flesh...
--Flesh... Flesh... Flesh...
Flesh!
Whoa, that man...
Don't get involved, you dummy!
What is this?
I know what's causing it!
Transfer her organs into him!
Blades such as knives or
kitchenware cannot hurt them.
If that's true...
If that's true... If that's true...
then this...!
What am I supposed to do now?
Kill a person... take their flesh!
What... am I...? It's almost as though I'm...
That scent...
It's the first time I'm
smelling it, but it seems so familiar...
A sweet aroma,
like Mom's home cooking...
There's something over
here that even I can eat!
Where is it? Where is it?
Where is it? Where is it?!
It's close...
A ghoul...
A human!
How could I have been
enticed here by the scent of a corpse?!
You're a ghoul... right?
What's the matter? Are you all right?
My name's Kazuo.
It's been a long time for me,
so I can't share too much with you,
but here, eat--
Sheesh,
don't go plundering
my feeding grounds. Hmm?
I've never seen you before.
For that matter, why is only
one of your eyes red? That's nasty.
You know what you get for
looting someone else's territory, right?
I-I wasn't... I didn't know...
I just happened to be passing by...
Okay, imagine this. Your girlfriend
is naked and lying on the ground.
Then someone else there
with his pants down says to you,
"I wasn't doing anything.
I just happened to be here."
That's the same as what you're telling me.
If it were me, I'd kill the guy.
That's why I'm killing you,
as punishment for trespassing
on my feeding grounds--
Whose feeding grounds, did you say?
Since when were these your feeding grounds,
Nishiki?
Toka...
I know she's dead, right?
The binge eating woman?
And that makes these your feeding grounds?
The task of distributing
the feeding grounds Rize stole
to the weaker ghouls, and
otherwise managing the 20th Ward...
belongs to those of us at Anteiku.
Huh?! A bunch of fence-sitters like Anteiku
have no right to go
picking over every little thing!
This was my feeding ground in
the first place, before Rize came--
Because you were weak.
Being insulted by a
smart-mouthed punk younger than I am
is something that really pisses me off.
Is it?
Enough!
You'll have to cut deeper than that!
Will I?
Can I go even harder next time?
Take your corpse with you, beansprout.
You want this?
You're not eating?
Then again, only one
of your eyes is different...
You're the one who was with Rize.
Why weren't you eaten? Then again...
your eye...
Please help me...!
I know you may not believe
this, but I'm human. And yet...
I want to eat that...
I want to eat it so bad I can't help it...
But if I do...
I won't be human anymore!
If you're in that much pain, then eat.
No way!
No way! No way! No way!
There's no way I can eat
something like that, right?
What is this? What is it to be a ghoul?
Killing people... killing each other...
I'm not like that!
I'm... human!
This is ridiculous.
Why not give in already?
If you don't have the nerve to eat...
then I'll give you a hand!
"Next Time" "Incubation"