Help! Somebody!
Mr. Tsukiyama!
Thank goodness! Mr. Tsukiyama, help--
Kaneki, bon appétit!
Tell me, oh tell me, the way it works
Who is that inside of me?
Here in this broken-down,
broken-down world,
you laugh, without seeing a thing
I'm just so damaged,
I hold my breath and freeze
Breakable, unbreakable;
shakable, unshakable
When I found you, it shook me
In this twisted world, I'm gradually
growing transparent and vanishing
Don't look for me; don't look at me
I don't wish to hurt you in a world
of someone else's imagining
Remember who I am
I heard another dove has shown up.
How many does this make now?
I'm scared to go on my own.
The 20th Ward is starting to get dangerous.
Kaneki, that will be all for today.
I've asked Kaya to take over.
Oh, okay. Huh? Where's Touka?
Touka said she was feeling ill.
Kaneki, why don't
you home go and see her?
Oh, but...
Touka lives just upstairs, after all.
"Kirishima Touka Ayato"
Kirishima... Ayato?
Okay Touka, keep an eye on Hinami, okay?
Hinami! You help out Big Sister, okay?
Oh, hi.
--Well?
--Huh?
What are you here for?
Oh, um, I heard you were
feeling ill, so I'm seeing how you are.
Mm-hmm... Empty-handed?
Um, well...
Big Brother, how do you read this?
Hmm? Which one?
Let's see, that's "orange osmanthus."
--Is that a flower, too?
--Mm-hmm.
I'll get some coffee started.
Oh, Touka, I can...
It's okay. You're helping
Hinami with her reading, right?
But if you're not well...
I just ate too much.
Huh? You ate too much...?
She wouldn't...
Non!
Yoriko?!
But why?
Yoriko, what's wrong?
Sorry for coming unannounced,
but you weren't at school today, Touka.
And you came just to check on me?
Mm-hmm. And also...
Huh?! No way! Touka, you're not...!
His name is Kaneki, and...
Touka, I made this for you. Eat it with him!
Huh? Hold on. You've got the wrong idea.
Hey, Yoriko!
Uh, have I done something wrong?
What are you planning to do with that?
Eat it! Yoriko made it for me, after all.
Huh?
When you ate too much
and made yourself sick...
Thank you for this food.
She must be a really good friend.
What do I do? What do I do?
What do I do to be able to
savor the partaking of Kaneki?
That's it!
The ultimate meal requires...
third-party intervention...
in a maestoso location...
with Kaneki reaching a crescendo...
until at last I...
fortissimo!
Oh, Kaneki...!
That smarts. Mr. Yomo
really could break my arm.
Mr. Nishio!
Well, how about we start with his arm?
Whoo-hoo!
After what Mr. Nishio did to Hide and me...
U-Um, excuse me...
You're overdoing it a little, aren't you?
K-Kaneki... Ken...
Are you pals with this piece
of crap Nishiki or something?
No, I wouldn't say that.
Then would you mind not bothering us?
We were just about to cannibalize him.
C-Cannibalize?
Huh? You wanna go at it, boy?
He's way slower than Mr. Yomo.
Am I seeing the results of my training here?
You bastard!
I hit him...
Damn you... Playing the goody-goody...
Is this it?
Nishiki!
Where have you been?!
You've gotten so hurt again!
I'm so hungry it's driving me crazy.
Don't Kimi.
But that man is...
Yeah... The punk ass who tore
a huge hole through my belly...
Miss Kimi, you're human, right?
Why are you and a ghoul...
I want him at my side.
Even though Mr. Nishio kills other people?
I'm sure that as long as he
doesn't kill my parents or siblings,
I'll keep turning a blind eye to it.
He needs the corpses, after all.
You... don't say.
Kaneki, what can I do to help Nishiki?!
If he doesn't eat any flesh, he'll probably...
But how am I supposed to...?
Miss Kimi, I'll...
see what I can do.
Thank you.
I'll do whatever I can do.
I'll trust Kaneki to do the rest.
Bonsoir, mademoiselle.
I need your assistance
with a little something.
It's locked.
So there are people who,
even knowing someone is a
ghoul, still want to stick by them.
A rose and a note?
Only one person would do this.
"Kaneki, let's enjoy
dinner at midnight tonight.
I already brought the woman
you were speaking with in the park.
Why don't the three of us have
an enjoyable evening together?"
Miss Kimi!
Mr. Nishio!
Kimi hasn't come back...
Damn it!
Why would Tsukiyama...? This is
terrible! Why did this happen? Why?!
I'm the one that Tsukiyama is after.
I'll go there and rescue Miss Kimi.
I'm coming with you.
In your condition? What are
you talking about?! That's crazy!
How am I supposed to lie down
at home when Kimi is in this mess?
I have to go.
Kaneki, do you like Beethoven?
Tsukiyama!
Nishio, I don't remember inviting you.
Give me back Kimi!
Unfortunately, I can't do that.
She is here to add
spice to tonight's banquet.
I want to let Kaneki eat
her at her maximum freshness.
Huh?!
To be more precise,
I want to eat Kaneki while he eats her!
That's what I want!
You dirty bastard...
Y-You're perverted.
Perverted? This is surprising.
Supposing that's how you feel...
Kaneki, you're the one
who's making me do this,
so you bear responsibility for it.
You'd better realize
how delicious you really are.
Mr. Nishio!
You take a load off over there.
You're still pretty flat-footed.
Just like a baby chick, toddling about.
Listen up. This...
is a real punch.
And... this...
is a real kick.
Now then, what kind of attack
would you like to take next?
How about this one?
It's a regular sneak attack.
Touka!
My, my, this is bad news.
It's been so long...
since I've gotten a scratch.
I'm gonna kick your ass so hard,
you won't be able to eat, Tsukiyama.
You've got a dirty
mouth there, Miss Kirishima.
He's not hurt!
Long ago, you were
well-honed, like a sharpened knife.
If you were as strong now as you were then,
that injury would have taken
longer than ten seconds to heal.
That was just by way of greeting.
It wouldn't be any fun if it came
to an end right away, would it?
My goodness, you are a handful. However...
That's also what makes you so cute.
Your reactions are as quick as ever.
Back then, you were fourteen,
and I was eighteen.
Those cold, piercing eyes
of yours, like crystal shards...
are something I can never forget.
You disgust me!
I'm getting nauseated!
I was pretty head over
heels for you back then.
I am not going to be eaten by you,
and I'm leaving here with Miss Kimi.
That was a good kick, Kaneki.
Oh, brother...
Let's see... Like this, right?
Now then, to have a sample...
Tres bien!
What a flavor this is!
Mingling so deeply over
my tongue in such harmony!
Damn! It's even greater than I imagined!
However, now I want
something even greater!
I don't want to allow Kaneki
Ken to come to an end like this!
Okay, now is the time
for me to treat you to her!
The coldness you possessed
back then was spectacular.
But right now, you're hopeless.
Something has ignited the heat in your eyes.
It's too bad, Miss
Kirishima. That's something...
you really didn't need.
Touka!
You're interrupting my dinner!
Stop! I'm the one you want to eat!
Have you forgotten?
I want to eat you as you eat.
How can you take people's lives so easily?
People's lives? I'm an
equal-opportunity carnivore.
If anything, when looking at life as a whole,
there are far more human lives to take.
But unlike them, humans are all we kill.
What is this ugly scar here?
Kimi...
Nishiki...
No... I really don't want to eat people.
We have no choice. It's just
like when humans eat cows or pigs.
But I feel bad for them.
It's okay. I'll do everything for you.
Work?
Yep. We can't go on living
like stray cats forever, right?
Don't worry. No one will find out.
Okay, I'm off.
Come back safely.
I'm off.
I got fired again.
Not again. Hmm? What?
You've gotten taller, Nishiki.
You look just like Dad.
Who's that?
The manager from where I work.
Which way did they run?!
Search over that way!
Sis! Sis!
Stay with me, Sis!
Nishiki... Keep on living, by yourself...
No! Sis! Don't you die! Don't you die!
Live...
You're the one who turned her in, all right.
P-Please, spare my life...
You reap what you sow; both you and Sis.
There's no way I'll ever trust anyone.
Hey...
Did you forget your change?
Huh? Oh...
Here.
Thank you very much.
She was a pale-looking girl.
But then, she may be useful for something.
That's a nice name.
Huh?
"Kimi," meaning "noble future."
Who thought of that, your mom or pop?
Hmm? Hey...
What? I don't get it.
Kaneki, you punk ass!
This wound just won't heal!
Flesh! I have to eat some flesh!
Nishiki?
Nishiki! What happened?! Is this blood?!
I'm sure glad I called out to you!
Let me feed on your flesh!
It's no use. I don't have the strength.
Nishiki, you're a ghoul?
Aww... Now I'll be reported,
and that'll be all for me.
My end will be the same
as Sis's. What a lousy life it's been.
Nishiki...
You know what? When you
first called out to me that day,
I'd lost my mom and dad
and my brother two years
younger than me in an accident.
I was so sad, I was
thinking I would rather be dead.
But Nishiki, you being
there for me saved me.
So...
it's okay. Live.
I don't need any more.
What are you, stupid?
It's hard for me to have faith in people.
But maybe being betrayed
by you wouldn't be so bad.
What is with you, for Pete's sake?
Ha! There's no way you can beat
me if you can't even use your kagune!
A ghoul's strength is
largely dependent on his kagune.
If your kagune is your engine,
then people's flesh is gasoline!
When you have a poor diet, you can
only deliver commensurate strength.
What he says is true.
Touka...
I didn't expect Yoriko's
cooking to affect me here...
Now then, that's enough of the sideshow.
You are becoming a pest.
Shut up!
Stop annoying me! Stop
annoying me! Stop annoying me!
Stop annoying me! Stop annoying me!
Let's be friends here, Nishio.
There's nothing...
There's nothing else...
Aside from Kimi, I have nothing else...
Lay a hand on her and I'll kill you...
Even if it costs me my life, I'll kill you!
If we don't do something...
A person's flesh is gasoline...
Fuel...
Touka...
At full strength,
who's stronger, you or Tsukiyama?
A long time ago, we were about even.
Listen, Touka...
You've had it. I'm this close to killing you.
Tsukiyama!
Here goes.
Mm-hmm.
Look away.
He belongs to me!
He belongs to you?
Are you dense?
There's not a single thing here...
that belongs to you.
Though the city sleeps,
its buildings are always
under construction
Urban planning carries on
Its belt lines morphing, snakes interlocking,
stirring up endorphins
and off you go, go, go
Souls ascend up into the night sky
Their procession and
their faith both resembling
an aberrant riddle
Our as-yet-empty tomorrows
are an all but black shade of gray
Without any possibilities
an all but black shade of gray
Ah, tonight, you're the one I want
Saints
Ah, I want you to signal the end
"Layout: Katsuya Yamada"
"Next time: 'Cloudburst'"