Yes, this is Control.
Yeah, it's Marude!
Give me a situation report!
A band of ghouls we believe to be
Aogiri Tree has attacked the branch--
What happened?!
He was the last one.
Hey, you, who are you?
All done?
Yeah.
Ready to go, Eto?
Mm-hmm, Mr. Tatara.
Tell me, oh tell me, the way it works
Who is that inside of me?
Here in this broken-down,
broken-down world,
you laugh, without seeing a thing
I'm just so damaged,
I hold my breath and freeze
Breakable, unbreakable;
shakable, unshakable
When I found you, it shook me
In this twisted world, I'm gradually
growing transparent and vanishing
Don't look for me; don't look at me
I don't wish to hurt you in a world
of someone else's imagining
Remember who I am
This is awful.
What do we know about them?
They're a band of ghouls
who call themselves Aogiri Tree.
We don't know precisely
how many of them there are,
but their leader is...
the One-Eyed King.
One-Eyed, huh?
Yomo, let's go back to Anteiku.
We're not getting many customers, are we?
It's because of the increase in doves.
At a time like this,
everyone is too wary to go outside.
Ah, welcome.
U-Um...
Is your manager here?
I asked you if your manager was here!
Th-The manager has stepped out for a bit...
Then where did he go?!
Hold on!
Huh?!
You just show up here
and what are you doing?!
If you've got business here,
at least order a cup of coffee.
What?!
Um, if you need something from
the manager, I can relay it to him.
There's something
I want to ask you guys, too.
Do you know Kamishiro Rize?
I'm Banjo Kazuichi.
I'm here from the 11th Ward.
I knew Miss Rize back in the 11th Ward.
So, what makes you think Rize is here?
When Miss Rize left the 11th Ward,
she had an interest in the coffee shop--
Why, that's--
Why do I smell Miss Rize on you?! Eh?!
Hey!
No rough stuff in the shop!
Mr. Banjo!
You him?
Huh? Eh?
Are you Miss Rize's man?
N-No, she and I aren't...
She and you?!
Y-You misunderstand! You misunderstand!
Mr. Banjo! Shake it off!
I'm so sorry!
He's out cold.
I knew it.
Sorry about our leader, here.
Wuss.
Shinohara and Amon, coming in.
Assistant Special Investigator Chino
and Senior Investigator Tainaka...
Not to mention Special
Investigator Arima's old partner,
Senior Investigator Hirako...
Special Investigator Kuroiwa is in on this, too?
Everyone have a seat.
As you may have already heard,
the 11th Ward Branch was attacked.
Despite the enemy only
occupying it temporarily before leaving,
according to police reports from
the scene, the number of survivors...
was zero.
Ah, he's coming to.
Are you all right?
Um, I'm sorry about earlier.
What's your name?
Kaneki.
Kaneki, huh? You're a
lot stronger than you look.
Oh, not at all...
So that's the reason why
Miss Rize chose you, is it?
Uh, it's not like that, Mr. Banjo.
Miss Rize and I weren't like that.
Then I was wrong?!
Yes.
Sorry! My bad! I apologize!
No, lift up your head--
No! If I don't do this,
I won't be able to live with myself!
So then, where is Miss Rize now?
Miss Rize is...
She is... no longer...
She isn't here anymore.
I-I see.
Yeah, I get it. She is a
capricious one, after all.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you.
Listen, Kaneki, I have a favor to ask of you.
A favor, you say?
Yeah. If you see her again,
I want you to tell her something for me.
Tell her to run.
Huh?
A few months ago,
a band of ghouls named Aogiri Tree
carved their way through the 11th Ward.
They have now set their sights on the doves,
in order to overthrow
us ghouls in the 11th Ward.
They are strong.
By now, all the doves in the 11th
Ward have likely been hunted down.
As of now, I'm one of their minor runners,
but this bunch is looking
for Miss Rize. I don't know why.
But I'm sure it can't be anything good.
Miss Rize?
They'll come after
the 20th Ward, too, in time.
Nobody's gonna blame you.
You should get running, too. Otherwise...
Mr. Banjo!
What are you screwing around here for, Banjo?
You want another beating until
you can't spit up any more blood? Huh?
A-Ayato...
H-Hey!
Touka!
Ayato...
So then, that is Touka's...
Yo. Long time no see, my dumb sister.
Where have you been
wandering around, you idiot?
I've been out learning about society.
Unlike you, who are
complacent in your peace.
You self-important little brat!
You're the brat. Look around you, dummy.
Is that long enough, Ayato?
Can we come in now?
Why are those two here, too?!
Forgive the intrusion.
Oh, now what do I do? Where could I be?
O-ho, I've located a police box!
How lucky for me!
The group's name is Aogiri Tree.
They have over two hundred
members that we know about.
There has never been an
incidence of this many ghouls
banding together before.
What could their objective be?
Who ever knows what
ghouls are thinking? However,
the 11th Ward has been
taken from us. That much is certain.
Once this fact gets around,
it is expected most of the ghouls
who have been acting on their own
will now join up with Aogiri Tree.
This will be a war
between humans and ghouls.
That's why you must
turn over your lives to me!
That is an order, by the way!
You have no right to refuse me!
From here on, the 11th
Ward special task force--
Excuse me!
I'm Mr. Shinohara's underling, Suzuya Juzo!
Sorry I'm late, but I got lost.
Ah, geez...
Please accept my regards.
Hey, Ayato...
Oh, my...
I'd heard that your older sister was here.
Aren't you both just gorgeous!
I'm so jealous.
I'm impressed that you found me, Yamori.
I was following Banjo. The men you
have under you are first-rate, huh?
M-Miss Rize isn't here!
It stinks in here.
It reeks of an odor I despise.
Hey, Nico, will this one do?
Sure, why not? Let's hurry up and kidnap him.
Yeah, right.
Kidnap? What kind of ego trip are you on?!
Ego trip?
Going on ego trips are
the right of the powerful.
Kaneki!
Get up or stay down? Which will it be?
If you behave yourself, you'll
get through this without getting hurt.
But right now...
Oh, my...
Oh, one eye, huh?
Why, you...!
You're weak, Touka.
A carbon copy of Pop.
Dad... fought for our sake.
What do you even know?!
You're the one who
doesn't understand, Touka.
Both Mom and Pop are dead.
They protected nothing;
they were just taken. But I'm different!
I'm going to show that trash
that ghouls are above humans!
You can't fly anywhere on that wing of yours.
Go ahead and crawl along the ground.
Ayato, that was cool.
Touka...!
This one still has some spunk left, huh?
That really does remind me of her.
I'm getting a little jealous.
You really are a tough one.
In that case, how do you like this?!
How do you like this?! How do you like this?!
All right, how do you like... this?!
How do you like this?!
How about this?!
--K-Kaneki...
--How about this?!
How do you like this?! How do you like this?!
How about this?! How do you like this?!
Awesome! I can't break him one bit!
M-Mr. Yamori! W-We should be on our way--
Huh?!
Macho-beard is right.
Nico...
Ooh, splat! Very nice!
Let's leave the rest for
after we get home, Yamori.
Thank you, Nico.
No problem.
Banjo, stuff the one-eyed guy
in the bag. We're going back soon.
Are you all right?
They took him away, didn't they?
Yomo, round everyone up for me.
Anteiku will be closing
up shop for a little while.
They are clearly starting to
show signs of an organized movement.
That is all we know about Aogiri Tree.
I'd like to charge after them right now,
but for the time being, we have to be patient.
We engage them in one week.
Until then, citizens of the 11th Ward
are under a mandatory
evacuation. Utilize the police.
I will deal with the media. That is all.
Dismissed!
Yes, sir!
So you're Suzuya, huh? You're an
awfully slender fellow, aren't you?
Hmm? Uh-oh...
Are you sure you're eating right?
Do you even have
anything in your coin purse?
Now, now, Maru,
Suzuya just got here and I'm sure he's tired.
Cut him some slack, okay?
What gives? I was just making small talk.
Okay, okay. Maybe tomorrow, all right?
Suzuya is the only 3rd Grade Investigator?
Maru will use whatever he can use.
He must have decided that we can use Juzo.
In any case, he was personally
admitted by Chairman Washu himself.
"Suzuya Juzo"
Following Arima...
Right.
Ugh, you know, the enemy
has a real problem case, too.
You mean Jason?
Yeah. The 13th Ward's S-rated troublemaker.
Sadistic bastard, who kills
more for fun than for eating.
He's one guy I wouldn't
want to go up against.
That's right. You've fought
him before, huh, Amon?
Yes. Together with Mr. Mado.
Right.
What is the deal with that eye-patched man?
Don't make me a killer.
His words... his expression...
They're dredging up
memories I don't want to remember.
Kotaro, who said you could come in?
Amon...
Amon!
Sorry. Could you repeat that, please?
I said your quinque got broken, right?
Oh, yes.
In that case, choose one from Mado's effects.
Huh?
It's in his will. Well, see you later.
Mr. Mado...
Rei, there are apparently
a lot of ghouls in the 11th Ward.
I may be able to get
a new quinque. I can't wait.
I have to be a good boy,
or else Mama will be cross with me again.
"CCG Urgent Press Conference"
CCG is moving quickly to increase
the investigator presence in the 11th Ward,
and pinpoint this ghoul organization's base.
I can state that it's only a matter of time
before this case is closed.
But isn't the full-scale
evacuation of citizens in the area
a little over-aggressive?
That is ultimately for everyone's safety.
CCG is on everyone's side.
--And so, I ask that you all
please not enter any off-limits areas.
--At least text me, would you, Kaneki?
--And so, I ask that you all
please not enter any off-limits areas.
Hinami...
Big Sister...
Mm-hmm.
He's not as soft as he looks.
Nishiki...
Looks like everyone is here.
There will be a few more coming later,
but let's get started now.
This concerns the problems
unfolding in the 11th Ward,
and the actions Anteiku is to take.
But before we get to that,
I have one thing to say...
about the kidnapped Kaneki.
You'll be served not
thinking we'll ever see Kaneki again.
Hey, you old coot! Don't even talk like that!
Stop!
Stop.
We're going, right? To save him? Well?!
Aogiri Tree is made up of
ghouls who live for nothing but to fight.
It will not be easy to sneak
into their base and rescue Kaneki.
No... It can't be...
Moreover, we cannot
ignore CCG's movements.
They will probably be sending a
detachment into the 11th Ward soon
to wipe out the Aogiri Tree members.
If we did go to save him,
there's a good chance that we'd
be the ones who were exterminated.
Hey, what is this? You're not
thinking of abandoning him!
I'm going.
What was the policy of this shop, again?
Sir, if you're not going...
then I'll go alone.
I'm going, too.
I do owe him.
I want to help, too.
Big Brother is always helping me out, so...
If there's anything I can do, I'll do it!
Hinami...
Let me say this,
so there's no misunderstanding:
I was always planning to go rescue Kaneki.
However, I wanted you to know
that I couldn't guarantee your lives.
I know how you all feel.
If you want to save Kaneki,
you must stake your lives on it.
In return, Yomo and I will
protect you with all our might.
It is Anteiku's policy to
help each other out, after all.
There is one more thing.
Come on in!
You! But why?!
Amore!
Heartbreak!
Imagine, my best
friend Kaneki, facing danger
at the hands of some irrational bunch!
No kidding!
Though the city sleeps,
its buildings are always
under construction
Urban planning carries on
Its belt lines morphing, snakes interlocking,
stirring up endorphins,
and off you go, go, go
Souls ascend up into the night sky
Their procession and
their faith both resembling
an aberrant riddle
Our as-yet-empty tomorrows
are an all but black shade of gray
Without any possibilities
an all but black shade of gray
Ah, tonight, you're the one I want
Saints
Ah, I want you to signal the end
Jiro, how does Miss Rize
feel about me, do you think?
Where's this coming from all of a sudden?
If you want to get on her
good side, why not give her a present?
A present? Oh, but I
couldn't ask her directly.
--It would ruin the surprise.
--He's going to have me go ask her.
How gutless.
Miss Rize, Miss Rize,
I have a question for you.
She says she likes any and all internal organs.
"Next time: 'High Spirits'"
I see. Thanks.
"Layout: Katsuya Yamada"