All right, that's about it.
You're working hard today, too, huh?
Obi.
Oof.
Oh, you're wearing proper clothes.
The master has guests today,
so I'm wearing a uniform, too.
Clothes like this make
me feel really stiff, though.
It's hard to follow all of the
confining rules in the castle...
Even so, I've decided
to continue on this path...
Ryu! It's about time to go back!
Ryu!
He can't hear you, can he?
Because the view I want to see is next to me...
Because views I haven't
seen before are waiting...
Oh, Ryu! It's time to go!
Just now, did she... with the whistle...?
Looks like it.
"Episode 10: Inexperienced Heart, Going Deeper"
Um, thank you very much!
For calling Ryu for me.
Red hair...
That's rare. It's my first time seeing it!
I hear that a lot.
It's amazing how you can get
the bird to fly with your whistle!
You're the first person
I've talked to since arriving here.
I finally feel less nervous.
You're...
I've got some business... I have an
audience with the second prince after this.
With Prince Zen?
You're the master's guest?
I'm not a guest.
Huh?
Perfect timing. Will you hear me out?
I don't want to be alone right now.
Um, I'm in the middle of work...
If it's just for a little bit, it's fine.
It's almost break time, anyway.
I'll go back first.
Okay!
What's your name?
I'm Shirayuki.
I'm an apprentice court herbalist.
I'm Kihal Toghrul.
I'm not good with formalities,
so you can just call me Kihal.
Okay.
And that's my friend, Popo.
Friend...
That's a beautiful bird.
It's my first time seeing one.
I raised Popo, but on the island where I live,
there's a whole flock living in the wild.
Now that you mention it,
I've heard of them before.
People who live with birds on
one of Clarines' southern islands.
You live with the birds?
Yeah.
Ever since my great-grandfather's time.
The birds we live with are
the same species as Popo.
When they spread their blue and green wings,
they're beautiful! Like the sea is flying!
The birds have really good hearing,
and they find the mineral ores
in the ocean near the island
by listening to the sound
they make in the waves.
They tell us where schools of fish are, too,
so we're always together
when we go out on the ocean!
This is the mineral ore
from the ocean, the walnut stone.
Once they're polished, they become shiny!
The whistle from earlier!
But...
Hm?
When it comes down to it, the island
is part of someone else's territory.
This happened a year and a half ago.
The lord who had just inherited
the lands brought his noble friends
and started to hunt the birds.
The lord did?
Yes. His friends loved it.
The birds' feathers were rare and
could be sold at a high price, they said.
He was even praised
with words I loathe to recount.
Popo was also the target of
a hunt and was seriously injured.
We've asked them to stop many times.
But they wouldn't listen...
The lord then said, "I'll let you
meet the prince, so you can ask him."
Even if I ask, it's not like he'll listen.
I'm sure he'll just laugh at me.
Those with high rank won't
listen to those with no rank.
That's not how I would
describe Prince Zen's character.
Wh-What are you saying?
He's nobility! Royalty, even!
Of course he's like that.
Kihal...
I'm sorry. Even so, I had to come here.
I had no other choice.
Sorry for interrupting your work.
It's fine. I have to go back soon, though...
Can I stay here until the audience?
Sure.
I understand the situation.
You want me to make it illegal to hunt the birds
and make Yuris Island a nature reserve, right?
Yes, sir.
I will consider it and
give my decision tomorrow.
However, from what I have heard,
I believe this should be discussed
among the concerned parties,
Lord Brecker of Yuris Island
and its resident, Kihal Toghrul.
Oh, excuse me.
Prince Zen, I apologize for troubling you
with a matter I could not resolve myself.
You understand now, don't you, Toghrul?
Kihal, I have prepared a room for you.
Please make yourself at home.
How was it?
He said the concerned parties should discuss it.
I see...
Nothing good will come of you worrying about it.
There are herbs protected
because of their efficacy.
If the birds also had
something special to offer...
Even if the birds are important
to the residents of the island,
that doesn't matter to the lord.
He's enjoying hunting with
his friends on his own land.
That's all it is.
The mineral ore on the island, the walnut stone,
isn't really something that
can be sold for much, either.
I can't do anything.
All I can do is say that it is
within the rights of the lord.
Lord Brecker brought this?
Yeah, it appears to be
a decorative arrow souvenir.
He probably believes his own values are
common sense and doesn't question them.
Why did the viscount bring this up
to you in the first place, Zen?
Probably because the previous
viscount and I met a few times.
It's my first time meeting Brecker, though.
Heh, you're being used, Zen.
--Shut up.
Why did you say it, too, Kiki?
Even so, I hate that I cannot help that girl.
Excuse me!
Shirayuki?
Zen, there's something
I want to talk to you about.
Kihal, is it true that with
a signal from your whistle,
you can get the bird to fly where you want?
Yes, sir. Everyone who has gone
through training on the island can.
Can you have the bird fly somewhere far?
Yes. We often send them out
to fishing boats in the open sea.
How do they know where the boat is?
Um, with this.
A bell?
Bells made from walnut stones
each have a unique sound.
These birds can tell the
slight difference between them.
If they hear the sound of the bell in advance,
they will land where they hear that sound.
I see.
If possible, I would like to look into using
that as a means of communication in Clarines.
But why...
I heard from a certain person
that perhaps the ability to control
the birds could be used for something.
I figured, if they can be used for
communication, it would benefit the kingdom.
That was definitely worth investigating.
First, I'd like to test it over a long distance.
Will you do it?
Test...?
Yeah. We'll test to see if it's
something we can make use of.
You mean, at the castle?
That's right. Tomorrow evening.
Then, may I name the
person who will hold the bell?
That's fine, but...
M-Me?
Yes, please! It might be a bother,
but to me, the castle is still the enemy camp!
Enemy camp...?
Even if it's a proposal from the kingdom,
I can't really trust it yet.
If you have faith in Prince Zen,
then I want to work with you
so maybe I can feel that way, too!
All right. I'll try!
Thank you!
Thank you, Shirayuki!
The test will be as follows:
To a point ten kilometers west of the castle,
at a lakeside watchtower that
would take 40 minutes by horse,
the bird will sent bearing a document.
The person at the watchtower
will receive the document,
sign it, attach the bell,
and send the bird back to the castle.
This will all occur within 25 minutes.
If all the conditions are met,
it will be acknowledged;
if not, it will be regarded as a failure.
To go and come back from the lake in 25 minutes?
It's easier than I thought.
Don't be stupid.
It's a bird that's going, you know.
The bird handler will be Kihal Toghrul.
Assisting her will be Shirayuki.
Three soldiers and a messenger
will accompany her to the watchtower.
That is all.
A red-haired girl...?
I see.
I was wondering why something so
outrageous was brought up suddenly.
To get the prince's friend on your side--
You're a clever one, Toghrul.
The prince's friend?
That has nothing to do with--
Lord Brecker.
Right now, we are looking to see
if this proposal will benefit Clarines.
I would like you to judge for
yourself as a lord of this kingdom.
Then, your highness, I would also like to
accompany them to the lakeside watchtower.
It is not that I am suspicious of anything,
but if those girls act dishonestly in any way,
it would reflect badly on you, sir.
Very well, Brecker, Shirayuki and the
others will head to the lakeside watchtower.
The bird will be sent at four o'clock,
and the test will begin.
Shirayuki...
Hm?
This is the sound, Popo.
I'll be waiting, okay, Kihal?
Okay!
It's time.
Yeah. Shirayuki should
be waiting by the lake by now.
Are you ready, Kihal?
Yes, sir.
Now, let the test begin!
Go, Popo. Shirayuki's
waiting for you in the west!
Such a clear sound...
Shall we go outside to wait now?
All right.
My lord?
What a beautiful view.
I like high places with a view.
Because there are things
you can't see when you're low.
Shirayuki.
Let's make a deal.
What?
I've heard a little about you.
You're an apprentice of sorts at the castle?
Even though you're the prince's friend,
without any kind of social status,
there are things that must be hard to do, right?
You can't attend parties
or balls where nobles gather,
so of course there will be discrimination.
Not even Prince Zen can continue
to associate with you forever.
That's why I will support you from behind.
In exchange, I want this test to fail.
The bird did not come here...
The bird will come!
Wh--
Are you saying you are planning on refusing?
Of course! What good will it be if it fails?
I don't care anymore!
Hey!
The bell...!
Stay inside until time runs out!
My lord, what are you doing?
Quiet! Does a mere soldier like
you dare to speak up against me?
Please open up, Lord Brecker!
Shut up!
What do you think will happen
if those island people and birds
became beneficial to the kingdom?
Do you think I'm so stupid that
I wouldn't notice that possibility
and would just let you do what you want?
Don't be ridiculous!
It's noisy up there.
I'll go take a look.
It's a piece of cake to keep a soldier quiet.
Listen, little girl!
It's no use crying to the prince!
No matter how he actually feels,
he wouldn't do something so stupid
as to believe you over me, his subject,
and risk antagonizing those around him.
Sadly, that's what it means
to be of different social status.
What you say is true.
I think there are times when
we can't act on how we really feel.
But if that's the case, then I will do all
I can to make sure that doesn't happen to him!
What can someone like you do?
Anyway, the status of one who can't see the
effort of someone trying to protect something...
...is lower than this watchtower!
Huh?
What?!
Miss!
What are you trying to do?
The bell fell into the lake!
If we don't find it and ring it,
Popo won't land here.
Was this the viscount's doing?
That girl... from this height...?!
Lord Brecker.
You are under arrest.
So you decided to side with the girl?
There is no one working for Prince Zen
who could hear her words and ignore them.
Popo's here!
Oh, it flew away!
Miss, around where did it fall?
A little ways out from where I jumped in!
Ten minutes left.
There's still no sign of the bird...
Popo... Shirayuki...!
Did you find it?
No, I didn't see anything!
Shirayuki!
Popo?
It came back?
What's that bird trying to do?
The birds have really good hearing,
and they find the mineral ores
in the ocean near the island
by listening to the sound
they make in the waves.
Two more minutes before time runs out.
It's almost been 25 minutes.
Will it not work, after all?
To make a bird fly with just a sound...
Be quiet.
I cannot hear the sound of the wings.
Welcome back, Popo!
Your highness!
The document and the bell!
I have confirmed the signatures
of everyone. There is no problem.
Then...
I have decided to bring in the bird
handlers as a means of communication!
Popo!
Thank you, Shirayuki!
Your highness.
What is it?
There was a report along with the signatures.
Mitsuhide, Kiki! Ready the horses!
I have arrested the
viscount due to his interference.
Standing by at the watchtower.
The assistant was injured...
Your highness!
I will tell you everything that happened.
When the viscount asked to
accompany the group to the watchtower,
I thought Prince Zen would refuse,
but he dared to allow him to go.
Dared?
It seemed obvious that the viscount was
planning to use Shirayuki for his own gain.
He must have believed in the soldiers
and that girl and left it to them.
However--
How will he protect what he wants to protect?
He probably hasn't decided yet.
I see. I understand.
I'll be back. Take care of my horse.
Master, if you're looking
for Shirayuki, she's upstairs...
Shirayuki said that if there were times
you couldn't act on your true feelings,
then she would make sure
that didn't happen to you, sir!
Zen!
Show me your injury.
U-Um, Zen, sorry...
But I wasn't going to hide it from you.
'Cause you'd get mad if I did.
Idiot...
Did something happen between you and Shirayuki?
Calmly... So no one will
think anything is strange...
Something happened, right?
I need some time to think by myself...
Hang in there, Miss.
"Episode 11: Encountering...
A Color for the First Time"