Here goes.
Mm-hmm.
He belongs to me!
He belongs to you?
Are you dense?
There's not a single thing here...
that belongs to you.
Calmato.
Amazing. So that's Touka's kagune...
I'm so glad, Miss Kirishima!
Imagine, me taking this much damage
from someone whose
kagune is well-matched to mine!
I didn't think I'd get
to see you like this again.
It's like the passion from that earlier time...
is being reborn!
Let me dress the area around Kaneki
using your organs as trimmings!
Such an unexpected hors d'oeuvre!
I'm grateful!
Not bad, Miss Kirishima.
I guess it's unavoidable.
It's absolutely not what I'd hoped for...
but tactically...
I need a bite!
Nishiki...
What are you,
a zombie?!
Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go! Let me go! Let go of me!
Kimi...
That's quite enough--
We can't have this, can we?
This will take...
an awful long time... to heal...
Kaneki... for heaven's sake...
Just one bite...
Just one... bite...
Go ahead and eat your own flesh,
you filthy gourmet.
Kimi...
Nishiki?
Just hold on... I'm coming to...
help you now...
Nishiki...
Stand aside.
Touka?
She knows about
both you and Kaneki, right?
I can't let a woman this dangerous
go on living.
Touka!
You can't! She's like...
Hide is to me, or Yoriko is to you.
What if that was Yoriko
up there and not Miss Kimi?
Would you...
be able to kill Yoriko?
Shut up!
I have to get rid of her,
to make sure that doesn't happen!
Nishiki...?
How pretty.
Oh, um...
What does that mean?
Nishiki...?
Nishiki!
Thank goodness!
How am I... pretty?
Tell me, oh tell me, the way it works
Who is that inside of me?
Here in this broken-down,
broken-down world,
you laugh, without seeing a thing
I'm just so damaged,
I hold my breath and freeze
Breakable, unbreakable;
shakable, unshakable
When I found you, it shook me
In this twisted world, I'm gradually
growing transparent and vanishing
Don't look for me; don't look at me
I don't wish to hurt you in a world
of someone else's imagining
Remember who I am
Following the incident at
--All right, that's perfect.
--Good work.
--the church, there were a number of
--We're still doing the daily prep, you know.
--changes around Anteiku.
Don't mention the little things.
What are you doing?!
M-Mr. Nishio?!
Hey, Nagachika.
I see you've got your usual
maggot-infested look on your face.
Mr. Nishio came to work at Anteiku.
For Miss Kimi's sake, as well,
I don't think you should
take any more human lives.
With the food that we gather here,
you can live a relatively
guilt-free life as a ghoul.
However, we make sure to exact a price.
That will be your
labor here at Anteiku, Nishio.
Wow, I have to say, Mr. Nishio...
Hmm?
The more I look at you, the less
you mesh with Anteiku's formalness.
I'll kick you out of here.
We're still just doing the daily prep.
But then, what made
you start working at Anteiku?
Shut up. I have my reasons.
Don't tell me you're after Touka!
Ha! Like I'd want that brainless girl!
Speaking of Touka,
is she still not feeling well?
Mm-hmm.
Touka hadn't been at work since that day.
I... I...
want to be with Dad!
What was that about?
Who knows? All sorts
of things can happen in life.
Oh, no! I've got class!
Thanks for everything!
Hinami?
It's my fault. With him not here,
I have to be twice as together now.
Um, what is Hinami
upset about, if I can ask?
We haven't heard anything from him--
from my husband, in some time.
So now she insists on going to see him.
Where is Hinami's father right now?
Yamori...
Things are awfully quiet here today, huh?
Take this with you and get on out of here.
This is very nice.
You really do do good work.
I'll get her with this...
W-Would you mind not
coming around here anymore?
I see I've fallen into disfavor.
I just want to live in peace.
Please.
All right.
Hinami... Ryoko...
We'll be together again soon.
But I wonder if you
would tell me something first.
When the hell did you
become a flunky of the humans?
He...
was apparently mixed up in some
dangerous business in the 13th Ward.
But,
once Hinami was born,
he got out of that for us.
He really is a good man.
To Hinami and me, he really is...
Okay, then...
U-Um...
It's all right. I'm her mother.
If I don't spoil Hinami, she'll
never get the chance to be spoiled.
A box-carrier...
What are doves doing here...?
It looks like it was worth
the wait, wasn't it, Amon?
Using small fry to catch the bottom feeders.
Then again, this one is a
bottom feeder in the truest sense.
Mr. Mado, that's...
Jason. What is the
13th Ward's big fish doing
swimming around in the 20th Ward?
Why don't we hear it
straight from his own mouth?
An S-rated... The 13th Ward's Jason...
Hinami? It's Mom. Can you open up for me?
No! I don't want to talk to you!
Hinami, your--
I want to see Dad! Why?!
Why can't I?! I hate you, Mom!
That's enough, Hinami!
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have raised my voice.
You miss Dad, don't you?
I think Dad misses you, too, Hinami.
But you see, if we go see
him now, we'll be in his way.
I'm sorry to always
make you put up with this.
Jason!
Jason! Jason!
You're pretty good.
Hmph, I'll entertain you for two minutes.
I'm sorry. I guess
I didn't step in close enough.
Don't worry about it.
You can nail him with the next one.
Yes, sir.
You seem...
quite easily breakable.
You okay, Amon?
Yes, sir!
Catch your breath!
What a shame.
Not bad.
Feeling sleepy?
Oh no you don't!
Time's up. Let's play again sometime.
Damn.
Mr. Mado?
Hmm, my quinque broke.
Now then...
what use might we have for this scum?
Hinami...
Mom misses Dad, too.
Oh...
Mom...!
Hinami...!
My, my...
Hinami, I'm sorry.
Mm-mm. Mom, don't cry.
Mm-hmm. I won't cry
anymore. Thank you, Hinami.
Let's wait together until...
Dad comes to get us.
Jason managed to get away, huh?
My quinque broke.
There's nothing we could have done.
Even so...
As long as we keep
squashing them one by one,
another opportunity will come around again.
Yes, you're right.
Hmm, we can use this.
All right, since I'm always
making you put up with this,
I want to go get you a
present to show you I'm sorry.
Is there anything you want?
Hmm...
Okay, you think about it.
Mm-hmm!
Mom, thank you!
No, thank you.
What do you want?
U-Um... It's about working tomorrow's shift.
Pass.
L-Listen--
I couldn't... kill that woman.
Huh?
Earlier,
Hinami and Mrs. Ryoko were fighting...
but they were able to patch things up.
Looking at the two of them,
I thought, families sure are nice.
I thought, the affection between
mother and child doesn't
care about being human or ghoul.
That shouldn't be a surprise,
but until my body ended up this way,
I didn't have any idea.
If we could all come to realize that...
The relationship between
Mr. Nishio and Miss Kimi
could serve as a guidepost for the way
things between human
and ghoul could be, I thought.
So, what did you want?
Oh, uh, nothing...
I shouldn't have opened
my big mouth back there,
without knowing anything
about you and Yoriko, and I'm sorry.
Okay, I'll let the manager know.
I'm sure Touka must have thought so, too.
After the way she herself
had been accepted. But then,
if she had been rejected,
after interacting with each other...
there'd be no going back.
Same for Hide and me.
Is Big Sister okay?
Hmm, good question.
I hope she starts feeling better soon.
Mm-hmm.
Big Brother, let's continue.
How do you read this?
Let's see... That's "cloudburst."
"Cloudburst"?
It means when it suddenly starts raining.
Hinami?
Ah, Mom!
Were you being taught how to read?
Mm-hmm.
Thank you for always doing this.
No, not at all. Well, I'll be going.
Thank you, Big Brother.
See you tomorrow.
Mm-hmm.
Mom, look! I learned
all of the kanji in this book!
You did? That's good work!
So now, Mom...
What?
I want a new book.
Huh?
I want to learn even more
words, so I can surprise Dad!
Also, Dad's birthday
is coming up soon, right?
You want to give him a book as a present?
Okay, why don't we go to the bookstore?
Thank you very much.
Looks like we're in for a shower.
You're right! It's starting to rain!
See? I was right, wasn't I?
Mm-hmm! Oh, Mom...
What?
This is called a cloudburst!
Cloudburst?
When it suddenly starts
raining, it's called a cloudburst.
Big Brother told me so.
Mr. Kaneki is well informed, huh?
Mm-hmm! I wonder if Dad knows, too.
Let's ask him sometime.
If I know something Dad doesn't
know, I'm pretty amazing, huh?
Yes, you are.
What's come over you, Hinami?
It's been so long since
I've gone out with you, Mom!
Come, on, Hinami, you're getting wet!
Hinami, let's go home.
Mom?
Aren't we going to one other place? Huh?
Mom...?
I just remembered something I have to do.
Hinami?
It's Dad!
Huh?
Mom! Dad is somewhere nearby!
I-It couldn't be...
He came to get us!
Ah, Hinami!
Mom, this way!
Hinami, wait!
Dad!
Wait for me!
Wait for--
Hinami!
It's Dad's scent!
Dad! Dad...?
Hinami!
What's that smell...?
Nice rain, isn't it?
But I wouldn't want it
raining any harder than this.
I wouldn't be able to
hear your death throes, after all.
Could I have a moment of your time,
Mrs. Fueguchi?
Mom...
Ho...
Hinami, run away.
Mom...?
It's all right. You head on
back to Anteiku ahead of me.
I'll be sure to come back later.
No... No!
I want to stay with you, Mom!
Kusaba! Your Q-bullets!
R-Right!
Go on!
H-Hold it!
Is that supposed to be
mother-daughter love? It makes me sick.
I won't let you go!
Somebody... Somebody...!
Big Brother... Big Sister...!
Mom...
Mom!
Though the city sleeps,
its buildings are always
under construction
Urban planning carries on
Its belt lines morphing, snakes interlocking,
stirring up endorphins,
and off you go, go, go
Souls ascend up into the night sky
Their procession and
their faith both resembling
an aberrant riddle
Our as-yet-empty tomorrows
are an all but black shade of gray
Without any possibilities
an all but black shade of gray
Ah, tonight, you're the one I want
Saints
Ah, I want you to signal the end
Say, Nishiki...
Yeah?
You want to both wear these?
Huh?
These are bangles. They're a set.
How embarrassing. Is she
seriously going for a "pair" look?
Well, it is a present and all.
Geez, these bangles are like horse crap.
Huh? Horse crap?
Er, no, Kimi... I meant, you know,
the good kind of horse crap--
"Next time: 'Captivity'"