Coming all the way out here,
it's no wonder it's cold.
We are pretty far from Clarines.
Sorry, Shirayuki.
We're in a hurry, so we
can only take you partway.
I apologize, as well.
Thank you for allowing me to travel
with you and even ride with you.
I can't believe you have to go
all the way to Laxdo for an errand.
Court herbalists have it rough, too.
It's because I'm still an apprentice.
And we often study outside, as well.
Speaking of which, when I told
Lord Haruka that you passed,
he said, "Congratulations."
But he said it with a sigh.
He's funny, isn't he?
You can tell what he's thinking immediately.
Yeah...
Zen, did something happen?
You're in a hurry?
No, it's the usual fort inspection.
Fort Laxdo is under my jurisdiction.
Well, I'll leave you here.
It's cold, so don't wander around.
Okay!
Later!
There is a lot that can be
gained from being outside.
Zen!
Be careful!
This country we experience...
And the people we meet...
And the feelings we come to know from them...
"Episode 5: This Path,
the Crystallization of Premonition"
I don't see anyone on watch.
Hey! Is anyone here?
We're from the royal guards! Hey!
P-Please wait...
Hey, are you all right?
Everyone... Even the prince is here?
Regular reports stopped coming,
so we came to see what was going on.
--You can't sta--
--Master!
Everyone inside the fort is sleeping.
Sleeping?
Wh-Who is he?
I'm his attendant!
It's still a trial period, though.
Come on, I've handed my reins to you.
I don't have them.
I'm going in.
Y-You can't!
This place has been
possessed by a fearsome evil spirit!
Evil spirit?
About twenty days ago...
One after another, everyone started to
complain about their bodies feeling strange.
Like their bodies felt heavy,
or their vision was going dark.
Most people seemed to
lose their sense of balance.
The physician also fell sick
while he was tending to the others.
We couldn't find the reason behind it,
so it must be the work of an evil spirit...
What about you?
I am not that sick.
However, I was in no state
to go down the snowy road...
I'll take a look inside.
Huh?!
Please, wait! What if something
happens to you, as well, Your Highness?!
If that happens, then there's no point.
I won't push myself.
You should rest.
You did well to endure it until now.
Yes, sir.
Zen, you must come out before sunset.
Yeah. Mitsuhide, stay outside and keep watch.
I want to avoid having everyone inside.
Roger.
W-Wait a minute!
Normally, wouldn't the
master be waiting outside?
If it's some kind of sickness.
If we know where that sickness is coming from,
it'll be better than going
back empty-handed, though.
Is it all right not to stop him?
He's worried about the soldiers.
Mitsuhide, aren't you
a close aide of the prince?
Yeah, Zen's.
I don't see anything out of the ordinary.
What if it really was an evil spirit?
If something like that really exists,
I'd like to try fighting it.
This is the armory, huh?
It doesn't seem like it'd have
anything to do with... this?
The armory was empty?
Seems the soldier earlier didn't know, either.
There were claw marks, too. Someone
probably took advantage of this opportunity.
Shall we switch to bandit hunting?
That's my specialty!
--Put those away. We need to investigate
the cause and help the soldiers recover first.
--Specialty...?
What if we ask Shirayuki to come?
She might know something about
what's happened to the soldiers.
Mitsuhide!
Right!
I hope he can bring her before sunset.
Hey, Miss Kiki, don't tell me Mitsuhide
doesn't tell Prince Zen his opinion?
You tell him what's important calmly, Miss Kiki,
but don't you think your
partner's a little soft on him?
I wonder...
They're here.
Hm?
Did the physician prescribe the medicine?
Yes, at first...
But there weren't enough
medicinal herbs during this time.
Weren't enough?
In cold climates, the medicinal
properties of the herbs are lower,
so a larger amount is necessary.
Really?
All right. Did you notice anything else?
No, I was often outside keeping watch...
Sorry I'm not much help...
Oh no, i-it's fine!
My name is Shuka.
Please let me know if there's anything I can do.
That'll be a great help.
But please rest for now.
Yes, ma'am.
He looks like he's weakened considerably.
Zen, you need to go outside soon.
It'll be bad if you pass out!
I'll stay a little longer.
I said, that'd be bad!
I don't like the cold!
Don't make excuses!
Do you think I can leave by
myself after calling you here?
If there was anything we could do
together, then I would do it with you.
But that's not the case now.
I'll try to do what I can to be of help.
Shirayuki...
I'll... stay, too...
Zen.
Didn't you say you'd only stay until sunset?
Right now, you have to
think of your own position.
I was being selfish. I take it back.
Call me if anything happens!
Zen, good job keeping
your stubbornness in check.
It's 'cause of what you said.
Stop sulking.
I know you're concerned about Shirayuki.
Don't those feelings show that that's
how much you can depend on her?
You're right...
But anyway, it was my first time
hearing that you don't like the cold.
Are you okay lying down in a place like that?
Stop nagging! I'm cooling my head!
--Master's actually listening to him.
--Hey, stop it--
--Go away!
To tell the truth, Mitsuhide's
really the only one Zen listens to.
So that's why he doesn't
say usually say anything.
It's not that he's being soft on him, huh?
Shirayuki, did you figure anything out?
Are you okay being up and about?
I rested for a while already.
I see. I haven't figured anything out yet...
Everyone had the same
symptoms at the beginning,
but there's a difference in their symptoms now.
Is there a reason for that...?
I don't know... But I did figure out
what medicine the physician was using.
I thought I'd prepare some with
the medicines I bought in town--
Shirayuki!
Are you all right?
It shouldn't... start this soon...
Is it different depending on the person?
Shirayuki...
Shuka, you said you were
often outside keeping watch, right?
Y-Yes...
That means, the reason
must be inside the room...
The people furthest from the
entrance have the worst symptoms...
It's pretty cold, huh?
Yeah.
Shirayuki?! What's wrong?
It's all right. I was just
working too close to these.
The cause was the firewood in the fireplace!
You can't burn this wood.
Harmful particles will scatter,
and if you keep breathing them in,
they'll start to have an effect.
Where did they get that?
According to Shuka, a band of travelers said
they didn't want to carry it while they traveled,
so they gave it to them for free.
I apologize for one thing after another!
Are you able to move around more easily now?
Yes! I received medicine from Shirayuki.
I'm glad...
It looks like it worked.
I'll try to do what I can to be of help.
I give up.
Shirayuki, you...
You're so cool.
Huh?
Will you stay here for a while?
I want to leave the soldiers to you.
Yes!
To have everyone recovered
this much in just a few days...
Shirayuki's skill is undeniable.
Yeah.
Zen.
Bandits?
Yeah, apparently there's a band
that uses the Laxdo area as their base.
Where's their hideout?
I need a little more time to find out.
Then, leave it to me.
I have more intel about the town than you guys!
That guy's a monkey.
No doubt about it.
Kiki, Mitsuhide. I want to
take care of this with just us.
Because we can't just keep relying on Shirayuki.
What's that?
It's an infusion of medicinal herbs.
Do you want some?
I-I don't like bitter things!
It has a lot of nutrients, you know.
Um, Shirayuki...
Thank you very much.
Huh?
I couldn't do anything...
I wonder if Prince Zen
is embarrassed by this fort...
Is that what you think?
Honestly, I'm worried.
I'm afraid he'll keep
his distance from us now...
Does Zen come here often?
Yes. He goes out with the patrols,
talks to the older soldiers about the town,
and even listens to apprentices
like me like he's having fun.
Even though I want to be of use to him...
He might not come here any longer.
I don't think you need to worry about that.
Huh?
I think he keeps coming here for a reason.
I want to see Zen having fun here, too.
All right, I'm done!
Next, I need to write the report...
and prepare... medicine for the afternoon...
Shirayuki!
Sorry, were you sleeping?
No!
Really?
The soldiers have starting getting up!
Huh?
You feel all right even when moving around?
Yeah, I'm fine, I'm fine!
Shirayuki, take my pulse later!
You just want her to tend to you, don't you?
If you're going to make a
complete recovery, then get to work!
Y-Your Highness!
Please excuse us!
Jeez...
They're looking good.
Just a little longer.
I'm leaving everyone to you!
Okay!
All right, before I prepare the food...
I don't think I'm getting enough sleep...
That's...
Ow!
Hey, hey, is she okay?
The master said not to go
near her without permission...
Now I've done it.
Y-You're...
What are you doing here?
I'm Prince Zen's attendant right now.
I-I see.
Thank you very much.
You're not wary of me?
Why would I be after you saved me?
What are you talking about?
See you.
Miss, you're not feeling well, are you?
Don't tell anyone.
Even if you say that, I have
to obligation to do as you say.
Then, I'll owe you one.
Huh?
She's not going to bring up the fact
that I threatened her with an arrow?
That's fine, but tell me why you're hiding it.
It won't open!
It's impossible!
Hey, bring hot water! Hot water!
Everyone's feeling better, huh?
Yeah.
That's why I just want it to end uneventfully.
What would I follow her for?
Aw, jeez...
Nothing to note in the south?
We should probably go to the
west tower to check things out, too.
Yeah.
Your Highness, we're gathering
those who can move to go on patrol.
Are you all right?
Yes, thanks to Shirayuki.
We cannot cause more trouble than this.
We will fulfill our duties
with everything we have, as well.
I see. Don't over do it.
Yes, sir!
Oh right, Shuka, is there any medicine left?
No, Shirayuki made it in time
for when people woke up.
I see...
Did everyone take that medicine?
Yes, sir!
We have three shifts right now, right?
Uh-huh...
Soldiers wake up every eight hours.
Yeah...
So, when does Shirayuki sleep...?
Zen?
Sit over there.
O-Okay.
Close your eyes for a slow sixty seconds.
Huh? Are you taking my pulse?
Just do it. Don't open
your eyes before time's up.
B-But...
All right, one...
O-Okay!
Two...
Three...
You look so pale...
Say something, Shirayuki.
Master, I found them!
Who woulda thought the
firewood would work this well?
If we just wait for the right
chance to sell the weapons,
we'll make a ton of cash!
Was it you guys?
The ones who attacked the fort?
Who the hell are you guys?
We're soldiers from the castle.
It won't do for you to take other
people's things without permission.
You call yourselves soldiers
with such a tiny group?
There's a woman!
You brought us a nice present!
Shut up!
I will not allow you to insult anyone here!
What, you playing at being friends?
It's nothing that cheap.
I can love this country because
I know those who live here.
Because Mitsuhide and Kiki are by my side,
I can look forward without
forgetting my position.
Because there is someone I want to face,
I can decide not to become
someone she would turn her back on.
Bastard, what are you saying?!
Don't worry about it.
I'm not talking to you guys.
These are words of gratitude.
Is that right?
Too slow!
Sorry!
I was too busy listening!
This is bad, Kiki. I'm moved.
Yeah.
Lucky. I wish he'd say that about me, too.
Did I wake you?
Zen, I...
Sorry it took so long for me
to notice you weren't feeling well.
As the person in charge,
I wasn't paying enough attention.
Huh?
But you know, if you had just said something,
I would have tried to come up with
a way for you to not be overworked.
It's not a problem you need
to deal with by yourself, Shirayuki.
Even if it were, don't hide it again. Ever.
Yeah. Sorry, Zen.
Don't misunderstand, though.
Just because you're lying here like this
doesn't change the fact that we were
all saved thanks to your hard work.
I didn't thank you properly.
I'm glad you were here, Shirayuki.
For the soldiers...
And for me...
This time, you were my driving force...
To me, that's what you are, Zen.
Ever since I met you, over and over...
I'm counting on you to
operate as usual from now on.
Yes, sir!
Shirayuki, I'll write you letters!
Thanks, I'll look forward to them.
Be careful! Thank you!
There is a lot that can be
gained from being outside.
This country we experience...
Lucky encounters with the people we meet...
And the feelings we come to know from them...
They give us so many lights that never fade...
Welcome home, Prince Izana.
Hey, little brother.
What's going on here?
I would welcome Shirayuki, as well.
I cannot answer that.
He's become a good-for-nothing prince.
"Episode 6: The Back Full of Meaning"