I fell asleep at my desk again...
That feels good...
The light that pours down on this town,
this country, shines on me...
On the place I've chosen...
On the new feelings inside me...!
"Episode 3: Shining Time of Promise"
Here you go.
Okay.
Oh, Shirayuki!
Hello!
Are you here to see Prince Zen today, too?
No, Mitsuhide and Kiki asked me to come.
Um, I've been wondering about this for a while,
but what was the object
hanging from that man's neck?
Oh, that's a piece of identification.
Identification...?
Everyone working at the castle has one.
You are not permitted to
enter the palace without one.
Oh, you're fine, though, Shirayuki.
We've heard everything from the prince.
Go ahead and wait at the entrance.
Thank you very much.
Being friends with the prince and all--
Shirayuki's so cool, isn't she?
Come on, let's get back to work.
You think so, too, don't you?
My lord, do you have business with the prince?
Yeah.
I'm terribly sorry, but he is currently
with someone else right now.
Someone else?
That person again?
Oh, they're beautiful no matter when I come!
She has nothing to prove her social standing...
That red-haired girl claiming
to be the prince's friend...
What a vulgar color...
We called you here today to help out with Zen.
Is something the matter?
After being out of the castle
on official business the other day,
he snuck out to observe the local area.
He snuck out?
Well, he always does that.
But this time, it made him late returning
to the castle without permission,
and the ministers around him seemed to
come down hard on him about it afterward.
Is Zen depressed?
No, it's just...
He decided to show his
contriteness with his actions
and shut himself up in his office,
working without rest.
Shirayuki...?
Am I hearing things?
No, I didn't say anything yet,
but it's really me.
Zen, Kiki and I asked Shirayuki to come.
"If I have time to sleep,
then I wanna see Shirayuki."
Isn't that what you said?
That's because you guys
kept bugging me about sleeping!
Before you start writing
"Shirayuki" all over your documents,
why don't you spend some time with her?
What's that supposed to be a symptom of?
Before all your replies become
"Shirayuki," you should spend--
Mitsuhide, we need to talk later.
Um... Should I go home for today?
Sorry for interrupti--
Zen?
You guys aren't being fair.
We know, sir.
Sorry they made you come out.
It's okay. Looks like you're having a hard time.
That's what happens when
I'm away from the castle for a while.
I feel like I'll become a
prince in name only one day.
Is that why you're overworking yourself?
I've finished twice as much as usual.
I won't give them anything to
complain about the next time I'm away.
Zen...
I don't mind deskwork.
It's just that it's easy to lose sight
of what's going on outside.
The country, Clarines,
spreads out past the castle walls.
That's what I like about it.
Zen, your country is great, after all.
Oh right, Zen--
What is it?
Do you want to sleep a little?
Sorry, but yeah.
Will you stay here until Mitsuhide comes?
Yeah.
Thanks.
He must've been really tired.
Zen is constantly fighting even
as he lives as this country's prince.
I need to work hard toward my own goal, too!
All right!
Oh? So that red-haired girl
is Prince Zen's friend, huh?
Zen, are you done sleeping?
Zen.
Where's Shirayuki?
Mitsuhide saw her off, and she went home.
I see... Hm?
That girl must've forgotten this.
Prince Zen, please excuse me
for interrupting your rest.
Oh, hello, Lord Haruka.
Don't meet up with people
from the outside so carelessly?
You mustn't forget your position
as this country's prince.
You must carefully choose
whom you become close with.
In order to protect myself,
and my authority, right?
I know.
If you understand, then stop inviting that
town girl of unknown lineage into the castle.
Does it bother you?
The girl will have expectations
and take advantage of you.
What if she asks for social status
appropriate for her position,
or asks you to introduce her to the king?
What will you do if she
asks you for selfish things?
Submitting quickly to the strong, and never
trying to advance with her own power.
Keeping a girl like that by your side
will only draw criticism from your retainers.
You have nothing to gain from it!
Never trying to advance
with her own power, huh?
I see. Then, what if it's a girl
without those expectations?
Your highness, where would
you find a girl like that?
I'm just asking if it would
be all right if there was one.
If you're saying such a girl exists,
then I would definitely like to meet her.
She was just here.
Didn't you see her, Lord Haruka?
Your highness! I did not come
to engage in wordplay with you!
This isn't play for me, either, Lord Haruka.
Very well.
I pray that you will open your eyes
to the truth as soon as possible.
Excuse me, your highness.
Zen?
I need a change of scenery.
I'm going to get some exercise.
Honestly, that prince...
There's nothing I can say to change his mind.
There is no choice but to
speak directly to the girl, after all.
Yes, sir.
Now, shall I begin?
This looks like the shironagi herb, but the
shape of the leaves is a little different...
I think the encyclopedia said...
Huh? Did I forget it at Zen's place?
What?!
Don't let Shirayuki pass from now on?
Why, all of a sudden?
Shirayuki has permission to pass
as Prince Zen's personal guest.
That has been rescinded.
What? No way!
It's an order from the prince:
"Regarding the treatment of Shirayuki,
because of the criticism of my retainers,
she shall hereafter no longer
have permission to enter the palace."
That's...
Please understand the
prince's agonizing decision.
Excuse me.
Hey, wait a minute!
Then, you must tell the prince
that we just allowed Shirayuki to pass.
What?!
Just before you came.
She said she left her book in the castle...
Don't tell me she's with the prince...?
Did she hear me?
Zen's being criticized?
But was the order just now really from Zen?
If I leave the castle today,
I won't be able to come back to see him?
No matter what happens to Zen?
I have to hear this directly from him.
You over there, wait!
That red hair...
Are you Shirayuki?
Uh... Yes.
That's what I thought.
I have heard that you are the prince's guest.
Please excuse me for stopping you suddenly.
That's all right.
It's fine. No problem here.
I knew... At least, I thought I did.
That I could only see Zen because of his power.
That's why...
I'm aiming for a path that allows me to be in
the same place as him through my own power.
Then, I can--
Wh-Why...?
"Red-haired guest, do not
take another step forward.
Leave at once."
This is...
...telling me not to go near Zen.
Who would...?
There is someone in this castle who will not
allow Zen and I to be in the same place.
But...
... Zen is here!
What? Wait, no way.
She's not gonna run away from that?
She sure is taking a roundabout way
to get to the prince's rooms.
Oh well, it's convenient for me.
Hurry up and go home, miss.
Shirayuki!
Shirayuki, what are you doing?
Zen!
Didn't you go home already?
Um...
I forgot my book...
Shirayuki, did someone talk to you before this?
A soldier did.
A soldier, huh?
Well? What's that arrow in your hand?
Someone shot at you inside the castle?!
Jeez, why didn't you call the soldiers then?
Sorry... But Zen, before you
get angry, hear me out.
How can I not be angry about this?
How can you be so unconcerned?
I was scared, you know!
And angry!
But I didn't want to stop
coming here without doing anything.
If there is someone who doesn't
want the two of us to meet,
then I have to try confronting them.
By yourself?
If I'm by myself, then the
other person might try to talk to me.
You can't--
--Zen!
--That's what I'd like to say, but all right.
I'll wait for you, Shirayuki.
But don't push yourself too hard.
If the other person won't leave you alone,
make them stop even
if you have to use my name.
It could also be the
work of more than one person.
Right.
If I find them, I'll keep watch, too.
Do you think you know who it is...?
I'm not confident, so I won't say...
Zen...
Sorry...
It looks like I make enemies easily...
Zen?
Is something wrong?
I have a favor to ask.
There's so much I don't know...
It was the first time I saw
Zen talking with his face downcast.
I will return to my residence,
so I leave the rest to you.
Hm?
Confidence, huh?
How will I be able to figure out who it is?
What are you doing?
Are you in the service of the court?
No, I'm...
What?
Um...
How did you get into the castle?
Through the Poet's Gate,
with permission from a certain personage.
I am going to see him now, so if you
doubt me, would you like to come along?
What?
This way.
Wait!
Once I have found an intruder,
I cannot allow them to go any further than this.
I will have you leave immediately.
One must have authority in order to
invite those from the outside into the castle.
You do not look like you have the social status
to be invited by one with such power.
This man is saying this with certainty.
If it is as you say, and I should not be here,
then stop me with your sword.
I didn't actually ask him,
but it was enough just to see him.
"She shall hereafter no longer
have permission to enter the palace."
Those were not Zen's words.
Never trying to advance
with her own power, huh?
Get back, girl!
I'll cut you!
As you wish.
This isn't play for me, either, Lord Haruka.
Do you know anything about an
order purported to be from Prince Zen?
Good job.
Someone like you wouldn't
be scared off by a little arrow.
Wh-Who are you?
Don't worry, I won't do anything.
It doesn't look like I can
run away, either, so I'll tell you.
That order and the arrow with
the threat on it were all my doing, not his.
Don't say stupid things.
I did these myself thinking of the prince.
I didn't ask for help from
someone of humble birth.
A lord with a strange sense of pride...
I agree.
Your highness!
Did you say it was for me, Lord Haruka?
It is as you say.
That was the wrong way to go about it.
Depending on the outcome,
it could have caused an uproar in the castle.
Sir.
Were you listening the whole time?
Ever since I found the marquess,
and he started talking to you.
Let me just say, I had to use all
my self-control not to come out, you know.
At least forgive me for eavesdropping.
Good answer, Zen...
Girl! How can you call the prince by his name?!
You know what, Lord Haruka?
I don't think it's bad to have
people around who value authority
and social status over everything.
Because I believe it is necessary as a
prince to understand different perspectives,
like those of you and Shirayuki.
Lord Haruka, is your title important to you?
Yes.
Then please treat it with importance.
This will not happen again.
Yes, sir!
Case closed, huh?
No, you--
My name's Obi, Master!
Who're you calling "Master"?!
Listen, I'm going to
keep you where I can see you.
You don't have to be so wary.
I won't lift another finger against that girl.
Do you think I'd believe you so easily?
I mean it! I like her, too.
Above all, she looks like
she'll be able to help you.
Right, miss?
Oof...
You're going overboard...
Kiki, Mitsuhide! Do something about that guy!
Yes, sir!
You'll be coming with us.
I'll go anywhere with a pretty lady.
You little...
Not "you." Call me "Obi."
I wonder who he is?
Who knows?
But there shouldn't be any
problems if we leave it to them.
Don't worry.
It looks like I make enemies easily...
I see.
Zen, look.
Hm?
Application information?
I decided to apply for this, so I'm telling you.
This is... for this castle's...?
Yup. Court herbalist.
I want to one day be able to go through
the gates by myself and come be your ally.
There's someone I want to
treasure my time together with.
I hope I can become his strength.
That's reassuring.
I'll wait, too, in this castle.
That is what pushes me from behind...
...and is my guidepost for moving forward.
I am the chief herbalist, Garak.
You're about to take
your test, right? Are you calm?
I mean, I'm a kid. It's weird.
We're locked in, huh?
Take a look for the sake of your resolve.
"Episode 4: From the Small Hand,
a Burgeoning Concerto Resonates"