Yes!
Spellamiso. A perennial plant
from the Aoshidare family.
If you steam the roots and dry them,
it can lower fevers and alleviate pain.
Oh, no. It's time to open the shop...!
This is...
...my own path...
...my own story.
If I had my wish,
I would keep writing my own path like this...
"Episode 1: Encounter...
Changing the Color of Fate"
Mirror, Mirror on the wall,
who's the fairest girl in the land?
Prince Raj.
What is it, Sakaki?
This is not a mirror.
He is an informant from town.
Ahem.
He's telling me everything as he sees it,
so he might as well be a mirror!
Well, please do not joke around too much.
You too! Don't just stand there!
Tell me your information!
Y-Yes, Highness!
You want to know who the most beautiful
girl in the kingdom of Tanbarun is, right?
In that case, what about that girl...?
That girl?
Yes, a girl born with exceptionally
rare red hair, as red as an apple.
Her name is Shirayuki, Highness.
Thanks, Miss!
Don't forget to take your medicine!
See ya, Shirayuki.
Yoshi, feel better!
Thanks for waiting!
Next is the medicine for you, Kino, right?
Don't worry about it.
I just came to let my eyes
rest on your beautiful hair.
Thank you. But since you're here,
I'll prepare some more medicine for you.
I got a hold of some good medicinal herbs,
so please take some with you.
You are a fine herbalist.
I wish your dead grandparents could see you...
Um... Kino--
I just remembered! I left the stove on!
Huh?!
Oh dear, oh dear.
I guess I can just bring it to her later.
Did you forget someth--
Prince Raj's... concubine?
Yes, in other words, a mistress.
That's absurd.
I can't believe he'd want a town girl
like me because of the color of my hair.
I'll be an embarrassment to the prince.
That Prince Raj has taken a liking to you.
Anyway, you must formally present
yourself to the castle tomorrow morning.
Dress yourself up tonight while you can.
For Kino, something to relieve the pain in her back
and stop the inflammation of her respiratory tract.
At Yuri's place, the father and
baby were coming down with a cold.
Okay, all that's left is...
That'll take care of everything.
It's not your fault, though.
Good-bye, Tanbarun.
Excuse me!
Excuse me! Is anyone home?
I can't just go in without permission...
And it's getting dark...
And I'm starting to get hungry...
Mitsuhide, Kiki! I'm going on ahead!
Jeez, you're going from a place like that again?
Ow...
Are you all right, Zen?
Are you injured? Did you hit your head?
What's one plus one?
Two.
Huh? Who're you again?
It's me, Mitsuhide!
Oh, was that your name?
Kiki! You, too?!
Well?
Who are you, really?
What are you doing, so deep in the woods?
O-Oh, I just followed a road without many
people in the middle of running away, and...
You have strange hair.
Yeah, people often tell me that.
Your right arm... It's hurt!
What about it?
I'm an herbalist. I have a
poultice you can use if you'd like.
I don't want it.
Huh?
It could be poison or something. How can I
use it if someone gives it to me all of a sudden?
It's not like I'm a dwarf or something.
I'm not going to trust someone so easily.
In other words, I've no business with you.
Right...
If you understand, then get going.
Well, what he said was true.
I guess there are arrogant people everywhere.
Hm? Wha--?
Wh-What are you...?
Unfortunately, I don't make it
a habit to carry poison around.
She got you, Zen.
Sorry about that. My name's Zen.
I'm Shirayuki.
Nice to meet you, Shirayuki.
It was half your fault that I missed
my landing in the first place.
Huh?
This is an unoccupied house,
but we hang out here.
And the one losing at
chess over there is Mitsuhide,
and the one winning easily is Kiki.
Zen, how can you say for sure
that I'm losing without even looking?
I can just tell.
You are losing.
Okay, that should do it.
Wow, you're good at this, Shirayuki.
I'm used to it.
I told you that I'm an herbalist, right?
Oh yeah, you did.
Well, why did an herbalist
like you run away from home?
That's not important.
I'm going for a walk.
Well, why did you come with me?
It'd be dishonorable as a gentleman to allow
an injured girl to go into the woods alone.
Weirdo.
I got used to the mountains and
forests while studying to be an herbalist.
The time and air flow differently
from the town here, and it feels so good.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Those were your honest feelings just now, huh?
Ow!
Ow...
Oh, it's caught.
You have a strand that's longer than the others.
Huh?
Oh, I must've missed it.
Sorry, Zen. Will you cut it off for me?
Huh?
It doesn't have to be straight.
No, no. I can't cut a woman's hair!
Does cutting off your long hair have something
to do with why you ran away from home?
If you tell me the reason, I can help you.
You're a terrible person.
Hm?
You were told to become his concubine?!
By a famous rich boy who learned to speak
in the red-light district and ate silver coins.
He thought red hair was unusual
and wanted to keep it by him.
If I did as he said, it'd be like he was
buying an apple at the fruit seller's.
--Shirayuki--
--That's why I thought I'd
have him tire of it little by little
and left my hair behind.
That was a great decision!
Huh?
Good job getting away from that lowlife.
I mean, it's your precious red.
My precious red?
Yeah.
Red is supposed to be the color of fate, right?
Even if it's annoying now,
it might connect to something
good when you least expect it.
Y-You have an amazing way of thinking!
What? Is that respect?
She doesn't seem suspicious after all, huh?
Not only that, but Zen seems to really like her.
What?
That's the ribbon I tied my hair in!
Huh?
So you were from Tanbarun, huh?
The person who sent this came all the
way to the border to get you, you know.
He seems to be a very spiteful gentleman.
Right?
This is no laughing matter!
Was this matter so serious that
you had to run across the border?
It's because of who he is...
It was the first prince of Tanbarun...
Raj!
That... idiot... prince... huh...?
Are you all right?
He's such a huge idiot that rumors
even spread to the neighboring countries.
It's because of who he is, huh?
He probably had people looking
through all the border crossing records.
He would go that far, huh?
If there's something he wants,
he probably already counts it as his own.
Even if it means caging it? No way, right...?
Hm?
It's starting to go bad.
This red is no good anymore.
Just kidding...
Zen?
Zen...
You're so impolite.
Don't do that, Zen. You should get it yourself.
What're ya--
You should either talk or eat. Don't do both.
I didn't call you. Stay out of it!
Man, that hurts.
Zen!
What?!
I said something stupid. Sorry.
Shirayuki. You shouldn't eat that apple.
Huh?
Kiki, Mitsuhide... Don't get... mad...
Zen!
What's wrong, Zen?
It's poisoned!
Do you have an antidote?!
Please wait a moment!
It's no use. I can't prepare one with this.
If I don't hurry...
Oh? Miss Shirayuki was
not the one who ate the apple?
Who're you?!
You're...
Hmm... Oh, well.
What do you mean?!
Do not worry. A certain person has the antidote.
I trust you will come with me quietly?
Oh, so it's you? I see.
I am surprised.
The red hair you left behind was real, huh?
Um, what about the antidote for my friend?
Hang on a sec.
Actually, Miss Shirayuki...
The world is a frightening place.
The fact that I courted you and
you ran away has made me a laughingstock
in town and in the royal palace.
Man, thanks to that,
public opinion of me has plunged.
However, the rumors all
agree that it's your fault.
So, in order to clear my good name,
I'll have you ask to be my concubine.
Even if you're just a lowly town girl,
I didn't want to cause a woman embarrassment,
so this is the solution I painstakingly came to.
A-Am I hearing things?
Um, more importantly, what about the antidote?
Do you think I could get the
antidote for my friend, Prince Raj?
Oh, right. If you just nod your head,
I will have it delivered, promptly.
Or, would you rather
I have this delivered instead?
Red is supposed to be the color of fate, right?
Even if it's annoying now,
it might connect to something
good when you least expect it.
I... to that person who gave me those words...
Hmm...
For me, now that I know you
are so easy on the eyes,
I do not want you to be far from me.
Wh-What...?
Oh, my apologies.
Prince Raj. Take me as you wish.
Wait, stay back!
Huh?
I object!
Zen!
Bastard!
Will you please stop retching such
dirty jokes that sully that girl's ears.
Zen!
Hey, Shirayuki. Tie this for me.
Huh? Wait, before that, what about your body?
I've been building up an immunity to
poison slowly in case I ever got poisoned.
But--
I see!
So you are the man who was poisoned!
Oh, that was unfortunate.
I was planning on making Miss Shirayuki
immobile and taking her home with me.
So you're the one who
handed over those apples, huh?
Watch how you speak to me, boy.
There's a big difference
between our social status!
Excuse me, first prince of Tanbarun,
Prince Raj Schenazade.
Huh?
Well, this is annoying,
but let me introduce myself.
Hm? That crest is...
Nice to meet you.
I am the second prince of the
kingdom of Clarines, Zen Wisteria!
Second...
P-Prince...
Z-Zen, get a hold of yourself!
Do you know who I am?
What's one plus one?!
I'm serious, Shirayuki.
But I never thought I'd be poisoned by a
prince from a neighboring kingdom, Prince Raj.
You... You... You have
no proof that I have the poison!
There's plenty, isn't there?
We can test that in an official inquiry.
Th-That's...
Well then, why don't have a trade, idiot prince.
If you don't want your
foolish actions to be made public,
then swear you will never approach
Shirayuki again or say her name.
How do you know Shirayuki--
A-All right! I promise!
I just swore!
Shirayuki, I'm sure you have
a ton of things to say to him.
Huh?
If you're going to complain,
you should do it now.
Let it all out.
Okay.
Prince Raj. This is hoping you get better.
Because it looks like you're
so surprised you can't get up.
Also...
Yes?
...hurry up and give the antidote to Zen.
Okay...
Thanks.
What is it, Shirayuki?
Thanks for helping me.
But, I'm sorry.
I only became poison to you.
Is that supposed to be funny?
Because I was poisoned
by an apple, and you're red?
Not really...
It's all right. It's not something
you need to apologize for, Shirayuki.
Zen ate it himself.
Zen, Mitsuhide, and I should
have been more careful.
That's all.
Mitsuhide carried on like he would die
if Zen died and got all teary-eyed.
Don't tell about that!
How sad.
Okay, okay. Next time, if I get fruit,
I'll have Mitsuhide peel it before I eat it.
Was that what we were talking about?!
Shirayuki, do you remember
what I said in the forest?
For me, I hope the fact that
we're here together right now is fate.
We were in the forest you were
heading toward on your journey,
where we met and tried to protect each other.
Whether that's poison
that's only found in this place,
or connections for the future
is something you can decide.
Is that okay for me to decide?
Of course! I'm deciding my own fate.
After you decide, it's up to you whether
or not you follow that path, right?
Zen, you--
What?
You really do have an amazing way of thinking.
But it's not how I think, it's how I live.
What's your answer?
It's literally my own story.
If I had my wish,
on the path in front of us after this encounter,
the sound of pages turning in this story
will echo like the sound of
footsteps one on top of the other.
I...
I could finally see you, Shirayuki.
Clarines is a nice place.
Sorry to make you wait.
What? Shirayuki's not here?
The reason I decided to come to this country...
Did you decide to stop running, Red?
"Episode 2: Following the Sound of Your Heart"