I don't know how much I will be able to
give back in return for what I get from you.
But even so, I want to be with you from now on.
That day, when Zen was leaving...
...he said, "See you later," as usual.
That was reassuring.
"Episode 12: Goodbye to the Beginning"
Oh, it's so lively.
Everyone looks like they're having fun.
Open Castle Day? What's that?
It's an event that happens once every few years
where a corner of the castle
is opened up to the public.
Really?
There are various kinds
of entertainment, as well.
Even so, us herbalists have work as usual.
Once you reach a good stopping place
with your work, you can go look.
Oh, okay!
Seems like something Zen would like.
That area is open right now,
so there are a lot of people, Shirayuki.
This way.
Huh?
Oh, Shirayuki...
Wait, Prince Zen?
I think today will be busy,
but I'm counting on you!
Y-Yes, sir--
Leave it to us!
H-Hey, I was going to say that!
Did you know it was me right away?
I knew from your voice...
But why are you dressed as a guard?
I had some time, so I was
looking around as I kept watch.
To see people in the castle at work,
and see how the citizens were doing.
There aren't many opportunities
to see both at the same time.
That's very like you,
but don't make anyone mad.
Also, Shirayuki, I thought
maybe I'd be able to see you...
...just the two of us.
The two...?
Something dropped.
I-It's fine, it's fine!
You came too soon... you guys...
Did we interrupt, Master?
Hey, Shirayuki.
Zen, we were looking for you.
Yeah. Even if the parts of the castle
that have been opened up are limited,
I thought I told you to
narrow your area of activity.
Sorry for walking around on my own.
Mitsuhide was starting to panic.
Obi, you don't have to tell him that.
Kiki, do I still have time?
A little.
I see. What about you, Shirayuki?
Oh, yeah.
Then, it's decided!
Why don't we go observe what's going
on around the castle, the five of us?
Welcome! Welcome!
Wow, there are food stalls, too?
We brought them in from
the castle town just for today.
Oh, there's alcohol, too.
Don't drink right now.
Hurry, hurry!
Whoops. Look in front
of you when you run, okay?
There are more people now.
Because it's almost lunchtime already.
Oh? You wear stuff like that, Miss?
Yeah, it depends on the place,
but when there are a lot of people,
it's easier to walk around like this.
Oh yeah? Now that you mention it,
your hair does stand out.
Oh? Looks like something's
starting on the other side.
I wonder what it is?
Shall we take a look?
Did Shirayuki run into some trouble before?
I see... Then, I can't blame her for hiding it.
I know. It's hard having idiots around.
Even though it's so pretty...
Shirayuki--
Hm?
That day, I heard from Zen.
Kiki, Obi, Mitsuhide.
From now on, I will take a path that allows
me to be with Shirayuki in this kingdom.
I told her that that was what I wanted.
What did she...?
She took my hand.
Really, Zen?
I see...
Zen said that he would take a path
that let him be with you from now on.
Shirayuki, you want that, too, right?
Yes, I do.
Okay, do your best. We'll be with you, too.
Right!
Oh!
Oh? Where's Obi?
Oh...
That's it! Nanaki wins!
Master! I won!
Look, here's the prize!
What are you doing going off on your own?
What the heck is Nanaki, anyway?
Times like that, it's cooler to use
a fake name, don't you think?
I don't understand it at all.
Forget about what's cool, I'm more
interested in how you became so agile, Obi.
Mitsuhide, wanna fight me sometime?
Oh, sure!
Zen, it's about time.
Right. Well, see you later.
Okay.
Obi, I'm leaving Shirayuki to you.
Let's go and see the
master when he appears, too.
Zen?
Before that, Miss--
You can have this.
It's the prize for winning.
A hair ornament from another kingdom.
Make sure to show the master later.
--Prince Izana!
--Prince Zen!
Prince Zen has become very dignified.
He looks like a different person.
--Prince!
Zen, have you changed
your thinking since then?
About what?
I was wondering what you
were going to do with the girl.
Lord Brother, you wish to speak of that now?
Yeah.
Of course, I have been thinking about it.
About the future...
Zen...
I see him around the castle sometimes,
and there are times like what we just had...
The feeling that he's next to me
is still left in my ears and my hands...
But in this castle,
I am still this far away from him...
Even so, Zen is always...
Good work.
What will you do after this?
Hm, let's see...
Ryu!
Do you know where Shirayuki is?
Did something happen?
It looks like someone's been injured!
Are you trying to test me?
No, of course not--
Then, why did you say such a thing?
This is a place of celebration.
It is not fitting.
I just wanted to know
you better, your highness--
Ow...
She missed a step...
Pain medicine! Do you have pain medicine?
I still have to go on!
What?!
I said--
O-Ouch...
Ow...
The bone is broken.
If you force it to move,
it'll take longer to heal, Miss.
No...
Damn!
This play was supposed to do well
so I could be allowed into the castle
and have the princes fall in love with me.
Is what she says.
You just want a reward so you
can make new costumes, don't you?
Of course! I'm an actress!
I want to stand on a
grand stage in beautiful clothes,
and have my name known
throughout Clarines one day...
Oh dear, how embarrassing.
No, I think it's cool.
Shirayuki.
Right.
Red hair?
First, I'll stabilize the injured part.
You... Will you stand in for her?
Huh?
Wh...?!
Please. Please go on stage as the princess!
Huh?
What?!
I must see if that prince is
really suitable for my princess.
However, the prince is careful,
and is never alone.
Are you ready?
I must hurry. It will be too late after
something has happened. Too late!
H-Here I go.
R-Right...
What's wrong, Master?
It... nothing...
The one on stage right now is
the knight who serves the princess.
The night before the wedding,
the knight will test the prince to see
if he is a suitable partner for the princess
by crossing swords with him.
Before that, there's just one
place where the princess appears,
but she only has one line.
You can just follow my lead for where to stand.
I-I understand!
I can hide my hair, right?
Yes, it's better that way, isn't it?
It's a waste, though.
I bet just that would make the audience happy.
I swear! Tonight, on my sword! On this body!
Okay, you're almost up.
Show me what you've got!
You're the stand-in?
I-I look forward to working with you!
What?!
--Even if you tell me
to do that all of a sudden--
--Shh!
It's fine, just do as I say!
If you do it, we'll definitely rise from being
a third-rate troupe to being stars in no time!
I'm counting on you!
Fine...
Okay, do your best!
R-Right!
I hope the actress' injury wasn't too bad.
Yeah... Huh?
Something wrong?
Kiki, is that...
...Shirayuki?!
Princess! Please, listen to me!
Y-Yes!
Good, she got it out.
She's really nervous, huh?
She'll be fine now.
All she has left is to be
kissed on the back of her hand.
Is what she said. Master?
I can't allow it.
Huh?
Of course I can't. She's not an actor.
There's no need to go that far.
I'll go talk to the troupe leader.
I wonder what's going on?
The prince is acting differently from usual.
Princess, will you pray upon my sword?
Princess...
Come on, hurry!
What are you planning, Mr. Troupe Leader?
To expose the princess' hair?
Why do that?
After finding a stand-in with such
rare red hair, how could I leave it alone?
You know what...
You can't stop it now.
With this, our troupe
will become a huge success!
Because her hair will lend the
brightest color to our performance!
Here it comes! The climax of today's play!
You... are my wife.
You have to stop this quickly!
Sir Knight, a moment?
Huh?!
Wh-What are you trying to do?
Don't act stupid in front of my master.
That's not something for people to gawk at.
Stay back, Princess.
The sword to protect you is still mine!
What?
Your highness, en garde!
I'm sorry, herbalist!
I almost couldn't keep my promise!
Um...
Good work.
Why is Zen...?
Oh, that? It's the job of the real
prince to protect the princess, right?
They must've been really important to him...
Your hair, and the kiss
on the back of your hand...
Huh...?
The master looked like
he really hated the thought of it.
He's so easy to read.
He's cool, isn't he?
Zen always shows me...
...his feelings...
...and his passion...
That's why I know, too, how important they are.
I didn't think I'd stand
on a stage with you, Zen.
Seriously. I'd like to watch the same
play as part of the audience next time.
Yeah.
But it was a strange experience being
a knight drawing his sword against a prince.
I even got this mask.
It looks good on you, Sir Knight.
That's...
Oh, I got it from Obi.
He said it was the prize
from the martial arts tournament.
That guy...
It's kind of frustrating...
Huh?
But it looks good on you.
I see. I guess I'll keep it on, then.
What did you do with your hair
when you were living in Tanbarun?
I walked around without anything.
Even after I moved to Clarines,
I did the same, at first.
Now that you mention it, I guess that's true.
I don't know if it's okay to ask, but there's
something I've been thinking about for a while.
Did you run into problems?
Even before Raj.
There were a lot, but I didn't always lose.
My grandparents were very strong people.
Grandparents?
That's right. The two of
them taught me a lot of things.
They thought ahead to
when I would one day be alone,
and they said, even when there
isn't anything you can count on,
you can always keep trying your
best at what you can do by yourself.
That's what they taught me.
I see.
I did think that you liked to do things
yourself instead of relying on others to help.
Their teaching was the basis of that, huh?
But, recently...
Hm?
I-I rely on you, Zen!
I don't know if I'm showing you properly,
but right now, I really am...
I think that's why I can do my best.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad I didn't lose
somewhere along the way...
Zen. Will you put out a hand?
Hm? Sure...
I'm glad I was able to come here, Zen.
I-I'm not used to stuff like this...
Sorry if it was weird...
N-No, uh...
Oh, what're those?
It's your first time seeing them?
It's how Open Castle Day ends.
People wish on the lights
and send them into the sky.
Wanna take a closer look?
Yeah!
Oh, Shirayuki!
Just until we get outside.
Zen...
Why are you calling my name?
Don't try to dodge the issue!
I told you to be careful of your actions!
Apparently, Mitsuhide saw the play.
That's why...
Wow, it's so pretty!
What?
Mitsuhide, you're always worrying
about the master, aren't you?
That's because he's my beloved master.
When you fought and
he wouldn't talk to you for a day,
you didn't eat a thing, did you?
I endured it for a day!
When it went to two days,
that was hard, though.
Two days? Woah, you're so childish, Master.
You guys...
Listen, I talked to Shirayuki about this, too,
but I'm not planning to think
about a future without you guys.
Zen, look! It's amazing!
He's kind of unfair sometimes, isn't he?
Because that's the kind of prince he is.
You're going to have a hard time, too, Obi.
On this path that we continue on,
how many more chances will
we get to have such peaceful times?
I'm sure I can find
happiness in taking this path...
I will continue to walk
on in order to find it...
Into the future with everyone...