We're dividing up into two?
Yeah. The waterway is a big place.
The rabbit and number 745--
Nothing would be better
than disposing of the both of them.
Are you sure they'll show up?
My instinct says yes.
Very well.
All right, let's go.
Mr. Mado, what are those?
Better that you don't know.
Mom?
Touka...
Where have you been?
None of your business.
If there's anything that I can do...
There probably isn't
anything that you can do now.
Hinami?
Hinami!
Why?
Tell me, oh tell me, the way it works
Who is that inside of me?
Here in this broken-down,
broken-down world,
you laugh, without seeing a thing
I'm just so damaged,
I hold my breath and freeze
Breakable, unbreakable;
shakable, unshakable
When I found you, it shook me
In this twisted world, I'm gradually
growing transparent and vanishing
Don't look for me; don't look at me
I don't wish to hurt you in a world
of someone else's imagining
Remember who I am
Hinami...
Touka!
No good! She's not here,
either! How about you?
Where is she?
You don't suppose...
Where is this?
Th-This is where Mrs. Ryoko...
Hinami...
Nobody else...
That's close!
Where is she?
Touka?
Is that...?
The man from before! This is bad!
Hinami!
That agility! It's the rabbit, all right!
Who are you?
Hinami...
Hinami, what is that?
It's... Mom...
Let's go, Hinami!
It's too dangerous here.
No!
Is it wrong for ghouls to live?
I want to go be with Mom.
Take me there. Take me where Mom is.
I'm begging you.
Hinami...
I miss... Mom.
One of the rabbit's friends?
I don't have time to waste
with you. Why don't you step aside?
You're not going anywhere!
Has your wound healed yet, rabbit?
Trying to lure us out here with false stories
is a ploy so cheap as to be pitiful.
Childish, childish.
Oh, right, did you like the present I left?
I'm sure you miss your dear mother.
Why, you!
Don't screw around with me!
I won't let him go. I can't let
this man go there. That is my...
You're coming around, are you?
In that case...
You really aren't like the
other small fry around, huh?
Bounce around! Bounce around even more,
you little gnat!
You can't use your weapon around here.
I've always wanted to
ask your kind something.
You calmly prey on innocent people,
compulsively devouring them.
Why does your kind exist?
The children whose
parents have been killed...
The grief of those left behind...
The loneliness...
Have you ever thought about that?
Answer me!
Is the terror of having your
life hunted for no reason...
something you understand?
Having the people dear
to you killed like worms...
Do you understand what that feels like?
Why, you...!
The rabbit killed one of my friends.
Why was he killed?
Because he was an investigator?
Because he was human? Get real!
Where was there any
reason why he had to be killed?
Tell me, what reason was
there for Mrs. Ryoko to be killed!
This whole world is messed up.
It's you guys who are screwing it up!
If it weren't for you people...!
Die!
Well? You recognize this, don't you?
It's your...
beloved...
mother!
Quinques are made from
your kagunes, after all!
Lowlife bastard!
Ghouls are screwing up the world...
Is that really true?
Was there a reason why
Mrs. Ryoko was killed?
What about Hinami?
Hinami also had the lives of
those dear to her taken, didn't she?
Ghouls have feelings, too.
No different than humans do.
Why don't humans turn
their attention toward that?
--Why don't they try to understand?
--I'm not done yet!
It's something so obvious.
--It's something so simple.
--You're pretty tough!
I'm the only one... who is aware
of it... who can communicate it...
Only me, the ghoul...
Only me, the human...
I'm the only one.
You're wrong...
It's not the world... that is messed up...
Sure, there are ghouls who
have taken the wrong path...
but... not all ghouls are like that.
We should... learn more...
Both humans... and ghouls...
It's not just ghouls who
are screwing up the world...
It's you, too.
What are you talking about?
You won't understand, will you?
Well then...
I'll make you understand.
You should make for some fine material.
However, that couple put
together is wonderfully easy to use.
When I put your mother down
with your father, it was a blast!
Stop... that...
Now then, which one
should I finish you off with?
I'll kill you, you filthy-ass geezer!
You're a dirty-mouthed ghoul.
Stop!
What do I do... to get through to him?
What do I do to make
us understand each other?
We can't compete with each other.
We can't keep taking from each other.
Both humans... and ghouls...
We have to break... the chain of grief.
So what do I do to do that?
Enough, already!
I don't have time to waste on you.
Why, you...
I can't let him go there.
If I can just do something about that...
But I don't have the strength.
That's it... I guess
that's the only way, isn't it?
If so, then now... just this once...
I will accept you, who are inside me...
Miss Rize!
Feels like my appetite
is going to overcome me...
I'm aware of myself
slipping toward hedonism...
But I won't lose sight... of the person I am.
He's going after the quinque?!
With this much strength...
Don't you mock me!
Now...
he can no longer fight.
Without my quinque,
there's nothing more...
No!
Once the foe is before you,
then even if it costs your arms and legs...
Please, run away...
The way this is headed,
I am going to kill you...
So... run away...!
Don't be ridiculous!
I would never run from a ghoul!
Hurry!
Go!
I'm begging you...
Don't make me a killer.
Would you say the same
thing if you were a ghoul?
What's wrong with wanting to be alive?
If people are all we can eat,
what choice do we have?
How are we supposed to live right
with our bodies the way they are?!
How, I ask! Die! Die, die, die, die!
You can all die!
I just...
want to live, the same as you.
I can't bear to hear any more.
--This will finish you!
--No!
My quinque...
Is gone?
No,
what's gone is my right hand.
Hinami?
Don't... hurt Big Sister anymore.
Don't use Mom and Dad for that!
Ha-ha! Incredible!
Fantastic! You've gone
and inherited only the best
from your mother and father! I want it!
Give it to me!
Hinami...
finish him off.
I can't.
He's the one who killed your parents.
I don't care... about that.
I don't care... about revenge.
Huh?
I'm just sad, that's all.
I miss Mom and Dad. I'm just sad, that's all.
Mom... Dad... I'm lonely all by myself!
Outstanding...
Yes... She should be with her family.
And then, she can become my quinque!
That's gone and done it...
Like it's even worth
it for your kind to live...
Don't make me laugh...
I'm not through yet.
I have to get back at your kind...
Not until I get him...
the one-eyed... and bury him myself...
I can't... die yet...
That ghoul...
Why did he let me go?
He was crying.
It's no use... I can't control it...
No! Somebody... help!
Flesh! I need flesh!
No... If I don't do something...
Who... is that?
Right now, I am awfully hungry.
You know?
I think I know now why Yoshimura
has taken such an interest in you.
Now, I, too, want to see
what you're going to accomplish
from here on out.
Come home, Ken.
Mr. Yomo...
What have I done?
Eat this.
You'll feel better.
You had to wear these.
Is actually having to touch us...
really that bad?!
Hinami!
Touka...?
Is it okay to live?
Is it okay for me to be alive?
Hinami...
Back there, Mrs. Ryoko...
was telling you to live, I believe.
Though the city sleeps,
its buildings are always
under construction
Urban planning carries on
Its belt lines morphing, snakes interlocking,
stirring up endorphins,
and off you go, go, go
Souls ascend up into the night sky
Their procession and
their faith both resembling
an aberrant riddle
Our as-yet-empty tomorrows
are an all but black shade of gray
Without any possibilities
an all but black shade of gray
Ah, tonight, you're the one I want
Saints
Ah, I want you to signal the end
Good grief, imagine,
me being done in back there.
Must be concerning for Amon.
I wonder what kind of eternal
reward I get in the afterlife.
"For Ghoul Use"
Man, this bathwater is great.
It hits the spot.
It feels so good, I might lose my head.
My head!
"Next time: 'Birdcage'"
Someone sure is making a racket.
It's your imagination.
"Layout: Katsuya Yamada"