24 Hours
with Asamori-san
Today's
release!
I'll buy you!
Rokuhara's
first work.
24 Hours
The Taiga Betrayal
with Asamori-san
Recommended
Released
Games
Today
The Taiga Betrayal
Recommended
Games
24 Hours
The Taiga Betrayal
with Asamori-san
Recommended
Released
Games
Today
Girls Beyond
the Wasteland
Zetsubou to kakki wa hitoe
Despair and energy are one and the same
Jinsei wa hakanakute
Life is short
Kusubutte irarenai
We can't stay like this forever
Dakara arukidasou
So let's start walking forward
Yukedo hatenai kono michi o
What are you moving towards
Nani o hoshite susundeiku
On this endless road?
Mizu o motome samayou you ni
You won't get anywhere with hope without desire
Yoku no nai kibou ni mirai wa nai
As if you're wandering looking only for water
Monogatari no algorithm
The pilgrims pursue
Tadoru junreishatachi
The algorithm of the story
Mune ni yadoru sono shin'nen ga
The faith in our hearts
Death march wo ikinokoru sube
Helps us survive this death march
Imagination no flow
The imagination flows!
Junsui no mama ja iranai kanaetai dattara
You can't stay pure if you want your dream to come true
Furenai unmei wo egakidasou
Let's create an impossible fate
Tada matteitatte tsumannai
It's boring just waiting around
Sou kanjiteitan janai
That's how you felt, right?
Yume wa jibun de ubaitsukamu diamond
Your dreams are a diamond you have to take for yourself
Chousen no turn
It's our turn for challenge
Jounetsu no zone
The passionate zone
Tomo ni tatte
Let's stand together
Fumidashite mezasu kouya wo
Take our first steps as we aim for the wasteland
"Beyond."
At or on the further side of something.
You should have learned that word in middle school.
Combine that with the English word "youth"
for the phrase "beyond youth".
Beyond the age of youth.
You are all in the midst of your age of youth.
But what lies beyond that?
Have you thought about what lies beyond youth?
Um!
What?!
No, you guys go first.
No, you say it, Bunta.
No, I'm fine.
What's fine?!
You're weird.
Later.
Y-yeah.
Later!
Bye bye!
Now that I remember, Nakajima made
that awesome flip today in gym.
Oh, you're right. That was crazy.
Oh, yeah?
I can't believe he made the landing
on that triple twist flip.
That deserved a gold medal.
Look, there's not enough consistency!
What?! There is too!
A consistency called love!
All that needs to be consistent are their lower halves!
Ugh, I'm so done with this.
Um, you heading up to the club room, too, Ando-san?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Yo.
Tori-chan!
A-are you all going to the club room?
Yeah.
Is it alright if I join you?
Yeah, I mean, we're going to the same place.
Um! Today's really our release date, right?
Huh? Yeah, why?
It just hasn't fully hit me yet.
You too, Tori-chan?!
I haven't felt it yet, either.
Seriously? Me too!
Oh, so everyone's feeling the same way!
I'm like "oh man, it's really on sale?"
Yeah, yeah!
I know, right?
What're you doing? Open it already!
Huh? Oh, yeah...
Are you nervous, Bunta?
S-shut up! I am not!
Is that so?
Thank you for calling.
Thank you very much.
Umm...
Kuroda-san?
Wh-wha--
What are you doing?! Hurry up and come in!
Um, that just now, was it...
It's just as I predicted.
We have a repeat order.
Huh?
All 3,000 of our initial units sold in an instant.
The shops are making additional orders.
I just finished up with ZEGA, they discussed
a proposal for more production.
How much more do they want?
Twice our initial order.
Twice?!
That many?!
They said they'd all sell right away.
So, combining that with the other numbers...
T-that's... nine thousand...
Whoa.
And looking at Typhoon's sales...
They sold out of all 4,000 of their initial order as well.
Huh?
They had more straight from the beginning!
That's so unfair!
S-so we lost.
No, their repeat order is different.
We have a repeat order of 6,000.
Theirs is only 2,000.
Congratulations. We've won.
Yes!
Atomu!
We did it, Bunta!
9,000 versus 6,000, isn't that kinda crazy?
Maybe we're geniuses!
We did it!
Asamori-san is a low-priced game.
"Taiga", on the other hand, is a full-priced game.
The price difference may have
influenced the difference in sales.
So we had the advantage from the start,
just 'cause we went with sale numbers?
I didn't know if we would win until today.
This is a direct result from our genuine hard work.
Kuroda-san?
What's up?
What's this?
To celebrate?
It's a cake, right?
Damn, you prepped well for this, Kuroda.
Huh?
Kuroda-san?
Brother!
Wait!
Sorry to interrupt.
Thanks.
Yakiniku
Kaifutei
Cheers!
Yakiniku Kaifutei
That hits the spot!
After working hard, you've gotta
drink a cold one of these!
That's cola... right?
Yup, cola.
Bunta, cook up some meat! Meat!
Alright, alright.
I wanna have some skirt steak. The top cut.
The top?! Can we really order that?
Then let's do the special cut.
That's even more expensive!
What do you want to eat, Atomu?
I'll have the beef tongue, I guess?
Is the salted beef tongue good?
How about you, Yuka?
One order of kalbi!
Then let's get the special cut of all of that!
No, the special cut is too much...
Let's get the special cut.
Are you sure?!
It's way tougher than the top cut!
It's a seriously heavy cut!
What're you talking about?
T-then I'll have the special green onion-stuffed cut.
Torry's way less hesitant than she used to be, huh?
Huh? Y-you think so?
At first you'd be like...
"I-I think everything is fine like this..."
You said that, right?
Yeah, yeah!
Huh? Whaa?
Really? I think she was always like this.
Shyness and a lack thereof can coexist.
So you can have your cake and eat it, too?
Either way, it's good that you're more honest.
Just be yourself!
You take that to the extreme, though, Yuka.
What'd you say?!
But man, there aren't many teams out there
that make it to the end
with everyone being honest
and saying how they feel.
W-what?
For once, we agree.
Hey, I was cooking that!
Give it back!
It's the rules of the wasteland.
If you didn't want me to take it,
you should've written your name on it.
The hell?!
C'mon, it's all cooked, so let's eat, okay?
Excuse me, we'd like to put in an order.
Alright, here we are.
Um, one skirt steak, kalbi, beef tongue,
and a green onion stuffed...
All special cuts!
Coming right up!
Huh?
What?!
Brother?!
Kuroda's brother?!
Why are you here?!
Why? I work here part time!
At a yakiniku restaurant?
The hourly pay's great.
But what about your debt?
The money you're making will
go into your next work.
Thanks to all of you, I've started moving again.
Thank you so much, and...
I'm so sorry.
Please, it's alright.
That's all in the past for us.
Oh, that's right, hold on a sec!
Hopefully this makes up for it a little!
Leaves?!
I want meat! Meat!
I'd like something sweet...
But I just work part-time...
Uh, you could have it if you like.
Huh, me?
Yeah. You seem like a nice guy
who'd eat this kinda stuff.
A "nice guy?"
Crap, he's reopening Atomu's old wounds!
Hey, uh, I'll eat it!
Wow, I love veggies, they're so yummy!
She said she loved me.
She said she loved nice guys.
Nice guys...
I'm sorry my brother was so rude.
That's my kalbi!
It's really juicy 'n warm!
Normies?!
Burn 'em all! No, cook 'em!
Cook all the normies alive!
Yay! Cook up that meat!
Atomu, eat, eat! Okay?
Meat!
Man, I ate a lot!
I don't want to see meat for a while.
Me too.
I ate so much meat, there's no way
they can call a vegetarian beta, yeah?
Kuroda-san? What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
This ice cream is great!
I want some, too.
Me too.
Thanks!
Kuroda-san, want some?
I'm alright.
Then I'll take it!
I'm dual-wielding!
The life of luxury.
I'm surprised you're not cold.
You don't get it.
It's 'cause it's daring!
I'm still surprised we actually won.
You didn't think we'd win?
No, it's not that.
Perhaps it was more dangerous for us
in the long run than just on the day of release.
Asamori-san was written in an easygoing,
everyday setting, so people are quick to pick it up.
On the other hand,
"Taiga" is a game with a lot of depth,
so it will continue to sell
hundreds of units every month.
Wow.
There may not be many people talking about
Asamori-san a year from now.
But "Taiga" might end up being a work that
people are talking about many years down the line.
I've gotta work harder, then.
This is just the beginning for us!
Actually, there was something
I wanted to ask you all.
I was thinking of dissolving Rokuhara.
What?
Dissolving?
Why? What happened to making two games?
That's right! You said we would!
It was really fun.
I didn't know that working together with people
and making something could be so fun.
No, I should have known.
But it was so much more fun than I'd thought.
That's why...
That's why I want to put an end to
everything the past me has done.
And I want to start over again.
I want to make a game from square one.
Why don't we make a game
purely for ourselves this time?
Purely for ourselves?
It means exactly what it sounds like.
Instead of worrying about what will and won't sell,
let's make something we really
want to make and enjoy making it.
It can be about anything.
Everyone puts in their input
and decides on a project.
The deadline will be flexible,
and we can really think the quality through.
And of course, this time I'll make sure
you're properly compensated.
How about it?
Would you like to make a game with me once more?
No.
I don't want to do it like that.
Hojo-kun.
I can't make a game with you in
such a lukewarm manner.
Huh?
I feel the same way.
I don't get why we have to pretend to be friends.
Me too!
Now that I've debuted,
my second work is pretty important!
I like having fun, but I dunno if I
can handle no schedule.
I thought professionals did their best
within their time limit?
But is that what you all want?
This world is a wasteland, isn't it?!
That's why you can't survive just doing what you want.
Only the ones with passion burning in their hearts
can grasp their dreams in this cruel wasteland!
Didn't you teach me that, Kuroda-san?
Yes. That's correct.
Let's win.
We'll definitely win next time, too!
Definitely?!
Of course!
I'll work hard!
Hells yeah!
Thank you.
Let's all work hard together.
Okay! So let's do a BL game th--
No!
What? Why? You meanie.
Mitsuteru-san
Calling
Hello?
Buntarou, did you hear the numbers?
Yes. We won, I heard.
About that.
Taiko-san's already started complaining about it.
Are you freakin' kidding me?!
Why me?!
She's making a big fuss about having to
bow down to high schoolers.
Do you think it'd be alright if I was the only one who--
No. I'm really looking forward to
Taiko-san bowing down to us.
You're more of a sadist than I thought.
Please. I'm begging you!
Hmmm... huh?
Hello, this is Kuroda.
About picking someone to join them.
How about you never ask that of us again?
Right. Then you owe us one.
Making people owe you is the best feeling ever.
Um, well, that's what my boss says,
so I guess that settles it.
Alright.
But all things aside, if you look at
the script itself, I win, right?
We won by units!
I read a bunch of reviews,
and mine had much higher ratings!
We still won our competition!
But I won the game, yeah?
I have no idea what you're talking about, Ohgi-san!
No, I'm the one who doesn't understand you!
But there was a ridiculous ending to our battle.
No, no, no...
PC game sales rankings
A few days later, I checked the
sales rankings on a big online store.
But the results were...
ChuChu.com
What are you looking for?
Games
1st      Wear LOVE: It feels best when you're wearing me!
2nd      24 Hours with Asamori-san
3rd      The Taiga Betrayal
"1st: Wear LOVE: It feels best when you're wearing me?!"
What kind of game is that?
It's a sexy battle game where the main character
gets turned into a suit of armor by a curse
and protects the heroine while also fighting evil.
Sounds boring.
That was written and produced by Hosokawa-san.
I hear it sold 20,000 copies.
And it's hard to find in stores.
Are you kidding me?
Computing Weekly
The game writer Hosokawa is huge in the media.
All about Hosokawa
His game quickly got an anime adaptation,
and of course a manga and
novel adaptation, and also a movie,
"Games are like parfaits!"
and an idol group was born from the project.
Another big project from
producer and writer
Blooters!
The world had a Hosokawa Fever like no other.
Signing Event
...Or so I thought.
Hosokawa-san?
Hello?
Heyo, Hojo!
It's been a while.
Things are kinda crazy, huh?
For various reason,
I'm gonna have to fade away for a bit!
Sorry if it causes trouble for ya!
Buh-bye!
Huh? Hey!
Yes, hello?
Hello, this is Kawakoshishi Productions.
Is Hosokawa-san there?
Huh? No.
This is the Kawakado Editing department,
is Hosokawa-san--
I don't know.
Is Hosokawa-san--
No.
No!
Hosokawa-san--
He's not here.
Hosokawa-san got a bit uppity and took on
too many projects, then suddenly deflated,
and the Hosokawa Fever met its demise
as quickly as it'd begun.
Scary...
and the Hosokawa Fever met its demise
as quickly as it'd begun.
Then...
As for us...
How much longer?
Graduation Plans
You're the only one who hasn't turned it in.
Hojo-kun?
Kuroda-san, I thought you'd already
gone up to the club room.
I was talking with our teacher.
Then let's head up together.
Hold it! You can't leave until you finish this!
Sorry, sorry.
Here.
Did you do it right?
Yeah, I was serious about it!
I-I'm gonna check it, okay?
Employment Plans
I'm still looking for one.
What's Hosokawa-san going to do from now on?
I don't think he's going to work for anyone for a while.
Trying to restore your name to what it was
once it's gone down is really difficult.
That's the wasteland for you.
But suddenly returning and working as if
nothing happened is also part of the wasteland.
Getting inspiration!
We'll continue on.
Marching forth in this land where there's
no place for lip service.
Yuka
Come up to the roof!
I don't know what'll make us keep on...
Or what's waiting for us in the distance...
But no matter how reckless...
Even if we don't know when it'll fall apart...
No matter what little seams we tear apart...
Even so...
Atarashii sekai tobikome mirai ga yonderu
Jump into the new world, our future is calling
Yasashiku yorisottettai
I want to gently be by your side
Kimi no yume ouensasete
Let me support you and your dream
Chotto jiman dekiru mono
Someone who doesn't have
Nan ni mo motteinakute
Anything they can be proud of
Ki ga tsuitara shita bakari
On cloudy days when they realize
Mitsumeteta no cloudy days
They've only been looking at the ground
Sonna uyamuya shiteiru
I want to change
Futoumei na kimochi wa ne
That wavering, murky feeling
Jibun datte ni kaete hoshii
Into a shout of "I can do it!"
Hajimete zukushi de
When I'm first starting out
Tomadoi darake dakedo
I'm full of so many doubts
Watashi mo onaji da yo
It's the same for me, too
Atarashii sekai tobikome mirai ga matteru
Jump into the new world, our future is waiting
Hikari ni mitasareta toki motomete
Pursue a moment full of light
Gamushara ni ikeru shunkan sono saki ima da yo
The present awaits us after this frantic moment
Yasashiku yorisottettai
I want to gently be by your side
Dakara issho ni ganbarou
So let's all work hard together