Tsukiyama!
Mmm... Long time no see, Miss Kirishima.
What do you want?
As cold as ever, I see.
Well, I suppose that's
what's charming about you.
You disgust me, you prig.
You, with the eye patch...
You're new here, huh?
U-Um...
U-um...
What's your name?
K-Kaneki.
What a wondrous aroma.
Hey, you're interfering
with our work, and you're gross,
so get lost already.
You really are tactless, aren't you?
I'll be by some other
time to enjoy some coffee.
Some time when Mr. Yoshimura is around.
O-Okay...
Ravissant. See you later, Kaneki.
We'll meet again.
W-Who was that?
Watch out for that guy.
He's one of the 20th Ward's parasites.
Mmm, merci.
Kaneki, huh?
How intriguing...
that scent is.
Tell me, oh tell me, the way it works
Who is that inside of me?
Here in this broken-down,
broken-down world,
you laugh, without seeing a thing
I'm just so damaged,
I hold my breath and freeze
Breakable, unbreakable;
shakable, unshakable
When I found you, it shook me
In this twisted world, I'm gradually
growing transparent and vanishing
Don't look for me; don't look at me
I don't wish to hurt you in a world
of someone else's imagining
Remember who I am
What?
A jam bun, again?
It's all right. This is the best on-the-go food there is.
You can't! You're still a growing girl!
Eenie, meenie, miney, mo!
Fried chicken!
Here you go.
Huh? That's okay.
You can't survive on
bread alone. Here, eat this.
Geez...
I changed the seasoning
on it. What do you think?
Huh? What?
Ow!
Well, it's pretty good.
Ah, I think you're just saying that.
No, really.
Pass it! Pass it! Pass it! Pass it! Pass it!
Pass it... Pass it...
Compliments to the chef. I ate it, Yoriko.
"Monochrome of Rainbows"
Kaneki...
Hey.
Oh, hi, uh...
Tsukiyama Shu. May I?
Oh, be my guest.
Merci beaucoup.
Um, Mr. Tsukiyama,
what brings you to Kamii University?
What if I said... I'm here to see you?
Huh? Uh, well, I don't know.
This man is a gourmet,
one of the 20th Ward's pests.
You appear to be quite the bibliophile.
I heard so from one of Anteiku's regulars.
Oh, not really. I wouldn't go that far.
Books are nice, aren't they?
With just one sentence,
you can get lost in all sorts of dreams.
The way I think of it, literature
allows the reader's consciousness
to more deeply relish the
author the closer he comes to him.
And so, we freely walk
around the world of the story
from the yarn spinner's view.
It's only when you immerse
yourself in the world of a book
that you are able to
forget just who you are.
You like books, don't you?
It has been many a
story that has seen me through
some bitter and painful times.
He's a lot... like me...
What a surprise.
You read Takatsuki, too?
Oh, yes.
His style may be delicate,
but it also has eloquence,
and I'm terribly drawn to the
elusive way in which he writes.
I like his style of writing, too.
You don't say. Takatsuki, huh?
Listen, Kaneki,
there's this cafe that's
run by an owner who loves books.
If you like, how about going
there with me sometime?
Rumor has it that Takatsuki
Sen sometimes goes there, too.
Huh? Mr. Takatsuki?
Oh, uh, on second thought...
Miss Kirishima must
have said something to you.
No, it's just...
No, it's okay. I've always
been easily misunderstood.
I haven't had anyone to talk to
since Miss Kamishiro died, either.
Kamishiro? Miss Kamishiro Rize?
I sensed the same kind of
vibe from you that she had.
There aren't that many
ghouls who are also into books.
I just wanted a friend
who I could chat with
about the things I like,
in a nice, quiet place.
L-Listen...
i-if you'll settle for me...
All right, this Sunday at three o'clock.
He didn't seem like all that bad a person.
Kaneki, you can go home now.
Oh, okay.
Have a nice evening.
Oh, and Kaneki...
Yomo said he was
waiting downstairs for you.
Mr. Yomo? Downstairs?
Um, where are we?
He's as tight-lipped as always.
Doves have entered the 20th Ward.
Huh? You mean...
If it comes to it, you will be
responsible for protecting yourself.
Let's go!
H-Hold on!
You do a fair job of dodging
but you're hopeless at the rest of it.
R-Right.
Stop by here on days
you work. I'll train you.
All right.
Are you coming with me?
Huh?
There's someone who wants to meet you.
So you're Kaneki, are you?
I'm so glad you came to see me.
I've heard all about
you from Ren and U, here.
I'm Itori, and this is
my bar. Pleasure to meet you.
Th-The pleasure is mine.
Now, now, don't be so stiff! Relax, Kaneki!
U-Um... Have you all
known each other long?
Well, we're pretty much stuck together.
Way back when, Ren and
Uta were on terrible terms.
Because of them, the 4th Ward
was even crazier than it is now.
We're on good terms now, though, right?
I guess.
Ren really was beyond
anyone's control, once upon a time.
Th-That bad?
Mm-hmm. Kind of like
Miss Toka when she gets mad.
Ah, very similar!
That is scary, huh?
Enough talk about me.
Itori, didn't you have
something to say to him?
Ah, yes I do!
Here, this is for you.
Oh, no, I'm still underage.
It's not wine, you know!
Wah! Whoa!
Whoo-hoo! Amazing! I've
never seen this! A one-eyed ghoul!
Sorry, sorry. But right now,
it's just us ghouls around.
Here, a token of my apology.
I wonder if the other
one-eye is like him, too.
Who knows?
U-Um, is there someone else
besides me with only one, uh...
Oh, did that grab your attention?
Yes.
All right. Kaneki, you see,
if a human and a ghoul fall in love,
what do you think
you get if you cross them?
A human and a ghoul, you say?
They die.
Death from infirmity.
The chances of getting
pregnant itself are pretty low, though.
However, in extremely
rare cases, one is born;
a half-ghoul, half-human baby.
A half-human ghoul...
A half-blooded ghoul is far
superior to a full-blooded one.
And this one only had a red eye...
on the one side.
But then, those stories
are urban legend grade.
A one-eyed ghoul...
U-Um...
Oh? What is it? Ask me anything.
Do you know... Do you know
anything about Miss Kamishiro Rize?
Oh-ho... Why do you ask?
The whole reason my body got to
be this way started when I met her.
Mm-hmm...
And yet, I don't know a thing about her.
I see. Rize, huh?
She was a troublemaker,
whose death is shrouded in mystery.
Indeed, over the last few months,
that has been the talk of the town.
A mysterious death?
But it was an accident...
Oh? Do you really think that was
just a common accident, Kaneki Ken?
Itori...
That day, you see,
rumor has it that a person was
seen standing on top of the building,
at the same time the accident took place.
Huh? S-So then, it wasn't a coincidence?
Somebody killed Rize... or some such.
Itori!
I'm just saying! It's only a rumor. A rumor!
Who would... Who would have done that?
Kaneki...
Kaneki?
Oh, yes?
Has something happened?
Oh, no.
Um, Mr. Tsukiyama...
Hmm? What is it?
What did you used to
talk about with Miss Rize?
Oh, Miss Kaneshiro?
We talked about books...
and of course, we talked about dining.
Tsukiyama, I'm pleased by your invitation,
but I have absolutely no interest
in your members-only gourmet club.
W-Why not? Don't you wish to
have a taste of something higher?
Well, whatever you can arrange
on a plate for me won't be enough.
Sure, there's nothing
that beats flavor when eating,
but ghouls, pretending to be
high society, devoted to their palates?
It's comical how human that
would be, isn't it, Tsukiyama?
Why, that little...!
How dare an ignoble sow like her
make a mockery of my dining!
Um, M-Mr. Tsukiyama?
Ow!
Oh, how could I let that happen? I'm sorry!
It's all right. I just cut myself a little.
T-Tell you what, Kaneki,
I know it's not much of an apology,
but Miss Kamishiro's
favorite hangout is near here.
Would you like to go there?
Miss Rize's favorite place? Yes, I would.
All right. With that settled,
let's head there right now.
Is your finger all right?
Oh, yes. The bleeding
seems to have stopped.
I'll be sure to wash this later, and--
O-Oh, no, it's okay. Don't worry about it.
I'll wash it myself.
That was a close one. I can't
believe I let myself spook him.
Be cool... Keep it smooth, why don't you?
Tsukiyama Shu, you just
have to be patient a little longer.
Such tender sweetness, and...
mellow harmony...
This newly discovered treat...
is, as regards my happiness...
even better than discovering a new star!
Monsieur Savarin...
you were absolutely right...
Why am I even taking a shower, anyway?
Mr. Kaneki?
Oh, yes?
I have left some clothes
here for you. Please, be my guest.
Okay, thanks.
Miss Rize used to come here, too?
I brought you a cup of coffee.
Enjoy.
Uh, excuse me, where is Mr. Tsukiyama?
What is this?!
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for waiting.
Presenting today's main dish!
Today's entrée is an unusual cut of meat.
A ghoul, of all things!
Ghoul?
I'm not quite up for cannibalism.
It is being furnished by Mr. MM!
Oh, Mr. MM!
It's Mr. MM!
Esteemed ladies and
gentlemen, the flesh of a ghoul
offers a coarse flavor
not worthy of devouring.
I am sure that those of you
here of such discerning taste
are well aware of this.
M-Mr. Tsukiyama!
W-Why...?
The thing that caught
my attention was his scent.
For while he is a ghoul,
the scent of human is also pervasive.
Oh, he's right!
How aromatic!
Magnificent!
Ah, I can't take it!
Aren't you fascinated?
What sort of flavor does a ghoul
who smells like a human possess?!
I've been set up.
This whole thing was a trap.
An adventur into the unknown
for the sense of smell and taste...
Now! Let us enjoy the
ultimate epicurean delight!
Now, here is the scrapper who
will be serving today's main dish!
Tell me, Madam A...
Oh, what is it, Mr. PG?
Which scrapper have
you brought with you today?
Today, it's my all-time favorite, Taro.
Pleazzure to meed you.
Sawnter, sawnter, sawnter, sawnter...
Gah!
Squash him good!
Hunh? W-Waid up!
W-Waid up!
Taro! Come on, run!
Mamma!
His owner, Madam A,
also offers her encouragement!
Gotta get outta here!
I-I've gotta do something!
You can't geddaway!
--Get him!
--This is bad! I can't get away!
See you, saw you!
It's no use. That had no effect at all.
What's the matter, Kaneki?
Why don't you use your kagune?
We have to hurry thing along, here.
I have to think of some
way to slip out of here!
Shood!
--What?
--Did his legs get all twisted up?
Ladies and gentlemen, it appears
the drug is starting to take effect.
Don't tell me the coffee was...
A-A-Awright! I-I g-godcha!
Get him! Wring his neck!
Rip his guts out!
This is... This is fun!
Tschüss, Kaneki.
Huh? What's that?
A-A one-eyed ghoul!
One eye?!
One eye? For real?
Taro, snap out of it! Get up!
It hurdz! It hurdz! It hurdz!
One eye... How rare!
Mr. MM?
Are you all right?
What a delicacy!
Get up! Taro!
Mamma!
It's hopeless...
That's it! What a good walker!
What a good walker! What a good walker!
Mamma is so excited!
That hurdz!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm terribly sorry for all the commotion.
I had no way of knowing that
he was a so-called one-eyed ghoul.
However, I have no intention
of ruining the dinner we all came for.
How does this sound to everyone?
It hurdz!
How about we enjoy
Madam A's pet boy, the scrapper?
Taro! Taro!
It hurdz...
Taro... you... good-for-nothing!
Embarrass me, will you?!
I hope you get fed on quickly, damn you!
Mamma...
Did you enjoy that, Kaneki?
I just meant for this to be a little joke.
I may have been a bit hard
on you. Can we forget about this?
Such a rare treasure...
I'm not going to let anyone else eat him.
Though the city sleeps,
it's buildings are always
under construction
Urban planning carries on
Its belt lines morphing, snakes interlocking
stirring up endorphins,
and off you go, go, go
Souls ascend up into the night sky
Their procession and
their faith both resembling
an aberrant riddle
Our as-yet-empty tomorrows
are an all but black shade of gray
Without any possibilities
an all but black shade of gray
Ah, tonight, you're the one I want
Saints
Ah, I want you to signal the end
Yes! Yes, Tsukiyama! That's
the face I want! Nice feeling!
Even more! Release
yourself even more! That's it!
Fantastic! This is great,
Tsukiyama! I can't say enough!
Um... What are you doing?
Oh? Well,
apparently, I'll be appearing on
an upcoming cover of the comics.
Kaneki, would you care to join me?
Well?
Huh? Oh, no, I'll pass.