I am Amon Kotaro, newly assigned
to Control Division One as of today!
Pleased to make your acquaintance!
This year's newbies
are quite strapping, huh?
S-Special Investigator Arima!
I heard about you from your
teachers. It's a pleasure, Amon.
I-It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance!
I'm going to place you under Mr. Mado.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Mado, huh? And you,
a newbie. Tough break.
He gets a little crazy, so be sure
not to let him push you around.
Mr. Mado, I'm going to have you
partner up with him starting today.
Oh? All right.
Mado Kureo. Nice meeting you, Amon.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
"Applehead," you say?
Yeah. Committed fifty
predatory kills in the last year.
Do you have anyone as a suspect?
There is one...
This woman, who was
in the area that evening,
Muramatsu-Kie, age sixty-eight.
Huh?!
Is that so strange? You think there
are no sixty-eight year old ghouls?
Er, no...
I don't think there can be
any doubt that she is Applehead.
Do you have any proof?
My instincts.
I-Instincts?
Instincts are nothing to sneeze at, Amon.
I'm pretty sure of my instincts.
Is this man really all there?
Good afternoon, Miss Muramatsu.
Ah, good afternoon. Nice weather, isn't it?
I see you have a
handsome man with you today.
This is my new partner, Amon.
Pleased to meet you.
This benign-looking woman is a ghoul?
Thank you very much
for the doctor's certificate
you sent me the other day.
Looking at your Rc factor,
it will be plainly obvious
whether or not you are a ghoul.
Your number is 231. If you were
a ghoul, that would be impossible.
I'm terribly sorry for having
cast my suspicion upon you.
If you had a doctor's certificate
from her, why didn't you tell me?!
There are any number
of ways to forge these.
It doesn't prove anything.
Even so...
He-he, it's part of my strategy,
to get her to give herself away.
You should learn from everything I'm doing.
You're still just a fledgling, after all.
Very well.
Oh, right! Amon, would
you show me your quinque?
Huh?
I'm interested to see what kind of quinques
the newbies are given these days.
Forgive me for saying so,
Senior Investigator Mado...
but I take this seriously.
I would prefer to refrain from anything
not involving the investigation!
Excuse me.
Of all the...
What is that man thinking?
What is someone like him
doing at the home office?
Miss Muramatsu?
You really are a big help.
Oh, no.
If only my own son were as kind as you are.
No, not at all.
I really am grateful.
To suspect a woman like this...
That man must be crazy.
I must say, this is heavy.
I'm surprised you got it this far alone...
Don't go treating me
like some old lady, kid!
So this is where it ends?
That won't do, Amon.
You can't drop your
guard in front of that scum.
Mr. Mado...
I'm sorry. I...
It's okay. I factored your
inexperience into my planning.
I highly regard that zeal of yours.
But just remember one thing, okay?
Once the foe is before you,
then even if it costs your
arms and legs, you fight.
That's what it is to be an investigator.
Yes, sir!
Hey, crybaby Amon!
Mr. Shinohara!
Hey! Been off blubbering again?
Mr. Shinohara, what are
you doing in the 20th Ward?
I needed to see you.
What's that?
I was going to see Mr. Mado...
That's right. Fourty nine days, huh?
Yes.
To think that he's dead...
I still can't believe it.
Anyhow, what did you need?
Oh, some other day.
I'll come back tomorrow.
But...
It's okay, go on.
Say, Amon...
He... was really proud of you.
Right. As was I.
Mado Kureo was my pride.
Tell me, oh tell me, the way it works
Who is that inside of me?
Here in this broken-down,
broken-down world,
you laugh, without seeing a thing
I'm just so damaged,
I hold my breath and freeze
Breakable, unbreakable;
shakable, unshakable
When I found you, it shook me
In this twisted world, I'm gradually
growing transparent and vanishing
Don't look for me; don't look at me
I don't wish to hurt you in a world
of someone else's imagining
Remember who I am
Multiple bodies were found on the
streets of the 11th Ward last night.
"Multiple unidentified bodies discovered"
CCG is investigating it
as a ghoul-related crime...
Big Brother!
Uh, H-Hinami?
That's me!
What's up with that outfit?
I borrowed some stuff from Big Sister Touka.
I'm going to go out now with Mr. Yomo.
Going out?
We're going to go buy a home for Hetare.
Oh.
Hetare! Hetare!
All right then, Yomo,
look after Hinami, okay?
I'm a cat. Hetare!
Off we go!
After what happened,
Hinami ended up living with Touka.
Little by little, she's regaining
her cheerfulness from before.
T-Touka...
Where's Hetare?
The manager took him inside.
There's no way I'm
keeping that bird at home.
Touka sometimes has
her head in the clouds...
What are you looking at? I'll kill you!
Oh, sorry.
Things are just about back to
normal. It actually feels that way.
However, such a thing just isn't possible.
While everyone accepts the tragedy,
though we may be sad,
we still have to go on living.
So we tried desperately
to get our previous lives back.
Ah, what do you think
you're doing, you damn woman?!
Huh? Is that any way to speak
to your senior, damn Nishiki?!
Huh?! You, my senior,
at this damn useless job?!
Ah, the future looks damn bleak indeed!
Having a damn sickening college
boy with a damn smart mouth
as my damn junior makes me
pretty damn discouraged, as well!
Why don't you hurry up and quit?
--Hey, you don't have the power
to ask that, you damn woman!
--Um, we're in the service trade,
--What's your problem, damn Nishiki?
--so would the two of
you knock of the "damns"?
--Damn Touka!
--Damn Nishiki!
--What is it with you? Can't you do
anything but parrot me, damn Touka?!
--I'm about ready to get angry, myself.
--What is it with you? Can't you do
anything but parrot me, damn Touka?!
--I'm about ready to get angry, myself.
--How dare you
compare me to a bird...
--You guys do know the legend
of the Devil Ape, don't you?
--...of all things, damn Nishiki!
--You guys do know the legend
of the Devil Ape, don't you?
Damn Touka!
Damn Nishiki!
There it is! That's all
an idiot like you knows!
Do you really think you can
pass an entrance exam like that?!
"Body of on-duty CCG investigator found"
That's none of your business, damn Nishiki!
Mr. Mado, I'm sorry. If I
had only gotten there sooner...
I swear, I would have killed
the rabbit myself. I swear it.
So you mean, you were
being controlled by Rize?
No, I'm not sure how to describe it.
I don't remember anything
that happened for that moment.
When I came back around,
I had attacked Mr. Yomo.
Hmm? Amazing. You actually stabbed
through Ren's tough-looking body.
Kaneki, you must be strong, huh?
Miss Itori!
I'm joking, I'm joking!
Kaneki, only Ren is worse
than you at recognizing my jokes!
Oh, sorry.
The same kind of thing
happened, once before.
It felt like Miss Rize
had taken over me then, too.
So you came calling on me,
to stock up on information about Rize?
Yes.
Good for you, Kaneki. You know
how to grease my wheels, don't you?
Rize, huh?
The truth of it is, Kaneki...
Yes?
I can honestly say that
I don't know a lot about Rize.
Huh?
You see, one day, she just showed up.
Just showed up one day?
Nobody knows where she was,
or what she was doing before then.
But, even so, it's not like Rize
just popped out of some tree.
If you dig around, you should
be able to find some leads.
Yes, I suppose.
Why don't you start
by going to the 11th Ward?
The 11th Ward?
Before she came to the
20th Ward, Rize was in the 11th.
I'm certain about that.
The 11th Ward...
Maybe I'll go there the next day I have off.
Oh, excuse me!
Ah, no, excuse me.
I lost myself there for a bit.
Well, g'bye!
--Must be going!
--Something about that person...
smells delicious...
Insurance card, library card...
and here we have...
his student ID! Kaneki Ken,
age nineteen. The same age as me!
And the all-important contents are...
That's a real shame.
Pickpocketed?
Mm-hmm.
Do you remember their face?
I never got a good look.
Did you file a report?
There wasn't that much in it.
Geez, you're pathetic.
If you were more vigilant, you
wouldn't have creeps coming after you.
--Uh, yes, you're right.
--We've just received some breaking news.
Following Chairman
Washu Tsuneyoshi's decision,
"11th & 20th Ward's investigator
personnel to be increased"
CCG has increased investigator
numbers in the 11th and 20th Wards.
--Hmm, is the 20th Ward really that unruly?
--This is in an effort to
clamp down on ghoul activity,
--Hmm, is the 20th Ward really that unruly?
--which has been on the rise,
beginning with the 11th Ward...
--Beats me.
--which has been on the rise,
beginning with the 11th Ward...
--I wonder if the balance has shifted.
--which has been on the rise,
beginning with the 11th Ward...
Huh?
Hmm? Oh, I thought that there
was some kind of ghoul organization
here in the 20th Ward.
W-Why do you think that?
Compared to the other wards, there are
remarkably fewer predatory cases here.
I thought it was because the
20th Ward ghouls were collaborating.
Oh, mm-hmm...
The binge eaters and the
gourmets also went missing
when they started getting
more active with their predation.
Which means it's conceivable
that this ghoul organization
cleaned house against the groups
that would be on CCG's blacklist.
Hmm? Hey, Kaneki, you look a little pale.
O-Oh, sorry. I'm all right.
Hide, you um, sure are
interested in ghouls, huh?
Yeah.
The thing is...
"Ogura Hisashi's Ghouls Dissected"
This book is super fascinating!
Huh?
It tells of a gang of ghouls in
the 3rd Ward that wear clown masks,
and of how Matsubara, the ghoul
from Wakayama came to Tokyo,
and about how
ghouls' hair grows and stuff!
Kaneki, I'll see you later.
Mr. Amon, the reinforcements from
the head office are waiting for you.
Understood. I'll be right there.
I wonder who they're going to assign.
There wouldn't be any
openings among the veteran force.
Yo!
Mr. Shinohara! Don't tell me
you're coming to the 20th Ward.
No, I'm on something else.
These two are going to the 20th Ward.
Mr. Hoji!
Kotaro, long time no see.
It's been too long!
M-Mr. Amon!
P-Pleased to meet you!
Investigator 2nd Grade Takizawa Seido,
Head Office Control Division One!
He apparently is a fan of
yours. He's been quite anxious.
A-Assistant Special Investigator
Hoji! That is to say, I mean...
Nice to meet you, Investigator Takizawa.
I-I am delighted to meet you!
Amon,
these two are going to be
overseeing the 20th Ward for a bit.
Huh?
You're being assigned
to a special task force.
Special task force, you say?
Mm-hmm. Marude told me.
The 11th Ward, together with me.
The 11th Ward...
Oh, yeah. Things have gotten
that bad in the 11th Ward, huh?
Mm-hmm. From what Yomo said,
the ghouls are working together
to hunt down the investigators.
It sounds like it's a real mess.
Oh, yeah?
The way things are headed,
there could be big trouble.
What sort of big trouble?
A war, maybe.
The day may be coming when
I get called the Devil Ape again.
Speaking of which, where is Touka?
She might be in with Hetare.
I thought she couldn't
handle being around birds.
That's supposedly true.
I'll go have a quick look.
He had a family, too.
Touka?
I wonder where this guy's family is.
Eh?
Everyone at least has a family, right?
Ayato!
What is it, sis?
Poor little guy. He's hurt, huh?
Dad...
How about we look after him at home?
Uh-huh!
Ah, I found a worm!
Don't cry! Be a man!
Yeah, but...
This is for Chunta!
Uh-huh.
You caught this many?
--Mm-hmm.
Touka, you're as much
a tomboy as your mother.
What about me? What about me?
I can't stand worms, either.
Ayato, you're just like your dad.
You two both need a bath.
Dad, give me a hug before we do!
Me, too!
All right.
You two sure are getting bigger.
Touka, you're the older sister,
so you have to teach
Ayato all sorts of things.
Mm-hmm.
Ayato, you're the boy,
so you have to protect your sister.
Mm-hmm.
Promise me.
What kind of people
did you have in your family?
Huh?
Oh, well... My dad died
before I can even remember.
My mom, too...
when I was in grade school.
Oh.
Hetare! Feeding time! Oh...
Big Brother!
Hinami, you got your hair cut, huh?
That's right! Does it look good?
It looks very good on you.
Did you go to a beauty shop?
Mm-mm. Actually, I had Big Sister cut it!
Huh?
What?
Oh, nothing.
You're thinking that's
not like me, aren't you?
Mm-mm, I'm simply
surprised at how good you are.
I-Is that right?
Hetare! Stupid scum!
Son of a bitch! Son of a bitch!
Why, you! You've got a
filthy mouth, you stupid cockatiel!
I'll deep-fry you in oil, you...!
Hetare!
Bitter...
You've met her before, haven't you?
Rize? I don't have
very fond memories of her.
She won't get away this time.
The 20th Ward.
It's my first time here.
I get the feeling that time
moves slower around here.
You idiots. Don't let your guard down.
Let's hurry and get to work.
Are you sure this
guy's really here, Mr. Banjo?
There's a coffee shop named
"Anteiku," run by an odd old ghoul.
Let's go. Miss Rize had to have gone there.
"11th Ward"
No fight in them at all.
Any word from the airhead Banjo?
No, none.
Damn that clown. At this rate,
Yamori and that fairy are
going to get the jump on him.
All right, we're heading
to the 20th Ward, too.
Our objective is to secure Rize.
Right!
Come to think of it, Mr. Ayato,
you're from the 20th Ward, huh?
I don't remember much about it.
They're basically a collection
of peace-addicted wimps.
Came to think of it, I do
still have one relative there.
One of the peace-addicted wimps.
Though the city sleeps,
its buildings are always
under construction
Urban planning carries on
Its belt lines morphing, snakes interlocking,
stirring up endorphins,
and off you go, go, go
Souls ascend up into the night sky
Their procession and
their faith both resembling
an aberrant riddle
Our as-yet-empty tomorrows
are an all but black shade of gray
Without any possibilities
an all but black shade of gray
Ah, tonight, you're the one I want
Saints
Ah, I want you to signal the end
Oh, what is this, a showdown?
The newly-arrived ghoul and
Mr. Uta are gonna go at it, Itari.
Are you the one who's been
making waves around here lately?
What's the deal with the goofy glasses?
Hey guys, you want to
watch me make him cry?
Mr. Uta means business!
They're gonna smash
up the 4th Ward like this!
"Next time: 'Aogiri'"
He's pretty strong, huh?
"Layout: Katsuya Yamada"