Then Takizawa's phone is a
"magic phone" that can do anything?
It's no good! Let's go grab one on the street!
Anyway, for now, investigate
the data Underpants sent us.
I can't get in touch with him either.
Okay, I'll give it a shot.
But you guys stay away from Toyosu!
Huh? Why?
The thing is, the missing NEETs
have poured into the movie
theater looking for Takizawa.
Huh?!
This place is done for.
I'll Kill you for sure, Akira Takizawa!
Episode 11:
The East That Continues On
I'm impressed you knew about this place.
I saw it in the real estate data.
Are we going to be okay
hiding in a place like this?
It's impossible to reason
with furious naked guys!
They're politely collecting their
cell phones, even though it's so cold.
So the phones are the most
important things to them.
Hello.
Oh, Kazuomi? We're going to head there after all.
I think it'll go faster if we
check out that data together.
I see.
But is there really going
to be a sixty-missile attack?
And if there is, what can we do about it now?
After all, we don't have magic phones.
I don't think Takizawa saved the
people because he had a magic phone.
He was just trying to do what had to be done.
Then why did he erase his own memories?
Why are all those NEETs angry at him?
He's right, Saki!
They wouldn't be so pissed
if he hadn't done something!
Osugi, Takizawa didn't just protect
the people from the missiles.
To protect the 20,000 NEETs who
were being regarded with suspicion
because they helped him with the evacuation,
he became the sole bad guy
and then erased his memories.
After he got that phone, Takizawa
used the information he got online
and gathered an elite force to
successfully evacuate the people
using means just barely within the law.
And you're saying that elite
force was the 20,000 NEETs?
Yeah, I think so.
But afterwards, those he rescued
started complaining via the media.
People asked how he and the
others knew about the missiles...
...and whether they'd had ulterior motives.
Even they didn't know whether
the missiles would really come,
so apparently some of them used
the opportunity to steal things.
Still, most of them were excited by
the fact that they'd saved citizens.
But the citizens who'd lost
everything in the missile attacks
couldn't dispel the cloud
of doubt in their hearts.
And then the people who'd
been observing the situation
started using the internet
to slander the evacuees.
That's one reason the incident
became more complex and bizarre.
So Takizawa used several fake names
to gather the NEETs in Toyosu,
and in order to direct the brunt
of the anger toward himself,
he told them he'd been the one
behind the missile terrorism.
I think that's why they know him
by several different names,
and why they're so openly angry at him.
After that, he sent them
to Dubai for three months
to hide them from the spotlight.
Most people are irresponsible,
changing their opinions easily
based on unconfirmed
information or convenient rumors.
Takizawa was betrayed by the
people he wanted to protect most,
and he lost hope, and that's why
he had to erase his memories.
Has he remembered that?
I don't know.
But this time, we have to do something
about the missile attack ourselves.
Why should you have to see it that way?
Even if Takizawa is really a
good person, he's a plain idiot!
Someone who screws up even with
a phone like that has to be an idiot!
I think the destinations of the
missiles are in the data Itazu sent.
Just like Takizawa did on Careless Monday,
if we post that on the net...
True.
In today's world, people get arrested
for a single line announcing a murder.
We'll probably get some kind of reaction
if we say there'll be a missile attack.
But...
But what?
That's currently impossible.
What do you mean?
The zombies have Itazu's data!
I'm sorry! I left your PC on the bar!
There! This is it!
Huh? Where?
Right here. This guy is holding it.
Yeah. But how do we get it back?
I have a proposal!
Perhaps we should strip! It would
also be a way to go on the offensive!
Huh? Why strip?
Sir, the best place to hide a tree is in a forest!
I think the best way to blend in with
the naked NEETs would be to get naked!
Huh?!
No way, no way, no way!
They don't notice us.
Our strategy is a huge success.
Looks like it.
Get over here! It's too late to hesitate now!
Well, true, but...
Whoa, for real?!
We have to meet up with
Hirasawa and the others somehow!
If we run through them really fast,
we might actually be okay.
Whoa, girls!
You found a PC?
Yes, but it's password-protected...
Let me see it for a second.
You guys have hair.
And you're really pale.
Well, if you'll excuse me...
Run!
They're following us...
I-It's okay. They're probably
only interested in 2D girls.
Osugi, catch!
Osugi!
Osugi, just keep going!
S-Saki.
Osugi, why are you naked?!
Don't touch the computer to it!
Hey, the hell?! I just went to
the trouble of getting it back!
Sorry! But right now, we need Itazu's data!
This way! Hurry, get inside!
Sis!
Good job making it here!
Never mind, hurry up and get the data!
Do Not Leave Open
I'm pretty sure I remember
there being some stuff in red.
This?
Attack Japan
with missiles
to restart it
from the
Postwar Era
Hack surveillance satellite and change
image feed to provoke preemptive attack.
Hack Tomahawk missiles deployed on cruiser
Fire 60 Tomahawk missiles
Targets:
Kasumigaseki
The Diet Building
Roppongi on cruiser
The Diet Building and Kasumigaseki are in here!
Let's split up. First, send this to our cell phones.
Okay.
Wait! No way...
Look at this!
Ikebukuro,
Toyosu,
Gunma
Toyosu?!
Wh-What is this?
Testing, testing...
I'm currently testing the camera.
--It's Takizawa!
Hi, Johnnys! There's a reason
I gathered you here today!
And that is to kill you who know
the truth about Careless Monday,
as well as all the citizens
who tried to criticize me,
with a new missile attack!
That's a lie!
What are you talking about, Takizawa?!
There's no way you'd do something like that!
Why would you tell such a lie?
This is not a lie.
However, there is still a slim
chance for you to survive!
All Johnnys who want to live,
start by assembling on the roof!
Takizawa...
That's just mean, saying we
can't get Juiz after all this!
Sorry, but you're your own
responsibility from here on out.
However, I plan to search for Mr. Outside again.
If I'm able to find him, let's meet again then.
But...
You got set up.
What do you mean?
I guess I mean you went too far.
What if he's the Supporter?
Mr. Mononobe told you to launch
the eleventh missile, right?
Saying you should eliminate the NEETs
who were living witnesses
to the incident, or whatever.
My condolences.
But man, that Number 9 is entertaining.
I think he'll pull something again this time.
It's too late for him to do anything now!
Didn't you hear the news? Two days ago,
they changed the strategic
programming for the Patriot missiles.
Leave us behind and escape!
We can't! The fire shutters are closed.
Can't we get out that way?
I'm telling you, you can't!
You can't all fit in here!
Osugi!
Hey!
Takizawa?!
Are you Osugi?
You've got guts. You're just like I imagined.
Takizawa, wait!
The truth is, you came here
to save everyone, right?
You're going to play the bad guy
all by yourself again, and save us...
So you listened over the
phone all the way to the end.
Yeah. But then my battery ran out.
When I went back to Itazu's afterwards,
he said he'd sent the logs to Hirasawa.
And I figured you guys were sure
to come here if you read them.
Takizawa, do you remember...?
Glad you all got back here, guys!
But the missiles will be
coming at us pretty soon!
This time, you have to post a
way to intercept the missiles
directly to the Eden site!
Hirasawa!
Yeah.
If you connect them in series like batteries,
they unleash pretty high potential.
I'm sure they'll think up an amazing
miracle, just like on Careless Monday.
It's not like I did that all by myself.
New Messages
Great, kthxbye!
Does he know what that means?
--Juiz?
--Yes, Juiz here.
I've taken the posts from
the Eden of the East site
and extracted the most effective
methods of avoiding the missiles.
I pray you shall continue
to be this country's savior.
Thanks.
Shall we begin, then?
Bang.
So you're okay?
Is Takizawa making this happen?
Yes. Him, and the NEETs here.
Is this happening all over Japan right now?
When will you come save me, Number 9?
I'm so good.
Missiles or no missiles,
this country's already headed for death.
Looks like he made it in time.
Bang!
What am I, the Sundance Kid?
Saki!
--Juiz.
--Yes?
This time I can't smooth things
over just by playing a terrorist.
So will you use the rest of my money
to make me the king of Japan?
The king?
Yeah.
There are a lot of smart people in this country,
but there's nobody to
take on the thankless roles.
I don't really want to do it either, but...
There was one girl who believed in me.
Accepted. Noblesse oblige.
I pray you shall be a splendid
prince the next time we meet.
I hope I'm the same then as I am now.
Oh, and Juiz...
Damn, there's no gold ring
on this merry-go-round.
And so he became a prince...
...in this country with no king.
The night is a seal
If we mix in some bewilderment, it will end
If we're in danger of wavering,
let's just abandon our reasons
We drown in dreams again
The future stretches on uncertainly
I can still forgive you,
I can still know the meaning
The night exists to be listened to closely
I can copy that reason, and change
I wouldn't mind cutting off
the future to know your breath
I wouldn't mind cutting off the future