That's impossible...
I'm the man they've been
callin' the Whiz Kid of Kyoto...
In 10 years' I'll be:
a NEET
In 20 years' I'll be:
In 30 years' I'll be:
a NEET
Hey! My pants!
That's my only pair...
Farewell, pants.
Thanks to you, I never have
to leave this room again.
Episode 9:
A Man Too Ephemeral
Major
I can't believe it!
Carp
World View News
Carp Get Multiple Offers from the Major Leagues
Bigwigs from the Major Leagues really
have announced transfers to the Carp!
But what I requested was for the Carp to win.
There's no guarantee they will yet.
What the hell?
Then you should've asked me for
something that'd get instant results.
Chances of Carp Victory
So even at this stage, their
chances of winnin' are 99.99%...
Huh? Oh, is that the World Computer you made?
Never mind that.
Wait, why do you know about it?
I don't get it...
To think that just by callin'
some dumb-soundin' broad,
you could pull off trades like this!
Fingerprint recognition?
So, there's logs from a different
Selecao in the other phone, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Come with me, Vintage Boy.
This place is amazing.
This is my secret base.
This is Mononobe. I just got here.
Could you come downstairs, then?
I'm parked outside. It's a green station wagon.
But I never would've thought
you'd come to Kyoto, too.
After all, you said Number 9
wasn't the Supporter.
Still, I just can't get along with Number 9.
I can't stand to let him get in my way again.
It's true that his logs rather
make him look like the Supporter,
but compared to you, the man who
devoutly tried to blast Japan full of holes,
he's too passive.
You flatter me. So, how shall we find him?
Good question. I suppose we'll
call around to all the cab companies.
That's very like you.
But life's unpredictable, isn't it?
After all, now I'm working with one
of the bureaucrats I used to hate so.
Oh, excuse me, a former bureaucrat.
Don't worry about it.
"Noblesse oblige."
The obligation of the privileged, eh?
Man, the Selecao are pretty different
from the organization I imagined.
I thought it was more American-style;
a national organization tryin'
to shape the public will.
What do you mean, "shape the public will"?
Well... Like the Cold War-era Red-baitin',
or all the conspiracy theories
set forth about 9/1 1 afterwards.
Stuff like that always happens
when national power wanes.
Just like Japan's is wanin' now.
Though there is the possibility
that the terrorist himself,
the spearhead of the conspiracy,
doesn't know about it.
Hey, Itazu, you're smart!
But how did you come to investigate Selecao?
I got interested in the incidents
when some conspiracy freaks were
talkin' about Careless Monday on the net,
but I also wanted to get revenge
for the NEETs who went missin'.
Aha, there's data left on this thing.
Just what did Osugi find?
He was saying Takky was a criminal...
From the posts on the Eden site, it looks
like he's using several other names.
Comment Tell me who he is!
Sis, ask Micchon what Takizawa's doing now.
Be casual, since we don't know
what's really going on yet.
Okay.
Hello?
Hi, Micchon, it's me. Is Takky there with you?
No... Why?
Oh, we were just wondering what he was up to.
He should be at Underpants's place
trying to get him to open the door.
Inbox
Osugi
Be careful!
I have to tell you something
important about Takizawa.
Please contact me when he's
not around.
Saki and I have been out shopping.
Oh.Well then, call me
when you find out anything.
What do you figure Sis wanted?
Is this it?
What's this?
Download brainwashing program from Ato Harima
Neuroscience Institute
February 12th... That's when
I was at the White House.
That was the "naked with a phone
and a pistol" thing I told you about.
Harima Neuroscience Institute?
Maybe you used this thing
to erase your memory.
Charter two large full-container ships from Japan
Pacifico Shipping
"Charter two large full-container ships"...
500 containers for sea transport from Shinbata Industries
"500 containers for sea transport."
So this is what Mr. Hiura was talking about.
Given how many containers you ordered,
maybe the ship left port with those 20,000 on it?
It's like you were exporting NEETs.
Can you tell where the containers went?
Round-trip fare to Dubai
The Dubai emirate.
Appeal to the Foreign Office to ensure the safety
of 20,000
Before the NEET disappearance,
you approached the Foreign
Office about somethin'.
Two weeks' worth of convenience store food for
20,000 delivered
Then there's this food...
Looks like you were housin' 20,000 for a while.
Then I guess I didn't commit mass murder!
Guess not.
And then... Here's the date for Careless Monday.
Tamper with the captions on open-air TV screens
150 propaganda vans
What's this?
I don't really know, but maybe
Charter 100 large buses
these are the mysterious incidents
that happened near the missile sites.
The biggest reason people wonder
if that missile strike was a conspiracy
is because there's rumors that
startin' several days beforehand,
there was a rash of strange
happenings in the six major cities.
A bunch of unexploded shells
were found all of a sudden,
the earthquake-warnin' system
malfunctioned and an evac was ordered...
As a result, there were no
casualties from the missiles,
but even a lot of the citizens
whose lives were saved said,
"Thank goodness I'm safe, but
somethin' just doesn't make sense."
The media sensationalized it at the time,
but while the public was focused
on the government's poor response,
that ended up dyin' down.
Can you get the logs from the other Selecao, too?
Huh? Okay...
Hey, look!
Bomb Japan's Six major Cities
"Bomb Japan's six major cities"?!
Looks like it was this guy
who launched the missiles.
Underpants, we bought your magazines!
This is our little secret.
I know.
Huh? Did Takky get let inside?
Itazu, what happened to you?!
--What's wrong?
--Weren't you skinnier before?!
Stop it, I'll blush.
What, because you haven't
seen any girls in a while?
Come on in and sit down.
What am I, a "beckonin' cat" statue?
Don't just invite them in!
They're like old friends...
These are the magazines you asked for.
Oh, thanks.
Got the info.
Apparently the person living there is
Yutaka Itazu, an engineering student.
He isn't a Selecao?
I've read all the logs, and I don't
see any Selecao in Kyoto but you.
Then what is Number 9 doing here?
Based on his actions so far,
I infer that he probably has
Number 4's Noblesse phone.
So it finally occurred to him to reread
all the Selecao logs that he'd
erased along with his memory.
I imagine that's why he's
visiting an engineering student.
So there were no texts or
addresses left on it after all?
Unfortunately not.
Sheesh! And we came all the way to Kyoto!
There was never anythin' on it to begin with.
If it'd been used even once,
someone of my skill could restore the data.
Huh... So can you tell where it's from?
Beats me. Must be some maker's
high-end prototype or somethin'.
I don't really know!
I mean, I have been a shut-in for a long time,
so I'm not up on the latest phones.
Yup.
Okay, shall we go home?
The bullet train is still running, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Can you fix that phone so it starts
receiving usage reports again?
It's powered up, so yeah, if I can
deal with the fingerprint recognition.
Okay. I'll leave it with you, then,
so start by analyzing the old logs.
I want to come out of this game on top.
Well, if everybody but the winner
gets killed, I guess you gotta try.
There's that, too, but I just won't be
satisfied till I punch out Mr. Outside!
I mean, come on! He's exploiting our lives,
telling us to save Japan while he
keeps himself safe somewhere!
I have to feed that old
bastard a knuckle sandwich!
You don't know he's an older guy.
No, only middle-aged guys who take
it for granted they're the winners
would think of something like this!
"Obligation of the privileged," my ass!
Itazu, you said you wanted
to avenge the NEETs, right?
I feel the same way.
Going NEET is a voluntary act
of terrorism individual people take
to resist men like that, isn't it?!
Naw, I wasn't doin' anythin' so cool...
Sounds interestin'. In its own way,
that's true social reform.
Allow me to help you out.
Write down your email address. I'll contact you.
Sorry to keep you waiting. Shall we go?
Um, I thought I'd give this to Itazu...
Um, Itazu...
I bought you some gym clothes.
They might be a little too small,
but you're welcome to them.
Oh, okay, sure.
I know there's a secret behind Takizawa's phone.
It's really not a normal phone, right?
I'm sorry, but I can't tell you anythin'.
What's the matter?
Nothin'!
Sometimes ignorance is bliss.
That's Number 9.
Wh-What should we do?
There'll be time to deal with him later.
More importantly...
Maybe if I access it through my application,
I can open the detail log!
All right!
Damn, I'm good!
What's with Vintage Boy?
At first I thought he was a nasty piece of work,
but not only was he not the missile terrorist,
he ran Juiz ragged evacuatin'
everyone from the landin' sites!
Don't you worry!
You're no criminal-- you're a hero!
Oh, right, there was someone
messin' with the Navy systems...
Bomb Japan's Six major Cities
Them hackin' into the naval system means...
I see, they made fake planes appear on radar
and provoked them into
launchin' Tomahawk missiles.
Who is this Juiz lady? She's pretty sharp.
And the day the PM said "Uncle,"
she fed the Opposition member
questionin' him real info,
but made the source look
like an email from his lover!
Which means...
Whoever made these phones is
friendly with the state powers.
What?!
This is bad... I gotta tell him.
What the hell?!
Shit, my contract expired forever ago,
not to mention the battery's dead!
That bastard... Why didn't he
give me his damn email address?!
So small...
Shall we have Juiz do something?
I thought so.
Did you analyze this?
Did he see the data on this thing?
Why did you make me do that?
You'll make a murderer out of me!
The hero who plans to wipe out
millions of people with missiles
shouldn't be freaking out
about running over one person!
Looks like the email environment
is up and running again.
Did you fix this?
Ah, so you're Selecao?
Well, whatever. So, what is
Number 9 planning to do?
He said he was goin' to punch Mr. Outside.
Oho.
Are you the one who launched the missiles?
You jerks are no heroes.
The real hero is...
Yuki. Ask Juiz to dispose of the car.
Attack Japan with missiles to
restart it from the Postwar Era
Hack surveillance satellite
Provoke preemptive attack
60 Tomahawk missiles
Transferring data
In 10 years, I'll be:
Still a NEET
Today, I'm
a hero, and then dead
Hello?
Number 9?
Who are you?
What was this place used for?
Hirasawa!
Did you see the Eden site?
Yeah.
Come over here.
I'll Kill you for sure, Akira Takizawa!
The night is a seal
If we mix in some bewilderment, it will end
If we're in danger of wavering,
let's just abandon our reasons
We drown in dreams again
The future stretches on uncertainly
I can still forgive you,
I can still know the meaning
The night exists to be listened to closely
I can copy that reason, and change
I wouldn't mind cutting off
the future to know your breath
I wouldn't mind cutting off the future