He became a prince out of necessity.
He realized that if nothing else,
the future we hoped for
would never come unless someone became
the sacrificial lamb called a "prince."
So even though it wasn't what he
wanted, he decided to be a prince.
In this world with no king...
But exactly how did he become a prince?
I still don't know that secret.
Well, here we are, Miss.
And here's your bag.
This is the center of the world?
Episode 1 :
I Picked Up a Prince
It's different than I imagined, somehow.
And the fountain is way
further away than I thought...
Washington
I wonder if everyone's mad at me.
If I had my phone on, Osugi
would definitely be calling me.
Well, I've come this far, so I
have to do what I'm here for!
No good... It's too far away!
Hey! Young lady, what did you just throw?
Hey, you wanna die?!
Hey there, are you okay?
What? For real?!
More like, why is he naked?
No. 9 is even more unique than I'd imagined.
But it ends here.
I see. That's rather regrettable.
Are you on his side? I'm jealous, Juiz.
Prepare for my return to Japan.
Yes, Sir. I pray you shall continue to be a savior.
Brr, I'm cold! For that matter, I'm naked...
A cell phone and... a gun?!
The White House...
I remember the White House,
but I don't know who I am.
Hey! Young lady, what did you just throw?
Hey, you wanna die?!
Hey there, are you okay?
Actually, I think I'm the one in trouble.
Was he hit?!
Get that guy!
Now's my chance...
No way!
You were almost in real trouble there.
You should get away while
you've got the chance.
I-I'm not in trouble...
But you know it's bad to throw
things at the White House.
You were watching?
Kind of.
Thank you...
Um, aren't you cold?
Yeah, I am.
Er, I'll lend you this.
Are you sure? I need to get away, too.
It's fine. It's my thanks for helping me.
Thanks. Don't mind if I do, then.
Bye!
It's totally blank!
Isn't there some record that'll
help me figure out who I am?
--Hello, this is Juiz.
--Juiz? Who are you?
I'm your concierge. I thought
you were just going to fade out.
It sounds like you're all right.
Huh?
Hey... Do you know who I am?
Who you are?
This is the first time
you've erased your memories,
and I received no order to prepare
a new background for you,
so I really couldn't say
who you might be right now.
Erased my memories?!
My last order was to tell you where
to go next, so I'm sending that to you.
Well then, I wish for your success
and sincerely pray you shall
continue to be a savior.
Huh?
So is this where I live, then?
I was so scared... what was that about?
I guess people really
shouldn't do unfamiliar things.
Oh, no! My passport!
What do I do?
It's in my coat pocket!
Hi there!
Well, considering how I'm dressed...
What do I do? I have to get it back!
That way.
There he is!
Wh-Why would that guy give him his pants?!
This makes no sense!
Woo-hoo!
Hey!
Hey! Excuse me!
Is this it?
Huh? No way, where'd he go?
Hey--
Hello.
Hey.
Dude, what do you think you're doing?
Say, my apartment's on the second floor, right?
Aren't you in Room B on the third floor?
Oh, this is bad!
If I don't hurry, I'll miss my flight!
What's his room number?
3B.
Thanks.
Hey, we got a suspicious male
and female couple on the loose.
I'm sending the pic from the security camera.
Aw, man...
I don't remember this at all.
Is this my apartment?
Perfect fit...
Wh-What the heck?
What is this, a terrorist hideout?!
It's like that movie-- what was it called again?
Taxi Driver!
No, then I wouldn't be naked,
I'd have a Mohawk.
Passports?
How many are there?
What, instead of De Niro, I'm Jason Bourne?
They're all me?
Someone's definitely setting me up.
For real?!
Am I a terrorist after all?!
Have I killed people?!
U-Um, you're the person
I loaned my coat to, right?
Would you mind giving it back?
You see, my passport and
wallet are in the pockets.
I'll give you the coat itself,
so please just give those back!
That's fine. Hang on a second.
Saki Morimi...
Born in 1 989, eh?
This is the one! I'll use this one.
The name is... Akira Takizawa.
Okay, from now on I'm Akira Takizawa!
What's he doing in there? Hurry up!
Hello. I need to ask you something.
What is it?
The girl in this picture-- is that you?
U-Um... Er...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go.
U-Um...
Wait a sec. Come this way, please.
Are you Japanese?
I need to see your johnny.
Whoa! It sure does look like me,
but where was that taken?
What do you think? I guess it is me, huh?
Thank you. Have a nice date.
Oh, it's someone else?
Okay, have a good one!
Safe! I was pretty cold back there, after all.
Let's hurry. Things are getting desperate.
What do you mean, desperate?
If we're unlucky, this whole
place could burn down.
When are you going back to Japan?
Well, now, actually.
Really? Let's go home together, then.
Wait, um, I...
What?
I left my bag behind on my way here.
You mean back at the White House?
Was anything important in it?
Presents, and clothes I like...
Then it's too bad, but you
shouldn't go back there.
Leave things to me. Will you
loan me enough for cab fare?
Okay, get in.
Go on.
Take us to the police station, quick as you can.
Why the police station?!
So this passport's not fake, anyway...
Here you go, ticket and passport.
You're well-traveled, huh?
You think so?
To think the embassy even booked us a flight...
I was secretly really nervous,
worrying about what'd happen
if they found out we lied...
We didn't lie about anything.
And we properly reported the theft to the police.
Otherwise, the embassy
wouldn't have lent us plane fare.
Government officials are more
cold-hearted than you'd think.
Really?
Um, it feels like you've ended up
helping me with a lot of things,
but can I ask you about one
thing that's been bugging me?
What?
What were you really doing
there when I first met you?
Staging some kind of protest?
The truth is, I'm a terrorist.
Nah, just kidding.
See, that's a popular game among
the exchange students over here.
Pretty awful how they make us carry
guns, huh? Even if they are fake.
That's a very extreme game.
I guess so.
What are you doing in D.C.?
Oh, I was on a college graduation trip.
It was a trip to New York, but I really
wanted to see the White House,
so I slipped away.
Huh.
Why the White House?
How should I put it...? I thought
maybe it was the center of the world.
That's strange, huh? I don't usually
pay much attention to the U.S.,
but I started thinking maybe
everything from my little problems
to the whole world situation was
connected to this place at the root.
And there's something
going on in Japan, you know?
A heavy atmosphere that we can't do
anything about ourselves anymore.
So I thought I'd wish for them
to help us out, even a little.
And I interrupted you.
No... I'd actually thought better
of it even before you came.
I realized this place has nothing to do with us.
I get you... not that I understand.
What's that mean?!
But a certain someone's little
terrorist act landed a blow for me,
and that's good enough.
My johnny landed a blow.
I'm Saki Morimi.
I'm...
Here.
"Akira Takizawa"?
What?
You were born on January 7th, 1 989--
you're the same as me!
Born during the last week of the
Showa era, right before it became Heisei!
Huh, so you're in the Showa 64 gang too...
But since you were born on
the seventh, I'm a day older.
Right, Takizawa?
Could Takizawa be my prince?
Nah, of course not.
What is it?
That "heavy atmosphere" you
were talking about... is it this?
A missile attack on Tokyo...
The night is a seal
If we mix in some bewilderment, it will end
If we're in danger of wavering,
let's just abandon our reasons
We drown in dreams again
The future stretches on uncertainly
I can still forgive you,
I can still know the meaning
The night exists to be listened to closely
I can copy that reason, and change
I wouldn't mind cutting off
the future to know your breath
I wouldn't mind cutting off the future