What's wrong?
Something came up.
Saki?
Later.
Takizawa!
Episode 10:
Who Killed Akira Takizawa?
Why didn't Takky get on the train?
I don't know.
Inbox
Osugi
Be careful!
I have to tell you
something important
about Takizawa.
Osugi
FW: Be careful!
Look at the data on
Takizawa I uploaded
to the Eden site!
He's using aliases.
Osugi
FW: Be careful!
I found proof in Toyosu
that Takizawa was
involved in the
disappearance of the
20,000 NEETs. Please
get away from him right
away if you can.
Be careful!
Are you the one who called me?
I'm Daiju Mononobe.
I hear you want to punch out Mr. Outside.
Did you get your memory back?
Wait, did you talk to ltazu?
Yes. He called you a hero.
I wonder if you can continue
living up to those expectations.
"Continue"?
What expectations?
So you still haven't regained your
memory or read the logs after all?
Perhaps I'm the one who overestimated you.
I intend to go to Harima Science
Garden City and win this game.
Huh? What number are you?
I didn't see any Selecao spending
like they could win right now...
I'm Number 1.
No need to worry. I'll make it
so you can finish this game, too.
What about it? Want to come with me?
I'll tell you the truth  behind that stupid phone
and why you erased your memories, too.
Takizawa, what happened?
Oh, something suddenly came up.
I'll catch up with you later.
--Sorry.
--Wait! Don't hang up!
I know that your cell phone is special.
When Osugi went missing, you were
in that hotel room with a woman.
You hadn't hung up your phone, and I
could hear your whole conversation.
That woman used her phone to make
those strange things happen, right?
Her phone that matched yours...
Takizawa, the "Selecao" are the terrorists
behind Careless Monday, right?
Do you have anything to do with them?
Yeah. Yeah. Hold on a second. I'll call you back.
Tell me, Takizawa.
Who are you?
Hmm, you're right. I mean,
even I think it's suspicious.
But I really don't know who I am.
Believe that.
Anyway, I'm about to talk with
someone who says he knows me.
So will you stay on the line and listen to us?
I won't hang up.
If it turns out I'm the criminal, forget about me.
And I'll disappear from your life.
But...That's not what I meant...
Well?
The only explanation is that he's
connected to the NEET disappearance.
Comment
Tell me who he is!
Takizawa used aliases in the six cities attacked
and gathered NEETs here
right after Careless Monday.
And then the NEETs vanished into thin air.
He's like the Pied Piper of Hamelin.
I just hope they're not buried
in some building somewhere...
I don't get it.
Why would he need to do such a thing?
I got Micchon on the phone.
She says Takky didn't get on the
train with them for some reason.
So Saki and Micchon are okay!
Well, that's a weird way to put it...
Anyway, I told them to come to Toyosu.
It's from ltazu?
Unable to display
more
Out of memory.
What's with this crapload of data?
I can't open it from a cell phone!
Receiving data
Get in.
A helicopter?
What happened to Takky?
Aw, man, it's from Underpants.
It looks like he sent
something to the Eden server.
I can't really open it because
there's too much data, though...
What are you calling yourself these days?
Akira Takizawa.
"Takizawa," eh? Do you know that's an alias?
How about the fact that you
sent 20,000 people to Dubai?
Kind of...
Does he mean the NEET disappearance?
Some things are starting to click,
but why did I erase my memories
or use aliases in the first place?
Have you heard of a firm called Ato & Company?
"Ato & Company"?
Mr. Outside, the man who got
you and me mixed up in this game,
is an old man called Saizo Ato,
its CEO and senior advisor.
Saizo Ato?
Yes. Haven't you heard of him?
He's a very well-connected
businessman who built a huge fortune
starting with a transport company
during the reconstruction after the War.
He's one of the relics of the Showa era
that some call "Japan's fixers."
What a boy of the times you are.
So why do you say Saizo Ato is Mr. Outside?
Hey, "Ato Saizo"... sounds like "outside"...
It's just a lame pun?!
There's the mocking name,
plus he's just about the only one
with the authority to get this stupid
game into automated operation.
Furthermore, it's the kind of idea
someone with his study experience
in prewar Europe would like,
and he's a peerless soccer fanatic.
The name "Selecao" probably
came from Brazilian soccer.
It was actually quite easy to deduce
his identity with those clues.
But why would an important old man like that
pass out ten billion yen
to do something so crazy?
There's no way that could fix our country!
Maybe to Mr. Outside, giving money
and power to a youth like you
and allowing serial murders and
missile attacks by prowar believers
seemed like valid possible ways of saving Japan.
Saizo Ato is someone who prides himself
on having laid the foundation of today's Japan.
But in this age,
he began to wonder if the nation
was really on the right path.
If what he'd done was right.
I think he took a good hard look at
the impasse our country has come to.
And then, by forcing power on the
people who found favor with him,
he sought to orchestrate another
moment of dramatic change for Japan.
I still think it's crazy.
I agree with you.
We're the victims of his whims.
But-- though I'm not defending him--
his time was running out.
By the time this game started,
he'd been diagnosed with terminal cancer.
And now, he must already be dead.
I wonder who this person he's talking with is?
How unfortunate that you
can't punch out Mr. Outside.
Well, I'm not sure I could
punch a senior citizen anyway.
More importantly, how are
you going to win this game?
Even if the old man's dead, there's the
Supporter, and the game's still going.
I intend to become the winner
by replacing Mr. Outside.
This game is ridiculous,
but the Noblesse phone
system itself is a fine thing.
After all, it contains all of Saizo Ato's power.
You get a talented concierge
on your phone, too, don't you?
Ah, you mean Juiz?
I'm going to make her all mine.
Mr. Mononobe, is this really where Juiz works?
This is a research lab run by the Ato Foundation.
In the years before his death,
Saizo Ato apparently spent
most of his time here.
You investigated that, too?
When I realized who Outside was,
I quit my job as a bureaucrat
and made close connections working at
companies that had dealings with Ato.
And the other day, I assumed
an executive post at Ato
and officially gained control of this place.
Including you, I've identified
nine of the other Selecao.
Two of those are already working with me.
Huh?
This is Yuki, Number 10.
He's the Selecao who
launched the eleven missiles.
Where's Tsuji?
He's waiting inside.
I see.
--This is Juiz.
--Juiz, prepare us some celebratory champagne.
I'd like you to deliver it to the control room.
It's rare foryou to make
such requests, Mr. Mononobe.
Is that a no?
Not at all. You should reward
yourself every so often.
Noblesse oblige. I pray you
shall continue to be a savior.
Thank you.
Hey, Mr. Mononobe. Is there only one Juiz?
I mean, the girl who answered your
phone sounded the same as mine.
Maybe I should feel bad about the
really tough requests I've been making.
I kind of pictured a bunch of
girls lined up in a huge room,
answering our requests.
You truly are unique.
This device below our feet is Juiz.
If Ato were alive, he'd be 100 this year.
I suppose creating a great machine
like this was his version of atonement.
Takizawa, now that Mr. Outside is dead,
there's no one left but us
who knows what this facility is.
Just as he manipulated this country
from behind the scenes to the last,
will you join us in our plan to
redo Japan from the Postwar Era?
Huh?
You're really going to tell him?
He is one of Japan's chosen representatives.
Whatever he may decide to do,
I think he may at least have the right
to know the truth before the general populace.
What do you mean, redo it from the Postwar Era?
Tomorrow at 8:00 am, we'll launch
another missile attack on Japan.
This time, it'll be sixty missiles.
Are these the people behind Careless Monday?!
Shh!
This was Yuki's suggestion, but
basically we'll become Japan's saviors
by redistributing its vested interests
through a targeted missile attack.
That makes no sense!
More like, it's totally messed up!
A "savior" doesn't attack his own country!
We're not messed up.
Japan is messed up, pretending to
have equality when it exploits people!
Yuki claims to have received his Noblesse phone
right after his parents died of overwork.
There was no place left for me in this society.
It was just your typical infinite
cycle of non-full-time jobs.
Even after I took out a loan
to get official qualifications,
my wage only went up ten yen an hour.
When I complained, even the NEETs mocked me,
saying it was my own responsibility
and I didn't work hard enough!
Those ten missiles were a message from me:
"You and the government don't
take enough responsibility!"
Uh, you might be right, but...
Anyway, I'm going to make the people
who mocked me feel just like I felt!
It's my noblesse oblige.
And you're all right with that, Mr. Mononobe?
I take self-responsibility in all situations.
But I thought Yuki might be
right that the fastest way
to downsize this country and
regain our global competitiveness
would be to first get rid of
the idlers and the gerontocracy
who keep such a tight hold
on their vested rights.
So I decided to go along with him.
What about you, then?
I already had ten billion yen,
so all I want is to be freed from
this annoying game already.
Don't interfere with me this time.
Whatever, you've got the meaning
of "noblesse oblige" all wrong!
Now I want to punch you guys out...
That's probably what you said
before you lost your memories
when you evacuated the
people from the landing sites.
You should just tell him
why he erased his memories.
If he still wants to interfere
with us, I won't say anything.
You were betrayed by both those you
saved and the friends who helped you.
Thank you for choosing the East
Japan Railway Company today.
Wait, are these Takizawa's cell phone logs?!
Number 10 has stuff written in red font.
What is this?
What are these numbers?
Hack into the Marine SDF radars
to display flying objects on radar
and trigger a missile attack
There's close to ten billion...
Hey, look at this!
Hack Tomahawk
missile Launch date:
It says Tomahawk missile!
Could Takizawa have been
involved in Careless Monday, too?
What's that?!
What is that?
What? What the heck is with that naked army?!
Hirasawa, is that...?
Yeah, and look at how many
there are-- wait, are they...
...the missing NEETs?!
Run!
Yeah, that might make me lose hope even today.
That's just not fair!
That's just too cruel to Takizawa!
But I'm the same. I'm the same
as the people who betrayed him.
That's not true. You're different, Saki.
But when the missiles came...
...even I said, "l wish something
even bigger would happen"!
Was it okay to let him go?
We don't have complete
command of the system yet...
Even if he asks Juiz for something,
it's too late for him to do much.
There's a little over eight
hours to the missile launch.
Ah, it's here.
Bollinger, eh?
This is empty.
The winner of the game
was not decided this evening.
Therefore, I ask you to post pone your toast.
Noblesse oblige.
Please follow Mr. Outside's orders
and continue the game
in order to become saviors.
Selecao Activity History
[Transfer Juiz to a secret
location]
"Transfer Juiz to a secret location"?!
Number 12 is the Supporter?!
No, he's Outside?!
The night is a seal
If we mix in some bewilderment, it will end
If we're in danger of wavering,
let's just abandon our reasons
We drown in dreams again
The future stretches on uncertainly
I can still forgive you,
I can still know the meaning
The night exists to be listened to closely
I can copy that reason, and change
I wouldn't mind cutting off
the future to know your breath
I wouldn't mind cutting off the future