I see... This thing does look like Eden's mascot.
Help
Board for the Lovelorn: AMORE PADRONE
There's no doubt about it.
Osugi always had that on his bag.
The picture was taken around noon today.
"Help me."
Help Me
Johnny Hunter
"Johnny Hunter."
I'm Gonna Die
"I'm gonna die."
Hotel
"Hotel"?
It's all written phonetically?
She picked me up in Dogenzaka
Re: "She picked me up in Dogenzaka" I wanna be
kidnapped too. If I go to Dogenzaka,
will she pick me up?
It's all written phonetically?
And the place the probable
johnny Hunter woman talked to him
Re: "She picked me up in Doganzaka" I wanna be
kidnapped too. If I go to Dogenzaka,
will she pick me up?
Re: "She picked me up in Dogenzaka"
Don't worry, you've got no chance.
is the same place Kasuga left him.
It's true we have enough
reasons to believe it's Osugi...
Hey, who's this "Johnny Hunter"
you've been talking about?
She's an urban legend that's
been the talk of the town.
A beautiful woman lures
innocent virgins like us into hotels,
and if we can't get it up, she cuts off
our johnnys with a sharp instrument.
They say she's actually
claimed 20,000 victims so far.
20,000?!
Naw, are you sure they're not just
confusing it with those 20,000?
Episode 7:
Flight of the Black Swan
But why would he ask for
help on a message board?
If it's really Osugi, he could've
just called or texted us directly.
This is a message board for the
lovelorn that Osugi frequents.
Board for the Lovelorn: AMORE PADRONE
Help
He's been very emotionally
vulnerable for some time now.
I think last night a cold wind
assaulted his already weak heart,
and he ended up going off
with a sketchy woman.
No way would his embarrassment
and guilt let him contact us directly!
I can understand how he feels!
So, who is this Osugi guy?
He was so drunk! If only I'd taken
him home after dinner last night...
...this wouldn't have happened!
By "dinner," do you mean...
Yes! The dinner he was supposed to eat with you!
Idiot!
Huh? What's going on?
A new image has been uploaded.
Board for the lovelorn: AMORE PADRONE
It looks like he took a picture
of his reflection in the window.
Is that Osugi's suit?!
Yes, it's definitely him.
Hey, look here.
A piano?
Try putting it through
Eden's image search engine!
Stanway Luis 15 Model M1150
**Super-rare
**Japan Purchased a few during the bubble
"Stanway Luis 15 Model M1 150. Super-rare.
Stanway Luis 15 Model M1150
**Super-rare
**Japan Purchased a few during the bubble
Legs show signs of repair work/Display model
japan purchased a few during the bubble."
If we know the maker, we can
figure out who bought it!
That's our Eden System for you!
There's a new comment.
"Her accomplice's name is Juiz"...
What does that mean?
Her accomplice's name is Juiz
"Juiz"... For real?
Where are you going, Takky?
I've got a hunch I know where he is,
so I'm going to take a look.
I'd like you to find a "Stanway
Luis 15 Model M1150" piano
whose legs have been repaired.
Accepted.
I've found it.
It's in room 1109 of the members-only
Hotel Insomnia in Roppongi.
Who's staying in that room?
A woman named Hanako Roppongi
has been staying there since the year before last.
That sounds like an alias.
Find out her real name.
Say, Juiz.
Yes?
Do you know about the "johnny Hunter"?
No. Would you like me to investigate?
No... That's okay.
I've finished. Her real name
is Diana Kuroha Shiratori.
She's the CEO of Monolom, an agency
for foreign models in Aoyama.
Where is she right now?
Location confirmed.
She's in a car traveling near
Roppongi Intersection in Minato.
Isn't that near the hotel?
Juiz, stop that woman for me.
How would you like me to do it?
Anything's fine. The police, whatever.
Accepted. Noblesse oblige.
I pray you'll be a savior of integrity,
even after abusing state power.
What is it? I don't think I was going too fast...
May I see your license, please?
[Detail Log]
[Stop Kuroha]
[Aoyama foreign modeling
agency Monolom's female CEO]
[Detail Log]
[Stop Kuroha]
[Falsely add her to repeat
offenders list]
[Aoyama foreign modeling
agency Monolom]
[Check contract for room 1109
of the members-only Hotel
Insonmnia in Roppongi]
[Look up her Centurion
Card account]
[Check contract for room 1109
of the members only Hotel
Insoniola in Roppongi]
[Search register of the
members-only Hotel
Insomnia in Roppongi]
[Search register of the
members-only Hotel
Insomnia in Roppongi]
[Search for a Stanway Luis
15 model M1150 with
repaired legs]
Number 9 is trying to make contact with me.
[Search for a Stanway Luis
15 model M1150 with
repaired legs]
[Metro Expy. Kasumigaseki
Toll Gate ETC Toll]
Why?
But what an honor.
H-Hey!
--Stop!
--Juiz, find me the motorbike
that entered the Metro through
Kasumigaseki about fifteen minutes ago.
Saki Morimi
Hello, Takizawa?
Saki! I've basically figured out where Osugi is.
Really?
Takizawa says he's found Osugi.
What? How?
Is he okay?
I think he's in room 1109 of
Hotel Insomnia in Roppongi.
I'm about to try to go get him. Later!
Um, Takizawa...
Thank you. But how did you find him?
Takizawa? What's wrong? Takizawa!
Selecao Activity History
[Cause a tanker truck accident
on the Metro Expy.]
[Find the motorbike that entered
the Metro Expy. from
Kasumigaseki 15 minutes ago]
Takizawa, are you okay?
Hello? Takizawa?!
So he said Osugi was at Hotel Insomnia, right?
Yeah.
I got the hotel on the line,
but things are crazy there and I
can't get them to put me through.
Hey, look.
WORLD VIEW NEWS
Tanker Overturns
on the Metro Expressway
That's between us and Roppongi!
Let's see you get into the hotel now.
If that's how you want to play it...
...I won't pull punches either!
Ah, Miss Roppongi. I'm sorry, but the
hotel has just changed ownership,
and no one is currently allowed in the rooms.
So, I'm terribly sorry, but I
need you to vacate your room...
But your companion isn't answering the door.
And I wasn't sure whether it would
be all right for me to enter, so...
That's no good, is it?
Selecao Activity History
[Purchase Hotel Insomnia]
[Hotel Insomnia purchase and
management instructions]
Number 9 bought this place for 1.5 billion?
Honestly, what unnecessary expenditure...
[Purchase Roppongi's
members-only Hotel Insomnia]
Where does the 200 million-yen difference go?
[Purchase Roppongi's
members-only Hotel Insomnia]
[Cause a tanker truck
accedent on the Metro Expy.]
You're quite ill-behaved, aren't you?
Time is running out.
Let's begin.
It opened, Juiz.
Though it took a feat of strength in the end...
Noblesse oblige. What a violent savior you are!
But I pray you'll be as frugal as possible.
I don't want to hear that advice right now.
So you're the Johnny Hunter?
You really are a Selecao.
And you're totally hot.
You sure don't look like a murderer
who'd blow up tanker trucks
or chop off people's johnnys.
Number 9, you're younger than I expected.
You don't look like the man
behind Careless Monday, either.
Huh? Wait, am I involved
in the missile crisis, too?
It's no good. Everything's
jammed down here, too.
Looks like a pretty big accident.
I wonder if Takky's okay?
Who knows? But I have
been wanting to meet you.
Though it's a shame you turned
out to be the Supporter...
I'm not the Supporter. I am a Selecao, though.
Plus, I just came to save this guy.
He's a friend of a friend.
A friend? Of this low life scum?
Well, from my understanding,
he's not really a lowlife...
Right, Osugi?
Stop--!
Even assuming this man is your friend,
I can't just give him back to you.
I'm a johnny-chopping killer
because of personal convictions.
I started long before I got this phone.
So I won't let anyone interfere,
even the Supporter.
I'm not the Supporter!
Wait, you got a Noblesse phone
even though you were a killer?
Yes. Though all I do with it is have
Juiz help me find the maggots
and dispose of their bodies afterward.
"Have Juiz dispose of their bodies"?
What are they talking about?
What is it, Saki?
Did you get through to Takizawa?
No...
I'm going to go on ahead!
Saki!
Morimi!
I guess there are all kinds of Selecao.
You're worlds apart from Mr. Hiura.
But do you really think you
can win the game that way?
For every enemy of women that I kill,
I import a fabulous foreign man.
But I never intended to win
this game in the first place.
In the end, no champion of justice can
get more than half the world on her side.
So until I use up my ten billion, I mean
to carry out my own form of justice.
Then I guess I have to take you
down if I want to get Osugi back.
I suppose that's right.
Your name is Kuroha, right?
How did you come up with the idea
of chopping off johnnys to begin with?
Do you hate them?
Yes.
Guess I've got no choice... I'll save you, too.
Because unlike you, I want to win this game.
There's seriously something
wrong with this country.
This Mr. Outside even lets killers in...
I'm gonna punch him out for sure.
Kuroha...
Did a man do something awful to you?
Why do you think so?
I get the feeling you've never
gotten love from a johnny.
Takizawa, who are you talking to?
What's a Selecao?!
I wonder whether a johnny that
could give me love even exists.
If it does, I'd love to try it.
Takizawa! Hey, Takizawa, what happened?!
Takizawa...
Welcome.
Takizawa...?
Who are you? This boy's girlfriend?
What did you do to Takizawa?
Takizawa?
Nothing in particular.
Well, now, looks like you've got a nice girl.
You'd better cherish this one.
Juiz? Do it.
Wait! That man is...
Don't worry. He's not your friend.
He's a wanted serial rapist.
His life has no value.
I wonder what gave that boy the wrong idea?
Goodbye, Selecao Number 9.
Let's meet again one day.
Takizawa?
Takizawa?!
What happened?!
Snap out of it, Takizawa!
Selecao Activity History
[Grand illusion material rental
fee (including costume) for
three varieties]
[Purchase Roppongi's
members-only Hotel Insomnia]
The night is a seal
If we mix in some bewilderment, it will end
If we're in danger of wavering,
let's just abandon our reasons
We drown in dreams again
The future stretches on uncertainly
I can still forgive you,
I can still know the meaning
The night exists to be listened to closely
I can copy that reason, and change
I wouldn't mind cutting off
the future to know your breath
I wouldn't mind cutting off the future