I worked up my courage and tried turning around.
By coincidence, Azuki turned around at the same time.
A tenth of a second felt like ten seconds.
Then I turned back and hurried onwards.
But I turned back again for two or three seconds.
In the distance, Azuki was looking back too.
It was like Azuki and I were on the same wavelength.
Translator
TLc
kewl0210
Chrno
Timing
Edit
KmE, Leet_Garaa
bobo343
Typesetting
Karaoke
scol, KmE
Jecht, KmE, pablo212
QC
Echo_Chidori
Z4kku
Encode
pablo212
darkphoenix
Summer and Name
Wavelength?
Azuki probably turned around ten times, two of them just happened to meet with you.
It wasn't like that.
That must be an awesome feeling.
It's not something that I can understand.
Are you making fun of me?
No, I'm jealous.
The first time I saw Azuki was in my sixth year of elementary school.
You and I went to Ake elementary and she went to Akeni elementary.
It was at a swimming contest between our schools.
While she was on the other side of the pool, supporting, we watched each other the whole time.
At that time, neither of us felt embarrassed.
School Entrance Ceremony
Also, at the middle school entrance ceremony,
our eyes met again.
At that time, we were pretty close to each other so both of us turned away quickly.
What?
You were conscious of each other since elementary school?
And you liked each other?
But it's really only looking back now that I realize it.
Well, okay, but no matter how much your wavelengths match,
if you don't exchange email addresses, you can't have a conversation with her.
It'll be fine as long as I get her email by graduation.
For now, it's manga.
Ah, right.
Here, I wrote five pages so far.
That was fast.
It's because I was writing while you were reminiscing.
Futatsu no Chikyuu
Futatsu no Chikyuu.
TL note: Futatsu no Chikyuu = The Two Earths
The Earth we live on is nothing but a clone of the real Earth,
Real Earth
Our Earth
and we humans are nothing but clones of the humans on the real Earth.
Yes, we were made by the "real humans" as materials for experiments.
By being in the same environment, we are left independent and observed by our copies
in order to create a better world.
So, for the real Earth, researching us has brought an end to war and global warming.
Shuujin...
What did you think?
I knew it, it sucks, right?
I knew a name was too high a hurdle to try to overcome so quickly.
I didn't know how to divide the panels and stuff, and the pictures...
Did you rip this story off from somewhere?
I didn't, but forgive me if it has something in common with something else...
Anyone could come up with something like this.
This isn't something anyone could come up with!
At least I couldn't.
Actually, I'm really getting drawn in by this setup.
You're kidding?!
Seriously.
But after that part, all I had was the people from the real Earth fighting with these humans.
I'm attracted by it because I can picture that happening.
It could be an all out battle, couldn't it?!
Or do you have anything more interesting than this in mind?
Hm...
Well, I had an idea for a sports story.
Ooh!
One called Gurasan Pitcher.
TL note: Gurasan Pitcher = Sunglasses Pitcher
An elementary schooler with a strong fast ball is trying to make it to the pros,
but he gets hit right in the forehead by a shot hit towards the pitcher, and is blinded.
Ten years later, suddenly a pitcher wearing sunglasses appears on a pro mound.
With 180 km/h throws at every angle; high, low, inside, and outside,
he pitches a perfect game.
Having never given up on his dream of going pro,
Next, 38.
there's a story of the secret special training he did for ten years with his dad.
Yes, sir!
Hang in there, Sunglasses!
Dad!
The fact that he can't see gets out, and while he's in a dispute with the baseball association,
he battles with rivals trying to hit his throws.
I knew you had talent, Shuujin!
Normally nobody could come up with that much of a story on that premise!
S–Seriously? You really think I have talent?!
Yes, usually it'd sound stu—
I'm so glad!
Honestly, I've been trying desperately to come up with stories day after day.
Even I thought I might've been over confident...
But now that you've recognized me, I've really got confidence.
I'm so relieved.
Honestly, I'm glad.
I'll do my best, too.
I'll draw artwork that can compliment your story.
So which story should we go with?
Futatsu no Chikyuu.
I've got a feeling Gurasan isn't suited to being a series.
Gotcha.
Is there an ideal amount of pages it should be?
I heard the Rookie Award has set 31 to 45 pages.
That sounds good, right?
Well, don't worry about the page count for now, just draw a whole lot.
Okay!
Ow...
That was fast!
I already had the beginning in my head.
Well, even if it's done at a fast pace, it doesn't matter if it's not interesting.
Saikou?
Yeah, okay.
There he is.
Takagi, come here a second!
She's calling you.
I don't wanna go.
Ah, she's coming over here.
Eh, really?
Ignoring people when they call you...
She seems kinda angry.
Ignore her, ignore her.
Takagi, I've got something to talk to you about.
What?
It's fine, stay.
Miho said, "Why does Takagi-kun know about my dreams for the future?"
"You told him, didn't you?"
Then she got angry at me!
It doesn't really matter, does it?
I just checked with her to see if it was true.
And I told this guy.
He's my friend Mashiro-kun.
Nice to meet you.
I told you Miho's shy and that you shouldn't tell anyone!
I know, I won't tell anyone else.
How about you ask her how she's gonna be a seiyuu if she's that shy?
Like hell I could say that.
Anyway, I won't spread it around anymore so relax.
So, did you get rejected by Miho?
You've gotta be kidding.
You said you talked with Miho, right?
I'm saying I just asked her to see if it was true.
Azuki likes someone else anyway, right?
You're kidding.
Who?
I don't know, but third year middle school girls usually have someone they like, right?
Yeah...
But Miho never said anything about that, so...
Hey, wait a second, why were you probing me about Miho anyway?
Hm? Well, that's because...
I wanted to talk to you, Miyoshi.
L–Let me think about it.
H–Hang on Miyoshi... san?
Ah, now you've done it.
If you say you were joking, she'll either cry or get pissed.
You know her, she's been in nationals for karate or aikido or something.
Also, she likes you in the first place, doesn't she?
You're kidding.
I mean, she told you her best friend's secrets.
It seems she likes you, doesn't it?
Then, she said, "Let me think about it.
There's no way she would say that if she didn't like you.
Now that you mention it...
But I can't let it go on like this!
She's not bad, that Miyoshi.
Not bad?
Why?
She's Azuki's best friend, so she must be a good person.
What is it Kaya?
You wanted to talk?
Takagi hit on me.
No way!
Really.
What do you think of him, Takagi?
Well, he's good at studying and exercise, and he's tall.
You're right!
I'm not good enough for him.
That's not true.
You're cute, Kaya.
I'm sure Takagi-kun thinks so too.
I'm cute?
Yes.
Kaya?
But Takagi can definitely get Iwase to go out with him.
It's even a rumor in our class.
I don't think Iwase-san is someone easy for boys to approach.
"Boys are stupid, hmhm." That sort of feeling?
Well, not that far...
Ah, that's right.
Who's the person you like, Miho?
Nobody...
I thought you'd say that.
Like I was saying...
Come on, hurry up and tell me.
There isn't anybody!
You're kinda stuck up, just like Iwase.
I've never seen you talking with a boy.
That's stuck up, isn't it?
Kaya.
Yes?
I'm just embarrassed around boys so I can't talk to them.
I really like boys, even more than you, Kaya.
What?!
Maybe it's because I don't have any brothers,
but I get really self-conscious
and go bright red from just trying to talk to them, so I can't.
Understand?
It's really funny when you start talking like a teacher, Miho.
Geez...
But when you do, you're always serious so I know you're not lying.
Kaya...
When you give Takagi-kun your reply, do it alone, okay?
I hate being around for those sorts of things.
Takagi and Mashiro are back.
W–What do I do?
Good luck.
Miho...
Maybe we're on the same wavelength.
Miyoshi was just turning around.
"Was just..."
END OF TERM EXAMS
MATH
JAPANESE
ENGLISH
END OF TERM EXAMS
JAPANESE
ENGLISH
END OF TERM EXAMS
I'm done!
Done!
No matter how many times I write it, I don't like it.
And it'll be summer vacation soon.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I'm still not at the level where I can do a manuscript.
Worst case scenario, you can write the second half while I'm drawing the first half.
I know.
First Semester End-of-Term Exams
Top Scorers
Takagi Akito
Iwase Aiko
Jinbou Seiji
Aida Sukuji
Mikami Shun
Sixth?
That's awesome.
Sixth in the class.
The test had the same pattern of questions you said it'd have.
Yeah.
Now we just...
Ah—
W–Wavelengths...
SUMMER VACATION
It's hot!!
I wanna go to the beach!!
I don't wanna do homework...
I don't want
any extra
Summer
courses
I know your dad said it was okay,
but to stay stuffed in a workplace all vacation long...
As your mother I need to put my foot down.
Please try to come home once in a while.
Okay.
Hey Saikou.
Let me stay here too.
It's fine with me, but didn't your parents make a big fuss about it?
They were pretty cool with it.
Catch.
He used to work hard and drink those, didn't he?
Kawaguchi Tarou-sensei.
Since we're gonna be working hard too.
You sure are trying to follow his footsteps.
Then let me revise my statement.
Let's finish the manuscript before the end of summer vacation!
Yeah!
Bitter...
Awesome!
My name is becoming a manga!
This is a name, too.
I'm fixing the panel division and composition.
Heh, even this looks like it'd make an amazing manga if it were inked.
It's still a long way off from completion.
Next I've got the under-sketch to do.
I won't be doing the inking any time soon.
Really?
It's not at that stage yet.
I'm trying to improve my level right up until I do the inking.
Saikou, even though you say manga doesn't have a limit,
aren't your standards a little too high?
From my perspective, this is plenty.
No, I'm still not there at all.
Okay, do it the way you want to.
And I'll keep doing the name until it's something I approve of.
Yeah, I won't interfere with your name, and you won't interfere with my drawings.
Right?
Yeah.
Saikou, are you asleep?
As if I could get to sleep that fast.
I know, right?
I've been thinking too much, so it's actually making it hard to sleep.
I'm going to read some more manga.
You sure are good...
Are there any manga you've been into recently?
Hm, it's got to be "Dragon Ball."
That's your favorite manga, isn't it?
It's kind of unshakable, and it's kind of my starting point.
Ah, did you ever make-believe Dragon Ball when you were a kid?
Yeah, I did!
Fusion!
Shuujin, your sion timing was late, wasn't it?
My sion was perfect, your sion was too fast.
No, you need to say sion with more of a SION! kind of feeling,
or it's not a real sion !
Are you saying my jan wasn't the real thing?
Who's Jan ?
Eh!
Wait!
AUGUST
SCHEDULE
School Day
Oh, Saikou, you're awake too?
Shuujin.
I'm going to try inking.
There's only a month left of summer vacation.
I'm still not fully satisfied with my pen handling,
but as I expected, I must get started.
I'm not saying you should rush the name though.
You stick to doing it until you're satisfied with it.
Okay.
All right, I've finished up to the middle.
Good job, take a little break.
Okay, you should too.
Yeah.
Want some?
Hm... Later.
Aw, now I've done it!
I wonder if I can fix this with white-out?
Wanna go outside for a bit?
Okay.
The top hit on the charts this week,
though it was only released in July, has already achieved one million in sales.
KOOGY's...
Are you okay?
I thought I was going to die.
Hey, this song sure is good, huh?
The world is fascinated
in this taste
For a Limited Time
Limited distribution in anticipation for KOOGY's collaboration.
It's KOOGY, right?
That song from his new album.
I want to go to his summer tour.
Yeah, you've got to enjoy your summer vacation!
Shuujin?
Come on, let's go back and work.
Okay.
It's about time for me to get some sleep.
Saikou?
He's already done all this.
I sure kept you waiting.
I'm going to the convenience store.
Rest for a bit.
If we need to buy anything, I'll go.
From this point on, I won't be touching the manuscript, so I'll go.
Okay.
By the way, maybe Azuki will come if we call her.
"Master, your meal is ready."
It'd be like that.
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
I just thought it'd get you energized.
You liar!
I know Azuki's not that kind of girl.
Excuse me, I'm trying to take this book.
Hey, excuse me.
You sure took a while, were there no convenience stores open nearby?
What?
This is from the same place as usual.
Ah, you bought a Jack for me.
Thank you.
The large
viruses
have increased
100,000 times.
Niizuma Eiji...
Eiji's amazing.
It's not just the drawings, the story's interesting too.
As we are now...
If we're losing... it's with the pictures!
S–Saikou!
I don't want to lose.
I don't either.
But even the story was good.
There's no way in hell I'll lose!
Is there anything I can do to help out?
You finished your name alone, Shuujin.
I want to finish my job alone, too.
All right, white-out is done!!
Now just for...
Saikou, let me.
I didn't interfere with your name.
You won't interfere with my artwork.
No, I just thought this way we'd both be working on it at the moment it was finished...
Can you attach the tones?
Sure!
Here, attach these to all of the Earth soldier's pants!
Ooh, thank you!
Let's keep going nonstop until we're done!
Right!
The drawings are good, but I don't about my story.
The story is good, but I dunno about my drawings.
Saikou.
Yeah?
What's this?
Don't you think this sort of thing is embarrassing?
Thank you, Saikou.
Function
Select
Monitor
Playback
Away
Telephone
Directory
Copy
Okay, let's call right away.
The number is probably stored in the phone's memory.
Copy
Do you think if we call this way, they'll think it's Kawaguchi Tarou's ghost?
No one will remember.
Call on your cell phone if you're that worried.
What should I say?
Just something like "I'd like to bring in a manuscript."
I'm calling.
Hurry up.
Hello, this is the editorial department for Shounen Jack.
Preview of
Next Episode
We're bringing our first manga into Jack's editorial department.
YUUEISHA
TIME FOR USE AS MEETING CORNER:
MANAGEMENT
I'm so nervous!
TIME FOR USE AS MEETING CORNER:
MANAGEMENT
Will the editor we meet be a hit or miss?
TIME FOR USE AS MEETING CORNER:
MANAGEMENT
Let's go see!
Next Episode:
Carrot
and Stick
Carrot and Stick
Dreams are sweet, reality is bitter!