YUUEISHA
Finally, huh?
I can't believe middle school boys like us can bring in a manuscript.
YUUEISHA
It's like a dream.
As long as you just write a manuscript, they say anyone can bring one in.
The problem is how that work is judged.
Yeah.
I'm Hattori from Weekly Shounen Jack, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you!
Well, to start with, may I see your manuscript?
Ah, okay.
Please, go ahead.
We're going to get told it's shit.
If he offers tea, it's a success.
I feel like a defendant awaiting a verdict.
Tea...
Me... Shuujin...
Success...
Sucteaess...
Tea!
Verdict!
You guys did well.
For now I think I'm going to send this manuscript around for the monthly award.
Is that okay?
Monthly award?
You mean the excellence award given to one of the works submitted every month?
So, does that mean it's good?
It's not that easy.
A work becoming a hit is, for the most part, a gamble.
It was a success, right?
On the first work we brought in, he gave us his business card and even his email address.
What do you think, Shuujin?
About what?
I think Hattori-san was good.
Hey, how did it go?
With the middle school pair?
No good, at least not yet.
I guess not everyone can be Niizuma Eiji.
But the artist had only been using a pen for two months, it seems.
The original story author also isn't proficient yet, but his general ideas were...
Well, if you liked them, then make sure to raise them properly.
I think that in three years, they'll surpass Niizuma Eiji.
I'm going to get another story done by the end of this year.
It won't be one that he'll say should be a light novel.
I'll fix the things he pointed out and show you some awesome drawings.
Translator
TLc
kewl0210
Chrno
Timing
Edit
GeRi, KmE
Z4kku
Typesetting
Karaoke
scol, KmE
Jecht, KmE, pablo212
QC
Echo_Chidori
Mistral[sA]
bobo343
Encode
pablo212
Tears and Tears
Morning.
Hey.
Did you finish the name?
No, no matter how hard I try, there's no way it'll be done that fast.
We're gonna have another work done by the end of the year, right?
I know, I know.
Last pitch!
Okay!
So, have you gotten used to being in the seat next to Azuki?
I'm not so nervous that I feel sick inside anymore.
You were that nervous?
But you must be happy, getting to sit next to the girl you like.
Well I guess you could say I'm happy, but...
It's fine as long as you're happy, right?
Here, the point is here.
Here. And one here, too.
koko
kokekokkoo
And another point here. Make sure you remember it.
Okay, now turn to the next page.
Azuki laughed.
Wow... I've made contact with Azuki.
What is your favorite season, Azuki-san?
Spring
Summer
Fall
Winter
Three?
Fall!
Favorite season?
What are you, in elementary school?
So, what else did you ask?
Stuff like favorite color and favorite food.
Azuki said she likes omelettes with fried rice.
So I said I liked curry.
So you wrote it to each other?
What's with this point-blank range long-range relationship?
There's other stuff to talk about, isn't there?
It's fine as long as we're happy, right?
Yeah, I guess...
So the next one's gonna be a sci-fi action?
Yeah, I'm still figuring out the contents.
I was wondering whether or not it'd be a good idea to do the same genre again.
Why?
I guess I want to progress beyond what we brought in before.
Like making it better and easier to understand.
I see.
Ah, by the way,
he said he'd send "Futatsu no Chikyuu" in for the monthly award, right?
Yeah.
For now I think I'm going to send this manuscript around for the monthly award.
Is that okay?
Monthly award?
You mean the excellence award given to one of the works submitted every month?
So, does that mean it's good?
It's not that easy.
But with manga, you get ten different opinions from ten different people.
There might even be people who say that this could get into the finals.
The first work we wrote might make it to finals.
That's amazing, isn't it?
Well, he said it wouldn't happen so easily, but...
If we do make it that far, I'm even gonna let Azuki know.
YUUEISHA
Yuujirou, hurry up.
Y-Yes, sir!
Looks like this time, the editor-in-chief himself is going to Niizuma Eiji's house.
So he really intends to have Niizuma Eiji debut in high school?
I guess it's because his semi-finalist work for the Tezuka Award took 2nd place in the readers questionnaires.
A fifteen year old getting 2nd place is unprecedented.
Even now, he's been submitting things for the Tezuka Award every month,
and they've all been interesting.
If it keeps up, they're saying he's gonna take every place,
from the lower prize-winners to the honorable mentions.
Sure is amazing.
Yeah, it is.
If he can write manuscripts every month while going to high school,
then if he has assistants, it'll even be possible for him to do a weekly series, huh?
And we can use the hook of genius high school student on it.
That is if the kid himself wants to move to Tokyo.
So that's why the editor-in-chief himself is going to convince his parents, huh?
Amazing.
That's the manuscript from the middle school combo that came this afternoon, right?
I'm a little unsure on what to do...
I told them that I'd send it around for the monthly award,
but I'm not sure if I actually should.
Hey, Hattori, Kimu!
My group is doing the selection for the August monthly award, so let's get it done.
Yes, captain.
Hattori, you said you were submitting that middle school combo's manuscript,
so hurry up and get it out here.
Ah, yes Sir!
Eager, isn't he? That Aida-san.
Looks like the whole Niizuma Eiji thing is motivated him.
Maybe.
Aida-san is always saying,
"Why do you think the editorial department has three groups?"
"It's so we compete to get hits out."
Looks like I might be outta here if I don't submit this now, huh?
Hahaha
Jack editor
So you really are happy?
Yeah.
I wouldn't mind sitting next to her forever.
So how about the main character invents a machine that can grant any wish,
but what he wished for is to sit next to the girl he likes,
and his wish is granted,
but the machine starts to go into over-drive...
and the distance to the girl gets even closer than the seat next to him.
And then—
Wait just a minute!
Don't be so angry.
Of course I'm angry!
Who's that?
It's Satou and Yamaguchi from class 3.
Now explain, clearly!
Okay...
We promised when we started going out, right?!
That we wouldn't keep any secrets from each other!
They're going out...
Scary.
This is one scary battlefield.
Why would you change your first-choice high school?
When we graduate we're going to end up separated!
Love sure is a pain, isn't it?
It'll be all right.
Azuki's not the type to accuse a boy.
That's not it.
When we graduate, Azuki and I are going to be separated, but...
I wonder if it'll always be like this...
Being right next to each other like this,
but not even talking.
I guess that's man's romanticism, isn't it?
Until the dreams come true, we'll work hard without seeing each other directly.
Until then we'll just encourage one another through email or something.
Why not until our dreams come true?
Azuki-san, is something wrong?
I'm sorry.
It's just that my pet died yesterday...
I understand if you're sad, but we're in the middle of a lesson.
Yes, ma'am.
"Not until our dreams come true,"
I trampled over Azuki's feelings.
And I actually thought of myself as romantic...
Why not until our dreams come true?
Well, that's all for today.
Thank you very much!
An email address!
You're saying you made her cry?
Yeah, but I don't understand.
About what?
Why she gave me her email address.
So even though you're on the exact same wavelength, you don't know?
We got too close, and our lines crossed.
I don't really understand girl feelings much either, but...
Azuki likes you, so you must've been happy, right?
She is telling you that now, even without your dreams having come true,
you can talk about various things and encourage each other.
Things like that.
She told you her e-mail address.
That's proof of it.
I don't feel like that's it.
I think Azuki cried because I tried to break what she had said about, "Not until our dreams come true."
Well anyway, she told you her email address, so I guess it means,
"Now we'll talk through email," right?
Miho, are you doing okay?
Kaya...
I heard.
So Momo died, did she?
She's alive.
But I heard that during class, you were sad, and were crying about how your pet died.
I just... didn't know what to do.
I didn't even realize I was crying.
What?
What're you talking about?
I don't really understand.
Yeah, I'll explain the whole thing to you another time...
Maybe.
Tell me!
You can be totally honest with me.
I'll give you some good advice, 'kay?
How's it been going for you, Kaya?
With Takagi-kun.
No, nothing has changed really.
Ever since then Takagi hasn't said anything to me, either.
Well, let's talk about that stuff tomorrow.
Okay.
Well, send my regards to Momo.
Back then...
I'll work hard.
I'll become a seiyuu and appear in your anime.
How great!
So if that dream comes true, please marry me!
We did promise, didn't we....?
Even though...
I have been looking at her for so long...
Now...
we can look towards the same dream.
Maybe when we change seats again,
I'll email you.
The time for us to always be together
will be when I become a mangaka.
Miho!
Well, well.
What?
It kinda feels like ever since this morning, you've had a refreshed-looking face.
Really?
So, what was it that was troubling you so much that you cried?
It's all right now.
It looks like my feelings got across clearly.
What? What? What?
What're you talking about?
You made her cry again?
But she smiled.
So they were tears of joy this time?
Maybe.
I'm glad, then.
I don't want to see Azuki's tears anymore.
Also, there's something I want to talk about.
Judges for the Tezuka Award
TEZUKA AWARD
Oda
Eichiro-sensei
Kishimoto
Masahi-sensei
Toriyama
Akira-sensei
The deadline for the Tezuka Award is September 30th.
Finding the
ultimate talent!!!
DECIDED!!
Let's get one work done by then!
THIS TIME'S JUDGES
That's different from what you said this afternoon!
We decided we were going to make a story we both approved of, right?
We are!
But it's already September 5th.
Even if I already had a name done,
you wouldn't make it in time, Saikou.
I'll make it!
Even on school days, I can do one or two pages.
On days off I can draw five or six.
And September has two national holidays, I can do it!
If I can get the first half done by the 13th!
But we already have stuff that Hattori-san is looking at.
We shouldn't fuss over the Tezuka Award.
We should be thinking about quality before prizes.
Of course we'll have him look at it.
We'll have him look at it before September 30th...
and have him send it in for the Tezuka Award.
Even if you want to get the Tezuka Award,
we should be more worried about drawing something interesting than drawing something fast.
What're you in such a hurry for?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Sorry.
There's nothing wrong with wanting to be able to do it as fast as possible,
but it has to be interesting.
I'm going to say something really selfish.
Okay.
By graduation,
like the time when we said that we were going to try to become mangakas,
I really want to see Azuki smile one more time.
The smile from when we promised we'll get married when our dreams come true.
So before graduation, you want to win the Tezuka Award and make Azuki happy?
It's Yuueisha!
Yes?
It's Hattori from Weekly Shounen Jack.
Is this Takagi-kun?
Yes.
Are you guys drawing?
Y-Yes.
Unfortunately, the work you left with me before...
just barely missed being a final candidate for the monthly award.
I thought I should report in and let you know.
Sorry, could you hold on a minute?
He said we didn't make it to the final candidates for the monthly award.
I see.
Thank you very much for contacting me about it.
But really, as a future prospect—
I'm glad.
Glad?
Yes.
To only get to the final selection,
with our names in small writing somewhere,
it would be uncool, and we couldn't show our girlfriends.
We're definitely going to get something in for the next Tezuka Award!
I-I'm glad to hear it.
That's the spirit.
Yes, excuse me, now.
With the next Tezuka Award, we'll definitely make Azuki happy!
Looks like there was nothing to be unsure about.
I want to be careful about how I raise them,
so I was debating whether or not to submit it for the award.
That middle school combo from before?
For their first work, no matter what kind of award it is,
if they win, they might be unreservedly happy.
If they didn't make it to the final selection,
They might lose their will.
I was worried about that sort of thing,
but they're quite something.
So then,
Eiji-kun's moving to tokyo has been approved by you, his parents, then?
Niizuma
Yes.
We're quite all right with it.
You must be glad, Editor-in-Chief.
Yes.
Eiji, some people from Shounen Jack are here to see you.
Niizuma-kun, this is the editor-in-cheif, Sasaki-san—
Niizuma-kun...?
This is quite a room.
About moving to Tokyo, I actually have one condition.
Condition?
If I become the number one most popular author in Jack,
please give me the power to end one manga that I hate.
Wha...?
Preview of
Next Episode
Our goal is the Tezuka Award!
This is actually so interesting it's almost miraculous!
Hattori-san was positive about it, too.
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
With this...
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
We'll definitely place!
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Great Newcomer
Tezuka Award
PRIZE WINNER
Iwase Aiko
Takagi Akito
Next time, Anxiety and Anticipation
Anxiety
and Anticipation
Dreams really shake up the ones who have them.