I was sure you'd come back for this.
So, I was waiting for you.
What the hell is he planning?
Work with me and become a mangaka.
I–I'm going to be drawing the art, and he's doing the stories.
I knew it!
Wow! Then I'm sure you'll make it!
S-So if our manga gets turned into an anime,
we'll reserve the role of heroine for you or something...
Really?
I'm so happy!
I'll work hard.
I'll become a seiyuu and appear on your anime.
Note: A Seiyuu is a Japanese voice actor.
How great!
So if that dream comes true, please marry me!
I couldn't sleep a wink.
Translator
TLc
kewl0210
Chrno
Timing
Edit
GeRi, Leet_Garaa
bobo343
Typesetting
Karaoke
scol, Kme
Jecht, Kme
QC
Alais
Echo_Chidori
Mistral[sA]
Encode
darkphoenix
Stupidity and Intelligence
How long do you plan on staying in your pajamas?
Please hurry up and get ready.
Got it.
Honestly, can't you be polite and say "Yes, Mom."?
So if that dream comes true, please marry me!
KING OF
MANGA
Anyone Can Draw
Introductory Level
Mako-chan and Rabi-Kun's
Drawing Course
Let's
become
manga
artists!!
If our dreams come true... marry...
He got me worked up, and I blurted out that I would become a mangaka, but...
Really...
Moritaka, Takagi-kun is here to see you!
Huh?
Please hurry!
Hi!
So annoying.
Morning, Saikou.
Please don't call me "Saikou" or suddenly show up to meet me in the morning like this.
Come on, I'll call you Saikou and you can call me Shuuto.
A Moritaka going by "Saikou",
Note: The name "Moritaka" uses the same kanji as "Saikou" (最高), meaning "the best".
and an Akito going by "Shuuto" are a bit different.
The kanji for "Akito" (秋人) can also be pronounced "Shuuto", as in the English "shoot".
Hm? How are they different?
The name "Shuuto" gives off a cool soccer image.
Saikou!
"Saikou" sounds like I'm being made fun of.
I guess so.
All right.
Then I'm gonna call you Shuujin.
"Shuujin" is a Japanese word for "prisoner."
Shuujin?! Like a criminal?!
It's fine, isn't it? Akito can be read that way too, can't it?
Right, Shuujin?
Then, at least as Shuujin...
Are you okay with it?
Sure!
Your uncle died three years ago, right?
Did you check up on it?
We're neighbors. My parents knew.
But they didn't know he was the mangaka, Kawaguchi Tarou.
It is a pen name after all.
His real name was Mashiro Nobuhiro.
Seems like it just said "Mangaka dies" in the corner of some newspaper.
If a mangaka can't get serialized, they're just a NEET.
Note: NEET stands for "Not in Education, Employment or Training"
After being a NEET for seven years in a row, it'd be no surprise that you wanted to die.
He committed suicide?
My parents said he died because he was overworked,
but he barely had any work for seven years, right?
So, do you wanna give up on being a mangaka?
Even if you quit, I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna do it too!
Teamed up with you, we'll be the top mangakas in Japan!
Like I said, I haven't decided if I'm teaming up with you or not.
That again?
I'm the one who inspired you to do it in the first place, aren't I?
It wasn't you, it was Azuki.
Eh? What's with that attitude?
But you have my thanks, cupid Shuujin-kun.
Even so, Saikou, let's work together eh?
Takagi-kun.
Iwase?
How are you doing?
Huh? Well... Same as always, I guess.
You can say that again.
I won't lose to you on today's test.
Even the results for the first term of third year will have a big impact on our high school applications.
Yeah.
Have you decided which high school to go to?
I haven't yet.
So these two are the top of our grade?
Ah, tests are such downers.
Yesterday, I just gave up and went to sleep.
I got my skin all shiny for nothing.
That's okay, Kaya.
I couldn't get much studying done yesterday either.
Yeah, right.
You always get good scores anyhow, Miho.
I do not.
Bye then.
Everyone, settle down and write.
Especially you, Suzuki.
At least try not to spell your name wrong.
Mashiro Moritaka
Year
·
Class
Name
Mid-Term Exam - Math
Azuki...
She's the same as always.
Even after something like what happened last night...
Azuki becomes a seiyuu...
I become a mangaka...
Dreams... marriage...
Me, marrying Azuki?!
I can't do this.
Sensei.
What is it, Mashiro?
I don't feel so good, could I rest in the infirmary until second period?
Your complexion certainly doesn't look good.
You can take a retest, if you want.
No.
I finished half, this much will be fine.
Are you okay to go on your own?
I'll be all right.
Sensei, me too...
I spent all last night studying and now I feel dizzy. Can I go?
What? You too, Takagi?
I finished the test!
Well, I guess it's all right then...
Hey now, everybody concentrate on your tests!
Infirmary
Excuse me.
What? You too, Takagi-kun?
Sorry, I didn't get enough sleep.
I'll just be borrowing a bed for a bit.
You really don't look it.
I'm so dizzy I feel like I'm gonna throw up, I've got a migraine...
Take care of yourself.
Are you okay, Saikou?
Seriously annoying.
You didn't sleep last night, right?
Have you eaten? Do you have a fever or something?
It was kind of suffocating, being in that classroom.
Suffocating?
From lack of sleep?
It's like my chest got all tight when I was in the same room as Azuki...
Are you two fooling around?!
S-Sorry.
Your chest felt tight?
Has there been any progress since then?
No, none.
"None?"
Did you guys at least exchange email addresses?
No, we didn't.
Hey! If you're well enough to talk, then please go back to your classroom!
We can't talk here. Let's go.
Fine with me.
Thank you very much.
We're going back.
Why did you two come here?
I'll ask for Azuki's address for you.
It's okay. I'd feel pretty pathetic if you did that.
But you can't ask her yourself, right?
If I could talk to her that easily, I wouldn't be stressing over this.
Saikou...
You really do like Azuki, don't you?
I like people like you two, Saikou.
You're as creepy as ever.
Look at other people who are going out.
They're being lovey dovey without caring where they are,
they prattle on about how proud they are to be dating and stuff...
They're all just like that.
Compared to them, I like people who get choked up from just being in the same classroom way better.
Like I said, what good does it do me to be liked by you?
But now it's really sealed that we'll team up.
Why?
Because I'm the only one who knows that you like Azuki.
Yeah.
Don't tell anybody, okay?
So I'm the only one who you can talk to about your love life.
We're each other's closest friends.
So let's combine our skills in both love and manga and give it everything we've got!
Love is love, manga is manga.
Ah, yeah.
Anyway, are you okay with not going back? There's still time—
I already finished the test flawlessly, full marks without a doubt.
I really don't get you.
You've got your sights set on being a mangaka, so why are you studying so hard?
You don't need an academic background for it.
Insurance.
Even I'm not a hundred percent sure I can make it.
Just as I thought... That's a wise way to live.
Do you see everyone in the class as idiots?
Eh?!
Do you think you're the smartest one in the class?
Why such an unpleasant question all of a sudden?!
So you do?
As for being a mangaka...
You think that unless you're smart, you can't become one, don't you?
I do.
To be a mangaka, you need brains and good sense.
But I don't think you can say "being good at studying equals being smart."
It's only been two months since we joined the same class, Saikou,
but I knew it as soon as I saw you.
"This guy's smart."
That's why I asked you.
If it were only your drawings that were good, I wouldn't have asked you.
As for that "Do you see everyone in the class as idiots?" question...
It's because you see everyone you asked it as idiots themselves, right?
Azuki's smart too.
Or rather, I think she's clever.
She's cute, but without standing out in an odd way.
She genuinely behaves with grace, you know?
It's because she's doing it without thinking.
I think she's much cleverer than me, who can just study well.
You saw Azuki's house, right?
Amazing, wasn't it?
She's even blessed in her own environment and household, that Azuki.
That's why she's not greedy.
Azuki's charm comes from her good family and wealth of spirit,
and she has a dignity born of her intelligence, don't you think?
Dignity, huh?
Anyway, you sure are praising her a lot.
I may be praising her, but you're not getting jealous or impatient.
It's because you're smart.
Man, good parents, a good house, a good face,
from the moment we're born, there's plenty of stuff that makes everyone different.
But in the end, past all that, the stupid ones who dream,
but are smart enough not to get lost in their dreams, are the ones who can get to the top.
That's what I believe.
Anyway, from this point onwards, we've gotta keep giving it all we've got.
Shuujin.
I think I might team up with you after all.
Your way of thinking is sort of similar to mine,
and I think a story made by you would be interesting.
Oh, is that so?
Then let's both do our best together!
I said "might."
I just mean that if you write a name that is interesting,
I'll draw the pictures for it.
Okay!
First period is over.
Do you think you can handle taking the next exam?
So what's a "name?"
Huh?
I've been thinking about your uncle's suicide, like you said.
Do you think your parents would be against you becoming a mangaka?
With something like that having happened to a relative,
it wouldn't be that strange for them to be opposed to it.
It's certainly true that since Uncle died like that.
They'll definitely be against the idea.
When I get home, I'll convince them.
Like with Kyojin no Hoshi's Hoshi Ittetsu
and Oishinbo's Kaibara Yuuzan,
parents are the first hurdle for their kids to overcome.
The rules in my house are like this:
If there's something I want or something I need to discuss,
I talk to Mom first.
Then, when I'm not around, my mom tells my dad.
Then if my dad is against it, she'll tell me later.
Award
Middle-School Men's Individuals
Championship
Mashiro Masahiro
If no objections are made, then that means it's okay and goes through.
In other words, my dad and I have almost never had a serious talk.
Go ahead, Dad.
No, I will when it's done.
Mom!
What is it?
You haven't even said "I'm home" yet.
I've got something I need to talk about.
Well? What do you need to discuss?
Yeah...
Please hurry up and say it.
Well...
I'm going to be a mangaka.
No.
That sure was a fast reply.
I'll go to high school and college, like normal.
If nothing comes of it by the time I'm out of college, I'll give it up.
By that you mean you'll settle for any old school and just draw manga, right?
Even your uncle had his debut when he was in college.
If I let you do this here, you'd just be doing the same thing as him.
I knew there'd be a comparison to Uncle.
Forget about manga and concentrate on your studies.
You don't know for sure that I'd go down the same path that Uncle did.
There's definitely no reason to think I'd kill myself!
Do you think your uncle committed suicide?!
Your uncle over-exerted himself—
Sorry, I know.
He wasn't selling anymore, and in order to get selling again, he worked too hard...
I meant that to draw until you die is like suicide, in a way...
Anyway, you can't.
I'm sure your father wouldn't allow it either.
All right, end of discussion.
Mom.
What now?
Please at least talk with Dad about it.
Dad still hasn't come home yet.
SUPER
This is funny!
Manga sure is amazing.
Though I said it in the spur of the moment, I've always wanted to be a mangaka...
like Uncle.
Uncle was always drawing.
As he kept drawing he'd get more disheveled.
He may not have been able to sell in the end,
and he may be gone now,
but this fascinating manga is still here.
I think, after all, no matter what I'm told,
even if I'm disowned,
I'm going to become a mangaka.
Welcome home.
Dad's... home.
Ten minutes... No, five minutes?
That was fast.
Must mean Dad gave a fast reply too...
Moritaka, I'm coming in.
G-Go ahead.
I talked to your father.
Y-Yeah?
"Let him do it."
"Men have their dreams that women can't understand."
Is what he said.
Come down.
Eh?
To your grandfather's room.
He's the one who lost a son to manga, so we have to let him know.
You'll tell him yourself.
I see...
Grandpa,
can I come in for a second?
Yeah...
Grandpa...
What is it, Moritaka?
I'm going to be a mangaka.
Heh, a mangaka eh?
Uh, yes.
Moritaka, take this with you.
A key?
Father!
Is this... your answer?
Yes.
What are these keys?
The keys to your uncle's room.
Nobihiro's room, his workplace has been left the same as it was when he died.
It's yours, Moritaka.
No, I haven't decided if I want to become a mangaka for sure.
It's still ten years too early to have a workplace...
That's true.
You won't be using it seriously for a long time,
but there's nothing wrong with being prepared ahead of time.
Also, that room is packed with things you need to become a mangaka, isn't it?
What? Do you not need it?
Thank you.
Is it all right if I go over there now?
What're you talking about?
It's past ten already and you have a test tomorrow—
Go.
Hurry up and go.
Thank you, I'm gonna get ready!
Father...
Moritaka has changed, hasn't he?
I was really worried that he'd end up a failure,
but he's fine like this.
Just seeing Uncle's manuscripts will be enough.
I'm going!
Hurry back!
I'm sorry!
Uncle's workplace...
It's been three years...
Yoohoo, my beloved Saikou-chan.
Did your parents give you permission?
I'll show you a name, so come.
Huh?
I got my uncle's workplace!
I got the workplace that my uncle left after he died!
D-Do you mean they gave it to you when you said you were going to be a mangaka?
Yes.
Awesome!
Where are you now?
I'm heading towards the northern Yakusa Station.
The workplace is in Yakusa!
Oh! One stop huh?
I'm leaving right now, wait for me at the station.
Okay!
Preview of
Next Episode
Let's go to Uncle's workplace!
What's left behind there are passionate thoughts and a harsh reality.
And the shocking truth.
I wanna know!
Parents
and Children
Next episode: Parents and Children
What supports dreams are love and romance!