Hey, is there something you didn't tell me regarding
this meeting we're having in front of the train station?
I don't get it either.
I know, really.
I keep imagining different things!
Quit thinking about weird stuff.
Oh, sorry!
Oh, it's fine.
G–Good evening!
So, where do you want to go?
Today, I'll treat you to anything you like.
We're celebrating the decision of you running in the magazine.
Eh?
Feast and Graduation
For some reason,
when newcomers get their first run in a magazine,
it has become tradition for the editorial department to treat them to a meal.
I was saving that meat!
You've have five more than me!
Well I'm the one who suggested we go for yakiniku in the first place!
It's okay, we can just order more.
Really?
Yeah.
Th–Then...
Even the ones that say "extra-special" on them?
Show some restraint.
For such a joyous occasion,
I would like you to have a feast.
Thank you very much.
But we can't just do nothing but celebrate.
Because we're going to win against Niizuma-kun, right?
As soon as you're done eating,
let's head back to the company and form our battle plan.
Yes, sir!
In the next issue of NEXT!, there are eleven works running.
One gag manga,
one soccer manga,
and the rest are so-called Jack-like battle mangas.
Besides our Kono Yo wa Kane to Chie, right?
In a way, this much is just as I had calculated.
Most likely, Niizuma-kun will take the lead in regards to the battle mangas.
Thinking optimistically,
it will be a one-on-one fight with Niizuma-kun.
Right.
Okay, now for the final check on the name.
Let's start from the first panel.
"Kono Yo wa Kane to Chie"
It has to be a story from beginning to end in 45 pages,
so there's no way around starting with narration.
But you've packed too much in.
Try to trim down the word count as much as possible.
Okay.
For this computer drawing,
something with a more "computerish feeling" would be better, even if it seems old.
Something that will convey a clear image to the readers.
Okay. I'll do something more mechanical-looking.
Okay, second panel.
On the explanation of the world's structure,
make the sentences more concise and more god-like sounding.
Um...
Are we going to go through each panel of all 45 pages, one at a time?
Yes, but would that be a problem?
No, thank you very much!
Doing every panel like this for us is incredible!
I told you, didn't I?
Even I seriously want to win against Niizuma Eiji.
Right.
Niizuma-san is getting ready for serialization...
so if we won against him,
serialization wouldn't be just a dream anymore, right?
Even if you do win,
I think you shouldn't be serialized for another three years.
Not until you've graduated high school.
Another three years...
There's no need to rush.
You should hone your skills and do something you're sure about.
Okay then, third panel.
Hattori-san.
If we win against Niizuma-san...
If we get first place in NEXT!...
Please think about us moving toward serialization.
That's what we're aiming for with this.
I've been thinking about it a while now, but...
why are you in such a hurry to be serialized?
I think that even Niizuma-kun is going too fast for his own good.
The editorial department just wants to market him as a genius high schooler.
But...
I understand.
We'll talk about serialization when you've beaten Niizuma-kun
and get good results on the questionnaires.
All right.
Okay, let's get back to the name.
Okay.
MEETING CORNER HOURS OF OPERATION:
MANAGEMENT
Mashiro-kun, the success of this manga
will depend on well you bring out the character's expressions and mentality in your drawings.
Is this really all right with you?
There are still trains running, and...
And?
The fare for going to Yakusa will be pretty steep.
You don't need to worry about that.
It's just because our meeting ran late.
You two must be tired.
No, not at all.
I learned plenty from all your intricate advice.
Honestly, thanks for everything.
Man, I want to win.
Especially for Hattori who did all that for us.
A high-class meal and a serious meeting...
Going home in a taxi...
It feels like... we're not middle schoolers anymore.
You sure ran late.
Yeah.
For only being in middle school, they sure work hard, huh?
What's wrong?
That's true, but for some reason those two are in a hurry.
Even about not getting serialized for three more years when they've graduated high school.
Well, you know...
thee years for us is totally different from three years for them.
"Kono Yo wa Kane to Chie"
You might be right.
Huh? Why KOOGY?
Looks like the second stage of his production plan.
Eh, is that right?
Besides that, he's designing clothing...
Hm? These are actually pretty tasty.
Want some, Miho?
No, I'm good.
What's wrong? You seem down.
Ah, something happened with Mashiro, didn't it?
Be careful with those emails.
Misunderstandings happen.
It could cause a fight.
I still haven't exchanged emails with Mashiro yet.
Huh?
You told him your email address, didn't you?
He's definitely busy.
You can tell how hard it is to be a mangaka just by looking at those two.
Miho...
Then why don't you send him one, instead?
Something like, "Do your best!"
Or, "I'm cheering for you!"
I still haven't... been told his email address.
What's Mashiro doing?!
There are limits even to being busy!
Miho, even with us graduating so soon, are you okay with that?
You won't be able to see each other like this anymore.
Won't you be lonely?
I'd be lying if I said I won't be lonely, but...
Right now I want to concentrate on both of our dreams coming true.
Mashiro-kun is working hard...
so I need to work hard, too.
Thanks for caring about all this.
What're you talking about?
We've been best friends since elementary school!
Stuff like that's a given.
We may be going to different places in high school, but...
we'll always be together, right?
What's wrong?
I...
Municipal
Mojiyama Park
What did you want to talk about?
Come on, say it.
I'm busy. It was decided that we're appearing in Jack NEXT!
Huh? You're running in Jack? That's amazing!
Doesn't that make you a pro?!
It's Jack NEXT!
And pros are people who can make a their whole living off drawing manga.
Takagi's so cool...
Don't go telling Azuki.
Got it.
So, what did you want to talk about?
What is it?
Miho told me not to tell you, but...
That sort of thing happens a lot with you.
If someone tells you not to say something, don't say it.
Miho's moving.
Eh?
Where?
To Hachiouji.
Could that be that she...
Because of how they're not meeting until their dreams come true...
I don't know that, but...
Don't tell Mashiro, okay?
If Azuki said not to, I won't.
Is she going to tell him herself?
Yeah, a little before she moves.
Then...
But don't you think they'll be lonely?
That will make it easier for both of them.
I want to...
before Miho moves and before they graduate,
get Miho and Mashiro have one date!
They should do at least that much!
Even if they won't kiss, they can at least hold hands and wish each other luck.
Those two... If they are alone,
I don't think they would even speak to each other, let alone hold hands.
Even that is good enough!
Even if they just look each other in the eyes!
But if you try to make Saikou and her do that,
they probably won't be happy about it.
That's not true!
If Mashiro invited her, Miho would definitely be happy!
But they promised not to see each other until their dreams came true.
I'm sure she would be happy if she was told he wanted to date her once before graduation.
That's the kind of person she is.
Really?
Are those two... just going to keep this up and say goodbye at graduation?
Until their dreams come true?
When will that be?
Is it certain that they will come true someday?
I–If they really like each other, then they wouldn't need their dreams to come true, right?
Why are you crying?
Okay.
I'll ask him.
It might be a waste of time, though.
Eh, really?
You were faking?
I'm different.
Azuki's moving?
I see...
So... we thought it might be nice if the two of you could talk one time before she moves.
We need to win against Eiji and get first place in the questionnaires.
We don't have that kind of spare time.
That's true, but...
Why didn't Azuki tell me herself?
But just a little chat wouldn't...
We won't meet until after our dreams have come true.
Not before that.
Why are you being so stubborn?
Are you some kind of idiot?!
You just won't go!
Miyoshi, calm down!
You don't understand girls' feelings at all!
Man, I feel bad for Miho.
I understand Azuki better than you do!
You do not!
You don't have a clue!
There's no way she wouldn't be happy to see you!
Hey, hey, hey!
This is a promise we made between the two of us!
Cool down a minute, Miyoshi. Saikou, you too.
Why would you promise something like that?!
Some outsider like you shouldn't be butting in like this!
I knew that wasn't going to go well.
Sorry, Saikou.
How about we leave for today?
I'll leave the the part of the name I fixed.
Miyoshi doesn't mean anything bad.
Please understand that.
You know, that's just how she is.
She gets a little wild sometimes.
I known.
Okay. I'd better follow after Miyoshi.
Later, Saikou.
Right.
Azuki's moving.
But it's not like she's leaving the country or anything.
And until our dreams come true,
no matter where she is, it will be the same.
If we both work hard,
those dreams will come true sooner.
Until then, just like Uncle,
I'll just look at our graduation album.
We'll encourage each other just through email.
Damn it!
When are we going to get serialized?
Oh!
Saikou, you're early.
So are you.
Well, my parents forgot to turn on the heat.
There is heating here.
It's cold out, so I took refuge here.
Heaters sure are nice.
Wish I had one.
I wonder if someone would buy what's inside my head for around 100 million?
How much do yakiniku do you think you could eat if you had 100 million?
Even though I ate all that before,
You're the real glutton.
It was like you had two bodies, Saikou.
Sure was.
Thanks, Shuujin.
About what?
You were watching out for me.
I must apologize to Miyoshi.
I called her an outsider.
She might not forgive me after so long, though.
Mind if I make a call?
Huh? To whom?
Miyoshi.
I'm sorry, Mashiro!
Huh?
After thinking about it,
I realized this is a matter about how you two feel.
I lost my cool and couldn't restrain myself.
Then I said some things I shouldn't have.
So I take back what I said yesterday.
I'm sorry!
It's okay, Miyoshi.
But...
I said some mean things when I got angry, too,
so we're in the same boat.
Mashiro...
Anyway, thanks for worrying about us.
Ah, now it's all good.
I kind of feel like we dragged you into all of this, Shuujin.
It's just your imagination.
We're here.
Welcome back.
How did it go?
The name was OK'd.
I don't really understand,
but that means you're making progress, right?
Yeah.
Great!
Now we can finally make it a manuscript.
Oh, you still have to do that?
Yeah, now it's the real deal.
Inking, backgrounds, filling in darks, tones, effects, whiting...
Woah, there's a lot to do.
Being a mangaka is quite hard, huh?
So you finally get it?
What is it?
I kind of thought we could go out together,
but it looks like you're busy.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
Really?
I was planning to leave early today, too.
We're not starting for real stuff until tomorrow.
Are you really leaving early?
Yeah, that's the plan.
So is it okay if we leave?
Have fun.
Thank you, Mashiro.
Thanks for the hard work.
Yeah.
Do your best!
Thank you.
So, where do you want to go?
We don't have much time, though.
Our usual park?
You're really okay with here?
Yes.
Ah, I see.
Hey.
Hmm?
Even though Mashiro said all that,
there's no way he's going home.
They're not going to meet until their dreams come true,
so he's doing his best with manga so he can see Azuki even one day sooner.
Don't you think so?
Looks like you're starting to understand Saikou a little bit, too.
So then, Mashiro really wants to see Miho a lot, right?
Miho does, too.
Those two really won't let this go.
Aren't you not interfering with those two anymore?
Yeah, but...
Then leave it alone.
You're poking your nose in too much.
Recently, at school...
Miho and Mashiro have been acting awkward.
It's like they're avoiding each other.
They may be together until graduation, but...
are they really all right with these being their memories of the end of middle school?
I feel bad for both of them.
You really are poking your nose in.
But...
I kind of like that about you.
Say that again!
My heart wasn't ready!
I–I kind of don't want to.
Why?!
Whatever...
What does that mean?!
You cheapskate, Takagi!
I'm fine with being a cheapskate.
Anyway, I just thought of something.
What?
A way to make memories for Azuki and Saikou.
Yakusa City Akehi Middle School
Class of 2008 Graduation Ceremony
I think we must say that we, juniors, have been taught a lot.
I'd like to leave you saying that we've benefited from their by having the upperclassmen at this school,
and we pray that you have prepared well for your future.
Now for the graduating class response address.
Yes, sir.
Reply address, by graduate representative Iwase Aiko.
Keep your spirits up, Saikou!
We're going to different high schools, but I'll always be cheering you on!
O–Okay.
You, too, Takagi.
R–Right.
Don't cry anymore.
But...!
Your snot!
Stop it!
Mashiro.
Ishizawa...
I can't forgive you, but I'm was wrong to hit you.
I apologize.
Give it your all.
What did that guy come here for?
It's about time we go, huh?
Yeah.
Let's hang out again, okay?
Okay.
Let me tell you about how I got a boyfriend.
Kaya, it's about time we head home.
Huh?
Miho...
What's wrong with Miho?
Sorry. I'll email you again later.
Huh? Okay.
Shuujin...
Huh?
Azuki already went home...
Miyoshi said she was going to take her time walking home with Azuki on graduation day.
Sorry.
I remembered something I have to do!
Okay! Hurry!
Miho, look! There's a weed growing in a place like this!
Life sure is amazing.
Kaya, you sure like weeds today.
I–I–Is that so?
This is the third time.
Man, she's home already!
Miho, look!
Well, I'll be taking my leave.
See ya later!
Kaya!
Miho, you idiot, don't do that!
Mashiro obviously came here for a reason!
Don't run away!
Fight, Saikou-kun!
I must say something...
Bad girl, Merry-chan.
I must say something soon...
But what should it be...?
Um...!
How long...
How long will you wait for me?
I'll wait.
I'll wait forever.
I knew it with just "I'll wait."
Congrats on Graduation!!
March 21, 2009.
We graduated middle school.
Preview of
Next Episode
Azuki's waiting for me. What I need to do now is...
Finish "Kono Yo wa Kane to Chie", right?
I really don't want to lose to Eiji!
Right!
Next
Title Here
Next time,
Early Report and Real Deal.
Jack NEXT! is the first step towards our dream!