I talked to your father.
Y-Yeah?
"Let him do it."
"Men have their dreams."
Is what he said.
Nobuhiro's room, his workplace has been left the same as it was when he died.
I'll show you a name, so come.
Huh?
I got my uncle's workplace!
I got the workplace that my uncle left after he died!
Translator
TLc
kewl0210
Chrno
Timing
Edit
GeRi, Leet_Garaa
bobo343
Typesetting
Karaoke
scol, Kme
Jecht, Kme, pablo212
Mistral[sA]
QC
pablo212
Encode
Parents and Children
It's this condo?
Yeah, 9th floor.
I'm kinda nervous.
E-Excuse u-
What is all this?
It's full of hero figures!
Uncle wrote nothing but hero manga, so he could buy these as business expenses.
A gag hero manga, though.
Are you making fun of him?
I'm respecting him.
Take one out and have a look at what's behind it.
Ooh, Jack!
TL note: "Jack" is a parody of "Jump" the magazine the Bakuman manga is serialized in.
'96, they sure are old!
But I'm gonna read 'em later.
It looks like he got all the Jacks from when he was serialized.
Now then, on the other side of this door is the real workplace.
What an incredible library of manga volumes!
I thought I had a collection, but this is a hundred times the size of it!
It sure takes me back.
Just how much did I use to come here?
How much did I talk with Uncle?
They're in the room over there, too!
Uncle used to say that the best data for manga is manga.
Though with his crappy drawings, maybe he was the only one who said that.
Hey, there are raw manuscripts and stuff here too, right?
Could I see them?
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure they were in that closet.
Names
Figures
He sure sorted them nicely.
Manuscripts
Data Materials
Figures
Manuscripts
Data Materials
Figures
Manuscripts
Data Materials
Hey, is it really okay for me to look at them?
Yeah.
Which one should I pick?
Might as well go with chapter one.
This is the first time I've ever seen a raw manuscript.
Manuscripts are fine, but you should take a look at these first.
Names.
Drafts showing where the panels split with rough drawings and the lines put in.
So this is a name?
It's like a rough draft of a manga.
I've seen these on the application pages for manga awards.
Name
First, the name is written and it's shown to the editor.
Editor Check
Then it's rewritten until he gives the OK.
Once he gives the OK, you can start making it into a manuscript.
Manuscript
Most people who can just show a name
are mangakas whose talent has already been recognized.
We'll be bringing in a completed manuscript because we need to be recognized first.
Yeah, I know that much already.
Hey, Saikou, do you plan on having me do all this?
You mean I can't just write it as text?
Of course.
Speaking of which, you can't just mimic that name either.
Uncle did a gag manga, so the panels were small.
And it's too simple.
Write a name that fits your own story.
I told you, didn't I?
Unless you can write a name I approve of, I won't team up with you.
Of course, when it comes to the point of doing the art,
I'll think of the composition and fix the panel splits too.
So Shuujin, please think of a story that would make me want to draw it.
Saikou... I knew you were great.
Got it!
I'll do it! I'm gonna do it!
I'm kinda fired up about it.
Saikou, what kind of manga do you wanna draw?
I like manly manga.
A manly manga, huh?
What kind, specifically?
What's your favorite manga?
Ashita no Joe!
With his elbow readied, planted under his left armpit,
aiming slightly on the inside, like he's boring into him, pow!
It was a real masterpiece, eh?!
What's your favourite manga, Shuujin?
Hm, Dragonball I guess.
Just like you said, it's a manga that was written by a genius.
Same with "Joe"...
Whether it's manga or novels,
I'm gonna read and study everything I can get my hands on.
Whatever the type; battle stories, love stories,
clear characteristics and rising plot developments...
are strong things to have, don't you think?
Maybe you really can do it.
Huh? Really? Why?
Uncle once entered to win the Akatsuka Award.
Akatsuka Award
Of the two big awards, that's the one for gag manga, right?
Uncle told me he gathered up all the past winning works...
and figured out which ones had value and should be studied.
And he concluded that gag manga with social satire were valued, and it seems it paid off.
So he won the Atatsuka Award?
He only got an honorable mention, though.
But if you're really going for it, I think that's one strategy.
And you actually just thought of starting with the same kinda thing, didn't you?
That's true.
Anyhow, I came all the way here, so...
I'm gonna look at as many names as I can.
They'll be great for reference.
Especially the places where corrections are marked in red pen.
I see what they meant.
I'm sure Shuujin will be able to think of an interesting story and make it into a name.
I've still never drawn real manga before...
Shuujin?
Hm? What?
Do you think we can get an anime version by the time we're 18?
No, not one bit.
You don't have to be so straightforward about it.
But I'm pretty sure that, like idols, lots of seiyuus get out there at 18.
Azuki's cute, so... Even before she's earned any real merit,
she may already have enough to get popular.
Saikou...
I want to become a mangaka with you.
But, right now I feel the same as you.
I really want you and Azuki to be able to get married.
An anime by 18 years old.
We'll make that our goal-
No, we'll make that our reality!
Shuujin...
We'll do it! For sure.
Hey, Saikou, is the manuscript this name was made into around somewhere?
I thought I'd like to compare them.
It should be in one of the boxes.
Okay, I'm gonna look for it.
I'll help.
Thanks.
But man, there sure are a lot of names.
And every one of these boxes is packed to the brim.
But to make just one into a manuscript, just how many minutes would it take?
No, how many hours?
At just what pace did he draw?
With all these...
I'm going to go outside for a bit.
Azuki?
I told you, I don't know her number.
It is now awaiting government action.
On to the next new topic, the popular rock singer, KOOGY-san's concert is having its premier...
with his female fans first in line, it's quite a happening as the opening time approaches.
What's wrong?
This is the first time you've given me a phone call, isn't it?
Dad...
What is it?
Sorry... I...
thought uncle committed suicide.
He wasn't such a coward.
He was a man that the more difficult things got, the more he'd bare with it and work hard.
And he never once complained about it.
Yeah, you're right.
He even gave up sleep, and just focused on drawing something.
Moritaka, have you read "Kyojin no Hoshi"?
Eh, yes.
Then you know Sakamoto Ryouma's line, right?
Yes.
You really liked "Ashita no Joe", right?
Dad, you don't need to say any more.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Sakamoto Ryuuma's words from "Kyojin no Hoshi":
"When men die, even if it's in a ditch, die pitching forward."
And Yabuki Joe, when he was completely worn out, burned away and turned into pure white ash...
Those manga scenes that Dad read to me...
I'm not going to give it anything less than my all.
Manga, Azuki Miho...
I'll put my life on the line for them.
This is interesting, but why was it rejected?
Don't plagiarize.
I'm don't intend on writing a gag hero manga.
What's that?
Letters?
Haruno Miyuki
These are...
We went to different high schools,
so we just exchanged letters like those.
What's up, Saikou?
Hm? Letters?
Uncle told me that he had someone he contacted with ever since his middle school graduation.
Contacted with letters?
Man, that's old fashioned.
So it was a long distance love relationship?
No, they lived in the same city.
Huh?
I kinda feel like we shouldn't look at them.
O-Of course!
That would be a violation of privacy!
Totally.
Anyhow, get to the name already.
I, Mashiro Moritaka, and...
Takagi Akito...
swear never to tell anyone about the contents of this letter!
I swear!
"Mashiro-kun, are you doing well?"
"I'm finally getting used to high school, too."
"To sum up my class, it's like that old youth drama "Tobidase Seishun", was that the name?"
"I went to an ALFEE concert."
"I hate the rainy season, but I bought two pretty umbrellas, so I've come to like it."
Looks like they only wrote about boring every day stuff.
I think that even though they both liked each other, they couldn't put it into words.
I don't get it.
Uncle said that he just couldn't confess...
until he wasn't a gambler anymore, and had become a full-fledged mangaka.
Oh, so that's how it was?
Mashiro Nobuhiro
"Congratulations on getting an honorable mention for the Akatsuka Award."
"I changed residence a little while ago, my address changed so I'll let you know what it is now."
You can really feel those two taking the steps along their lives.
Is that the last letter?
Huh?
Mashiro Nobuhiro
There's a gap of over a year.
There hadn't been a letter in a while.
"I haven't said anything about it up until now, but I'm getting married next Spring."
What is this? She didn't even once tell him she had a boyfriend.
married
I wonder how Uncle felt when he read this letter.
When did "Chou Hero Densetsu" start?
Yeah, uh, I'm sure it'll be in the volumes.
Compiled from issues
ran in Shonen Jack
1996 Issue 20 ~ 1996
Serialized from Spring of 1996, huh?
The Spring two years after that letter, huh?
And it wasn't an anime for another two years.
Looks like he didn't make it in time.
But it's amazing that even after getting so discouraged, he kept it up until it became an anime.
But she was the reason I was able to try so hard.
Hey, what's that?
Inside the box.
There's still something in there.
Yakusa City Akehi Middle School
Graduation Album
An album?!
Uncle said he couldn't even ask for a photo.
Just how pure-hearted was he?
Haruno Miyuki! Look for Haruno Miyuki-chan!
Come on! Haruno Miyuki!
I know, I'm looking!
Azuki?
It's her mom!
This is Azuki's mom!
It's DNA! It's totally scary!
Even the idea of sending each other letters is just like you guys only sending emails to encourage each other!
It's exactly the same!
We don't know for sure that it's Azuki's mom!
I'm telling you, there's no mistaking it!
Let's go confirm it.
How?
We go to Azuki's house again, and we ask her mother directly.
Tomorrow, Tuesday, Azuki has dance classes from 5 to 7.
Why do you know that?
Don't underestimate my network of information!
Why don't you just ask Azuki what her mom's maiden name is?
Cause I wanna ask about some other stuff, too.
Receiving call
Mashiro Kayoko
Aw, man. It's my mom.
Receiving call
Mashiro Kayoko
Hello?
What time do you think it is?!
Come home already!
When the test is over I'm going to KOOGY's concert!
You got dome tickets? You're so lucky!
I guess we'll just go to Azuki's house, then.
Oh, so you think those two have some connection too, huh?
I do not.
Okay, let's go.
Hey, aren't you a little embarrassed sneaking around like this?
It's fun!
I feel like Giovanni from Death Note!
You didn't have any trouble pushing it today.
The second time is always easier.
Yes?
It's Miho-san's classmate, Takagi.
Sorry, Miho just stepped out.
No, today we'd like to talk to her mother.
Me?
It's about the mangaka Kawaguchi Tarou.
This response will tell us if she really was the one who was exchanging the letters...
We, Mashiro-kun and I, are aiming to become mangakas.
It sure is nice to be young.
I'll serve you some tea, so come on up.
All right!
Come in.
Uwah, she really does look like Azuki.
She's a real beauty.
Um, if she was in the same grade as Uncle, she's 42...?
She looks so young!
So Azuki will be like this in 28 years?
But, I think I'll have her give up on the long hair rolls at 42.
What is it, you two?
Ah, nothing.
Come on in, now.
Sit wherever you want, I'll go get some tea.
Ah, okay.
Thank you.
This is the living room where Azuki spends time in every day.
Mashiro-kun, you're the son of Mashiro Nobuhiro-kun's brother, aren't you?
Ah, yes. That's right.
Your father was two years ahead of me in middle school.
He really stood out as captain of the judo team.
Yeah.
Would you two be all right with coffee?
Yes.
Mashiro-kun, ah, I mean Mashiro Nobuhiro-kun,
he drank black coffee when he worked hard every day.
He told me all about it in his letters.
Like I thought, this person really was the recipient of Uncle's letters.
So, ask me anything youngsters.
Um...
Hey, first we have to...
Oh, right.
We're sorry!
We read all of your letters, ma'am.
Oh no, I'm embarrassed. All of them?
Yes.
She's blushing, she sure is cute for her age.
Hey, I didn't write anything that embarrassing in them, right?
Right?
Y-Yeah!
They were unbelievably eloquent.
I'm glad I didn't write anything too drastic.
So Mashiro-kun kept my letters, did he?
And you two read them?
Well, what's done is done.
I forgive you.
Thank you very much.
Um, by saying they were eloquent,
I mean, in a way they were all meandering
You really liked him, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Then why didn't you ever write it in your letters?
It wasn't so much that I didn't, but that I couldn't.
It was so embarrassing I didn't feel I could write it down.
Maybe I was just waiting for us to tell each other "I like you" together.
But I couldn't wait that long, and I found a new love and got married, but...
When Miho was 3 years old, I saw on TV...
Kawaguchi Tarou-sensei's manga had become an anime, I was surprised.
I was so happy to know that Mashiro-kun was still working so hard, too.
I was a bit embarrassed, but,
I went to the convenience store and read "Chou Hero Densetsu".
And in it a hero named "Otokono Roman" appeared.
TL note: Otokono Roman is a pun name, meaning "Men's romanticism."
When I read that, I think I cried a little.
I understood that Mashiro-kun really did have these kinds of feelings.
Otokono Roman.
He always worked hard, dreaming of becoming the greatest hero in the universe,
and to confess to a princess he fell in love with at first sight.
He was extremely weak; a failure of a hero.
But when he was still weak, the princess approached him herself and confessed.
Great
Don't come to me yet, wait until I become the greatest hero in the universe!
Don't just show up out of the blue.
So that story was a message to you, ma'am?
That's how I took it.
Not bad, that Kawaguchi Tarou.
So Uncle told his feelings through manga?
Then would it be all right if I asked something?
Yes.
Takagi-kun, Mashiro-kun,
which one of you is going out with Miho?
Neither of us yet.
But if one of us does in the future, it'll be him.
Hey!
I'm so glad!
Ever since the old days, I've never been into the hard studying type.
Girls tend to like the guys who are kind of the bad boys.
No, it's just this, ma'am.
That's only your personal preference, but I'm popular with girls too.
Also, I have bad eyes.
Hey, sit down.
You're right, I'm sorry.
Well, if you know what I mean.
I don't think I do at all.
Um, there's one thing that's on my mind.
About how Uncle and you were in the same grade,
and my uncle being a mangaka, Miho-san doesn't know, right?
No, she doesn't know.
I'd really like it if you wouldn't tell Miho-san those things.
Got it.
I definitely won't tell her.
You mustn't tell her either, Takagi-kun.
Ah, okay.
Takagi Akito-kun.
Yes.
Mashiro Moritaka-kun.
Become great mangakas.
I'll be here, rooting for you.
Okay, thank you very much!
Okay!
She was a really nice person,
and an amazing beauty, wasn't she?
I can understand why your uncle fell for her.
They were both real romantics, weren't they?
Men's romanticism, huh...?
Yeah.
We becoming mangakas is a man's romanticism too.
Hey, why do you think your uncle's workplace was left like that?
When I was in elementary school, my dad and my grandpa both probably knew I admired Uncle.
That's why neither of them objected.
Yeah.
They knew this would happen.
Or rather, they probably hoped.
I sure am blessed.
Not "I", "we"!
No matter what, I will make this dream a reality!
Not "I will", "we will"!
If I can't do this,
I'm not a man!
I won't be!
Starting tomorrow, no, today, I'm going to start making my drawings into manga artwork!
All right, and I'll take on making a name!
Preview of
Next Episode
I've started running toward the goal of being a mangaka.
Not "I've", "we've", right?!
And I'm making a certain decision.
Not "I'm", "we're," right?
Time
and Key
Next time, Time and Key.
A dream starts with a choice.