This is several levels better than last time.
I'm surprised.
In both the story and the artwork, you got rid of the things I pointed out.
It's much better.
The story is especially good.
Yes, sir!
It's because this time, I took a lot of opinions from Mashiro too!
Today is September the thirtieth.
Do you want to submit this for the Tezuka Award?
Yes!
It didn't make it past the final selection...
There are four prizes from the placing finalists to the honorable mentions,
but they said ours wasn't good enough.
Compared to this guy who won and was also a finalist, Niizuma Eiji,
do you know what the difference is?
It's the drawings, the drawings.
Honestly, both stories were about a four out of five.
But his artwork is a five, and yours is a three.
A three if I'm going easy.
So in other words, Takagi has talent but Mashiro's pulling him down.
Ishizawa-kun, you're being too brutally honest.
Well it's the truth, what choice do I have?
Hey...
You...
Shuujin, stop!
It's true that my drawings aren't on par with his.
See? There it is from the man himself.
Have you ever once drawn a thirty-one page manga?!
Nope.
But I could do much better than this piece of crap.
See?
If you team up with me, we could definitely—
Shuujin!
Apologize to Mashiro!
W–What're you doing?
I'm telling a teacher!
I don't care who you tell!
I'm telling you to apologize!
Hey, did you hear?
I heard some third years had a fight yesterday.
Eh, who?
I don't know their names,
but I heard they were students that always have top scores on tests.
Eh? There were people like that fighting?
Hey, Saikou!
So the reason you were being so stand-offish was because you were drawing manga, eh?
I never would have guessed.
Hey, that's awesome about the Tezuka Award.
Getting to the final selection and all.
I've really formed a new opinion of Takagi.
To allow his grades to drop so he can write manga and all...
Hey, did that thing with Ishizawa yesterday have anything to do with manga?
I heard that guy's trying to become a mangaka too.
Eh, seriously?!
Huh?
Saikou?
So, this problem can be solved if you apply this formula.
Got that, Kawasaki?
Sensei, why do you always call on me?
Because if you can understand it, that means everyone does.
I don't think Suzuki-kun understands.
What are you talking about?
Well then, let's solve this next problem.
It's from Shuujin.
There he is.
Mashiro!
Where's Takagi?
I haven't seen him today.
He told me he's suspended for a week.
Eh?! Why?
Ishizawa came to school!
It's his fault for saying such terrible things!
Well, I think Takagi might have gone a little too far,
but I didn't think he had guts like that!
I guess I need to reconsider him a bit.
Huh, what?
Are you just leaving?
Mashiro!
Work with me and become a mangaka.
I decided I would become a mangaka together with Shuujin.
An anime by eighteen years old.
We'll make that our goal—
No, we'll make that our reality!
Then I'll go to North High too.
Just in order to become mangakas a little faster,
he changed his path in school.
And yet I...
The story is especially good.
So in other words, Takagi has talent but Mashiro's pulling him down.
If I could just... win a prize.
Hey Miho, check this out.
I think this is what Ishizawa had been talking about.
It really surprised me.
To think that Takagi is trying to become a mangaka and all.
I didn't know anything about it.
So that's why he's been half asleep lately.
I understand now.
Hey, what are you reading?
Mina!
Oh, Jack.
Do you know about Jack, Mina-chan?
Everyone in my class reads it.
Really?
But why are you reading it?
Because someone I know has their name in it.
Amazing!
Can I see too?
You mustn't bother your sister, Mina.
But...
You can look at it later.
I've brought out some cake here on the table, why don't you have some?
Okay.
Sorry for all the noise, Kaya-chan.
Not at all, she's as quiet as a church mouse compared to me.
By the way, is the Takagi-kun you were talking about earlier the same Takagi-kun as from your class?
Do you know who he is?
Yes. He's quite famous, being the top of his grade.
But Takagi got suspended.
Ah, why?
He beat up this annoying guy.
But in a way, boys being a little bad makes them attractive, doesn't it?
Mom...
What would a girlfriend do in this sort of situation?
Wah, amazing! Kaya-chan got a boyfriend!
No, it's not like we're actually going out yet or anything.
It's just he's probably feeling down.
You're really something, Kaya-chan!
That's what they call "supporting your partner," right?
No, no...
Good luck to you too, Sis.
Be quiet.
What is it, Moritaka?
Just having a little trouble sleeping.
I see.
How's the manga going?
Yeah. Well, I'm doing my best.
I see.
Oh, thanks for taking care of the utilities and such for the work place, Grandpa.
The one who paid for that is Masahiro.
Dad?
Did something happen?
Not really.
Well, as long as you're alive, there will always be something.
Grandpa...
Mm?
There's a guy I'm drawing manga with.
But I feel like I'm holding him back.
Maybe because he's teamed up with me,
he might end up not being able to become a mangaka.
So I've been wondering if he regrets it.
That's all right, isn't it?
It's something he chose himself.
So he can accept it.
There's no one who would be seriously worried about it,
if it's something you chose yourself.
That's what Otokono Yasegaman said.
TL Note: Otokono Yasegaman is another pun name meaning "Man's false courage."
I'm pretty sure that was in... volume four.
He read them? And even remembers?
Uncle, also...
Kawaguchi Tarou also... thought so, did he?
I'm heading out!
Here, do you understand this here Kawasaki-kun?
Here? Do you mean here sensei?
No, not there.  Here.
Um, you mean here?
Sensei, the lesson isn't getting anywhere.
Could you please just write the important parts on the board?
Okay...
Here, the address of the Takagi residence.
It's because he's suspended at the moment, isn't it?
Ah, yes.
But he's quite a popular one, isn't he?
This is it.
Oh, yeah...
Avenge...
Your dad...
You've got to avenge him, okay?
It doesn't look like his Mom's home.
Hey, I'm coming!
Oh, Saikou?
You came at a good time.
I was just thinking of e-mailing you.
I had time, so I came up with some pretty good stories.
I've been wondering which one to make into a name and wanted you to take a look at them.
Surprisingly...
That's a relief, Shuujin is doing way better than I imagined.
Alright, let's head up. The place is kind of small though.
Okay.
I'll bet this worn out, old apartment surprised you, huh?
Well, we don't have slippers or anything, so just come up like that.
Why?
E–Excuse me.
They're still just in text form, but I'm rather confident about them.
Ah, let me see.
If you don't like them, don't hold back.
This many...
I still have plenty more.
I can amend them, too.
What he's showing me is just the small portion of he thought was good out of all the ones he wrote.
Oh, I recommend this one too.
Anyway, what's up with those two?
It's because I slugged Ishizawa.
I suddenly got really popular.
Looks like it really is true they like boys who are a little bad.
Should you really be saying that sort of thing right now?
I'm worried about it too, that's why I said you came at a good time.
It looks like Miyoshi came because she was worried.
Well I guess I can understand that, but why Iwase?
Seems like Iwase and I are going out, somehow.
Eh? What do you mean by seems like?
Well, I had forgotten, but in the third semester of the first year...
I'm Iwase Aiko.
Uh... Um...
I was second place at the end of this term. Iwase Aiko.
Oh, really?
Let's encourage each other and do our best.
Yeah, let's do our best.
Seems we said something like that.
Just that alone meant you were going out?
Yeah, according to Iwase...
We shook hands. In other words, by holding my hand, you acknowledged we were going out.
...she said.
At the time, I thought it meant we were just heating up our sense of rivalry.
But, could this be because of how serious Iwase is?
You and Azuki didn't hold hands, so
I guess that means Iwase and I have gotten further than you.
Haha.
"Haha" nothing.
So did Miyoshi hear that "seems like you're going out" conversation?
Yeah, Miyoshi said...
Takagi-kun, are you really going out with Iwase?
If you were already dating then why did you confess to me?
...and she got angry.
Then you showed up and the conversation ended.
Then I came at the worst possible time!
This is a battlefield, isn't it?!
Hey.
What are you two whispering about?
Be a little more manly.
Ah, right.
Me or Iwase-san. Which one are you going out with?
Wait.
I never said I was going out with either of you.
I just shook Iwase's hand,
I did not think that equaled going out.
All I said to Miyoshi was, "I wanted to talk to you."
I did not think that equaled a confession.
That's all!
This is ridiculous.
I'm going home.
Takagi-kun, do you hate me?
No, I don't hate you, but...
Then, do you like me?
Well if it's between like and hate, then...
like.
Goodbye.
Wait Miyoshi.
Between liking and hating, I like you too.
Huh?
What are you doing, announcing you're going to date two girls at once like that?!
Ah? Uh, is that what's happening now?
It is.
What are you thinking, Shuujin?
Then let me ask this,
do you two both like me?
I like you.
In a special way.
Of course I like you.
If I didn't, I wouldn't have clasped your hand.
What the hell?
Why am I so popular?
This is messed up!
Wait a second—Wait a second—Eh?!
What're you panicking about?
Just because I'm pretty good at studying?
Me or Iwase-san. Which one do you like?
Please just answer that.
Here... When I say that I like one, does that mean I'm going out with her?
Wait a minute, I have a dream of becoming a mangaka.
Love takes second place to that!
Even if we are going out,
I won't have time for dates or anything!
Okay, that's fine.
I'll support you.
Please quit manga.
If you're doing such a thing,
you will definitely regret it.
If I follow my dream and it shatters,
I can accept having to regret it.
But I don't want to regret not pursuing it in the first place.
Before I started drawing manga with Mashiro,
every day was just passing by.
But now I'm happy.
I embrace life...
Iwase.
I'm going to North Yakusa High with Mashiro.
I see.
Goodbye.
Takagi-kun, you will regret what you just did for the rest of your life.
Without a doubt.
Yeah.
When that time comes, you can laugh at me.
I can't laugh.
North Yakusa is my first choice, too.
You're kidding!
It's decided. Iwase was rejected.
Really? North Yakusa?
Takagi, you're really smart so I was sure you would go to a different school.
I'm so glad, now we can be together next year too.
But before that, you've got to show me how you study for—
Miyoshi.
Mashiro and Azuki are going out.
Or rather, they both like each other.
Eh, seriously?!
Why are you saying that now?!
The reason I asked you things about Azuki... was for Mashiro.
Eh?
So you didn't want to talk to me?
Yes, I just wanted to get information about Azu—
Sorry, it was wrong of me.
It was.
So I'm going to hit you ten more times.
B–But don't you do stuff like karate and aikido?
Boxing, too.
Ok, I'll discount it to three punches.
If I hit you that much, I'll feel better.
Okay, hit me!
After I'm done we can go out.
What does that have to do with it?
You said you liked me before, didn't you?
Oh, just be quiet and hit me!
Are you all right, Takagi?
Just go home already.
Saikou, wait.
I've got something to talk about.
About manga?
Yeah.
I understand.
I don't want to get in the way, so I'll see you later.
Good luck with the manga!
Miyoshi's a pretty good person, isn't she?
Basically.
So, you had something to talk about?
I received a phone call from Hattori-san earlier.
While looking at the comments for the last Tezuka Award,
he said we should have a review meeting.
He said to come by when it was convenient for us.
Alright.
We'll get a prize next time and make our debut, right?
Yeah.
An anime by eighteen, right?
I've finally got some time, so this time I'm going to think of an awesome name.
I'm going to practice drawing more and more.
There's no way I'll make you have any regrets.
I sure am popular today.
Ow!
Don't say creepy stuff.
Guess I'll head to the work place!
Make sure you remember the way.
This area's usually pretty chaotic, so...
But the school is close, and I don't think you'll have to worry about places for food.
Eh, Niizuma-kun?
Niizuma-kun, it's not that way!
Niizuma-kun!
Hey Takagi, maybe we can go on a date to—
No.
Then, tomorrow—
We're starting out on our next work.
Takagi!
Next time: Ten and Two.
I have a dream called "Mangaka!"