Sorry... I...
thought uncle committed suicide.
He wasn't such a coward.
He was a man that the more difficult things got, the more he'd bare with it and work hard.
And he never once complained about it.
Yeah, you're right.
He even gave up sleep,
and just focused on drawing something.
Moritaka, have you read "Kyojin no Hoshi?"
Eh, yes.
Then you know Sakamoto Ryouma's line, right?
Yes.
You really liked "Ashita no Joe," right?
Dad, you don't need to say any more.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Azuki?
It's her mom!
This is Azuki's mom!
Become great mangakas.
I'll be here, rooting for you.
Okay, thank you very much!
Okay!
I sure am blessed.
Not "I," "we!"
No matter what, I will make this dream a reality!
If I can't do this...
I'm not a man!
I won't be!
Starting tomorrow,
No, today, I'm going to start making my drawings into manga artwork!
All right, and I'll take on making a name!
Translator
TLc
kewl0210
watchrocksgrow
Chrno
Timing
Edit
GeRi, Leet_Garaa
bobo343, Z4kku
Typesetting
Karaoke
scol, KmE
Jecht, KmE, pablo212
QC
Mistral[sA]
Echo_Chidori
Encode
pablo212
Time and Key
Most pros use G-pens.
They let you control the strength of the lines...
and brings out more atmosphere in the drawings.
But I couldn't master them, so I use a kabura pen.
TL note: The "kabura" in the pen name means "turnip," coming from the shape.
I do gag manga so I can barely get away with it, but pros use G-pens.
Once in a while I try to use them, but they're really hard.
Mashiro.
Mashiro, wake up!
Eh?
Crap!
Mashiro, it's fine to work hard all night,
but if you fall asleep during the test then there's no point to it, is there?
S-Sorry.
Finally done...
Are you all right?
I've never seen someone fall asleep during a midterm.
Saikou!
Did you study so hard it caused ya to doze off?
Not really.
Anyhow, the test's over, so you wanna catch a movie?
Yeah, yeah! That sexy one!
Sexy one?!
Sorry, I've got stuff to do.
What?
He's been spending all his time with whatever that is.
So were you up all night practicing drawing?
I was at the workplace since midnight.
All the way until I got called by my parents to come home.
In school, when I couldn't calm down, taking the test with this pen gave me momentum.
Woah, you really did bring it...
Anyhow, if I can't get used to this, the whole thing's not gonna happen.
Manga doesn't have limits.
Limits?
It's not like a test which has answers.
There's no upper limit to drawings or stories.
The better you can make them, the better off you are.
I'm going to the workplace, you coming too?
Sure!
You seem happy, Shuujin.
Here, your duplicate key, Shuujin.
C-Can I really have it?
It's more convenient for you to be able to go whenever you want, right?
T-Thanks.
The test's over, so I can fully devote myself to this now.
Awesome! I knew your talent for drawing wasn't half bad!
After just one day you're able to do manga quality drawings!
I'm saying those are totally no good.
What about them?
The lines are stiff and they're way too thick.
Those aren't drawings that can be used for manga.
Really?
I knew G-pens would be tough...
I can't draw the thickness of what I'm imagining in my head.
It was giving me trouble, so I tried using a kabura pen, too.
Kabura pen?
This.
Yeah. When I hear of dip pens, I think of these.
Uncle used these when he couldn't figure out how to use G-pens either.
He was told to use G-pens by his editor,
but because of its odd tendencies he couldn't master it,
so he just used the kabura pens.
It's hard to get different line strengths, but its easier to draw lines at a fixed thickness.
G-pens let you control the strength of the lines, but...
it's easy for them to get caught on the paper.
I see.
So even though your uncle became a pro using a kabura pen,
that's no good for us, huh?
Of course! It can't give the drawings flavor or atmosphere.
Uncle shrugged it off, saying "my drawings are crappy."
And since he was doing gag manga, he said he could get away with it.
That's true...
Anyhow, it's totally different from doing rough sketches with a pencil or doing watercolor painting with a brush.
I've got no choice but to keep drawing until I get used to it.
I drew these yesterday, too.
These are good!
But I better not say so.
Saikou's still not satisfied with them
Kabura pens are good for drawing backgrounds.
And round pens are good for extra-thin lines.
So you drew by looking at those?
Yeah.
I got them all out of the boxes and lined them up.
So they sell this kind of sample material?
With these you'll be able to draw manuscripts perfectly, won't you?
I need to put effects in, too.
Effects?
These.
Uncle directed his assistants on which to use with numbers,
but first I have to be able to do them myself.
All these kinds of lines can be drawn by hand?
While using these sorts of rulers.
We don't have any assistants,
so I even have to put in the screen tones myself.
I used a cutter to cut these out and put them in.
So in short, in order to make one page of a manuscript...
First you start with a name and make it an under-sketch on a paper used for manuscripts...
Then you ink the characters and backgrounds.
Yeah. And then you ink in the effects and affix the screen tones...
And then it's finally finished, huh?
There sure is a lot to do.
Yeah.
The exact operation may vary depending on the person, but
I think it's got this feeling in general.
When I realized how much I have to master before I can draw something we can bring in, I got impatient.
Still humans are easy,
but movement, facial expressions, composition...
Unless I can draw them all, I'll never be a pro.
I don't know how long it's gonna take...
Thinking about it now, it's amazing that Uncle only took three years to go from a total beginner to his debut.
And he didn't even know about the existence of white-out,
so if he made even a little mistake, he'd have to redo that whole page.
H-Heh, is that right...?
But we've gotta do it!
An anime adaptation by 18...
I really can't waste even a single second!
Saikou,
I understand how you feel but I think you should at least study on days before tests.
Yeah, I know.
I planned to study a little yesterday, but it was morning before I knew it.
"Before you knew it..."?
Anyhow, right now I just need to put in effort.
Uncle used to say that too.
It was one of his requirements for becoming a mangaka.
Requirements for becoming a mangaka?
For the "Kawaguchi Tarou type."
Three major requirements for if you're not a genius.
T-Tell me, too!
First: hubris.
First
HUBRIS
Think you're better than everyone else.
I've got that.
But then it's not so much hubris, I have actual talent...
That's what hubris is.
Second: effort.
Second
EFFORT
So he can be straightforward, too, that Kawaguchi Tarou-sensei.
And last:
Yup?
Third
LUCK
Right, luck.
Eh?
What? So in the end it's all about luck...?
Of course.
If you're not a genius, you're just a gambler after all.
But just talking about dreams won't make them a reality.
I'm gonna keep drawing all weekend.
Okay! Then I'm gonna read all the manga in this place!
This "Chichi no Tamashii" is so sad...
TL note: Chichi no Tamashii = Father's Soul
"Along the way,"
"people stood in line, and until they could see their shadows behind them,"
hey send them off as much as they could."
Okay, that's enough.
Ok, next is... Suzuki.
O-Okay!
Please stop with the "okays."
Wh-Why?
I don't really have a reason behind it.
That's mean!
Okay, Kawasaki!
So we're gonna head straight to the workplace?
Yeah.
I'm gonna buy "Jack."
Go ahead.
Let's see, this week's opening color is...
Hm, I also need...
Saikou!
H-Hey, come here a sec.
This!
Niizuma Eiji (15)
Aomori
Tezuka
Award
Semi-Finalist Winner
SEMI-FINALIST PRIZE WINNER!!
Prize
1 Million Yen
It's the semi-finalist prize winner for the Tezuka award.
Th-This semi-finalist...
What?
The age, look at it!
Niizuma Eiji (15) Aomori
Fifteen years old?
It says here he's a high school student.
Received high praise from all the judges.
Niizuma Eiji.
This is kind of annoying.
His acceptance speech.
"Even when everyone was playing video games and hanging out,
I found it worthwhile to work hard.
I am looking forward to continuing that work and contributing energetically to the pages of Jack Magazine."
It's like he's taking a jab at me, since all I did was play video games up until now.
It'll take us no time at all to surpass this guy.
If you look closely, you'll see that the only thing he's being praised for is his art.
That's some confidence.
Confidence, effort and luck are all that count.
More like hubris, effort and luck.
I think "confidence" sounds better.
Anyway, check out the new "Kochikame."
15 years old and he's a semi-finalist.
Moritaka.
I understand you're happy about getting that key,
but do you have to spend every day hanging around your uncle's studio?
You have exams to worry about.
I know that.
Do you really?
If you do, then start studying.
Can I get seconds please?
Sure.
Thank you, Kayoko-san.
I'm heading up to the roof.
Wait up, I'm coming too.
Awesome, it's totally moe.
It's like, you're gonna be a pro mangaka in no time.
Well you know, if I really get serious I might just change the industry.
Yeah!
I'll come up with the story this time, so you can just focus on the art.
Well, I don't mind, but I have high standards.
Hey, can I ask you a question?
What?
Why are they all looking in the same direction?
And you've only drawn them to the shoulders.
Those guys were laughing at us!
That was Takagi from Class 2.
Who was the other guy?
Not sure, what was his name?
Who was that?
Miyoshi Kaya.
Azuki's best friend.
I know that.
I was talking about the guy doing the drawing.
Ishizawa, he was in my class during second year.
Is he also trying to become a mangaka?
Who knows?
I think he's just telling people he's drawing manga in order to attract attention.
Miyoshi was making fun of him, so I don't think he'll get too far.
Don't start slacking off just because midterms are over.
Your real test is going to be the high school entrance examination.
Please use these midterms as a base to think seriously about your future.
Yes sir.
Alright, then I'll begin the class.
Alright! I was able to polish up the story.
Let's get to the studio and work our asses off writing names!
Saikou?
Hey.
I guess there are a lot of guys like us trying to become mangaka.
SUMMER TRAINING COURSE
This Summer is Your Chance!!
Get Ahead by
Improving
Your Basic Skills!!
-North Shirokita Prep
Maybe.
That guy, "Niizuma Eiji", was only 15, and there's Ishizawa..
I don't really know where he's going.
I don't mind going to North Yakusa High.
North Yakusa?
It might be easy for a top-scorer like you, Shuujin,
but this is the lowest level my dad will accept.
I want to set aside some time to just draw manga.
All in order to become a mangaka, huh?
I've never thought of my time as being so precious before.
I've never gotten this much into anything before.
But Saikou, are you sure you're okay going to a different high school from Azuki?
I don't know where she's going.
She might even wind up at an all-girls school.
Ask her then.
No, I'll go to a different school.
That would be more... romantic!
There it is!
The DNA of a romanticist!
GRADUATION
The next time we meet after graduating from middle school,
will be when I am a mangaka, and Azuki is a seiyuu!
Do your best
Until then, we'll just encourage one another through mail.
That's right...
Yeah.
Hey, you don't have to try so hard to imitate your uncle.
I want to.
I'm sure it's what Azuki wants too.
Saikou, are you even thinking about the possibility that Azuki might get a boyfriend in high school?
I'm not.
I trust her.
You're going to North High, even if it means being apart from Azuki?
In order to have more time to write manga?
Yeah.
Then I'll go to North High too.
Huh?!
You should go to prep school!
If we're seriously trying to become mangaka,
it would be more convenient and time efficient for us to be in the same school.
I feel the same way you do.
Besides, I was really happy to get this.
I was going to try to get into a good university,
in case this mangaka thing didn't work out.
But it wouldn't be right to assign priority to a contingency plan.
Shuujin?
So North High, it's decided.
Don't flunk the test, Saikou.
Yeah, no problem, then we can focus on manga.
We can't keep letting our peers beat us.
You're right.
So our current rival is Niizuma Eiji.
I heard something about Eiji getting assigned an editor...
and being serialized at the time of his graduation.
He already has an editor?
He definitely got one.
He got one automatically when he won the prize.
Even if he hadn't won, he could have just found an editor he was on good terms with.
That's what my uncle was saying.
An editor, huh?
It seems Eiji is getting ahead of us by leaps and bounds.
And there are good and bad editors too,
so it doesn't seem like it'll be as simple as just getting one.
It's not in our power to choose though,
so whether or not we can find a good one...
Luck, huh?
There are editors who do nothing but spew misguided criticism,
or who just slack off after picking up the manuscript.
That sucks.
Let me tell you a story I found a bit moving, about an editor.
He told a newcomer that had some work published in another magazine "your work has promise,"
"so write as much as you can and bring it here," and kept putting pressure on him to write more.
But when he finished reading through the tenth manuscript the newcomer brought him...
He fed it through a shredder?!
Why do you find that moving?
That newcomer was always getting rejected after only having the first few pages of his manuscript read.
So, he was happy that the editor had read his work to the end,
and he used the frustration of seeing his work shredded as a spring, and proceeded to become a popular artist.
I guess it becomes a good story from there.
Then, at the meeting to discuss his serialization,
"I'm sorry about that,
but I thought that you would grow more if I didn't praise you."
"Thank you so much."
Sounds like bullshit.
That editor went on to become editor-in-chief.
That sounds like a manga plot.
My uncle said most editors out there are just as passionate about manga as that.
That they all love manga.
Hey.
Yeah?
Wanna go meet an editor?
If we call 'em up and tell him we want to show him a manuscript, we could meet one.
Meet, but- We don't have a manuscript to bring yet.
Let's finish one up by the end of summer.
Then we'll bring it to "Jack."
If we're looking to get it serialized and turned into an anime,
"Jack" is our best bet, right?
If we get rejected then we'll be no worse off.
We'll see how they react after seeing our manuscript.
Let's see how far our current skills can go.
Alright, let's do it!
We'll complete our work during summer break,
and bring it to "Jack!"
If that's decided, then let's get to the studio!
Right!
Hey, look.
Azuki?
I heard she had a little sister in 5th grade,
but her sister's cute too!
This is bad, what should I do?
What's bad about it?
This is your chance to ask her for her email.
She's with that powerful mother of hers.
Would you ask her if it was one on one?
Shut up.
We'll just pass by and pretend we didn't notice them, okay?
You'd notice her.
Just do it.
Looks like Azuki noticed us too.
She's clearly blushing, and she's moved behind her mother.
I don't need you to report.
Hey Miho, aren't those your friends from class?
Hey Sis, you're blushing!
Mina!
Wow, you and Azuki are shy.
I'm surprised you can feign indifference when you're in the same classroom.
I said shut up!
Niizuma
The editor-in-chief is also showering you with praises for your work.
Of course I also think you have great talent.
So, we were wondering if you would be willing to come to Tokyo?
Niizuma-kun?
Preview of
Next Episode
Doesn't Takagi-san like you, Miho?
Huh?
I mean, wasn't he asking you about your dreams before?
That's...
What, what?
Maybe I'll tell you later.
"Maybe?!"
Summer
and Name
Next time, "Summer and Name"
A busy dream-filled summer!