[Opening]
[Eyecatch]
[Ending]
Yuueisha is a parody of Shuueisha, the company who publishes Shounen Jump.
YUUEISHA
Hello, this is Shounen Jack's editorial department.
Is this your first time submitting something?
Is that so?
Then could you give me your name and phone number?
Mashiro Moritaka-san...
Ah, a two-person team.
Takagi Akito-san.
All right.
Then, how about tomorrow?
Middle school students?
Translator
TLc
kewl0210
Chrno
Timing
Edit
KmE
bobo343
Typesetting
Karaoke
scol, KmE
Jecht, KmE, pablo212
QC
Echo_Chidori
Z4kku
Encode
pablo212
Carrot and Stick
Okay, I understand.
Thank you very much.
Tomorrow, three o'clock, at the reception desk.
"Tell them that they have an appointment with Hattori-san from Weekly Shounen Jack," they said.
All of a sudden, it's set for tomorrow. Amazing, eh?
I guess that's what you'd expect from a publisher.
So, what do we do?
I think meeting an hour beforehand is early enough.
How about one o'clock at North Yakusa Station?
Just as long as we get there.
Right.
I'm going to look through the manuscript.
Yeah, let me check the lines too.
Where's Moritaka?
He came home, didn't he?
When he does come home, he shuts himself away in his room.
I wonder if he's pushing himself too hard.
Thanks for the meal.
Mangakas sure are cool!
You have books you wrote by yourself all lined up in a row.
I'm still a gambler though.
A gambler?
A mangaka is someone who can make a living by drawing manga their whole lives.
You either need to have a big hit or a lot of smaller hits.
Beyond that, you're just a gambler.
The drawings are good, but I don't know about my story.
The story is good, but I don't know about my drawings.
Our first manga.
You're early.
You're even earlier Shuujin, why is that?
Why? Well...
Even though we worked all last night, for some reason I woke up early.
Me too.
I just, kind of, can't sit still about this.
My older brother asked me to return with next week's Jack for him.
We can't ask for something like that.
By the way, your brother goes to a good college, doesn't he?
After he failed to get into the national university, he basically stopped trying.
Now he spends all his time with club activities and going on group dates every day.
Enjoying his youth, that sort of thing.
I guess he sees what's ahead of him.
So that's why you thought of becoming a mangaka?
No, the reason why I decided not to become a salaryman was because of my parents.
My dad used to work at Oute Bank...
Dad's going to be late today as well?
Yes.
What about big brother?
He said that he has a cram school test, so he'll be late.
Acchan, so that you don't lose to your big brother,
you must study hard, okay?
Okay...
Oh yeah, how did this afternoon's test go?
My old lady was a high school teacher.
Every day she'd fervently make me and my brother study.
You're amazing, Acchan.
I'm sure you'll make your dad proud.
Actually, by watching me study,
it felt like she was trying to distract herself.
For the next one, keep it up and do your best.
Well, that's how it feels, thinking about it now.
But even so...
Why?!
So covering for your boss's responsibility means getting fired, doesn't it?
There's nothing I can do.
Nothing you can do?
Then what are we going to do?
Huh? What?
To be honest, back then I didn't really understand what was going on.
What about our kids and the mortgage we still have to pay on the house?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You went shopping, Dad?
Your mother asked me to.
Let me go with you next time.
Sure, next time.
It's a promise.
Then when I was the in fifth grade of elementary...
Avenge.
Your dad...
You've got to avenge him, okay?
Acchan...
Avenge?
Does that mean work at the bank and become a manager?
Was that why she was making me study?
When I thought that, I started to hate it.
Or rather, I just couldn't take it anymore.
Acchan...
I'm...
I'm not your tool, Mom!
I'll decide my own future!
Ever since then, they haven't had any objections about what I do.
They're good parents, really.
Ah, sorry.
I got a little melodramatic there.
Then, it was the same with you wanting to become a mangaka with me?
Yeah, they know; they're ignoring it.
What?
No, I'm glad I got to hear it.
You're smart,
but I've been a little unsure if I can rely on you when it comes to plans about the future.
Well, maybe you were right to think that.
All right, how about we get going?
Okay.
YUUEISHA
Finally, huh?
I can't believe middle school boys like us can bring in a manuscript.
YUUEISHA
It's like a dream.
As long as you just write a manuscript, they say anyone can bring one in.
The problem is how that work is judged.
Yeah.
What business do you have at the company today?
Ah, um, we came to bring in a manuscript...
Then please follow the procedure at the reception desk.
T–Thank you very much.
Welcome, how may I help you?
We came to bring in a manuscript.
Do you have an appointment?
Y–Yes, at three o'clock with Hattori-san from Weekly Shounen Jack.
In that case, please fill this out.
T–There are two of us, so shouldn't each of us fill one out?
No, it'll be fine as long as you fill in the number of people.
Uh–Uhm, I'm still a student, so what should I put for company name and such?
Well for that, just to be safe, please just put in your school's name.
Ah, I'm sorry, I made a mistake!
It's okay, I'll give you a new card.
I–I'm done.
Good job.
Please wait just a minute.
Okay, however long it takes.
She said it'd just be a minute.
This is the reception desk.
Takagi-sama and Mashiro-sama are here to see you.
Yes.
Sorry for the wait.
Hattori-san will be down very soon.
Please wait in booth number three over there.
Thanks for your time.
Thank you very much.
MEETING CORNER HOURS OF OPERATION:
MANAGEMENT
Bringing something into Jack...
MEETING CORNER HOURS OF OPERATION:
MANAGEMENT
doesn't mean we are going to the editorial department.
MEETING CORNER HOURS OF OPERATION:
MANAGEMENT
Looks like it.
I understand your enthusiasm, but...
You need to be more considerate of the readers.
Yes, Sir...
So let's just forget either of us ever saw this manuscript.
Eh?
So, think about it some more and try drawing something else.
I'll be waiting for an interesting manga next time.
T–Thank you very much...
D–Did you hear that just now?
He brought something in, like us.
Probably.
I was pretty confident on the way here, but...
I'm worried we're going to be told that what we have is shit.
It'd be scarier to be heavily praised the very first time you brought something in.
My uncle used to say that if they offered you tea, it was a success up to that point.
R–Really?
Takagi-kun and Mashiro-kun?
Ah, yes!
I'm Hattori from Weekly Shounen Jack, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you!
Well, to start with, may I see your manuscript?
Ah, okay.
Please, go ahead.
You two don't need to be so up tight.
O–Okay.
F–Finally...
He reads fast!
Let me read it one more time.
Futatsu no Chikyuu.
The Earth
we live on
is not the
real Earth.
It is all
nothing but a
duplicate made
for observation
and experiments.
The Earth we live on is not the real Earth.
It is all nothing but a duplicate made for observation and experiments.
Yes.
By "them".
Yes, by them.
Yes.
By "them".
Having been
injured in war
and returning
home, Hayato...
stepped on
the ground
of his
homeland for
the first
time in ages.
Having been injured in a war and returning home, Hayato...
stepped on the ground of his homeland for the first time in years.
But all
that waited
for him was
the "death" of
his lover, Amy.
But all that waited for him was...
the "death" of his lover, Amy.
It was a
cruel world.
It was a cruel world.
Amy!?
Pull yourself
together, Hayato.
She's dead.
Pull yourself together Hayato.
Pull yourself
together, Hayato.
She's dead.
Pull yourself
together, Hayato.
She's dead.
Pull yourself
together, Hayato.
She's dead.
Pull yourself
together, Hayato.
She's dead.
I saw her.
She was
over there!
Pull yourself
together, Hayato.
She's dead.
I saw her.
She was
over there!
Pull yourself
together, Hayato.
She's dead.
I saw her.
She was
over there!
Pull yourself
together, Hayato.
She's dead.
I saw her.
She was
over there!
Pull yourself
together, Hayato.
She's dead.
I saw her.
She was
over there!
Pull yourself
together, Hayato.
She's dead.
I saw her.
She was
over there!
I saw her.
She was over there!
Amy!
Ugh. It's
so bright...
It's so bright...
When the light that
covered his whole
body disappeared,
he was in a place
he did not recognize.
When the light that covered his body disappeared, he was in a place he did not recognize.
Where...
the hell am I...?
Where... the hell am I?
Amy!
Please wait,
Why're you
running!?
Please wait,
Amy!
Why're you
running!?
Please wait,
Amy!
Why're you
running!?
Please wait,
Amy!
Why're you
running!?
Please wait,
Amy!
Why're you
running!?
Please wait,
Amy!
Why're you
running!?
Please wait,
Amy!
Why're you
running!?
Please wait, Amy!
Why are you running?!
Please wait,
Amy!
Why're you
running!?
Welcome,
"other Hayato-kun".
Welcome, "other" Hayato-kun.
Welcome,
"other Hayato-kun".
You're
calling me
"other"......?
What are you
talking about?
Where am I?
Welcome,
"other Hayato-kun".
You're calling me "other?"
Welcome,
"other Hayato-kun".
What are you talking about?
Where am I?
Earth.
Yes.
The "Real Earth".
Earth.
Yes, the "Real Earth."
The "Other Earth"
where you clones live
is a test model
made for the sake
of the "Real Earth".
The "Other Earth", where you clones live...
is a test model made for the sake of the "Real Earth."
In order for us
"Real Earthlings"
to simulate different
problems.
In order for us "Real Earthlings" to simulate different scenarios.
No way...
Having gotten too close to the truth, Hayato was taken prisoner.
Having gotten too
close to the truth,
Hayato was taken
prisoner.
A resistance
organization
calling themselves
"Missing"
rescued people
like him.
Then,
you guys,
too?
A resistance organization calling themselves Missing rescued people like him.
Yes. We're
"Other Earthlings".
Then, you guys too?
Yes, we're "Other Earthlings."
In order for them
to send in investigators,
they take us "clones"
captive.
And when the
investigators return,
our memories are
erased and we're
sent back again.
In order for them to send in investigators, they take us clones captive.
Then when the investigators return, our memories are erased and we're sent back again.
But if the investigators get
into some sort of trouble
and end up dead,
we lose our means
of getting home and
have no choice
but to live here.
But if the investigators get into some sort of trouble and end up dead,
we lose our means of getting home and have no choice but to live here.
In this
goddamn
annoying
"utopia".
In this
goddamn
annoying
"utopia".
In this
goddamn
annoying
"utopia".
In this
goddamn
annoying
"utopia".
In this
goddamn
annoying
"utopia".
In this
goddamn
annoying
"utopia".
In this
goddamn
annoying
"utopia".
In this
goddamn
annoying
"utopia".
In this goddamn annoying utopia.
If it's a
way home you need,
I have one!
If it's a way home you need, I have one!
If it's a
way home you need,
I have one!
If it's a
way home you need,
I have one!
If it's a
way home you need,
I have one!
If it's a
way home you need,
I have one!
If it's a
way home you need,
I have one!
Having returned to
the "Other Earth",
Hayato reported
the truth
to the populace.
Now we have to
let them know
that we're their
puppets to be
manipulated!
Having returned to the "Other Earth", Hayato reported the truth to the populace.
Now, it's time to let them know that we are not their puppets to be manipulated!
And the
counter attack
of the
"Other Earthlings"
began.
Hey, hey.
Can you really
shoot me?
Your original?
Then, the counterattack of the "Other Earthlings" began.
Hey, hey.
Can you really shoot me?
Your "original"?
We're not
test subject
for your
experiments!
We are not test subject for your experiments!
Eat
this!!
Eat this!
Eat
this!!
Guh!!
I knew it...
you guys are...
I knew it, you guys are...
beasts......
beasts...
The "Real Earthlings" surrendered.
The "Real Earthlings"
surrendered. But
that was the conclusion
that they had reached
after many years of
observation.
That is, that the
Other Earthlings were
foolish savages.
But that was the conclusion that they had reached after many years of observation.
That is, that the "Other Earthlings" were foolish savages.
Amy... It's over...
It's all over.
Amy, It's over...
But you're
still
not here.
It's all over.
But you're still not here.
I won't forgive
you people.
I won't forgive you!
I'm your Amy.
Your girlfriend
that died was
an investigator.
If the investigator died,
then the "clone"
shouldn't be able
to return,
but you appeared
right in front of me.
I'm your Amy.
Your girlfriend that died was an investigator.
If the investigator died, then the clone shouldn't be able to return,
but you appeared right in front of me.
Your "original'
forgave me.
He was a kind man.
Your "original" forgave me.
But,
the one
I love
is you!
the one
I love
is you!
Ah,
I missed you,
Hayato!
the one
I love
is you!
Ah,
I missed you,
Hayato!
the one
I love
is you!
Ah,
I missed you,
Hayato!
the one
I love
is you!
Ah,
I missed you,
Hayato!
the one
I love
is you!
Ah,
I missed you,
Hayato!
the one
I love
is you!
Ah,
I missed you,
Hayato!
the one
I love
is you!
Ah,
I missed you,
Hayato!
the one
I love
is you!
Ah,
I missed you,
Hayato!
the one I love is you!
I missed you, Hayato!
While feeling an
intimate connection
with his loved one,
Hayato had some
feelings of
bitterness.
The
"genuine one"
and
"fake one"...
While feeling an intimate connection with his loved one,
Hayato had some feelings of bitterness.
The genuine one and the fake one.
"Real Earth"
and
"Other Earth"
---------------
In the end,
which one
was truly
right...?
"Real Earth" and "Other Earth."
In the end, which one was truly right?
You guys did well.
I'm getting some coffee, do you want anything?
W–We'll both have coffee too, please.
Right?
Y–Yeah.
Um, did you think up the story together?
No, I did the story and Mashiro did the drawings.
It's totally split.
I see.
Are you trying to become pros?
Yes, as soon as we can!
"Yes" would've been enough.
Well, I'll give you my opinions on the story first then, okay?
All right.
As a whole, it's a well put together sci-fi story,
and I think people who like that would be drawn into it.
Okay.
But this is more of a novel than it is a manga.
There's too much narration and the lines are very expositional too.
Unless the story progresses through the drawings and characters, there's no point in it being a manga.
We decided I wouldn't interfere in about the story, so I didn't say anything about it,
but I thought that too, a little.
But for an editor, saying something like that is a given.
As a story, it's really well made.
So maybe you would be suited to do something like a light novel?
There are hit and miss editors.
No, I definitely want to be an original author for a manga.
I wonder if we can have faith in this person?
Is that so?
And, Mashiro-kun, wasn't it?
Yes.
I think you definitely have a great ability for rough sketching.
Thank you.
But even so, this isn't manga artwork.
There are too many lines, there's no difference in lines between the characters and the background.
Put in more distortion.
You need to make the drawings your own style.
Okay.
Mashiro has only been using a pen for two months.
Two months?
Really?
Y–Yes.
If that's true, I'll really be looking forward to what you do in the future.
Do you two like this kind of story?
So you're saying that it doesn't stand out as something you'd see in Jack ?
Takagi-kun, you're the type who writes while calculating how you can become popular and sell, aren't you?
This might be just my observation, but
there are two general types you can divide successful mangaka into.
First, there are the types that put everything they have into drawing what they want and make a hit.
If you're being positive, you could say they're geniuses.
If you're speaking negatively, you might call them naturals.
Then there are ones like Takagi-kun, the type that calculates as much as they can to produce a hit.
However, the ones who make big hits are, overwhelmingly, the people who don't calculate.
Ah, sorry.  Maybe that wasn't the best way to phrase it.
I suppose what I'm saying is, those who draw with calculation have much higher hurdles to overcome.
On the other hand, the ones who can produce hits by calculating are strong.
They won't be done after just one work.
Even for us editors, those types are life-savers.
I can't force you,
but I would like for you to not bring your work to any other publishers.
If possible, I'd like to see you two later as well.
Hattori Akira
Corporation:  Yuueisha
Weekly "Shounen Jack"
Editorial Department
Hattori Akira
Corporation:  Yuueisha
Weekly "Shounen Jack"
Editorial Department
Hattori Akira
Corporation:  Yuueisha
Weekly "Shounen Jack"
Editorial Department
Hattori Akira
Corporation:  Yuueisha
Weekly "Shounen Jack"
Editorial Department
Hattori Akira
Corporation:  Yuueisha
Weekly "Shounen Jack"
Editorial Department
Hattori Akira
Corporation:  Yuueisha
Weekly "Shounen Jack"
Editorial Department
Hattori Akira
Corporation:  Yuueisha
Weekly "Shounen Jack"
Editorial Department
Hattori Akira
Corporation:  Yuueisha
Weekly "Shounen Jack"
Editorial Department
Hattori Akira
Let's do our best together in Jack.
If anything comes up, send me and e-mail at the address I wrote on there.
When I have time, I'll reply.
Don't get so excited over an email address.
When I find a golden egg, I give out my cell phone number without a second thought.
You guys are still around bronze.
Not only did he give us thorough opinions, he's being this frank with us.
Maybe it's all right to trust him.
For now I think I'm going to send this manuscript around for the monthly award, is that okay?
Monthly award?
You mean the excellence award given to one of the works submitted every month?
So, does that mean it's good?
It's not that easy.
But with manga, you get ten different opinions from ten different people.
There might even be people who say that this could get into the finals.
To be honest, even we don't know for sure what'll be a hit or not.
If we did, there wouldn't be new series that end so quickly.
A work becoming a hit is, for the most part, a gamble.
Beyond that, you're just a gambler.
Please contact me once you've got your next work done.
Until then.
It's been nice working with you!
Thank you very much.
It was a success, right?
On the first work we brought in, he gave us his business card and even his email address.
What do you think, Shuujin?
About what?
I think Hattori-san was good.
Yeah, I think so too.
Hey, how did it go?
With the middle school pair?
No good, at least not yet.
I guess not everyone can be Niizuma Eiji.
But the artist had only been using a pen for two months, it seems.
The original story author also isn't proficient yet, but his general ideas were...
Did you like them?
Yes, even if they were fourteen years old.
Also...
Two man teams sure are tough.
They're still kids, so they don't know if they'll get into a fight and split up someday.
Well, if you liked them, then make sure to raise them properly.
I think that in three years, they'll surpass Niizuma Eiji.
If you don't get a hit out in three whole years, you'll  be out of here.
Good luck.
TL note: This is a sort of voice training exercise where a sentence is said for every vowel and consonant type in the Japanese alphabet.
Water striders red. A-i-u-e-o.
( Co. ) Prince Eight
( Co.) Prince Enterprise
( Co.) Crazy Prince
( Co. ) Prince
( Co. ) Narration Performance Studio
Little shrimp swim in the floating algae.
Kaki persimmon, chestnut tree, ka-ki-ku-ke-ko.
Woodpecker clicking, dried out zelkova tree.
Put the soya bean in the sake, sa-shi-su-se-so.
Those fish bit on the shoals.
Even with summer vacation ending today.
That Saikou guy sure is hard to hang around.
Yeah, I really wanted to see that sexy movie too.
Seems he was with Takagi all break.
They even went to prep classes together, didn't they?
Maybe.
I'm going to get another story done by the end of this year.
It won't be one that he'll say should be a light novel.
I'll fix the things he pointed out and show you some awesome drawings.
Thinking about it now, in Futatsu no Chikyuu,
the "I don't know what's truly right"  theme was really more into the novel category.
I'd be better off doing a story that's a little more refreshing.
So you figured it out?
I thought so too.
You thought that?
Then say something earlier!
I promised I wasn't going to interfere with the name, right?
Then this time it's fine if you interfere,
so let's take our time and work it over until we have something we both approve of.
If it's fine with you, then all right.
You're too close!
Quiet down.
It was always like this when I was in middle school.
We'll be having this seating arrangement for the second semester.
What do I do if my stomach rumbles during class?
Preview of
Next Episode
We have got a contact address for an editor and now I'm in the seat next to Azuki.
Looks like everything's going well.
Also, our rival has started to act.
What?!
Tears
and Tears
Next time, Tears and Tears.
Tears are drops of dreams!