Original Work
Kawaguchi Tarou
Super
"Hero" - a legend
"hero" sore wa densetsu
Hero Legend
Chou Hero Densetsu
"Hero" - is cool
"hero" sore wa kakkoi
SUPER
"Hero" - lives within you
Series Organizer
Yoshida Oureiko
"hero" kimi no naka ni aru
Hot energy
atsui enaji-
If you're in trouble for some reason
Character Design
Kamiaya Toshiyuki
dou iu wake da ga dai pinchi
sonna toki koso
In times like that
Keep smiling!
waratte miro yo
Stand firm and face your enormous enemy
kyodai na aite ni tachi mukae
Art Director
Shibata Chikako
Color Design
Tanahashi Mayumi
Photographing Supervisor
Yamaishii Kazuya
Yes, now is the time to rush forth
sousa ima, hashiridasunda
(Music)
Sound Supervision
Wa Tanabejyun
minna no egao wo
Everyone's smile
Her smile
ano ko no egao wo
Infinite power builds up when you think of them
omoeba minagiru mugen no pawa-
"hero" sore ga densetsu
"Hero" - a legend
Opening Theme
"Chou Hero Densetsu"
Songwriting
Kaasui Keniiche
Arrangement
Suzuki Masaki
Song
Kageyama Hironobu
"Hero" - really cool
"hero" totemo kakkoi
"Hero" - lives within you
"hero" kimi no naka ni aru
Animation
Producer
Matsukura Yuusan
atsui enaji-
Hot energy
Production
Management
Saitou Kenji
Masa Noshima
Negishi Tomoya
Burning energy
moeru enaji-
Director
Kaasui Keniiche
Hey, Taka.
So you won another art award?
I didn't know you were coming, Uncle!
Yeah well, I didn't want to get in trouble for not visiting my folks on New Year's.
Mashiro
New Year's Gift
Here!
Thanks!
But wow.
Certificate of Honor
Second Place
Mashiro
Moritaka
You've even got a cabinet minister's name on this one.
I guess you're gonna grow up to be an artist or a designer, huh?
Uncle never said “mangaka”.
A blue bird flying through a blue sky
Can you see that bird?
Happiness is always, feeling invisible colors
I look up at a spring sky, full of nothing but worries
Translator
TLc
watchrocksgrow
kewl0210
and hang my head
but I'm looking up again
Timing
Edit
FAbian101, Chrno
Z4kku, bobo343
I decided I would find them in this town
and hold close to my chest the things I must not lose
Typesetting
Karaoke
scol, Kme
Jecht, KmE, pablo212
A blue bird flying through a blue sky
QC
Alais
Echo_Chidori
blazephantom
Can you see that bird?
Encode
cryptw
pablo212
Happiness is always, feeling invisible colors
Dream and Reality
Moritaka! Time to get up!
You'll be late for school.
Moritaka!
In the third year of middle school, the last year of compulsory education,
adults are always asking us what our dreams are for the future.
As for me, Mashiro Moritaka, I answer:
“I don't know.”
“I still haven't decided.”
It's considered normal to move onto a better high school, to the best possible university,
and then on to the best company possible.
Yeah, just live life normally.
Tanikusa City
Akehi
Middle School
That's why even though I find it easier to keep myself busy with games and computer stuff at home,
but I still go to school every day.
I don't want to cause problems for my parents.
I don't want to be called a recluse.
I don't want to be called a “permanent part-timer”.
That's why I'll take the normal route into society, and become a salaryman.
Tosho News
National Book Report Contest
Results Announced!!
Congratulations to Takagi Akito-kun!
The ones who'll jump to the top at those places
are the ones who're getting good grades now and have a high rank.
The rankings are already fixed, so the future will be nothing more than an extension of the present.
A boring future.
Life is tiresome.
That is my outlook on life, having lived these last 14 years as a good kid should.
There was something in a book I just read,
that the greatest event, the highest purpose of life, is love.
Who am I kidding?
That's some crap said by a womanizing adult.
For me, who can't even talk to the girl he likes,
love is just sad and painful.
Fruitless love...
that will cast me into the abyss once again.
Please work hard for your mid-terms tomorrow.
Thank you very much!
Saikou, let's go home.
Y–Yeah...
Saikou! Suzuki!
Let's get outta here.
Here.
Oh, thanks.
Tests start tomorrow huh?
Who cares?
We can head home early.
Well, let's just use that time well.
Yeah.
Miho.
Let's go home together.
Sure.
I'm lonely without you in my class!
Knock it off, Kaya!
Let's go have some fun!
Saikou!
Let's see...
What should we do?
Want to see a movie?
Ah! That hot one?
Yeah, that one.
Sounds good.
What about you Saikou?
I don't want to wind up in the bottom half of the ranking board.
I'm going to study.
See ya.
Saikou! He's no fun.
Huh?
My math notebook...
I can study without my notes,
but I don't want to leave them at school.
Takagi Akito...
What are you up to?
Shouldn't you be studying to protect your number one spot?
My notebook!
Did he find out I have a crush on Azuki?!
Don't make such a serious face.
This isn't the Death Note.
Why do you have your hands on my notes?
Because I sit all the way in the back.
I saw you drawing something in this notebook during class.
And I knew that you'd come back for it.
Sorry, but I took the liberty of looking inside.
I was sure you'd come back for this.
So, I was waiting for you.
What the hell is he planning?
Anyway these are good, Azuki Miho.
She's quiet, so she doesn't stand out, but she's top class for this school.
Does Takagi have a thing for her too?
I think Azuki probably has a crush on you, too.
Huh?
N–No way!
We haven't even talked yet, and first of all what makes you think that?
Didn't I explain that to you?
I sit all the way in the back.
As if you can understand everything about the class just because you sit in the back!
Well, pretty much.
But, if it were the case that the person in question did not feel that way,
I'd freely admit that my instincts have their limits.
What's up with this guy?
What's he so happy about?
Don't worry.
I'll return your notebook and I won't tell anyone your secret.
Thanks.
However!
There is one condition.
Here it comes.
What?
He'll definitely tell me to stay away from Azuki.
Work with me and become a mangaka.
I've loved manga ever since I was a kid,
and I've always dreamed of becoming a mangaka.
I've considered many others, but I need your art!
You're ranked top-class academically, even at the national level,
and you want to be a mangaka?
Is it not the desire of men to achieve greatness?
To get rich?
I have neither the looks nor the singing ability to enter the world of show business.
I have no extraordinary skill in sports.
But I have literary talent, and you can draw!
In that case, what is there but manga?
Japan's manga is already world renowned as a great culture.
Let's leave our mark on the world with manga!
You, who have won awards for your papers and compositions, will write the stories,
and I will draw.
Interesting.
Right?
But I refuse.
“But I refuse,” huh?
You too are quite the manga lover.
I can't become a mangaka.
Only that tiny fraction of people born with true talent and genius can.
Beyond that, it's just gambling.
Gambling?
When you say “mangaka,”
you're talking about someone who can make a living off of nothing but drawing manga.
Even if you get your work serialized in a weekly publication,
it'll be ranked every week through reader surveys,
and if it's not popular enough you'll be dropped after ten weeks.
If you hit it big or churn out multiple volumes of reasonably popular manga that's one thing,
but if you can't do that then you're just a gambler.
Only 0.001% of those who try actually make their fortune in manga.
That's about 1 in 100,000.
What's up with the probability theories?
Who'd you hear that from?
Whatever.
My uncle was a mangaka...
No, he was just a gambler.
That's right... was.
Your uncle was a mangaka?
You're kidding!
It's true.
Who? What's his name?
It was a long time ago, and even if I tell you...
Who is he?
His name is Kawaguchi Tarou, and he used to write in Shonen Ju—
What?!
He wrote "Chou Hero Densetsu"?!
TL Note: Chou Hero Densetsu = Super Hero Legend
I used to watch the anime when I was a kid!
I bought the manga volumes, too!
I really love his manga!
That settles it!
You have the DNA of a mangaka!
You know a lot about manga.
If there's something we want to know, we can just ask your uncle.
What DNA? He was my uncle.
My dad's little brother.
Anyway he's...
Wait.
Now that you mention it, Kawaguchi Tarou's art was horrible.
You're good.
I guess DNA has nothing to do with it.
Anyway, I'm not going to do it.
If that's your condition, then I don't need the notebook.
See you later, you thief.
Wait!
It may be a gamble,
but you'll never win the lottery if you don't buy a ticket!
If you don't make manga, then you'll never make it big!
Which way are you more likely to get the ¥300,000,000?
My uncle also used to say things like that.
Come on, let's try it!
You know, book reports and manga are completely different.
I know that.
I wrote my compositions after carefully calculating the best way to earn the approval of the judges.
Now, I just have to aim to earn the approval of publishers and readers.
Then why don't you aim for the Naoki Prize?
TL Note: The Naoki Prize is an award held semiannually for upcoming novelists.
No, right now manga makes more money, and I like it better anyway.
Feel the dream.
Then why don't you draw the art yourself?
They have classes for people trying to make original work.
You could apply for one.
What?
Are you trying to get a job as a public servant
or an employee in a stable company or something?
No, I don't know about my future...
Then why would you refuse?
Why?
Now that you mention it, I'm not really sure myself.
I guess... it's too much trouble.
Well, I'm going home to study now.
Thanks for the notebook.
You're just going to coast through life like that!
That's all you want out of life?!
People like you, who are already working towards their dreams in their third year, are more unusual.
It's best to start early!
Everyone else just can't decide what they want and they go through life dragging their feet!
You and I, we can definitely do it!
You're persistent.
I hear you.
I'll go home and think about it.
Really?
But I think the answer's going to be, “No.”
That's okay.
Just think it over carefully!
If your answer's still “no”, then I'll give up.
I wanted to become a mangaka when I was in elementary school.
Hey, why did you become a mangaka, Uncle?
I'm still just a gambler.
I see.
Then why did you become a gambler?
I wanted to become popular with girls.
Mangaka are popular with girls?
I thought that if I became famous and rich, that would make me popular, I suppose.
Don't tell anyone.
When I was in middle school, there was this girl I liked.
I graduated, having barely spoken with her.
What a short story!
But on the day of graduation, I received a letter from that girl.
A love letter! Great!
No, all she wrote was stuff like, “Let's both do our best from now on.”
So, I wrote her a reply saying, “Yes, let's both work hard.”
We went to different high schools,
so we just exchanged letters like those without even seeing one another.
Huh, that's actually kinda nice.
But you know, after graduating high school she got into a top corporation.
I went to a fourth-rate college.
I had gotten it into my head that I wanted to marry her, so I thought to myself,
“Things can't keep going like this,”
“I want to do something to earn her approval.”
That's what I was thinking when—
You became a mangaka!
But she became the president's secretary,
and I was a beginner mangaka with doubtful prospects.
I felt like the gap between us was growing day by day.
Chou Hero Densetsu
TV Anime On the Air
Finally, when "Chou Hero Densetsu" became an anime,
You confessed, right?
She married someone else.
Aww...
I may have lost the gamble for her love,
but she was the reason I was able to try so hard.
But two years later...
Please take care of the rest.
Thank you so much for everything.
But it really was sudden, wasn't it?
I wonder what could have caused it.
It seems he was under a lot of stress...
But he wasn't even all that busy lately.
I heard he had a lot of debts. Also—
Thank you for coming today.
I'm sure Nobuhiro appreciates it as well.
O–Oh... I'm glad to hear it.
In the seven years after "Chou hero Densetsu", my uncle wrote two more series,
but they were quickly canceled.
They told me he died of overwork, but I thought he committed suicide.
Even if I had a dream, there was nothing I could do.
If it just won't come to pass, then I might as well live like everyone else...
Moritaka?
What?
What's wrong with you?
Just when I think you're home, you go out again.
What are you doing?
Don't you have a test tomorrow?
You'll never get into Minami High with that kind of attitude!
What the hell.
Every single person is just saying whatever the hell they want.
Leave my future...
the hell alone!
Ah, it's me, Takagi.
Takagi? How did you get this number?
I got it from Suzuki.
Which means...
More importantly, I'm going to Azuki's house now to confess to her,
and I want you to come.
But you know I like her, so why—
If you don't come, there's no point!
Hurry up and come!
What the hell!
I'm telling you I don't understand you.
Can't you confess on your own?
I won't do anything bad.
I love your art, and I like you!
Are you okay?
You're confessing to the wrong person.
Anyway, I looked a bit into Azuki and I found out something amazing!
Why do I have to attend your confession?!
Don't worry about that, just get here quickly!
I'm at the convenience store in Nishi-chou!
Hey!
I was waiting, Saikou!
It's not “Saikou,” it's “Moritaka.”
Alright, let's go!
It's right over there.
H–Hey!
Nice house, huh?
A house fit for a madonna.
Indeed.
H–Here I go.
Have you ever even pressed the doorbell of a girl's house before?
Have you?
If you have then push it for me!
No, don't want to.
It's your confession after all.
Then keep quiet.
Here goes...
He pushed it!
I'm going home!
Are you trying to play doorbell dash with me, you bastard?!
Yes?
U–Um, this is Takagi. I'm in the same class as Miho.
There was something I wanted to ask Miho about tomorrow's test.
He messed up.
Takagi-kun?
The top student for the year?
No, ah... yes.
Wow, she knows his name.
Please wait a moment.
Ah, sure.
I think she's kinda suspicious of you.
Hello.
Ahh, Azuki's voice! Aw, man!
Um...
Azuki-san!
This is Takagi.
Could you step outside for a moment?
I have something very important to talk to you about.
Wait a moment.
Ahh, she's going to come out?
I wonder what her casual clothes are like!
Hey! Let her know that I'm here too!
S–Sorry!
I'm about to blow a fuse here!
I thought so.
Azuki-san!
Yes?
I... am going to become a mangaka!
I came to confess that to you!
This is what he meant by “confess”?!
I heard from your friend, Miyoshi-san.
Azuki-san, you're trying to become a voice actor, right?
Voice actor?
Yeah.
“Yeah”? Seriously?!
You even took some voice recordings you recorded yourself to a production office, right?
What is this, a fantasy? Could she really be...
You're really doing your best.
And they said you were really good, right?
Is Azuki going to become a voice actor?
Then, next, a word from Mashiro.
What...?
Say what?
What should I say?
I–I'm going to be drawing the art, and he's doing the stories.
I knew it!
Wow! Then I'm sure you'll make it!
Her eyes are shining! Her eyes are all sparkly!
How pretty!
S–So if our manga gets turned into an anime,
then we'll reserve the role of heroine for you or something...
Really?
I'm so happy!
I'll work hard.
I'll become a voice actor and appear on your anime.
How great!
Wow, what a smile!
Looking at me, and so close.
You're so cute, Azuki!
When I was in middle school there was this girl I liked.
I wanted to marry her...
So if that dream comes true, please marry me!
What the hell did you just say?!
Yeah, what the hell was that?
I was remembering what my uncle said...
Oh no, this is so embarrassing!
Mashiro-kun...
Yes!
I'm sorry!
I'm not sure what to say but just now, that...
I understand.
I promise.
Huh? Promise what?
You can't mean the marriage...
Yes.
But only if the dream comes true.
Until then I won't see you again.
Ah, um... The manga becomes an anime, and you do the voice work,
then we suddenly get married without so much as seeing each other once?
Yep. Until the dream comes true we have to work with no distractions.
Until then we'll just encourage one another through mail or something.
Is that bad?
No! That's fine! Please!
Ah, mom is coming! Bye.
So this is what it's like.
I understand, I understand, uncle!
So this is what it was like for the two of you.
But I promised to get married if my dream comes true.
Aren't the terms of the bet better for me?
I will become a mangaka.
Woah! This is even better than I planned!
Let's become Japan's top mangakas!
No, aiming for the top is meaningless.
In this rapidly aging society, it will be impossible to overtake the likes of Dragon Ball and One Piece!
That's a logical analysis.
Also, I haven't decided whether to join you or not.
Books
I'll do it.
I'll definitely become a mangaka!
Then I'll marry Azuki!
KING OF
MANGA
Anyone Can Draw
Introductory Level
Mako-chan and Rabi-kun's
Drawing Course
Preview of
Next Episode
I'll become a mangaka!
We will, right?
But I'm sure my father and grandfather will be against it.
Huh, seriously?
The dream is over?!
Idiocy and
Intelligence
Next time: “Idiocy and Intelligence”
Who will be the one to capture his dream?