Takahashi.
I'll say this once, so listen carefully.
I love you.
No way...
Takahashi...
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 5 ...
We kissed...
It was with boy I've liked since spring...
...and I had confessed to him once before, but...
...I didn't really understand the response I got...
...and I thought that it was all over for us.
Yet...
I love you.
As if it were a miracle...
...I saw the entire world change before my eyes.
Yano cast a spell on me.
Morning!
Good morning!
Morning.
I didn't get a wink of sleep.
Nana, is your face puffy?
What am I gonna do about my face?
Until yesterday...
...he was a really annoying, loud-mouth classmate...
...but because of what happened, I was up all night...
...wondering how to face him today.
Morning.
G-Good morning.
Hey, morning.
That thing went pretty well the other day, don't you think?
It's... it's no good...
I might not be able to look him straight in the face anymore...
Or so I thought...
Hey, take a look at this. Looks cool, right?
...but he's the same as always.
That's pretty awesome.
Mizu-chin.
You. Is it true that you and Yano kissed?
What? When did...?!
I won't forgive you! Spill the beans!
No way... we were seen.
So, what's going on now? Are you two gonna go out?
Huh? Oh, I see...
Sorry, but you'd better not come to me with your love problems anymore!
Though I'll definitely support you when you're breaking up, so come to me for that!
We'll be dating, won't we?
Yano hasn't said anything to me yet...
And I haven't gotten any text messages...
But he never sent me any text messages before, either.
He's slowly starting to get on my nerves.
Here he comes!
Takahashi.
Y-Y-Y-Yes?!
Umm... they said that thing will be on Saturday.
Ah... okay.
I see...
You okay? You seem a little out of it today.
I-It's because I couldn't get to sleep last night!
Crap!
Um, I mean...
I'm such a moron for not being able to fall asleep over a kiss!
And what was he talking about? He's reminding me about upcoming events?
Repeat after me, then.
Today, a student council meeting at three.
Thursday, a student council event review meeting.
Saturday, the event.
Today, a student council meeting at three.
Tuesday--
Thursday.
Thursday, the event review meeting.
Today, a student council meeting at three. Lunch at twelve.
Saturday, the event.
Thursday, the event.
Moron. Saturday, the event. Today, a movie at four.
Geez... what's up with him?
Today, the student council meeting.
Thursday, the event review meeting.
Saturday, the event!
Today, a movie at four!
Correct! Good job.
Today, a m-movie at four?
A movie... at four?
Ah, geez!
My heart hasn't stopped pounding since this morning...
...yet how can you say that stuff so easily?
Don't give me that cute smile!
Now that I feel so relieved, my sleepiness has caught up with me...
Yano finally smiled at me today.
It means it wasn't a fake.
I wasn't taking it the wrong way.
What happened yesterday really did...
Geez, she's still sleeping!
Didn't she sleep at all last night?
Nana! The student council meeting's at three!
A date... a date...
Sign: A date... a date...
What am I gonna do...?
I'm so nervous...
Huh? It's already this late...
Ah, the student council meeting...
Shoot... it's long over...
No way... no way!
Ya--
He lef--
You're finally up.
Y-You're still here?
What do you mean?
I went to the student council meeting in your place.
I took notes for you, too.
And here are the handouts.
You need to take survey during homeroom, and this is to be submitted next week.
What?
You went in my place?
That's what I've been saying.
I... I can't believe it...
Yano, a guy who finds everything a pain and skips out all the time, did this?
Can you make it to the movie?
Ah, wait one sec.
After watching the movie and getting something to drink, I wonder if we'll go out to eat, too...
And I can't forget bus fare, either...
Don't worry about that. I'll pay.
I'll pay you back!
I'll pay you back tomorrow, okay?
You don't have to.
No, I will.
Here's an open seat.
Go on, take it.
Actually, I think I'll stand.
It's gonna get more crowded, you know.
I-It's okay.
What?
Nothing.
I feel like I'm wearing myself out...
I need to act natural... natural...
What do you want to drink?
U-Umm... h-hot chocolate.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Looks like there are a lot of open seats.
Ah! I should've asked for a milk tea....
Ahh... I'm pushing myself too hard again... I need to act natural! Natural!
I didn't know you liked movies, Yano.
Ah, yeah.
Especially because it's so dark, if you know what I mean!
You don't get it, do you?
Mind if I rest my arm here?
Ah, sure.
Takahashi, you can also rest your arm here if you need to.
Ah, yeah.
Where...?
The seat next to me...
...is a lot closer than I thought.
The movie was about a woman who kept passing by the one she loved without realizing it...
Ah! There they go again!
Hurry and let them meet each other!
They were finally able to meet again...
Finger exercises.
No... it's nothing.
He... kept half of the armrest free the entire time...
And that's when I thought...
...that having mutual feelings for each other is great.
Mizu-chin's
&
Taka-chan's
"We were
there too!"
Mizu-chin's...
...and Taka-chan's...
"We Were There Too!"
Mizuguchi
Nagami
Cutesy girl
Hi there! I'm Mizuguchi!
And I'm Nagami!
Moving straight to our topic of the day...
Yes, yes?
What's up with Nanami kissing him?!
Yeah, I was really surprised!
It makes me want to cry!
In the first place, when... when did Nanami fall for Yano, anyway?!
Now, now, calm down, Mizu-chin.
I'll never listen to her love problems ever again!
But we can't just leave Nanami alone, can we?
Yeah...
But...!
But I can't forgive her!
And so...
Please enjoy the second half of the show!
That movie was really good, huh?
You think so?
Yeah! The ending was really moving!
What scenes did you like, Yano?
Me?
I...
...liked the part where we held hands.
I wonder if it's because I got so whirled up today...
Yano just seems different than normal.
They way he speaks, and his behavior... The intonation in his voice.
They're all different than normal.
Are you sleepy?
Not at all.
I'd feel bad if I made you go out of your way today.
Let's go home after we finish eating.
Yano.
Why are you being so kind?
What do you mean?
Why?
I'm a kind person, under everything.
T-That's not what I meant.
It's just so strange.
Up until the other day, you were mean to me all the time...
So why did you suddenly become such different person?
Before you told me you loved me, did you not love me?
You're the one who's changed.
Obviously, my girlfriend isn't the same as my other classmates.
To me, you're the one who's become different from before.
T-That's...
His girlfriend...
What does he mean?
This basically means that you're an insider in my circle.
An insider?
Yeah. Everyone else is split into insiders and outsiders, right?
What do you mean? That's weird.
Is it really that strange?
What am I gonna do...?
Right now, I...
...really want to hold Yano tightly.
I've never been with anyone special for this event before...
...but this year, it's different!
But the problem here is that Yano has a better sense for this sort of stuff than me...
I have to be careful so he doesn't say something like "laaame" to what I get him.
This'll be tough...
I wonder what sort of things make boys happy?
W-What?
Nothing.
Even though he doesn't have anything to say, Yano unexpectedly comes really close sometimes.
But only when no one's around.
He's just like a cat.
Ah, Yano.
Is there anything you want for Christmas?
Nana-chan!
I'd like you to answer seriously.
He was
fairly serious
Worcester sauce!
Oh, it's Yano.
Soy sauce tastes best with it!
No, it's definitely Worcester sauce!
And just when I thought they weren't getting along.
It's definitely soy sauce!
Worcester sauce!
Soy sauce!
I keep telling you, it's all about the soy sauce!
Hey.
Ah, Takeuchi-kun.
Long time no see.
I'm going to the bathroom.
What were you two arguing about?
Huh? Oh, which is better on sunny-side up eggs, soy sauce or Worcester sauce.
We must seem like stupid love birds...
Not at all.
I'm glad, though.
It's soy sauce!
No matter what anyone says, soy sauce will remain on top!
He sure shows off...
It's deja vu...
Geez... I didn't think you could be such a doofus.
You're unexpectedly childish, aren't you?
Let's go get some pizza.
Geez, how do you have so much money?
You don't even have a part-time job.
My parents give me whatever I ask for.
That must be nice.
My parents are really stingy, and they won't even give me allowance.
I bum money off them by doing the whole filial piety thing.
Let's hold hands.
Yano's hand is warm.
That's why... whenever I touch it, my heart lets out a small squeal of joy.
Why's your hand so cold?
Girls are more sensitive to the cold.
Yano, what do you want for your present?
Ah, and this time, excluding living things.
I don't really need anything.
Don't say that.
Yano must've realized that I only have a small allowance...
He's really watching out for me...
But... I want to give him something.
Just as long as you're there, Takahashi.
Ah, gross!
W-What?
Sorry. It was just so embarrassing to say.
Ah... there's such bad taste in my mouth now!
Yeah, yeah...
Moron...
Winter came quickly this year.
Girls Restroom
But my heart is warm and cozy!
Just kidding.
And I kinda feel like I've become prettier!
Could it be because of love?
You serious? Talk about bad taste in girls!
So ugly.
She's so ugly, so why did he...?
It's so annoying.
Really... young girls these days.
They're just jealous, so don't take it to heart.
What?! They were talking about me? "Ugly" and all?
I guess I'm now in a position where people are jealous of me...
I'm sure...
...there are a lot of other girls who cried, too.
So, what do you want for your Christmas present?
I don't need anything.
Yano likes the snow.
Hey, am I ugly?
Ugly girls are more... impressive with their looks, to put it a certain way.
Then, am I beautiful?
Beautiful girls are more...
Never mind.
Honest bastard.
What did you find attractive about me, Yano?
You're cute, Takahashi.
Why do I sometimes get anxious like this?
Takahashi.
Let me borrow your hands.
When Yano touches me with his warm hands, my heart clenches up...
I've decided on what I want for a Christmas present.
Give me a promise.
Promise me that you'll never leave my side.
That you'll never...
That you'll never ever betray me.
Yamamoto Nana
Speaking honestly for a second...
I don't know.
I thought I'd never be able to go out with anyone again.
Do you really, really like someone like me?
Is it funny?
Over something small like that...
"Something small like that..."
She...
...died together with the guy she loved.
I won't ever feel sympathy for her.
It's as if...
...the puzzle...
...was slowly falling into place...
...piece by piece.
Koko ni ite itsudemo
Be here... always...
Koko ni ite watashi wo
Be here... look...
Koko ni ite miteite
Be here... at me...
Someone beloved to me...
Kono mama zutto
Just like this, forever...
I first learned what that meant... during the winter when I was fifteen years old.
Te no hira no naka
The "first time" you gave me
afuredashisou na
seems like it's going
Anata ga kureta "hajimete"
to overflow in the palm of my hand.
Watashi hitori ja kokoro ga yuretara
If my heart wavered alone
Minna koborete shimau
it seems like everyone would vanish.
Anata no ookina te de
On that day, you
Watashi goto tsukamaeteite
took hold of me
Konna ni mo konna ni mo
even though, even though
Tayorinai watashi no koto wo
I'm so unreliable.
Dakedo ima wa anata no te wa
But you still stretched out your
sukoshi tookute
arm and hand to me, just a little bit.
Koko ni ite yasashiku
Be here... with that...
Be here... gentle hand...
Koko ni ite anata no
Koko ni ite sono te de
Be here... of yours...
Tsutsundeite ne
and embrace me.
Itsumo hitori de aruiteru michi ha
The path I always walk alone
Hirosugite samishii dake
is too wide, and only makes me lonely.
Episode 6 Preview ...
Yano embraces me.
Futari de arukeba shiawasena kimochi
If we walked together, I'd be filled
Yano's hands touch my back.
And... Yano's hands on my chest...
Sore dake de ippai yo
with happiness, and that'd be just fine.
Wait just a second!
You won't let me?
Obviously not!
She threw you out.
Anata ga egao dattara
If you're smiling,
You sisters, both older
and younger, are the worst.
Don't... group me with her...
Watashi mo onaji de itai
I want to be smiling too.