The culture festival is finally drawing near...
...so our days have been filled with nothing but preparations.
Yano, where are you?
Hey, have you seen Yano?
Ah, Yano? I think he's around here somewhere, so I'll take a look.
Are you sure that's really all right?
Yeah.
One thing I'm especially good at...
That's amazing.
Really?
...is finding Yano, whenever or wherever he may be.
Yano.
Because he's the one I love.
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 4 ...
He's the one I love.
But...
Do you have your lines down pat?
Yeah, I guess.
Is it just my imagination, or has he seemed distant lately?
He's been like this ever since the day we had those steamed meat buns...
Oh, Yano.
What's up?
You see...
A happy dream?
Yeah.
What's happiness...?
I wonder what it is?
That's a tough one.
Umm...
Uhh...
Ah! Something warm.
Something warm?
Yeah! Like a steamed meat bun or a roasted sweet potato.
Something that warms you up on a cold day.
Something that soothes your heart.
A steamed meat bun, huh?
Well, it can be anything, like a book you like or a CD.
Or someone you like.
Let's go get some steamed meat buns.
Nana, that ring's really cute.
Huh? Ah, this?
Yeah! It's adorable!
Thanks.
It's glass, though.
Who did you force into buying that for you? Really!
I bought it myself.
Buying a ring for yourself... is pretty sad, isn't it?
Yeah.
Really?
Ah, sorry!
Geez! I can't believe this!
It's running. What are we gonna do about this?
Ah... that really sucks.
That'll have to be completely redrawn.
You're so mean.
After it was looking so good, too...
We're out of time now. What are we gonna do?
We're going to have to buy new paper.
Unless we have any leftover...
Should I help out?
Huh? You don't mind?
Nope. I'm free right now, and it's just some painting, right?
Thanks a ton!
Yano's pretty nice.
How unusual...
Yamamoto-san, could you get a brush for Yano?
You're always slacking off, and you only pretend to be helpful at times like these.
You're pretty good at that, aren't you?
I... I don't think so.
After all, since he's the lead in the play, he must be having the toughest time.
It's true that he's skipped a lot of rehearsals, but he also memorizes his lines quickly...
...so he's getting done what needs to be done.
Takahashi-san, you're too easy on Yano.
This is kind of weird, don't you think?
Whenever anyone says anything to Yano...
...he avoids the question or shuts them up. It's always one or the other.
But when Yamamoto-san said that stuff to him, he didn't respond at all.
Isn't that weird?
Do you think it could be because of that?
She's Nana-san's little sister.
There's history between them.
Nana-san...
...was the girl Yano was going out with in middle school.
But last year, she died in a car accident.
That's what I don't get!
What's the big deal? She's just the little sister!
It's not like it was Yano's fault her older sister died.
He should be the one blaming other people!
Not only did she betray him, but then she went and died!
Really, Yano should be the one holding a grudge, not Yamamoto-san!
Anger
Now, now. Mizu-chan, calm down.
I wonder if I'm really that soft with Yano...
Huh? Don't you act the same as anyone else?
Yamamoto-san's the one who's a little weird. Definitely.
Yamamoto-san... might have liked Yano.
Ah, I could see that!
And she resents him for turning her down.
I... don't think Yamamoto-san's like that.
Ah... maybe. She doesn't seem that simple.
I'm not a big fan of her myself, but I do think she's a pretty reasonable person.
That's why I think Yano always restrains himself around Yamamoto-san.
It's like he has some hidden reason he feels guilty about.
Yano.
Sorry about earlier.
Huh? For what?
You seemed like you couldn't really respond to Yamamoto-san, so I...
Ah, I really didn't care.
Take!
You heading home?
Yeah, in a bit.
Let's stop by the plaza on the way.
There's a long-sleeved T-shirt I really wanna get.
How many T-shirts do you need before you're satisfied?
Well, excuse me for buying so many.
You're so bizarre.
That I am.
Ah, Takahashi.
Yes?
You don't have to be so protective of me like before. It's unnecessary.
I... I guess.
But I really thought you were doing your best...
And I'm telling you, you don't need to say that sort of stuff.
I... I guess you're right...
I'm sorry I stuck my nose into your business.
Sorry.
Let's go.
Why are you so mean to her?
I don't think I am... I'm just being me.
Then, why don't you try being kinder?
Why do I have to?
You're weird.
Whenever she's around I can't concentrate.
Did you say something just now?
Never mind.
Recommended by the Ministry
of Education?
The Peak
of Hope
Class 1-7
Calligraphy
by Me
My name is Kohsaka, and I'm in charge of producing this class's short play.
"The Peak of Hope".
This story is a masterpiece that will make anyone and everyone cry.
And with the culture festival right before our eyes, the rehearsals should be coming to a close.
After all, the real thing's happening the day after tomorrow.
"Don't you think we've had enough rehearsals?"
"Let's hurry and get the real thing over with!"
...are some of the things I should be hearing in these final preparations.
BUT
But!
It's actually nothing like that right now!
And that's because...!
Yano-kun, you skipped too many rehearsals.
This isn't a laughing matter.
All right. Let's do this, Yano!
Yeah, yeah.
Will Yano really be all right?
It doesn't look like he has a drop of motivation in him.
Didn't someone say he always gets things done when they need to get done?
We have no choice but to put our faith in that, huh, Nana?
Y-Yeah...
I won't say anything... I won't say anything unnecessary.
Okay! Starting from the scene on page 25!
Drawing your sword on someone holding a mere hoe... I can see how the mighty warriors have fallen.
I can't say anything untoward, but drop your weapon, and do as I say.
Otherwise, I cannot guarantee your life.
Cut!
What's with that reading?!
Put more feeling into it! Feeling!
Umm... I don't really want to ask, but don't you have your lines memorized?
Well, there are so many long scenes.
The real thing's the day after tomorrow!
Get someone to hold up cue cards during the real thing.
That's impossible!
It is?
Memorize your lines!
He doesn't take care of things when they need to get done at all...
Will we really be all right in time for the actual show?
Nana, say something to him.
You're the class president, right?
B-But that and this don't really have much to do with each other.
And I'm busy enough with my own role...
Yano, please! It's the day after tomorrow!
By the day after tomorrow, cram as many lines as you can into your head!
I'll be sure to have it perfect. Perfect, perfect.
I'm being serious here!
Ah... my stomach's starting to hurt.
Hey, how do you read this?
Mount Kyokurin? Mount Kokurin?
You're still only at that low level?
He turned away from me...
You don't have to be so protective of me like before. It's unnecessary.
Let's go get some steamed meat buns.
Nana-chan.
Y-Yes?
Let me borrow your chest.
I don't understand...
I don't...
...understand Yano.
I don't understand...
I just don't understand.
I wonder if we won't...
...be able to talk like we did before...
Today, I heard a strange tale from a monk travelling the countryside.
He spoke of a golden lichen growing upon the peak of Mount Kyokurin...
...so holy that if one were to sow it elsewhere...
...it would transform a wasteland into a land of abundant harvest...
...and all quarrels between people would vanish, and peace would flourish everywhere.
And because of this, people have called that peak upon Mount Kyokurin the "Peak of Hope".
Yano can really be amazing at times...
Yano, that was wonderful! Your acting was spectacular!
Don't cry over it.
Thank you! Thank you!
You're amazing... I want to tell Yano that he's amazing...
But...
I should be memorizing my lines right now! I have to get all three down! All three!
Nana...
I see you're still as easy as ever...
School Festival
There's a huge crowd!
Yano's fame really is incredible!
I hope this goes off well, Nana.
She's still reading the script...
Sir Samurai, please calm down.
Book: The Peak of Hope
Where is Yano, anyway?
Ah, he's changing right now.
He's always doing things last minute...
I'm not sure whether to call it airheadedness or what...
Even though I'm just Village Girl #2 and I only have three lines...
...I wish he'd share some of his courage... sheesh.
Ah, Yano!
I... won't say anything.
Why are there so many people here?
What do you mean? They're all here to see you!
Now, Yano-kun, we're counting on you today.
What was my first line again...?
Crap... I might've forgotten all my lines.
F-First, calm down!
Take deep breaths! Deep breaths!
Just picture yourself doing it correctly!
Have some water!
The script, the script!
He doesn't have to read it! Yano will do just fine!
Right, Yano?
Yeah.
All right!
Okay, you're almost up.
Yeah! You're on standby!
Yano-kun, go for it.
I said something unnecessary again...
Br...
Break a leg.
Umm... there's something on that mountain over there. Er, what was it called again?
D-Do you mean Mount Kyokurin?
Ah, yeah! That one, that one.
It's supposed to have this so-called... Umm... what was it again?
The something-or-other peak.
It's the Peak of Hope!
They like it...
Amazing...
Even though all of his lines are random...
The audience hasn't realized.
He has such a way with words...
And that complete lack of stage fright...
He's strong in these serious events.
It's such a pain, though...
P-Please! We beg of you!
You don't have to be so protective of me like before.
I was actually really happy.
...was the mistake you're making it out to be.
I don't know which is the real Yano...
You're up.
You're
up.
Sir Samurai, please calm down!
I guess I will! If I were as out of hand as you, I'd fall over!
Or could it be that they're all the real him?
All right! All right!
It was a huge success, huh?
Sign: Swordfish
But anyway, this is really heavy!
So this is how it ends, huh?
Nothing really happened...
Coming through!
Ah, watch out.
What's the matter, Nana?
The top of my ring came off!
Ah, the one you bought for yourself?
Nana, just give up on it.
It'll be impossible to find.
I liked it, too...
Ow.
What are you do--
Weird ring.
He surprised me...
Die, you jerk.
A person shouldn't go around telling people to "die" all the time.
Why's that?
If I were to actually die tomorrow in a car accident or something...
...you'd feel bad, even though it wouldn't have been your fault, right?
As if something convenient like that would--
Did you tell her that...?
I'm not you.
So I don't say things like that!
I'm different from the savage Takahashi!
W-W-W-Wait a sec!
In the first place, saying "die" is so boringly simple.
Boringly simple?
Okay. Then how about, "I'll kill you, bitch"?
Takahashi's of low character!
Before I knew it, we were speaking normally...
Don't you think dying's such an easy way out?
Then, what would you do?
First, I'd break a person's fingers one by one...
...then pull each of his nails...
You don't have to keep going...
Let's just agree that you're a sadist.
That's not what I meant, anyway.
It's not that...
It's just that when you die, you don't feel anything or know what happened.
Isn't that too boring?
Umm...
It always feels like I'm about to understand him, but then he gets away...
Love confession time!
I hear that during things like this, couples step forward and dance cheek-to-cheek!
Oh, stop it!
I wonder if someone's confessing to Yano right now...
I'm especially good at...
Could you imagine if someone confessed to you?
Where are you?
Takahashi.
I'll give you something nice.
Ah, whoops. Wrong thing.
It's yours, right?
Let me fix it for you.
Even if the ring's weird, I still feel kinda bad for it.
He's so cute...
Hold out your right hand.
It won't fit!
You've put on weight, haven't you?
It doesn't go on my thumb!
Then, on this finger.
It's like we're exchanging wedding rings...
The words they say at weddings sure are nice, huh?
"Do you take this woman to be your wife, and vow to love her forever?"
I do!
Are we getting married out here?
I-It just slipped out.
Don't laugh, moron.
B-But words aren't good enough!
If I were in that situation, I'd probably say something like this...
Please break my fingers.
What are you saying?
You're crazy. Crazy!
Takahashi.
I'll only say this once, so listen carefully.
I love you.
No way...
Takahashi...
Jama da te wo futta ushirosugata anna ni mou
Everyone's in the way. I waved my hand, but your back is
Yuugure no hitonami ni yurenagara chiisaku naru
already swerving through the crowd of people and sinking into the evening sun.
Anata ga kureta kotoba wo hitotsuzutsu
I closed my eyes and began to remember
Far in the distance, I heard the sound of fireworks...
Omoidashi me wo tojita Shiawasena omoi dake
the words you told me. Only happy memories
koko ni aru hazu nano ni Fuan ni naru
are supposed to be there, but I become anxious.
doushite nano kokoro ga furueteru no
Why does my heart waver so?
Tsutaetai motto sou afureteru kono kimochi
I want to tell you about my overflowing feelings...
Suki dakara suki dakara zettai suki dakara
"I love you, I love you, I love you more than anything."
Furimuite kakedashite oikakete ikitai kedo
I want to turn around, run after you, catch up with you, but
Yuugure no sabishisa ga sonna yuuki nomikonda
the sadness of the twilit sky swallowed my courage.
Anata no egao no naka ni watashi ha iru
I'm in your smile.
Sukoshi hanareta dakede
Even a short time after we've parted
Episode 5 Preview . . .
We kissed.
Mayoigo ni natta youna
I want to cry out like a
As if it were a miracle...
...I saw the whole world
change before my own eyes.
kodomo mitai nakidashisou
lost child.
Yano cast a spell on me.
Ah, Yano.
Is there anything
you want for Christmas?
Sunao nara konna omoi
If only I could be honest with myself,
Nana-chan!
Give me a serious answer.
shinakutemo sumu no ni na
I wouldn't have had to go through this.
I've decided on what
I want for a Christmas present.
Give me a promise.
Karappo...
Only...