I have a copy of this, too.
So Yamamoto-san also reads poetry books...
Nana, hurry up and give it!
Ah, yeah!
Nana!
Yes?!
Are you waiting for someone?
A-Ah, nope...
Then let's hurry up and go already.
The lunch counter's gonna get crowded.
Y-Yeah.
I guess you're right.
What am I gonna do...?
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 10 ...
I'm sure Yamamoto-san's upset, since she lost the picture...
I have to get it back to her.
But I can't find the right time to talk to her...
And...
What? You also had a copy of it?
I don't understand...
...why Yamamoto-san had a picture of Yano.
Ah... someone just went to throw the trash in the incinerator.
Were you looking for something?
No...
You serious?
Hey, listen to this! You won't believe what he did!
Come on, shut up!
Just spill it!
Nana-chan.
Let me see your English homework.
Again? You need to do it yourself sometimes, you know.
Please?
Sheesh.
All right. Thanks a lot.
Ah, I'm... getting jealous again...
...because of that picture.
Nana-chan, is something bugging you?
It's like you haven't been able to relax all day.
N-Not really.
I guess that's fine, then.
But remember, no secrets between us.
That's not fair... with just one smile, I'll let you do whatever you want.
Go ahead and take my homework.
You're gonna be called on today, right?
Really? Yay!
That's why I want him all to myself...
Oh, now I get it!
That picture... wasn't of Yano. It was picture of Yamamoto-san's sister!
I see! It all connects now!
It makes sense for Yamamoto-san to have it.
Huh?
Did you do the English assignment?
I've got it down pat.
Oh, no!
Let me see it?
My English notebook!
No.
Nana-chan's notebook is only for me.
That's... mine.
Give it back.
Is this some sort of harassment?!
Yano.
U-Umm...
In my notebook before...
Umm...
W-Was there maybe.. a picture in it?
A picture of what?
Ah... never mind. If you didn't see it, don't worry about it.
I gave it back.
I gave it back to Yamamoto.
Ah... I see...
Umm... did Yamamoto-san say anything about it...?
Not a word.
Umm, nothing like "where'd you find it" or anything?
Nothing like that.
Ah... I see...
He's...
...mad.
Yano...
Nana-chan... why'd you have that?
He's really mad at me...
Snooping around in other people's things is pretty awful, don't you think?
Nanairo no niji ga koi no yukue shitteru no
The seven-colored rainbow knows where our love is headed.
Kiseki wa meguru to miageta yozora wa
As the seasons turn, the night sky I gaze up at
Let me see your textbook.
Why are you working ten pages ahead?
There's nothing else to do at home.
Kakomare maboshi kumo no ue de odoru
surrounds me, and illusions dance above the clouds.
There's nothing else to do, so you study?
You sure are different.
Ikibasho wo sagashita tameiki ga irodzuku
I tried to find where it led, but it only colored my sighs.
Ushinau sono mae ni furete hashiri
I need to reach out and touch it before it fades away.
Anata wa tenohira nukumori de
The palm of your hand is filled with warmth.
Hanasanaide mou sukoshi dake kowaresou yo
Don't let go just yet. Everything seems about to fall apart.
Kokoro yurete namida tte ochiru
As my heart wavers, tears fall from my eyes.
Anata no kao wa shizuka ni
Your face in my mind
If you hate me that much, we shouldn't have even gotten to know each other to begin with.
Kirakira ni terasou
twinkles brightly and silently.
You only used me to get revenge on my sister, anyway.
"Revenge"?
That wouldn't mean anything, and I'd have no reason to do that.
Ah... sure.
No... never mind.
Mi no sono mae no sono hitomi
Your eyes before me
On second thought...
Let me see yours, Yamamoto.
Kaze ni utau yume no hito
sing in the wind of the one I dream of.
Thank you.
Mayou kibun utare omoidaseta nara
When I'm lost, I feel really down, and when I think of it...
Hohoemu sono tabi ni setsunasa tsumoru
Every time you smile, the pain piles up.
Mabushii sora no naka...
In the blinding sky...
Nana, you're not gonna buy those clothes you just tried on?
They looked so good on you, too.
I'm broke.
Then why did you invite me to go shopping?
Did you have a fight with Yano?
What's Yano doing today?
"Pretty awful..."
I wasn't really snooping around...
Yano can be really cold sometimes...
He hasn't called me, even though it's Sunday...
It's Yano!
It is Yano.
Hello---
Hello? Hi there!
Nice to meet you! Are you Yano's girlfriend?
Huh?
I went to the same middle school as Yano.
We're at Take's house right now.
Yano's throwing him a birthday party today.
Wanna come over?
Ah... sure... but I'm out shopping with a friend right now...
A friend?! Is she female?!
That sounds great! Bring her with you!
We'll make a whole hook-up party out of this!
W-What?
By the way, is your friend cute?
Hey, what are you doing with my cell?
Yano's voice!
Huh? I was thinking of making a hook-up party.
Are you a moron?
Hello?
Ah, Ya--
You don't have to come.
H-He hung up on me...
I... just snapped.
Ah, you really came?!
You son of a bitch.
Have a seat, heave a seat!
That annoyed look was blatantly obvious.
What'll you have to drink?
We have everything, since he runs a liquor store.
Want some sake?
Just kidding, just kidding!
Moron.
Why don't you sit next to Yano?
Ah, no... here's fine.
You don't have to hold back.
Hey, Yano.
I'm getting kinda tired. Maybe I should head back?
Ah, that little... he's ignoring me!
For being my boyfriend, he's really ruining things!
Ah, that reminds me...
I thought coming empty-handed might seem rude, so I bought you a present, Takeuchi-kun.
Huh? You don't have to.
A-Ah, don't mention it. It's nothing special, so, umm...
Don't expect too much.
Thanks. What could it be?
It's a cellphone strap.
Sign: Sea Urchin-kun
I... I told you it wasn't anything special...
I... I was going for a gag gift, yeah...
Was it a bit too corny...?
No... I think I actually kinda like it.
Really?! Thank goodness!
I had a really hard time choosing, so that's great to hear!
Cheers!
Ch-Cheers...
This is bad...
You're too transparent, Yano!
Ah... let's try to nonchalantly change the topic...
By the way, it's that, isn't it?
A-Ah, yeah! It is, isn't it?
It's the season for sea urchins, right?
You didn't change the topic one bit!
Take! Take!
Keep going with the topic change!
Just like you always do! You're good at it!
Sea urchins?
You jealous of the sea urchin?
What are you doing?!
What was that?
You're jealous, aren't you?
You've had such a bored look on your face this whole time.
I'm not jealous at all of that weird strap.
Weird?!
Then why don't you find a different look?
It's my birthday, you know.
I'm sympathizing with you.
Getting such a lame sea urchin like that.
Lame?!
You're just pitiful, getting so happy over it.
What's this? You're obviously just jealous.
Yano... be an adult about this.
I can't believe you!
What the hell are you doing?!
Throwing away someone's present like that... you're scum!
The world doesn't revolve around you, Yano!
Think about what you did!
I'm leaving!
Wait, Takahashi!
Where's my sea urchin?
Hell if I know.
Takahashi!
You don't have to take me home!
Wait up.
You're annoying. Go away, you bastard.
The world may not revolve around me...
...but you're here for me, aren't you?
Didn't you say that?
But what you just did was a mistake.
You can't do that sort of stuff, Yano.
I don't need anything that won't be mine.
Sometimes...
...Yano can be cold.
Then, you don't need me...?
Really cold...
Don't you need me?
There's something wrong with you being unable to believe in people.
Have you ever believed in someone and been betrayed by them?
Have you?
You'll never...
...understand how I feel.
Yano, you're not fair.
Takahashi.
It's okay if you don't understand.
Didn't you throw it out the window...?
I threw a peanut.
I'm sorry. I got jealous.
It annoys me.
I want one, too.
But you said it was weird and lame.
Despite that, I want one.
He didn't deny it...
Here.
Give it to Takeuchi sometime when I'm not watching.
Can I ask for something else out of selfishness?
Yeah.
Don't be nice to any other guys when I'm around.
Is it okay if you're not looking?
Takahashi, I know you don't want to, but please.
Try to read between the lines here. Please.
And one more thing.
I love you.
So...
...don't go anywhere.
Don't go anywhere.
The starry sky looks just like the planetarium...
If a shooting star whizzed by, what would you wish for?
"I wish to become rich as soon as possible."
Please don't talk about unrealistic dreams.
They're just dreams.
What about you?
Me?
I'd...
...wish to marry Yano.
...wish to be with you forever.
Oh, I like that.
Umm... me too.
I'd wish to be your first and your last.
Why do you always attach that stuff to what I say?
And you say that pretty easily, but do you know what it really means?
Yeah.
To be together with you until you die.
Do you swear it?
I swear it on the stars.
If there's a shooting star, I wish to be with Nana-chan forever.
Takahashi, I'm sorry!
I'm really, really sorry!
I can't seem to find the sea urchin anywhere.
I looked for it all night, but I couldn't find it at all.
I'm sorry.
Yano only pretended to throw it out.
I see.
I'm sorry, too.
I should've told you sooner.
No... I'm just glad I didn't lose it.
Ah, but I won't put it on my cellphone.
He'd probably get the wrong idea if I did.
I-I'm really sorry about this, and for making you have to do that...
Bye!
Takeuchi-kun is... Takeuchi-kun is...
My heart's squeezing in delight?
Not that!
Did you say something?
Nope, not a thing...
It'd be nice if Yano tried taking some pointers from Takeuchi-kun...
By the way, Yano...
...when you keep flirting like this, it's hard to study.
You're kind of like my boy cousin.
He's only five, but he always gets in my shirt and hugs me.
Perverted little runt.
It's not like that. He just want to touch me.
When I carry him around, he gets really happy.
And he's only happy if a girl does it.
Even though the three-year-old girl doesn't do that at all...
Yano?
So I'm the same as a five-year-old brat?
I wonder If I hurt his pride?
There's nothing to worry about. It's just me here.
I'll give you a hug, so why don't you come on over?
As I thought, he really is the same as a five-year-old.
Motoharu.
Yes?
Some girl from school is waiting outside for you.
I wonder if she's here to confess her love?
That kind of pisses me off...
And it kinda looks like he's used to this!
I'll be back in a minute!
Yes, yes.
Makes me wonder...
Taisetsu na anata no hitomi ni
I wonder if I'm reflected
Watashi wa utsutteru no ka na
in your precious eyes?
Don't you want to know...
Komorebi sashikomu madobe ni wa
I wonder how I can always be happy
...why Onee-chan was riding...
...in Kagawa's car that day?
Doushite yashiku nareru darou
on the windowsill where the sunshine always falls?
Kokoro kakushite kodou kakushite
I hide my true feelings and the thumping of my heart.
Itsumo no you ni
As always,
Wakariaenai tsurasa ga tamaranai
the pain of not being able to understand each other burns.
Waraitai waraitai kokoro no mannaka de
I want to smile, I want to smile, down to the core of my heart.
Anata ni wa uchiakeyou
I'll open up to you
Tsuyogaru watashi yowaki na watashi
about how I pretend to be strong, about how I'm weak,
Kinou no hanashi
about what happened yesterday,
dou demo ii koto mo zenbu
about everything that means nothing.
Aishiteru kore kara mo zutto
I'll continue to love you forever.
Yde wo kunde asuite ikou Yeah!
Take my arm and let's walk. Yeah!
Kisetsu wa watashi dake nokoshite
The seasons leave only me behind
Taisetsu na hito tsurete yukun da ne
and take my precious person away, don't they?
Kimi wo sagashite kimi wo sagashite
I look for you, I look for you,
Donna toki demo kimi wo sagashiteiru kedo
I'm always looking for you,
Mitsukaru no sore wa kimi na no?
but when I find that person, is it really you?
Episode 11 Preview...
You... haven't forgotten
about Onee-chan at all.
Kanashikute kanashikute
I'm so sad, I'm so sad,
You betrayed both
me and her at the same time.
nakidashisou ni naru
I could cry.
Everything is going the
way you want it to, isn't it?
Dore dake no omoi nara dakishimete kureru no?
How much feeling must I give to be able to embrace you?
Are you satisfied
with yourself now?
Go home.
I love you, more than
anyone else in the world.
That's why, Yano... talk to me.
Ah waraitai waraitai
Ah, I want to smile, I want to smile.
No matter what happened...
...I'll accept it.
Nanimokamo nage...
Throwing everything...