You may not believe me, but...
...even before he told me his name...
...I felt as if...
...I already knew who he was.
Yano... Motoharu.
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 1 ...
I'm Takahashi Nanami.
This is my second day of high school.
It'd be nice if I could make lots of friends.
F-For now, I'll try to...
U-Umm... I'm Takahashi Nanami.
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm Yamamoto Yuri. Nice to meet you.
U-Umm, what middle school are you from?
Asahi.
Ah... we have to change classrooms for home ec, right? Can I go with you guys?
Ah, you were in the first seat in the front, right?
Yeah. I'm Takahashi Nanami.
What middle school are you from?
South.
We're both from West.
There don't seem to be any girls in our class from Asahi, huh?
Ah, this girl Yamamoto-san who sits next to me is from Asahi Middle School.
No way! You talked to her?
You must've heard a lot about him.
About who?
Motoharu!
Who...?
We were with Motoharu during the winter session, and he's just so cool!
He was popular with both the girls and guys.
They even say that in his last year of middle school...
...two-thirds of the girls in class were in love with him at the same time!
So someone like that is in the same class as me...
Ah, hey, you're from the same middle school as Yano-kun, right?
Yeah.
I heard two-thirds of the girls fell for him?
I hate him.
Hey, Nana, wanna be on the class committee?
Ah... I prefer an easy life, so...
I really wanna be with Motoharu on the committee...
What's the procedure for joining it? Do you get nominated?
Though announcing it by yourself is kinda lame...
How about I nominate you?
Will you really?
Sure.
Er... what was her name again...?
Mizu... Mizu something...
I'll be counting on you!
A-Ah, yeah!
I can't possibly ask her...
U-Umm, what was that girl's name again...?
Mizu... Mizu...
Mizuhara.
You may not believe me, but...
...even before he told me his name...
... I felt as if...
... I already knew who he was.
Yano Motoharu.
April 9 (Tues) Daily Helper
Be the class president.
I was right...
Don't you think this nomination's a little arbitrary?
But nobody nominated anyone else or nominated themselves, so...
I'll nominate someone. I nominate myself as vice president.
There you go, taking the easy way out again...
Vice President Yano-kun, huh?
Ah... umm, I'd also like to nominate someone...
...for the role of secretary, Mizuhara-san.
Mizuhara
Did you mean Mizuguchi-san?
HEH
So in the end, I ended up as class president...
April 9 (Tues) Daily Helper
I'll assign everyone's duties and decide the class goals, then.
That was pretty rude of you.
You lied to me before, didn't you?
Ahh... was I more rude than forgetting someone's name?
This guy is kind of annoying...
But isn't it really my fault for forgetting her name...?
So, um... you...
What was your name again?
Hey, I wonder if Yano-kun's had a girlfriend before...
I've heard he's gone out with a lot of different girls...
Both younger and older!
Seriously?
I dunno. They're just rumors.
Let's try asking Yamamoto-san!
It seems like I'm a part of the other third of the class...
Don't ask me about him. I don't know. Not interested in the least.
She said she didn't know...
Friends.
Moron?
gaaaaaaa - n
High school...
...isn't as fun as I thought it'd be.
Nana, did you finish your career counseling session?
Yeah.
How was it?
Umm... I didn't understand it very much...
What's up with that?
See ya!
Bye!
Bye bye.
I wonder if I should've joined a club, too...
Takahashi!
How long did your career counseling session last?
Seven minutes.
Seven minutes?
Ten minutes.
No, it took half an hour.
Seriously, it took only five minutes.
Just kidding, it took fifteen.
Moron?
I don't want to hear that from you.
Bye bye.
Bye--
Umm, bye by--
What?
I... I thought you didn't hear me, so...
Bye... bye bye...
Why...?
Bye bye.
No, no! This isn't my heart beating faster for him... he only surprised me.
I just didn't think he'd call out to me like that.
That's why... that's why...
What's your problem?
I... I just don't understand Math I at all, and I was getting frustrated.
What? You plan on using math down you career path?
N-No, I plan to go to a liberal arts private school...
Then why bother worrying about the sciences?
Don't you think it'd be wiser to use this time focusing on liberal arts instead?
But... when you're so bad at something, then...
Even if you're bad at it, nothing will come from it.
It won't help you at all.
I don't understand why people do useless things they don't even like.
Hey! I heard the week after next is a school trip?
But we have tests before that...
I don't know what I'm gonna do. I haven't studied at all.
Gonna be a piece of cake for you, Nana?
No way, I've practically given up. I'll probably get a zero or something in math.
A zero, huh?
Takahashi Nanami
Year 1, Class 7
Math I Test
Amazing... I actually got a zero...
Takahashi.
Yes?!
We should probably decide who's in charge of the trip soon...
Ah... the people to head the teams, yeah...
And about buying stuff for the trip...
Ah, yeah? About buying stuff?
It's a pain, so can you go with the girls to take care of it?
Sure, sur- huh?! Why?!
I can see that, you know.
Math I Test
This is... umm...! I just wasn't feeling well, so...
I'd like you and the girls to take care of the shopping...
No! Why do we always get the annoying stuff?
Hey, guys, amazing stuff! Takahashi's math grade was...
We'll go! We'll go!
Thank you.
Don't be tricked, don't be tricked.
Even if he smiled like that, it's just because he threatened to blurt out your math grade...
You can't go on to the next grade with a failing mark...
Surprise...
But Yamamoto-san, didn't you say to drop math if I was aiming for liberal arts school?
But a failing grade is no good, obviously.
How should I put this... there are times when you begin to hate everything around you.
It's Yano...
Thump
W-What's up with my heart thumping like that?!
What are you doing?
Ah... I wanted to look at the sky, so...
Because of that zero, right?
Did you get the same...?
Me? I got an 87.
What's up with that?
But anyway, do you really think it's worth worrying about?
I wonder...
Yeah. Everyone is good at something. Isn't it all right if you just try your best at that?
And besides, don't you think getting a zero's pretty impressive in another way?
Have a seat.
Yano, is there anything you're not good at?
Me?
Next to nothing, I bet.
There is!
You're lying.
There is, there is.
I'm too popular with the girls.
Are you stupid?
What?
Besides that, do you have trouble with anything else?
Yeah.
I stand out, so I'm always being watched.
And even though it's annoying, I normally get picked to be on the class committee.
I can't sleep at night.
And I hate... fickle girls.
That makes five! Yay!
Hey... none of those are problems.
And when you say "fickle", do you really have the right to talk that way about others?
What? Are you making fun of me?
Despite my looks, I'm pretty single-minded.
Don't I seem that way?
Not at all.
I wonder what kind of girls Yano falls for...
I wonder what kind of girls he's fallen for...
Hey.. if the girl you were going out with was fickle, what would you do?
I wonder why I want to know his answer...
Yano?
I'd kill her.
Just kidding.
I'm not sure why I asked...
Yano, if you have any problems, I'll lend an ear.
Well... about anything. You just listened to me go on, so...
That's too bad. I don't have any problems.
There's that smile again...
I don't believe this is happening...
This is definitely going to be the worst mistake of my life...
Yano... I like--
Oh, and about your problems...
That's a right reserved for the living, don't you think?
Well... yes...
At that moment... I didn't know what Yano meant when he said that.
Uh... umm...
Take note of these important points during our walkathon school trip.
We will travel by bus to the starting point.
The entire length is 42 km, and... hey, Yano!
Explain this important stuff to everyone!
The use of cell phones is prohibited.
And no shopping at any shops along the path!
Oh, Take.
No using you cell phone.
O-Okay.
How was that?
Geez... I feel so pathetic, falling for someone incredibly irresponsible like him...
Ah, we're here!
I'm going to collect everyone's cell phones now!
I don't have one.
Does he really not have one...?
What's with that grin...?
I'm telling you, I forgot to bring it.
What? Yano really doesn't have one with him?
Ah, it's so nice out!
This might actually be fun!
I wonder if we'll be able to make it the whole 42 km...
Heh, really?
Hey... I sure want to eat lunch with Yano...
Nana, talk to him for us!
Me?
Well, you have a relationship with him since you're prez and he's vice prez.
Please! I'm counting on you!
Ah... I guess I have no choice, huh?
Ah, hey...
Motoharu!
W-Want to have lunch together, Yamamoto-san?
What are you doing, inviting Yamamoto-san...?
Get Yano, too!
My timing was off...
You don't want to eat with Yamamoto-san?
Well, it's not that we don't want to, she's just hard to talk to.
She gives off a dark aura...
D-Don't say that.
Well, it's just fine and all... but be sure to invite Yano and the others, too.
Okay.
I hate him.
Oh no, what am I gonna do?
If I invite Yano now, it'll be like I did it to harass Yamamoto-san...
Even though almost nobody hates him, I wonder why Yamamoto-san does...
Hey... who's that person?
That person
Ah, that's Takeuchi-kun.
Takeuchi-kun
Apparently, they were both in same class in middle school.
Even now, they still seem to hang out a lot.
It's the half way point!
That went by fast!
Think you'll be able to walk the whole 42 km?
Yeah. Piece of cake.
We did it!
Yeah!
Yano.
W... Want to eat lunch with everyone?
Ah, sure, but... can you keep up with our pace?
Ah... I'm starting to get tired...
The scenery isn't changing a bit, either...
I'm starting to get bored of nature.
We should've retired at the 20 km mark...
Hey... wanna sit down for lunch now?
I'm exhausted.
Yeah...
In the end, we lost track of Yano and the others, anyway...
Yamamoto-san?
Are you all right?
Want some water?
Huh? What's the matter?
Takeuchi-kun.
She's not feeling well...
Do you think the teachers will pass by in their cars?
Ah... I think they're eating lunch at the cabin back at the 20 km halfway point...
They should be by in an hour or two.
An hour or two, huh?
For now, if I find someone who can get in touch with them, I'll let them know.
Thanks.
Yamamoto-san, can you eat some fruit?
It might refresh you...
I brought some cold juice with me...
What are we gonna do?
I wonder if she'll get better if she takes a break...
I wonder if we have to wait for the teachers...
This is no good... I'm the one who's supposed to be responsible, but I can't do anything to help...
Huh? Someone's heading back this way.
It's Yano.
Huh? Why?
Take got in touch with me.
Got in touch with him?
Hey. Did you eat breakfast?
Do you have any symptoms of dehydration?
Did you try licking some salt?
Do you have a fever?
She has a fever.
No way! What'll we do?
We should get someone with a car to come over here.
But how will we contact the teachers?
Ah, it's me. Where are you right now?
About 25 km in?
How long before you reach the goal?
Another two hours?
This guy... he kept it hidden...
The teachers haven't passed by yet, right?
Ah, okay.
I'm going to return to the halfway point.
The halfway point?
They're eating lunch in the barbecue house at the lodge back there.
If I go now to get them, they can be back here in five minutes if they drive.
You guys stay here.
Hey, do any of you have your cell phones with you?
None of us... they were taken away.
Huh? How about you two?
No...
I don't have mine.
Why can't you girls keep control of your own cell phones?
"Why?"
I have mine...
I have mine... so we'll be fine...
No way...
Ah, I'll come with you.
It's fine. You stay behind.
But I'm pretty much the responsible party here, so...
If you start slowing me down, I'll leave you behind.
Your number hasn't changed, right?
They know each other's cell phone numbers because they were in the same class in middle school, right?
Why are you walking like a snail? I'll seriously leave you behind.
Yeah...
Ah... I'm such a bad person... worrying about something else when Yamamoto-san is like that...
Hey, were you close to Yamamoto-san in middle school?
Not really. She hardly talked to me.
She's been pretty quiet since a long time ago.
I see...
So she's been like that since long ago...
What do you mean, "like that"?
Well, she doesn't really express her feelings... I wonder if she's a single child?
She isn't.
She had an older sister.
Really?
Er... huh? Past tense?
Ah, yeah. She died last summer.
I had no idea...
Isn't it better that way?
She seems like the type who would hate being pitied.
How'd she die?
It was a car accident.
Yano... did you go to the funeral?
No.
It was summer vacation, after all
I've... never experienced anything like that, so I don't really understand, but...
It must be really difficult, huh?
Probably...
I'm... really an unsympathetic girl...
Even though we're having this discussion, my heart's beating really fast because of Yano...
Yamamoto?
It looks like she came down with a fever.
The 25 km point, huh?
Yeah.
Then, Sensei, I'm counting on you.
Ah, yes. I haven't had any beer, so I should be fine.
H-Hey, shouldn't we go with him?
There's nothing more we can do, right?
Let's just leave the rest to him.
Two plates of beef ribs and two Oolong teas, please!
I'm amazed at you...
They say one should be efficient in life, right?
Ah... and some cow tongue and barbecued beef giblets too, please.
Well... whatever.
Yano.
Today...
It really helped that you were here...
Th-Thanks.
I've never seen someone with as carefree a smile as his...
Ah, you're late! What were you doing?
Yamamoto-san was taken home by the teacher.
Looks like it was just the common cold.
Is that so? Thank goodness.
Umm... buses will be leaving from all over, so please make sure you board the right one.
Understand?
Even though we just parted from each other... I want to see him again...
Takeuchi-kun.
Yeah.
Thanks for before. It really helped.
Ah, how did things turn out?
Well, we got a teacher to come by in a car and take her home.
Really? That's good to hear.
I was just thinking you were all so great, thinking on behalf of your friends.
Huh, really?
Well... a lot's happened, so...
A lot?
She died last summer.
Yeah... I guess so...
So you heard about it...
Yeah.
It must be hard, huh?
Yeah... if it were me, I wouldn't be able to get back up...
R-Really...?
No one close to me has died yet, so I don't really get it, but I wonder how it must feel...
I wonder if a person would just put a stopper on their life...
Though, I feel like they're a different type of person...
Yeah... but you can't just tell from their outward appearance, so...
Yeah...
But, really... it's kind of bad...
Really?
Yeah.
I've never seen them cry before... and I think it'd be better if they'd just cry or let it distract them...
But I have no idea if they're over it, or if they're still saddened about it...
...or something else entirely... I just don't know.
It's really scary.
You don't have to talk about them like that!
Saying they're "scary". I think they're really strong.
Well, yeah, but...
I think it's okay not to keep it all bottled up sometimes.
It can be really frustrating because you're friends, don't you think?
Takeuchi-kun, you're really that close...?
Huh? Even though we're in different classes, we're still friends, right?
Hey...
Who are you talking about...?
Taisetsu na anata no hitomi ni
I wonder if I'm reflected
Good morning!
Morning.
You're sunburnt.
I want to peel it all off...
Nice face you have there.
Watashi wa utsutteru no ka na
in your precious eyes?
What? Is that something you normally say to a girl?
How about "that's quite a face".
He's so shameless, stuck-up, irresponsible, and impossible to deal with, but...
Kimorehi zashikomu madobe ni wa
I wonder how I can always be happy
I love him a whole lot...
What is it?
Doushite yasashiku narerun darou
on the windowsill where the sunshine always falls?
Yamamoto-san's older sister, right?
Kokoro kakushite kodou kakushite
I hide my true feelings and the thumping of my heart.
Yeah. That's why.
Itsumo no you ni
As always,
It's nothing.
Wakariaenai tsurasa ga tamaranai
the pain of being able to understand each other burns.
She died last summer.
Waraitai waraitai kokoro no mannaka de
I want to smile, I want to smile, down to the core of my heart.
Probably...
You big liar.
She was... Yano's girlfriend.
Anata ni wa uchiakeyou
I'll open up to you
Tsuyogaru watashi yowaki na watashi
about how I pretend to be strong, about how I'm weak,
Kinou no hanashi
about what happened yesterday,
dou demo ii koto mo zenbu
about everything that means nothing.
Aishiteru kore kara mo zuttoo
I'll continue to love you forever.
Ude wo kunde aruite ikou YEAH!
Take my arm and let's walk. Yeah!
Kisetsu wa watashi dake nokoshite
The seasons leave only me behind
Taisetsu na hito tsurete yukun da ne
and take my precious person away, don't they?
Kimi wo sagashite kimi wo sagashite
I look for you, I look for you,
Donna toki demo kimi wo sagashiteiru kedo
I'm always looking for you,
Mitsukaru no sore wa kimi na no?
but when I find that person, is it really you?
Kanashikute kanashikute
I'm so sad, I'm so sad,
nakidashisou ni naru
I could cry.
Dore dake no omoi nara dakishimete kureru no?
How much feeling must I give to be able to embrace you?
Ah waraitai waraitai
Ah, I want to smile, I want to smile.
Nani mo ka mo nagesutete
Throwing everything away,
Yano, I...
Episode 2 Preview ...
Anata ni wa uchiakeyou
I'll open up to you.
I think I might like you...
Then, wanna go out?
Huh? You really like me back?
Kinou no hanashi ashita no hanashi
About yesterday, about tomorrow,
Yeah, I guess.
Not that sort of "like"...
Futari no mirai kakaekirenai hodo zenbu
about our future and everything, so much that I can't even take it all myself.
I'm asking if you
really, really like me.
I'm sorry... I don't know.
Yakusoku wa shinakutemo ii yo
You don't have to promise me anything.
What's up with that...?
My girlfriend was a cheat.
She was with
another guy when she died.
Futari massugu ni arukou YEAH!
Let's just keep walking. Yeah!
It was her previous boyfriend.
They were never
through with one another...