I can't see Yano.
Summer vacation is so boring.
Rehearsal!!
Good morning!
Morning!
Everyone's already here.
Let's get all the desks pushed to the front.
I wonder if Yano's in the bathroom or something...
Huh? It's from Yano.
He can't make it today.
Take a look.
Sorry. I can't make it to rehearsal today, so get some to stand in for me.
Sorry. I can't make it to rehearsal today,
so get some to stand in for me.
We can't even start without the lead! Call him back!
He must've turned off his cell phone. It's impossible.
He has no sense of responsibility.
Don't worry. He'll get things done when they need to be done.
That's not the real problem here...
Geez... and I was looking forward to today, too...
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 3...
In the end, Yano didn't come to the rehearsal after that, either...
Hello?
Ah, Mizu-chin?
A festival?
Yeah, I'll totally go.
You're gonna wear a yukata?
I don't think I will...
I also invited Yano and the others.
He skips out on practice, but he always shows up at times like these...
Once he shows up, I'll really let him have it.
Mom! Get my yukata out!
Huh? You're wearing a yukata too, Nana!
S-Sorry for being so late.
Nana, you look really cute today!
Y-You think so?
Yeah! That yukata suits you surprisingly well!
That color is perfect for you!
I-Is it really?
I borrowed it from my cousin's older sister.
The pattern on mine was just too childish.
Your cheeks look really cute, too!
It's apricot.
It looks like you just got out of bath.
Oh! They're wearing yukatas! The yukata brigade is here!
The boys are here.
Huh? Where's Yano?
Ah, about that... we haven't been able to reach his cell at all.
He's not coming?
No, I think he will... but probably with his local friends.
We might run into them.
It'd be nice... if he makes it...
Huh? Takahashi, you look completely different!
That's what I was telling her! Doesn't she look good in a yukata?
Not at all...
They do say that baby-faced kids unexpectedly look good in classic Japanese clothing.
Compared to the normal you, Takahashi, you look like a heron tonight!
Ah... such a waste. If only yukatas had been the school uniform, I might've been so popular...
Ah, geez! Yano, what are you doing?
Nana, they said they'd still give you one.
Here you go!
Yay!
How nice!
Nana?
Takeuchi-kun!
Ah, you surprised me! I wasn't sure who it was.
It's been a while!
Who are you here with?
I'm here with some classmates. What about you, Takeuchi-kun?
Some people from my neighborhood.
He's... not here.
I... I wasn't implying that or anything!
You're so innocent.
Yano couldn't make it?
That guy just doesn't seem to need other people...
I can't say it very well, but...
...no matter how much we talk about something, he doesn't budge an inch.
It's like we're not reaching him or something.
Sometimes it seems so futile...
I just feel like whatever we do will be useless in the end.
Even though I got really excited and even wore a yukata...
...counted down the days to the rehearsals on my fingers...
...it all feels so useless...
Nana, want a snow cone? I'll go buy some!
Okay.
Sorry, looks like I can't get in touch with him.
Ah, don't worry about that.
I just wanted to complain about how he skipped out on the rehearsals.
It was... the anniversary.
The day before yesterday, for Nana-san.
It must be pretty harsh, don't you think?
I... didn't know at all...
I was just getting all festive, without knowing a thing.
That's fine.
Having someone always excited and happy around you.
As long you keep your spirits high, that's fine.
Me?
Catch you later.
You look cute in that yukata.
What... can I do?
Yano
Why am I here?
I won't, after all...
I don't know what to say.
Oh, it's a stalker! She's loitering in front of my house!
Yano!
I-I'm no stalker.
That caught me off guard!
Then what are you?
How long has he been watching me?
I had some business with you!
Aimlessly lingering around my place?
No!
See!
Let me in!
Sorry, I refuse degenerates.
Y-You...! Yano, open the gate, dammit!
The female pervert stalker has gone berserk!
Are you a moron?! Mrs. Yano, I've come for a school visit with your stupid-ass son!
I said open up!
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting...
Ah... the worst possible situation...
Please stay as long as you like.
Have some.
Ah, yeah...
Thank you.
I'm all alone with Yano in his room...
I-I'm getting nervous...
Takahashi, why did you come poking around here?
I-I th-th-thought you m-might be sick, so...
Why would you think I was sick?
Well, like, you've missed every rehearsal so far.
Why didn't you just get right to the point and ask why I've missed them?
You sure are one to speak right now, since you're the one who missed them!
Why did you miss them, then?
Er, shoot!
Yano?
I've been drowning in my memories of Nana-san...
I'm no good in the summer.
That's why...
...can I skip the rehearsal the day after tomorrow, and the one two days after tomorrow, too?
You're lying.
Damn.
Why did you miss them?
It's summer break, and you expect me to wake up at nine in the morning?
T-This guy...
It was my own fault for worrying about you.
You got to eat some bean jelly, so don't complain.
It's not like I come here just to eat bean jelly!
Then don't eat any!
No, I'll eat some!
What the...? He's totally cheerful.
Thank goodness.
And.. I finally got to see him.
Ah, is that a photo album?
Lemme see!
No.
Why not?
Wait a sec. I'll take out all the bad pictures.
What do you mean, "bad"?
Was your middle school trip to Sapporo?
Same as mine.
Hey... can I see a picture of Nana-san?
What are you gonna do after looking at something like that?
Here you go.
I'm not even sure... what I want to do after I see it.
You're pretty careless, aren't you?
Do you realize where you are right now?
On my bed.
B-But the door's open, so...
The window, too.
People are passing by outside.
And you're my classmate, Yano...
What are you doing?
I haven't done anything. She just fell on her own.
S-Sorry for making such a fuss...
Are you a moron? Don't take me so seriously!
Is that... is that just it?
Hey, this isn't a picture of Nana-san.
I don't have a single picture of her.
He doesn't budge an inch....
I thought of you every day.
I went to rehearsal all excited.
I got really happy wore a yukata.
I even come over your house.
But none of that seems to matter to you at all.
You'd better be at rehearsal the day after tomorrow.
That's all I could say.
He's just another classmate.
Takahashi.
Thanks for today.
I just... wanted to see you.
Yano!
Yano, you may not have someone left who you really, really love...
...and that might be a really sad thing for you, but...
...because there are people out there who really, really love you, shouldn't it all equal out?
So... please don't think you're all alone.
I'm watching you, so..!
I'm always watching you, so...!
I'm always watching over you, so...!
Sorry for having bothered you!
I'm always watching you... I'm always watching over you.
So... please don't think you're all alone.
Did you check on the props?
They're going pretty well so far.
It's because Yamamoto-san's so reliable for things like this.
And Yano?
He's not here again today.
He's just no good.
Now that it's come to this, I'll just have to cover with my acting skills.
It's easy to say.
But really, nothing's changed.
I'm... so powerless.
Ah... good morning.
Morning.
He... showed up.
Nana.
Nana, the happi coats.
I borrowed some samples.
Which color would be better?
I think red's pretty cute.
Yeah, I thought so, too. Red's better, isn't it?
Yano!
Yeah! It really does look cute.
And this way, dirt won't stand out.
What's up with that?
Look, look!
The red looks good on you.
We're totally going with white.
There's no other person who can make my heart beat this fast...
Is white all right?
The white suits you. It must be nice, Yano. Everything looks good on you.
You looked good, too...
...in that yukata.
What are you talkin--
How...?
Takeuchi sent it to me.
He took a pretty good picture.
I regretted not going.
You said you're watching me, didn't you? Always watching me.
Can you really do that?
I.. I can!
Bullshit.
You're so unreasonable.
And what about that "it all equals out" junk? As if that logic works!
You're watching over me? Spewing out a guy line like that!
You're really conceited, aren't you?
You're so mean, saying it like that!
Ow.
S-Sorry.
Yano?
Just kidding.
I was actually really happy.
Nana-chan.
Y-Yes?
Let me borrow your chest.
I promise to always watch over you...
You're not alone.
September 4th
Helpers:
Mizuguchi
Miyamoto
Summer break flew by in an instant.
But there's been no change between me and Yano.
It's pretty impressive that Yano can fall asleep in a place like this.
And he's using my bag as a pillow.
I wonder if he's dreaming?
Some airheaded dream.
I wonder what kind of dreams Yano has...
Isn't that Yamamoto's older sister?
Geh! That guy with her is Kagawa.
Ah, you mean that guy who skipped out of our grade and graduated?
He's always with a different girl.
She's really going out with a loser.
He threw his water on her!
Is that a battlefield?
He left...
He's the worst.
Hey, you guys are in the same class as Yuri, right?
I'm sorry, but could you lend me some cash?
He left without paying.
If you put that much Tabasco on, you'll get hemorrhoids!
Hemorrhoids, huh?
You don't resemble your younger sister much, do you?
Ah, you think I'm some kind of idiot, don't you?
What's that?
Huh? Ah, this?
Did you fall?
Whenever he's in bad mood, it always turns out like this.
He can be such a kid at times.
Your boyfriend doesn't have the best reputation, you know.
But isn't he so cool?
His bad parts are part of his charm.
There's no perfect man out there.
As long as I can understand him, that's good enough.
They call that sort of thing "being blind."
You haven't really fallen in love with anyone before.
They call people like you "immature know-it-alls."
Hurry and fall in love.
Huh? Is Nana-san waiting for her boyfriend?
She should wait in a warmer place.
She has no cash. If she sees us, she'll probably try to sponge us.
What do you wanna do today?
Let's go to your place, Takeuchi.
Ah, could I change first?
So cold...
Ah, the new Sunday's out!
What's this? It looks so funny!
I could really laugh at this!
Do you still think he's gonna come?
He won't.
Then why are you waiting around?
To gather my rage.
Your rage...?
I'll gather my rage and curse him to death!
Don't underestimate women.
That's not a hand warmer. It's a drink.
He says not to talk to other guys...
...but if I respond with "didn't you have sex with that other girl?" things really get messed up.
He completely enjoys every minute of this.
Every time I cry, he says "I've made another girl cry" all arrogantly.
That jerk can just die!
He should fall off a bridge, break his neck, fall headfirst into a dump truck and smash his head, and die!
Why don't you say something?
Huh?
You must think I'm some kind of moron, don't you?
Hey... what do you think I should do?
What? Figure out your own problems by yourself.
Because I'm a moron, I don't know!
I could tell you, but in exchange, you better do as I say.
Will it make me happy?
What's happiness?
I don't know.
Probably something where no ones cries or gets yelled at.
Where no one gets hit or has stuff thrown at them.
Something like that.
Am I wrong?
I don't know.
What's up with that!
Then.. why don't we both go searching for our own happiness?
Hey! That's a bean jelly bun! Trade with me?
No.
Stingy!
Just kidding.
Here's half.
Hey, is something like this...
...happiness?
Who knows?
I really let him have it when I broke up with him.
What did you say?
"You'll definitely regret this later!"
Serves him right!
Ah, I figured it out.
Happiness is a hot chocolate on a cold days!
What should we do?
There are still people around.
It's fine. They're leaving.
I'm sure this will become a memory.
If we're seen by anyone, it'll become a huge fuss.
Because I graduated today, I don't really care.
I still have another year.
This'll only make you look even better.
Is that so?
Hurry.
The beach...
I want to go to the beach.
No way. It's cold and it stinks.
Let's go! Take me to the beach!
It's so cold!
And it stinks like kelp! It wasn't supposed to be like this!
Didn't I tell you?
Ah! A bug! Over here, too!
Gross, gross!
Let's go back! Let's go back!
We just got here!
Let's go back! Let's go back! Let's go back!
Mocchan.
Motoharu-kun.
Are you mad?
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to see something beautiful.
Then I'll take you to the southern islands one day.
Really? When?
Well, first I have to save crazy money... So about ten years, I guess?
You moron!
Stop.
Stop here today.
Why?
No reason.
What the heck?
Should I get us something to drink?
Is coffee all right?
What is this?
I bumped it.
Are you still seeing him?
I only met with him.
I said I only met with him.
You're mean.
Kagawa, a junior is here to see you.
A junior?
Did you fall?
As if, you moron.
So, did you win or lose?
Winning and losing doesn't matter in these kinds of situations.
I kept on punching until I was satisfied.
Which means you were also punched until he was satisfied.
Thank you.
Ow! Don't touch them, you moron!
Hey, I wanna take a picture of this.
What? Are you an idiot or something?
It'll be proof that you fought for me.
You're... the same.
As that arrogant guy.
You really like crying, don't you?
There's no human out there who likes crying.
That's why I'm here like this right now.
Promise me...
...that you absolutely won't betray me.
Yeah.
There's no second chance.
I promise.
I absolutely won't betray you.
Ah, Motoharu?
Calm down and listen carefully.
You see... Nana-san was riding with Kagawa in his car, and...
Takahashi.
Ah, you're up?
What are you doing?
Well, you fell asleep.
Ah... sorry. I was using your bag as a pillow?
You should've just woken me up.
Well, you looked like you were having a happy dream, so I didn't want to wake you up.
A happy dream?
Yeah.
What's happiness...?
I wonder what it is?
That's a tough one.
Umm...
Uhh...
Ah! Something warm.
Something warm?
Yeah! Like a steamed meat bun or a roasted sweet potato.
Something that warms you up on a cold day.
Something that soothes your heart.
A steamed meat bun, huh?
Well, it can be anything, like a book you like or a CD.
Yuuhi kage wo hosoku nobashita
The sunset stretches my shadow long and thin.
Or someone you like.
Kokoro wo fukaku somete yuku
Its colors deeply dye my heart.
Kitto saigo no jikan da to
When you said this was probably the last time,
Let's go get some steamed meat buns.
Namida koraeteta
I held back my tears.
It's already the season for steamed meat buns?
This was the first time...
Omoide nante itsumo kanashisugiru bakari
Memories are always too sad.
...the first time I wished for someone else's happiness.
Isso wasurete shimaitai yo
I just want to forget them all.
Nido to aenai kimi no senka to
I continued to watch the last sunset
Saigo no yuuhi mitsumetsudzuketa
and your back that I would never see again.
Sotto sotto koboreochiteiku
The sun that slowly, slowly sets in the distance.
Ima wa kono ame ni utare
Right now, I'm being drenched by this rain.
Mou naite ii ka na
Is it all right if I cry now?
Kimi wa inai yo
You're no longer here.
Namida afuretemo tomenaide ite
Even if my tears begin to overflow, don't stop them.
Ame yo koorasete kokoro made
Rain, freeze me down to my heart.
Sotto kono mama kiete shimaitai yo
I just want to silently fade into nothingness.
Stop the sunset ima wa utawanaideite
Stop the sunset. Don't sing right now.
Umi ni ochiteyuku kanashii iro ne
The sun casts sad colors as it sinks into the ocean.
Episode 4 Preview ...
Is it my imagination...
...or has the person
I like seemed distant lately?
Zutto kono basho de hitori ni sasete
Just let me stay here alone forever.
Since the day we had
the steamed meat buns together.
Yuuhi yo kono mama shizumanaide ite
Make it so the sun never sets.
You don't have to be
so protective of me like before.
I don't understand...
I don't understand Yano...
I wonder if we'll be
able to talk like we did before...
I'll only say this once, so listen carefully.
I love you.