Hey, the float's coming along pretty nicely.
How's the cafe going?
Right on schedule. Wanna see?
Ah, umm... has Yano been showing up?
Huh? Yeah, he's been there. Why?
Ah, well... I was a little worried he might be slacking off or something.
After all, that's all he did last year.
After what happened, he completely stopped coming to see me...
...so I thought he might've been skipping out, but...
I see... he's been showing up...
Hey, gimme a break!
You're so clumsy!
Thank goodness... he's the same as always...
So full of life...
Even though we broke up...
Even though I broke up with him, why is it that I still don't want to hurt him?
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 15 ...
Nana! Over here, over here!
You didn't come in a yukata this year.
Neither did you.
Well, it's just us girls tonight.
But Nana, didn't a certain someone invite you to come?
Like Yano?
N-No... actually, I was wondering how to decline the invitation if he had asked me...
But he didn't.
Seriously?!
How about Takeuchi-kun?
There's no way he would, Mizu-chin. Don't make me repeat myself.
I had decided to decline anyway...
...so why do I feel so disappointed?
All right! Since it's just us girls, let's make something of this!
Yeah!
What's up with that? That's awesome!
Y-Yano-senpai...
U-Umm...
Would you please do a round of goldfish scooping for me?
I heard you were really good at it...
...and I really want a goldfish!
It'd be cheaper to just buy one at a goldfish store.
P-Please...
Who's that? One of the underclassmen?
She said "senpai" really loud.
Is she a first year?
I'm so much better with the wafer plates than these pois...
Oh, well.
Wow!
He got me one! Yano-san got me one!
No way! Are you serious? Lemme see!
Even if it's cheaper at a goldfish store, it wouldn't mean anything!
Look! It's a big pop-eyed goldfish!
He's so nice!
So Yano's here, too...
Looks that way.
I see... Yano's also here...
I'm going to treat it well for the rest of my life!
Yeah!
He's here...
Hey! We should be having a blast, too!
Let's beat them with some turtle scooping!
T-Turtle?
He's here with other people...
Hey, twilight in the summer really makes you want to see the one you love, don't you think?
Twilight in the summer?
Or on rainy days, or during the season when cherry blossoms fall, or in those long nights...
Being single is so lonely!
That's all year round for you...
Whoa! It's alive?!
Shoot, I messed up.
It's harder than it looks, huh?
Hey mister, one try please.
Being single... is so lonely...
Oh... he's pretty good at this.
Hey, what do you wanna do next?
I'll give you one.
Since you're such a cutie.
I... I'm a "cutie"?
Nice! Go on and take it.
Go on and take it, miss.
I-Is it really all right...?
Excuse me.
She's my girlfriend, so would you please not do that?
Let's go!
That guy was a decoy.
He was working with the guy in the stall.
He would give you the turtle for free, then try to sell you expensive food for it.
It's hard to decline something you're getting for free, right?
I see...
Why is Takeuchi-kun looking at me so gently?
You sure know a lot about this stuff.
Ah... a friend of mine was asked to do it part-time a long time ago.
Ah, and I'm sorry about calling you my girlfriend!
I-It's fine. Thanks.
It's just such a pain once you get mixed up with them.
Yeah.
Y-You got separated from your friends because of me...
Ah, don't worry. I just got a text message from them.
1 New Message
Text Message Menu
Write New Message
Old Messages
Sent Messages
New Messages
Voice Mail
Text Message Settings
Old Messages
Main Folder
Mizu-chin
Taka
Takeuchi
Folder 4
Good going, Nanami (
(No Subject)
Message 001
Mizu-chin
Good going, Nanami ('  ')
Nice, Nanami. Go for it!
Make things go well with Takeuchi.
('  ')
Well, I'll be going then. Will you be all right?
Y-Yeah.
I made plans with people from around my area again, like last year.
Nothing but guys, though. Not really appealing at all.
Yeah.
See you.
I'm such a moron...
What was I hoping for?
Being single... is lonely.
Takahashi.
If you ever think you're getting into a dangerous situation, call me right away.
I'll be there in a flash.
What? Takeuchi-kun left?
Of course he did.
"Of course"?
Nana, you're blushing...
This is the same girl who said it wasn't possible because Takeuchi-kun was Yano's best friend.
If Takeuchi-kun found out he was being refused for that reason, he wouldn't be able to do anything either, I'm sure.
Of course, this is just considering the off-chance that he does actually like you.
The off-chance...
...that he actually likes me...
What?
Sign: Octopus Balls
I thought you would've invited her.
Well, she did say "it's not possible."
What about you? You didn't invite her?
Oh, right. She said you bothered her, didn't she?
Die.
I wonder if she's here in her yukata again...
I haven't seen her.
She might've come in a yukata...
Knowing her, she might've come alone with her girlfriends, and been an east mark for some stall keeper.
An easy mark?
I wouldn't worry about that. They don't make marks of really cute girls.
You're really... a nice guy.
I... plan to settle things soon.
When?
Unlike you...
...I'm not some big-hearted guy.
I don't say things like "no matter what happens, we'll always be friends."
What's that suppose to be? A threat?
Just the truth.
If only I were a good guy like you.
Hey... before, you told Takahashi you'd be waiting for her, but...
...if something happens again, do you realize that Takahashi will be the one hurting?
When you still haven't organized anything there's no way it'll go well.
Right now, it's impossible for you.
Impossible?
You're in love with Nana-san, aren't you?
She's dead.
She's still alive within you.
Which is why you have no right to go out with Takahashi.
I'm going to make my move.
Coffee
Orange Juice
Hot Chocolate
Tea
What've you been doing? You look so strained.
About this... no matter how many times I calculate it, there's hardly any profit.
Yano, it doesn't matter if we make a profit, as long as we break even.
After all, this is for the school festival.
Anyway, we'll scare away customers if the prices are too high, right?
Then, what? We're all gonna work for nothing?
We're gonna get nothing out of all the blood and sweat we've put into it?
AWKWARD SILENCE
It's begun again...
...this year!
Their one-on-one battle...
Let's at least make enough to take care of the fees for putting this up.
It's too stupid and pointless like this.
I couldn't agree with you more.
Let's leave the drink menu alone, and raise the prices on the side order menu slightly.
Menu
Coffee
Orange Juice
Hot Chocolate
Black Tea
Oolong Tea
Green Tea
But in exchange, let's add some sort of special deal.
Oh, that sounds good.
If we manage to sell a lot, we'll be able to eat and drink for free afterwards.
This should definitely make everyone a little more excited about selling.
Hey...
Can I ask you something?
How is one able... to forget about the dead?
How do you...
...organize your feelings?
Please...
...tell me.
It's...
...impossible to forget something like that.
Something wrong?
Ah, nope... I just came to grab some duct tape.
Those two are getting along unusually well this year.
Last year, you could feel the cold vibes coming off them.
Y-Yeah. I wonder what happened this year...
Sign: The 43rd High School Festival
Welcome!
Please come to Class 2-7's Asian Cafe!
We have refreshing drinks and sweets!
We also offer special discounts for couples!
It's really hot out today.
And we have less flyers than we thought we'd need...
I'll have to go copy some more.
Nana! Have a drink!
You must be thirsty, right?
Ah, it's so cold and good!
Yeah, it's great. What is it?
What's this leaf?
Mizu-chin, you really know what hits the spot!
It's from Yano.
He told me to tell you it must be hard handing out all those flyers, since it's so hot out.
Oh. Long time no see.
Asian Cafe
Order incoming!
Two iced teas!
Here we are.
Shock
Surprise
Argh
W-Why are those two together?!
Welcome...
What's up with that costume?
An iced tea and... um...
...another one of those drinks you got for me.
The master's recommended special shake. Got it.
So that's what it's called on the menu.
Ah, um... it was really good. What's in it?
A piece of banana, milk, ice, and syrup.
It's a complete ripoff!
Order incoming.
Where you off today?
Hurry up
and leave
already
I'm working the late shift today.
What? You also graduated from here, Ayaka-san? I had no idea!
Don't go
putting
strange
things
in her head
I'll never
trust you
again
Be the way, do they still have that whole
"confession time" during the closing festival?
I just can't seem to relax in here.
Moto, make the drinks to go, would you?
Right away.
I see... so they still have it.
That brings back memories.
There was this one time where I was confessed to and ran right into the relationship.
But we broke up right away.
I have some good memories because of it, though.
That reminds me. Do you have a new boyfriend yet?
I heard you broke up, so I thought there might be someone else you like.
Ah, no, that's not exactly it...
I haven't really sorted out my feelings on the issue yet...
That's why, for now...
You're sorting them out.
Hey. Do you know how to forget about an old love?
You find a new love.
You should completely immerse yourself in it.
If that new love is true, then the old love will naturally become part of the past.
It's not that you can fall in love with someone new because you forgot the old...
It's because you fall in love with someone new that you're able to forget about the old.
Only love can heal a heart that was hurt by love.
Are you...
...talking about me?
Who knows?
Think about it and make your decision.
Whatever you do or don't do, you're the one who always makes the decision.
You're the one who always makes the decision...
Now, let's see how this all comes to rest.
Oh... we made enough to pay everyone...
I can't believe it, but that ripoff menu produced results...
Yamamoto-san, you're amazing!
It's all thanks to Yano.
Aren't we going to leave yet?
Just wait another ten minutes!
They said they're running late because of the traffic.
Hey! Line up, line up!
She's still alive within you.
It's impossible.
I can't make you happy.
I... plan to settle things soon.
It's impossible for you.
Hey, is it really all right for you to go out with me?
I'm famous for being the "stupid girl."
Your reputation will take a hit.
That's so dumb.
People who call other people stupid are stupid.
So... you think you're stupid.
Yeah. I know I am.
You don't know anything.
People are truly stupid when they can't even realize their own stupidity.
So don't ever call yourself stupid.
Ow! I fell over!
You're so stupid!
People who call other people stupid are stupid!
You turn them into memories.
The past holds as little reality as your dreams.
Hurry and realize that already.
And turn her into memories.
Let go.
You'll be fine, Yano...
...because you're so much smarter and stronger than that.
There's a ton of people here again this year!
Everyone, let them hear you shout!
Hey, you're going too fast!
Give some space to the people in front of you!
You're gonna wear yourselves out!
Hey, if it all goes well, I'll treat you to something.
What are you talking about?
You're going to confess, right?
Honestly, I'm not sure...
He's been my best friend since elementary school.
He's more important to me than my family is.
No one can replace him.
I... don't want to lose him.
So you'll choose friendship over love?
I don't want to lose either.
I wonder if I'm being selfish...
But...
...I think I'll take my chances.
Which is why you'd better treat me to something if I lose my best friend tonight.
This year really went by quickly...
Tsudzukanai ame ga furu
Endless rain keeps falling.
You think so?
Ah, come to think of it, Yano confessed to you on this day last year, didn't he?
Suzushi tsumetai ame
The cool, chilly rain.
Now that I think about it, it didn't even last a year.
Akanai tsudzuketeru
It continues to fall, refusing to let up,
Is it time to rotate yet?
Not yet. Wait until the next intersection.
Yano!
Kono kokoro wo tamotsu you ni
almost as if it's sustaining my feelings.
Who's that?
My old friends from middle school. They must've been bored tonight.
Itsu no hi ni mo mitsuketeita
I've always found your gentle back
Yasashi ushirosugata mawarikudoi omoi
on that day, but where do
Stop! Stop!
Wait for the traffic light!
Doko he mukau no
my winding feelings point?
Something interesting's bound to happen this year...
Kimi ga mitsumeru saki ni wa
I wonder what you see
Who will end up crying, and who will be left laughing?
Nani ga aru darou
before you?
Bokura wa hitahashiru
We keep running
If that new love is true...
Todokisou de todokanai
and it seems like we'll make it, but we don't.
Wait for the traffic light!
Sono toori de
Just like that.
Right now...
...give me just a little courage.
Shizuka ni ame ga furu
The rain continues to fall softly.
Please.
Sukoshi sabishii ame
A slightly lonely rain
Hirogaritsudzuketeru
will pour all around.
Kono kokoro wo nadameru you ni
It's as if it's meant to soothe my heart,
Itsumo kimi wo mitsumeteiru
I'm always looking at your
Kawaii ushirosugata mawarikudoi omoi
cute back, but these winding feelings
Mukou ni mukau no
point me in the other direction.
Boku ga motomeru saki ni wa
What's waiting for me
Nani ga matsu darou
at the end of my search?
Bokura wa hitahashiru
We keep on running
Oitsukesou de oitsaukunai
and it seems like we'll make it, but we don't.
Sono toori de
Just like that.
Bokura wa hitahashiru
We keep on running
Todokisou de todokanai
and it seems like we'll make it, but we don't.
Episode 16 Preview...
I'm glad you were my friend.
Sono toori de
Just like that.
You better make sure
you don't forget those words.
Sono toori de
Just like that.
That's dirty!
You're too naive.
Yano's headed
your way right now.
Sono toori de
Just like that.
And one more thing...
If my intuition's correct,
Takeuchi-kun's coming, too.
Sono toori de
Just like that.
No way...
Both of them are coming...
What'll I do...?
I'm still undecided
about my feelings...