Well, you might think number three's the weirdest one.
Oh, enough already.
Three. Yamamoto and I had sex.
Yeah, nothing but weird ones.
It's weird, isn't it?
It's so stupid.
I'm surprised you could think up something that weird...
Yeah.
Especially that third one... Even if you were just joking, that's just sick.
Yeah. It is sick.
No matter what happened...
I'll accept it.
Kisetsu ga sukoshi ugoita ki ga suru
I feel like the seasons have changed slightly
Hizashi mo mijikaku itsukazurete
and the sunbeams have thinned and will one day shift.
Futari no basu ha kawaranai machi
But I was relieved, knowing our bus
Hashitteiru koto...
was riding through...
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 12 ...
It's already been three days since I last spoke to Yano.
Yamamoto and I had sex.
I know Yano was hiding it because he was being kind, not because he was being fair.
But... she's Nana-san's little sister.
Were you lonely?
Or did you just see Nana-san in her?
Either way...
...you also betrayed her.
Whoa, Yano couldn't make a single basket.
No way, that's so unusual.
Oh, the boys are being tested right now.
Ah, goddamn it.
My record of making all five shots since I was in 4th grade...
It's easy to tell when you've got something on your mind.
It's a good thing you're not going to be a pro athlete.
That's fine, since I'm going to become a romance novelist.
Even with your B- essays?
That's out of the question.
I'll use my own story as the plot. I'll have a ton of material.
Am I a moron?
Maybe a little. You can be unexpectedly clumsy sometimes.
But I guess that'd be a compliment for a guy, huh?
It sounds a hundred times better than saying you're graceful.
But I can't really approve of that.
You're just a moron.
No matter how much I call her cellphone, she won't pick up.
She won't even look at me.
Keep calling her.
I've already called her fifty times.
Then call her a hundred times.
I'll be right there!
My.
Oh, my. Oh, my.
Tell him I'm asleep!
Even after he's come all the way out here?
I don't care! I don't want to see him right now!
I'm really sorry. Nanami's in the bath right now...
Don't tell him I'm in the bath! Tell him I'm asleep!
If I spoke with him now, I'd only be able to say cruel things.
I'll wait.
Umm... I understand how you feel, but... I think it might be best to leave her alone right now.
Sometimes it's easier to talk about things after everyone's calmed down a little.
By tomorrow, I'm sure Nanami will---
Can you really guarantee that things will be better by tomorrow?
I understand.
Please give those to her.
Oh my, oh my!
What beautiful flowers!
Please tell her "I'll see you tomorrow at school" for me.
Be careful on your way home!
Aren't these flowers wonderful?
Even after he came all this way to give you these...
I've raised an ogre as a daughter. Really.
D-Does he really think flowers will make everything better?
Who would fall for something like that?
Don't mess with me, you jerk!
Sometimes you really don't deserve him.
That man I don't deserve had sex with his ex-girlfriend's little sister.
But aren't the flowers splendid?
I wonder if his mother went through a lot of effort getting them to grow this beautifully?
Look at all of these roses.
You moron.
You moron...
You big moron...
This is so dumb...
They smell really good.
I'm sure he picked them all from his garden in a rush and wrapped them in a newspaper without thinking...
I wonder if he really rode a bus carrying this huge bouquet with him...
I wish I could rewrite my past.
If I could, I'd do all I could...
...if it would stop you from crying.
He's got me...
I'm going out for a bit!
Where are you going at this time of night?
To the bus stop!
You're not fair!
You're really not fair at all!
But...
But Yano...
...could've been hurting from it, too!
Yano!
I really wanted to tell him off, but...
...these are the only words that will come from my mouth!
I love you, you big moron!
Ah... I'm too soft...
I might not've been able to forgive him.
But when I see his face, I feel like I don't have any choice.
It's frustrating, but I still want to be beside him.
Like they say, you'll always give in to the other when you're in love...
Yeah.
Mizu-chin once told me I wouldn't be able to beat someone who's dead.
But I can't change his past.
So shouldn't I try to make the present as happy as possible?
Don't you think so?
Yeah.
Yano hates Nana-san.
I... hate her, too.
I don't want to speak badly of the dead...
...and I've never even met her, but...
But... Nana-san's not fair.
That's why I'm going to make Yano happy.
I must sound pretty dumb, huh?
No, that's great.
Could I warn you of something, though?
Yeah.
If it's just going to be a relationship of hardship and mental agony, you should put an end to it.
Why...?
We're going to be happy...
Where should we go on Sunday?
Ah, how about the zoo?
When I suggested the zoo before, you made fun of me!
Come on. Let's go see the monkeys!
I'm not in the mood for monkeys.
Then what are you in the mood for?
The beach!
No?
It's not that...
Girls really love the beach, huh?
I know of a beach near here that's not like the ones you see in pictures. Is that all right?
Yeah.
Then let's go to the beach.
If people could do things over, I wonder if they...
...would choose a different path to walk down?
Check out this kelp!
Ah, stop it!
See, see?
Would they choose the people they encounter...
...and choose the things that made them happy?
The sea's shining... it's so pretty.
I'm glad.
Aren't you glad we came?
Yes, yes. I'm glad. I'm glad.
Sheesh.
There's no one around.
We could probably do it over there if we used that as a bed.
Ow.
If they only picked the things that made them happy...
...how wonderful life would be.
Let's collect seashells!
I brought a jar with me.
What about this one?
Only the pretty-looking ones.
See? That one isn't.
What are you gonna do after collecting these?
Make them into a memory.
Takahashi, can I say something?
I can see your panties.
There aren't any cherry petal shells, huh?
Cherry petal shells?
You know, the pink ones.
Don't you think we'd have to go a little further south to find nice ones like that?
Ah, what about this one?
What?
You tickled me.
How?
What do you mean, "how"?
Takahashi, it's just a sea slater!
No, no!
No, no, no, no!
It won't bite. Don't wor--
Ah! A bug! Over here, too!
Gross, gross!
Let's go back! Let's go back!
Yano?
I'm sorry. I made too much of a fuss.
Let's go back.
But we just got here.
You hate bugs, don't you?
Not really...
It just surprised me a little...
Who are you... confusing me with?
Let's forget about...
...Nana-san.
Nana-san's not fair.
She lied to you, betrayed you, and left you all alone.
It makes sense for you to get angry.
You're right to hold a grudge.
You must want to complain to her, but you can't.
Because Nana-san's dead! She's no longer here!
Tell me here, now, Yano.
Tell you what?
Everything you've wanted to say. All about your grudge, or whatever.
There's nothing like that left.
That can't be true.
There has to be something you've wanted to say to her.
Oh, shush already. There's nothing.
"It pisses me off."
"You big idiot."
"Drop dead."
I'll listen to everything you have to say.
If Nana-san were here, what would you say?
If Nana-san...
...were here...
I promise.
Hey, you guys are in the same class as Yuri, right?
I'm sorry, but could you lend me some cash?
He left without paying.
Yuuhi ga kage wo hosoku nobashita
The sunset stretches my shadow long and thin.
They call that sort of thing "being blind".
You haven't really fallen in love with anyone before.
They call people like you "immature know-it-alls".
Kokoro wo fukaku somete yuku
Its colors deeply dye my heart.
Hurry and really fall in love.
Kitto saigo no jikan da to
When you said this was probably the last time,
Do you still think he's gonna come?
Namida koraeteta
I held back my tears.
He won't.
Then why are you waiting around?
To gather my rage.
That's not a hand warmer. It's a drink.
Omoide nante itsumo kanashisugiru bakari
Memories are always too sad.
Isso wasurete shimaitai yo
I just want to forget them all.
Hey... what do you think I should do?
Nido to aenai kimi senaka to
I continued to watch the last sunset
What? Figure out your own problems yourself.
Because I'm a moron, I don't know!
Saigo no yuuhi mitsumetsudzuketa
and your back that I would never see again.
I could tell you, but in exchange, you better do as I say.
Itsumo itsumo yasashisugita ne
You were always too kind.
Will it make me happy?
Ima wa ososugiru keredo
And even though it's too late now...
What's happiness?
I don't know.
Probably something where no one cries or gets yelled at.
Stop the sunset kimi wo ushinaitakunai
Stop the sunset. I don't want to lose you.
Where no one gets hit or has stuff thrown at them.
Something like that.
Am I wrong?
I don't know.
Sora wo dakishimete tsutsumikomu you ni
Like the sky enveloping me,
What's up with that!
Then... why don't we both go searching for our own happiness?
Sotto utsumuita kimi no yokogao
your face would always look down at me.
If you saw her now, what would you tell her?
Yuuhi yo kono mama shizumanaideite
Make it so the sun never sets...
Tell me what you're feeling.
You're... a liar.
Itsumo sugoshita futari no heya to umi wo aruita photograph
The room we always lived in, that photograph when we walked on the beach...
What you're saying and what you're doing are contradictory.
I promise I won't betray you.
That you absolutely won't betray me.
Hitotsu kawashita yakusoku ga hatasezu sugite yuku
The promise we made will go unkept.
Yeah.
There's no second chance.
I promise.
Kokorobosoku natteta hitori no heya ni suwatte tooku ni kikoeru amaoto
I became so lonely alone in my room, listening to the distant rain.
Itsuka...
One day...
Yano!
How can I hate...
...the woman I loved so much?
Ya...
Everything...
I'll forgive you for everything.
So, please... I want you to come back to me alive.
Come back to life...
That's why I'm going to make Yano happy.
That's why... we need to make my past pale in comparison to our present.
I swear it on the stars.
If there's a shooting star, I wish to be with Nana-chan forever.
I love you.
You liar...
Yano...
I... can't do this anymore.
I can't make you happy.
I'm sorry for not being able to keep our promise...
Yano made his wish long ago...
Anata no yobugoe kikoeta ki ga shite
I felt as if I heard you calling out for me.
Takahashi...
Nana-chan.
Omowazu atari wo boku ha miwatashita
Without thinking, I looked around.
Nana.
Kaze no itazura da yo
It was just the wind pulling a prank on me.
Nana...
Unless he hated her... Yano seems like he'd be crushed by all of the sadness...
Oka no ue dare mo inai
There's no one on the hill.
That was his way to protect himself...
Give me a promise.
Futari wakareta toki to
The sky's the same color
Promise me that you'll never leave my side.
Onaji sora no iro
as on the day when we broke up.
I wonder why people... make promises they won't be able to keep...
Itsuka kisetsu ha futatabi meguri
One day, the seasons will change again,
Oka ni ue ni ha hana mo saku no ni
Even though flowers are blooming on the hill.
Who betrayed who?
Mou ai no hibi ha
Those days of love
Mou kaeranai yo
will never return.
Subete ha yume no naka sa
It's all a dream now.
Yuri-chan.
I was dumped.
Are you satisfied?
You said "serves you right" before as well, didn't you?
Takahashi-san's pretty gutless, huh? I didn't expect that.
Tooku no machinami akaruku hi ga sasu
The bright sunbeams glint off the distant houses and stores.
Do you want me to comfort you again?
As if I'll ever fall for that again.
Chiisana takaramono ga
My small things are
Hashi wo watatteru
already crossing over the bridge.
Totemo yasashii machi
It's such a gentle city,
Keredo mou ima ha tsurai
But right now, it's painful to me.
Everyone was dreaming...
Futari aishita toki ga
When we were both in love with each other,
...happy dreams.
amari utsushiku
it was just too beautiful.
Boku no kokoro ni ikiteiru kara
Those days still live on in my heart,
Hitori kore kara boku ha doushiyou
but I don't know what to do from now on.
Mou ai no hibi ha
Those days of love
Mou kaeranai yo
will never return.
Subete ha yume no naka sa
It's all a dream now.
Mou ai no hibi ha
Those days of love
Mou kaeranai yo
will never return.
Mou ai no hibi ha
Those days of love
Mou kaeranai yo
will never return.
Subete ha yume no naka sa
It's all a dream now.
Episode 13 Preview...
I regret what I did
so much that I want to die.
Back then... back at that place...
those actions I took...
Everything I choose
is always wrong.
But I want you to listen to me...
...Takahashi.
I...
What I told you this
morning was my final notice.
Didn't I tell you
that you'd regret it?
Sorry!
I can't hold back anymore!