Don't you want to know...
...why Onee-chan was riding...
...in Kagawa's car that day?
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 11 ...
On that day two years ago, I was with Onee-chan.
We were both out shopping.
You hadn't called or texted her, so Onee-chan was feeling down all morning.
Did you two have a fight?
Not really.
You've been obsessed with your cell phone this whole time.
It's so stupid.
He should just apologize already.
Yeah, I know!
And that's when he drove by.
Kagawa.
Onee-chan's ex. The worst man ever, who had a habit of beating her.
Want a ride?
That's quite all right.
What's up with that? You're awfully cold.
What happened to your little boyfriend?
What was his name again? Yano?
He left you alone on a beautiful day like this?
Mind your own business.
Nana.
Happy birthday.
I had also completely forgotten.
July 29th.
It was Onee-chan's birthday.
It makes sense why she was waiting for her cell phone to ring all day, doesn't it?
Wait a second.
She got into his car over a simple "happy birthday"?
I guess she'd go all the way to his house with a "Merry Christmas"...
...and straight to a hotel with a simple "I love you, let's get back together."
There's really no saving her.
You should've...
...apologized to her sooner.
But you were too late.
Do you regret it?
You tried calling her...
...that afternoon.
"I'm sorry"?
Of all the things she left behind, I checked Onee-chan's cell phone.
I guess you didn't want to text her.
Important things should be spoken out loud, I suppose.
You must've wanted to apologize, right?
But unfortunately, she didn't pick up.
You called at 4:15 PM.
Conveniently, that was when she was out driving with Kagawa.
Onee-chan's accident was at 4:38 PM.
Who knows why Onee-chan didn't pick up the phone.
Stop it.
Stop it...
Why are you telling Yano this sort of stuff now?
Why did you decide to finally come tell him something from two years ago now?
Takahashi.
Why are you trying to confuse him with all of this stuff?
What are you trying to get out of this, Yamamoto-san?
Don't worry about it, go back inside.
I have to worry.
I'll be fine.
Yeah, don't worry.
There's nothing to worry about.
Not a single thing happened.
So relax and go back inside like a good girl, Takahashi-san.
This all happened in the past.
It has nothing to do with you at all.
Yano...?
What are you trying to do?
Some kind of revenge?
Harassment?
Are you saying it's my fault she was riding in his car?!
You're saying I'm cold-hearted for not going to the funeral?!
Is it because I wasn't with her on her birthday?
In that case, tell me why she didn't answer her phone!
She couldn't pick it up because she was with Kagawa?
She got what she deserved!
Yano?
That's a pretty rude way of speaking about the dead.
Just because she's dead doesn't mean her sins have gotten lighter.
Even after she started going out with me, she was never through with Kagawa.
I can't hear anything.
Then, what about your sin?
What about...
...your own sin?
Have you forgotten about that day two years ago?
That day, two years ago...
Yano, what are you doing?
If we don't hurry, Mom will come back.
There was a cat.
A cat?
A black cat. A really small one.
Today's... Friday, right?
Black cats are bad luck when they cross your path.
Hurry up.
What is it?
It's nothing...
Just tell me already.
You've been like this the whole time.
Isn't this your first time?
It is.
Did you get cold feet or something?
Don't talk like that.
You... hadn't forgotten about Onee-chan at all.
You betrayed both me and her...
...at the same time.
Or did you just try to use me as a replacement for her?
Everything is going exactly how you want it to, isn't it?
Are you satisfied?
Go home.
Let me...
...lighten your sin a little.
In Onee-chan's incoming call history...
...a lot were from Kagawa.
It wasn't just that day.
It looked like they were talking all summer.
She betrayed you first.
Aren't you glad?
Did Yamamoto-san go home?
A-Ah, Yeah.
That's good.
You're leaving?
Hey, wait up!
Takahashi.
That hurt!
You hit me with the corner of your bag!
Why are you so fast to throw things at me?
Hey! I'm bleeding!
Hey, Takahashi!
Wait!
You liar!
Why am I an outsider?!
Why couldn't you let me hear what she had to say?!
You're hiding something, aren't you?!
I'm not hiding anything...
You're the one who said there'd be no secrets between us!
You tell me not to betray you, but you go and betray me!
Takahashi, betraying someone isn't like that.
Should I tell you what it means to betray someone?
It's when you never treat someone special, walk all over him, tear him to pieces, and then abandon him.
Can't you tell how special you are to me?
Can't you tell how hard I'm trying to keep us together?
When have I ever betrayed you?
When did I ever toss you away?!
Yano...
It hurts...
Just go home by yourself.
When did I ever toss you away?!
Does Yano think Nana-san tossed him away?
It's when you never treat someone special, walk all over him, tear him to pieces...
I never would have thought such words could come from Yano's mouth...
You'll never...
...understand how I feel.
What can I do...
...to get closer to Yano's heart?
Isn't loving him enough?
Can't my love become his strength?
I want him to trust me...
No matter what happened...
...I'll accept it.
Definitely don't do something stupid like tell Takahashi about it.
Just try telling her the truth.
You'll regret it for rest of your life.
I won't tell her.
There's no way I can.
Besides...
Besides?
It was just with Yamamoto that time.
That's all.
But you regret it, don't you?
Regret?
I don't regret anything I've done.
Never have, never will.
Why are you hiding it, then?
Because I don't want to see her cry.
She'll cry, without a doubt.
That's why I'm not going to tell her.
In other words, you regret it.
I don't regret it.
I don't.
I just feel like I... screwed up a little.
It's kinda hard to talk to him...
I've been thinking about it yesterday and today this whole time, and now it's lunch break already.
Nana! Everyone's going to play dodgeball.
Ah... I have to take care of the class's day book, so go on without me.
Daily
helper
Okay.
It's so quiet.
Everything that happened yesterday seems so unreal.
Yano and Yamamoto are pretending it didn't happen, too.
It's weird.
Takahashi.
You forgot your English book yesterday, right?
I brought it with me.
Don't you need your text book?
Won't you be in trouble in fifth period without it?
Nana-chan, they're gonna call on you today, you know.
I guess you couldn't do your homework since you didn't have your textbook, right?
Man, that must suck!
Completely
forgot
about it
Completely
forgot
about it
I thought you might be called on today, so I translated all of the sentences for you last night.
I wrote them all out for you.
I was up until 2 AM.
Thank you...
You're welcome!
In the end, I just can't hate him.
Yano, your drawing...
I'm good at it, aren't I?
He's awful at it.
Yet... he did all this for me...
Yano.
I love you more than anyone else in the world.
That's why, Yano...
Because I love you, I don't like being deceived.
If you understand what I'm trying to say...
...then talk to me.
Talk to me.
I'll be fine.
No matter what happened...
...I'll accept it.
Here's three choices!
One. I confessed my love to Yamamoto, and was turned down.
Two. Yamamoto confessed her love to me, and I turned her down.
Three. Yamamoto and I were in love with each other.
Now, which is true?
N-Number two?
Bzzt.
One?
Three?
Bzzt!
Ah, that was just a warm up!
What?
For real this time.
One. I sexually harassed Yamamoto.
I've had enough already.
This is so stupid...
Ah... two. Yamamoto stalked me.
Geez, just forget it.
What? We're still in the middle of the questions.
Yano, you're just trying to sneak out of it.
You never intended to discuss this seriously.
I am being serious.
It's too weird, you moron.
Well, you might think number three's the weirdest one.
Oh, enough already.
Three. Yamamoto and I had sex.
Yeah, nothing but weird ones.
It's weird, isn't it?
It's so stupid.
I'm surprised you could think up something that weird...
Yeah.
Especially that third one... Even if you were joking, that's just sick.
Yeah. It is sick.
No matter what happened...
I'll accept it.
Kisetsu ga sukoshi ugoita ki ga suru
I feel like the season have changed slightly
Hizashi mo mijikaku itsuka zurete
and the sunbeams have thinned and will one day shift.
Futari no basu wa kawaranai machi
But I was relieved, knowing our bus
Hashitteiru koto hotto shiteta
was riding through our unchanged city.
Mado no soto itsumo mitai ni miteru anata
You always gaze up at me from outside my window
You'll regret it for the rest of your life.
I don't regret anything I've done.
Never have, never will.
Soshite watashi mo mane wo shiteru
and I mimic you by doing the same
I just feel like I... screwed up a little.
I just feel...
Itsumo mitai ni
like always.
...like I did something stupid.
Nee futari wa onaji na no ka na
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Ikitai basho wa namattetatte iin da yo ne
Even if the place we want to go to has gotten dull, it's all right.
Nee futari wa onaji na no ka na
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Itoshiii kimochii anata no shisen wa ima mienakute
I still feel love for you, but you're no longer looking at me.
Nee futari wa onaji na no ka na
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Ikitai basho wa namattetatte iin da yo ne
Even if the place we want to go to has gotten dull, it's all right.
Nee futari wa onaji na no ka na
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Itoshiii kimochii anata no shisen wa ima mienakute
I still feel love for you, but you're no longer looking at me.
Episode 12 Preview ...
Yano...
I... can't do this anymore.
I can't make you happy.
I'm sorry
I can't keep our promise...
Everyone was dreaming...
...happy dreams.