With his face shimmering brightly in the pitch black darkness...
...and his eyes like all the stars in the sky gathering as one...
...he told me that eternity does exist.
Even now, I clearly remember how he was that night, when he was only seventeen years old.
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 20 ...
Huh? The girl from the hook-up party the other day?
Yeah. As it turns out, I'm seeing her again this weekend.
But meeting her by myself is a little embarrassing.
You, embarrassed? That's a rare sight.
Not me! Her.
She asked if she could come with a friend.
So, would you come, too?
What? Go see her by yourself! Such a pain.
Please! Pretty please?
You only have to stay for half the time! So won't you come, friend of mine?
Get someone else.
You're the only guy I know who's always doing nothing!
See you at 1 PM tomorrow at the plaza in front of the station!
Yano?
What jacket are you going to wear on Sunday?
Huh? Why do you ask?
If you're not going to wear one, I was thinking of wearing my stadium jumper.
You know, my red one.
Oh, that one? The one that looks a lot like mine, right?
Why wouldn't you?
If we both wore the same one, we'd have that whole couple look going, and that'd be kinda scary.
What's wrong with the couple look?
No, don't say that! Don't you dare wear yours, okay?
Oh, what should I do?
Geez.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Hey!
This is my friend. He was with us the other day, remember?
Oh, right! Hi there.
Hey.
So, let's get going!
Why don't we go get a cup of tea?
You really know what hits the spot! Where should we go?
It's nice having you as a fellow tag-along today.
Ah, yeah! Same with you.
You see, I can't really handle really spicy food.
That's fine! Why don't we have something you like?
Here you go! Open wide!
Did he really need me to come along...?
The other day...
At the hook-up party, you sat on the far right the whole time, didn't you?
I was on the left, so we never got a chance to speak, right?
Ah... yeah... was it like that?
Yeah! Are you sure you just don't like hook-up parties?
No...
Then, do you remember my name?
Sorry... I'm really sorry. I'm bad at remembering names.
It's alright. I never really stand out at those things anyway.
That's not true! You're cute, Chisa!
Yeah! Chisa-chan, you were the most popular girl there! No joke!
Though you're my number one, my cute little Mai!
Oh, you're so honest! Open wide!
He's good...
Is it good?
It is!
I'm glad!
Even though you were the most popular, you're just a tag-along today?
Well... I really think you have to like the person back, or it won't work.
Ah, really?!
You couldn't be more right! I feel the same way.
Takeuchi-kun... don't you have someone you like?
Ah... yeah.
But... it ended up not working out.
That's why I got all desperate and ended up going to that hook-up party.
It must be hard getting over that sort of stuff, huh?
Yeah...
It sure was good!
It was a good meal!
Where should we go next?
Wherever you want Mai-chan.
A perfect escape!
Those two should be fine by themselves.
It's hard to believe she thought it would be embarrassing by herself.
Let's leave them alone.
Later.
Good work today.
The bus I take is this way.
So, umm... have a safe trip home, Miyata-san.
Umm...!
It was all a lie! I had those two set this whole thing up for me.
I just really wanted to see you again!
Since I didn't have a chance to talk to you the other day.
And when I actually had the chance today, you turned out to be the type of person I thought you were...
A really, really nice person.
I'm sorry for lying and fooling you like this.
I know you don't like these sorts of things.
But would you please consider hanging out with me some more?
Would you please give me a chance and go out with me for just one month?
You're so heavy...
Lala... don't jump on me...
Lalami. Lala.
Nana... Nanami. You're heavy.
Don't get on top of me like that.
Just kidding.
Sign: A refreshing Sunday morning.
What the heck is this, first thing in the morning?
We'll be borrowing your room today.
It's time to celebrate...
...Take-chan's first girlfriend!
Apparently, the girl asked him to give her a chance, and to go out with her for a month!
Ah, you just can't turn down those sorts of things!
Oh, here he comes! Hurry and prepare the party poppers!
Hurry! Hurry!
But don't you think the whole time limit thing is awesome?
After all, you never really know until you go out.
Congrats!
I... have plans for today, guys.
Dumbass.
Nana-chan, I'm sorry!
Nana-chan...
Red jacket
It totally skipped my mind. I didn't do it on purpose. I swear.
After I went on and on about it the day before last.
I'm sorry.
You don't listen to anything I say.
Before I left, things were a little crazy...
What else could you have possibly been thinking about when you put it on?
What are you doing?!
I'll take you somewhere nice. So, forgive me?
I won't be tricked so easily.
We shall see, won't we?
Anyway, put on your jacket.
Sign: Pet Land
They're so adorable! I could just eat them all up!
My Lalami is the best, though!
Ah, it's a corgi.
Parakeets
There are squirrels over here.
Wait a sec! I'm gonna make this my background.
It was so much fun, wasn't it?
You look refreshed.
I could definitely own a corgi.
The kittens were so cute!
But my Lalami's the best.
Hey... do you think you can fall in love with someone you don't like to begin with?
What's this, so out of the blue?
For example, even if you don't like someone, you still go out with them and force yourself to fall for them.
I like someone now I used to hate.
Really? Who?
You.
What? You hated me?
When we were freshmen, yeah. Why are you so shocked?
Didn't he realize...?
D-Don't they say love and hate are two sides of the same coin?
You get mad because they're "stuck in your head", right?
Didn't you say something like that before?
But some things never go right with these things, don't you think?
What doesn't?
Your feelings.
How so?
For example...
A couple in red!
That's really popular, huh?
Yano, let's not holds hands!
It's fine! Just forget that ugly woman!
You moron! Doofus!
For example, when your boyfriend's being a complete moron and you want to kick him...
...his smile ends up being too cute, and you forgive him.
You always give in to your feelings.
Love is the opposite of great effort, don't you think?
Tell that to him, would you?
Never mind.
I love you, Nana-chan.
Will love come to Ms. Mizuguchi Kana?
How will the last episode turn out?
Will she fall in wonderful love, or will someone fall in wonderful love with her?
"Come to me, love! Come love, come!"
Mizuguchi Kana will now sing "Come On, My Love"!
Come on my love!
Like I've been saying, it has to be love when girls take off their glasses.
It's so obvious now!
But who'd go out with her?
I'll pass.
You don't even have a girlfriend!
You're evil to suggest someone like that!
Well, you are single!
They don't suit you.
I'm just not used to them yet.
Dirt gets in them so easily.
Your eyes are bright red, like a rabbit's.
You look better in glasses.
Ms. Rabbit.
I'm gonna go get another ball.
Hey, Moto.
Why are you getting so mad?
I'm not.
There are things you just can't know until you try going out.
Just try going out with her for a month.
"Well, it looks like I really couldn't fall for you. Sorry!"
It would've been much better to decline at the beginning.
Hey!
Saying you'll "try going out for a month" is the same as saying you'll keep going out after a month!
I know!
I've been prepared for that much since the beginning.
Don't underestimate me, moron.
Oh? So you'll go out with her even though you don't like her?
You sure like to volunteer for anything, huh?
I'm going out with her to fall for her!
You won't.
You sound so sure of yourself, huh?
After all, you've never fallen for someone who's fallen for you first.
It might happen!
I don't think so. I'd go so far as to swear it won't.
Then what do you suggest?
Don't go out with some girl you don't even like. You're just wasting time!
I don't want to hear that coming from you.
You just think about making your own girl not cry!
What the hell did you say?!
What?
Hey!
You little...!
Wh... What's the matter?
J-Just some advice on how to style his hair.
For the hottest and coolest look this fall.
Don't you think it'd look cool to lengthen your sideburns some more?
Just take some from the left.
Ah, I was just thinking the same thing!
It's all about the lack of balance, right?
But... isn't that Yano's hair in your hand?
You're already losing this much hair!
Here, I'll give it back.
Th-This could be bad!
Blood... Takeuchi-kun, you're bleeding.
They say if you lick it, it'll heal!
Lick, lick, lick!
Oh, thank you!
Are you sure you two weren't fighting?
Us? Of course not!
Moto, I went too far. Sorry.
It's fine. After all, I'm usually the one going too far.
I do understand what you're saying. You're right.
But I... need to move forward.
Try to understand.
What kind of girl is she?
Like Kanno Miho...
Note: A famous Japanese actress and J-Pop singer.
Kanno?
Take her, and make her a little more plain.
No idea what you're talking about...
She's really pale.
But...
I think she's a good girl.
Takahashi! Over here!
I brought your notebook.
You could've just brought it to school tomorrow...
There was no reason to come out this late.
That's all right.
And here are some steamed meat buns.
Steamed meat buns?
So I heard Takeuchi-kun got a girlfriend?
Why can't you be happy for him?
That's no good, Yano.
Because it's not like him.
Umm... I think love that you have to work at is also all right.
What's up with that? You're weird.
I'm not too sure myself.
You're too split on the issue.
I wanted Take to go out with a girl he actually liked.
After all, he's a really good guy.
Yeah.
That's why everything will be all right!
Since the girl he's going out with is a girl who can understand that goodness in him.
It'll definitely turn out okay!
W-What?
Your hair's wet.
Ah, maybe. I took a bath earlier tonight.
You'll catch a cold like that! Don't tell me those are your PJ's?
Take my sweater.
It's all right! You'll catch a cold!
I've got a lot on underneath, so I'm fine.
Then should I warm you up some more?
It'll be too embarrassing if someone walks by! Stop!
She's... not wearing a bra!
Oh, yeah. I've got a bandana in my pocket.
There you go.
This way, your head should be protected from the cold.
Little Red Riding Hood!
I'd like to go on a trip with you, Takahashi.
Ah, I know we can't go, not yet.
We're in no hurry.
And it doesn't have to be a full-blown trip...
I'd just like to go somewhere... someplace where we can be alone together.
Someplace where no one can disturb us.
Someplace where we don't have to think about having to go home later...
...or where we don't have to go our separate ways for the evening.
I want to hurry and become an adult...
I want to hurry and become an adult... so I can come and steal you away.
If only... there was such a thing as eternity.
There is.
It does exist. I'm sure of it.
Ima kimi ga iikaketa kotoba ga
The words you were just about to say
Yubisaki ni sotto oritekita
fell softly onto my fingertips.
Nanimo iwanakute ii yo
You don't have to say anything.
With his face shimmering brightly in the pitch black darkness...
Tsumaida yubi wo gyutto atatamete
I'll clasp your hand tightly and warm it up.
...and his eyes like all the stars in the sky gathering as one...
Kotoba wa kotoba dakara kokoro hanbun mo tsutaenai kara
Because words are words, I can't express half of the feelings in my heart.
...he told me that eternity does exist.
Even now, I clearly remember how he was that night, when he was only seventeen years old.
Setsunakute modokashikute yuuyake futari wo tsutsundeiru
It's so wrenching and irritating as the sunset engulfs the two of us.
Even though we're now both adults, we know there's no such thing as eternity.
Now that we're no longer kids...
Komiageru mune no omoi kokoro ga itai yo
My heart aches from all the feelings welling up inside of me.
But back then... time truly stopped, and we were the only people in the world.
That moment was so real... and yet so dreamlike...
It felt like it only lasted a moment... yet also an eternity.
Within our youthful hearts at the time, I'm sure eternity really existed.
Moshi kimi ga tabibito ni nattara
If you were to become a traveler,
Hello?
Ah, yeah. I saw your message.
Yeah, it's no problem. It's really no problem at all!
Kore gurai kimi wo matteru darou
would I be able to wait for you as I do now?
Yeah. Then, see you tomorrow in front of the station.
Kisetsu wa kawaru sono tabi ni
As the seasons change,
Kioku ga usuragu koto ga attemo
even if our memories are to fade.
However...
dareka wo konna fuu ni kokoro ippai de aisenai kara
I wouldn't be able to love someone with all of my heart like this.
Everyone...
...eventually becomes an adult.
Mamaritai taisetsu na kimi
I want to protect the precious you.
Itsu datte futari wa hitori ja nai
The two of us are never alone.
Kono mune ga kawaresou de
Me heart feels so fragile
Furete hoshii yo
and I want you to touch it.
Setsunakute modokashikute kaerenai kono mama aruiteitai
It's so wrenching and irritating that I can't go home. I want to keep walking like this.
Yabaisaki ni kanjiteiru kokoro no kotoba wo
I feel the words from your heart on my fingertips.
Episode 21 Preview ...
Why don't you sleep
over on Sunday night?
I thought we'd be able
to be together all day, so...
Yamamoto's mom collapsed...
...and I'm with her
at the hospital right now.
Why today, of all days...
...do you choose
Yamamoto-san over me...?
What the hell are you doing?!
I love you...
I've loved you this whole time...