I-It's fine by me...
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 9 ...
For some reason, it's come to this...
And I don't know how...
...it's come to this...
But... I really don't understand how I was the one to suggest it...
Ah, geez! He's already getting naked!
If I were to say something like "let's stop here" now...
I can't...
I-It's embarrassing, so turn around.
Okay.
I... I can't make a fuss about this now.
Y-You can turn around now.
You haven't taken anything off.
I-It's okay like this.
I'll take everything off one by one...
No, instead... you undress me.
Wow...
I can't believe I said something as stupid...
...as telling him to take off my clothes!
But at a time like this...
...I don't know what to do, or what to say...
Takahashi.
Y-Yes?!
Raise your head.
B-But... I don't know where to look.
Don't worry, Takahashi.
Just think of it like you're at the beach.
This is the beach.
You're on the sandy dunes.
I'm in swimming trunks.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Now, why don't you change into your bikini, Nana-chan?
Crap! I laughed!
But... I see.
This is the beach.
The beach.
The beach!
If you're scared, we can stop here.
I don't want to make you regret this.
Takahashi, I want to do something that will make us both happy.
Didn't I tell you?
I don't just want your body.
If you feel like you're pushing yourself even a little, then it's wrong.
Don't make a mistake.
I want love.
I know... I'm not making a mistake.
Please make me your own.
Hurry!
Hurry...
This is bad... even I'm starting to get nervous.
I see... so even guys get nervous.
I see...
Well... without holding back...
...I will let you give yourself to me.
Huh? My Japanese is weird.
I'll have you.
Well, whatever.
If it hurts, please raise your right hand.
Are you a dentist or something?
I won't regret this at all.
There's no way I will.
Mom, Dad... I'm sorry.
I have someone I want to devote everything to.
Everything...
...to the one precious to me, who's difficult to replace...
...with anything else in the world.
Encountering him must have been destiny.
And if anyone says differently, I won't believe in destiny at all.
But even despite that, I wonder if I've been dreaming?
Ever since that day...
...there's just been so much fortune... beauty... fascination...
...that the reality seems so dreamlike.
Or is this all just a dream that seems so realistic?
A dream?
Ah, it's Yano.
Huh? Why's he wearing a happi coat?
A happy dream? What's that?
Huh? He was talking about something else when he wore the happi coat...
The words they say at weddings sure are nice, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
For a Christmas present... give me a promise.
Not that, Yano...
Is this all just a dream?
Or is this reali--
Ow!
It's reality!
It's reality! Thank goodness!
But... it hurts!
I think this sorta hurts, Yano!
Right hand, right hand!
Ah, yeah. Sorry, Takahashi.
Just stick with it for now!
Sorry.
Think of something else right now!
How?!
Think of something fun.
Like what?!
Umm... like you're cramming your mouth full of those steamed meat buns you love so much.
Yeah, something full of happiness like that!
What's up with that?!
Your mom's back!
Crap! Get dressed! Get dressed!
Our study stuff is downstairs!
I'll bring it with me, so sneak out of the house!
Ah! She must've seen my shoes!
Hurry!
I can never show my face in front of your mom ever again...
Don't worry about it.
Shouldn't something else be bugging you more?
After all, her coming home was the worst punch line ever...
Yeah, I guess so...
Isn't it funny? Like, really funny?
It's just so like us.
Ah, sorry. Did I hurt your feelings?
Yeah, I'm a guy, after all.
Anyway, Yano, you're dressed pretty lightly, aren't you?
I was in a rush.
Don't be disappointed, Yano.
But... I made such a huge thing out of it, and now I look completely uncool.
And anyway, didn't it feel like a play, with all of those overdramatic lines?
Yeah...
Is this supposed to be a theatre? Who do you think you are?
Please make me your own.
I feel embarrassed about it now.
But... I was moved by it.
I'm so glad the person I love is Yano.
But there's no chance that we'll make this an anniversary, huh?
For our first...
No... you see...
I didn't even enter you!
Though, I think you know that yourself.
No penetration. No nothing.
Not even my head.
Ah... is that so...?
Yes.
Should we head back, then?
Will things be okay with your mom?
I'll pretend like nothing happened.
Ah, damn it!
Why'd the old hag have to come home at a time like that?!
I was almost there!
My house is no good at all! Totally out of the question!
I love you.
"Up until now, I've just thought of sex as a sport!"
"But I was wrong."
"Sex is something sacred."
What's that? Who told you that?
Yano.
You serious?
Last night, he came over to my place and said that with a straight face.
Does he have a loose screw or something?
Or what? Is he really that into his current girlfriend?
Did he have sex with Takahashi?
Yeah, didn't you hear?
No...
Is that her name? What's she like? I've never seen her before.
Ah... I saw them walking and holding hands once, but...
...she's kind of round.
Round?
She's really normal.
She's so normal that you'd be surprised.
But she's a good girl.
Well, isn't it fine the way it is, though?
How so?
It means he's starting to heal from what happened with Nana-san, right?
Who knows about that one?
But you know, the one left behind just has to keep living.
You should do more than just that. You should have the time of your life.
Welcome!
Your finest sake, please.
Speaking of which, he had a couple screws loose when he was going out with Nana-san too, didn't he?
Only 8,000 yen. A special bargain, just for you! But you have to pay up-front.
How about it?
That's a little expensive. You sure you're not overcharging?
I bought them for 14,000 yen, and they're practically right out of the box.
It's not expensive at all.
How many times have you worn them?
Maybe two or three times?
You're lying. They're dirty.
Clean them off with an eraser.
Then, how about this?
You still have more stuff?
I'll throw in a cap and this one-of-a-kind secret figure as a special service.
What's up with that?
10,000 yen altogether.
You're raising the price!
What's going on over there?
What's up with you, anyway?
What do you want to buy so badly?
Yano came to sell today.
Why's that?
For the shoes alone, 3,000 yen.
7,500.
3,250.
6,000.
3,500. I won't go any higher.
I couldn't even pay for a hotel room with that.
I'll get him. He's at the end of his rope.
If you were selling your One Stars, I wouldn't mind paying 8,000 yen.
Does he stare at my feet?!
Screw you. I'm not selling them.
8,000 yen's too cheap in the first place, moron.
Then I'll pay for them using my Internet account.
I need the cash right now. I'm in a rush.
Hey, Yano-kun. I'll buy this.
How much is it?
2,000 yen.
What are you saying? You're so funny.
Here you go.
What a cruel, cold world...
No... I think you're the cruel one here, no matter how I look at it.
And I had my hair just right, too...
What do you mean, you had it just right?
It'll all fall apart...
Like a marimo youkan?
He smells good...
Yano... there's some strange rumors going around.
Strange rumors?
That you've become a miser.
Sign: A miser ~~
Are you saving up for a hotel room...?
Yeah... my house is just too dangerous.
And I don't know when my parents will be out again.
Ah... about that...
I've done a lot of thinking about it too, but...
I... kinda think that love hotels...
...are not really what I want.
Ah, yeah.
Yeah... you're right, I guess.
You'd prefer...
Yeah, so...
Since we kinda rushed the other day...
...I was thinking I really want to make it something special in the right situation.
If you're going out of your way, I'd like to go somewhere like hot springs or the beach.
That way it'll become a memory, right?
Y-Yeah.
I... guess so...
It'll... become a... memory...
The hotel fee... the train fee...
And if it were Tokyo Disneyland, it would be even better!
How much is that...?
H-How much would that all cost?
And so... here!
Let's both save up, little by little.
It might take some time, but I'm sure we'll double the happiness!
H-Huh?
W-We'll save up?
We'll really both save up for it?
Yeah!
O-Okay.
I'll gamble on Takahashi's smile.
I wonder if it'll take about half a year?
And it's really okay with you, right?
Yeah!
We'll probably have enough in time for our graduation class trip...
I sometimes think...
Takeuchi!
This is the newest issue!
Oh! Let me see!
...that the happiness I feel right now once belonged to someone else long ago.
I sorta feel like I'm being gypped here.
I definitely am.
How much have you saved so far?
721 yen.
It sure is pretty.
Yeah.
Yano...
Let's go see the fireworks this summer.
It's my dream.
Okay.
I want to go to the festival, the Kiri Festival, and the beach, all together with you!
Let's create a ton of memories together.
I don't really like the word "memory".
Why not?
No reason. In my Japanese class in elementary school, I read a story.
What story?
A story called "What Color Was That Girl's Dress?"
Heard of it?
Nope...
Two girls, named A and B are recalling an old story together.
They get into this discussion about a picture hanging on the wall of one of the staircase landings in their elementary school.
A picture of a girl picking flowers in front of a deep red sunset...
You really never read this?
Nope.
A says, "Oh! How nostalgic. You're talking about the picture of the girl in a pretty yellow dress, right?"
But then B says, "No, the dress she was wearing was red, just like the sunset!"
"No, it was red!"
"No, it was definitely yellow."
"Alright, then why don't we go see for ourselves?"
The two of them, filled with excitement, reached the old, nostalgic school building.
"What color was that girl's dress?"
What color was it?
It...
...didn't have a color.
It was just a black and white picture.
The dress that dark silhouette wore was scribbled completely black.
Yet in their memories, both bickering girls were sure that the dress in the picture had a color.
See? Human memories are too vague.
Thinking something has color when it doesn't, making things more dramatic than they really are, glorifying things...
It gives new, greater meaning than was actually there.
That's why I don't believe any of this talk about "beautiful memories".
What do you believe in, then?
You.
Absolutely you.
What's right in front of me now.
Nana, wanna come shopping with me today?
Shoot! I dropped her stuff all over the place!
Whose is this?
Yamamoto-san's.
She'll get really mad at us.
I have a copy of this, too.
So Yamamoto-san also reads poetry books...
...even though she's always reading all that hard stuff, too.
Nana, hurry up and give it!
Ah, yeah!
She won't notice we dropped it, right?
W-What am I gonna do? I took it as soon as I saw it.
They're a little younger, and...
...it's Yano, and to his left, Takeuchi-kun.
And... this is probably... Nana-san.
Why does Yamamoto-san have...
Kisetsu ga sukoshi ugoita ki ga suru
I feel like the seasons have changed slightly
Hizashi mo mijikaku itsukazurete
and the sunbeams have thinned and will one day shift.
Futari no basu ha kawaranai machi
But I was relieved, knowing our bus
Hashitteiru koto hotto shiteta
was riding through our unchanged city.
Mado no soto itsumo mitai ni miteru anata
You always gaze up to me from outside my window
Soshite watashi mo mane wo shiteiru
and I mimic you by doing the same
itsumo mitai ni
like always.
Nee futari ha onaji nano ka na?
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Ikitai basho ha? Damatteitatte iinda yo ne?
Even if the place we want to go to has gotten dull, it's all right.
Nee futari ha onaji nano ka na?
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Itoshii kimochi... Anata no shisen ha ima, mienakute....
I still feel love for you, but you're no longer looking at me.
Episode 10 Preview...
What am I gonna do?
I'm sure
Yamamoto-san's upset...
...since she lost the picture...
That's mine...
Snooping around
in other people's things...
...is pretty awful,
don't you think?
Don't you want
to know why Onee-chan...
...was riding in
Kagawa's car that day?