Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Sorry, but they suddenly
asked me to help out at
the store, so I can't go.
Go on ahead by yourself.
Sorry, but they suddenly asked me to help out at the store, so I can't go.
Takahashi.
Yeah?
Wanna go somewhere today?
Episode 7...
U-Umm... I was going to an all-you-can-eat cake buffet with Mizu-chin and Taka-chan.
Ah... I see.
She's broke whenever she's with me, and she hates having me pay for her, so she only asks for fruit milk...
Yano!
Mizu-chin
Weren't you guys going to an all-you-can-eat cake place or something?
All-you-can-eat cake?
Ah, yeah, we went last week.
Nana couldn't go, because she didn't have any money or something.
She was pretty green with envy, so why don't you go with her sometime?
Yano, where are you headed? I couldn't get Takeuchi.
Don't follow me.
W-What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm in the middle of...
...stalking my girlfriend.
Huh? For a Christmas present?
Yeah, I thought you'd know what Yano likes, Takeuchi-kun, so I was hoping we could go shopping for a bit.
I'm sure he'd be happy with anything you picked out yourself, Takahashi.
Don't say that!
Please!
Takeuchi-kun?
What? You can't make it? Why not?
I really think Yano will like something you pick out yourself a lot more.
But I have no sense for those things...
Think about it this way. If Yano got you a present...
...would you prefer something your friends picked out for him that they knew you'd like...
...or something you don't really like that he picked out himself after lots of consideration?
Which would make you happier?
Well...
Of course, the one that Yano picked out himself...
See?
She's on the move again.
Ah, she slipped.
What's she doing, really?
I could ask you the same question.
What? She must be out buying you a present.
Even though you're penniless...
You big dummy.
So what's going on with Takeuchi?
Ah, he said he had to help out at the store, so he couldn't come.
It's the end of the year, so it makes sense.
I see.
I was just overreacting.
Ah, here she comes.
And she has a bag.
All right!
That ends today's stalking!
I-Idiot! She'll notice us!
I thought you couldn't make it...
I was worried that you might not've been able to get anything.
But I see you did. I'm glad.
That was it. See you later.
Ah! Since you're out this way, wanna get something to drink?
Ah, it's okay. That's really all I came for.
It's so tiny...
I heard from Masa...
That girl who was in the accident last year... she was your girlfriend at that time?
I also heard that you haven't even visited her grave yet, either?
You can't do stuff like that.
Why not?
I'm not saying this for your girlfriend's benefit. I'm saying this for yours.
Go buy some flowers she liked, some water, and get out there, Motoharu.
People need to cry every now and then--
I don't want to hear it!
She was a stupid bitch.
Moto!
Even stupid bitches feel regret.
Even if she does regret it, it's too late!
Closing Ceremonies
Clean-up
Snow shoveling
December 24
Hey, boys! Take this seriously!
Don't have a snowball fight!
It's so cold!
Geez! We'll never finish like this!
Yano hasn't looked at me once today.
Is it just my imagination?
It... isn't my imagination!
Yano!
Come on!
What's he so mad about?
Yano!
Takahashi.
Hey, that's stupid. Get up.
Yano?
Don't screw around like that.
It was obviously a joke...
You're so mean...
I still might not have fully understood Yano at that time...
Yano!
There's your Christmas present, you bastard!
I'm sorry...
I didn't do it out of spite...
It's okay. Because you're still alive.
It can be really painful at times...
What could it be?
Umm, I had a really hard time deciding.
Ah, it's a cap.
W-What do you think?
You said you liked hats, and I didn't think you had one with a fuzzy ball on top...
And I had a really hard time picking the colors...
...but if you don't like it, they said you could come back and exchange it for another!
Why would I?
Don't you think it suits me?
It does!
Incredibly...
Then it's fine.
Thank you.
Here's mine, too.
I guess I'll be drinking nothing but fruit milk for a while myself.
You're crying? Doofus.
It's just that...
Everything and anything moves you, doesn't it?
Yeah.
People are always telling me to only cry when I'm sad.
If you have to cry, then I think tears of happiness are a lot better than tears of sadness.
Ever since I met Yano, I've felt that my tears have gotten so much more fragile.
Ah! I left my Math book in my locker!
Huh? Let's go back and get it.
It's such a pain...
Don't say that. We were assigned a ton of homework.
Ah, I'm going to the girl's room  for a second, okay?
Yep.
For when I fell down the stairs the other day...
Thank you.
Y-Yeah.
But don't save me ever again.
I don't want to owe you anything.
If you hate me that much, we shouldn't have even gotten to know each other to begin with.
You only used me to get revenge on my sister, anyway.
"Revenge"?
That wouldn't mean anything, and I'd have no reason to do that.
Don't go giving everything a hidden meaning.
Then, why did you cry back then?
Why did you cry that time?
Yano!
"Cry"?
Yano cried?
Has something like that ever really happened?
Then, why did you cry back then?
When did this happen?
And in front of Yamamoto-san...
What could make that happen...?
Sorry for making you listen to my problems again.
And we're on winter break, too...
It's okay. I was wondering what was up.
Speaking honestly for a sec, I... can't really believe it.
That he actually cried.
I've known him almost my whole life, but I've never seen him cry or show his soft side.
Yeah, you told me that before, didn't you?
Well, I guess it's because he's human.
Everyone can always do that when nobody else is around...
...but I always thought Yano was different.
You can understand, right?
Yeah.
Umm... did something happen between Yamamoto-san and Yano in middle school?
Sometimes, I think there's something strange between them.
Not really. Nothing unusual, at least.
Yamamoto was like that back then, too.
If they seem kind of awkward to you, then isn't it just because...
...they're both related to Nana-san in some way?
I wonder why Nana-san was in that car with her ex...
I wonder why she did something like that to betray Yano...
Was her ex really that charming?
No way.
He was the worst.
Everyone was always asking why she was going out with a bum like him.
She was always bruised all over.
Bruised?
Why would she stay with someone like him?
People also always asked Yano, "Why are you with someone as stupid as that?"
That's just what love is.
I guess...
It's something only those in the relationship could know.
Thanks.
Sorry for calling you out when it's so cold.
Yano and I must really seem like such a stupid couple, too, huh?
Getting everyone involved like this and working ourselves up over every little thing.
Not at all. I think any couple that isn't stupid isn't a real couple anyway.
Takeuchi-kun, when those two first started going out...
...did you also think "why was he going out with someone so stupid?"
Yeah.
It pissed me off... they were so dumb and stupid that I couldn't take my eyes off them.
Ever since the beginning.
Murai
Hasahiba
Tahara
Mori
Sasaki
Aihara
Ohtsuki
Narita
Nakao
Shirakawa
Meduro
Yamaguchi
Takahashi
Oka--
Sugiyama
Nishi--
Azuma
Yoshi--
Third Quarter Seating Chart
I'm in the front again!
I have no luck with getting seats!
Hey, look.
Geez...
Talk about the worst possible combination.
That seating change was the worst.
I won't be able to leave anything behind now.
Ah, when you forget your textbook, you can ask me for mine.
The person next to me will let me share.
Thanks. And when I start nodding off and it seems like I'm gonna be called on, poke me, okay?
That's a little impossible.
Ah... this will be the second time I'll be sitting next to Yamamoto.
The second time since my second year of middle school.
Really? She didn't share her textbooks then, either?
Ah, yeah. Or... maybe not. I don't think I ever forgot them back then.
What is it?
What happened
between you and
Yamamoto-san
during middle
school?
No... it's nothing.
I'm no good. When I think Nana-san's involved, I can't help getting weak in the knees.
Hey, when you went to get my present did you try to buy it with Takeuchi?
Yeah.
Why did you lie and say you were going to an all-you-can-eat cake buffet with Mizu-chin?
Lie...? I just wanted to surprise you.
I know...
I know, but...
Don't lie to me if you're going to be meeting with another guy.
I don't want any secrets between us.
Promise me that you'll never ever betray me.
Yeah.
English
What page are we working on today?
Let me see!
Isn't it kinda harsh to be sitting next to Yamamoto-san?
She doesn't say anything.
Asahi Middle School
She scowled at me the other day.
It's kinda hard to ask her to see her textbook, huh?
I hope they change seats soon.
Anzai
Sakurai
Saitou
Ishikawa
Fujii
Mitsuhashi
Yano
Yamamoto
Seat Changes
Let me see your textbook.
It's hard to see from here, so could you put it between our desks?
Open to page 45.
Ah, sorry.
Why are you working ten pages ahead?
There's nothing else to do at home.
There's nothing else to do, so you study?
You sure are different.
Study hall!!
Keep quiet.
I'd sure like some money right about now.
You shouldn't talk about your unrealistic dreams.
I have dreams!
If I were rich, we could go on a date at Disney Land!
What about you, Yano? What would you do if you were rich?
Me?
I don't need money.
I don't need any money, but instead... I want love.
What's wrong with me, wishing to be rich?
Yano, don't worry! I'll give you as much love as you want!
Really?
Yeah!
Then, why don't you come over on Saturday? My parents won't be around.
So love meant the perverted stuff to Yano...
Sign: Slurp
Yano... in that case, want to come over my place on Saturday?
Huh? Your parents won't be around?
They will.
Then that's no good.
Yano.
Yes?
Is that all you think about?
Yes.
You're such a moron.
I'm sorry, Yano. I can't live up to your expectations.
My heart hurts, too.
Ah, check it out!
They look just like you, Takahashi.
Should I give it a whirl?
Huh? I thought you were broke.
This is my entire life's savings.
Here we go.
As long as Yano smiles back at me, that's all I need.
Ah, that yellow one is cute.
I should just put my other worries to rest.
I want Yano... to always smile.
Huh? I don't have my biology textbook.
Even though I somehow managed to bring it home, I guess I forgot to bring it back.
You're such a doofus. Want to borrow mine?
Ah... sure.
Biology
No, never mind.
On second thought...
Let me see yours, Yamamoto.
Thank you.
What is it?
N-Nothing! B-Bye bye!
What do I want...?
Yamamoto-san sure was nice, showing you her textbook.
Ah... yeah.
Yano, wanna come to my house on Sunday?
It should be convenient for you, since it's Sunday.
Are your parents going to be out or something?
Yeah.
Welcome!
H-Hello.
It's kinda cramped in here, but...
You... knew from the very beginning, didn't you?
Whatever are you talking about?
It's smaller than your room, but...
Oh. You can put your bag down over there.
Yano's in my room!
I'm... a little moved by it all.
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
So, where do you live?
Yanagimachi.
It must've taken you a while to get here, then.
Not at all. I just have to take one bus.
Mom and Yano are talking...
You're so handsome. Your class must really talk about you.
It feels so weird.
Ah, no... not at all.
Mother in the middle of appraisal
Ah, geez... I'm starting to feel bad for Yano.
What does your father do for a living?
I told you, he's involved with realty. Umm, Yano's house is really huge!
Really? And just when did you pay them a visit?
Crap!
Takahashi, that house isn't as big as you think it is.
You've never come in, but my room is only four and a half tatami mats.
O-Oh? Is that so?
My. I see.
S-Should I play a CD? What do you wanna listen to?
Anything's fine.
I knew it... it's totally different from meeting with him outside.
I'm so nervous!
Someone save me from this silence!
I'm not gonna do anything, so calm down.
After all, it seems like your mom would just walk in without knocking.
H-How rude!
She wouldn't do anything like that!
Please have some more tea.
Sorry.
For what?
A lot of things.
Don't worry about it. You're just being treated preciously.
Yano, I really, really love you.
I feel like I've learned so much more about you since we started dating!
Like?
Like? Like...
You can be a bigger doofus than I thought.
Like your more childish aspects...
And how you brush my hair like this...
I just keep falling more and more in love with you.
I'm jealous of Yamamoto-san.
Of Yamamoto-san, who knows more about the unknown Yano than me.
I want to be the closest one to Yano.
I want to know more and more about him.
I want to know everything.
Is it selfish of me to want that? I wonder...
Yano, umm...
You said before that there'd be no secrets between us, right?
Yeah.
I'll never lie to you ever again.
So don't lie to me either, okay?
Yeah.
Would you tell me...
I'm sure it's all just in my head...
...what happened between you and Yamamoto-san in middle school?
Yano?
Why?
Why what?
For the same reason you have.
It's making me uneasy.
There aren't going to be any secrets between us, right?
Yano...
Yano?
Why won't you answer me?
Kisetsu ga sukoshi ugoita ki ga suru
I feel like the seasons have changed slightly
Hizashi mo mijikaku itsukazurete
and the sunbeams have thinned and will one day shift.
Futari no basu ha kawaranai machi
But I was relieved, knowing our bus
Hashitteiru koto hotto shiteta
was riding through our unchanged city.
Mado no soto itsumo mitai ni miteru anata
You always gaze up to me from outside my window
Soshite watashi mo mane wo shiteiru
and I mimic you by doing the same
itsumo mitai ni
like always.
Nee futari ha onaji nano ka na?
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Ikitai basho ha? Damatteitatte iinda yo ne?
Even if the place we want to go to has gotten dull, it's all right.
Nee futari ha onaji nano ka na?
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Itoshii kimochi... Anata no shisen ha ima, mienakute....
I still feel love for you, but you're no longer looking at me.
Episode 8 Preview...
Yamamoto-san loved you?
I don't care whether
Yamamoto loved or hated me.
It has nothing to do with me.
Not interested one bit.
I saw you two go
home together that day.
How could you do
it with her little sister?
Come with me, Takahashi!
It's fine with me...