Everything...
I'll forgive you for everything.
So, please... I want you to come back to me alive.
Come back to life...
Yano...
I... can't do this anymore.
I can't make you happy.
I'm sorry for not being able to keep our promise...
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 13 ...
All right!
Amazing!
Our class won the basketball tournament!
Good job!
For me? I'm so lucky!
Look over here!
Ah... there he goes with his popularity again. Are you okay with this, Nana?
Ah, hey. Next up is the boy's bullet finals.
We totally have to see that.
Nana, why did you break up with Yano?!
It's bugging the hell out of me, so spill already!
I've heard so many rumors that it's starting to drive me nuts!
R-Rumors...?
Like, you wouldn't let him do you, which pushed Yano to the point...
...where he couldn't deal with it anymore, so he lost his patience and fell out of love.
It sounds pretty reasonable to me.
W-What's up with that?
So, what's the true story?
Sorry... I can't say.
I'm really sorry, Mizu-chin.
I really am sorry.
I guess that's fine...
But I mean... you loved him so much.
I guess things like this wear out, huh?
Um, here's a towel!
Thank you.
Ah... about that...
Please return it once you're done with it.
And feel free to give it back just like that.
Okay!
It's been a week since we broke up.
I returned the manga and CDs I borrowed from him, as well as a mechanical pencil I had taken without him noticing.
I thought I might find the girl manga I forced on him in my cubby the next day, but...
...it still hasn't shown up.
We don't even look at each other in class anymore.
With the way things are going...
...just like this...
...we're slowly becoming strangers, aren't we?
He was definitely a two-timer.
That's all it could be. I can't think of any other reason he'd be dumped.
Not possible. If he was cheating on her, she'd hate him so much that she'd want him dead.
No... I think he was cheating, too. Though it was mentally.
Li'l Nana must've had it really bad.
What? "Li'l Nana"?
Separate classifications! Li'l Nana and Stupid Nana.
What's up with that?
Pretty easy to understand.
Takahashi!
You free today?
Wanna come see something nice later?
Something nice?
They're so cute!
How'd you get them?
They were left in front of my house a week ago.
What? That's so mean...
I'm looking for someone to take care of them...
How about at your house, Takahashi?
I can't... my parents hate pets.
Can't do much about that. I guess I'll have to raise them myself.
Both of them?
I don't have much choice.
I can't just abandon them.
It must be fate that they came to my house. Right?
He's licking my face!
Aren't they cute?
It tickles!
You finally laughed.
Huh? I've laughed before...
I mean like you just did.
I think it's important to make time to just forget everything and laugh.
I see...
He might be right...
Takeuchi-kun just stays by my side without asking a thing.
Hey, quit it!
Can I come over to see them again?
Sure. Whenever you want.
If you ever get lonely, come on over.
Ah... I'm not really implying anything.
Thanks, Takeuchi-kun.
Really, thanks...
...for today.
Ah... umm...
Y-Yeah.
B-Bye then.
Ah, yeah.
A hook-up party?
Yeah, on Saturday. I told you before.
Ah, sorry... I can't make it. I'm broke.
Don't screw around like that. I got a lot of girls by promising you'd be there.
Oh, really?
You little bastard... you never planned to go, did you?
Uh...
Well, you know, it's that.
I'm still in the 49 days of mourning.
It still hasn't passed.
How about going with something like that?
Saying things like that to make people feel pity!
Things like that don't suit you. Sheesh.
This riverbed's kinda nice, huh?
Yeah. It's cute.
Didn't I say so?
I'd like to go sometime.
Let's go, let's go.
Yes.
And let's invite some friends, too.
Yeah.
Oh, and could you hide your face with glasses or something?
What? You really don't have a girlfriend?
Y-Yeah.
How long has it been since you've had one?
I told him to hide face, not to stand out...
Come on, how long?
Did you just break up?
Ah, he just got dumped. You better go easy on him.
You were just dumped?
Why'd you break up?
Who cares? Don't worry about it.
Did we hurt your feelings?
I'm so sorry!
He's getting depressed!
I want to go home already.
Hey, when's your birthday?
Your birthday.
July.
So you're a Leo?
I'm a Cancer.
Hmm... so you're more sensitive than you look.
Is she a fortune teller?
Anyway, I happened to see your cell phone before, and it looked like the same model as mine.
Can I see?
See? Only the color's different, right?
Ah, who's this?
Huh? What's that?
Could this be your girlfriend?
His background is still the girlfriend he broke up with!
No way! You're right!
Lemme see, lemme see!
Huh? But she's...
...kinda plain, huh?
Yeah. I thought he would've been going out with someone cuter.
I guess Yano-kun doesn't care about looks.
Yeah.
Here you go. Thanks.
What? Shouldn't they be calling her "really cute" or something?
Are you still in love with her?
Not really. It's just a pain to change, which is why it's still there.
Then I'll change it for you.
I'll also erase this old picture, okay?
Hey!
I... I erased it...
Shocked
I'm going to the bathroom.
Now connecting you to voicemail.
Takeuchi, do you still have that picture of Takahashi in her yukata that you sent to me a year ago?
If you do, send it to me right away!
Please!
Don't say a word.
I won't.
Can I leave now?
Yeah, sure. Actually, I'm kinda sorry.
Sorry about before.
Forget about it.
Hey, wanna make like a tree and... you know?
Ah... I'm broke today.
I'm not, so we're okay.
Seriously? You want to spend the night?
If it's with you, I don't mind.
I'm really no good if I'm not with the girl I love.
Sorry.
Take...
Take, wake up.
Take!
What do you want? What time do you think it is?
The picture!
Where's Takahashi's picture?
I don't have that old thing anymore.
Ah... it's 02:30. Get out of here. Geez.
Hey, Take!
Even if you're secretly hiding that picture from me, I won't get mad.
Just please send it to me again!
I don't have it!
What would be fun about having a picture of someone else's girlfriend?
Here. Look for yourself.
The girls I met today...
They called Takahashi ugly.
They said she was "plain."
What's wrong with her being plain?
Please... let me sleep...
Takahashi's a hundred times cuter than those arrogant, unsympathetic, "delicate" bitches...
...who drench themselves in makeup. Don't you think so?
Ah, correction... I meant a thousand times.
Who's cuter, her or Nana-san?
What's up with all of you? Every single one of you...
As if I know.
Try bringing them together and lining them up.
Try lining both of them up in front of me!
I want to know...
...who I'd pick.
What would you do if I went out with Takahashi?
What's up with that?
I'm saying that you have no right to complain if she finds another guy while you idle around like this.
After all... love is all about timing.
If you don't say the right thing at the right moment...
...no matter how much fate was involved in the relationship, everything will be ruined.
Even if you regret it, it'll be too late.
Even if you regret it...
Here's the money I borrowed the other day.
A-Ah, yeah.
What was that arrogant little boy's name again?
Moto?
Yeah, Moto. Could you give this back to him and say thanks from me?
Huh? We didn't give this much.
Huh?
There's 220 yen here. That's 80 yen more than what we gave you.
On, it's fine. It's just 80 yen.
It's small change.
It's not fine. Whether it's 80 or 800,000 yen, money is still money.
Let's even things out.
Ah, shoot... nothing but junk.
What's that key for?
It's my bike key.
50... 60... oh, I'm 20 yen short.
This caramel should be fine.
What? It's morning already?
What the heck? I can see my breath here in my room.
Come to think of it, how did he get in last night?
From now on, I won't forget to lock it.
I'll actually get some sleep.
He was in the middle of writing a message?
Takahashi,
I never thought
of you as a
replacement for
her. None of my
feelings have been
false.
Takahashi, I never thought of you as a replacement for her.
None of my feelings have been false.
I regret what I did so much that I want to die.
Back then... back at that place... those actions I took...
Everything I choose to say is always wrong.
But I want you to listen to me.
Takahashi.
I...
is always wrong.
But I want you
to listen to me.
Takahashi,
I
Before
High School
Because you took my futon, I caught a cold!
Shut up!
If you have time to worry like this, you should hurry up and say what needs to be said already.
Don't you dare touch Takahashi.
That's not what I meant...
Hurry and tell Takahashi that.
Otherwise, you'll be too late.
Takeuchi-kun, can I come to see the puppies again today?
I brought something for them.
Umm, umm...
Don't you think this is cute?
I heard puppies like plush toys, so I brought some from my house.
Umm...
I'm sorry, but I have other plans today...
I... I see...
I'm sorry.
I see... I must be an annoyance.
Umm... but you can go see them even if I'm not there.
I see...
Yeah... maybe some other time.
Sorry.
Even though I'm just the ex of one of his friends...
Doko ni itemo donna toki mo
Anywhere, anytime,
Kimi ga kieta hi kara
I'll accept the unreasonable memories
When I suddenly have all this time to myself again...
Kesenai omoide nokoshite
left behind since the day
...an empty hole has formed inside me...
...and I notice the things I forgot to give back to him.
Uketomeyou
you left.
The memories of Yano...
Tomadoi wa itsuka fukai umi de
This bewilderment will become blue sand
Aoi suna ni natte
deep in the ocean.
Cute Yano...
Samenai omoi issho ni
I wonder if these unrelenting feelings
Hateful Yano...
Childish Yano...
Kono you na no darou
will be just like that, too?
Kimi ga inai kono beddo de
I'm quivering alone
Teasing Yano...
Sweet Yano...
Hitori yureteiru
in this bed without you.
Everything Yano left behind...
Negaeri wo uttara aozora ga mieta
But when I rolled over, I couldn't see the blue sky.
I need to not rely on people so much...
...and move forward.
So... I'd like to start discussing what sort of float we'll have in the Culture Festival this year.
This year, Class 2-7
Float
Candidates
This year, Class 2-7
Float
Candidates
Our class didn't win anything last year, so we have to win this year, no matter what!
So, going by what won last year...
None of these are any good!
This years, Class 2-7
float
Candidates
o
Elephant
Pyramid
NORA Rabbit
Can't you guys do anything but cut corners with circles, triangles and white things?
Don't you want to at least clear our sucky name from not even making 3rd place last year?!
But isn't there more meaning in just being able to participate...?
Forget that half-assed crap! We're gonna win this year, no matter what! Got it?!
Does anyone have any ideas for a style filled with our dreams...
...has plenty of color...
...something vivid...
...that'll surprise anyone who sees it?
What's up with that?
Sounds like a pain in the ass...
What does she mean, filled with our dreams?
Vivid...?
What does she want?
Can you give us an example?
Huh? An example? Umm, umm...
Plenty of color...
L-Like a peacock?
Filled with our dreams...
A-A rainbow? Huh?
Vivid...
Umm... it's pretty difficult to come up with.
A peacock?
She said a rainbow?
D-Does anyone have any ideas?
Ah, yes?
Oh, great! Who's going to suggest something?
A-Ah... Ya-Yano-kun. Please.
What about Disneyland?
We could build the castle, use that mouse character, and light it up with decorative bulbs and stuff.
N-Nice idea...
And if it were...
And if it were Tokyo Disneyland, it would be even better!
...indeed.
It couldn't be... right?
Sign: Nora Rabbit, Disney Land, It's decided!
Ya-Yano.
That idea for Disneyland was really good.
You really helped me out.
Thanks.
I spoke to him...
Umm...
Well, then...
I'll be going to the student council meeting...
This is no good.
Whenever I see Yano's eyes...
...I waver.
Please... don't confuse me.
Before
High School
Take.
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
Hey, mind if we stop by the plaza?
What do you want to buy?
What do you think?
A long-sleeved T-shirt.
That's you.
Bye bye.
Nana, where are you off to?
Why don't we go shopping?
Yeah. I think I might wanna get a bag.
A bag? That'd be nice.
Yeah.
Why don't we go to that store in front of the station?
Before
High School
Ah, here's the bus.
Is it ours?
Huh? Where'd I put my pass?
Ah, here it is.
Moto, I just remembered some things I need to take care of.
I gave you my final notice this morning.
Didn't I tell you...
...you'd regret it?
Sorry!
Hey!
Love is...
Kisetsu ga sukoshi ugoita ki ga suru
I feel like the seasons have changed slightly
...all about timing.
All of it!
Hizashi mo mijikaku itsukazurete
and the sunbeams have thinned and will one day shift.
Futari no basu ha kawaranai machi
But I was relieved, knowing our bus
Hashitteiru koto hotto shiteta
was riding through our unchanged city.
Change of plans.
You can come see them again today.
Mado no soto itsumo mitai ni miteru anata
You always gaze up to me from outside my window
I can't...
Soshite watashi mo mane wo shiteiru
and I mimic you by doing the same
itsumo mitai ni
like always.
...hold back anymore!
Nee futari ha onaji nano ka na
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Ikitai basho ha Damatteitatte iinda yo ne
Even if the place we want to go to has gotten dull, it's all right.
Nee futari ha onaji nano ka na
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Itoshii kimochi Anata no shisen ha ima mienakute
I still feel love for you, but you're no longer looking at me.
Nee futari ha onaji nano ka na
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Ikitai basho ha Damatteitatte iinda yo ne
Even if the place we want to go to has gotten dull, it's all right.
Nee futari ha onaji nano ka na
Hey, I wonder if we're both the same?
Itoshii kimochi Anata no shisen ha ima mienakute
I still feel love for you, but you're no longer looking at me.
Episode 14 Preview...
Do you think
Takeuchi-kun likes you, Nana?
Take! If you lay a finger
on her, I'll fucking kill you!
I'm prepared for that.
It's the period of the
Warring States again, I guess.
I... I...
...will wait for you...
...to return!
Why do you say
that now, of all times...?