Apparently, Yano was going out with a girl two grades above him...
Sign: Rumors about Yano...
So he likes older girls...
How long were they going out?
From the end of his 2nd year to the summer of the 3rd.
Only half a year? That's short.
The rumors came out of nowhere and spread like wildfire.
Isn't that long?
Right now, I'm having a really hard time.
Yamamoto-san!
You're well enough to be running in gym again?
Yeah.
Oh, I got a 34 on the last math test!
I'm finally free of that zero!
I guess next time you'll have to get higher than a 56.
You'll fail if your average is under 30, right?
What? Really?
I-I'll try my best!
Yano is still the same as ever...
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 2 ...
No way! They don't look alike at all!
Seriously, they really don't.
What are you guys talking about?
The Asahi Middle School yearbook.
Yamamoto-san's older sister is in here.
You know, the one Yano was going out with!
Nana, come take a look!
Ah, I'll... pass...
Hey, anyone have change for a 5,000 yen bill?
I dooooon't!
Okay...
Hey, anyone?
Anyone have change for 5,000 yen?
Yano just doesn't change...
I guess it's to be expected.
Since we met, Yano's just been like that.
I guess I just don't know anything about him yet...
See you!
Bye bye!
That committee meeting lasted longer than I expected...
What class was she in again...?
Class 3-5.
I'm sorry, Yano...
I was just curious...
This must look pretty bad.
Book: Asahi Middle School Yearbook
Show me that.
I still haven't looked at it myself.
Wanna see?
Not really!
I guess I do!
Though I didn't want to see it under these circumstances...
Since I don't know what kind of expression to--
Yamamoto Nana
He only goes for pretty faces!
Surprised
S-She's really pretty, isn't she?
Yeah, but this is nothing. In person, she's even prettier.
I-It's over...
I've completely lost to her.
She doesn't really... resemble Yamamoto-san, huh?
I guess not.
Which one of you fell for the other first?
Me. It was love at first sight.
So you started dating right away?
No, it took a while. She had a boyfriend at the time.
Did you steal her away?
That's right!
Er, are you trying to make me look bad?
What is it?
Nothing...
I've just never seen Yano so fixated on one thing before...
You must have loved to brag about her, huh?
She was my first. The first I'd ever really loved.
My chest hurt, but since Yano smiled as he talked, it quickly settled down.
I probably didn't want to accept it...
The existence of someone Yano loved...
Yano, I...
I think I might like you...
Just ignore me! I just wanted to try sayin--
Then, wanna go out?
H-Huh? W-Wait a sec...
You really like me back?
Yeah.
W-Wait a second! You hesitated!
Did not.
Did too! You definitely did!
Forget it!
No.
Do you really like me?
Yeah, I guess.
Not that sort of "like".
I'm asking if you really, really like me.
I'm sorry... I don't know.
What's up with that...?
Then, let's just forget it.
I don't want something like that.
If we're going to go out, I want you to like me back...
Okay.
"Okay"?
Even though it was the first confession I'd made since I was born...
...to get a quick and painfully honest "okay" as an answer...
I wonder if I should've pretended to not hear him and said "yeah"...
Yano.
You were sound asleep.
What? Can't you do it?
That's unusual.
Yamamoto, show me you can fill in the rest.
Yano, you stay here and watch.
Yano? Yano.
What's the matter? You look pale.
Yano!
Here. Take this.
It's good against anemia.
How do you feel?
It's so lukewarm and gross...
I-It's leftover from my lunch.
Don't worry. It's not expired or anything.
Probably...
Uh huh...
Thank goodness... we can still talk normally.
Hey...
Before, you kept badgering me if I really, really liked you, right?
W-Well... I wouldn't call it "badgering"...
You were quite the badger.
Let me ask you back.
Do you really, really like someone like me?
You have to hesitate to answer, right?
Are you sure you don't just feel the same way I do?
Hey, I'm pretty hungry.
Wanna go get something sweet to eat?
Huh?
Ah, Takeuchi-kun.
I don't usually see you around here.
Out shopping?
Ah, I get it. Asahi Middle School is around here.
This is our haunt.
Then that means Yano hangs out here, too?
He might be here now.
Wanna take a look inside?
This is pretty good.
Ah, he's here!
Make room for two more.
Huh? Who are they?
That girl's my class president.
Class president?
She must be pretty smart.
Yeah. Especially in math.
Oh, really?
She's scary.
Hey, I heard you're in the same class as Yamamoto Yuri?
Ah, yeah.
She must be so dark and annoying.
Yeah, she's nothing like her older sister, huh?
Not only is she antisocial, but she's so creepy, too...
It must be an inferiority complex or something.
After all, those two have always been compared to each other.
How can you say that?
What do you mean?
You don't know anything about her. You just judge her by her looks. Quit it.
Huh? We were in the same class for three years of middle school.
I think we'd know more about her than you.
Oh? You knew her for three years, but those are the only things you can say about her?
You don't know anything yourself.
She can't even leave messages for people correctly...
That's why Motoharu and Nana-san got into a fight.
If they hadn't fought...
...they would've been together that summer vacation, and what happened would--
Stop it.
That's not something to talk about here.
Ah... s-sorry.
Why are you guys getting so serious all of a sudden?
Oh, it's my fault!
I won't forgive anyone who badmouths Nana-san.
Ah... and about Yamamoto's little sister...
She's... yeah, she's fine just the way she is.
She's not as bad as you all say.
Also, Takahashi Nana.
This isn't homeroom, so quit acting like the class president. It's annoying.
Die, you jerk!
What was up with that?
I dropped my wallet...
Darn it!
Your wallet.
You're the first girl who's ever told me to die.
Then let me say some more!
Moron! Idiot! Jackass! Son of a bitch!
Give it back!
You can only see Nana-san in your eyes, anyway...
"Moron, idiot, jackass", huh?
And my mother isn't a bitch...
She's...
...a prostitute.
And my girlfriend was a cheat.
Rea--
She was with another guy when she died in the accident.
It was her previous boyfriend.
They were never through with each another...
Just kidding.
I actually don't know if that was really true.
Though, I don't really want to.
But if there's one thing I know for sure, it's this.
If she ever felt that she wanted to see another guy, then...
...it must partially be my fault for making her feel that way.
I'll take you home.
I... can't find any words...
Ah, I'm getting a text message.
"Where are you and what are you doing?"
I'm... taking... Takahashi... san... home.
Ah... you don't have to take me home.
You don't have to, so why don't we go to a pho--
Pho...?
Why don't we go get our picture taken at photo booth together?
I'm such an idiot, asking at a time like this. Such a total idiot...
Wouldn't one that takes our whole picture be better?
No... not one of these.
I really feels like it's been forever since I've been in one of these.
Yano's... smiling.
Actually, when I think about it... he's always smiling.
Yano, you're really strong, aren't you?
Normally, a person can't say the sorts of things you just told me...
I'm going to press the "confirm" button!
Ah, I thought so. This one's no good.
You're like the woman of 1,000 masks! It's hilarious!
And... I think it's a lot easier to place the blame on yourself than someone else.
Huh? Not the other way around?
Let's do this!
Isn't it easier to blame someone else?
If you blame someone else, you'll just get stubborn and say you'll never forgive them.
But when you blame yourself, you can shrug it off since there's nothing you can do about it.
And you won't get angry that way, either.
It's easier.
Basically, I'm not being fair.
I pressed the "confirm" button, by the way.
Look at the dork! Look at your head!
I look like a guy...
And not only that... my head's bigger than his.
I look like some octopus alien or something...
Yeah. It's cute.
Cute...? As an octopus...?
Here's the bus.
Bye, then.
Everyone, we decided what we'll be doing for the school festival at the last committee meeting.
Sign: What to do for the School Festival
Unfortunately, due to the large number of classes doing cafés, we weren't able to do one. Instead...
Our third choice, a short play, won in the ballot!
Short play
What do you mean "our third choice" won?! "Our"?!
Takahashi, were you asleep when we voted?!
It's because I suck at rock-paper-scissors...
But there's a problem. isn't there?
Since you borrow a classroom instead of the auditorium for those...
...only the student judges and teachers will come to see it, right?
It's just too lame...
I have no motivation.
I figured that, so I thought about what I could do to increase the audience...
...and I came up with the perfect idea!
And it's...!
(Still not sure what we're
going to do yet, but...)
How's that sound?
That'll bring them in!
That'll get all the girls here!
Let's do it!
Yano, I'm gonna decide what play to do today. What do you wanna do?
Don't ask me. Do whatever the heck you want.
Y-You don't have to get so mad.
Do I always have to clean up your mess?
Clean up my mess...?
What are you gonna do?
I... I was thinking of being the costume director...
It must be so nice to always take the easy way out.
Sometimes... you can really be a bastard.
So whenever someone does something inconvenient for you, he's a bastard. I see.
This is the person who
confessed her love to
him last week ...
You're just mad about before, aren't you? It's true that I was a little hasty, but...
I guess I don't have a good eye for these sorts of things.
What I said before was a mistake!
What are you talking about again?
This little...
W-When I said I liked you, I was wrong!
Told you so.
I... just... don't get it anymore.
Ah, how should I put this?
Do either of you have any stories involving murder?! One that really lets the main character have it?!
Love stories are out of the question!
I could kill him! I could just kill him!
It seems like Nana wants to kill Yano...
Damn it! I'll draw a mustache on this devil! Yes! A mustache!
Takahashi-san.
Yes?!
There's a student council meeting during lunch tomorrow.
They said they'll assign the classrooms for the festival.
I-Is that so? Thanks.
Hey.
Ah, Takeuchi-kun.
Sorry about the other day.
What do you mean?
Even though you all got together...
Ah... that's a daily thing for them.
They all have big mouths.
That aside, I heard your class is putting on a play?
Yeah. It's really a pain in the neck.
No thanks to him, either.
Him?
Yano, that douchebag!
Did he do something?
Let's not talk about him. My mouth will rot.
He must've done something to really annoy you, huh?
Yeah! Sometimes he's so cold, it's hard to believe his blood is flowing!
He doesn't even think of others! He could be a little more sensitive!
The complete opposite of you, huh?
Even though I'm really trying my hardest, I get nothing in return...
When I feel like that, it really aggravates me to see people like him...
He's the worst?
He's worse than that!
But... people will still come.
Because of Yano, everyone was cool with the play.
You know that type of person, right?
The one who brings a soccer ball to recess, so all of the other kids cheer and go to the field to play.
And when that type of person leaves...
...everyone just gets bored and quits playing. The type who really has a strong presence.
He's one of those types, and I...
...really...
...admire that part of him.
Just kidding! If I talk about that moron any more, not only will my mouth rot, but so will my brain!
Bye!
So, what do you think of that?
What do you mean?
From that day forward, we were really busy looking for a good script...
...and we had no idea of the incredible thing that would happen two days later.
Huh...? Our... our...
...our class has no classroom for the festival.
There's a student council meeting during lunch tomorrow.
They said they'll assign the classrooms for the festival.
I forgot about it...
I heard our class might not be able to put on a play after all.
Seriously?! That doesn't bother me one bit!
Why, why?
I heard Takahashi forgot to go to the room assignment meeting, so we couldn't get a classroom.
We're not completely out of a classroom yet.
There are still open classrooms in the third building.
The third building? That's totally far away from everything!
Nobody would come to that run-down building, anyway!
I just can't get into this anymore.
What was that girl doing?
It's not Nana's fault! I heard the person deciding who goes where forgot about our class.
Nana tried her hardest to protest, but she was told it was too late to move things around.
They didn't listen to her at all... they said it was her fault for missing the assignment meeting.
Takahashi.
When's the meeting today?
It should've just ended...
You think some people will still be around?
Probably.
I'll go.
But...!
It'll be fine. If anything happens, I'll take responsibility.
You don't have to worry about a thing.
About the classroom distribution...
Yano and I... are different.
What? I'm telling you, it's already been decided. Just use one of the leftover rooms.
I'm telling you the leftovers are no good, so change it.
Yano has a different way of thinking than most people...
I wonder when I began getting that feeling from him...
Even though he's totally irresponsible, he's serious.
Even though he cuts corners, he's confident.
The first school building was impossible to get, but...
Why do you keep... contradicting yourself, Yano?
I thought... you weren't going to clean up after my messes anymore.
In the end, I'm just too full of pride, too weak-minded, everyone's "friend"...
Koko ni ite itsudemo
Be here... always...
...have too strong a sense of responsibility, not reliable in the least...
...and just a timid coward...
Koko ni ite watashi wo
Be here... look...
What's up with that?
They all mean someone who's too softhearted!
I have no eye for anything... I confess my love too quickly... I rely on people too much...
Koko ni ite miteite
Be here... at me...
In other words, a...
Moron?
Yeah...
I'm not trying to put on a comic skit here!
Kono mama zutto
Just like this, forever...
I don't think that's so bad, though.
Te no hira no naka
The "first time" you gave me
What's not?
Being softhearted.
afuredashisou na
seems like it's going
And...
Anata ga kureta "hajimete"
to overflow in the palm of my hand.
I don't think confessing...
...was the mistake you're making it out to be.
Watashi hitori ja kokoro ga yuretara
If my heart wavered alone,
Minna koborete shimau
it seems like everyone would vanish.
What...do you mean by that?
Huh? Who knows?
Anata no ookina te de
On that day, you
Why do you always evade the important questions by saying things like "who knows?" or "I dunno"?
Watashi goto tsukamaeteite
took hold of me
I don't.
You can call it irresponsible or whatever.
Konna ni mo konna ni mo
even though, even though
You can call it whatever you want, but...
Tayorinai watashi no koto wo
I'm so unreliable.
But?
But...
Aren't I all right the way I am, not knowing?
Dakedo ima wa anata no te wa
But you still stretched out your
There he goes...
sukoshi tookute
arm and hand to me, just a little bit.
He's saying it again...
He's contradicting himself again...
But...
Yeah... he might just be all right the way he is...
Koko ni ite yasashiku
Be here... with that...
Be here... gentle hand...
Koko ni ite anata no
Koko ni ite sono te de
Be here... of yours...
Tsutsundeite ne
and embrace me.
Itsumo hitori de aruiteru michi ha
The path I always walk alone
Hirosugite samishii dake
is too wide, and only makes me lonely.
Futari de arukeba shiawasena kimochi
If we walked together, I'd be filled
Sore dake de ippai yo
with happiness, and that'd be just fine.
Anata ga egao dattara
If you're smiling,
Watashi mo onaji de itai
I want to be smiling too.
Sore na no ni sore na no ni
Yet... yet...
Watashi dake furuete shimau
It seems like I'm the only one who will disappear.
Kaze yo douka suki no kimochi
Oh, wind... please gently tell him
sotto tsutaete
of my feelings towards him.
Episode 3 Preview...
They call that
sort of thing "being blind".
You haven't really fallen
in love with anyone before!
They call those sorts
of people "immature know-it-alls".
Hurry and really fall in love!
Yano!
Yano, there may not be
anyone left who you really love...
...and that might be
a really sad thing for you, but...
...I'm watching you, so...
I'm always watching you, so...
I'm always watching over you, so...!