You like him...
...and he likes you...
And it's perfect.
But...
I can promise you one thing.
I'll never...
...make you cry, Takahashi.
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 22 ...
Thanks for walking me home...
Not at all. You should warm yourself up inside, and go to bed early.
Yeah...
Takahashi!
I was just at the station, and you weren't there...
I'm sorry for breaking our promise.
Go home...
Head inside.
You didn't think something like this would make her cry, did you?
You thought something like this was nothing, since you didn't have feelings for Yamamoto.
That's why you were able to go, right?
Because there'd be nothing to feel guilty about.
But it's different for Takahashi!
How do you plan to explain your actions to Takahashi, who's still not confident about all of this yet?
You and Takahashi experience things totally differently, all the way down to the bottom!
I don't intend to blame you for going to see Yamamoto.
But...
I don't think the important thing to do is always the same as the right thing to do!
Isn't it important to not hurt Takahashi?
You didn't think something like this would make her cry, did you?
You thought something like this was nothing.
But it's different for Takahashi!
You hurt Takahashi.
Training
School
Damn it!
Morning!
You catch a cold or something?
Your face is bright red.
It took me two hours to walk home last night...
Huh?! In that snow storm?!
I didn't have enough for the bus...
...because the taxi ride was too long.
Go rest somewhere... you look like you're about to collapse.
Congrats!
Umm...
Nana, so you're finally...!
Yeah!
We were so worried for you, like we were your parents.
So, how was it?
Did everything go well?
U-Umm...
Takahashi.
Ah... I have to get the class day book...
I'm sorry!
Takahashi!
W-Wait up!
Let go of me!
Takahashi.
Ah, Takeuchi-kun.
I heard he fell?
Ah, yeah. He went home early.
Seriously? Did he have a fever?
He'll be fine.
They said it was just a cold.
Gotta go.
Takahashi.
Are you... avoiding me?
No...
He stood you up and went to see Yamamoto instead?
What's up with that? He's scum!
Nana, you're just being selfish.
What? He went to see another girl!
Isn't that awful?
But it's not like he hid it. He told her.
When accidents like that happen, you can't do anything about it.
You don't fully understand the situation.
I don't know about that! Why does Nana have to be the one to wait, and not Yamamoto?
Because she's his girlfriend, right?
Always expecting him to put you first because of that is a bit much.
If there's trust in the relationship, something like that shouldn't bother you.
Trust, you say? It's because he goes and does things like this that she can't trust him!
That's not really his problem, is it? It's hers.
My... problem?
Yano probably went because he didn't think there would be a problem, right?
And he trusted you, too.
Am I wrong?
Trust...?
But... if my mom collapsed, I don't think Yano would come running to me.
You wouldn't even call Yano, would you?
Isn't that kind of sad?
I'd come to you, Mizu-chin!
I think I'd come, too!
Trust, huh...?
That's something I always seem to be lacking...
It's like we kept hitting on the same point every time...
Yamamoto and I had sex.
Deep in my heart, I may not have been able to forgive that.
The problem...
...may really be with me.
But please... don't make me any more uneasy...
How do you feel?
Your fever seems to have broken.
You slept for almost a day, you know.
And there's someone here to see you.
Can I let her in?
Someone's here to see me?
Ah, stay in bed.
How do you feel?
I heard you almost had pneumonia?
Not really.
I'm better now.
I see.
I was worried, since you took two days off from school.
I made a copy of the class notes for you.
That's all right. I can get them from someone else.
I sliced up the cantaloupe.
Ah... excuse me.
She brought it as get-well-soon gift, Motoharu. Be sure to thank her.
I've loved you this whole time...
Your mom's really pretty.
You might catch my cold, so go home when you're done.
I hardly ever catch colds, so I should be fine---
Go home.
I ended up coming...
I don't really want to see him yet, but I got worried because he's been absent for two days...
I'll look in on him, and then leave--
Why...?
Yamamoto-san!
I think it's a bit selfish to say this, but...
...I don't want you to see or call Yano anymore.
Why?
Because Yano's the guy I'm going out with.
Then why don't you tell him that?
Because you're Nana-san's little sister.
Because you're not just some stranger.
That's why Yano finds it hard to make a decision!
I don't see him as "my sister's boyfriend".
What do you even know?
You've only been his girlfriend for a year.
But I've known him since before he was going out with my sister...
...and after she died, when he was about to cry and ready to die!
I know I can understand him a whole lot more than you can!
A whole lot more than you can!
I can't do anything about that, can I?
I can't do anything about what I don't know, can I?
Or... am I the wrong one here?
Takahashi...
Can I not understand him enough?
She says she knew him when he was having the hardest time ever...
I'm trying so hard, too... so very hard...
But it's still... not enough?
Takahashi.
There's a limit to things.
You're right to try your hardest.
But... really understanding him is impossible.
The same way he can't do what you want him to do, you can't understand what he wants you to understand.
There's nothing you can do about the differences in the way you two think.
Then... what am I supposed to do?
Take.
Huh? Are you alone?
I thought I heard someone else. Were you talking to someone?
I... I was on my cell.
Don't bother coming to visit. You'll catch my cold, so go home.
It's cold out, so close your window.
Yeah.
Take... I don't understand anything.
You don't understand what?
How to go out with Takahashi without hurting her.
I wonder if it's just one of my defects as a human?
This isn't a first for you, right?
This is a first.
I'm not confident.
I must be really pathetic, huh?
I can't forgive myself for making her cry.
But... I'm not confident that I won't be able to keep from hurting her.
But...
...I definitely don't want to give up on her.
Takahashi!
What's the matter?
You have to get some rest.
Hey... are you sure no one else really came?
Huh? Yeah.
Motoharu! You can't go outside like this!
Motoharu!
Let go!
There's no one here!
Motoharu, look out there!
You don't see anyone, do you?
Just because your fever's dropped a little doesn't mean you can let your guard down.
Takahashi! Wait--!
Don't be so nice to me when I'm weak!
When you're weak...?
It's not fair.
Then... smile.
Make your fun smile like usual, and be yourself.
Then I'll be able to...
This is useless...
Why do you always have to cry?
I'd always make you smile.
Aren't you supposed to be happy with him?
I'd be by your side.
Aren't you happy?
Why else would you stick with this relationship?!
I'd always find you before you had to go looking for me!
I'd do whatever you wish for!
There's only one way to allow such a thing.
If you can't figure it out, you don't have the right to do such a thing.
I... can make you happier than he can.
There's something I've been wanting to talk to you about, Motoharu...
What is it?
I know it's a little weird to tell you when you're like this, but...
...you're not around very much.
Shizuka na ame ga furu
A silent rain falls.
I'm thinking of getting divorced.
Sukoshi tsumetai ame
A slightly chilly rain.
I can make you happier than he can, Takahashi!
Atattaneai tsudzuketeru
But it continues to fall, without actually hitting me
I've actually been worrying over this for about a year.
But I wasn't able to make up my mind.
But about one month ago, one of my old friends gave me a call.
Kono kokoro wo hiyasu you ni
as if it's trying to freeze my heart instead.
I think you remember her. You know, that lady who used to be my hair stylist?
Itsumo kimi wo mitsuketeita
I've always found your gentle back
I can't leave you like this anymore.
And she asked if I could come help her with her work.
Yasashiii ushirosugata mawari iku kono omoi
on any day, but where do my
Finding employment at my age was one of my big worries, so I thought this might be my chance.
Doko he mukau no
winding feelings point?
And I don't want to let it pass me by.
Kimi ga mitsumeru saki ni wa
I wonder what you see
Let's put an end to all the crying and worrying.
Nani ga aru darou
before you?
When two people are together, aren't you supposed to have more fun than when you're alone?
Bokura wa hitahashiru
We keep on running
Todokisou de todokanai
and we seem like we're going to reach, but don't.
Are we moving to Tokyo?
Sono kyori de
At that distance away from you.
I want to protect you, Takahashi!
Shizuka ni ame ga furu
Rain will fall again someday.
Sukoshi tsumetai ame
A slightly lonely rain
Every night before falling asleep, I wish for my dream to come true.
And each morning manages to be different.
Hirogaritsudzuketeru
will pour all around and spread
And I still can't see the future.
Kono kokoro wo nademeru you ni
as if it's meant to soothe my heart.
Itsumo kimi wo mitsumeteiru
I'm always looking at your cute back
Kawaii ushirosugata mawari iku kono omoi
but these winding feelings
Doko ni mukau no
point me in the other direction.
Boku ga motomeru saki ni wa
What am I waiting for
Nani ga matsu darou
at the end of my search?
Bokura wa hitahashiru
We keep on running
Oitsukesou de oitsukanai
and we seem like we're going to catch up, but don't.
Sono kyori de
At that distance away from you.
Bokura wa hitahashiru
We keep on running
Todokisou de todokanai
and we seem like we're going to catch up, but don't.
Sono kyori de
At that distance away from you.
Episode 23 Preview...
I might not be the
right girl for Yano after all...
Sono kyori de
At that distance away from you.
I can't understand
his feelings at all.
Why can't we do
something so easy...?
I'm sorry. I take back the
words I said two years ago...
That was still the worst
thing you could've done.