Yano, umm...
You said before that there'd be no secrets between us, right?
Yeah.
I'll never lie to you ever again.
So don't lie to me either, okay?
Yeah.
Would you tell me...
...what happened between you and Yamamoto-san in middle school?
Yano?
Why?
Why what?
For the same reason you have.
It's making me uneasy.
There aren't going to be any secrets between us, right?
Yano...
Yano?
Why won't you answer me?
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Ya...
Would you like some more tea?
Geez, knock before coming in...
Episode 8 ...
I completely forgot that I had received this cake recently.
Come on, we're full... give us a break.
My, but I went through all the trouble to...
Not at all. Thank you.
See?
I'm sorry, but could I use your bathroom for a second?
Of course! It's down the stairs to your right.
Talk about bad timing...
Moron.
Ah, I'm really sorry about this... My mom just doesn't know when to back off.
Don't worry about it.
Should we finish where we left off?
Huh? Ah... yeah.
Where were we again? Oh, yeah.
Before I answer, I'd first like to ask you something.
What do you think happened between us?
U-Umm...
If you suddenly ask me like that...
If you ask me that, I don't know... that's why I asked you.
Yamamoto and I were in the same class all three years of middle school, and...
...my seat was next to hers once.
Since our student numbers were close, we were the daily helpers together every once in a while.
We hardly ever spoke.
We never had any fights, and neither of us confessed love to each other or anything.
The scale of your question's too wide that I can't answer it.
Do you have any other questions?
Did Yamamoto-san... love you?
That's the first time I've ever heard anything like that.
I...
During the field trip...
...you touched Yamamoto-san's forehead without a single drop of hesitation, right?
That's been bugging me this whole time.
I might've been jealous of her the entire time...
This is probably...
Yano... how do you feel...
...what I wanted to ask the most this whole time...
...about Yamamoto-san?
Who cares about her.
I don't care whether Yamamoto loved or hated me.
It has nothing to do with me. Not interested one bit.
Hey...
You know the opposite of "love" isn't hate.
Then...
There was nothing between you two.
Of course there wasn't.
Relax.
I see... I...
...wanted him to reassure me...
...that everything would be fine.
Yano I... believe you.
City Bus
Bye.
I'll call you later tonight.
I believe you.
I'm sorry, Takahashi...
I asked Yano directly!
It was just like you said, Takeuchi-kun. He said there was nothing between them.
I knew it.
Takahashi, you worry too much about those things.
I'm glad.
Yeah, me too!
Thanks a lot, Takeuchi-kun!
Now that I think about it, there's no way you wouldn't have noticed something happening, right?
You changed your bangs.
Y-Yeah, I tried splitting them. Does it look strange?
You look cute.
Girl's Bathroom
He said I look cute.
Nana, did you finally do it?!
Yano came to your place, didn't he?
We haven't done anything yet... That's still a long way off.
Yano's being forced to hold back, I see.
I-Is it all that strange?
No... "to each her own" is my motto. So I guess it's all right?
But, but... the pressure's building up more and more every day...
Why are you against it, Nana?
I'm not exactly against it, I'm just not really sure how I feel about it...
Unlike Yano, it's not like it's always welling up inside me all the time.
So when he suggests doing it, it's a little scary, don't you think?
Even if it doesn't well up in you...
I totally agree with you!
Nana, you don't have to push yourself to do it. Right?!
You need to hurry up and get a boyfriend, too.
At least, that's what Mizu-chin said, but...
Moving onto question #5... Yano.
Yano!
Ah... yeah.
You're up for question #5, part A.
Question #5, question #5...
#5) a
Replace the underlined phase with another
expression that has the same meaning.
She was so beautiful that I wanted to make friend with her.
And the translation?
She was so beautiful that... umm... I wanted to make friends with her.
All right. Now replace that underline phrase with another expression that has the same meaning.
Umm...
She was so beautiful that I wanted to... to...
Make... friends with her?
Intimacy?
Go out with her?
"Get acquainted with..."
"Get acquainted with."
What's this? Didn't you do the assignment?
I wanted to... to... make love with her.
"I wanted to make love with her."
Well... grammatically, it isn't wrong, but...
Could you come up with another phrasing?
Fuck her.
"Fuck her."
I wonder if it all really has built up inside him...?
Thanks for before.
Yeah... he's really holding it in.
Poor Yano.
I wonder what Nana's gonna do?
I'm sure she'll reach her limit sooner or later.
After all, there is that story about Yano...
Ah, yeah, you're talking about that, right?
Does Nana know about it?
I don't think so.
I think we should keep it a secret...
...from Nana.
Dispenser
A story about him...?
Lend me your Math textbook?
Huh? At least knock first.
You didn't even ring the doorbell.
Ah, fine, fine.
Excuse me for intruding.
So where is it?
It should be on the shelf over there.
Unusual for you to ask, though.
That girl sitting next to me wouldn't show me hers.
Hey, it's not here.
Ah, maybe in one of the drawers.
Did you get a haircut?
I just changed the mousse I use.
Organize your stuff, geez.
Who's sitting next to you now?
Yamamoto.
That must be something.
What do you mean?
What's up with both you and Takahashi asking about her?
She's suspicious of me.
She thinks something happened between Yamamoto and me...
...when nothing like that did.
Something did.
I'm gonna borrow this.
I saw...
...you two go home together that day.
Holding hands, you went over to her house, didn't you?
I saw it.
Incense.
We went to put some up.
Sorry for failing to meet your expectations.
Motoharu! Don't you think you can fool me, too.
It pisses me off.
Why...
...did you pretend not to know until now?
I didn't pretend not to know. You simply didn't tell me.
How...
...could you do it with her little sister?
How...?
Yano.
This is... her room, isn't it?
I'm using it now.
The sun comes in best through here.
Onee-chan's room is now over there.
Though it's now the family altar room.
Nana, I hear you're finally going over to Yano's today?
It's not what you think.
We're just going to do a report together.
But his parents won't be around!
No, they'll be there.
If they weren't, I wouldn't go.
Go for it!
I'm telling you, it's not like that.
Don't worry! You're his girlfriend, so have so more confidence!
Ah, crap.
Nana-chan, wanna get some steamed meat buns at the convenience store?
I'm not hungry, so don't bother.
She seems to be in a bad mood.
Nana-chan. Is looking at the scenery fun?
Look at me, damn it.
Ah, that's the swimming school I used to go to.
Oh? When was this?
Till my first year of middle school.
Why'd you quit?
"Why?", because there was a really fast guy I could never beat.
So I thought it was stupid, and quit.
I see... so unless you're first, you're never satisfied?
So hey... what is this?
What do you mean? It's a hand. Mine, to be more specific.
Does it look like a foot to you?
Yano, quit the lame jokes.
It tickles!
They look so happy...
Like they don't have a care in the world.
Why do we seem to keep...
...running into one problem after another?
Excuse me for intruding.
"Motoharu, I'm going to my doctor's appointment."
Motoharu.
I'm going to my doctor's appointment.
I'm going shopping after that, so I might
be a little late. Your dinner is ready and
waiting in the freezer
"I'm going shopping after that, so I might be a little late."
"Your dinner is ready and waiting in the freezer."
So she's out for the day...
Y-You tricked me!
N-No! This is pure coincidence!
You're so mean!
I'm telling you, it's not what you think!
You're lying! You're trying to get back at me for the other day!
Are you a moron? If I was gonna do that, I would've done it fair and square!
What do you mean, "If I was gonna do that"?!
God... will I be able to protect myself...
I'm telling you...!
...in this house today?
I'm telling you, it's fine.
Don't make me repeat myself.
So could you sit... a little closer?
No... it's hot in this room.
Then why don't you take off your sweater?
Wasn't
really
implying
anything
...
Black tea's okay?
One spoon of sugar, right?
Ah, I'll help.
If you trap the steam, it tastes better.
What a clean kitchen...
It feels kinda strange when two of us stand here like this, like we're married or something.
What kind of stupid things am I thinking?
I'm having a delusion!
Umm...
Is she feeling better?
My mom and dad started going out in high school, and got married after ten years of dating.
You serious? That's hard to believe. I'm surprised it lasted so long.
Ah... crap.
Well, I guess me and Yano getting married after going out together...
...might only be the unrealistic delusion I thought it was, but...
I see... the person standing here ten years from now may not be me...
Sit next to me, Takahashi.
The more my love for him increases, the more lonely I think I'll be...
Okay, okay. I won't say anything to make you uncomfortable.
English
I won't screw around when we're working on English.
I'll hide my gum in a place where you can't see it.
And I won't touch you at all today.
I promise.
How about it?
You can't... Can you really just change your principles for one girl?
I can't for my friends and other people, but for a woman, I can change them as much as necessary.
Those are my principles.
Get it?
So, why don't you...
...tell me why you're in such a bad mood today.
During middle school...
...is it true that you had sex with Nana-san in school gym?
If it's not one thing, it's another...
Like I was saying, you did, didn't you? In the gym.
Ah... yeah.
I don't...
...intend to blame you for things in the past.
Since there's nothing I can do about it.
It's fine.
It's fine?
Even if I'm jealous of Yano's past, there's nothing I can do about it.
Even ten years from now, Yano will still be the same.
I should already know that...
But why do I still feel I want Yano all for myself?
Honestly...
His hand...
...didn't bug me at all.
That was close, that was close.
I almost touched you.
Math I
It'll be hard for me to hold back if I sit close to you, so I'll sit on the side.
I have to keep my promise, after all.
Moron.
Takahashi.
I wish I could rewrite my past.
But I can't.
If I could, I'd do all I could...
...if it would stop you from crying.
But... that's impossible.
My past won't change.
That's why... we need to make my past pale in comparison to our present.
I've always wanted... to make someone my own.
I guess I say some pretty stuff now now and then, huh?
Yano.
I-It's fine by me...
I said it--
What is?
Don't tell me you mean sex?
Just kidding!
Taisetsu na anata no hitomi ni
I wonder if I'm reflected
Watashi wa utsutteru no ka na
in your precious eyes?
Kimorehi zashikomu madobe ni wa
I wonder how I can always be happy
I wonder if I'm caught in the flow of it all...?
Doushite yasashiku narerun darou
on the windowsill where the sunshine always falls?
But...
Kokoro kakushite kodou kakushite
I hide my true feelings and the thumping of my heart.
I don't see any reason...
Itsumo no you ni
As always,
...to hold these feelings back.
Wakariaenai tsurasa ga tamaranai
the pain of being able to understand each other burns.
Waraitai waraitai kokoro no mannaka de
I want to smile, I want to smile, down to the core of my heart.
Anata ni wa uchiakeyou
I'll open up to you
Tsuyogaru watashi yowaki na watashi
about how I pretend to be strong, about how I'm weak,
Kinou no hanashi dou demo ii koto mo zenbu
about what happened yesterday, about everything that means nothing.
Aishiteru kore kara mo zuttoo
I'll continue to love you forever.
Ude wo kunde aruite ikou YEAH!
Take my arm and let's walk. Yeah!
Kimi wo sagashite kimi wo sagashite
I look for you, I look for you,
Donna toki demo kimi wo sagashiteiru kedo
I'm always looking for you,
Mitsukaru no sore wa kimi na no?
but when I find that person, is it really you?
Kanashikute kanashikute nakidashisou ni naru
I'm so sad, I'm so sad, I could cry.
Dore dake no omoi nara dakishimete kureru no?
How much feeling must I give to be able to embrace you?
Ah waraitai waraitai
Ah, I want to smile, I want to smile.
Nani mo ka mo nagesutete
Throwing everything away,
Episode 9 Preview...
Anata ni wa uchiakeyou
I'll open up to you.
For some reason, it's come to this...
Kinou no hanashi ashita no hanashi
About yesterday, about tomorrow,
And I don't know
how it's come to this, but...
...I really don't understand
how I was the one to suggest it...
Futari no mirai kakaekirenai hodo zenbu
about our future and everything, so much that I can't even take it all myself.
Yakusoku wa shinakutemo ii yo
You don't have to promise me anything.
Ah, geez!
He's already getting naked!
Futari massugu ni arukou YEAH!
Let's just keep walking. Yeah!
If you're scared, we can stop here.
Please make me your own.