Stop! Stop!
Wait for the traffic light!
Something interesting's bound to happen this year...
Who will end up crying, and who will be left laughing?
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 16 ...
We won't be able to make it any smaller than this.
Doesn't matter. It's going into the bonfire anyway.
Are we really gonna light it all on fire?
I'll take back what I said before.
What I said on the day of the summer festival.
I don't say things like "no matter what happens, we'll always be friends".
After all, there's no one who could replace you.
That's why I'm going to try my hardest to keep our friendship intact.
I guess I must like you or something.
This must be the real "confession time", huh?
Just kidding.
I'm glad you're my friend.
You better make sure you don't forget those words.
W-What the hell?! What are you guys doing here?!
Hold him down!
Hurry and tie him up!
Don't hate us for this!
Don't hate you for this? Moto! Help me!
I told you that I'd try my hardest to keep our friendship intact, didn't I?
If everything goes well between me and Takahashi, everything will be fine!
That's why I'm not going to let you confess to her.
This is the best way to do that, right?
T-That's dirty!
You're too naive.
Sorry! Once I'm all finished, I'll let you go.
Love you, Take-chan!
See ya!
H-Hey!
Ah, carry him over to the science room.
Moto!
I didn't want this kind of confession!
They just turned on the music.
Here comes the time for confessions this year!
Ah, look over there! He's confessing to her!
No way!
I do!
Jama da te wo futta ushirosugata anna ni mou
Everyone's in the way. I waved my hand, but your back is
Are we getting married out here?
You're crazy.
Yuugure no hitonami ni yurenagara chiisaku naru
already swerving through the crowd of people and sinking into the evening sun.
Takahashi.
I'll only say this once, so listen carefully.
Anata ga kureta kotoba wo hitotsuzutsu
I closed my eyes and began to remember
I love you.
Omoidashi me wo tojita Shiawasena omoi dake
the words you told me. Only happy memories
Every time I remember, my heart beats so fast... as if it happened only yesterday.
koko ni aru hazu nano ni Fuan ni naru
are supposed to be there, but I become anxious.
Umm, excuse me...
Do you have a minute?
Doushite nano kokoro ga furueteru no
Why does my heart waver so?
I'm sorry. Save it for later.
Later...?
Mizuguchi.
Tsutaetai motto sou afureteru kono kimochi
I want to tell you about my overflowing feelings...
Hello?
Nana. Where are you right now?
Huh? I'm helping out at the announcement booth.
Something happen?
How can you ask something like that right now?
Suki dakara suki dakara zettai suki dakara
"I love you, I love you, I love you more than anything."
He's here...
The announcement booth?
Tell her I'll be right there, so stay put!
Yano just left, headed your way.
And one more thing...
If my intuition's correct, Takeuchi-kun's coming, too.
Think hard about it and give them an answer, okay?
No way...
Both of them are coming...
What'll I do...?
Is Takahashi here?!
Huh? She was just here a minute ago...
Did she go somewhere?
Huh?
She ran away, didn't she?
I... I couldn't help...
...running away.
Doko ni Itemo donna toki mo
Wherever I am, whatever time it may be
Kimi ga kieta hi kara
you're always there for me.
Kesenai omoide nokoshite
And I'll accept that because
Uketomeyou
these memories won't fade.
What'll I do?
Tomadoi wa itsuka fukai umi de
One day, under the deep sea, the time we had
I'm still not sure about my feelings...
Aoi suna ni natte
will become blue sand.
Damn it! They locked me in!
Out of my way!
Samenai omoi issho ni
And I wonder if it'll be put to sleep
Nemuru no darou
like these undying feelings I have right now...
It's no good... I'm too much of a coward...
I'm too gutless to actually break the glass...
Kimi ga inai kono beddo de
I'm quivering alone
I'm sure he could shatter it without a second thought!
You're too naive.
Hitori yureteiru
in this bed without you.
Negaeri wo uttara aozora ga mieta
But when I rolled over, I couldn't see the blue sky.
I have my own way of doing things.
I can drop down onto the roof of that storage shed.
If I screw up... I'll come back as a ghost and haunt you!
Kono heya kara
You always loved
Takahashi!
Mieru machi ga
looking out at the town
Kimi wa suki datta ne
from this room, didn't you?
Takahashi!
Toorisugiru kisetsu wa
The passing seasons
Yasashikatta
were gentle to us.
Kaii ni natte hanasenaku natte
Things got awkward, and we became unable to speak to each other,
Kimi wa umi he kaetta
and you returned to the sea.
I'm sorry, Yano...
I'm... too much of a coward...
Dakedo ichiban chikaku de
But I feel that you're still
Tomo ni ikiteiru
living the closest to me, with me.
Where are you?
Toriageru samishisa ni
When I accept the loneliness
Pick up!
Takahashi... Takahashi!
Makaseyou na toki wa
I try to leave it to someone else
I cannot pick up the phone right now.
Sukoshi dake raku kara
because it's a little easier that way.
Damn it!
Takahashi--
Yoake moratte
Come dawn,
I won't let you go to her!
Hey! Let go of me!
As if!
When did you even...?!
Kimi ga inai kono beddo de
I'm in this bed without you
Too bad for you, huh?
God damn it! I won't forgive you for this!
That's my line!
I'll get to her first!
I'll die before I let you!
You wanna fight?!
Hitori yureteiru
quivering alone.
Damn straight!
Enough!
Hitomi wo tojitara aozora ga mieta
But when I close my eyes, I can see the blue sky.
Fighting over her is useless.
She doesn't want to talk to anyone right now.
Let her be.
She... wanted me to pass that along.
It just means she doesn't want to hear us right now.
That's it, right?
That's pretty much her answer, isn't it?
What the hell is up with that...?
If she doesn't want to hear us out, she should tell us to our faces.
If she wants to refuse us, she should say so herself!
Please try to understand Nana's feelings.
I can't.
Well... I can sort of understand how Yano feels, too...
Hey. Do you know how to forget about an old love?
You find a new love.
If that new love is true, then the old love will naturally become part of the past.
What is... true love?
Takahashi.
You're in there, aren't you?
Please say something.
You're not being fair, running away like this.
Why are you hiding?
It's not like you.
Come on out.
But I can't come up with an answer!
I don't know what's best... what's most right...
Will I be able to get through this without crying?
No matter how much I think about it, I just don't know...
I don't want to be hurt anymore...
I don't want to hurt anyone, either.
Hey, Takahashi...
I don't think anyone wants to hurt anyone else...
But I think the person... or people...
...you don't want to hurt are probably ready for it if it turns out that way.
And of course, no one wants to make you suffer.
But... in the end, if it has to be that way...
...those other people are the ones who are wrong, not you.
You should stay hidden like this tonight, Takahashi.
But... can I say one thing?
Takahashi... no one knows what's the best, or what the future holds.
Until you actually see the results, no one ever knows.
So at the very least, why don't we rely on what we do know?
Let's keep the feelings we have right now precious.
The feelings I have right now...
Can I really...
...return to those days?
You found...
...your answer, didn't you?
It's that easy.
Goodbye.
And of course, no one wants to make you suffer.
Takeuchi-kun!
Is that all you came for?
Didn't you have something you wanted to say to me?
Like... didn't you have another reason to come?
Yeah.
What was it?
I...
Moto and I...
...were looking for you.
I thought I'd say that... but anyway, hurry and go see him.
He's being really sulky.
You're both... so nice...
I need to answer you...
Yano, where are you?
I'll give you as much love as you want!
Hora natsu no yozora ni hoshi ga mata hitotsu nagareta
Look, another star shot by in the summer's night sky.
I'm watching you, so...!
I'm always watching you, so...!
I'm always watching over you, so...!
Nanami, you big liar...
Kokorogoto karadamoto subettete koi wo shitteiru watashitachi
We lovers could feel it in our hearts and upon our bodies.
I don't want to hurt him...
...but I get hurt by him, and I run away...
And then I chase after him again...
Why do we keep falling in love with each other?
Tsunaideiru kono te no nukumori dake de
With just the warmth of your hand holding mine,
Doko made demo yuketara tobeta nara ii no ni
I feel like I could go anywhere, fly anywhere.
Hoshi wo kazoeru yori mo
Instead of counting the infinite stars,
Kou shite kimi to zutto
I'd rather stay like this with you,
Zutto tsunagattetai yo
forever connected to you.
Tatoe kizutsuite kizutsukete shimattemo
Even if I get hurt, or hurt you,
Dou shiyou
I don't know what I'd do.
Daisuki da yo
But I love you.
Why did you come?
Because I thought you'd be crying.
I'm not crying, damn it...
I'm not...
Hora kimi ga warau darou mune ga chiisaku takanaru
Look, you're smiling, and your heart must be beating faster.
You've always annoyed me from the start...
You say your own selfish things, and you stir up all my feelings...
You're so clingy...
Jouzu ni kotoba ni dekinai ni dekinai bukiyou na watashitachi
We're clumsy, and we can't say things very easily.
...but then you leave me and go away so easily.
You're cruel.
Yet despite all that...
...I love you.
You annoy me.
"I wish I could rewrite my past."
Ashita mo todokanakute kinou demo naku
I'd like to keep the feelings we have now precious
"But I can't."
"That's impossible."
What kind of present will make your past pale in comparison?
Ima no kono kimochi taisetsu ni shitain da
and not wait for them to arrive tomorrow, or have missed them yesterday.
Something like this...
A reality where I exist and you're there next to me.
Yume wo egaku yori mo
Instead of painting my dreams,
Will I be able to become stronger...?
Kou shite kimi to zutto
I'd rather stay like this with you,
Zutto dakiattetai yo
forever embraced.
I have a condition.
Tell me all about Nana-san.
Kimi wo mamoritai
I want to protect you
I don't know much about her.
Tsuyoku haneru you ni
so you'll strongly leap into my arms.
I haven't pressed the issue so far because I've been thinking of you.
Dou shiyou
I don't know what I'll do
I want to hear about your feelings for her, and once I sort out my feelings about them...
Daisuki da yo
but I love you.
...I think I might be able to keep going with you.
It might be difficult for you, but... I think it's necessary for this to work.
I want you tell me about Nana-san with your own words from your own mouth.
If you can't do that, I can't come back.
Can you?
I didn't see the meaning in doing something like that...
Will you just run away from it?
I guess you would. There's no way you could confront it now.
After all, you've been running from it for two whole years now.
Who said I couldn't do it?
So you do feel like talking about it.
If you can do it, and do it well, I'll give you this as a present.
You...!
Didn't you tell me you erased it?!
I asked you over and over, but you kept telling me you didn't have it, didn't you?!
I was obviously lying.
Looks like you're a little naive yourself.
Don't worry. I won't try to pull you down.
I just want to say that now that Takahashi's serious, you'd better get serious, too.
If you only take a half-assed attitude towards this, you have no right to make up with her.
That's so lame!
Shut up.
So in the end, you didn't confess to her at all?
Shizuka na ame ga furu
A silent rain falls.
There's no way I could...
...when she so clearly knows who her heart wants to be with.
Sukoshi tsumetai ame
A slightly chilly rain.
Why are you going about this in such a roundabout way?
Atattaneai tsudzuketeru
But it continues to fall, without actually hitting me
As long I'm going out with Yano, we'll eventually run into this problem again...
Kono kokoro wo hiyasu you ni
as if it's trying to freeze my heart instead.
I wonder if he'll be able to talk about it...
He told me he would.
I'm kind of interested to know how he feels in his heart.
Itsumo kimi wo mitsuketeita
I've always found your gentle back
Umm... Takeuchi-kun, would you listen with me to the story about Nana-san?
Yasashiii ushirosugata mawari iku kono omoi
on any day, but where do my
Huh? Me?
Honestly, I'm really uneasy about it...
Doko he mukau no
winding feelings point?
I'm also a really nice person, I guess.
Huh?
Kimi ga mitsumeru saki ni wa
I wonder what you see
Nani ga aru darou
before you?
Or maybe...
Bokura wa hitahashiru
We keep on running
...I just don't know when to give up.
Todokisou de todokanai
and we seem like we're going to reach, but don't.
Sono kyori de
At that distance away from you.
Shizuka ni ame ga furu
Rain will fall again someday.
Sukoshi tsumetai ame
A slightly lonely rain
Hirogaritsudzuketeru
will pour all around and spread
Kono kokoro wo nademeru you ni
as if it's meant to soothe my heart.
Itsumo kimi wo mitsumeteiru
I'm always looking at your cute back
Kawaii ushirosugata mawari iku kono omoi
but these winding feelings
Doko ni mukau no
point me in the other direction.
Boku ga motomer saki ni wa
What am I waiting for
Nani ga matsu darou
at the end of my search?
Bokura wa hitahashiru
We keep on running
Oitsukesou de oitsukanai
and we seem like we're going to reach, but don't.
Sono kyori de
At that distance away from you.
Episode 17 Preview...
I met her in my
second year of middle school...
Bokura wa hitahashiru
We keep on running
...and she accidentally died in
the summer of my third year.
That's all.
Takahashi... are you
sure it's not Moto...
Todokisou de todokanai
and we seem like we're going to reach, but don't.
...but you who's so
obsessed with Nana-san?
Oh, just forget it...
There's no helping it today.
It'll just be a normal date.
Sono kyori de
At that distance away from you.
I've never done
anything with my dad before.
Sono kyori de
At that distance away from you.
My chest hurts...
Sono kyori de
At that distance away from you.