Huh? Where'd I put my pass?
Ah, here it is.
Moto, I just remembered some things I need to take care of.
I gave you my final notice this morning.
Didn't I tell you...
...you'd regret it?
Sorry!
Hey!
Love is...
The timing...
...all about timing!
Usotsuki na anata nakimushi no atashi
Why can't things go well between
Doushite umaku ikanai wa
the liar, you, and the crybaby, me?
Oshare shita kami mo rain suton no tsume mo
You don't notice my styled hair
Anata wa kidzuki mo shinai ne
or my nice set of press-on nails.
Love kanashii namida nanka ja nai yo
Love isn't about the unhappy tears that go along with it.
Me ga kawaite hirihiri suru dake
Those tears only leave my eyes dry and hurt me.
Kono unmei bakari I love
I love this destiny
Kimi dake wo atashi dake wo
between only you and only me.
Atsui omoi wo uketomete
I want to accept your hot feelings
Doko made mo tsunagattetai
and be taken by you forever.
Kawaikunai nakigao mo se mo aishiteru
Despite your uncute, tearful face and your shortness, I still love you.
Episode 14 ...
Wha...
What the fuck?!
C-Calm down! You're on the bus!
Pick up! Hurry and answer your phone!
I cannot answer the phone right now, but after the beep...
Take! If you lay a finger on her, I'll fucking kill you!
The use of cellphones while on the bus is...
We're terribly sorry!
Hey! Are you getting off?
What are you planning on doing?
I'm going to stop him.
Puppies are just sooo adorable!
Y-Yeah...
Mizu-chin... it won't be able to breathe if you hug it that hard...
Let me hold him, too.
No! He's mine!
Come on, come on.
I might have completely...
...missed the timing for this.
Takeuchi-kun!
Take a picture for me?
Well, I guess it's okay.
Menu                     Settings                    Back
Save                  Text Msg                 Cancel
I see... so you found someone to take care of them.
Yeah. I'm going to drop this one off at relative's house next week.
Honestly, I wanted to keep one here.
Wait up, wait up!
Who did the other one go to?
A neighbour.
Then that means I'll still be able to see them again, right?
Um... yeah, I guess.
Voice Mail
1 New Message
If you lay a finger on her, I'll fucking kill you!
Heeey! Wait up!
Come on, puppy! Woof, woof! Wait up!
Come on, wait, you...!
Waaait!
When he came over...
...my heart raced for a second.
But Mizu-chin's here, too...
...so I shouldn't attach any special meaning to it... right?
Now that I started thinking about this, it's suddenly become hard to talk...
Um, hey...
Y-Yeah?
Ah, sorry. Phone call for me.
It's from my house.
Yes?
Masa?
Mom was hoping you could make some deliveries that were just ordered.
Ah... yeah. I'll take care of them when I get home.
And when will that be?
Dunno. In a bit.
When exactly is "in a bit"? We're in kind of a hurry here.
Soon, soon. I'll be there.
He's so persistent...
By the way, where are you now?
Oh? He hung up on me.
That boy's really smart... unexpectedly.
He must take after me.
Damn it. Where the hell did he go?
Let me say that I've never even touched any of his girlfriends.
So, what's up with this?!
Takeuchi might've learned that it's more fair to outwit someone in a fight...
...even if it's someone close to him.
Shut up! Takahashi's my girl!
Though she dumped me...
Poor you.
You worked up quite a sweat running here, didn't you?
You didn't even consider your best friend betraying you, huh?
Should I teach you some points to assure certain victory in love?
One. Pick the right partner.
Two. Be honest.
If you try to skip one or the other, it won't work at out all.
Who's the "right partner"?
Isn't loving someone good enough?
In the end, people can only be together with the one they're fated to be with.
Whatever. If fate isn't involved, then I'll just make my own.
You're pretty confident.
Screw that.
But... when you fall in love with someone, I want to believe that it's because of fate.
Go ahead and laugh.
Then you're just lacking the honesty.
I'll tell you another good thing.
From what I can remember, they took the puppies and made a right in that direction.
They're probably at the park near the supermarket.
Ayaka, they didn't take a right. They took a left didn't they?
You're so mean.
Adolescence is so annoying, don't you think?
Never mind.
It's good for them to experience pain while they're young.
If they have strong spirits, they should be able to surpass any difficulties.
No... instead, aren't you just having fun with this?
Fight, fight... and become good men, you two.
Wait up, wait up!
Come on, come on! Bark, bark! Bark, bark!
Over here, over here!
Run away!
Wait, wait! Wait, you!
Oh, no! Sir magistrate, you!
Isn't it all right? Isn't it all right?!
I-I'm getting tired of this already...
I'm giving you two time alone, so what the heck are you doing?!
Please, just talk to each other!
Mi-Mizuguchi really loves dogs, huh...?
It surprised me...
She's had her eyes set on him the entire time...
Yeah... definitely. She doesn't seem to get sick of him...
Mizu-chin totally took up all of my attention, and we've wasted all this time in silence...
I wonder if he took it the wrong way...
I hope I didn't make him feel bad...
Why is this even bugging m--
I... th-think... I-I'm gonna take a... l-little b-break...
Ah, sorry! I interfered!
No! Not at all!
Not at... all...
I... I see...
W-What is this? It's just my imagination.
I'm such a moron for being so self-conscious about this...
Besides, I'm the ex of Takeuchi-kun's best friend.
It's obvious why Takeuchi-kun's being nice to me.
There's no way there's any special meaning to this.
That bitch tricked me!
If I took a second to think about it, I would've realized it!
They took the dogs... they took the dogs with them... Obviously, they'd be by the riverbed!
What am I doing?
Isn't the bus stop that way?
No... it's faster to go this way.
I think the bus should arrive soon.
Ah, really?
Takahashi... you might think you've broken up with me, but I don't accept it.
I don't think we've broken up.
You might think you're not good enough, but...
...that's not something for you to decide. It's for me.
Here's the bus.
Get on.
Y-Yeah.
Takahashi!
If you're saying that I'm not good enough, then I'll do whatever it takes!
I'll do whatever it takes from now on!
Whatever it takes!
I'll do whatever it takes for you!
I won't hold anything back!
I'll give you everything! Listen to me! I'll...!
I'll...
...wait for you...
...to return.
I'll be waiting.
The bus fee...
Y-Yes!
Why did you say that now, of all times...?
"I'll be waiting..."
Hey.
Shut up. Don't talk to me.
You're dirty.
Since when did you have a dog?
Why don't you take it?
I told you I'd kill you if you laid a finger on her.
I wasn't kidding.
You better remember that.
I'm prepared for that.
It's the period of the Warring States again, I guess.
How scary! Woof woof!
She brought this with her, didn't she?
How do you know?
I know because it's like her.
H-Hey. Give it back.
No.
Masa, what were you doing walking around in your school uniform like that?
Not much.
A lot of deliveries have piled up.
Did you meet up with Moto?
He was looking for you.
Ah... yeah.
The girl you were with today was his girlfriend, wasn't she?
Or should I say his ex girlfriend?
Which would mean...
Shut up!
You're pretty good.
Good luck.
Here you go. It's a toy.
You remembered where the bathroom was, so it's your reward.
Like it?
I'm glad.
Motoharu.
Are you back? The bath's all heated up, so go take one.
Don't bring that dog you brought home with you into the bath.
I'll be fine.
I won't be.
Ah, and you handed in your career search paper all on your own, didn't you?
You left the parent/guardian signature line blank...
My career is my own problem, isn't it?
It's your family's problem.
Talk to your father about it.
After all... the ones who pay are your parents, huh...?
It'd be nice... if you could hurry and see Nana-chan again soon.
Umm... something like this.
What the heck is that?
You big moron!
This is just hilariously bad.
You sure said it!
Me? I didn't say anything like that!
Something like that's not in Disneyland!
Isn't it about time to go?
Where are you guys going?
Bathroom.
It's time to go to the bathroom!
Sounds suspicious to me.
Ah, Ya-...
What is it?
U-Um... uh...
Your suggestion of Disneyland the other day...
T-They didn't approve it at the student council meeting.
I'm sorry... it was a really good idea, too...
Apparently, there's a lot of stuff when dealing with the copyright on Disney...
Ah... I see.
Is that all?
Y-Yeah.
...to return!
Even if you say that...
What am I supposed to do?
Hey... don't you think she's a lot cuter with her hair down like that?
Don't you think so?
I think it's just your imagination.
It definitely is.
It's the same hairstyle as when she had me undress her...
Is she trying to get at me...?
This is no good. When I look at her head during class, I can't concentrate at all.
What?
2 - 7 Summer break
Takahashi. Need me to do anything?
U-Umm, could you do some painting?
Yeah. I pretty much finished it.
Are you carrying that?
Ah... yeah.
Give it to me.
Th-Thanks.
Yano sure is devoted this year!
Completely different from last year.
This is...
Takahashi!
Work, please!
Yes!
Takahashi, I'm done!
Do this next!
Takahashi, I'll carry that!
O-Okay.
Takahashi.
Yano?!
I can really see your motivation!
That's why I'll leave the big job to you!
Huh? Weren't you the head of the float group?
NEW person
in charge and
responsible
for the cafe
Exile...?
She exiled me...?
Takeuchi-kun.
Drink this. It's nice and cold.
Here you go?
Ah, thanks. Could you leave it over there?
I actually gave it to him!
I really can't drink this sweet stuff...
Where are you going?!
Why are you...?!
Oh, a sugar-filled drink?
You can't drink this, can you?
I'll drink it for you!
Let go!
I'm busy working on the cafe with the rest of the group. This isn't a fair fight.
Therefore, approaching her is forbidden while working on the school festival.
She didn't like you out here, right?
And furthermore, why is the head of the café group out here in the courtyard?
Nana. There's something I want to talk to you about.
Shoot! Hide!
She'll find out that I'm already slacking off!
Don't you think Takeuchi-kun likes you, Nana? That's how it looks to me...
N-No way...
You should be able to tell just by looking. You can be really slow sometimes.
B-But Takeuchi-kun is friends with Yano.
He wouldn't do something like fall in love with his friend's ex.
Takeuchi-kun isn't that type of person.
It's not possible.
I-If you put it like that, you're pretty persuasive...
Then, what about Yano?
What do you plan to do about him? You even threw him inside for the café.
Isn't he working his hardest for you?
Are you thinking of starting over at some point?
Yano...
When he does stuff like this, it bothers me.
Honestly, I don't know how to react to it...
I wish he'd leave me alone...
Right now, I want to be alone... and have some time to think.
Hey...
It's no big deal.
It isn't.
Being pushed away...
It doesn't bug me one bit.
I've learned my lesson.
This is still much better than her leaving and not being able to do anything about it.
I'm lucky.
Don't you think?
I won't lose to you.
Negai hoshi hitotsu yurete
A single wishing star twinkles
Shiawasena kimochi de nemuru
and I sleep happily.
Mou aitaku natteiru sakki sayonara shita bakari
I already want to see you, even though we just said our goodbyes.
Na no ni
Yet...
Kimi no ai ha totemo ookikutte
Your love is so large
Yozora no youni tsutsunde kureru
that it wraps me up like the blue sky above.
Wow moshi namida ga yattekitemo
Even if there are tears coming.
Kitto heiki watashi dake no kimi ga iru
I'm sure I'll be fine because you're there, the only one for me.
Ai ha totemo ookikutte
Your love is so large
Yozora no youni tsutsunde kureru
that it wraps me up like the blue sky above.
Moshi namida ga yattekitemo
Even if there are tears coming,
Kitto heiki watashi dake no kimi ga iru
I'm sure I'll be fine because you're there, the only one for me.
Episode 15 Preview ...
Even though we broke up,
I still don't want to hurt him?
Excuse me.
She's my girlfriend, so
would you please not do that?
How is one able...
to forget about the dead?
You turn them into memories.
Who will be left crying,
and who will be left laughing?