Why did Kyousuke say that?
I won't lead the Little Busters from now on.
From this moment on, Riki,
you are the leader of the Little Busters!
I'm the leader?
This has to be another one of his jokes.
He's just screwing with me.
Yahoo!
The Little Busters are the best!
It's time for baseball!
I'm so pumped up!
What the heck?
Yo.
Wh-What's with that jacket?
Oh, I made this Little Busters jacket myself.
Huh?!
You made it yourself?!
Even the embroidery?!
Creepy.
You made this logo yourself too?
Yeah.
It took me all night.
What do you think?
I'm not sure what to think.
I'm honestly feeling really happy right now.
Let's go!
Time for some baseball! Time for morning practice!
Kengo's turned into an idiot.
What the heck's going on?
A screw must've come loose when he jumped off the roof!
He probably always had the potential to be like this.
I didn't think he'd go straight to top gear though.
Everyone! Let's go!
Alright!
We'll head over with the Little Busters March I thought up!
One, two, Little Busters!
That's great for muscles too!
Three, four, Little Busters!
One, two, Little Busters!
At long last, Kengo has joined us.
Playing baseball with these members...
Three, four, Little Busters!
It's like we're kids again.
And everyone else is here too.
Game time!
We're winning this!
Wafu!
Tomorrow is our first game!
Episode 26
The Best Friends Ever
Alright.
Let's do some final touch-ups before our first game.
What are we going to practice, Riki?
You're in charge, you know.
I am?
I already told you,
I'm not the leader anymore.
Are you serious, Kyousuke?
Of course.
I'm a third-year.
It's about time I drew the line.
I'm thinking of leaving everything to you from here on.
W-Wait, this is way too sudden!
I've been thinking about it for a while now.
Ever since we decided to start playing baseball,
I thought of some day making you the leader.
But I don't think everyone would agree—
Riki!                           Riki!
Ri-Ri-Ri-Ri-Riki-kun!
Riki-kun! Riki-kun!
Fan, fan, fan.
Makes sense. Kyousuke's got job searching to do, anyway.
You're kind of unreliable, but you'd make an okay leader!
Congratulations on being the new leader!
Congratulations!
Don't worry too much about it.
Just try giving it a shot.
Who knows, you might even be good at it.
Yeah.
You're undoubtedly much weaker than Kyousuke-san,
but that's also a moe point.
I have no objections as your manager.
Alright, so what should we practice first?
Why don't we do a roll call?
A roll call?
You know, that thing where you call out people's names and they count.
It would raise our morale.
I-I'll try it.
Kyousuke!
One!
Komari-san!
Huh?
Kurugaya-san!
What is it?
Saigusa-san!
Hup!
Kud!
Wafu!
Rin!
Can't you see I'm here?
Nishizono-san.
Yes, that would be me.
Masato...
Sorry, Riki!
I wanted to shout my number like I'm supposed to,
but I don't know what number I am!
I don't either.
Riki, what about me?
Sorry!
Kengo!
Nine!
It's... perfect.
All's well that ends well.
It would've been better not to do it...
Well, anyway, how about we all do some fielding practice?
Just what I wanted!
First order!
Yay!
Wait right there!
You're not allowed on the field today.
They're doing maintenance on it.
The school said they had already told Naoe-kun about it, seeing how his name was on the request form...
Huh?
It's off...
Looks like your first order immediately ended in failure.
Too bad about that. Let's do individual training!
Yeah!
Practice swings! That's right!
How about some snacks?
Snacks? Wafu!
Don't forget about the batting order and fielding positions for the game, as well as the strategy.
I'm looking forward to seeing them.
You look nothing like an actual leader.
I'm the leader?
Batting order, fielding positions, strategy...
Where on Earth do I even start?
What should I do?
Hey, Kyousuke—
That's right.
No matter what happened, I would always rely on Kyousuke.
It's been forever...
Ever since then...
Back when I had lost my parents and was all alone.
I was diagnosed with narcolepsy and was afraid of falling asleep at any second.
Despite my condition, Kyousuke took me into a world of fun and laughter.
Kyousuke's back protected me.
There was always something fun waiting for me when I followed Kyousuke.
Let's play baseball.
We'll call ourselves...
"Little Busters"!
He gave me courage.
If the world is full of things we never wanted to know,
is our only option to look the other way?
To run away?
You won't solve anything by running away.
Kyousuke!
I was thinking back.
I was always so small and worried.
But when I was with you,
all my worries and sadness would just disappear.
It's no different now.
We're having so much fun because you wanted to play baseball.
I can think of no other leader but you.
I want to keep following you.
You can't always rely on me.
Riki, you're not as small as you think.
You're simply unaware of the scale of the things that you've done.
But I know.
You've worried for others as much as they did.
You helped them overcome their hardship and saved them.
It was something only you could do.
The Little Busters consist of people that you gathered.
I'm not as amazing as you make me out to be.
You can't follow me forever.
You need to surpass me, Riki.
Become stronger.
Baseball Team
No no no...
Komari-san
moodmaker
it's over if she messes up!
Surpassing Kyousuke...
That never even occurred to me.
Riki...
Hang in there.
S-Saigusa-san?!
Did I scare you?
I was hiding in here.
I figured it'd make you smile.
I mean, you seem to be worried about something.
Well, I just don't think I can replace Kyousuke.
I'm not the type that can lead a bunch of people.
There's no way I can think of something to make everyone happy.
You know, if you weren't around,
I would probably still think the world was full of hate.
I would've been crushed by my own hate.
But because you faced my trouble with everything you had...
Because I watched you make everyone happy...
I can believe now.
That if people think about each other,
the world can be filled with light.
Thanks, Riki-kun.
Haru-chin will always be rooting for you.
Saigusa-san...
Yo, Mio-chin!
Are you finished with it?
I've collected some data.
Sure Win Databook
I looked into each member of the all-star team
and noted their habits and how to deal with them.
You can use this to think up a strategy against them.
You looked this much into it?
It's only normal for a manager.
But this is way more than normal!
I was always searching for a way to be of use to you.
Ever since I was a child, no one could remember me.
I was just a pebble on the side of the road.
If you had never called out to me,
I would have been alone forever.
I would have wished for everyone to forget about me.
But now, I'm living a satisfying life with everyone else.
I'm grateful that I was born.
I'd never imagined feeling like this before.
You gave me a miracle, Naoe-san.
I only thought about doing for you what Kyousuke had done for me, Nishizono-san.
Kyousuke is the reason I was able to do anything.
You're a great leader, Naoe-san.
Thank you.
Riki-kun,
congratulations on becoming leader.
Here's an invitation to a snack time to celebrate!
At the place closest to the sky!
The place closest to the sky, huh?
Aw, Riki-kun, you're already here!
Kuu-chan and Yui-chan are getting some tea right now.
Come on up!
Have a seat.
It's been a while since I saw the sky from up here.
Yeah.
You know, I'll never forget...
This was where you taught me not to run away from sad and painful things.
And that we can keep smiling when we're with everyone.
Komari-san...
Look, here's the picture book you drew for me.
You said that I'd have to draw the rest of it.
So, I did.
It's the Little Busters!
When one of them smiles, everyone smiles.
When one is happy, everyone is happy.
Everyone is in a happy, sunny place.
And that place is sunny because of you.
That's right.
It's because you gathered us all together.
Kud...
And you were the one who told me that I should just be myself.
So now it's my turn to say...
You should just be yourself!
I should just be myself?
You've helped us all already, so now it's our turn to support you.
That's the type of kind leader you are.
That's right.
Your kindness is your strength.
You haven't realized it yet, boy,
but your kindness drew all of us together.
And that is why we all trust you.
I came up with our batting order and fielding positions.
I've thought up a strategy too.
I want to tell everyone about them.
As the leader of the Little Busters.
I knew you could do it.
Kyousuke, I'm still weak right now.
But when I think about others, I feel like I can become stronger.
I want to become even stronger so that I can support everyone.
So that, one day, I can be as good a leader as you were.
Riki, ever since we were kids,
we shared our fun and laughter.
We've spent time together that made our hearts dance.
But every story has to come to an end.
No one can stay a kid forever.
Time passes, and people grow up.
There will come a day when we will no longer be together.
I know that you're graduating a year before us.
And that we'll all go our separate ways some day, ending all of the fun that we've had.
That's why you told me not to rely on you anymore, right?
Even without me, you'll be able to keep going.
I'm going to become stronger.
I know I will.
The day will come when we go our separate ways.
But for now, let's play some baseball!
Yeah!
Let's enjoy the fact that the Little Busters are one.
Alright.
Let's start the game.
My balls aren't good. They'll hit them.
Is that okay?
Rin, even if they hit them, we have your back.
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
That's right!
Rin-chan!
Wafu!
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
Throw it!
No fear!
Believe in us, in your friends!
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
Let's give this everything we've got!
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
Guys, it's not about winning or losing!
Let's give them the best game we can!
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
Yeah!
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
minna de tsukutta wa wa ookiku narisugite
The circle we came together to make became too large
toki ni wa kimi ga doko ni iru no kamo wakaranakunatte
Sometimes I don't even know where you might be
sotto dare ka ga kureta yasashii kotoba ga
But those kind words that someone once told me,
kimi no mono da to oshietekuretanda
I knew that they were yours when I heard them
ude wo kaki kaze wo kire
Swing your arms, cut through the wind,
mae wo muki namida ga nijimu hodo ni
Face forward, and run through the sky,
massugu kono sora wo kakenukero
So straight and fast that the tears fly past
kimi mo hitori boku mo hitori
You're alone, I'm alone
minna ga kodoku de irunda
In the end, we're all alone
kono wa no naka de mou kidzukanai uchi ni
Even in this circle, before we knew it,
sono ashi wa furuedasu chiisana kakoku ni mo
Those legs began to shake, even in the face of the least of grief
bokura minna onaji yume wo miteta
In the end, we were all having the same dream,
The best friends I've ever had—
The Little Busters.
sugisaru ichi pe-ji no
A single, passing page in life
koko kara wa issatsu shika motteikenai yo
You can only take one of them out of here with you
Little
Busters
All
Stars
sore de yokatta no kai?
Is that really what you wanted?
mune ni wa tsuyosa wo
Gather your strength in your heart,
kedakaki tsuyosa wo
As much heroic strength as you can
Yahoo!
hoho ni wa namida wo
On your cheek, a tear
The Little Busters are the best!
itteki no namida wo
A single, lonely tear
The best!
We're the best!
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
Muscles, aw yeah!
One, two, Little Busters!
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
One, two, Little Busters!
norikoetekureru yo
You'll overcome it for me
shinjisasetekureru yo
Make it so I can believe you will
I wanted...
Rin, stand closer to Riki.
...this moment to last forever.
Here goes!
Forever...
Forever and ever, just like this.
The secret of the world.
What is the Little Busters?
What do you think it is, Riki?
A symbol of friendship.
It's a called game.
Dreams disappear once you wake up.
Just one wish.
The time that had stopped begins to move once more.
That is where it all starts.