presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Futaki-san?
Why?
Why are you pretending to be me?
Chiffon cake?
No way...
No way!
You can't do that!
Futaki-san!
I even put color contacts in.
You'd bake chiffon cake better than me...
You're trying to show Riki-kun that
you're better than me at everything!
You're laughing at how pitiful I am, aren't you?
But how?!
You can't touch eggs!
How did you bake a chiffon cake?!
You simply assumed that I can't touch eggs.
You said so yourself!
You said you were allergic to them!
You lied to me?!
Losing your patience?
Cooking eggs was the only thing you could do, huh?
Anything with eggs in it.
Shut up.
It's the only thing you could do better than me, huh?
Shut up...
Shut up!
Let go!
Let go of me!
Calm down!
Why do you always have to take everything from me?!
Trying to play the tragic heroine?
You want someone to pity you for being the unhappiest person on the planet?
Good for you.
You've found someone who'll do that.
But you see, it's all an illusion.
People can't save each other.
They're not God.
What's wrong?
You hate me, don't you?
Then hit me harder.
They call you a good-for-nothing because you don't even have the guts for that!
I wish you'd just die.
You liar.
You liar!
That's right.
I'm a liar.
I've been one for as long as I can remember.
Goodbye.
For some reason,
the pouring rain seemed to me like Futaki-san's tears.
Naoe-san, do you think that
Kanata-san is a mean person too?
Kud?
Please, don't think of her as a bad person.
In our room, she's a very kind and mellow person.
There has to be a reason why she pretends to be so cold outside.
She must be hiding something painful from us.
Something painful?
She always tosses and turns in her sleep.
And I saw!
You saw? What?
Um... um...
I don't think it's something I can tell you!
Um... I...
I wanted to do something for her,
but I can't do anything...
Forget I ever said that!
Sorry!
I hope one day we can walk...
...hand-in-hand.
You don't need to leave.
Naoe Riki.
You came to ask me why I did that.
Am I right?
And if I did? What would you say?
I wanted to test you.
You want to pretend you're God and save her.
But what do you really want?
Why did you lie to Saigusa-san?
Of all the things I thought you'd say.
In a home economics class in elementary school,
we had to cook something at school and bring back pictures to show our families.
We happened to have a competition that day.
A competition?
Our relatives were going to compare us to see who was better, as always.
Incidentally, our cooking would be used to judge us.
What are you going to make, Kanata?
What about you, Haruka?
An omelette, I think.
The family told me to make an omelette as well.
But if I made the same thing and won,
they'd beat Haruka.
So...
So?
I made miso soup.
I messed up again.
They kicked me out.
But why didn't you make an omelette too, Kanata?
Huh?
How come?
Well...
You lied that you couldn't touch eggs?
Yes.
So I'm the only one who can cook eggs?
Y-Yeah.
Oh...
I see.
Something only she could do.
That became Saigusa-san's hope?
She believed that lie to this day.
Funny, isn't it?
I told you I was a liar.
For as long as I can remember.
Always.
In other words, Futaki-san lied so you wouldn't get hurt.
Why are you telling me this?
Are you trying to say it's not her fault?
You're saying it's my fault?!
Because I'm his kid?!
Because I'm a criminal's...
Saigusa Shou's kid?!
No! That's not it!
If it's not her fault, then who am I supposed to hate?!
Who?!
Baseball
Team
Saigusa was reviled and rejected for ages.
She could only keep her sense of self by hating Futaki.
Without someone to hate, she wouldn't have lived this long.
What should I do?
At this rate, Saigusa-san's dark emotions will overwhelm her.
Baseball
Team
But what can I do in this situation?
Only Saigusa can find the answer.
Saigusa needs to figure out what she really wants.
Maybe that's what you need to tell her.
Because it's the only way to free yourself from the invisible chains of hate.
Don't you think so, Riki?
What Saigusa-san really wants...
What could that be?
H-Hey-yo.
Sorry for yelling at you back there.
Everything I do is trouble for you.
I'm really sorry.
Didn't you promise not to apologize all the time?
Yeah, I did.
Oh, right.
Here.
I think it's best if you gave this back to Futaki-san.
Why?
Hey, Saigusa-san...
What do you really want?
Th-That's obvious.
I want to know whose kid I am.
Will that really solve the problem?
It will!
If I really am his kid, I can have closure!
What if it turns out that Futaki-san is his kid?
Then they'll tear Futaki-san apart.
You'll force something negative on her.
Why not?
She deserves to feel my pain.
Really?
Do you really feel that way from the bottom of your heart?
If you two keep forcing negatives on
each other, neither of you will be happy.
I think you know that deep down inside.
What should I do?
Riki-kun, what should I do?
I can't tell you.
No one can.
The answer is inside your heart.
Inside my heart?
If it's clouded with hate, you
won't be able to see the answer.
You need to find what you really
want from the bottom of your heart.
Something more important than hate.
Something more important than hate?
I hope one day we can walk hand-in-hand.
Baseball
Team
Kuu-chan, Rin-chan, are you worried
about Futaki-san and Haru-chan too?
Yes, I am.
Yeah.
Haru-chan's trying as hard as she can.
I'm sure happiness will find its way to her.
We'll all be happy in the end.
You... think so?
I really hope so.
Muscles! Muscles!
You gotta train your muscles when you're worried!
Nishizono-san isn't answering.
I wonder why.
Hey there, Psychopathic Maracas.
You've got the face of someone with happy muscles today.
Looks like you've gotten over something.
I've figured out how I feel.
Mind explaining why you called me out here?
I've decided.
I need to talk to you.
I'm not going to hate or fear you anymore.
I'll tell you the truth.
What do you want from me now?
I want you to tell me.
Who my real father is.
What a waste of time.
Please!
Then get on your knees and beg.
Please, tell me.
Are you stupid?
Have you no shame?
I've decided to stop running away.
I'm going to face it.
Looks like you've got some confidence.
Did one of you become God and save her?
There's no God here.
All we've got in this world is us.
We simply faced each other, talked
things through, and found our answer.
I think you want to talk things through with Saigusa-san from the bottom of your heart too.
If you knew, you'd lose the life you've had until now.
Do you still want to know?
I have friends I can count on.
For the first time in my life, I don't
want to think that no one needs me.
I don't want to hate anyone anymore.
I don't want to be the person I've been up till now.
So tell me the truth.
For a long time, they would give me all the toys and snacks I wanted,
as long as I beat you.
When Dad refused to tell the truth after he was put in prison,
our relatives wanted to know which of us was the daughter of the criminal.
But even when I won, and they said that I was better than you,
their suspicion that I might be the
disgrace of the family never disappeared.
The Futaki family loved whipping me with a leather belt whenever I went easy on you.
They were all monsters who rejoiced in the idea of giving me more scars.
Kudryavka would know.
Anyone who saw what's under these long sleeves would be horrified.
I put up with the pain.
I got used to the pain in my heart.
I worked really hard.
Studying, sports, and etiquette...
I couldn't even sleep because I had to be better.
I had to secure the succession of the Saigusa family.
Why?
They said that if neither of us was good enough, they'd no longer have any use for us.
No way!
Wasn't it just to decide which of us would succeed the family?
They couldn't bear it.
They didn't want the family's reputation sullied from having the daughter of a criminal.
So they ordered me to hate you.
But I couldn't.
Because...
You're...
my little sister!
And nobody can ever change that fact!
But they told me not to talk to you.
Not to hold your hand.
Not to be nice to you.
They said they'd buy me
anything I wanted if I listened.
Still, I shook my head.
Then they told me...
If you won't listen, then you can be her.
Pitiful little Haruka.
I wasn't scared of being whipped or yelled at.
I...
I was scared because I couldn't nod!
They said that they'd kill one of us.
"If we had to kill one of them, it would be Haruka."
"Right, Kanata?"
Is that why you had to be hard on Saigusa-san?
If I didn't, Haruka...
They'd kill Haruka.
Haruka...
It's okay now.
It's okay.
It's not!
It can't be okay! There's no way it could be!
I did so many bad things!
I'm not even worthy of touching your hand!
Haruka?
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Because I kept thinking that only I had a hard time.
Even though I should've known all along.
Mom and Dad sent us these in secret.
They're birthday presents for us!
You're giving me one too, Kanata?
Yeah.
We have to pretend we don't like each other right now.
But trust me, Haruka.
One day, we'll go see Mom and Dad together.
Yeah!
Walking hand-in-hand.
At some point, I lost my trust in you.
But my heart always remembered.
That we promised that day.
Will you forgive me?
Thank you.
Haruka, if you want to,
let's end it all now.
Kanata?
Haruka?
Dad, I've decided to leave the family.
So tell Haruka the truth.
Your mom and us
were childhood friends raised in the Saigusa family.
We both loved her.
And they forced her to marry both of us.
But the one she truly loved wasn't me.
The pain of all three of us living together was too much.
When you twins were born, I decided to take myself out of the picture.
She and he tried to leave carrying the two of you.
But the Saigusa family was angered and took you both from their arms.
That's where I came in.
You were too important.
I had to protect you both from that sick, twisted family at all costs.
Your lives were too important.
In the end, I couldn't protect you two.
But please remember.
All three of us wanted both of you to be born.
None of us have forgotten you even for a moment.
This is a letter from your mom.
She can't wait for the day
she sees both of you again.
Now, Haruka, let me answer your last question.
The one you wanted to know most.
Haruka?
I thought everyone in the world hated me.
I thought everyone's heart was full of hate.
But I was wrong.
I just wanted to know if there are evil people in the world.
It's no one's fault.
I don't need to hate anyone.
I know that now.
So I don't need to know whose kid I am.
I can love myself.
That's all I really wanted to know.
I wanted to believe it more than anything.
That no one was evil in the world.
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
Episode 18
The Answer Is in Your Heart
I am a Japanese stupid!
No, Kud, it's "student."
This is bad! Our tests are coming up!
Let's all help Kuu-chan study!
Mission, start!