Looks like I fell asleep again.
Narcolepsy.
And,
just like always, it disconnected me from this world.
I had a strange, inexplicable feeling.
As if something were buried at the bottom of my memories.
The boy and girl solve each of the dwarves' worries, one by one.
And once they solve the worries, the dwarves
say goodbye to the boy and girl and disappear.
I had seen that picture book before.
But when?
Where?
There was something I was forgetting.
Something very important.
What was it?
I can't remember.
Suddenly, a strange thought ran through my mind.
What if there really was a secret in this world,
and I just couldn't remember it?
There is a secret in this world.
then clear all the tasks I give you.
If you wish to know it,
Hey, Riki!
We've got a game this Saturday!
Game?
The Little Busters's first game!
What?!
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Kyousuke, what's this about a game?
Since our foundation, we, the Little Busters,
have shared in our youths and
developed marvelous teamwork.
With that in mind, I have set our first game!
Hooray!
Wafu!
Yay!
What team are we playing against?
A team worthy of our abilities.
An all-star team.
Huh?
An all-star team?
A team consisting entirely of the captains of various sports teams at this school.
Soccer Team
The soccer team,
the volleyball team,
Volleyball Team
the basketball team,
Basketball Team
the tennis team,
Tennis Team
the track team,
Track Team
the gymnastics team,
Gymnastics Team
and the swim team captains.
Swimming Team
Then there's the former captain of the baseball team
Baseball Team
and the captain of the judo team.
Judo Team
These nine!
That's crazy!
They're way too good!
Though I have to give you credit for
assembling a team of such amazing people.
It's safe to assume that they are well-endowed in athletic ability.
Why not? It sounds interesting.
No—
Right?
See? She understands.
There's no way we can win!
It'll be fun.
No no no...
That's right. Listen to Kurugaya.
No, wait!
Not everyone thinks like you two!
Riki, can't you say anything but "no"?
No no no...
Wait, aren't you forgetting something?
We only have eight people on our team.
We're missing one person for a real game.
Really?
Nishizono's a manager, so she doesn't count.
Riki, Rin, Kyousuke,
Komari, Saigusa, Kurugaya,
Rin... then there's Kud-o, and Riki.
Huh?
If you add me, it's ten!
There were two of Riki and me.
I'm sure he meant something by it.
Don't be too hard on him.
I just messed up my counting!
I'm sorry!
It's true. We only have eight members.
It's not a particularly big problem.
Or is it?
It's a huge problem!
I wanna win this!
We need nine members!
Okay.
I'll see what I can do.
I'll try to find one more person.
No. You've already done enough.
No need to worry.
It's only a matter of time
before our last member joins.
Oh, I get it!
You already have someone in mind!
Oh? Really?
Anyway, we're training like crazy for the game!
We're going for the win!
Got it, everyone?
Wafu!
Our first game! I'm so excited!
I wonder what Kyousuke's got in mind.
Does he really have someone
in mind for the ninth member?
I don't think he does...
Kengo would be such a boon to us if he joined.
But it won't happen.
He wouldn't change his mind now.
Oh man, they're flirting again.
Huh?
They were having tea over there the other day.
It's Koshiki Miyuki-san from the archery team.
Who's that?
She's the daughter of a famous line of professional archers.
She was known as a genius, and
everyone had high expectations of her...
but she lost her right eye to a disease.
Alright! Let's make it super awkward for them!
No, don't.
It looks like they're talking
about something important.
Let's go.
O-Okay.
'Sup, guys.
Eat up and build that body for the game.
Allow me to introduce a few
members of the all-star team.
Saturday's gonna be a blast!
We ain't holdin' back.
Yo!
It's gonna be fun.
The game starts at—
I really don't want to!
I don't want to have a game!
I can't pitch against those crazy strong people!
Rin...
This isn't the time for that.
Can you pitch at them, then?
You begin a battle by controlling your feelings.
Rin, if you hold any anxiety or
misgivings towards your opponent,
you have already lost the battle.
You need to control your feelings first.
What the heck?
It applies to me too.
I will be fighting someone better
than me at my match next week.
But everyone says you're set to win the whole thing.
They say you'll be bringing home our school's first ever trophy.
The result of the battle is in the hands of the gods.
I will simply swing my sword as myself.
Ha! Like we'd believe a guy who secretly flirts with a girl behind the cafeteria!
What?!
Miyazawa was with a girl?!
No way!
Kengo-sama has a girlfriend?!
Is that for real?
And he made her cry too!
I don't think he's got the right to swing a sword.
There are things you can and can't say.
You wanna fight? Sounds good to me!
I'll send you flying to the other side of the school!
Kengo! Masato!
Please stop!
Koshiki-san?
I was just asking Miyazawa-san for advice!
That was all!
Sorry.
Sorry we made things so awkward.
I was simply asking Miyazawa-san's advice as a martial artist.
Yeah. He's not good with people, but he's a nice guy.
He's really reliable.
I regret it now.
Miyazawa-san simply comforted me like anyone else.
I put everything I had into archery.
And it was all for nothing!
My future is over!
You just think your future is over.
You can find another way of life if you look for it.
A strong person like you who's never
once lost hope could never understand!
You understand nothing!
Koshiki worked harder than anyone.
That's why she feels the pain so strongly.
She's in the depths of despair.
She can't see anything else.
All students are to return to
their classrooms immediately.
You may not leave them until further notice.
What? What?
What's going on?
Huh? Did something happen?
This isn't good! Koshiki-san's on the roof!
The roof...
What?!
Is she planning to jump?!
She's going to give up on life itself?
We need to save her!
Don't we?!
Kengo!
Let's go!
Killing yourself is just plain wrong!
Kengo may be regretting it.
He could have done something to stop this from happening.
Come back here!
Before something terrible happens!
You're a brilliant student!
You don't need archery! Just study and get wonderful grades!
No... No...
What do we do?
It doesn't look like she wants to die.
She's shaking.
It's only a minor obstacle! You can't give up now!
No one here understands her.
Koshiki!
Kengo...
If Kengo couldn't do it, those adults definitely can't.
Hey! Do you hear me?!
Koshiki!
Stop it!
Stop!
Stay away!
No!
Wait!
Go back to your classroom!
If you don't, you'll be punished!
What happened?
She's fine.
Yeah, he's totally awesome.
The fact that your legs are fine can only be
explained by your outstanding athletic prowess.
Yeah.
But... your arm...
I've taken even your dreams from you.
It's just a fracture.
It'll be back to normal in two months.
But you can't participate in the match anymore!
That's all it means.
That's not all it means.
You can't practice with your team...
What do you mean, practice with your team?
The Kendo Team moderator has suspended Kengo from all practice sessions this term.
Why?!
Because Kengo pushed his moderator out of the way.
You serious?
But you saved Koshiki-san!
I'm sorry.
Koshiki.
Can you promise me something?
Never do anything like that again.
Yes.
You saved my life.
I won't throw it away again.
I'm not trying to guilt you into anything.
You just need to live your life as yourself.
I'll live like myself as well.
But you can't do kendo anymore...
Can you really be yourself?
Koshiki, I told you.
You can find another way to live.
Even if you despair in losing one way.
You'll find something else to do.
You're seriously going to bat?!
Rin, pitch!
As hard as you can!
How're you gonna hit with that arm?
Wafu...
One arm.
Normally, you wouldn't be able to do a full swing,
let alone scrape the ball.
And even if you could hit the ball, you can't run with that thing.
Bring it, Rin!
That's enough.
Just stop.
Rin, keep going.
Pitch.
Not yet!
Just quit it, idiot!
Rin.
I told you not to go easy on me.
Give me all you've got!
Come on, Rin.
Do it!
Pitch, Rin! With everything you've got!
Okay.
He did it with one arm...
Well done.
Yahoo!
Wow! Wow!
Amazing.
As long as I hit home runs, I can run the bases slowly without fear of an out.
Yeah!
Kengo will keep proving that it's true...
That you can find another way to live.
A wounded rookie appears.
Alright! We've got our ninth member!
The Little Busters is now complete!
I never thought I'd play baseball.
It's only a matter of time
before our last member joins.
He wouldn't change his mind now.
But he changed his mind.
Thanks to a completely unpredictable incident.
Something you couldn't predict...
But Kyousuke predicted it?
How?
I'm forgetting something very important.
We've got all our members.
Now I'll announce the captain for our first game.
Captain?
It's not you, Kyousuke-san?
No.
The captain...
will be Riki.
I won't lead the Little Busters from now on.
From this moment on, Riki,
you are the leader of the Little Busters!
Episode 25
The Last Member
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
Riki, you're our leader for our first game!
Kyousuke, what do you mean?!
Naoe-san is...
...the leader?
That's not gonna work.
Mission, start!
It's finally time for the game!
Let's do this!