Aw yeah!
Cutlet! Cutlet! Pork cutlet!
Thanks for the food.
Oh, Rin-chan, mind if I sit there?
Not at all.
Thanks.
Doesn't look like we've got sauce.
Kengo, could you get some?
Sure.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, Masato, we saw you do it.
Huh?
You took a bunch of Kengo's cutlet.
What?!
Hey, man, it was totally weird.
I was going to stop with one piece, but no matter how much I took, it was still there!
It's a magic cutlet!
A magic cutlet?
No, that's Komari-san's cutlet.
Yeah.
But don't worry.
I don't eat that much.
What're you talking about?
Komari, you gotta eat more or you won't get big!
Here.
What're you doing, you idiot?!
Don't you feel sorry for Komari?! She's trying to be nice!
Why don't you give her some of your cutlet, then, huh?!
Huh?!
There wouldn't be enough for me if I did that!
I've got a tournament coming up! I need all the nutrition I can get!
Don't fight, I don't mind.
You don't need to eat and get any bigger, you—
Shut up, retard! You're giving Komari-chan a hard time!
Where's your magic cutlet now?
I'm sorry.
Here, Komari-chan.
Thanks.
Here, Rin-chan.
Rin-chan used to be so shy.
Here.
But she's a bit more outgoing now, thanks to Komari-san.
Thanks, Rin-chan!
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Oh, I got a text from Komari-chan.
Oh?
So you and Komari-san are texting each other now?
Kyousuke put her number in for me.
Received Message
Kamikita Komari
Rin-chan!
with you
But her texts are really long. I don't understand them.
Is it some kind of code?
What do I text back?
Huh?
Lennon?
Riki, it's a letter!
It's another mysterious task!
What do you have to do now?
Do the puppet show.
A puppet show?
What does that mean?
Riki, how do you do a puppet show?
Are you going to do it?
Of course.
I've already completed the other tasks.
They'll tell us the secret of the world if I finish the rest!
The rest?
How many more mysterious letters are we going to get?
Do the puppet show.
Does the sender really plan to tell us the secret of the world?
You totally did it on purpose!
No we didn't!
Stop lying!
You stop!
Why'd you do it?
It's your fault!
Yeah! Yeah!
What's wrong?
These boys hit the panda with the ball on purpose!
It wasn't on purpose!
Ew.
I was using it for a puppet show too.
A puppet show?
She said she wanted to see a puppet show for her birthday, so I was going to give her one.
But look at it now.
I can't do it anymore.
You still can.
How about you do it, then?
She was really looking forward to it.
No way!
What about the panda?
It's scary now. I don't want it.
Wait!
I'll...
...do it.
The puppet show.
I'll fix him up and do the puppet show.
Come back here tomorrow.
It's a promise!
Rin wants to complete the task.
Rin-chan, you're doing a puppet show?
I wasn't thinking, and...
Do you know how to do a puppet show?
No.
Don't worry!
Puppet shows make everyone happy!
Ask me anything you'd like!
Leave it to me!
Komari-chan...
You've done a puppet show before?
I haven't.
Um...
I think you need to write a story first.
Then you make puppets to match the story.
I have to write a story?
I'm not very good at that.
Let's think of one together!
These are stories I wrote.
You wrote all of these, Komari-san?
That's right!
Once upon a time, there was a penguin.
The penguin always messed up.
What's this?
That's a story about a boy
and a girl and eight dwarves.
The boy and girl solve each of the dwarves' worries, one by one.
And once they solve the worries, the dwarves disappear.
They disappear?
Yeah.
They say goodbye to the boy and girl and disappear.
They disappear?
That's kind of sad.
I haven't thought of what happens after that.
Oh, you three!
What are you planning?
I smell something exciting happening!
Get away!
You'll just make things crazy!
Rin-chan's going to do a puppet show!
What?!
A puppet show?
Oh? A puppet show?
I like the sound of that.
Actually, I was thinking of doing one too.
Dedicating your youth to baseball is nice and all,
but we should do puppet shows sometimes too!
Huh? What'd you say?
One day, we'll do it at a community center!
At a community center?
Why?
That's obvious!
For the elderly and the young!
Bringing the community's hearts together as one is one of the goals of the Little Busters!
Oh dang, he makes it sound so good!
No, I don't think so.
It's the first I've heard of this goal.
You're doing a puppet show?
Well, it may be a good way to pass the time.
Japan does have a long history of puppet theatre, starting from the ningyou joururi.
Alright!
Let's start with a script!
Yeah!
How'd this happen?
Why don't we see where we go with this?
Alright.
You guys all done?
Yeah.
How about this?
Smack.
A strange, wet sound rang through the streets.
Wait!
Stop!
What? Calling it no good already?
That first word...
Huh? It gives it a good atmosphere.
No, it's no good.
It needs to be hotblooded!
Mine's a story of friendship between an iron dumbbell and a steel dumbbell!
That's enough, steel dumbbell.
Leave me here and go on.
I know. I was just extra weight for you guys.
That's not true, iron dumbbell!
I was even more extra weight!
He's an idiot.
We should be traditional and go with a traditional story.
Once upon a time, in a faraway place, an old man and old woman lived together.
The old man went to the woods to gather firewood.
The old woman went to the river
to fight a life and death battle with the tentacles.
Tentacles?!
No way, retard!
I think the story's pretty touching.
How about an SF action?
A newlywed couple is attacked by an extraterrestrial lifeform.
A newlywed couple?
An extraterrestrial lifeform?
I've made the cast with what I had on hand.
This is the wife.
That's the wife?!
The story begins in the newlywed couple's home.
Sounds good. Let's see it, Nishizono.
At the Cafeteria
Dinner is ready, darling, sir!
Sir, yes, sir!
I made Salisbury steak tonight! I tried my best, sir!
Thank you, sir!
The bath is ready, darling, sir!
Sir, yes, sir!
It's precisely 41 degrees, sir!
Thank you, sir!
Whoa...
Begin bathing!
Is that really Mio-chin?
Did you say something?
You didn't like it?
No, it's perfect!
Well done, Nishizono!
It's great, Mio-chan!
Wafu!
Keep it up!
What are you doing here?
Oh no! It's the disciplinary committee!
It's past curfew.
Rules are rules. You will go back to the dorms now.
This assembly is dismissed!
She promised to do it tomorrow.
I wonder how she's going to.
Komari-san?
Riki-kun, I'll take care of Rin-chan.
Relax, relax!
Komari-chan!
Ow...
Oh, Rin-chan!
If we're close, we'll butt heads!
Komari-chan...
Did you come to help?
Yeah!
Let's do it together!
I brought cookies and seaweed 'n salt chips!
What happens in the penguin story?
The penguin works really hard, but nothing works out for him.
The cat and dog and raccoon laugh at him.
But in the end, a star lets the penguin ride him!
He flies through the sky on the star, waving to everyone!
I like that story!
It's perfect for the puppet show!
I'll make the penguin, then.
Do you want to make the star?
I'm not good at sewing...
It's easy!
You just do this!
Ow...
Are you okay?
I'm okay!
When you don't think you can do it, you do some optimism magic! Say, "Alright!"
It gives you positive energy!
Alright!
Let's get started, then.
If you put your heart into each stitch, you'll make a happy, sunny place!
You do this here...
Oh no! I fell aslee—
Komari-chan...
Wow, Rin!
You got everything ready in one night!
Need me to help with anything?
No.
Komari-chan did her best to get me here.
I need to do my best alone too.
You're really going to do a puppet show?
Look.
The panda's a penguin now!
It's the start of the story of the hardworking penguin!
And so, the penguin rode the star into the sky and waved down to everyone.
Isn't it great that he worked so hard?
It was really good!
Take good care of the penguin, okay?
Yeah!
Thanks, Onee-chan!
Bye!
See you again!
It was a huge success.
Task cleared!
I need to go tell Komari-chan!
At that moment, I wondered...
Do the puppet show.
Why did the person who wrote the letter tell her to do the puppet show?
It was as if they knew what was going to happen next.
It was the same before.
The letter to save the cafeteria came before the cafeteria needed saving.
They foresaw it.
How?
There
is
a
secret
in
this
world.
A strange feeling welled up inside me.
Even though I had never seen that
picture book before, I felt that I had.
The boy and girl solve each of the dwarves' worries, one by one.
And once they solve the worries, the dwarves disappear.
I had seen it before.
Komari-chan!
They say goodbye to the boy and girl and disappear.
It went well!
The puppet show!
Yay!
Isn't that great, Rin-chan?
It's all thanks to you, Komari-chan.
Thank you.
I was wishing on the first star.
Wishing that you'd do well.
Wishing on the star?
This is a wishing star.
I've been wearing it for a long time so my wish could come true.
Wishes...
You have two of them?
Oh, right.
I have two of them, so I can make two wishes!
Okay, this one will be for my wish...
and this one can be for your wish!
My wish?
Yeah!
Are you sure?
It's your star. Can I—
What will you wish for?
I'll leave that to you.
Okay.
That's a promise!
I'll think of one for you!
A wonderful wish.
Episode 24
If You're Happy, I'm Happy, Rin-chan
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
It's finally time for the Little Busters' first game!
No way! We still need another member!
What are you going to do?
Find one more.
Mission, start!