The same footage played back
on the television, over and over.
Tebwa Rocket Accident
Communications with the Novyi
Baikonur launch site have ceased.
We are still awaiting details of the accident.
Tebwa Rocket Accident
Half a day has passed since the rocket accident,
and we still don't know if Kud's mom is safe or not.
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
From satellite imagery of the site,
the entirety of Novyi Baikonur has been caught in the explosion.
It appears that a large conflagration is spreading through the area.
Because the rocket's experimental reactor may have exploded,
there is a chance of biological hazard...
The situation is just getting worse.
We still don't know if there are survivors or not.
What the hell? The rocket didn't just explode?
Why did this have to happen?
Why does everything have to be beyond our control?
Anything can happen.
No one ever thinks it will until it does.
What will happen, happens.
That's how the world is.
The most important thing is to not let the tragedy defeat you.
To believe that you can get through it.
Kud!
Kud-o!
Kuu-chan!
Kudryavka!
Kuu-chan...
I remember...
I remember everything...
I was... in prison.
Prison?
Calm down, Kudryavka.
It's okay, Kuu-chan.
We're all here for you.
That night, Kud returned to the dorms.
The next day, she didn't go to school.
All we could do was worry.
Look.
Tebwa
Rocket
Failure
Experimental
Reactor
Explosion?
They're saying it's even more likely that the experimental reactor exploded.
"To reduce risk of contamination, travel to and from Tebwa has been restricted."
What's that mean?
Basically, it's dangerous in there,
so it'll be harder to get in or leave.
Do we still not have any updates on the crew?
Kuu-chan's so worried about her mom that she can't take it anymore.
I'm sure she wants to go back home to Tebwa.
But no one can get into Tebwa.
The Tebwan Embassy...
just sent Kudryavka a plane ticket.
Her mother is a hero in Tebwa.
She received special permission to enter as her daughter.
Just to see if she's safe.
People from the embassy are coming for her tomorrow.
So, Kud's going back to Tebwa?
But it's dangerous! She might not come back if she does!
But...
Kuu-chan wants to see her mom...
And I'm sure her mom is safe and waiting for her...
Don't you think so too, Rin-chan?
I...
don't know.
But...
Her mom might already be...
If she goes home...
she'll just feel sad!
Rin!
Rin...
She shouldn't go home.
She doesn't have to see sad or scary things.
I feel bad for Kud.
G-Good morning!
No, I mean...
Good afternoon!
Um, uh...
Kud, you don't need to mind us.
But I'm causing trouble for you all...
That doesn't matter.
The most important thing right now is you and your mom.
I heard you got a plane ticket.
Are you going back to Tebwa?
What should I do?
I want to see my mom.
But...
I can't go back to Tebwa.
Because I came here—to Japan...
to escape.
To escape?
Will you listen to my story?
It's just a silly one.
When I was a kid, I looked up to my mom.
I didn't tell anyone, but I
dreamed of being a kosmonaut.
Wait, Kunya, what'd you just say?
You want to be a kosmonaut?
Yes.
You want to be an astronaut...
I've never been happier in my life!
Kudryavka!
Kudryavka.
I'm so glad I gave you that name.
The first dog in space, Laika.
One small life gave hope to all of mankind.
Kudryavka became a key gear of the world.
Become a gear of the world, just like her.
A good gear.
Wafu!
And one year ago, I was admitted into Tebwa's aviation school.
Aviation school?
An educational facility for aspiring kosmonauts.
I studied so I could fulfill my dream.
But in reality, it didn't go as well as I had thought.
You need to speak Russian and English in space,
so the lessons were all in English.
I couldn't keep up at all.
Hard work didn't pay off.
My mom was so talented,
and yet I was useless.
They called me a waste of their tax money.
Stupid, isn't it?
After all that effort, this was all I could be.
Welcome!
I thought I couldn't be my mom's daughter.
I left the school after half a year.
I came all the way to Japan without telling my mom.
And even here, I'm half worthless.
Not one or the other.
Nothing.
Useless to the world.
A failure of a gear.
I wonder how disappointed my mom is with my weakness.
So I won't go back to Tebwa.
Isn't Kud's weakness something everyone has?
Rin looked away, as though looking away from herself.
So that's how it is.
Kud-o doesn't know what to do.
What now?
What do you think, Masato?
Like I could answer a tough question like that!
Riki, you think of something.
You're good at that, aren't you?
I...
I think Kud should go home.
I'm worried about her mom.
But if she isn't ready to go back...
If she doesn't go, she'll regret it.
She may never get another chance to see her mother.
Kudryavka.
Rather than staying here and regretting it,
it may be better to go and regret it.
If you don't move forward, you can't gain anything.
Kud.
I-I know!
I have to go!
Um, uh...
But...
I'm scared.
I want to stay here!
I want to stay with you all!
I'll call the embassy!
I'll give the plane ticket back!
This is what Kud decided.
There's nothing else we can do.
All I can ever do is run.
I can't fly.
I can't go.
I'm Kudryavka.
It seems you've remembered everything.
You'll just experience the same thing, the same time?
Has your wish changed?
No! No!
No matter what you decide, Riki and
the rest of us won't criticize you for it.
I'm sorry, Kyousuke-san!
I'm sure Kyousuke thinks Kud should go back home.
Telling someone to stand up
to something is an easy task.
Just telling is easy.
I'm not strong enough to tell Kud to face it.
No matter what you decide, you'll regret it.
There isn't a right answer.
Naoe-kun!
Suginami-san?
Are you not feeling well?
Uh... I'm fine.
Here.
Class Trip Itinerary
Author: Saigusa Haruka
Bye.
Oh, right. It's almost time for the class trip.
I doubt I can feel happy about it, though.
Saigusa Haruka
I'm sure Saigusa-san feels the same way.
Maybe she's in the clubroom.
Nishizono Mio
What was that?
Rin, you need more muscle!
Shut up!
What's wrong, Riki?
What're you standing around for?
That box...
Oh, that too?
Are you going to burn it?
Yeah. We're on day duty, after all.
Hold on a second.
Sure we don't need to check what's inside?
What if it's inflammable trash?
Hey, you're right! It might be something edible!
Let's see here...
I've seen this stuff in Kud's room.
Hey, this is nice! But it won't get me any more muscles...
Did Kud throw this away?
And I can't eat it.
What's that?
Parts for something?
A dog tag... It's an ID tag.
Russian?
Kud-o wants to burn something this important?
Mind if I took this box with me for a while?
Space development.
After World War II, the Soviet Union
launched the first manmade satellite.
Thirteen dogs went to space aboard the Sputniks.
Isn't this...
That's it.
Chernushka.
In English, "Blacky."
Kud's mom has black hair...
It's her mom's ID tag.
Space Engineering Theory.
Dewitt and Everett.
Saint-Exupéry.
The Little Prince.
Kud's dreams are all in this box.
I proved why the sky is blue!
So exciting!
If Everett's many-worlds interpretation is true,
then there's an infinite number of Southern Crosses in this world!
It's so wonderful I might just faint!
I wrote a little essay about black holes and the theory of relativity last night.
It's embarrassing, so I won't let anyone read it.
Kud...
Congratulations on getting in, Kunya!
Mom!
This is the cloak and cap I've worn ever since I started at TASA.
I hope they'll protect you in my place.
I'm sorry!
So that cloak and cap...
were your mom's.
Are you just going to throw away your precious box?
Those are...
what remain of my dream.
It's all of my regrets.
I have no right to keep them.
I wasn't cut out to be a kosmonaut.
Don't lie.
No matter how much you deny them,
you can't extinguish your true feelings.
My true feelings?
You love space from the bottom of your heart.
You don't have to be like your mom.
You can be awkward and clumsy.
You just need to find what you can do.
You can be your own gear and chase your dream of space.
Your mom showed you that dream, and you looked up to her.
You want to see your mom.
You can't run away from your feelings.
Sure, you're weak, and you might
get an earful, but it doesn't matter.
You love your mom.
I...
I won't run away anymore!
I want...
I want to see my mom!
I want to see her!
I...
I'm going to go see her!
My words were probably meant for myself.
That I shouldn't run away.
Thank you, Riki!
Thank you!
Do you have your plane ticket?
Yes.
Take care on your trip.
I'll be lonely without you.
Strelka...
Belka...
Rin-san!
Could you please take care of Strelka and Belka for me?
Y-Yeah, I will.
Thank you.
Goodbye, then.
Make sure you listen to Rin-san.
Everyone...
The people at the embassy told me
that I might not be able to come back to Japan.
You'll be able to!
It's a promise!
Definitely!
You're coming back here.
We'll be waiting for you.
Yeah.
Coming back is your mission.
A mission that only you can complete.
I was trying to be someone else when I was with my mom.
I wasn't really myself.
No matter where I went,
everyone laughed at me as weird.
That's why I was always alone.
But now I have all of you.
You've all accepted me for who I am.
I'll come back for sure!
I'll come back!
Wish me ni puha ni pera.
It's a curse for good luck.
Ni puha ni... pera?
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, Kuu-chan.
We'll be waiting for you, Noumi.
Proshaite.
Farewell
Kud left alone to face what
great difficulties stood before her.
Episode 22
I'll Come Back for Sure!
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
The situation in Tebwa was
worse than we could imagine.
Unbelievable hardships awaited Kud when she arrived.
Is praying for her safety all we can do?
Kud's life is in danger!