Kyousuke's back!
So the time's come at last...
Where are you going?
To fight.
He's back!
Kyousuke's back!
Hold it! Hold it!
Stop!
Stop—
Like hell we'd stop!
After all...
Kyousuke's back!
Kyousuke!
This is bad!
Stop them!
Oh, is that you, Riki?
Sorry, but I didn't sleep last night.
Those two don't fight unless you're around!
They need you to make things fair!
Let's establish some rules then.
In a fistfight, Masato is too strong.
But with a sword, Kengo's too strong.
So, could everyone here throw anything you can find into the ring?
Any random stuff you can get your hands on.
They'll use whatever they catch as a weapon.
That should make the fight safer than it is right now.
Battle, start!
A banana?
Why are you holding a cat?
It's my weapon.
Got a problem?
And how the heck am I supposed to fight with this, anyway?!
Stop!
Our idol, Rin-sama, has arrived!
Don't pick on the weak!
The weak?
Is she talking about you?
No, I think it's you.
That's not even funny.
I mean the cat!
Now, why are you two fighting?
Listen to this, Rin.
This guy told me that "snails from my eyes" meant something it didn't.
And then I tried to use it in conversation today, casually saying, "Hey, that's like snails from my eyes!"
That's a really dumb reason....
You're the one who came to me asking what it meant.
I figured you probably just misheard "scales fall from one's eyes",
so I told you that it means
"having a sudden realization".
So why didn't you tell me that to begin with?!
Why the hell would snails come out of my eyes?!
Rin.
You can see who's at fault here, right?
What the hell? You running away?!
I'll cut you to ribbons with my cat claws—
Now you've done it!
I'm not going to go easy on you just because you're Kyousuke's sister!
Guys, get me a weapon!
This one's mine!
Three-
Section
Staff
Three-
Section
Staff
Three-
Section
Staff
E-Eel pie?!
Inohara-kun! You can do it!
This is a perfectly normal scene for me.
Ever since I got to know these guys after meeting them when we were young,
it's been a normal part of my life.
Those were the hardest days of my life.
I had just lost both my parents.
When all I could do was cry, the four of them appeared before me.
We're going up against a powerful enemy!
We need your help!
What's your name?
Naoe Riki...
Alright! Let's go, Riki!
Hey, who are you?
Us?
We vanquish evil and deliver justice!
They call us...
"Little Busters"!
It was indeed a powerful enemy.
We fought like there was no tomorrow.
Honey?
I'll leave the rest to you guys!
Masato!
Your sacrifice won't be in vain!
I didn't ask for this!
That was how we met.
It was the start of an exciting life for me.
Civil Disturbance or Civil Service? Elementary School Wasp Exterminators!
The kids who did the extermination.
After living with them for a while,
Civil Disturbance or Civil Service? Elementary School Wasp Exterminators!
The kids who did the extermination.
I was able to forget the pain and loneliness in my heart.
Civil Disturbance or Civil Service? Elementary School Wasp Exterminators!
The kids who did the extermination.
Everything was just so much fun.
If only every day could be like this forever...
That became my only wish.
Man, that seriously hurt.
All thanks to Fido here.
He's not Fido!
He's new, so he doesn't have a name yet.
Lennon.
Lennon?
You always pick such random names.
Einstein, Gates...
Audrey...
Akutagawa...
So, Kyousuke, where'd you try to find a job this time?
A publisher in Tokyo.
You walked to Tokyo?!
Yeah.
You know...
You're an idiot.
I'm flat broke, so I had no choice.
You guys will be third-years next year, too.
You'll be in the same boat.
I don't think I'll be walking to find a job, though.
I guess that's true, though.
Next year, we'll either be applying to college or looking for work.
We've been together up until now, but we might go our separate ways when we graduate.
At the very least, Kyousuke won't be here next year.
I don't want to think about the future.
If only things could be like this forever...
Hey, why don't we do something together like we used to?
What's with you, all of a sudden?
Like what?
You know, like how we used to walk around the neighborhood together looking for evil to vanquish.
Don't lump me in with you guys!
Kyousuke would always be leading us,
and we'd always jump into something really exciting!
Let's do something we can only do now, then.
Let's play baseball.
Huh?
You know, baseball.
We're starting a baseball team.
We'll call ourselves...
"Little Busters"!
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Right there.
Stand right there.
Rin, you're the pitcher.
I'm the pitcher?
May I ask why?
It makes for a more exciting plot.
What plot?
Our team, the Little Busters, always makes our matches dramatic and exciting!
He's been reading too many comics...
Riki, you're the catcher.
Alright! Time for your virgin pitch!
It's the season-opener!
So I just throw this thing?
Yeah. As hard as you can.
As hard as I can?
And thus...
Rin!
I bestow upon you the title, "Godly Lack of Control"!
Rin has earned the title "Godly Lack of Control"!
No!
The Little Busters will use this locker room for the time being.
It seems that the school's baseball team had a bit of trouble,
so right now they're practically nonexistent.
But...
Why baseball in the first place?
Now that I'm a third-year looking for a job, sometimes I think,
"What am I doing with my life?"
I'm going to get a stable job and work the rest of my life.
But that's only because I'm just following the same path that everybody else does.
And so, in order to prove to myself that I exist as my own individual,
I decided to play baseball.
Huh?
I was with you for most of that, but...
That last line didn't follow.
I play baseball to exist as my own individual.
But why baseball?
Just think about it.
Who'd ever think of playing baseball while looking for a job?
Well, I guess...
You wouldn't normally think of that, right?
Yeah...
That's what makes it interesting!
So you're just dragging us along for the ride?!
I've got a tournament coming up.
I have my own responsibilities as the fourth position.
See you.
I swing my sword to exist as my own individual.
Kengo!
Let him go, Riki.
The day will come when he'll understand too.
You know, it's not like we understand at all either...
Agreed.
1853, Perry Expedition ports at Uraga Harbor.
1860...
Aliens invade.
1862...
War on Mars.
Hey, shouldn't you be doing homework too?
I'm doing it now! Just like usual!
But baseball, huh?
Yeah, I'll bet you weren't expecting that either.
It's just like Kyousuke to jump into something random like that.
That much we should expect.
Yo!
What, more baseball recruitment?
No, I've got some homework I'm having trouble with.
Help me out with it.
I need to gather words spoken by great people.
Great people? You mean famous quotes?
Yeah, that.
"Even cats fall from poles."
That's not a quote, that's a proverb.
And you miraculously messed it up too!
I'll take it.
Huh?
Just now, in this room, a new quote was born.
Even cats fall from poles.
Inohara Masato
So why did you have to call me all the way to the boys' dorms?
I don't have the time to help you guys with your homework either.
I'm gonna bust some quotes out and show all the ladies my intellectual side!
This guy's an idiot.
I'll take that!
This guy's an idiot!
Natsume Rin (in reference to her old friend Inohara Masato)
Don't specifically include the context!
This simple phrase is a brilliant description of Masato.
Hey, you wanna go?!
Will you...
Shut up!
Nma, tsa, chogi!
Another deep quote is born...
Inohara Masato
(reflecting on his life)
Nma, tsa, chogi!
Inohara Masato
(reflecting on his life)
I wonder what he's been through?
It can't be anything worthwhile.
I went through you stabbing my sides!
Hey!
Oh, right! I got us a match date for our baseball team.
It's the Little Busters' first match.
It's coming up soon, so get ready!
Listen Kyousuke, right now our team's seriously lacking a few things.
More members, practice time,
motivation for everyone besides you,
and more members!
This guy said "more members" twice.
I'm sure he meant something by it!
Don't be too hard on him.
It meant nothing, okay? I'm sorry!
Yup, he's definitely an idiot.
Say that again and I'll infect you with my idiocy!
I'll find the remaining members in due time.
You'll need at least nine people to play baseball.
Are you sure you can find five more?
When you say five, does that mean you won't be a part of the team?
Rin, I want you to recruit us some members.
Recruit members?
I can't do that!
I'm not good at talking with strangers...
A headset?
Hello?
Huh?
Go, Rin!
Go find us those last five members!
That's your mission!
I see...
So you want Rin to go back to the girl's dorm...
...and ask the girls there to join the Little Busters!
Why girls?
Because it's never good to have too many boys.
This is Rin. I'm in the dorm.
Start with a greeting.
I hear girls nowadays say "good morning" even in the afternoon.
"Good morning" is too long.
We should take the professional approach with a "G'morn."
That doesn't sound professional...
Wait, I just realized something ground-breaking!
Say "goon mugging" really quick!
Doesn't it sound like "good morning"?
Uh... Does it?
So that's the plan? Roger.
Goon mugging!
Huh?
Mission failed.
Then how about "I'm Melvin!"
It kind of sounds like "good morning".
Huh?
I'm Melvin!
It sounds exactly the same!
Like hell!
Then think of something yourself.
Roger.
Hey, you're Melvin!
Huh? I'm not Melvin...
This is Rin. Mission failed.
Rin, just say, "Good evening."
Okay, got it!
Good evening.
Good evening!
Perfect. Now recruit her!
Are you interested in baseball?
Are you, Natsume-san?
Not really.
Say you are!
I can't lie!
I'm not really interested either.
See you!
Oh?
Natsume-san, is that your way of killing time?
Hey, are you interested in baseball?
What did you...
Don't tell me...
Are you not aware that I, Sasasegawa Sasami, am a candidate for the next softball team captain?!
Had no idea.
Even though you might be the school idol, Natsume Kyousuke-san's little sister,
and friends with the hero of the kendo team, Miyazawa-san,
and with that muscle maniac, it doesn't mean you can get cocky!
Muscle maniac?
And you're a hero?
So it would seem.
Rin, tell them that when Miyazawa takes a bath, he
always stays fully clothed and wears a sock on his head!
No way, dummy!
Did you call me a dummy?!
Are you stupid?
S-Stupid?!
Girls! You know what to do!
Like this?!
Ow!
Take this!
Why, you little...
No!
That's our Sasami-sama! So graceful!
Before we knew it, we were all
caught up in Kyousuke's big plan.
Kyousuke would always just be reading comic books,
but girls from all over school would come to look at him.
It was because the sight of him reading was always so...
...divine.
His laugh, his anger, and sometimes, his tears...
His expressions were just as if he were still a little boy.
They drew people to him.
We've been together up until now, but we might go our separate ways when we graduate.
At the very least, Kyousuke won't be here next year.
Let's do something we can only do now, then.
Maybe I'll look for new members for the Little Busters, too...
That's what I began to think.
I was the one who proposed doing something together, after all.
It wouldn't hurt to ask.
E-Excuse me...
I-I'm sorry!
There are all sorts of mysteries in this world,
like snacks and candy and sweets falling from the sky!
Episode 1
We'll Call Ourselves... "Little Busters"!
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
Riki, let's play baseball.
We'll call ourselves "Little Busters"!
Huh? Kyousuke, are you sure?
Find us some new members!
I'm waiting with my heart on fire!
Mission, start!