I-I'm sorry!
There are all sorts of mysteries in this world,
like snacks and candy and sweets falling from the sky!
Um... What are you doing here?
You're Kamikita-san, right?
Naoe-kun?
Not the school counselor mimicking Naoe-kun's voice?
I don't think we have any teachers with that particular talent.
Oh...
Give me a second, 'kay?
I'll just...
Oh no!
I'm stuck!
Naoe-kun, pull me out!
Uh, okay...
Thanks.
Is that...
an anteater?
Or is it an armadillo?
What's wrong?
Um, Kamikita-san...
I think your skirt might be caught on something.
Are you okay?
Thanks, Naoe-kun.
Um...
Anteater?
Oh, so it was an anteater.
You saw them!
Well, um...
Wh-Wh-What should I do?
Now I can't get a wife!
I don't think you can get one in the first place.
I'll try to find a husband, then.
Yeah, good luck with that.
What?
You didn't see anything.
Okay?
Okay.
No one saw anything.
All problems solved!
S-Sure...
I guess that works.
Well, since you're here, do you want a donut?
Uh... sure...
I've got tea too.
This is my favorite spot.
I come here a lot.
But I can't let many people know about it.
That would be bad.
So it's a secret!
Okay.
Now you're my partner in crime!
Yummy!
You like sweet things, don't you, Kamikita-san?
That's my happiness.
Eating sweets makes me happy.
It's a small thing, but the fact that it makes me happy is amazing.
That's why sweets are amazing!
I see.
If you're happy, then I'm happy.
When you make someone happy,
you make yourself a little happier too.
If you're happy, I'm happy.
If I'm happy, you're happy.
And that repeats over and over, making a happiness spiral!
I guess if you really believe in a theory like that, you'll end up happy.
What do you think?
I think so too.
I'm glad you came here, Naoe-kun.
We're in the same class, but we've never talked before.
Oh, right! I came here to recruit you!
Recruit?
We're forming a baseball team.
We don't have enough members yet, so we're looking for some more.
Baseball?
Like with grass?
Is the third baseman a dandelion?
Plants playing baseball.
I don't think they could.
No, it's not the plants playing baseball.
We're going to play a casual game of baseball under the blue sky.
A casual game?
Under the blue sky?
No matter how you look at it, Kamikita-san and baseball don't go hand-in-hand.
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Alright!
I'm starving!
Time for food!
Hey! That's mine!
Cheapskate.
Cheapskate?! What do you mean, cheapskate?!
Hey now, I'll give you another. Calm down.
We formed a baseball team, the Little Busters.
It's your fault!
What did I do?
The members, not including Kengo, are
You took my rice!
I need carbohydrates for my muscles!
Masato,
What?!
Rin,
Give it back!
me,
Come on, it's for my muscles!
and...
Hey.
What's with all the hubbub this early in the morning?
It's this idiot here.
...and Kyousuke.
Hey, don't call me an idiot! Call me muscles!
Just us four.
Who'd call you that?
Listen up, guys.
Let's form a band.
We'll call ourselves...
"Little Busters"!
A band?
Hold it, Kyousuke.
Weren't we playing baseball?
Oh, right. It was baseball.
I got riled up after reading a band comic.
So you don't actually care what we do?
So forming a baseball team was on the spur of the moment too?
Sorry.
We needed five more members, right?
Let's find them and dedicate our youth to baseball!
What I want to do isn't some boring sport like baseball,
but a passionate action battle thing!
A bug! Go away!
Rin?
Rin, stand back.
Holy crap!
Tsukahara Bokuden?
Hey.
Let go of it.
I see it!
You wanna go?!
Masato snapped first?!
You asked for it!
And he accepted?!
Weapons! Get us weapons!
Fine by me!
I've got soap!
Soap?!
Battle, start!
Human Bubble Bath!
Hi-ya!
What was he trying to do?
Why soap?
Inohara Masato.
I bestow upon you the title...
Masato has earned the title "The Man Who Lost His Brain Somewhere"
We need five more members...
I doubt there's even one person who'd consider picking up baseball in their second year of high school.
Let alone five...
Hey, have you seen Natsume Rin?
She's on duty today, but she hasn't erased the board.
She's probably playing with cats again.
That's all she ever does.
She doesn't care about anything but herself and those cats.
Seriously.
Just because she's popular with the guys...
Yeah.
Come on, come on.
Whoops!
What now, Isoroku?
Guts! Guts!
Be the first in history to walk on two legs!
I figured you'd be here, Rin.
Riki?
You shouldn't be playing when you're on duty.
No one will like you if you don't do your job.
You aren't getting along with the girls in class, right?
That's not true.
So are you friends with any of them?
The girl sitting behind me.
What's her name?
You don't know?
But you're friends?
Be quiet! Shut up!
What's so bad about not having friends?
It's not like I'm causing any problems for you!
Are you going to die if I don't have any?
I'm worried for you.
I know we grew up together and that we can hang out now,
but once we graduate, you know...
Mind your own beeswax.
Huh?!
...is what Lennon said.
Oh, I see.
What's this?
What?
There's a message on here.
A letter?
There is a secret in this world.
then clear all the tasks I give you.
If you wish to know it,
"There is a secret in this world."
A secret in this world? What does that mean?
There's another one here.
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
on problem
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
on problem
Fix the sanitati
"Your first task: Fix the sanitation problem in the boys' dorm storage shack."
Your first task:
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Your first task:
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
on problem
Your first task:
Fix the sanitati
on problem
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
in the boys' dorm
storage shack.
Fix the sanitati
Who wrote this letter?
It's not from the cat?
Cats can't write.
We could tail Lennon and find out who wrote it.
But that wouldn't be fair.
Wait, Rin, are you going to do this task?
I just need to clear the task, right?
This is just some childish prank.
It might be someone trying to mess with you.
We'll find out.
Who did it?
What they want to tell us.
I could see the excitement in Rin's eyes.
Almost as if she was a cat,
chasing after the tuft on a cat wand.
But...
What kind of secret is there in this world?
All there is here is an unchanging everyday life.
But...
If I had to name something that made me uneasy, it would be...
Narcolepsy.
A sleep disorder I've had since I was young.
I get sleep attacks.
I don't know when I'll suffer an attack and fall asleep.
By the way, Riki.
I'm thinking of making you the fourth batter.
Me? Fourth batter?
Having the weakest-looking player grow into the best clean-up hitter is absolutely necessary in any plot!
Seriously, what plot?
We only have four members.
We can't have a fourth batter yet.
Anyway, get a load of these!
These muscles!
Well? Well?
Guys!
Quit your grumbling!
We're going to fix the boys' dorm's sanitation problem!
So this is the storage shack?
It definitely needs some work.
The last time they cleaned this place was probably before the Meiji Restoration.
You're seriously going to do this, Rin?
Of course!
Well, it's not like cleaning the place is a bad thing, but...
So why the hell do I have to help clean this place?
You know, I have allergies that
make me want to dance and yell,
"Muscles, aww yeah!" whenever I try to clean stuff.
Woohoo!
Wow, this place is full of treasures!
The entire series is in here!
Over here too!
Hey, stop!
We're trying to clean up here!
Don't take them out of the box!
Hey!
Found you!
Oh, Kamikita-san?
What's up?
You know,
I've decided to be recruited!
Huh?
Baseball out on the grass.
I'd be really happy to help you out, Naoe-kun!
What?
Wait, does that mean you're joining the Little Busters?
Huh?!
Natsume-san, you're a member too?
I'm so happy!
Hey, wait...
Let's do our best at this baseball thing!
Okay?
Sorry, Rin's really shy.
Really?
Hey!
Look out!
Nice, Rin!
Rin!
Kamikita-san!
A-Are you okay, Kamikita-san?
Come on Rin, apologize!
I'm fine, I'm fi—
K-Kamikita-san?!
So, Kamikita, was it?
Hm?
Why do you have mittens on?
Don't you need these for baseball?
I know that much!
Sorry, but those aren't the kind you use in baseball.
Precisely!
These are the real ones!
No, they're not.
But I want to do something before I become a member.
S-She ignored me!
So what she wanted to do...
...was cleaning, it seems.
Fine, fine.
It'll be good for my muscles.
You're going to finish the task, aren't you?
Muscles, aww yeah!
I didn't think we'd get it this clean...
I sure did a good job!
You did?!
Rin, you should say thanks.
We finished your task thanks to Kamikita-san.
Now that the baseball team's room is nice and clean, let's play baseball!
Huh?
This isn't the baseball team's room.
It isn't?
Uh, yeah.
And...
A-one, two!
And a-three, four!
Is she okay?
This is bad.
Gotta do my best!
How bad, you ask?
A-one, two!
So bad that I can't undo the furrows in my brow.
And a-three, four!
Well, it looks like she has drive...
Four 'n' five!
All I see is a big liability to the team.
Five 'n' six!
Let's give her a membership test.
Six and seven!
Seven and eight!
I see.
Eight and nine!
If we say she fails, we gracefully turn her down, and that'll be the end of it.
Nine...
Ten!
Huh?
A test?
That's right.
Question one!
What is necessary for baseball?
Um...
Guts!
Bravery!
And friendship!
You pass!
Wha—
I'll try my best!
Wait a moment!
My bad.
Your words were so righteous
that they rang deep in my soul.
Aren't these kinds of tests
usually for physical aptitude?
Motor skills...
Don't forget muscular strength!
I guess that's right.
In that case, let's start with...
A batting test.
Oh man, I can't bear to watch this.
Here, let me see that.
I'm sorry!
A plastic bat is lighter.
Now you shouldn't have any problems.
No problem!
I'm pretty sure there is...
Next up, running bases!
Finally, fielding!
So this is a real glove...
Let's do this!
Hey, a dandelion!
She's hopeless.
Unfortunately...
Alright, this is the last question.
I ask you once again.
What is necessary for baseball?
Um...
That would be...
Guts!
Bravery!
And friendship!
You pass!
No question about it! You pass!
Kamikita Komari, you have
everything it takes to play baseball!
Admission granted!
Starting today, you're a member of the Little Busters!
What was that test for?
I hope we can be good friends!
Call me Komari-chan if you'd like!
Oh, still shy?
Well...
Come on, Rin!
Let's be friends, Rin-chan!
R-Rin-chan...
I'm not used to this!
Darn, she ran away...
She's just not used to it.
She doesn't know how to interact with you.
She's never been called Rin-chan, after all.
Wait, so does that make me Muscle-chan?
Call me Muscle-chan, okay?
Gross!
Damn.
I thought it sounded pretty good too.
You're okay?
Huh? Why wouldn't I be?
Masato's always been like this.
Here.
Rin-chan!
Wait up!
Ow!
Kamikita-san...
Owie...
Uh, are you okay?
Thanks for fixing my skirt...
Tickle, tickle, tickle!
S-Stop that!
Stop! Stop!
The same wish crossed my mind again.
If only every day could be like this forever...
A secret in this world? What does that mean?
Just like always, it came without warning.
Narcolepsy.
I was disconnected from this world.
I fell asleep.
Episode 2
If You're Happy, I'm Happy
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
I was invited to a mysterious tea party!
Who's trying to seduce you, Riki?
Exceptional IQ, godly reflexes.
You know, her! She's invincible!
Make her a member.
Mission, start!