Ball!
Close, though!
Nice pitch!
Pitch!
She's not getting any strikes in.
Her pitch speed is about 80
kilometers per hour on average.
Hey, stop it you guys!
Cats!
Wafu!
Looks like a break to me.
Stop!
I'll step on you if you stay there.
You'll be squashed flat.
Could you please not corrupt these holy grounds with your cats?
Sasasasasa Sasami!
It's Sasasegawa Sasami!
The sparkling ace of the girls' softball team, and...
...the most beautiful girl in school!
Who's that?
Rin's rival.
These grounds are a place for sportsmen to
release their sweat as they aspire to greater heights!
It's not a place for people like you,
who play with cats with no goals in mind!
I think we're trying to win some match.
You think?
Doesn't seem like you care very much.
I really don't care.
I've let you off this long, like kids playing catch on the sidelines,
but this is it.
You will clear off these grounds so my softball team can practice!
No thanks.
Natsume Rin, you dare to mock my softball team?!
Get off Sasami-sama's foot!
Insolent rogue!
Tezuka!
Are you okay?
What?
I'm not letting a bully go.
Apologize!
It's your fault for bringing cats—
We'll make it a contest.
Your hitting against Rin's pitching.
If you win, we'll leave.
But if Rin wins, you'll apologize for your underlings' behavior and go back to your own practice.
I accept your challenge.
There's no way that I can lose!
Strike! Batter out.
I was just helping you with your pitching practice!
Oh my, look at the time!
We'll finish this contest next time!
Sasami-sama!
Get back here and apologize!
130 kilometers per hour...
What?! How?!
There, there.
She got serious when her cat got bullied.
Super power at a time of crisis.
So that's how much she loves them.
Anyway, let's give that fastball a name.
Can't we just call it a normal fastball?
Well, there's a cat soul in it.
Rising Meowstball!
Well?
Uh... I can tell that you like it...
Rin learned the Rising Meowstball!
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Right, right, left.
Right, right... left!
No, it's right, right, left.
Right, right, left.
Good.
Now for a trick.
Huh? You're up for it, Tezuka?
Okay.
Right, right, left.
Right, right... right.
You fell for it!
Who's next?
You already did it.
You want to play?
You still can't even if you beg.
No...
Fine.
That was easy.
Oh, it's just you, Riki?
A letter!
It's been a while since the last one.
I wonder what it is this time.
Mysterious letters that appear every so often...
This is the third one.
We still don't know who's sending them or why.
They said they'd tell us some secret of the world if we complete all their tasks, but...
Are you still doing them?
Don't you want to know the secret?
What is it this time?
Ease number 1 in 2-A's lovesickness.
Whoever gave this order's a real busybody.
Rin, do you know what lovesickness is?
Love is sick?
Lovesick... lovestink?
You mean "love stinks"?
No, it means sick with love.
Sick? It's a disease?
2-A is probably the class.
1 is probably the student number.
Which means it's a guy!
Yeah.
Let's go see him later.
I have to talk to a guy I don't know...
Hello?
Natsume-san and Naoe-san?
Are you number 1 in 2-A?!
Huh? Y-Yeah...
My name's Aikawa...
So you're the one giving us trouble.
Why are you acting like the bad guy?
Excuse me, but what could you be here for?
We're both second-years.
No need to be polite.
Okay. Whaccha want?
Now you're pissing me off.
Hey, you shouldn't say that!
Right now, you're lovesick.
Huh?!
H-How...
Don't say anything. We know.
We have evidence.
We don't have any evidence!
Who'd you hear that from?
That's a secret.
We have a source.
So, what are your symptoms?
What do you plan to do?
We'll cure your disease.
It'll be easier on you if you tell us.
Don't worry, we'll keep it a secret.
Okay. Just don't tell anyone, okay?
My chest hurts.
It hurts?
Yeah.
When I see her, it feels tight right here.
Tight?
I can't even study.
During class, all I can think of is her.
I think she's my first love.
What kind of person is she?
She's really smart and athletic.
She's an amazing person and very popular.
I'd never make a good match for her.
Well, that's too bad.
Wait, you haven't even confessed to her yet!
Confess?! No way!
You're not going to?
If she rejects me, I'll feel horrible.
But wouldn't you feel worse if you just gave up and didn't do anything?
Yeah, but...
Can you tell us who it is?
Huh?!
Yeah. If we knew who it was, it'd be easier for us to help.
You don't have to, though.
Sa...
Sasasegawa-san.
Why did you just say that name?
Because you asked me...
No, I didn't ask for her name.
No, no, you did.
No, no.
No, no, no.
No, no. Aikawa means that he's in love with Sasasegawa-san.
Oh!
What?!
What? What's going on?!
Stand back!
Rin, stop it.
Calm down and think.
But, Riki, that would only confuse me.
Because...
He said this person is smart, athletic, and popular.
That's not the Sasasasasa Sasami I know!
Let's not shatter his dreams, please.
That's not the problem.
I guess so...
Okay.
Hey.
You'd make a good couple.
Really?!
She always has an entourage with her.
You can be one of them.
Wouldn't that put me in her friend zone?
No... it might be even worse than that...
She and I actually know each other.
I might be able to get you together.
What? Why are you shocked?
Well, uh...
So what now?
Can you really get them together?
I'll think about it now.
I knew it...
There you are! Rin-chan!
Komari-san?
Good evening.
We're having a tea party in my room tonight.
Do you want to come too?
R-Right...
Go on. You can ask them about it.
Yeah...
Komari-chan... I'll go.
Yay!
Are you coming too, Riki?
No way!
Open wide!
I can eat by myself!
To think you'd come just like that.
Well, sorry!
Don't be. It's a very good thing.
I have a question for you guys.
Oh? Bring it, bring it!
What is it?
Ask anything you want!
Um... How can you get someone you like to like you back?
Rin-chan, are you in love with someone?!
It's love!
Lovey-lovey, lovey-dovey!
With me, I hope!
No, not me!
I just want to know how...
Naoe-san and Kyousuke-san are connected by a strong bond.
They don't need any help.
In fact, you'd just get in the way.
No!
If you both reach for the same book and run into each other
while rounding a corner and shouting "I'm late!" in the library you'll fall in love, apparently.
You got a few things mixed up there...
What do you think I should do?
Well...
Let's ask her what her hobbies are and the kinds of guys she's into.
What's the point of knowing?
We'll tell Aikawa-kun, of course.
I'm sure he wants to know more about the person he loves.
Natsume Rin!
Sneaking behind me all morning!
Just so you know, it won't go like it did last time!
No...
More importantly, what are your hobbies?
What do you do on the weekends?
She's jumping right in!
Why would you want to know?
Are you going to use it to make fun of me?
I won't make fun of you.
I just want to know more about you.
To get closer.
To the female named Sasasegawa Sasami.
You were so close...
So you are mocking me.
So?
"So"?
What was the question?
My hobbies?
What do you do on the weekends?
And what kind of guys are you into?
Like what they look like and their personality.
Can you be really specific?
I don't have any hobbies.
I practice softball on the weekends.
My ideal man is...
Miyazawa-sama from the kendo team.
Kengo?!
So Sasami likes Kengo?
How are we supposed to tell Aikawa-kun?
Yeah.
Let's ask Kengo what he thinks first.
That's kind of a crazy first step...
Huh?
Anyway, that's how it is. What do you think?
I don't know what to think.
First off, do you know who Sasasegawa-san is?
I do.
We always run into each other in the hallways, and she always greets me.
So she's trying to make passes...
So what?
What answer would end this talk?
Just say, "I don't care for her."
I don't care for her.
Is that good enough?
Kengo doesn't care for her.
What does Miyazawa-san have to do with it?
Well, Sasasegawa-san...
She likes Kengo.
What's wrong? He looks really shocked.
Or maybe he's feeling ill?
I'm pretty sure it's the former.
You're overreacting.
Kengo doesn't care for her.
It's a chance for you.
Chance?
Yeah.
What's Kengo's charm?
Charm
We'll think about that first.
Okay...
Kengo is freaking huge, scary, and brusque, but he's strong.
His charm is his strength.
Well, if you mean he's manly...
Beat Kengo up!
What?!
Charm
That's kind of random...
If you beat up the ever-so-strong Kengo in front of Salami's face,
she'll fall for you, no doubt.
But I don't do any sports.
There's no way I'd win...
I guess...
Hobbies
Then we'll take the "shared hobbies" route.
Charm
Hobbies
Sasasegawa-san said she didn't have any...
Just suggest something that you might be able to share.
What are your hobbies?
I like manga and games...
She wouldn't be into those.
What about music?
Is there anything you listen to?
Hip-hop, mostly.
Desktop? As in computer?
No, that's completely different!
How about lending her a CD you like?
What? Just out of the blue?
That's kinda difficult...
Then sing.
Charm
Hobbies
You can imply your secret love for Sasami through your own original lyrics!
Remember that last line?
Yeah.
"Sasasegawa Sasami, it was you!"
Good! Mission, start!
Hey, yo! Hey, yo!
Yo, yo, come on!
Check it out, yo!
Sasasegawa, you was cicada!
He messed it up!
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?
No...
That was a mistake!
Wait right there!
You can make up for it!
Just beat Kengo up!
I thought so...
I told you, I just can't do it.
Yeah. If you don't take him by surprise, that is.
You've got no choice.
I still don't think I can win!
Then it'll be a sneak attack times 3.
Times 3?
First, I'll pretend to trip and take out Kengo's legs.
Me
Kengo
Naturally, Kengo will jump to avoid me.
Next, Riki will shout, "Set meal A, coming right up!"
Me
Kengo
Riki
and throw a tray at Kengo's head.
Then he'll put his hands behind his head in defense.
Then you'll shout, "Miyazawa Kengo, I've got you!"
while kicking him from behind.
I'm pretty sure he won't even feel it...
Get a running start and put your soul into it!
Sprint from 200 meters away!
That's a long hallway...
You mean slam into him?
Yeah.
He'll have no way to dodge.
If you have the momentum, he'll fly!
I can't imagine him flying.
You'll need to hit him hard.
And then...
You'll be a legend.
Sasami's here.
Okay.
Kengo's here.
Mission, start!
Hey, you!
Look out!
Set meal A, coming right up!
No, Aikawa-kun!
Miyazawa Kengo, I've got you!
What's this? Some new game?
Here.
Kyousuke made you do it, right?
What a troublemaker.
Who is that assailant?
My, it's that rude fellow from before!
I saw the whole thing.
You're amazing, Miyazawa-sama!
I mean, Miyazawa-san.
Um... sorry.
We'll think of something better next...
No, it's okay.
What do you—
I'll just forget about it.
Thanks for everything you've done for me.
You're just going to give up?!
Rin.
Rin, have you ever been in love?
That's sudden.
Maybe we tried to fix everything so fast because neither of us have been in love.
Isn't love a happy thing?
I'm pretty sure it's a painful thing.
Lovesickness...
Just as the word says. It's a real sickness.
What about him?
He wants to forget, but he can't.
He'll be in pain forever.
Is that how it is?
Probably.
Sounds painful.
What was the task this time?
Ease lovesickness, right?
It didn't say to realize his love.
We don't need to get them together.
We just need to ease the pain of unrequited love.
Riki, I'll be right back!
Why do you keep calling me out?
I'm sorry.
Um...
It was all my fault.
All? You mean that rude fellow too?
Yeah.
So please forgive him.
Well, if that's the case...
And...
C-Could I get your phone number?
What? You want to be friends with me?
Not me...
There's this person who wants to be your friend...
Then that person can come talk to me directly.
Whenever he sees you, his chest tightens.
He can't even study because he's thinking about you all the time.
That's the kind of person he is.
I don't know much about stuff like that.
But he was in a lot of pain.
Sasa... Saza...
Sasasegawa Sasami!
Please!
I don't care about him.
But I know the pain in his chest.
Wait right there.
I'll bring my phone.
Sazazegawa Sazami!
It's Sasasegawa Sasami!
It's Sasami's phone number.
But you can only send one text per day!
You'll need to get to know her better before anything else!
Also, try not to think about her except when you're texting.
And do your studying.
Okay?
Yeah. Got it.
Thank you.
Did that resolve it?
It's up to him.
But you've done as much as you could.
I think you did a good job.
Really?
I wonder if the day will come when Rin falls in love.
Strike!
Nice!
Her pitch speed's back down.
Let's take a cat and—
I'm not letting a bully go!
I haven't done anything yet!
Sasasagawa Sasami!
It's Sasaseso—
It's Sasasegawa Sasami!
You messed up your own name...
What now? Come to get in our way again?
No, today...
I'd like to ask you something.
Um...
Could you tell me what
Miyazawa-sama's favorite food is?
Wow, he's popular.
Tell her it's cup yakisoba without throwing the water out.
It's cup yakisoba without throwing the water out.
Not throwing the water out
is good for the environment!
She believed it!
I wonder how it tastes.
Have you ever eaten it?
I've never eaten it.
And it was a lie from Masato anyway.
Again?!
You dare to mock me?!
Fine! I'll seal that mouth of yours shut today!
Girls, you know what to do!
Like this?!
It's starting again...
Episode 20
Ease Lovesickness
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
On a night of shooting stars,
I watched Kud perform a strange ceremony.
Riki, have you ever seen the Southern Cross?
One by one, Kud's secrets are revealed.