I was raised as part of the Saigusa family.
It's an old, respected family.
It has a lot of pride in itself.
They started a tradition to ensure an heir.
Each woman in the family takes two husbands.
One of those husbands was that man.
Two husbands per wife?
Great way to keep a family going, right?
Makes you laugh, right?
But I can't laugh because we were born like that.
"We"?
Futaki Kanata is a member of the family.
We're twins.
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
After the two of us were born,
our three parents just couldn't take it anymore.
Saigusa Shou went to the main house and became violent.
He was arrested for attempted murder.
Saigusa Haruka
With a criminal in the family, the Saigusa family's reputation was destroyed.
The relatives were furious.
They kicked out our parents and took us in for themselves.
I was raised by the Saigusa family.
She was raised by the Futaki family, a branch of the Saigusas.
After the incident,
the Futaki family took control of the Saigusas.
And then, we learned of a shocking secret.
The two of us were born from separate fathers.
Twins born from separate fathers?
Sometimes, when a woman
consummates with two men,
she can have children from both simultaneously.
So basically, one of us is the daughter of Saigusa Shou, a criminal.
Only our three parents know who's who.
But no one knows where the two who were kicked out went,
and Saigusa Shou refused to say anything in prison.
The Saigusa family held a family meeting
and decided to identify which of us wasn't the criminal's daughter so she could succeed the family.
We were raised and judged against each other.
For example, whoever learned to read first...
You know a lot of words, Kanata.
Or whoever was more mature...
You can sit really straight, Kanata.
Whoever was healthier...
Whoever was smarter and more athletic...
Kanata won first place in the
school marathon even with a fever!
She's at the top of her class too!
The one chosen to be heiress...
was her.
I was dubbed as the daughter of the criminal.
That's what they decided.
After that, they treated me like a harbinger of misfortune.
The daughter of a useless man.
A worthless good-for-nothing.
Everyone wished I'd never been born.
When the business wasn't doing well, it was my fault.
If there was bad gossip going around at a meeting, it was my fault.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It's my fault! I'm sorry!
I was beaten whenever anything happened.
I was a wretch.
Since she was such a model student,
I decided to do things to piss her off.
I did the exact opposite of whatever she did.
It was fun to see her so annoyed.
The Saigusa family planted a spy in the school.
That's why they had weekly reports on what I did.
Our relatives would lecture her for hours.
"She did that because you weren't watching her closely enough!"
"She shames the family because you're not good enough!"
Saigusa
Serves you right!
I didn't belong in my family.
I finally became free after coming to this school.
I was able to make friends, and I could finally have fun.
But then...
she distributed those flyers.
And now I'm going to lose my place here too.
No!
I don't want that!
That's just terrible...
I did bad things on purpose.
They told me they wished I'd never been born.
If I...
If this...
If I knew this was going to happen...
I wish I'd never been born!
Don't say that!
You can't.
Why?
Because it's too sad.
If you say that...
Yeah!
There was a time when I thought that way too.
I wished I'd never been born.
I was about to give up on life.
But that's when Kyousuke told me...
Nothing good can come from rejecting yourself!
Nothing that's happened up until now matters!
That's right!
You're our friend, Haru-chan!
Now and forever!
Forever! Forever and ever!
You won't...
hate me?
Of course not!
Don't think so lightly of us now.
We're not like those worthless adults.
It's so much fun when you're around, Saigusa-san!
You're always so bright and cheerful! Among us, you're the best...
Um, what's the word...
Moodmaker.
Yeah! Moodmaker!
You're lying...
You're all too nice, so you must be lying to me...
You're really thinking that you don't need me!
As if!
We'd never think that.
Trust us.
Get back in the game, Psychopathic Maracas!
Where'd the jerk who ate my cutlet bowl go?
How can I fire myself up if you aren't screwing around with a smile on?
Come on, let's fight again!
Come on!
Haru-chan!
Saigusa-san!
I wanted someone to stay by my side.
I wanted someone to say, "Yeah, you're right."
Saigusa.
We're by your side now.
You're one of the Little Busters.
We'd be in a bind without you.
We need you.
This is where you belong!
After that, we played baseball with Kyousuke managing practice.
Until Saigusa-san could smile again.
This is where Saigusa-san belongs.
You're okay now, right?
Yep.
Promise us now.
You won't think that no one needs you again.
Sorry. I won't.
You shouldn't be apologizing to us.
You should be thanking us.
Okay.
Thanks, Riki-kun.
Thanks, guys.
Did you distribute those flyers?!
You did!
I wonder.
You bitch!
Yes, I know.
I'm a bitch.
That's why I'll do whatever it takes.
It seems you told those people about our family.
I'm warning you.
Don't drag your so-called friends into any trouble.
Troublemaker.
Shut up!
No matter what you say, Saigusa-san is an important member of the Little Busters.
And everyone hates you.
What an honor.
Unlike someone, I'm not weak.
I don't care if everyone hates me.
Did you hear? It's her, right?
Her father's...
Yeah. That's the type of person she is.
Attempted arson and multiple stabbings!
Time out!
Thanks.
But I'm okay now, Rin-chan.
But...
And I'm making a chiffon cake!
It's my treat!
Care to try?
Thank you.
It's so dry...
Huh? Not too good?
No, it's great! Right, Rin?
Yay!
I'm horrible at cooking, but I'm
good at cooking things with eggs!
Cooking things with eggs?
If it has eggs in it, I'm the best!
Cakes, omelettes, and fried eggs!
Especially chiffon cakes!
Now then! Down the hatch!
I'm really happy I can do this.
I've never had friends before.
They didn't really let me go to school often in the Saigusa house.
Really?
I'm not used to being around other people.
I can't really figure out the mood, and I mess up all the time.
Don't worry. You'll get used to it soon enough.
I don't have much confidence in myself.
But since you'll stay with me through
thick and thin, I want to do what I can.
So I've decided.
I'm going to go see Saigusa Shou.
Saigusa Shou? Isn't that...
He's been in prison all my life,
but he was released recently.
I found out where he lives.
I'll go see him and ask him...
which kid is whose.
We just decided without any evidence.
Don't worry!
Even if I get the short end, I'll still have closure.
If that's what you really want...
I'm tired of not knowing.
If I find out who my real father is,
I think that in itself will make me happy.
Thanks for coming with me.
I wouldn't have the courage to come alone.
Are you okay?
We're almost at the address.
It's around here.
Whaddaya want? Quit starin'.
Saigusa Shou.
That's you, isn't it?
Who's that? Wrong guy.
You are!
You're just like the picture!
You worthless, good-for-nothing bum!
What'd you call me?!
I'm Haruka!
You understand, don't you?
I'm here to ask you...
Who's my real father?!
Tell me! Tell me, damn it!
Is it you?
Go home.
Get lost!
Saigusa-san!
Saigusa-san has suffered for a long time.
After all that suffering, all she wants to know is who her real father is.
Could you please tell her?
And what if she finds out?
Knowing won't do her any good.
It's better...
if she didn't know.
Stop!
I... I'm that man's daughter.
That's my real...
H-He might not!
Futaki-san might know the truth!
Maybe.
She went to see him in prison sometimes.
Then you can ask—
She'd never tell me!
This situation is better for her!
I want to know the truth...
Is Saigusa-san really Saigusa Shou's daughter?
Maybe...
It is not my place to say this, but I think
distributing those flyers was going too far—
Drive.
Just die.
Was that the Saigusa family...
It's rare for the main family to come to a place like this.
What?
Why the face?
No...
I didn't think you'd respond.
Those people care more for outward appearances than anything else.
They're on pins and needles with our father out of prison.
I met Saigusa Shou today.
With Saigusa-san.
I see.
"I see"? Is that it?
What do you want me to say?
Sympathy for Haruka?
How nice you are to her.
Are you pitying her?
I don't pity her.
You shouldn't say things like that.
You're right.
I apologize.
But she has more needs and indecision than anyone you've ever known.
If you aren't really ready to deal with her, then—
From what you're saying,
I'd say you're worried for her.
Naoe Riki.
Don't you think life is a zero-sum game?
Do you think the amount of happiness is constant?
Let's say the amount of happiness and unhappiness in the world is fixed.
Life is a game where if one person becomes happy, another becomes unhappy.
Everyone thinks that they're the most unhappy.
And everyone who thinks they're unhappy thinks everyone else is happy.
Were you...
unhappy in the Futaki family too?
Do you know who Saigusa-san's real father is?
If you do, please tell me.
Why?
Saigusa-san is suffering.
That's why—
That's why you'd ask me something so heartless?
Do you think you can save her like that?
Like you could save someone.
Who the hell do you think you are?
I...
I just want to help someone.
Just as I was helped.
If someone is suffering, I want to be of help to them.
But just like you said,
I might be drunk with the desire to save Saigusa-san.
To think that anyone could
save someone else is arrogant.
I was heartless.
Sorry.
I apologize.
We may be fighting against something we can't see.
Saigusa-san and Futaki-san are trapped in a manmade web of chains.
How can we free them from those chains?
Riki-kun!
Are thoughts of me troubling you?
N-No...
Let's take a break from thinking!
I made some chiffon cake!
Okay, sure. Thanks.
Eat it! Eat it!
I wonder how it is...
It's good!
It's softer and fluffier than last time!
It's moist!
Last time?
Did you practice a lot?
Saigusa-san?
What's wrong?
Another prank?
You shouldn't waste food—
Hey, Riki-kun, do you...
like me?
Futaki-san?
Episode 17
I Wanted Someone to Stay by My Side
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
Saigusa-san and Futaki-san.
How can we untangle the chains around their hearts?
What do they really want?
Find it.
Mission, start!