Riki-kun, this is serious!
Really serious!
What's wrong?
Well, I was told to come get you by saying it was serious!
Serious!
Right...
Is it a fight?
Come to get some muscles?
Oh man, what to do?
I don't think that's it.
What's serious? Did something bad happen?
Muscles, muscles...
I wonder.
Oh dear...
It's not really that serious, so I guess we'll go back.
Thanks for your time!
Are you sure about not going?
We are in the middle of a game.
I see.
So you chose us, huh?
Then we'd better burn out the night better than they could.
You're always so competitive.
Who do you like, Riki?
Huh?
That came out of the blue.
Love and romance make the night, don't they?
Why me?
What about you?
There's nobody I like.
So who do you like?
Nobody.
Like we'd believe that.
You're right in the middle of adolescence.
Then shouldn't you have one too, Kyousuke?
So who do you like?
Why me?!
We couldn't get him.
We're sorry.
So it failed.
In that case...
Right now, I love you the most, Riki.
Huh?
Hey, you're blushing!
No, I'm not!
I see. That's good.
If you two got hitched, I wouldn't be able to spend as much time with Riki.
A love triangle?
So, what about you, Riki?
Sure it's not Kyousuke?
Huh?
You serious?
No, no!
I don't like you!
I don't like you at all!
I see.
I need a little fresh air.
He's looking pretty down.
Well, he just got completely rejected.
Kyousuke!
Wait!
You...
You don't like me.
That was a lie!
I love all of the Little Busters!
That also means...
I love you too, Kyousuke!
Riki!
I should've known.
Yeah!
The Little Busters are the best!
Yup!
The heck are they doing?
The Little Busters are the best!
I don't know.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
The Little Busters are the best!
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
The Little Busters are the best!
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Rin
This is serious
Come to my room.
Alone.
Yahoo!
The Little Busters are the best!
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Rin asked me to go to her room alone.
Did she get another of those letters?
What do you want to drink?
Something carbonated maybe?
Think they've got anything new?
If they find me in the girls' dorm at this hour,
they won't let me off with just a written apology...
Capital punishment.
Capital punishment?
Fifty pages of written apologies, half a day of lecture,
being made an example of at the morning assembly, and a month's worth of detentions?
Too many students have been
breaking the school rules recently.
In order to straighten the
twisted discipline of this school,
we will cover every inch of this dorm tonight.
If you find any students breaking the rules, apprehend them immediately.
I will make one round before attending the meeting.
Dismissed.
Yes, ma'am!
Of all the days for that!
Welcome to Rin's room!
Now then.
It's time for a seriously happy fun sleepover.
It's serious!
Really serious!
Wait, give me some time...
There's no time to give.
I think it's best if you don't resist.
Rin!
Sorry, Riki.
They bribed her?
Hello?
Where exactly did you go to get drinks?
Kyousuke! I'm in Rin's room—
We're going to have some pleasant,
bubbly, giggly, and lovely girl talk tonight.
Riki-kun will be our toy until morning.
What'd Riki say?
He's been kidnapped.
The doughnuts from this store are really good!
I brought cream puffs!
Or would you rather have seaweed?
I...
No, I can't stay here.
I'm going back.
That was close...
You'd be in a serious predicament if the disciplinary committee finds you.
Serious!
Really serious!
Now, what should we do?
Let's rescue him.
Yeah.
Wait. If all three of us go,
we'll definitely get caught.
Kurugaya isn't the only one we're up against.
Futaki Kanata and her disciplinary committee...
What?!
Disciplinary Committee
If they find Riki, he'll... he'll...
Who's going?
Let's decide with this.
Once the disciplinary committee is done with their rounds, I'm leaving.
Now that Riki-kun's made up his mind,
or rather, now that he's thinking, "Ain't this a harem? Hell yeah, this totally rocks"...
No, that's not what I'm thinking...
Okay, Rin-chan, you take a bath first!
A bath?!
That's right.
Look, we brought our pajamas!
I don't need to take a bath.
Rin-chan, you need to take a bath to wash off the day's sweat.
But he's around! I can't take one!
So she is concerned about that kind of stuff...
How about this, then?
Oh?
We might as well tie his hands too.
Why?!
Want a gag in that mouth, boy?
What's the point of all this in the first place?!
No need to mind him now!
I do mind!
Then I'll take a bath with you!
N-No!
Then perhaps I should go with you.
That's even worse, you retard!
Me, Komari-kun, or Riki-kun.
Who will go with you?
Why am I included?!
We should give her three choices.
Komari-chan.
Yay!
Let's bath time!
Okay—
No.
I didn't even say anything.
Hey, can you take these off yet?
It's more fun this way, so we'll leave it on.
What?!
You keep making invisible pitches!
Be thankful I'm not pitching my curveballs.
Like anybody could hit that!
Why don't we decide with this?
Here, Riki-kun, a choco-pie.
The cream puffs are yummy too! Here!
I get the feeling I'm being
..completely humiliated right now...
Are you happy?
Not really.
I'll wash your back!
N-No! You don't need to!
There, there!
Hey! You touched me in a weird spot!
There aren't any weird spots on you, Rin-chan.
Here. Let's clean the back of your ears too!
The boy has grown quiet.
He seems to be envisioning the scene.
How lewd, Riki-kun! How lewd!
No! I wasn't!
How? On the first sword?!
How about playing some Concentration?
Perfect!
Sorry we took so long!
Rin-san, let's take a bath together!
Why would I bathe twice?!
So you won't take one with me?
You'd bathe with Komari-san but not me...
Rin-chan.
I-Is it too hot?
No, it's just right!
Wafu!
That felt really good!
I'm gonna faint...
I guess that means you won't be taking one with me.
Of course not!
Anego, let's take a bath together!
Alright.
What about you, Mio-kun?
I took a shower before I came here.
You guard yourself well.
And you, Riki-kun?
Uh, y'know, you shouldn't be inviting me.
Well, how do I put this...
Her boobs were like, boom!
Anego, you're amazing!
You really do pack a serious punch!
Don't say that.
You're making me blush.
I wish I was as sexy as you.
They're too much!
A body like mine is more than enough.
This makes me mad!
Well, let's leave this flat puppy alone...
Flat
She just came right out and said it!
Don't worry.
You're already 120% cute enough this way, Kudryavka-kun.
You have this creepy look.
Okay, you're next, Riki-kun.
Huh? Me?
Take a bath, you!
That's right, you!
But I didn't bring a change of clothes...
Have these, my liege.
My pajamas? When did you get them?!
We figured this might happen.
I get the feeling this is heading in a really bad direction...
What photos are you planning on taking?
Wh-What photos?
What photos...
Uh, what are you envisioning?
Looks like Kurugaya-san can get
several times worse than Kyousuke.
But I guess it's a good thing that Rin can now participate in a sleepover.
Did they force me to stay here
because it would help Rin settle in?
If that's the case...
I guess I can spare tonight.
I take that back.
Kurugaya-san?!
Would you rather wear a fundoshi?
That's even worse!
So you can't even walk around in your underwear.
Geez!
Sure is busy up there.
I will give them a warning.
Nah, you stay here.
I'll go let them know.
Riki-kun, you're so cute!
So cute!
Th-Thanks...
It suits you.
You're about as tall as I am, so it fits you perfectly.
I'll tie your hair!
What color ribbon should we go with?
I don't even care anymore...
What?
She wants to say, "Riki-kun, so moe."
I don't.
Nothing wrong with it.
Riki-kun's pretty cute right now.
Don't get so close!
Stop taking photos!
I'll be sure to treasure this photo.
Please don't!
We can hear you from the first floor!
Sorry, we're having a little gathering here.
That's fine, but don't make too much noise.
Otherwise scary disciplinary officers may drop by.
Okay.
She's so nice.
Your cover didn't get blown, Riki-kun.
Nobody would notice if you went to the female side of a public bath.
You can let your nose bleed a fountain
while thinking, "Shit, this is awesome."
Why are you treating me like some kind of mega pervert?!
I gave them a real earful about making less noise.
Let's leave them be until the lights go out.
Alright.
Kud-o! Gimme 'nother pint!
That's just normal tea, right?
Anego, your boobs are sexy!
Mad sexy!
You make me seem like the epitome of sexiness.
So sexy!
Something like this?
K-Kurugaya-san!
There, there.
This is way too sexy.
I think some lilies in the background would be perfect.
You mean something like this?
You're very cute.
Very nice.
I told you to stop taking photos!
Kurugaya-san.
Right, let me send this to the
older Natsume and the idiot duo.
Seriously, don't!
Oh, you read newspapers, Rin?
The cats like them.
I got you!
Stop bullying Komari-chan!
Huh? It doesn't hurt.
Let's play a game. Swordfighting!
Swordfighting!
Let's fight!
They're starting something.
My deepest gratitude!
Mine contritions...
Directly translated, those mean "thank you" and "what a shame" respectfully.
Wanna play too, Anego?
I'm playing too?
This isn't really my thing, but...
Come on.
You'll see how fun it is when you play.
Just plain old swordfighting is pretty boring.
Let's add some sort of penalty for losing!
Good idea.
The person who gets hit the most
has to tell everyone who they like.
Wafu... That's kind of...
My deepest gratitude!
If we don't hurry, Riki will...
Quick... next...
Your display of willpower moves me to tears.
Kengo, right hand blue!
Futaki-san, let me prepare the tea.
I won't be long.
Alright.
My deepest gratitude!
Not bad, Naoe-san.
We played this a lot back when we were young.
My deepest gratitude!
M-M-Mine contritions...
In that case...
Heavenly Technique: White Blade Catch!
What?!
Do you surrender?
My deepest gratitude.
M-Mine contritions...
Let go!
Come on, join us.
No!
I won't do it. It's lame.
Oh? You're running?
Well well, my deepest gratitude.
This isn't a game where cowards can go "my deepest gratitude."
My deepest gratitude!
Mine contritions...
I'll do it.
I can't forgive bullies!
Use my sword!
My deepest gratitude.
Rin's totally into this.
Here I come.
Evildoer, prepare to taste my blade!
Very well. Bring it.
This looks to be an awesome fight!
My deepest gratitude.
Your line.
Mine contritions...
Wait, Mio-chin! That wasn't fair!
I'm sorry, but you were full of openings.
In that case...
My deepest gratitude!
Sorry it took so long.
New Punishment for Dorm Rule Violations
Fifty pages of written apologies,
half a day of lecture,
being made an example of at the morning assembly,
and a month's worth of detentions!
All violators of dorm rules shall receive
capital punishment
Effective immediately, patrols will cover every inch of the dorm.
Patrols will cover every inch of the dorm!!
Ponytail Defense!
Let me explain. The Ponytail Defense—
My deepest gratitude.
M-Mine contritions...
It's done!
Let's roll another one in to reinforce it.
Take this!
Tachi of the Void
Ryuugetsu
Not bad.
How much of a racket do you plan on making?
You girls again?
You.
Come over here.
Oh no...
You...
Your ribbon isn't straight.
I've never seen you around.
Do you live at home?
Only residents are allowed in the dorms after hours.
I brought her in.
It's not her fault.
Then, Kurugaya-san, you will submit a written apology tomorrow.
If the disturbance continues past curfew, you will all be punished.
Understood?
She didn't find out.
Naoe-san's crossdressing is perfect!
Mine contritions!
Be careful on the way back.
Thanks, Kurugaya-san.
Thanks.
Rest well.
Riki! You're safe!
Kyousuke!
We couldn't decide who'd go until just now.
Decide on what?
More importantly, you've changed back already?
She actually sent it?!
What's wrong? It suits you.
You're cute, Riki.
Riki... I'll come rescue you...
Episode 15
Hell Yeah, This Totally Rocks!
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
Futaki Kanata is the head of the disciplinary committee.
Why is she out to get Saigusa-san for every little thing?
The time has come for a deep secret about them to come to light.