Take this!
Bring it on!
Muscles!
Muscles coming through!
There!
Alright!
It's over here, Komari-kun.
Found you!
Alright, let's end practice here.
Sure.
Okay.
Rin-chan, Yui-chan, good work!
You're a very happy camper, Komari-kun.
Let me give you a pat on the head.
But where is this "Yui-chan"?
Kurugaya Yuiko.
What?!
You mean me?!
At least call me "Kurugaya-chan"!
But you're Yui-chan.
I'll call you "Komarimax", then!
Komarimax
How's that? Embarrassing, right?
Sure. I don't mind.
Speaking of which, can you call her "Komari-chan" yet, Rin?
It seems that the younger Natsume is quite shy.
Here.
Komari-chan
Try reading this, Rin-chan.
Come on, Rin.
You just have to read it.
What're you doing, stupid?!
When you try passing someone on a bicycle, you have to pedal a little bit harder, right?
Just put the same kind of effort into this.
Go on.
Komari-chan
K-K...
Ko-Ko-Ko...
Komari-chan
Komada!
Who's that?
Formerly of the Tokyo Giants?
I'm not a former Giant!
Are you okay, Komari-chan?!
You called me "Komari-chan"!
Komari-san's smile was like the sun.
She probably doesn't think about him when she's outside.
Kamikita Takuya
About her brother, who only appears in her dreams.
Does her brother really exist?
Or is he...
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
You know, yesterday...
I had another dream about Onii-chan.
He was smiling.
There were white flappy things blowing in the wind.
White flappy things?
I don't really know.
It was somewhere close to the sky, I think.
Onii-chan called me, "Komari".
And when I woke up, his voice echoed in my ears.
He might be looking for me somewhere.
Maybe that's why he's calling me in my dreams.
White flappy things...
Somewhere close to the sky...
A hospital?
What's wrong?
Komari-san's brother might have been in a hospital.
And...
he passed away.
No! He has to be alive!
It'd be great if he were...
Riki, is there some way we can find him?
Kojirou-san, I'm coming in.
Get out!
Oh, it's just you, kid?
You don't need to yell.
Who wouldn't yell at a rude kid entering without permission?
But I knocked...
Go back out and do it again.
Ask for permission with a loud, enthusiastic voice.
If you sound like a punk, even better.
Yo! Naoe Riki here!
I'm here to see Kojirou-san!
Alright! Come in!
Roger!
I'm just an old man trying to make the most of what little time he still has.
Don't take it too hard, kid.
So, what do you want?
You wouldn't come here unless you wanted something.
I know it's not my place to ask,
but I'd like to know about Komari-san's brother.
You know something about him right, Kojirou-san?
Komari-san often dreams about her brother.
She wants to see him.
If she really has a brother, and he's still alive, I want to look for him.
How much do you know, kid?
Nothing.
But I think her brother was in a hospital.
Well, you're right.
As for where he is now, it's probably exactly where you think.
Do me a favor and don't tell the girl.
Alright.
If you really care about her, don't pry any deeper.
But why hasn't anyone told Komari-san—
I told you not to pry.
I'm sorry.
I can't tell you any more.
Consider what I've told you thanks for cleaning my room the other day.
Thank you very much.
Next time I come, I won't ask about this.
Muscles...
Yay...
So Komari-san's brother really did pass away.
But why doesn't Komari-san remember anything about him,
and why hasn't anyone told her that he died?
Because she'd be sad?
That can't be the only reason.
They're hiding something.
A secret from Komari-san.
Huh?
I was just hungry!
I had to do it!
Komari-san?
No!
I'm not Komari, but I am Komari,
but I'm a different Komari...
Wait, maybe I should calm down first.
You scared me there.
I thought I was going to be in trouble.
I accidentally fooled you completely.
You didn't fool me completely, though.
Why are you outside?
To get some more snacks.
I'm going to stay awake until morning with some crackers and chips.
Until morning?
There's a meteor shower tonight.
I think I can see it from my window too.
Oh, I know!
If you want to join me, we can watch it there!
Let's watch some shooting stars!
From somewhere close to the stars!
The view here is incredible.
It's like the city is part of the stars in the sky!
It's something you can see anywhere,
but when you say that, it really does look like part of it.
Did you know?
When you see a shooting star, if you make a wish three times, it'll come true.
A wish?
It doesn't look like it's started yet.
I'm not a very lucky person, so it's all up to your luck, Komari-san.
What should I wish on for a shooting star to fall?
Did I say something funny?
No, it's just that we thought the same thing.
"What should I wish on for a shooting star to fall?"
Since we're already here, why don't we go somewhere higher?
If I go up first, you'll see them.
And it's a bear today...
I-It's not that I like wearing kiddy panties!
I just happened to wear a bear today and a flower yesterday...
I wore grown-up ones the day before that...
I didn't ask anything.
What if I cover my eyes?
Is this okay?
Okay. Don't look.
Wow, this is high.
This will be the best place to see them.
Have some black cossee.
They didn't have any seaweed 'n' salt ones, so I got some lightly salted ones.
Thanks.
Let's munch down on these while watching the shooting stars.
This'll be my first time seeing a shooting star.
I was never even interested in seeing one before.
I think you're really good at finding things like this.
Things like what?
Wonderful things.
I think you can see more things than normal people can.
I'm normal.
I think your eyes can see more than normal too, if you tried.
I think I have a wish.
Riki-kun, I wish your eyes could see just a little more than you do now.
There's another!
A second one, just now!
Really?
Looks like you could see it.
Maybe because of your wish.
Hey...
What did you just wish for?
That all the Little Busters can be happy.
I wished for the same thing!
Really?
Yeah. I love everyone.
It's fun being together because that's everyone's happiness.
It's fun because there's so much happiness.
The sixth shooting star fell as Komari-san slept.
And so, I wished...
I wished that whatever secret there was, it wouldn't be something sad.
I wasn't sleeping! I wasn't sleeping!
The sun should be rising soon.
There's the seventh one!
That might have been the last one.
There's one more. That makes eight.
I thought the seventh was the last one,
but one more disappeared.
What's wrong?
I remembered.
The story of the little match girl.
The little match girl?
On New Year's Eve, the little match girl went to Heaven.
The girl's life disappeared along with the last shooting star.
Just like how my dream of Onii-chan disappears when I wake up.
Komari-san may have started to realize what happened to her brother.
Komari-san...
Hey, Riki-kun...
This Saturday, would you, you know, maybe...
Would you go on a date with me?
I want to go somewhere kind of far to look for it.
For something I lost.
Something you lost?
My memories.
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
No, I just got here.
I've always wanted to say that.
It's what everyone says when they wait for someone.
Yeah. Those clothes...
Do they look weird on me?
I don't think so.
I think they're just right.
Alright, let's go!
To find what I've lost.
You know, I used to live around here.
Really?
But I don't remember it very well.
Even though I should have a lot of memories.
Forgetting things you don't want to and things you have to remember is really sad.
Komari-san came here to remember her brother.
A hospital?
Is that where her brother passed away?
Riki-kun...
Are you... kind of sad?
No, not at all.
Let's go on a boat!
It's so pretty.
Yeah! It really is!
Wow, look at all the fishies!
What are you looking at?
The bottom of the lake.
I can't see it.
Her eyes were sad, as though she were looking for the bottom of her memories.
No matter how much her eyes were able to see,
she was unable to see it.
Hey, I was thinking...
You really want to remember your brother, right?
Yeah.
Losing something is sad.
Even when I lose something as tiny as a worn-out eraser,
I feel pretty down for a day or so.
That's why I'm looking for them.
Do you really have to look for them?
Your brother is always in your dreams.
Isn't that good enough?
I... I guess so.
Then, Riki-kun...
Would you be my Onii-chan?
Did I surprise you?
Can I sit next to you—
We're back a bit later than planned.
And they said there was only a 20% chance of rain...
I don't like the rain.
Crackers get all soggy.
Let's go!
No!
A thunderstorm with a 20% chance of rain?!
I don't like scary things or spicy things...
Let's find a convenience store and get an umbrella.
What's wrong?
A kitten?
It's not moving?
Why...
isn't it moving?
Komari-san?
Komari-san!
Onii-chan, let's ride a boat when you get better, okay?
It's a promise!
Listen, Komari.
This was all just a dream.
All a dream.
Episode 5
To Find What I've Lost
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
Komari-san has finally remembered.
Her lost, sad memories.
But that's really sad for Komari-chan!
You can't go back anymore.
Riki.
Mission, start!