No!
Komari-san...
Are you alright?
Let's head back.
Oh, you're back, Riki!
What's that you've got there?
A cat?
Come on in.
Huh? Komari?
Hey, what happened to her?
I don't know either.
You're both completely soaked.
She'll catch a cold like this, right?
Go take her to the showers.
I'll go bury him.
Whatever happened,
cheer her up.
Masato
Thanks, Masato.
I remember.
Everything.
What I lost.
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Onii-chan...
He wasn't very healthy, so he stayed in the hospital.
Found you!
But you haven't caught me yet!
Wait, Komari!
That night, the little match girl went to Heaven with the last shooting star.
Did the girl die?
No!
I don't want that!
Sorry.
I won't tell you sad stories anymore.
I'll write a story for you.
One day, an egg became a chick.
A chick! A chick!
The chick became a hen and laid an egg.
After taking three steps, the hen forgot that it was once an egg.
Onii-chan, you're so warm.
Onii-chan? What's wrong?
Listen, Komari.
When you wake up, I might not be here anymore.
But there isn't anything to be sad about.
It'll all be a dream.
A dream?
That's right.
All a dream.
So...
Good night.
Onii-chan?
Hey, wake up!
But there isn't anything to be sad about.
It'll all be a dream.
It's all a dream, so...
It's not sad.
She believed what her brother said and thought everything was a dream.
She's been using that to escape from her sadness all these years.
Just as Takuya-san wished, so she wouldn't be sad.
Thanks to his wish, Komari-san could smile the way she did.
When I was little, I found a pretty flower.
I picked it so I could take it to Onii-chan.
But it wilted shortly after.
I regretted doing it.
I didn't know it would wilt.
There are lots of things in this world I don't want to know.
I wish they were all gone!
What happened?
We heard from Masato-kun.
It's not much, but we brought a change of clothes for her.
Are you alright?
What happened?
It's probably better if we don't ask.
Come on.
Could you take her back to her room?
Komari-kun.
Let's go.
I wanna stay here.
I wanna stay with Onii-chan.
Onii-chan?
Can I, Onii-chan?
Komari-san, you have to go back to the girls' dorm.
It's almost time for dinner.
You won't go anywhere?
You won't go anywhere while I'm not with you, right?
Yeah.
I won't go anywhere.
That's a promise.
Regardless, let's get you back to your room, Komari-kun.
Bye-bye, Onii-chan.
How did it end up like this?
I see.
So that's what happened.
Komari-kun may be thinking that Riki-kun is her brother as a defense mechanism.
But that's just too sad!
Can't we do anything for her?
We can't do anything for her now.
It's impossible.
If she never remembered what she didn't want to know,
she would still be smiling like the sun right now.
I didn't want to know either.
I didn't want the truth.
But now that you know, there's no running away anymore.
If the world is full of things we never wanted to know,
is our only option to look the other way?
To run away?
It isn't.
You're someone special to Komari right now.
That means the only one who can do
something for her—to save her—is you.
Kyousuke!
You won't solve anything by running away.
I'm the only one who can save Komari-san.
But how?
Hey, Onii-chan...
I'm not him.
I'm Riki.
What are you saying?
You're Onii-chan.
Don't look at me like that.
When we saw those shooting stars, your eyes were shining.
Your eyes could find all sorts of wonderful things!
We saw shooting stars together?
When did we do that?
You don't remember?
That...
It's all wet!
I dropped it in a puddle.
But it's your picture book!
If you want it, you can have it.
Onii-chan will make me another one, so I don't need it.
Kamikita Takuya
So what I feared has happened...
Komari-san's memories are in a complete mess right now.
She should return to normal in a few weeks.
She'll forget everything, then return to her normal, happy self.
That's what happens every time.
Some kind of death triggered it, right?
That's how it always happens to her.
She cried and screamed when my wife died, too.
She wandered around looking for her brother in a daze,
with her memories in a total mess.
And as time went by, she gradually forgot it all.
Even the fact that she had a brother.
I heard she went through the same thing when her pet goldfish died.
So Komari-san's been through this a few times already?
Yes.
When she witnesses death, she
remembers her brother's death,
and as time passes, she forgets it all again.
She's repeated that cycle over and over.
That's why I stay away from her.
I don't have much time left.
I can only imagine what she'll go through if she sees me die.
I'm sure she'll be able to meet you normally someday!
I'm sure there's something I can do too.
I'm sure... something...
What on Earth do you think you can do, kid?
A friend told me.
If there's anyone who can save her, it's me!
Please tell me where Kamikita Takuya-san rests.
I'll go there to think about it!
Kamikita
Family
Takuya-san...
What can I possibly do?
Kamikita
Takuya-san's wish was for Komari-san not to be sad.
If he saw Komari-san in her
current state, what would he do?
That's it!
What?
Riki? Drawing?
He seems to have started drawing something for Komari-kun.
I...
Rin, want some pork cutlet with rice?
This isn't the time for dumb nonsense like that!
It's not dumb!
I'm just an idiot, so I don't know what to do!
In that case, let's bring Riki some pork rice balls!
That should beefen him up!
Good idea!
That makes two idiots.
There has to be something I can do too!
That girl...
In Takuya-san's book, the hen forgets it was once an egg.
Komari-san is the same way.
She keeps forgetting
after she remembers Takuya-san.
But at the very end, the hen does remember.
It remembers it was once an egg.
You won't solve anything by running away.
If you turn your eyes away from sad things, they'll happen again one day.
If you keep running away, you'll just repeat the same mistakes.
That's why you have to face the truth straight on.
I suck at this, but it's all I can do!
Please help her
I'm out of paper...
Riki!
Use this!
You collected all that, Rin?
The drawing paper and seaweed bowls are from Kurugaya!
Thanks!
Beef yourself up with these pork rice balls
Masato
I can't do anything, but give it your all
Kengo
Don't be too hard on yourself.
Also, your pictures are pretty good
Kyousuke
Beef yourself up with these pork rice balls.
I can't do anything, but give it your all!
Don't be too hard on yourself.
Also, your pictures are pretty good!
That's right...
They've always been there for me.
It's done!
There you are, Onii-chan.
Komari-san.
I'm Naoe Riki.
Not Takuya-san.
Then where's Onii-chan?
He's no longer here.
He passed away.
It's sad, but that's reality.
You have to accept it.
No! That's just a bad dream!
It's not a dream!
Sad things happen all the time!
Read this.
"The hen remembered that she was once an egg."
The hen opened her eyes to reality.
I added some more to the story.
The chick looked around herself,
and she realized that she had lots of friends around her.
They were always with her,
through happy times and sad times.
I was once the same.
There was a time when I cried like you.
Those were the hardest days of my life.
I had lost both of my parents.
That was when those four appeared before me.
Kyousuke took me on adventures.
Masato and Kengo and Rin laughed with me.
I ran forward alongside everyone.
It's the same for you too.
You can start running forward, alongside me and Rin!
So smile!
Even in the saddest and hardest times,
the Little Busters will always be together!
So smile like the sun!
Then you can start writing your own story!
A whole new story!
A whole...
new story?
You'll fill those blank pages with your own story!
Riki-kun!
Komari-chan...
Komari-chan!
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
Komari-chan!
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
Hang in there!
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
Komari-chan!
Hang in there!
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
If I keep crying...
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
Riki-kun, Rin-chan...
Everyone will be sad too.
Onii-chan...
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
isn't here anymore.
But there are so many wonderful things!
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
And I'll find a ton of them!
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
Starting now!
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
I'll make a picture book.
And I'll study too.
I'll eat sweet things, and I'll go see Grandpa Kojirou.
I'll find a ton of wonderful things.
I'll find them with everyone!
Onii-chan, I think I'm okay now.
Even if sad things happen and I cry, I know I'll be able to smile again!
Episode 6
Let's Find Wonderful Things
Hey, hey, everyone! Let's start with a bang!
Haru-chin will join your party!
What?!
You serious?!
You're joining the Little Busters, Saigusa-san?
Ya-hoo!
Mission, start!