I accidentally studied during class today.
Now I'm all sleepy.
We've got English next.
You forgot your homework last week.
Did you do it this week?
Crap! I forgot!
Hey, someone! Let me copy your homework!
Just use the same excuse you did last week.
"Aliens came down and beamed my notebook into oblivion."
No, that one won't work more than once.
Now matter how you look at it, aliens aren't going to be coming down that often.
Why don't you make the aliens Osakans, then?
I see...
Osakans came down and beamed my notebook into oblivion.
Aw, yeah. I rock!
But wouldn't they ask why Osakans have a grudge against me?
Start by changing the "beaming into oblivion" part.
You guys are idiots.
What'd you say?
I said, "You guys are idiots."
What do you mean, "you guys"?!
Don't lump Emperor Muscles here with that kendo uniform bum!
What do you think you're doing to Lennon?!
Anyone who wastes a cat is worse than Kengo!
Worse than Kengo?
I've gone sleazy on you all these years because you're Kyousuke's sister...
but now you've gone too far.
"Gone sleazy"?
Do you mean "gone easy"?
Rin!
Put up your dukes!
Here we go! They're going at it again!
It's a battle!
Alright.
Could you guys throw weapons for them into the ring?
What's that? You guys wanna fight too?
Rin's weapon is cats.
What about Masato's?
Nail clippers?
So be it.
I'll cut your nails so short you can't pull up the tab on soda cans!
Battle, start!
First strike, certain victory!
Masato cut Rin's nails!
They're cut too short!
Now you can't pull up tabs!
Damn!
I'll give you guys some Mon Petit later, so just hang in there!
Mon Petit
Get him!
N-Not bad...
Oh crap, he cracked the desk...
Winner: Rin!
You guys are amazing.
So you weren't just cute.
And now, according to the rules, the winner will bestow a title upon the loser, Masato.
Trash.
Masato has earned the title "Trash"!
No!
I don't want that title!
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Hey, Trash, could you pass the sauce?
Here.
Masa—I mean, Trash. Do you want some mayo?
Fine.
Do you really need that much, Masa—
Trash.
I'm sorry!
I want some too, so hurry up, Trash.
I can't take it anymore!
Are you having fun teasing Muscles?!
If you don't like it, I'll change it for you.
Retard.
Did you just call me "Retard"?
Who's the retard here?!
Shoot! I just realized that this one hurts even more!
And that's why...
What's why?
We, the Little Busters, must rededicate our time
to practice and let flow the sweat of youth.
Or so I'd like to say.
I hope you haven't forgotten that we don't have enough members yet.
Members, huh?
You're right.
I want one of you to take responsibility and find us some new members.
One of us?
One of who?
Riki, you recruited Komari and Kurugaya.
You're best suited for the job.
Good luck.
Make sure you find people with
actual skills to build our arsenal.
Okay...
People with skills to build our arsenal...
Dunno anyone like that.
What are you doing?
Now then, guess who!
Saigusa Haruka.
Yup! That's right!
Hey there, Riki-kun and Rin-chan!
Going on an after-school walk?
Hey...
Why were you standing here covering your own eyes?
Playing guess who?
You're supposed to cover the other person's eyes for that one.
Guess who!
Oh!
Don't act like you never knew that!
I was just waiting for someone to pass through this hall,
but no one came!
Well, I guess it's fine since you guys came.
I can't see the logic behind that...
Thanks!
That wasn't a compliment.
Let's go, Riki.
Hey, Saigusa-san.
Are you interested in baseball?
So I've got us a new member.
Yay! It's Haru-chan!
Riki, do you remember what I said?
Huh? What did you say?
I don't remember either.
What trash.
Trash!
Don't point at me!
For now, let's start with a membership test.
That would be best.
Yay!
What? What?
What's happening now?
First, we'll play some catch.
Where do I hit for ten points?
This isn't Struck Out.
You serious?!
No, I'm joking.
You just need to throw the ball back and forth.
I see!
We're playing catch!
I just said that...
She's not a very good listener.
Haruka-kun, over here.
Wow! That was good!
Haru-chan, you're so good!
Wait, what's she doing?
Playing catch with herself.
Saigusa, are you...
Huh?
Try putting this on her.
A left-handed mitt?
Is she a southpaw?
Probably.
You're right!
Watch this!
Saigusa Haruka!
There you are!
Oh no!
Disciplinary committee members?
Skipping detention...
and leaving this bad joke in your place!
It's not a bad joke.
It's a work of art!
This is the principal's wig!
That's all, folks!
Wait right there!
This month alone, you've been late for school 20 times and broken curfew 15 times!
You never do what you're
supposed to during detention!
We're putting you in the slammer!
They caught me!
If you skip detention again, the school's turning you in.
I'm not skipping!
I'm just having a little fun!
They're the same thing!
Psychopathic Maracas.
What a woman.
Really?
You invited Saigusa to join the Little Busters?
Does she really want to be a member?
I wonder...
I hope she will.
No way that's happening.
She's a flake.
Huh?
Kengo?
Trash! You little...
The hell was that for?!
What're you talking about?
The only person who'd do
something this stupid is you!
Hey, hey, everyone!
Good morning, good morning!
Hey, what're you doing here?
Well, sir, thanks for asking!
You see, I wanted to see how things were going over here.
How things were going?
Don't tell me you did this...
Well, um, sure.
I didn't do it.
What's with that terrible acting?
Actually, yesterday, I set up a trap as an experiment.
But no one came, so I got bored.
So I left it here and went home.
She doesn't feel guilty at all.
Have you seen Saigusa Haruka?
She took a couple buckets from the dorms without permission.
You mean these?
Huh?
Hey—
What are you doing?
There she is!
She's not!
Saigusa Haruka isn't here!
Hey—
Wait right there!
Wait, why are you taking me with you?
If I'm Going Down, I'm Taking You with Me, Vol. II!
A hostage has its uses!
Wait right there!
Running away is the only skill you've got!
You're not getting away!
Secret technique: Marble Roller!
What's this?!
Come on! Now's our chance!
Wafu?
Wafu?!
Kud?!
Wafuu!
Are you alright, Kud?
Wafuu...
Oh, Naoe-san!
Um...
How are you and I'm fine thank you!
Um, sorry, but I'm in a bit of a rush.
You shouldn't be running away, you know.
I'll need to go back to pick up those marbles later.
Causing trouble like always, I see.
Saigusa Haruka.
Disci-
plinary
Troublemaker.
President!
This girl is making fools of us!
We can't handle her!
Do something about her!
I'm going to raise a few issues at an administrative meeting with the student council.
Finding and removing troublemakers is your job.
And you.
What was your name?
Naoe Riki.
It seems you're always raising trouble with those rowdy friends of yours.
You cracked a desk yesterday with one of your little games.
Destroying property is a serious violation of the school code.
We're still working out a punishment for you.
Warn your friends.
Wait!
I told you my name, but you haven't told me yours.
Futaki Kanata.
Remember it.
Futaki Kanata?
She's an outstanding disciplinary committee member.
Kanata-kun?
She's the head of the disciplinary committee.
She's extremely talented and makes no compromises.
I wonder what she'll want for us cracking that desk.
Was it that bad?
I'm the one who cracked it...
It's partially my fault too.
Well, whatever.
There's no point thinking about it now.
Let's start practice.
Oh shoot. I forgot my gym clothes.
You guys go on ahead!
Heyo, Riki-kun.
I think this should do the trick.
You fixed the desk that Masato broke?
Wow, you're pretty talented.
I'm actually a maintenance committee member.
It's usable, so I don't think you'll have to pay for it or anything.
Thank you!
Everyone will be glad to hear it.
I know I caused you a lot of trouble.
It's the least I could do.
Were you that worried about it?
Well, Futaki Kanata might not be as lenient since I'm the one who fixed it, though.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
No, nobody trusts me after all.
I'm always late, and I lie about everything.
Lie?
About everything?
Dunno.
Who knows!
Were you always good at that sort of thing?
I guess...
You acquired cans from the vending machine unlawfully earlier, am I correct?
We have a witness.
I believe an inspection is in order.
I see. So it was true.
How did you get these?
I was incredibly lucky today!
I won the roulette, got another one, and just when I went "Yay!" I won again!
WINNER
I ended up with four in total!
Impossible!
Who'd believe a liar like you?
Anyway, you're coming with us.
I'm innocent, I swear!
Hey, are you listening to me?!
Let me go! Let me go!
Wait!
Stop, Futaki-san!
You shouldn't assume she's guilty!
Saigusa-san isn't the type of person who would do that!
Hey, what's up, Riki?
Everyone was worried since you took so long...
Huh?
What's going on here?
Dunno.
Naoe-kun, was it?
This has nothing to do with you.
You have no proof.
Judging her solely by your impression of her is going too far,
both as a disciplinary committee member and as a human being!
She's guilty of repeatedly
skipping classes and being late!
Of course she's lying!
Even if she's telling the truth,
winning a roulette in a vending machine is unfair to those who actually pay!
She shouldn't have played it!
Exactly! Why should this slacker deserve to get all that for free?
If you're saying that that's the problem...
Then you'll leave her alone if you get payment for those cans, right?
I need 300 more...
Don't you two have any?
I don't know what this is all about, but...
Riki says he needs it, so he needs it.
Come on now.
That's a total of three hundred and twenty...
I'll pay you back later!
Sure.
That's enough!
That's enough?
Let's go, it's time to go on patrol!
Excuse me...
Stop dawdling around!
We'll leave her punishment for the next time she causes trouble.
Well, geez...
What if everything I said was a lie?
You're not a liar, Saigusa-san.
You do play tricks sometimes, though.
Wow, you're so gullible.
You're such a softy.
What?
I still don't get what's going on.
What's up with Saigusa?
You see, Saigusa-san wanted...
Haru-chan wanted?
...to join the Little Busters!
Are you serious?
Yay! Another new member!
Hooray!
It's not my fault if something crazy happens!
Alright, let's have another membership test.
Saigusa, what do you feel with that mitt on your hand?
Mmmm! The scent of youth!
Perfect! You pass!
From today on, you're one of the Little Busters!
Hooray! Yay!
Well, fine by me.
If someone stupider than me joins, I'll look better than more of you.
Don't call her stupid, Trash.
What?! You're still calling me that?!
What if we called you Retard instead?
Huh?
Retard! Retard! Retard!
I'm serious! Who's the retard here?!
Stop it!
Anything but that!
Episode 7
Now Then, Guess Who!
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
Wafu!
I'm looking for a roommate!
What?! Riki's going to be Kud-o's roommate?!
Um, you know, I'm a guy...
It's a mission, start time!