Alright, I can do it!
It's great that you can,
but you'll run into something like that.
Sorry about that.
Are you okay?
Don't worry.
I wasn't looking where I was going.
I'm sorry.
This is Kud, a girl who transferred here this spring.
Good morning, everyone.
Have a nice day.
Come on...
See you again.
He said good-bye!
I was just kidding!
Because I'm just... I'm just...
...someone who got a "Try harder next time, good-bye girl!" on an English quiz!
That's right...
That's right!
That's... that's... that's...
A one-man Doppler effect?
Um...
Can I speak Japanese?
I know you can speak Japanese.
You don't have to force yourself to speak English.
But see! You understood, right?
Yeah, I did.
I'm...
Um...
You can just speak Japanese.
I-I know I can, but as you know, I lied a little when I first introduced myself here.
Like how I said I didn't know much about Japan because I was living overseas.
I really was overseas, but...
Where were you taking these?
My room in the girls' dorm.
But I don't want to trouble you!
The girls' dorm, right?
Th-Thank you very much!
Are they heavy?
Not at all.
They're lighter than I thought.
My clothes are inside.
My grandpa sent them here from Finland.
Alright.
Thank you so much!
If you ever need help again, just ask.
Thank you!
Naoe-san!
Thank you so much for helping!
I almost forgot!
Good, good.
Meow, meow.
Rin, here.
Took you long enough.
What were you doing?
Nothing much...
Lennon?
No letter today either?
Letter?
Oh, you mean a task?
I was hoping for a task so he'd tell us the secret of the world.
The secret of the world, huh?
I wonder what amazing secret he has to tell us.
Huh?
Fabre, what happened to you?
You hurt your paw...
I never noticed.
Who put this bandage on you?
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
What the hell?!
Inohara    Masato
This! This! And these!
Inohara      Masato
Inohara     Masato
How'd my name turn into "Inohara-star-Masato"?!
Who did this?!
Me!
So you're the culprit, Sarcastic Maracas?
It's Saigusa Haruka!
You little...
You come here from some other class to hang out, and now this?!
Masato, were you taking a nap just now?
Huh? How'd you know?
I thought so.
He was sleeping so peacefully, his face was just begging for me to draw on it!
Riki.
I've figured out who took care of Fabre's paw.
Komari-chan gave this to me!
Kamikita-san did?
It certainly looks like something she would use.
Tell her I said thanks.
Ko-Ko...
Tell Komari-san?
Yeah.
Why don't you tell her yourself?
I wouldn't be asking you if I could.
How long are you going to avoid her?
She's part of the Little Busters now, you know?
Give these to her for me as thanks.
Okay?
Good grief.
Boy,
Komari-kun went somewhere with a bag of snacks just now.
Kurugaya-san?
Thanks!
She's just so carefree.
I wonder what she's dreaming about.
I'm sure it's a happy dream.
Onii-cha—
Na-Naoe-ku—
I smacked both sides...
Are you okay?
Not really...
What about you?
I'm, uh... I'm fine.
But why did you headbutt me when I woke up?
Well, um...
You were drooling...
How embarrassing!
I've been embarrassed by Naoe-kun!
No, I didn't do anything...
Though, you were talking in your sleep.
I was?!
You didn't hear anything.
Okay?
O-Okay.
I was never heard. Yup.
All problems solved!
Oh, why don't I call you "Riki-kun" from now on?
You can call me "Komari" too.
I guess I'll go with "Komari-san", then.
Riki-kun, do you want some snacks?
Plain scones and the sweetest apricot jam.
Have some with this afternoon tea.
Oh, right, Komari-san.
You took care of Fabre's paw, right?
Fabre?
Yup! The cat, right?
I love cats!
Rin asked me to give these to you as thanks.
They're from Rin-chan?
I'll save these for tomorrow.
I'll invite Rin-chan here and eat them with her!
Invite Rin here?
As a thank-you.
A thanks for a thanks?
If I can make Rin-chan a little happier by having snacks with her right here, I'll be happy too!
If you make someone happy, you'll be happy too.
Komari-san's happiness spiral theory.
So, Komari-san, you have an older brother?
You really did hear me talking in my sleep!
Don't worry, that's all I heard.
But you see...
I'm an only child.
I don't have a brother.
But I always see him in my dreams.
An older brother existing only in my dreams.
Only in your dreams?
He always reads a picture book to me with a warm voice like the sun.
A picture book with eggs and chicks.
The story is a little sad.
A sad story?
I don't remember what the story was about.
I always forget whenever I wake up.
That's why I always feel a little lonely when I wake up.
It was the first time I saw a little loneliness in Komari-san's smile.
Can I help me?
A picture book with eggs and chicks?
I want to see if I can find it.
Komari-san might've actually read one when she was younger.
I think she'll be really happy if I can tell her what kind of story it was.
I see.
You're joining me on the roof today, Rin.
Stop.
Komari-san's really looking forward to this.
Do you want to disappoint her?
Only for a bit, okay?
Huh?
Riki-kun.
Rin-chan.
What's wrong?
You're giving off some kind of sad aura.
Yeah. I'm kind of sad.
I went back home yesterday afternoon.
I thought I might find that picture book I used to read.
And I did,
inside our storage shed.
Isn't this...
It's cute.
I like chicks.
One day, an egg became a chick.
The chick became a hen,
and laid an egg.
After taking three steps, the hen forgot that it was once an egg,
One day, that egg became a chick.
The chick became a hen,
and the hen forgot everything...
and laid an egg.
The story's back to where it started.
They keep forgetting.
And it just repeats, over and over.
It made me feel really sad.
But the hen remembers again at the end.
"I was once an egg."
Yeah.
I think...
Onii-chan drew this picture book.
Kamikita Takuya
Kamikita Takuya?
You mean you really had a brother?
Maybe you have another relative with that name?
No.
I asked my mom, but she said that there wasn't anyone with that name.
But I know.
I know my mom is lying about something.
I think it's something I can't ask about.
Did he run away from home?
But if he did, why don't I remember anything about him?
Why is he only in my dreams?
He might be somewhere out there.
My brother.
I want to meet him.
Meow!
Meow, meow, meow!
Meow, meow!
I think Rin's saying, "I hope you can meet him one day."
Me-Meow.
Thank you!
Do you have any plans on Sunday?
Wanna go to a retirement home with me?
Let's go!
What're you doing, Riki?
It's Sunday.
I'm going to a retirement home with Komari-san.
Huh? To do what?
I don't really know,
but Komari-san goes there a lot.
Hold on a sec.
What the heck?
So we can't play together today?!
You just smashed my plans to have a happy fun time with you!
How could you do this to me, man?!
What's up?
Looks fun.
Does it look like I'm having fun—
No, it doesn't.
The girls' softball team is using the field.
I thought maybe we could have some fun together.
And so...
Everyone else is coming too.
Why're you here?
I was feeling a little too bored, you see.
But so long as it's with two beautiful, young girls,
it would be my pleasure to go to any strange place!
We're going to a retirement home, you know.
So?
What do you want us to do at this retirement home?
We'll make a happy, sunny place.
We'll talk to the residents and help clean their rooms.
I think a lot of them feel really lonely.
If everyone's really happy and the place is full of smiles, it'll be really warm and sunny!
In other words, community service?
It's my first time doing community service.
I'm getting pumped up!
Really?
Hello everyone!
Oh, it's Komari-chan!
Komari-chan!
Welcome back!
Granny, did your cold get better?
Slowly but steadily.
Thanks for the cough drops.
That's great! I'll bring some more next time!
Let's have a nice conversation when you do!
Talking with you is always a delight, Komari-chan!
She's really popular!
Komari-kun's idol aura is at full strength!
Here!
This is the scarf my dear wife had knit me!
Thank you! Thank you, Komari-chan!
What a beautiful sight!
I'm moved beyond words!
Alright, our job is to go around cleaning the rooms and talking to the residents here!
Talking?!
Can we really do this?
I can't think of any shared topics of interest.
Nothing to talk about.
Alright!
What do you mean, "alright"?
Optimism magic!
When you're feeling down, you say it out loud and follow it with an "alright"!
See, everything negative gets flipped positive!
Alright!
Alright.
Alright...
Aww yeah!
Alright.
That was perfect!
Let's get started then!
Hi!
Would you like some muscle today?
I'll take one order of muscle then.
Coming right up.
He just went with the flow...
Elderly wisdom is quite something...
Komari-san spreads happy, sunny places wherever she goes.
Is Komari-san's brother still around somewhere?
Or is he...
I didn't want to think about that possibility.
I don't ever want to see Komari-san sad.
What the hell do you want?!
Don't enter without permission!
I did knock, sir.
This room doesn't need any cleaning!
What?!
There's stuff all over the floor!
That's none of your business!
Do you have to scream so much?!
I may be thin and withered, but I am not so senile as to ask something of a kid!
I'm doing it whether you ask me or not.
I'm telling you I don't need your help.
But it feels better to have a clean room, doesn't it, gramps?
I'm not gramps, I'm Kojiro!
In that case, Kojiro-san, I'll feel better when your room is clean.
What's with that self-centered way of thinking?
I'm borrowing one of my friends' theories.
Feel free to clean, then.
Just keep it quick.
Of course!
You're a weird kid.
Not nearly as weird as you, Kojiro-san.
Muscles, aww yeah!
Flip over the tatami and what do you find?
It's Paris!
Beautiful!
Komari-chan!
Hmph.
I think that feels a lot better.
It'll be back to the way it was soon enough.
Come back to clean again sometime, kid.
You can bet I will.
Huh? Did you just come out of that room?
Yeah.
You're amazing!
I've come here so many times, but I've never been able to meet the grandpa in that room.
I simply put what you told me into action.
Huh?
Alright!
Hel—
Hey!
Get the hell outta here!
What are you doing?
What did Komari-san ever do to you?
Is something wrong?
Komari...
Is that the girl's name?
She's really grown up.
Do you know her?
Don't let her come near me.
Um...
I said, don't let her come near me again.
Why not?
Because my name...
...is Kamikita Kojirou.
That's why.
Kamikita...
Kamikita Takuya
Episode 4
We'll Make a Happy, Sunny Place
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
Hey, Riki-kun, let's go see the stars!
We're going to the rooftop at night...
Come on, let's go!
...to find a shooting star.
Mission, start!