Crap, that's the second bell.
We're not going to make it!
Damn it! Whose fault is it this time?!
It's yours!
And now we're all late!
Geez!
You're all in the same class, so get Rin in there first to get yourselves excused!
Just Rin? How?
Throw her to the third floor!
It'll be easy enough if Kengo and Masato work together!
No way...
Shouldn't be a problem with Rin's reflexes.
Why do I have to work with this loser?
Same to you!
Come on! We're out of time!
We have no choice.
This is too dangerous for you.
Wait here.
Mission, start!
Hey, nice lift, man!
Yeah!
Mission complete!
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
But seriously, Rin must have hit a record altitude!
My muscles are awesome.
What's that about awesome, Retard?!
I'll throw gentler next time...
There won't be a next time!
Nice catch!
Wafuu!
Kud!
Naoe-san!
And, um, Rin-san and Inohara-san.
You can call me Muscles-san, too.
Wafu, wafu!
Weren't these dogs...
...the ones the Disciplinary Committee uses?
Let me introduce you!
This is Strelka,
and this is Belka.
They're helping the Disciplinary Committee with their patrols.
They're my grandpa's dogs.
He sent them here from Finland so I wouldn't be lonely.
Oh?
That's nice of him.
Strelka is a girl.
Coincidentally, I'm a girl too.
I think we knew that.
So I'm Strelka and Belka's big sister!
Big sister?
I've been taking care of them since they were this little.
They were naughty little rascals back then.
They're dogs, but they're even smarter than me now.
The fact that you admit that is, uh...
They want to play more!
Try throwing this.
Okay! Go fetch!
Wafu!
Did you see that?
The way she moved...
I caught it this time!
We could use her on our team!
Oh? Noumi Kudryavka-kun, is it?
You transferred here recently after moving back to Japan, right?
Yes, but... um...
What am I doing here?
Sorry, Kud.
We'd like you to join us.
Do you want to play baseball with us?
We need more people on our team.
Baseball?
What's that?
You don't know baseball?
It's no surprise.
They don't care for baseball in the country that Noumi-kun lived in.
It's something like "baseball" in English.
Oh! Baseball!
I've heard of that!
The name of our team is Little Busters.
It'll be a lot of fun if you join!
Really?
And you'll get some muscles on you if you play, too.
But...
I don't know anything about baseball.
That's okay.
I don't know anything about it either.
I have no clue what I'm doing!
These two make a good case for it.
Either way, how about giving it a try, Noumi?
Okay!
So I catch the ball with this?
That's right.
Just catch it like you did with the frisbee earlier.
Okay.
Now then, Noumi. Get out there.
Roger!
Should we try with her a bit farther away, Kyousuke?
Yeah, you're right.
A bit farther back and to my right!
Roger!
Um... Naoe-san!
Did my "Roger" just now sound native?
Huh?
Uh... Yeah, maybe.
Wafuu!
Man, she's like a little dog...
Yeah.
All right! Let's get started!
Wow, she's amazing!
Didn't expect that...
She's good!
It seems we've found a diamond in the rough.
Kud, you're in!
Really?
Yeah.
Starting today, Noumi Kudryavka is a member of the Little Busters.
Yay! Good job!
Congratulations!
Friends...
My first friends since coming to this school...
I don't know what to say...
I hope we can be the best of friends!
You got it, Kud-o!
I'm very happy to have another cute girl on our team.
I'm gonna spin you all day long!
Spin, spin, spin!
Hey, stop. Her head's spinning.
Noumi-san!
Oh, it's the Resident Assistant!
You have another package!
Could you sign for it?
Okay!
It must be another package from Grandpa.
I'll be going now!
Need any help?
No, I'll be fine!
Girls' Dorm
I knew it.
She's not fine at all.
Yeah.
Let us help you with that, Kud-o.
Th-Thank you!
May I help you?
No, um, that's what we're supposed to say.
Um...
In this case, it's...
Help me!
That makes us sound like dangerous people.
Th-That was wrong?
Help you?
So we're being helped?
Um...
You're taking these to your room, right?
Th-Thank you very much.
But, um... Boys can't come into the girls' dorm.
I heard recently that the Disciplinary Committee posts guards around it...
Alright! Leave this to me!
O-Okay.
Thank you very much!
So this is your room?
You have some sophisticated tastes.
My grandpa loves Japan.
He sends a lot of things to help me blend in with Japanese culture.
Are you staying alone in this room?
Yes. I don't have a roommate.
It's...
a bit lonely.
You two are roommates, right?
Yeah. You can call us musclemates, too.
No idea what musclemates are, but we are roommates.
How did you become roommates?
We submitted a request, and they granted it.
We've known each other since we were kids,
so the RA probably took that into consideration.
Friends from childhood?
Being good friends is a very good thing.
What's wrong?
When I was little, I moved from country to country, so I've never known anyone for that long.
And... I have a hard time making friends.
Come on. Say something.
Do you want a roommate, Kud?
Yes.
I hope I can find one.
I don't like being alone.
Oh, really?
Sounds like you get lonely easily.
That's not...
completely true...
or completely false...
So basically, you need someone in your room to be on muscles duty.
That's an interesting "duty"...
How about Riki?
He might not look it, but he's got some good muscles under those clothes.
He'll be an amazing muscles dutyman in the future.
Naoe-san? Really?!
Um...
Well, um...
You wouldn't feel lonely with Riki here, right?
Huh?
But wouldn't that mean I'd be alone?
No!
Riki!
Then it'd be like you didn't like me anymore!
Don't cry just from imagining it...
My heart is as naive as toilet paper.
Please keep that in mind.
Maybe you should train that instead of your muscles.
Wafu!
Roommates are as wonderful as I thought!
Why don't you ask the RA about it, Kud?
The RA?
I'll go ask now!
Okay.
I'll sign off on the search and the move.
Really?
But the new term just started.
It'll be hard finding someone who wants to change rooms.
I see...
Anyway, I'll put a memo on the billboard for you about looking for a roommate.
I'll send something out on the mailing list about it too.
But if no one responds, we'll end the search there.
Is that okay with you?
Yes!
You okay?
I'm kind of excited.
I hope you can find someone.
Yes. We'll be together for a long time.
But now that that's over, you boys had better go back to your dorm.
If the Disciplinary Committee finds you, they'll kill you.
It seems it's always you people causing trouble.
But this is quite a blatant infraction right here.
I'm sorry.
Naoe-san and Inohara-san came here to help me—
Regardless of the reason, boys are not allowed in the girls' dorm.
You will be punished.
All three of you will be writing formal apologies.
Now come with me.
Yes, ma'am...
Pick up the pace!
Damn it, it's like her blood ain't red!
Futaki Kanata, the Ice Queen of the Disciplinary Committee?
Yeah.
Her and the counselor held us for an hour after that to wring us out,
threaten us,
Rules
and lecture us!
I'm very sorry about that.
It's not your fault.
Hey now, Kud-o.
Your tiny body'll get tinier if you're down.
Well, speak of the devil.
We're waiting on approval from the student council's executive committee for that.
You know what that means.
We're cracking down extra hard on rule-breakers this month.
That was so scary!
Yes...
Don't worry about it.
More importantly, about Noumi's search for a roommate—
Hey, hey, Kud-o! I saw your ad in the mailing list!
I'm in a triple, so I'm full up!
It's too bad!
I would spin you around three times a day if we were roommates!
Y-Yes...
Komari, don't you have a roommate too?
I do. Sorry, Kuu-chan...
That's okay.
What about you, Rin?
You don't have a roommate, right?
Really?
Rin, how about it?
Sorry!
When is she going to get over her shyness?
She doesn't like me...
No, Kuu-chan!
It's not you, Kud.
Rin's like that with everyone.
Oh, that's right!
We have another girl without a roommate!
Oh, right! Kurugaya-san!
It looks like she's skipping class today too.
Oh?
You want to be my roommate, Kudryavka-kun?
We heard that there were a lot of people who wanted to be your roommate,
but you turned them all down.
Being alone is easier for me.
But Kud shouldn't bother you.
Une Vie
Maunpassant
Oh, do you feel lonely, little girl?
I'll welcome you with open arms any time, any day.
Ah, so cute.
Kurugaya-san, I think Kud's suffocating.
Oh dear. It seems I've gone too far.
Ah, hugging Kudryavka-kun at a 45-degree angle feels best.
Are you okay with that, Little Miss Noumi?
Wafu...
Come with me.
Are you trying to kill me painfully, boy?
Being roommates means that she'd be sleeping right next to me at night.
What am I supposed to do?
Wh-What do you mean—
Just imagine her sitting on her bed in her pajamas after a shower.
I'd get on top of her without a second thought.
You can't do that!
It's too dangerous.
She's too dangerous to be Kud's roommate!
Sorry, let's ask someone else.
Yes. Please do so.
Um...
Why?
I guess I'd just bother Kurugaya-san if we were roommates.
No, that's not it...
Kurugaya-san is so well-proportioned, tall, smart, good at English,
has such big breasts, and acts so grown-up.
Meanwhile, I'm poorly proportioned, short, stupid, bad at English,
don't have any breasts, and act like such a kid.
We're just too different.
Now I feel really sad after saying that.
Th-That's not true, Kud!
Um, er... Well...
Oh, it's Nishizono-san.
Nishizono-san?
She's in our class.
You don't know her yet?
Um...
Well, I guess she doesn't have much of a presence.
I've never seen her talk with anyone.
She might not have a roommate either.
Why don't you try asking her? Just take a chance.
But...
It's kind of hard to approach her.
Did you need something?
Um...
If you don't mind us asking, do you have a roommate?
No, I don't.
I'm looking for a roommate.
If you wouldn't mind...
I have a lot of things.
Mostly books.
What kind of books?
I read anything, so it's a chaotic mix,
but I recently finished a book on Fermat's Last Theorem.
It was very interesting.
But maybe it wasn't interesting.
Which direction does your room face?
Um...
It faces south.
I had an avalanche recently.
An avalanche?
My books fell, all at once.
You wouldn't have been able to escape.
You would have been stranded in the dorm.
W-Wafu...
That's a lot of books...
I think I would just be a bother after all.
I'm sorry, but I must respectfully decline.
I thought so...
I see.
So you couldn't find a roommate for Noumi.
Today's the deadline for it too...
The RA came by to tell me a minute ago.
Apparently, no one asked about being my roommate.
Cheer up, Kud.
Yeah! It might be nice being alone!
Yes...
I'm already unbelievably happy to be part of the Little Busters.
A roommate would be asking for too much.
It might be better this way.
So no one volunteered to be Kud's roommate?
No surprise there. Her room's all weird.
She's a funny little foreigner, after all.
Just gotta laugh.
Why I oughta...
You there.
You're not allowed to take that magazine from the library.
Go return it immediately.
Yes, ma'am! We're sorry!
And you, Noumi-san.
Y-Yes?
It seems you haven't found a roommate yet.
Y-Yes...
I'll put a request in to the RA later today.
I don't have a roommate either.
My room is too big, so there's some space.
You can move into my room.
You'll...
be my roommate?
It's not like you have anyone else.
You move tomorrow. Be quick about it.
Okay?
Now then.
Strelka, Belka, we're going on our evening patrol.
Go on, go on.
Hey, what's this?
Why the head of the Disciplinary Committee of all people?
Kud, if you don't want her, you can turn her down.
No...
Thanks to all of you, I've finally found a roommate!
Thank you very much!
Episode 8
Let's Looking for Roommates!
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
This is bad!
None of the lunch ladies are here today!
Let's cover the kitchen for them!
Rin
No Subject
What should I do?
Cut! Cut! Pork cutlet!
And jelly!
It's time for Muscles-chan here!
Mission, start!