It's been getting pretty hot lately, hasn't it?
There, there!
Never mind summer, we haven't even had the rainy season yet...
My heart is always hot.
7 School Horrors
Did you come up with another crazy idea?
Kengo, what you need is a free spirit.
A taut string can easily be cut by one swing of a blade.
However, cutting a loose string that sways with the wind is next to impossible.
What are you trying to say?
I've thought of a lighthearted activity to pass the time.
What do you have in mind?
A test of courage!
It's not the season for that...
It'll be fun!
You're in this too.
No! I'll get killed!
No one's going to kill you...
Actually, you do get killed in one ghost story I've heard.
If you knock two doors to the right of the second floor girls' bathroom at night, you'll hear a voice...
"Would you like to wear a red gown?"
"Would you like to wear a blue gown?"
"Would you like to wear a yellow gown?"
If you answer red...
you'll be covered in your own blood!
If you answer blue...
your blood'll be gone and your body blue!
Wh-What about yellow?
Yellow?
You'll be forced to eat so many bananas, your body will turn yellow!
Like that could happen!
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Sign: First-Ever Little Busters Test of Courage: See, There Ain't No Ghosts
The First-Ever Little Busters Test of Courage: See, There Ain't No Ghosts!
Applause!
What's a test of courage?
Well Kuu-chan, it's that thing...
You take a pen and stab it between your fingers!
Wait, are we doing that?!
Are we?
No, we aren't.
I've hidden talismans on each floor of the building. Each team will find four.
This is the finish line.
It's like a real test!
We'll start by picking teams.
Me and Riki got split up!
Just leave it to me.
Anego!
Alright, first will be Rin's team.
I'm going back.
Let's do it!
Yay!
It's dark...
I'm not scared... I'm not scared...
Call me for helper!
There's nothing to be scared of with Belka and Strelka around!
Now then, let us go, Takumi no Kami!
They're not following us!
Maybe the Disciplinary Committee trained them not to come into the building?
Oh, right...
Well, good night, Belka, Strelka.
What do we do?
I'm scared!
Leave it to me!
Cats!
Unlike the dogs, they're not trained!
Hey guys!
They all left...
Komari-chan...
Let's just go.
Aren't you scared?
Nope.
As long as you're with me, I won't be scared.
And since I'm not scared, you two won't be scared, right?
Yes!
But I'm scared...
I'm scared too, then!
I-I-It's okay!
I'm here!
It's about time for the next team to go.
Okay.
Hey Riki, why don't you come with us?
We'll skip along shoulder-to-shoulder!
That'd make me feel like an alien being taken to the authorities...
Shall we go then?
Let's go!
Science Room
This is our first stop.
I'm scared...
Me too...
You two stay here.
I'll take a look.
We don't know what my stupid brother might have set up.
Alright!
I'll go!
I'm sure it'll be okay!
You're so cool, Komari-san!
Here I go!
Do you see anything?
No...
Komari-san?
Komari-chan died!
That "hiiya" scream just now kind of sounded like "fear"!
It was a joke, right?
Don't die! Wake up!
You still have a chance! Don't give up!
Sounds like one of them's down for the count.
The first talisman is in Kyousuke's classroom.
Where are you going?
Kyousuke's classroom.
It's this way.
This way's faster.
Oh, really?
Out of my way!
So lame...
Why do my cheeks hurt?
A cheek demon attacked you.
Demon?!
And a forehead monster too.
Scary!
A yellow gown!
I knew this way would be—
Yellow!
This sure is fun!
You guys seem fine.
Are you disappointed we aren't screaming and jumping into your arms?
Not really...
Alright, let's go.
What's with this cursed melody?
It's an old cassette player.
Fine Arts Room
What's with that piercing glare?
They're shiny one-yen coins.
Here they are!
Blood?
A severed hand!
That reminds me... Wasn't there some story about severed-hand ramen a while back?
A glove and ketchup?
Alright, let's fill it with seaweed and lower it so it touches your neck as you pass.
The last one's in the science room.
Yui-nee sure is reliable!
Yep.
Boy, you can lead the way from here on.
I think I'll just watch you two getting scared out of your wits from behind.
That's not fair, Anego!
Um...
Couldn't we go a little slower?
You were fine just a second ago.
Well, when I'm behind Yui-nee, it's like we could even take on the President!
I get scared like anyone else.
You look okay, though...
Well, I'm scared too.
Yeah, it's scary, right?
What?!
I just got the shivers!
Was that just wind?
Really? That gave me a fright...
Well...
I think it'd be better if—
Huh?
Where'd Yui-nee go?
Fine Arts Room
L-Let's search...
Be careful!
That was Rin's team!
It sounded close.
Komari-chan! Komari-chan!
Don't die! Live!
There's no response.
It's just a corpse.
That's Komarimax for you.
She's completely out.
What was that for?!
Wh-What do we do?
Well, let's see...
Flap.
Anego!
What are you doing?!
It's fine.
We're both girls, and there's plenty to go around.
That's not the problem here...
Okay, fine.
Komari-chan!
She's back!
That's a sexy way to wake her up.
You disappeared on us for this?
I thought it would be more fun to be on the scaring side.
How many talismans did you find?
Three.
Wow! That's a lot!
Wafu!
Kud!
Wait, you guys!
Wafu!
Just keep go straight!
Spin, spin, spin...
Is she okay?
Yeah. My muscles cushioned her fall.
You two stay here.
Take care of Kud-o.
You too?
Yeah.
That feeling. They've been watching us.
Principal
Kud. Kud!
Naoe-san?
It's horrible!
What's wrong?
It's not "no ghosts", it's "yes ghosts"! They're here!
Doesn't look like anything's here.
Hey, what now?
It won't open.
Huh?! Yeah, right.
What the hell?
Hey, Riki, that you?
Yes ghosts?
I don't know...
Masato and Kengo!
The number you have dialed is temporarily not available.
I'm not getting through.
Naoe-san...
Don't worry.
Okay.
This isn't something Kyousuke would do.
I made sure to hang a few basins in case anyone tried to escape.
Now this is something you would do.
Quit it!
Sorry.
Message Received
Riki
Emergency
Message Received
Riki
Emergency
Message Received
Riki
Emergency
Think your muscles can beat mine?
"Yes ghosts"?
Kud says she senses something.
What's wrong?
Well...
The test of courage is cancelled.
We're going to go ghost busting!
Sign: Ghost Busting
Ghosts?!
Another offbeat idea.
It's hard to believe, but we can't just leave them be.
Riki, help me out here.
Okay.
I'll go too!
Rin?
Me too!
If I'm with Rin-chan, I'll be okay!
Can we count on you?
I can't possibly refuse.
I shall assist ye!
Wafu!
Alright!
Mission, start!
None on the first floor. Over.
Roger. Over.
No response.
Second floor!
Let's flank it!
Masato!
Was that it?!
Did we lose it?
Can we really stop that thing?
Natsume-san! I've called in some help!
A-ha!
Why me?
Good job!
Wafu!
Nishizono, how do you catch a ghost?
Let sleeping dogs lie.
We've already invoked its wrath.
Do they have any weaknesses?
Yes.
Spirits and the like tend to be weak against powerful energy sources.
It may try to avoid loud noises and briht lights.
This is getting crazy.
I'm excited.
What about you?
Let's go!
Third floor. No signs of it.
Don't let down your guard.
The cats are scared.
Be on your toes. It's close by.
I'll protect you, Nishizono-san!
There!
West stairs!
It's coming this way!
Demon begone!
Begone! Begone! Begone!
Rin-kun, Komari-kun.
Okay!
Here it comes, Rin-chan!
Mister Ogre, over here!
Komari-chan, don't call it!
Oh, right!
It's heading your way!
Riki.
A bird?
It's huge!
Look at it glisten.
Why'd you fill it with seaweed?!
Kyousuke?
It's alright.
Holy crap, it's Tweety!
Tweety?
Yeah.
When I came back from Hokkaido one time, a young eagle followed me back.
I named him Tweety and loved him very much.
Oh, yeah! We used to play with him!
He didn't like me at all.
But we couldn't keep an eagle as a pet at home.
Though it broke my heart, I sent Tweety back to Hokkaido.
Did he come down here to see you?
Yeah.
Thanks for coming.
Tweety!
Tweety, come visit me again someday.
So it was all Mister Kyousuke's fault.
What's wrong with you?!
It's a good thing it wasn't a ghost.
Mission complete!
That was a pretty hot night.
Oh? We're the last ones back?
Oh, hey. Where the heck were you guys?
Like you need to ask.
We got held up by your trap in the Principal's Office.
Man, that one was good.
What are you looking all pale for?
I didn't set any traps there...
Then what's this?
You might want to burn it.
Episode 11
See, There Ain't No Ghosts
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
Nishizono-san is always looking at the sky with such distant eyes.
Are you going to invite Nishizono to join the Little Busters?
Yeah.
To be friends with us.
Mission, start!