Alright!
Take this!
You're mine!
Now that we've found more members,
the Little Busters seems even more like a baseball team.
I'm sorry...
Leave it to me, Kudryavka-kun!
We've got this!
Home run!
What the heck are you doing, Cuckoogayer?!
That was your own fault.
What was that?!
Show some respect for Muscles!
This really is the best.
You're what I can't respect.
But fun times like this can't go on forever.
Kyousuke will graduate in less than a year.
It won't be long before we all go our separate ways.
Strike!
I did it!
That's your first strike ever, Rin.
You can call me the Fastball King from now on!
Hey! Fastball King!
I wonder why...
At that very moment,
I recalled that mysterious letter.
There is a secret
in this world.
If you wish
to know it,
then clear
all the tasks
I give you.
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Baseball
Team
Yay!
Komari-chan's homemade chocolate cookies!
Down the hatch!
Wafu!
Thank you very much!
Hey, Rin-chan, why don't you eat with us?
They're delicious!
Baseball
Team
Bye.
Baseball
Team
But they're so good...
That's too bad.
It seems there's still no cure for Rin-kun's shyness.
Rin, what about the other girls?
Baseball
Team
Shut up!
Why do you guys have whiskers?
Are whiskers that handy?
Don't they get in the way?
Like when you're drinking milk.
Boing, boing.
Boing. Boing!
Oh no!
Stick back on! Stick back!
It won't...
What now?
Should I get hair tonic?
Is that something I should ask a cat?
Another fell out?!
Or... are you just shedding?
Oh, okay...
It's Riki!
Hey, Rin, why don't you try getting closer to the girls?
I've told you this plenty of times.
Masato, Kengo, and I can't hang around with you forever.
When we all graduate, you'll...
Mind your own beeswax.
Hey! Don't!
Quit it!
Huh?
Riki!
Lennon brought another letter!
It's been a while!
A letter?
Those mysterious letters.
If we clear all the tasks, they said they'd tell us the secret of the world.
We have a second task here.
What is it?
"Save the cafeteria."
Save the cafeteria?
Is there a problem with the cafeteria or something?
I know!
The croquette soba is super disgusting.
It's a big problem.
Isn't that a matter of taste?
The cafeteria will be saved if the croquette soba is taken off the menu.
Really?
Then are there any other problems?
Why don't we ask the cafeteria ladies?
Excuse me...
Have there been any problems with the cafeteria lately?
Problems, huh?
Like any trouble or anything.
No, not really.
You all eat everything we make.
We're always happy about that.
But the croquette soba is disgusting!
We put that on the menu because some students requested it.
They serve them at some street stalls.
The croquettes get all mushy from the soup.
Mushy croquettes are super disgusting!
Oh my.
Natsume Rin.
It seems you don't understand.
Those who do can't live without it!
Slurping a croquette soaked mushy in soup!
You! Sasasasasa Sasami!
It's Sasasegawa Sasami!
The sparkling ace of the softball team, and...
...the most beautiful girl in school!
Viva, croquette soba!
So the person who requested croquette soba was...
Me.
Is there a problem?
It should be taken off the menu immediately!
Even though you like your tempura soba?
I saw you last week.
You were slurping up totally mushy tempura in soup.
Tempura tastes good when it's mushy!
It's not the same with croquettes!
You insolent rogue!
I will not simply stand back while you insult the mushy croquettes I love so much!
Um... Excuse me...
Silence, outfielder!
I'm a catcher...
Girls! You know what to do!
Like this?!
Ow! Take this!
What now?
How can you be so useless?!
I'll handle this myself!
Ow!
Take this!
Now we know who's right!
Viva, croquette soba!
Damn it...
So how are we supposed to save the cafeteria?
No idea...
Besides, we don't even know if there's a
meaning to those letters in the first place.
We don't know who's writing them, either.
But if we clear all the tasks, they'll tell us the secret of the world!
I wonder what the secret of the world is...
Rin was set on doing it until she learned the secret.
The same way she would keep buying snacks until she won a free one.
The way she did when she was young.
But what kind of secret could this world have?
All there is here is an unchanging everyday life.
But...
If I had to name something that made me uneasy, it would be...
Narcolepsy.
I don't know when I might fall asleep.
Without any warning.
Riki, this is bad!
Listen, it's really bad!
Okay.
I was shocked, too.
It gave me the shivers!
Okay, just tell me.
Listen, it's really bad!
I'm listening as hard as I can!
None of the cafeteria ladies are there.
Man, I'm hungry.
Wake up already!
Hurry and come with me!
Look.
The cafeteria ladies usually start preparing dinner around now,
but none of them are there.
None of them?
Why?
There was one until a few minutes ago.
But she suddenly felt dizzy and went to the hospital.
The other ladies had emergencies, so they left early.
And there were already two out sick today, too.
All of them had to leave?
Is that even possible?
Either way, there isn't anyone here to make dinner!
Spaghetti
Omelette
combo Meal
Cutlet and Rice Meal
Fillet Cutlet Meal
Pork Cutlet Meal
Minced Cutlet Meal
Grilled Salmon Meal
Grilled Mackerel Meal
Grilled Pike Meal
Utensils
But that means...
Where am I gonna get dinner?!
My stomach's howling like a wild animal here!
We'll make it.
Return Trays Here
For the whole school!
We're saving the cafeteria!
We're out of time!
If we don't start now, we won't make it in time!
Help me!
I can't do it alone!
But...
There's a massive number of students in this school.
It's impossible for just the three of us to handle.
Once upon a time, there was a penguin.
It's so cute!
Komari-chan! I have a favor to ask!
It's an emergency!
Okay?
Please!
Oh?
You came all the way out here to ask for my help?
It must be quite a crisis.
I see.
I understand the situation.
Making dinner for every student in the school will be no easy feat.
But it seems you intend to do it.
Yeah.
This has to be the first time you've ever pulled everyone together.
But it's strange...
Lennon's letter predicted that the cafeteria would have a problem like this.
How did the writer know that this would happen?
What's wrong, Riki?
Oh. Nothing.
What are you going to do for this mission?
I'm going to see it through with Rin, of course.
Alright.
Then let's put our heads together for this.
Mis—
Mission, start!
Let's make a lot of yummy things!
This is so exciting!
Now that I've seen pretty girls in aprons, I'm ready to do anything.
My, Anego, you look quite sexy as well.
I'd do anything to have a wife like you making dinner for me!
Really?
So what do we do first?
First...
Let's see...
Make some rice!
Shouldn't we figure out what we're serving first?
Is that how it works?
I think.
The menu is right here!
Pork cutlet meal, fillet cutlet meal, cutlet and rice meal,
combo meal, meat and vegetable cutlet meal...
We have to make all this?
Impossible.
We can't do that...
What should we do, Rin?
Give me a minute!
Rin
No Subject
What should I do?
Um...
Rin
None
Why not just pick
three things to serve?
Okay, listen!
Why not just pick three things to serve?
That's a pretty normal idea to get excited about.
It sounds like you were reading something.
And why was it in the form of a question?
Well, it is an emergency.
We'll have to make do with three dishes.
Hey look!
I found something nice!
Wow, shrimp!
Okay, how about fried shrimp?
No, it's gotta be cutlet!
Then how about fried shrimp and some cutlet for a combo dish?
Add some julienned cabbage, apple slices, and a bowl of miso,
and you've got a combo meal.
I see. That's a good idea.
How about a rice ball meal, too?
We can put omelette on the side!
I can make omelette!
Um...
Actually, omelette is my specialty.
My grandpa told me to learn how to make Japanese-style omelettes,
so I learned how to make them back home.
Sounds good to me!
Then you're in charge of omelettes, Kud.
Okay!
We'll need curry for the third dish.
Looks like it's all settled.
And jelly for dessert!
Alright, we don't have much time till dinner.
Let's go full speed!
Mission, start!
Alright!
How do you make the shrimp and cutlet?!
You batter them with flour and bread crumbs, then fry them.
Fry...
With this?
You use this.
We have stuff like this?
I'll turn up the heat.
Leave the frying to me!
Haruka-kun, hurry up and make the daikon miso soup.
I'll supervise.
Um...
Sign: Depression
What on earth are you...
Eggs... eggs... eggs...
Wafu!
Damn it....
Weak sauce, Kengo!
What?!
Let me show you a real move!
We're making good time!
Here they come!
Man, I'm hungry!
It's food time!
Is everyone ready?
Miso soup, ready!
Fried foods, ready!
Eggs aren't ready yet!
Calm down, Kud!
We'll put out the stuff we've done first.
Combo meal here!
Curry here!
Why are you guys cooking dinner?
Rice ball meal here!
We just need to put them on the trays!
Keep it up, everyone!
Add a jelly!
And a jelly!
Alright!
Jelly! Jelly!
Jelly!
What the heck?
Another jelly!
What's with these apples?!
How many jellies do I get?
Hey, this is practically a cabbage meal!
I got a combo with curry!
Why doesn't mine have a jelly?!
Masato! Get me some plates!
This is bad! We're out of trays!
We've got more over here!
Rin-chan, here too!
Alright, more jelly!
Jelly here!
More jelly!
Jelly! Jelly! Jelly!
Jelly!
Next please!
Here!
Alright!
This is the first time I've seen Rin so lively around other people.
But just one thing bothered me.
How did the writer of the letter Lennon brought us predict this crisis?
Who on Earth wrote that letter?
And then, it suddenly hit me again.
Narcolepsy.
Just like always, it came without warning.
I was disconnected from this world.
How long did I sleep?
I was all alone, as if the world had left me behind.
I couldn't tell how much time had passed or what time it was.
Just like the first time I had a sleep attack
and was hospitalized.
Kyousuke...
How are you feeling?
Nothing broken?
Yeah.
Want to rest some more?
No...
Then come on.
Everyone's waiting for you.
Hey, it's Riki-kun!
You look better now!
Thank goodness!
Here's your fried combo meal!
You waited this long for me?
It was Rin's idea.
We couldn't end this mission without you.
Everyone worked really hard after that.
We managed to pull through in the end.
Thanks to everyone...
Mission complete, right?
Alright! Let's get this party started!
Cheers!
Episode 9
Save the Cafeteria!
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
A girl sitting quietly at lunch under a big tree.
Always reading a book under her parasol.
Find the book Miss Nishizono lost.
Mission, start.