Narcolepsy:
A chronic disease I suffer from.
I get sleep attacks.
I'll suddenly lose consciousness and simply sleep.
Without even dreaming.
And before I know it, I'll wake up.
As if nothing had happened.
Naoe-kun!
How are you feeling?
You really surprised me yesterday.
You just suddenly fell asleep.
Sorry.
I'm fine, though.
No need to worry.
Yo, Riki!
Hey, Riki.
Yo.
Kyousuke, Kengo, and Masato never complain when they help me,
and always smile when I wake up.
Kind of like telling me there's nothing to worry about.
So I suppose Kamikita is part of the Little Busters now.
Yup! I'll try my best!
What about you, Kengo?
Have you decided to play with us?
That's fine.
The day will come when you'll understand.
No, it won't.
Go find someone else.
But seriously, we probably won't be able to get a third-year to join us.
If there's someone willing to play baseball when they're supposed to be studying for exams,
they'd have to be a total idiot.
Wait.
Are you calling me an idiot?
Whoops.
I am an idiot.
We might have no luck with the normal students,
but someone who already has a
job offer might have some free time.
This is a college prep school.
If there were a third-year who didn't plan on going to college but has a job offer,
then why the heck would they come here in the first place?
Why the heck did I come here?
Whoops.
Youth!
But Kyousuke, you still haven't found a job, right?
I haven't?
Cat...
Food...
Where do you think you're going, Rin?
We're about to start the Little Busters's first morning practice.
What? Morning practice?
Wait, we're seriously doing that?
We can only use the field when the girls' softball team isn't.
Let's play!
Come!
The dawn of our youth is now!
I don't wanna!
Our team, the Little Busters,
still needs four more members.
presented by UTW-Mazui!
hitori ga tsurai kara futatsu no te wo tsunaida
It was too hard for one to do, so two of us held hands
futari ja samishii kara wa ni natte te wo tsunaida
But two would be too lonely, so we all came together in a circle and held hands
kitto sore ga ikusen no chikara ni mo nari
I'm sure that will be strength in itself,
donna yume mo tateru ki ga surunda
Enough to end any dream we have
takaku tobe takaku sora he
Fly high, high into the sky,
takaku kere takaku koe wo age
Jump high, and raise your voice high,
itsuka kujiketa sono hi no mukou made
Until you can move on past the day we'll have died
kimi no koe wasurenai namida mo wasurenai
I'll never forget your voice, and I'll never forget your tears
kore kara hajimaru kibou to iu na no mirai wo
The future, what we call "hope", begins now
sono ashi wa arukidasu
Those legs will keep on moving forward,
yagate kuru kakoku mo
Even in the face of the oncoming grief
Hey, Riki.
Here's that idiom dictionary
I borrowed from you the other day.
Idiom
Dictionary
What's this?
Why is it in a bag?
Now then, first period is language arts...
Why is it in a bag? C'mon, tell me.
Hey, suspicion begets monsters, you know?
To get straight to the point...
That question's without parallel!
Hey, don't speak in idioms just
because of the idiom dictionary!
Come on. Actions speak louder than words.
I'd like an explanation in words.
Well, basically,
I kept it in my desk, so it got mixed in with a few things.
You know, like food.
So, all hell broke loose.
Hey, it smells good, right?
I searched left and right. I nearly lost my grip.
I tried to save it, but it was doomed to disaster.
I practically split my sides in hysteria.
Hey, hey! Morning, morning!
Riki-kun, Masato-kun, morning!
Good morning.
Huh? Who're you?
I wish you'd remember.
I'm always coming over here to hang out.
Saigusa Haruka!
Psychopathic maracas?
The first bell already rang.
The teacher's on his way.
You'll be late again.
You don't need to say "again".
I'm late every day!
But it looks like Anego isn't here yet.
Anego?
You mean Kurugaya-san?
Yeah. I came here to borrow an
idiom dictionary from Kurugaya-anego.
An idiom dictionary?
Wow! You have one right here!
Lucky me! I'll take it!
Thanks!
Hey!
Wait a second!
Bye-bye!
Wow, look at all those zeros.
First I thought they were straight 0's,
but they're all 100's!
Dang, Cuckoogayer's crazy!
It's not "Cuckoogayer", it's "Kurugaya".
Kurugaya-san is a genius who scores
within the top ten in the national exams.
What a strange, demented feeling it gives me
But she only comes to class when she feels like it.
when I realize I have spent
whole days before this inkstone,
No one knows what she does, or where she does it.
with nothing better to do, jotting down at random
whatever nonsensical thoughts that have entered my head.
Sold out?
Hey, Riki! Class is starting!
Hey—
Over here, boy.
Not over there. Over here.
Kurugaya-san?
You're Riki-kun, right?
If there's no coffee here,
perhaps you'd like some of mine?
I'm looking for something stimulating.
I was getting quite bored being by myself.
But class is about to—
Just shut up.
If you try to run, I'll kill you.
If you call for help, I'll kill you.
You dimwit.
Dim—
You might make for interesting conversation.
W-Wait!
It's like a sidewalk cafe.
It's a bit too gloomy to be called a sidewalk cafe.
Call it a sense of Japanese wabi-sabi.
Wouldn't I make a good painting of a young
daughter from a noble family sitting like this?
W-Well, you might make a good painting...
Though the only feeling you'd get is,
"What fallen noble's daughter is this?"
Come have a seat, Riki-kun.
I... I should get going.
I'm a cute schoolgirl, am I not?
Any normal boy of your age would give the world for this kind of invitation.
Or do you swing that way, boy?
Of course not!
It seems your heart is immovable.
Relax, sit down, and let us talk.
Alright, just for a bit.
You fell for it splendidly, boy.
I'm leaving.
Now, now. Wait.
That was just a little joke.
Why would you go to all the trouble of doing something like this?
Why?
Perhaps because it's fun.
No other reason is necessary.
You do look the type to be picked on.
You make me want to tease you.
I don't really want to be that type.
Is that so?
I consider it a compliment.
I like cute things, you see.
Well, it may have been in poor taste.
Drink some of this and relax.
Have some kimchi.
No thanks.
Oh, that's right.
It seems you've started a strange pastime with your friends.
Pastime?
You mean the Little Busters?
Is it fun?
Yeah. A lot.
In what way, may I ask?
Let's see...
It feels like it's where I belong.
Oh?
Where you belong?
When I'm with my friends, it feels like I really belong.
I see.
It seems you're quite the time waster.
You're one to talk, Kurugaya-san.
You stay out here every d—
Come now. Listen, boy.
Doesn't it just ease your heart?
Hearing the sound of the bell from here.
The bell?!
Crap!
I fell right into her trap!
I oughta give you a piece of my mind, Riki-kun!
You opened it?
Have you?
No...
I haven't opened it.
You need to open it, then.
Pudding in dying agony.
Jam on its deathbed.
Yogurt yowling yucky yellow!
Riki-kun, listen.
You don't keep pudding in your desk!
You keep printouts!
Keep your idiom dictionary in the refrigerator!
Damn it, Kengo!
What's wrong?
The same as always, I'll bet.
What's all the fuss?
Gotham!
Gotham?
It's a long story, but...
Intense cold
Uh, how do you read this?
You can just say "Gotham".
Intense cold
Really?
So I can say, "This winter's going to be really Gotham!"
Intense cold
Alright! I'll use that sometime this winter!
That's what he did.
But I just looked it up,
and it's actually pronounced "gokkan"!
I almost said, "Man, this winter's Gotham!" because of you!
It's your fault for not being able to read it in the first place.
Well, when we were in art class in middle school,
you mixed up the characters for "bag" and "shoe"
Bag
Today's subject
and ended up making a clay shoe!
Shoe
I'll never forget the sight of the entire class laughing at you that day.
So what?
I'm saying you're a bigger idiot than me!
Idiots have no right to call others idiots.
Get up.
What should we do?
When I'm done with you, your face'll be unrecog—
You fools.
Know the time and place to enact your horseplay.
Kurugaya-san!
What the hell?!
I should be saying that.
What the hell are you doing in a place like this?
You little...
This ain't some tea party a girl like you should be getting into!
What was that?
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?
I'm threatening you.
You ain't worth me picking a fight with!
I've lost my interest.
This is too ridiculous for my taste.
I'm done here.
Kengo!
You running away?!
Masato, just so you know...
It's best if you don't underestimate her.
This is a friendly warning.
Well? You were going to beat me to a bloody pulp, right?
He didn't say that!
You're going to be crying by the end of this!
I've yet to meet a man who could make me cry.
Masato-kun.
Oh?
W-Wait, Kurugaya-san!
Are you really going to fight Masato?
Just be quiet and watch.
I hope you're ready for this.
If I win, your name'll be "Cuckoogayer"!
He's such an idiot.
And if I win, my broadcasting club will air a show called "Today's Inohara-kun",
where I'll reveal all your
embarrassing secrets to the world!
Bring it on!
He's okay with that?
Idiot.
It's a fight!
They're going at it!
Masato's serious!
Kurugaya's going down!
What's all the ruckus, Riki?
This is Kurugaya-san, from my class.
You're Natsume Kyousuke, right?
You know me?
That makes things easier.
You guys should be aware that you're famous around here.
Allow me to referee this, then.
This fight will have rules.
Muscles, aww yeah! Muscles, aww yeah!
The spectators will throw in objects, and you will pick one to fight with.
You are not permitted to use anything else.
I see. Sounds interesting.
Enough talk! Let's start this!
Alright! Let's get this started, people!
Battle, start!
That's your weapon.
I'll use this.
Isn't that illegal?!
It's just an imitation.
It can't actually cut.
But I'm sure it'll hurt if you get hit with it.
Alright, I'm all fired up now!
Bring it on!
You want me to hit you that badly?
No.
Do you have any idea how dumb you look?
Shut up!
Take this!
What an idiot.
I'll play with you for a bit.
You should have listened to your friend.
Making light of me will only end badly for you.
Not bad.
I admire your guts, at least!
Kurugaya-san's movements aren't human!
Inohara-kun! You can do it!
I'd like her on our team.
Here, Riki-kun.
All this exercise is making me thirsty.
Get me a sports drink.
O-Okay...
Quit screwing around!
This is the end.
If you're going to surrender, now's the time.
If you cry and beg at my feet, I might forgive you.
I'm afraid you just released my final limiter.
My anger has reached its ecstasy!
He messed up...
"Reached its climax".
Has reached its climax!
He corrected himself...
Idiot.
Feel free to do your screaming in ecstasy, then.
Take this!
Go, Popping Bluebeard!
Too bad.
If I can get that toy back, I'll have the last laugh!
What the hell, man?!
I only have one of those!
Bluebeard!
Think of all the times we've spent together!
This is sad...
Come back!
Alright, got ya!
Well? Not going to surrender?
Like hell!
I see.
It's time for some fun punishment, then.
Spartan Kick Combo!
Acid Storm!
Dragon Somersault!
Shining Wizard!
What the hell?!
Oh, sorry.
I forgot that I was only allowed to use my weapon.
I got a little carried away.
I lose, Masato-kun.
It's settled, then.
Hey Masato, you won.
Damn it!
I can't accept a victory like this!
Well, she admitted she broke the rules herself.
Training!
Training?
Training in the mountains!
Right now?
Yeah. I'll see you later.
I haven't had that much fun in a while.
I quite like that idea of Kyousuke's.
What's wrong, boy?
Do you object to running errands?
No, I just couldn't take my eyes off you.
Off my boobs?
No!
It's okay.
I'll go buy it myself.
Wow...
We just saw the birth of a legend!
What on Earth is she?
I'm back!
Already?!
W-Welcome back...
So that's what happened?
The next time I go head-to-head with her, I'll show her the results of my training!
What kind of training is that?
How did it go that way?
I don't know...
That was a great pitch, Rin-chan!
Rub, rub, rub!
Stop it!
Kurugaya?
What?!
I can't stand it.
I can't stand how you're having so much fun all by yourselves.
Allow me to enjoy the sunshine of youth with these beautiful, young girls.
The Little Busters seems like the perfect way to kill time.
Huh?
I'm telling you to let me join.
What?!
Wha?!
Kurugaya-san...
Of course!
Playing with you all looks to be quite fun.
Alright!
Starting today, I'm one of you.
Episode 3
I Like Cute Things, You See
akaneiro no kumo
The clouds, lit bright orange,
omoide mo futatsu
And two of our memories
tooku nagareteyuku yo
Floating far into the distance
hibiku kane no oto
The sound of the bell echoing,
kakera kimi to hitotsuzutsu
Those pieces we shared, one each
ashita wa tenki ni nare
I hope tomorrow will be sunny
hoshi no mukou ikeru kana
Can we go beyond the stars?
sora mitsumete aruku hitohikari
Walking, looking at the sky, a single light
tsuki no ue hitori demo
Even alone, on the face of the moon,
rasen no hate he kaketeyuku yo
Run right past the end of the circle
kimi wa naita ato waraeru
You'll be able to smile after you cry,
hazu dakara tte ittan da
I said that because I know you can
bokura no tabi wasuretari shinai yo
You'll never forget our journey, even for a moment
nakusanai you ni mahou kakete
I'll cast a little magic so you never lose it,
sayonara wo tsutaenai
And I won't say good-bye
arukidasu yo mata itsuka
You'll start walking again one day
You can always find the blue sky, warm sunshine, and Kamikita-san on the roof.
Hey, Naoe-kun,
I always have this strange dream.
I wonder why.
Seek out the meaning of the dream!
Mission, start!