Hello there, everyone.
I'm here at Okinawa, where the second-years will be taking their field trip this year.
So what's a third-year like myself doing here, you ask?
The Newspaper Club has no
second-year members, you see.
Why aren't they going to Kyoto like last year, you ask?
Well, that's probably my fault.
Undaunted by such past failures,
I vow to uncover the sex lives of these teenagers, set free in the land of the endless summer,
and expose them for all to see!
Oh dear.
That's way too much pee.
The second-years' field trip starts tomorrow, huh?
Yeah.
We'll be away for about three days.
Look forward to souvenirs.
Sure!
Look out for a Memento.
Memento?
Ousai Academy Student Council Rules:
article two, clause three!
When adjusting your swimsuit,
use your middle finger, nice and lewd!
Oh man...
Adjust how your d*ck hangs!
We're talking about guys here?!
Do you know what cherry-blossoms symbolize?
No, I don't.
Tell us, Shino-chan.
Do you know what cherry-blossoms symbolize?
A good education, nobility, and purity!
Most awesome legendary days!
Monday morning, get up, off to school
Getsuyou asa kara iza yuke gakuen Days
Careful with that afternoon yawn, school's out, boo-yah
Daiteki na no wa gogo ichi akubi houkago banzai
I can handle all the classes just fine
Koku suu ei ri sha nante mondai nai kedo
But I'm still less experienced than most people
Ren'ai keiken heikin ika
I mean, it's against the school rules
Datte kousoku kinshi da shi
Get closer! Get closer!
Kyuu sekkin dai sekkin
I'll get you tomorrow! Just kidding!
Ashita wa Get You nanchatte
Most of your wishes should come true
Negaigoto wa daitai kanau yo
If you've got a shooting star in your hand
Nagareboshi tenazuketa nara saa
I want to take the sweetest spot in peace
Heiwa ni iitokodori shitai
Come on!
San hai
Yeah, yeah!
Hai hai
Twinkle, please?
Kirari onegai
Try this at home, kids
Yoi ko wa mane shite
Let's discuss what's most awesome
Kyoushitsu kara ginga made
From the classroom to the ends of the universe
Saikyousetsu ni hana sakasete
We'll walk there again today
Watashitachi wa kyou mo yuku
A woman's secret weapon is her smile
Otome no buki wa egao ne
Come on, smile wide!
Hora nikkori ii kanji
Screw common sense, let's take on the world
Joushiki yori karen na
With a dainty yet original charm
Original na bigaku de shoubu
Come with us, boys and girls
Tsuite oide yo Boys And Girls
The lights are all green wherever we go
Doko made mo shingou wa Blue
Right, all right!
Migi oorai
Left, all right!
Hidari oorai
Nothing can stop us now
Mou watashitachi tomerarenai
The spring wind feels amazing
Kaze kitte chousoukaikan
Don't get in our way
Jama shinai de ne
At the end of the universe, "How are you?"
Ginga no hate de How Are You
Nice to meet you
Yoroshiku ne
Learned that thing from earlier?
Perfectly.
Remember that thing from earlier?
Of course.
A good education, nobility, and purity!
Ousai Academy
Field Trip Guidebook
That should do it.
Come in.
'Sup, Taka-nii!
Packed and ready?
I just finished.
You didn't forget anything, did you?
No, I didn't.
Probably.
What about you-know-what?
Don't leave home without them!
What do you mean?
Tissues!
I'm talking about tissues!
Not just pocket ones, either. Boxed ones.
Wouldn't that take up too much space?
There's no telling when your
youthful libido will spin out of control.
You might have to wash your
underwear early one morning.
Don't worry. You've got me
slamming the brakes on already.
Now I'm worried about leaving you on your own.
What do you mean?
Well, whatever.
Kotomi!
Yes?
I'd like you to do me a favor.
Seitokai Yakuindomo
Three-Day Vice President
OUSAI STUDENT COUNCIL
Please proceed to the boarding gate.
Come to think of it,
I've never been on a plane before.
I think this'll be my second time.
Oh?
Guess I don't need to ask you,
since you've studied abroad.
Well, it goes without saying that
flying was part of my everyday life.
I couldn't be more used to it.
I've gotten used to it too.
Bzzzzz
I think I've taken off around four times today.
Control tower!
Requesting permission to land!
Could it be my glasses?
Huh?
That's a relief!
What was setting it off?
Well...
Please switch off any electronics
you may have on hand before takeoff.
click
That's what you're switching off?!
Perhaps it's a sign that we're really reliant on those two.
This room feels a lot more spacious now.
It's a bit lonely without them around.
On the other hand, we were
the ones who were away last year.
We'll have to pick up the slack in their absence.
You're right.
That said, the next three days
are going to be quite hard on us.
Yeah.
Though I do like it hardcore!
You can say that again!
This is throwing me off a bit, though.
Same here.
You seem troubled, my dear seniors.
I'm Tsuda Kotomi, and I'm here to pinch-hit for Taka-nii!
I don't know if you'll be much help.
Man, I totally dozed off on the flight.
Me too.
Did you wake up with a bon*r?
No, I didn't.
Me neither.
Ms. Yokoshima will now tell you some
guidelines with regards to your free time.
How are we supposed to take her seriously?
Well, she is a teacher.
This is your teacher-in-charge,
Yokoshima, speaking.
Over the next three days and two nights,
you will all enjoy your long-awaited field trip.
I would be happy if you could take full advantage of the hands-on learning, observational visits,
and other opportunities you'll only have here and now to broaden your horizons.
I wish you a happy and fun trip, but
do not forget to show some restraint.
As a student, and as a member of Ousai Academy,
you need to behave in a
manner that is appropriate.
Always keep that in mind.
And above all!
Do not do outrageous things like hit on a local boy and *****!
Well said, Ms. Yokoshima!
Make sure you all keep what she said in mind.
Okay!
Man, I can really feel the weight of this student council armband!
Indeed.
We, the student council, need to set an example for the entire student body with our behavior!
I hear you loud and clear, Prez!
I'll set an example of how not to behave!
Don't give up without even trying!
Good morning.
Morning.
A stand-in for Vice President Tsuda, huh?
She looks a little unreliable.
So sleepy...
Taka-nii did this almost every day, huh?
That's about as often as he f*ps.
W-Wait, do I have to play
the straight man on my own?!
Pinch-hitting
for Captain
What a bother.
Pinch-hitting
for Captain
So sleepy...
No, I gotta keep it together!
I agreed to do this!
Quit dragging your feet...
me!
I hear you're helping the student council out.
That's right!
Wanna join me in being
wrung out by the prez?
Don't wanna.
You're not wet. Looks like
you really don't want to.
You have a strange way of judging things.
Kotomi!
What's up?
Hey, are your brother and the
student council president...
Shurijo Park
Land of Propriety
Artist's Rendition of Reconstruction
Under renovation, huh?
Our school keeps hitting the jackpot.
Last year, wasn't it Honnou Temple that was being renovated?
Didn't a student go on a rampage because
she was so shocked she couldn't visit?
Welcome, mensore!
Okinawa
Suzu's Head
What are you doing here?
The Newspaper Club has no
second-year members, you see.
That doesn't mean you had
to come all the way here—
M-My desire for a scoop
has my ***** dripping wet!
Surely there were other ways to say that.
Regroup here at twelve, okay?
Okay!
So you came here without
the school's permission?
You'll be held back a year, you know.
Oh, I'll be fine.
Could you all do me a favor, if possible?
What is it?
Keep an eye on Ms. Michishita and Mr. Daimon for me.
Is it too shiny?
Absolutely not!
Don't wanna.
Oh no, negotiations broke down.
Take some yachimun  back home with you
Excuse me!
How can I help you?
Limited Flavor ! !
Only available in Okinawa!
Wh-What sort of obscene thing
is this "yachimun"?!
It ain't obscene.
It's just chinaware.
What?
Chinaware?
Nene Todoroki's
Great Knowledge!
Todoroki Nene's Great Knowledge!
Well, I dunno if I know that much—
Just hurry up and start already!
Sorry about that!
This has me completely on edge.
Before the war, it wasn't plastic that was used, but ceramics. Chinaware!
Huh? What are you talking about?
They still ran on electricity, though.
Oh, is that a kotatsu?
I mean, ceramics are cold to the touch, right?
So they used to be fitted
with electrothermal devices.
These really existed
Chinaware?
D-Does it look like this?!
Limited Flavor ! !
Only available in Okinawa!
My eyesight just ain't what it used to be.
I can't handle Nene's nonsense.
Me neither.
If this keeps up, we really are going to cause problems for the locals.
I guess.
The two of us need to keep a proper eye out.
Stop giving us half-hearted replies, dude.
My bad.
Huh?
Wait, what?
AM I
LOST
Protected Turn Signal
Me?
Man, how wonderful.
Does he mean me?
Uh, I don't think so.
We've got big trouble!
What's wrong?
Suzu-chan's...
Suzu-chan's missing!
What?
Seitokai Yakuindomo
Pretty Woman
OUSAI STUDENT COUNCIL
Oh well.
I dropped my cellphone somewhere...
Wear panties!
DISCIPLINARY PLAN
WEAR PANTIES
Objection!
DISCIPLINARY PLAN
WEAR PANTIES
Still with us?
Student council work is so hectic!
So you feel like a spinning cowgirl, I take it?
She's asking if it's enough
to make your head spin.
Where did you last see her?
Around the souvenir shop.
I see.
I'm sorry, Ms. Yokoshima.
This happened on my watch.
Don't let it get you down.
Tsuda, let's go look for her.
S-Sure.
She's a smart kid, so she might end up wandering all over the place instead.
Ms. Yokoshima...
If we don't find her, I'm taking your virginity tonight!
No, don't! Please don't!
Anything on your end?
Nope.
What's the matter?
P**nsuko!
She actually said it! We apologize!
Tsuda, it's P**nsuko!
It's P**nsuko!
Hang on a second!
It's "Chinsuko"!
You're practically insulting the locals here!
What else can I do? It's P**nsuko!
I can't believe I found P**nsuko here!
Just knock it off already!
Come on, see for yourself!
Peen suko
A big new product!!
Whoa, she's right!
Peen suko
A big new product!!
Peensuko
How you amaze me, Okinawa.
I'm buying a box of this.
Can we please look for Hagimura?
No need for that.
A big new product!!
Peen suko
Hagimura! We looked all over for you!
I'm sorry.
Nah, I'm just glad we managed to find each other.
I figured I'd run into someone here.
Huh? How come?
A big new product!!
Peen suko
I knew someone was bound to react to this.
Oh wow.
You're truly incredible, Hagimura-san.
Thanks for coming to find me.
No problem.
It made me a little happy.
MEANWHILE
AT OUSAI ACADEMY
I'm beat.
I never realized Taka-nii did so much stuff.
Sorry I messed up so many times.
Nah, don't be. You've never done this before, after all.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Really?
Really.
Everybody messes up
some time or the other.
Like today, I tried to pull my
tamp*n out, but the string broke.
It threw me into a panic!
That does happen.
It totally does!
Huh?
We're missing Tsuda-kun and Suzu-chan.
Looks like we really can't manage without the two of them.
Yeah.
If Tsuda were around,
I'd be able to focus more tightly.
I don't want to be considered a loose woman!
Haven't heard that phrase
in a while, Shino-chan!
School Friends
Kaede Igarashi
Ousai Academy
Ousai General Affairs
Takatoshi Tsuda
Kotomi Tsuda
Aria Shichijou
Suzu Hagimura
Naruko Yokoshima
School Friends
Kaede Igarashi
Ousai Academy
Ousai General Affairs
Takatoshi Tsuda
Kotomi Tsuda
Aria Shichijou
Suzu Hagimura
Naruko Yokoshima
School Friends
Kaede Igarashi
Ousai Academy
Ousai General Affairs
Takatoshi Tsuda
Kotomi Tsuda
Aria Shichijou
Suzu Hagimura
Naruko Yokoshima
School Friends
Kaede Igarashi
Ousai Academy
Ousai General Affairs
Takatoshi Tsuda
Kotomi Tsuda
Aria Shichijou
Suzu Hagimura
Naruko Yokoshima
Takatoshi Tsuda
School Friends
Kaede Igarashi
Ousai Academy
Aria Shichijou
Suzu Hagimura
Naruko Yokoshima
Takatoshi Tsuda
Would I be bothering him?
Time to look for treasure!
Treasure, treasure...
Where art thou, treasure?
I'm the stand-in Vice President, Tsuda Kotomi!
I made it in time today!
Good. I'm proud of you.
Let's give it our all today as well.
Got it!
By the way, Shino-chan.
About yesterday's meeting...
DISCIPLINARY PLAN
WEAR PANTIES
Maybe I should just wear some panties.
Listen to yourself!
An Aria in panties is no Aria at all!
Look, just put them on!
I've got some on!
Oh? Are you wearing a
school swimsuit underneath?
Yeah. I've got swimming today.
This won't do at all!
Girls have to pay attention
to what can't be seen, too!
Wow!
There's a gorgeous shadow
on each and every crease!
Hah!
I knew going commando was better!
Look, just put some panties on!
Mantadick
Takatoshi's
Head
Suzu's
Manta!
Dick!
Manta, manta!
Dick, dick!
It's see-through!
Yeah, totally see-through.
Completely visible!
You can see everything!
It's erect!
Takatoshi's
Head
Suzu's
It's erect!
Long and thick!
Standing tall and proud!
We're truly sorry to all the locals!
Kaiji Beach
Looks like they're having fun.
Shall we join them?
Sure thing.
Hold it right there!
Have you forgotten about
my request from yesterday?
What was it, again?
Come on. It concerned
Mr. Daimon and Ms. Michishita.
Those two are fishy.
What? Really?
Is it too shiny?
Absolutely not!
They do seem awfully close.
Where did you see that?
Why didn't you tell me about it?
I kinda had my hands full at the time.
Guys!
The scuba diving ship's about to leave!
Okay!
I appreciate your help! You have my thanks!
Fine.
Hagimura-san, do you know about Star Sand?
I do.
I've been meaning to check it out too,
but we don't have time to
go that far today, do we?
Très bien!
Je t'aime!
A flower garden!
I guess this does feel kinda forced.
Please put all this away!
It tickles!
If I put food on my ***** and *****, how awesome would it feel?
You're clearly thinking of something dirty.
By the way, Prez...
There's a rumor circulating among my friends
about you and Taka-nii dating.
Wha—
What the heck?
The two of us aren't like that!
Figures.
That's what I told them, too.
Besides, I checked his rubbish bin,
and it's still full of c*m-stained tissues.
Achoo
Where are you going, Tsuda?
There's still some time until our
boat leaves, so I'm going for a walk.
He actually went off alone.
This place really is pretty.
star sand
My!
star
Thank you!
I should keep this a secret from Hata-san.
Tsuda?
It's me.
Prez?
What's wrong?
Nothing. I was just thinking about you.
Am I bothering you?
Not really.
I'm just wandering around
on my own right now.
Really?
I called at the right time, then.
I've been wanting to tell you something since yesterday.
What is it?
I hope you haven't had any *et dreams.
Can I hang up now?
Sakura no hanabira
The cherry blossoms fill the air
Magireru kisetsu wo
Dancing as the wind blows
Yurashite yuku Melody ga
I can hear a gentle melody there
Wakuwaku suru you na
My heart's racing, I'm aware
Kimochi sekasu kara
But before I can even prepare
Ima sugu mou hashiridasu yo
To find it I go; I'll search high and low!
Yume ga
My dream
(Shining Shining)
Hanatsu
Transmitted
(Shooting Shooting)
Uchuu kibo no Signal wo
A universal signal to me
(I'm a mermaid in the ether)
Tetsuya de tokiakashita kotae wa
I stayed up all night to decode it and found
Uta ga suki ichiban daiji na koto
That I love singing, and that's what matters most right now!
Aimai mirai kagayaki e Dive
It's our future, shining for you, so dive!
Hajikesou na kurai
Let's make it come alive
Ooki na hana sakaseyou
A sunflower bloom for every seed you sow
Aimai mirai osorezu ni Dive
It's our future, don't be scared, just dive!
Yokubari na negai
Dream big dreams to strive
Ryoute hiroge tsukamou yo
Spread your arms wide and catch them as they go
Mayoi mo fuan mo
All your worries and your woes
Uta ni shichaeba ne All Right
Put them into song and it'll be all right
Soshitara mata ashita Smile Again
And when tomorrow comes, you can smile again
Okinawan
Sata
Andagi
They're sata andagi!
How did you find student council work, Kotomi?
Well...
I had a rough time since
there was so much to learn.
Oh, but my knowledge of sex
proved to be enough!
So, business as usual, huh?
Biology Lab
What could that be?
Guess I'll start with the *****.
M-Ms. Yokoshima! What do you think you're doing?!
Oh shit!
THE MUSIC TEACHER
SAW IT!
NAUGHTY ENGLISH TEACHER
FISH-FEEDING
MASTURBATION
NEXT EPISODE
Hagimura Suzu here.
For some reason, the next episode
flashes back to around Golden Week.
squeeze
It'll be an amazing story about looking
down on people from atop a ferris wheel.
How twisted.
Next episode, we'll mainly be covering chapter 180, in volume 7.
Watch it, or I'll kick you
with my indoor shoes!
Emphasis on Bzbzbz
Moe Tail
Groundbreaking Skin Peeling
Stay ripped!