Mashiro
Listen!
The next serialization committee is the real deal!
You're going to put everything you've learned so far into your next work!
Right!
But just what kind of manga should they make?
There's no guarantees with manga, but there should be something only you can do.
And if you can pull it off, it won't lose, not even to Niizuma.
But can we draw that manga?
We haven't even been a match for him so far...
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Hint and Best
First off, did you enjoy making your last manga, STOPPER OF MAGMA ?
No.
How about Tanto ?
I feel bad saying this in front of Miura, but not really.
Actually, it was painful.
I didn't really like it, either...
I'm sorry.
I guess if the authors aren't into it, it won't be a good manga.
Normally, yes...
But I agree with the editorial department's decision to deny KTM  a serialization.
It was interesting, but probably lacks the tension expected from a shounen magazine.
The setting might be too complicated for young people to understand._____________
tittiestittiess
Integrated Publication Corporation
KTM's setting is too elaborate.
Selling brains and physical appearance.
Rankings based on the interaction between the two.
Considering all that, a protagonist who spends all his time trying to raise his rankings isn't appealing.
You're trying to move the story forward by the strength of its setting alone.
I see. So that's why you had us make a mainstream fantasy after that?
With as simple of a setting as possible.
Yes, but there was another reason for that.
Humor.
Humor?
I don't understand that bit.
You wanted them to make a humorous fantasy, right?
This is something I wanted the three of you to realize,
but perhaps it would have been easier to understand if I had said to make an unconventional manga with humor in it.
Listen, there is absolutely no humor in this manga.
You could say the same about +NATURAL.
I don't think serious stories need humor.
That's because you're thinking about
putting in silly things to make people laugh.
When I read Tanto, I couldn't help feeling that it was a waste.
I thought there should be a more effective use for Takagi's humor.
Ashirogi Muto's defining characteristic is definitely unconventional stories.
What you should aim for is...
serious humor!
Er, I don't get it at all.
Do you remember the human-faced rescue chapter of Otters 11 ?
Yes.
This is a rare human-faced otter!
When the TV crew captured Otter #11's friend, the human-faced otter,
they made a spectacle of him, and Otter #11 got angry.
Whats that? It looks gross!
He smashed a truck into the TV
station building and ran to save him.
That chapter was pretty funny.
Do you think Hiramaru was trying to get laughs with that scene?
No, I think it's drawn seriously.
Oh, I see!
Making people laugh without trying to make them laugh.
The kind of humor that can only be done in a serious story.
It'd be amazing if you could do that deliberately!
Yes.
And I think you're the only one who can do that.
There's one more thing.
Mashiro's serious art.
The more serious the art, the more what we're trying to do will shine.
It'll cause a chemical reaction!
I'm quivering with excitement...
M-Me too...
We've gotta do it.
Yeah.
He thought of something that really suits them...
An idea like this...
Hattori.
Yes?
Did you pair up Akina Aiko and Niizuma for Natural...
and make that speech at the wedding...
just to bring us to this point?
You're reading too much into it.
KTM, STOPPER OF MAGMA, and Tanto.
Listen, nothing you did so far has been in vain!
The three of you together can definitely make a great manga!
Yes!
This is all the advice I can give you.
I can't wait to read it.
Thank you.
Thank you, Hattori.
All right! Lets get started with the meeting!
Please do!
Stop right there.
You suspicious individual...
Mr. Yoshida!
M-My otter is talking!
You've already seen the promo a bunch of times.
I want to see it in real time.
Besides, since I've got an anime, I can take a break for a week or two...
So you can take a break, can you?
Then I'll take an eternal break from "This week's Aoki Kou".
No, anything but that!
I'll draw! I'll do it!
Good boy.
So without further ado, "This week's Aoki Kou!"
Ta-da!
Aoki Kou
Secret Diary
Aoki likes Earl Grey tea.
End.
Earl Grey?
That's it for this week?
What do you mean by that?
What if you go out to tea with Aoki?
Then you can order Earl Grey for her!
She'll definitely think better of you.
I-I see.
Please tell me more about Aoki next week, too.
Leave it to me.
Luckily, Aoki's editor is my subordinate.
Go, subordinate!
Yana
Festival
I have to decide the setting pretty soon.
Hattori went out of his way to give us advice.
I want to live up to his expectations.
Yeah.
Even though we have a clear direction...
No, because  we have a clear direction, I want to really nail the setting.
Nail it, huh?
Akito, Mashiro!
Since we're here, let's enjoy the school festival!
All right?
Thanks for the food.
There's no octopus in here!
Mine, either.
Don't be silly.
This isn't a manga, so that couldn't...
It's all octopus...
What's with that?
This kind of surprise makes me happy.
It's just more octopus than usual.
What's wrong with that?
I'm going to a meeting.
Miura.
What's going on with Ashirogi's storyboard?
I told you to show it to me soon!
I'm sorry.
Sorry?! Hey, you...
The Chief may have said he wouldn't allow them to draw for Jack any more, but he's not really going to enforce it...
No, he's serious about it.
If he allows them to continue being selfish, it'll be a bad example for the other authors.
Well, I guess so...
Serious humor... it's more difficult than using silly stuff to get laughs.
Thinking of a setting is difficult, too.
I think something just needs to come to me.
Um, just in case you don't have a flash of inspiration,
don't you think you should touch up KTM 's setting and make a storyboard from that?
No, I don't think we can do serious humor with KTM.
TRAP!!
____________Why are you
_______________ here?!
If anything, it would have been TRAP...
Like a criminal caught in a trap, or something.
I see!
Like that "I didn't expect that!" feeling.
That's pretty good.
That line of thinking's pretty good!
"I didn't expect that!", huh?
But putting in an "I didn't expect that!"
moment would be trying to make them laugh.
I think serious humor is something else.
Yeah, you're right.
I heard that their storyboard wasn't
considered at the last serialization committee.
Thanks for worrying about them.
But they're already working hard on their next manga.
Well, they seem kinda desperate, though.
I suppose so. This is their last chance, after all.
What do you mean by last chance?
I'm sorry, I may have said too much.
No, please tell me the details.
It can't be... if they don't pass at the next committee,
they can't draw for Jack anymore?
Ninja Squad
I haven't heard about it from Mashiro.
Apparently, it was their condition for quitting Tanto.
I can understand why Akito didn't tell me, but...
Kaya.
Let's just silently watch over them for now.
Let's believe in them, okay?
Okay.
I thought I put it in here...
Saitama Prefecture, Yakusa City
Tokyo Metropolis, Sumida ward, Kikugawa
Hattori Akira
Takagi
Akito
This has to be it!
Why did we have to come all the way to
Hattori's apartment to ask him for advice?
Who said we were asking him for advice?
Huh? We're not?
We're going to tail Hattori all day today.
Huh? Why?!
I don't really know myself.
We're tailing him without knowing why?
Well, I don't know, but... you know how Hattori always helps us out?
But this time, I felt like we were being manipulated.
It's kinda frustrating.
I guess.
So if we tail him for a day, I feel like I can come up with an idea!
And we'll get him back at the same time!
There he is!
I thought he wouldn't leave until past noon. He's pretty early.
All right, let's go.
This reminds me of the time we staked out Azuki's house in middle school.
Yeah. We were pretty young back then.
He's going to work, I guess.
I think so too, but let's get on the train car next to his without him noticing.
Good morning.
It's Yueisha after all.
What'll we do?
Wait till he comes out?
Of course!
Let's get something to eat. I'm starving.
Shujin, you're not just playing around, are you?
I'm serious.
It's Yuujirou.
Seems like he's in a good mood.
That's Ibaraki from Jack SQ.
He's in an even better mood.
Oh, it's Takahama!
Let's say hi to him!
No, that would make this whole thing pointless!
Pointless?
Just what are we trying to do here?
We're not going to do anything, but we're tailing him in secret.
There he is!
Thank goodness.
Resume tailing!
How-Tos
He's really into whatever he's reading.
What is  he reading?
Oh, he's going to buy it!
I'm gonna go take a look!
Don't let him notice you.
Jinbouchou Book Store
"Key Points of Women in Love"?
Also, "Basic Manners for Relationships" and "The Art of Taking the Initiative in Love".
Seriously?
Crap, this tailing thing just got fun.
I know, right?
Is it a meeting?
Probably.
But aren't we sitting too close to him?
My heart's pounding in my ears.
If we don't sit this close, we won't hear what he says.
You're wearing sunglasses, so it should be oka—
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No problem.
That voice... it's Iwase, isn't it?
Y-Yeah.
But she's dressed up really nicely.
And she's wearing more makeup than at the New Years party.
Oh?! I really want to see!
Then let's get started.
Right.
I read the storyboard you sent me.
How was it?
Her skirt's so short! i can see everything!
It was good, for the most part.
Saiko, can I turn around?
I marked the spots that need fixing.
No way. I'll tell Kaya.
Thank you.
Do you have any questions?
Hattori.
Which part?
Am I pretty today?
Well?
Sit down, Iwase.
Please answer my question.
Am I pretty?
Rather than pretty, I would say that your youth is dazzling.
N-Now, let's get back to the—
Will you take me out to a movie on your next day off?
"Your youth is dazzling"?!
Well, as editor and author—
No.
Socially.
More importantly, this storyboard—
More importantly?!
You're cruel, Hattori!
I can't take anymore!
Let's wait outside till he's done.
I see. Akina's a troublesome one.
For sure.
Strange, they both have their phones turned off.
Ashirogi?
Yeah.
I want those two to go for it.
Yuujirou, are you already drunk?
There haven't been any newcomers aiming for the top lately.
But those two have that kind of ambition.
Right, Hattori?
Yeah.
Since the time they first consulted with me,
I felt their drive and ambition.
I felt it from their manuscript, as well.
Ashirogi Muto will become great authors, for sure.
I want to bet on them.
I'm sorry I got chosen as their editor.
It doesn't matter who their editor is.
My judgment as an editor was correct.
Maybe that's all I wanted to prove.
No, it wasn't wrong!
That's why...
Hattori...
Hattori, Miura, let's drink up tonight!
My treat!
Really?
Yeah!
And he gets home a little before 3 AM.
Instead of getting back at him, we were kind of encouraged by him.
Yeah, I'm fired up now.
Well, let's get back.
Actually, we have to wait at a restaurant till the first train.
So what was today all about?
A hint for serious humor?
Hmm? Didn't anything occur to you?
Did you think of something?
We had that "I didn't expect that!"
conversation with Miura before, right?
I got caught up in that.
Me, too.
So from that, and from trailing Hattori, I know what we're going to do now.
What kind of manga can you make from trailing and "I didn't expect that!"?
Long story short,
it's a perfect crime manga.
Huh?
Perfect crime?!
The protagonist  is a boy who admires and is fascinated by perfect crimes.
But he doesn't commit real crimes.
For example, he observes the pencil
case of the boy who sits next to him.
What kind of case it is, what condition it's in...
How many pencils are in it, what
kind of pencils, how long they are,
how worn down the erasers are...
Then he creates a perfect replica and
exchanges them without anyone noticing.
And he's satisfied when the boy doesn't notice a difference.
I see. That's the "I didn't expect that!" bit.
I'm kind of excited!
Even if it's not a real crime!
Yeah.
What kind of splendid crime will he pull off?
The tension it causes! The excitement! The shocking turn of events!
Even if it's stupid at first glance, the more serious you treat it, the funnier it is!
That's where the serious humor will come from.
Swapping a pencil case, or tailing like we did.
It's okay if the protagonist's perfect crimes are all small.
Eventually, he notices others who enjoy doing the same thing.
Some stuff happens, and they end up teaming up.
About three of them will form an underground society at the school... a perfect crime club!
A perfect crime club! That's so cool!
This could work!
Elementary school kids who commit perfect crimes!
It's great!
Maybe they match wits with the police and evil organizations,
and use their intelligence to avoid being caught, or something!
Sounds good, we can run with that!
Takagi
Hey, you should at least tell me when you're going out data collecting.
I was worried.
Sorry.
I'm going out the day after tomorrow.
Where?
Miho's house!
I'm bringing her a present, since it's her birthday.
You two won't be going, will you?
What did you get her?
I bought her a one piece at Yakusa Hill Town!
She's turning 20, so it's okay to splurge, right?
I took the opportunity to get myself one, too!
Sorry, Saiko, were you sleeping?
Accompany me one more time!
I need you for this.
I thought of a perfect crime!
Something exactly the same as this?
We can't tell what store she bought it from by this picture.
We'll start by finding it.
Finding it?
We don't know the name of the store.
And how many clothes stores do you think there are here—
Right?
If this were a manga, it'd be...
Shit! We don't know which store!
That kind of thing.
Serious humor, yeah?
I see.
You really thought this through.
So how are we going to find the store?
We'll search one by one.
So you haven't thought that far.
Is it okay to let me see your wife's sleeping face?
Huh? It's cute, right?
Stop that, Akito...
That was close.
Even Mashiro isn't picking up his phone...
Are they really going to be okay?
It's important to get a taste of what the protagonist is feeling, after all!
The thrill of the crime, and the sense of accomplishment when you pull it off!
Its fun and addictive!
Tailing Hattori also came in handy for the storyboard...
My pencil won't stop moving!
Shujin..
Yeah?
This storyboard...
This is the best storyboard you've ever done!
I'm a new man.
Okay then, make a clean copy of this eight page scene!
Yeah!
Editorial Department
Shounen
Jack
Jack SQ
Miura!
Y-Yes?
Do you still have nothing from Ashirogi Muto?!
You know they can't fail next time, right?!
Of course! I'll get them to hurry!
Maybe this is as far as Ashirogi Muto goes.
We shouldn't have let them quit Tanto!
Oh, it's Miura.
Crap, I never got back to him!
Hello—
Why didn't you call me back?
Aida's worried, too!
He's asking if you've gotten anything done yet!
We're doing it now.
It's gonna be great!
What?!
A hundred times better than KTM !
And suited for Jack!
Congrats, Sis!
Thanks, Mina.
The next one's from me!
Happy birthday, Miho!
Here's your present!
Thanks, Kaya.
Oh, it's big! What is it?
Can I open it?
Yeah! Go ahead!
Since you're turning 20, I went for a more mature look...
Thank you!
Out of all the presents I've gotten, this one makes me the happiest!
Really?
I'm gonna get embarrassed if you say all that...
Did you ask Mashiro to draw this?
Huh?
But don't you look a little too pretty?
I don't think so.
It's beautiful...
Mashiro's really something.
So where's the present I got you?
Tues
Wed
Thu
Fri
Sat
Azuki's birthday
I wonder if Kaya's dress got there yet.
She'll complain about it later.
No, she won't.
A call? From who?
Azuki is calling  me?!
H-Hello?
T-This is Mashiro.
Thank you, Mashiro.
I'm really happy.
Is it rude to ask a professional manga author to draw a picture for me every year?
Of course I can, if you'd like...
Oh, happy birthday!
Thank you.
Creating surprises is also part of a perfect crime.
We'll use those surprises to shock and amuse the readers!
If there's no octopus, it's a surprise.
If there's too much octopus, it's a surprise.
That's right.
Then 80% of students headed off to have fun in the campus etc.
The other 20% remained in their seats
For
example,
Mari,
studying
in her seat
This'll work.
This manga's gonna be great!
Everyone will definitely get excited when they read it!
Your storyboard!
Hurry and show me the storyboard!
Here it is.
Ashirogi Muto
"Perfect Crime
Club"
First chapter
Ashirogi Muto
"Perfect Crime
Club"
First chapter
Ashirogi Muto
"Perfect Crime
Club"
First chapter
Ashirogi Muto
Perfect Crime Club?
Is this really a hundred times better than KTM ?
Just read it!
W-What is this?
toomawari wo eranda no wa
The reason I chose to take a detour
motto kimi wo suki ni naru tame datta n da
was to fall ever deeper in love with you
boku no namae yobu sono koe wo
I have a feeling I've always known
zutto zutto shitteta ki ga shita n da
what your voice sounds like when it calls my name
boku no yubisaki de egaita
With my fingertips I drew
subete no sen wa kimi ni tsuzuku kakehashi sa
many lines that make up a suspension bridge leading to you
Show me the way
Show me the way I'm sure our path
bokura no michi kitto
Believe in your way
your way connects us without any turns
hitosuji ni tsunagari
Show me the way
Show me the way It leads to the place where we promised
yakusoku no basho e tsuzuku
Show me the way
Show me the way I will never give up
akirametari shinaide
Believe in your way
your way Raise your gaze
sono hitomi wo agete
Show me the way
Show me the way and see that we're certain to meet again
bokura wa massugu deau sa
It's not about yes or no.
Next Time
Preview
It's about whether or not Ashirogi
Muto's work can really beat Niizuma's!
I won't lose! SPIN!
Next time on Bakuman: Win and Lose.
Win and
Lose
Will Ashirogi Muto's dream be broken?