I'm doing great! They decided to serialize my manga!
Yes, Hattori-san just told us. Congratulations!
Thank you, getting serialized feels great!
I'll do my best to catch up with you!
I think he's declared war...
Takahama-san and Fukuda-san. This is getting interesting.
Let's do our best to beat them!
You bet!
The results...
+Natural is 4th!
We're still fine.
Dammit.
6th place is no good.
Hey, if I could be with you right now
Then I could keep my voice from fading
The goals I've set for myself seem too high to reach,
and I feel like I've lost my way
I'm relying on a broken compass and hiding in someone's shadow
If we keep letting go of what we have to find something else,
then I'm convinced we can never grow up
Never
Everynight and Unite
Understood!
We'll switch in Giri... Yes.
Whew, that feels great!
Just as Kiyoshi Knight is ending we have a new serialization.
We're too cool!
The one with the motorcycle?
Yeah, it's about motorsports in a way...
Um, Yuujiro-san.
Hattori-san doesn't look too happy.
He says PCP in 6th place won't cut it.
Why not?
PCP does have special limitations.
Limitations?
They have a tacit agreement...
PCP is missing something...
But what?
Are you even listening to me?
Ah... sorry.
Please take this a little more seriously!
I definitely won't lose to Ashirogi Muto.
Don't worry.
In 6 months, PCP will probably be over.
6th isn't good enough.
If PCP can't compete with +Natural and Crow within 6 months,
It will be cancelled.
What?!
Those are the chief's conditions.
That isn't really a surprise.
Back when we quit writing Tanto...
We will beat Niizuma Eiji.
So please let us end Tanto!
Oh, right!
I kept quiet about it because I didn't want to pressure you.
But at this rate if we don't do something, it'll be cancelled.
+Natural's anime is starting in April...
And Fukuda-san and the others have a new series starting.
That's pretty rough.
We're not just competing with Eiji and Iwase now.
Now there are three new series.
PCP will be over...?
From what he said, that's how it looks.
Aren't those conditions a little unfair?
That means if I try my hardest, Takagi-kun will...!
Isn't that what you wanted?
Didn't you want to beat PCP?
Akina-kun...
Do you enjoy competing with Takagi-kun?
Does it make you happy?
N-no!
But it's important for Takagi-kun to be there so I can beat him!
Well... at this rate we won't have to
worry about them pulling ahead.
What do you mean?
I just came from Niizuma's...
Then I guess that's it for Ashirogi-sensei.
You really think so?
Yeah,
I don't think they can beat me like this.
When it comes to manga, Niizuma-kun's always right.
Hattori-san said he's psychic.
And Niizuma-san said at this rate...
Yeah.
Call Takagi-kun and then give me the phone!
Just do it.
Ok!
We won't make it at this rate,
We need to find something to boost our potential.
Sorry, let me get this...
Miura-san?
Miura...
This is Iwase.
Iwase?! Why?
I apologize.
At one point I had planned to kick you guys out no matter what it took.
Huh??
But I'm done with that cowardly plan.
From now on I'm going to fight fair and square.
Alright?!
You guys won't be able to beat me.
W-wait a sec, I don't even know what you're talking about...
Apparently Niizuma-san said at this rate you PCP doesn't have a chance against him.
Eiji...
So think of something!
Scheme! Give it your all!
Now that I've told you this,
If you lose to me, it's your own fault, got it?!
Iwase...
Ok.
Thank you for the warning.
Now watch us pull ahead!
I would like to see you try.
Niizuma and Iwase...
Are good rivals.
Yeah.
I need a break!
I don't care what you say, Yoshida-shi!
Then, what if I said a break means no tea party with Aoki-san?
Tea party?!
I... I finally get to have tea with Aoki-san?!
That's right.
Here at your place.
Yoshida-shi!
So just sign here.
Yoshida-shi, why will it be here?
Isn't that why you have such a cool place?
Oho! Designer Condoooo!
You've done so well!
Yup!
And you'll work hard after the tea party?
Of course!
And after this, you won't take any more breaks from Otters?
Sure!
YES! That'll keep him for another six months!
So he doesn't think PCP can win at this rate?
Yeah.
PCP could beat him if we made some changes.
Yeah...
If Niizuma-kun said that, it means you're almost there.
Oh hey, you said PCP did best with the under 10 and over 18 brackets right?
I think younger kids admire the characters,
And adults can see their younger selves in them.
But middle and high schoolers are
going to be a little more distant.
So should we make the party's actions wilder?
You could, but you want to keep it realistic...
It has to be fairly ordinary.
Yeah, you're right...
This isn't a battle manga, so there's a limit to what we can do.
There must be something that our manga lacks.
Once we fix that, we should be
able to prove Niizuma-san wrong.
That's what I was thinking.
Dammit, what did Eiji have in mind?
I know,
I'll study some more popular manga.
Mashiro-san, we're running out of #62 gradation tone.
Huh? Already?
"Already"? We're following your instructions here, so you should know how much we've used.
You're right. I'll stock up.
If I may,
As someone with design school experience, I think you rely on tones a little too much.
If you overuse them, it can end up flattening things out.
Um...
It's dangerous for a young woman to be alone with a guy in his apartment.
Remeber when you said that PCP can't beat us at this rate...
I've been thinking about that.
Yeah, I won't lose.
PCP's too plain right now.
Plain?
...You're right.
It's not flashy like a battle manga. The story is very simple.
No.
It's not the story, it's the art.
The art?!
Hey...
Don't you think PCP's art is a little too dark?
Too much ink and tone?
...Not really.
I mean, that's part of it.
But it's not very shonen manga-ish.
But the story's a little different, too.
That's what makes it unique right?
No...
A shonen manga shouldn't be this dark...
In order for this to become a popular manga...
I'll need to change my style to
suit the taste of our audience.
PCP is realistic, so the drawings should be realistic, too.
But it is a manga after all.
Realistic drawings aren't good enough.
I have to do things you can only do with manga.
You have to be artistic every once in a while.
Make things pop.
Be stylish.
Like this!
Do you get it?
That's enough Niizuma-san.
I didn't come here to ask what Ashirogi Muto is missing.
Huh? Really?
I came here to make sure you don't tell them.
You're soft on them for some reason.
That's because I'm a fan.
I told them you don't think they can beat us at this rate.
But I don't want to give them any more help than that.
Got it!
I don't want to lose, either.
Let's make +Natural even more popular!
You're talented, we can do it!
T-talented?
Of course!
You're quitting school?!
I don't need to be a college student anymore.
I just want more time to work on my art.
I've already talked to my parents and emailed Azuki.
I see.
More time for our series I suppose.
Saiko, you said you would change your style gradually
I can already see a big difference in chapter 8.
Really?
Chapters 5 and 6 were in 7th and 8th place respectively...
If it gets any worse, Niizuma's warning...
Will the art in chapter 8
make enough of a difference?
Huh? 5th place?!
And close behind +Natural?
That really went up!
So it was the art and not the story after all...
It's still trial and error, but if I keep this up...
The general concensus in the editorial department is that PCP's ranking this week was just a fluke.
Then you're not looking at PCP closely enough.
This is bad.
Bad?
At this rate, it'll beat both +Natural...
...and Crow as well.
Ashirogi-sensei is changing his drawing style.
It's even better in the preview copy of chapter 9.
So that's why you drew something different from what we discussed?
Yeah, I changed it after seeing that page in chapter 8 of PCP.
But don't you think that'll make it worse...?
That won't happen.
But Ashirogi-sensei might close the gap after seeing that manuscript.
Akina-kun?
Huh? Where's Miura?
I'm here by myself today.
Zoom out here!
CAW!
CAW! Like this! C-CAW!
Huh? These two...
...Now that I think about it, Hattori said Akina-kun kept asking him what he thought of her as a woman.
Could she be going after Niizuma-kun now?
...No, that's just overthinking it...
You're really working hard on Crow, aren't you?
Yes!
Do you think +Natural will be ok?
What do you mean?
I mean, will it do better than PCP?
I think the next chapter of PCP will beat it in the early results.
...Niizuma is usually right about this stuff...
But.
The +Natural anime starts that Tuesday,
So I think we'll put up a good fight in the final results.
Ashirogi-sensei is changing his style bit by bit starting with chapter 8.
So this page will make Crow even better than PCP!!
I definitely won't lose!
C-CAW!
This is bad... PCP pulled ahead in the early results.
Even with the color pages to celebrate the anime. Crap...
PCP is in 4th, and +Natural is close behind.
But...
Watch out!
It's hatching...
This is pretty interesting...
Yeah, this'll get the kids' votes for sure.
Azuki could have been in this...
I have to get PCP an anime for her sake...
Just like Niizuma-san said...
PCP can't beat this.
Let's make +Natural even more popular!
You're talented, we can do it!
As I thought, this country's food is delicious!
I recommend this pack of clams!
Otters 11 promotional deal:
Buy now and get this limited edition Otters gift!
It's so cute!
Thank you, Hiramaru-sensei!
That's so great!
A limited edition figure! Just seeing one is a treat!
Yes!
Please forgive us...
No! Don't worry about it!
I...I bought this Earl Grey myself, it's the finest there is!
I'm sorry.
I usually drink Darjeeling, so I'm not a very good judge of Earl Grey...
Darjeeling...
Y-Yoshida-shi, please join me in the other room.
Yamahisa.
Isn't the citrus flavor of Earl Grey wonderful?
I like Darjeeling too.
I drink it from time to time.
Isn't the flavor of muscatel delightful?
muscatel is the musky spice flavor in Darjeeling tea.
You're surprisingly knowledgable...
Oh, not especially.
Niizuma-kun, here is next week's issue of Jack.
Why thank you!
Your drawings are amazing...
But you really should do what we agree on...
Roger!
Anyway, +Natural is in 4th place.
When the anime started, it passed PCP.
Did Miura already tell you?
Yes, It was just as I thought.
Is that Akina-kun again...?
Yes.
Has she been coming over often?
Almost every night after my assistants go home.
Niizuma-kun, I know you're both adults.
And I don't mean to sound
coarse but take it easy, okay?
Take what easy?
Besides, I'm an eternal boy. That's why I write shonen manga.
I guess...
That's practically living together!
Idiot! Not so loud!
S-sorry.
But I never thought Akina-kun...
And every night... I'm jealous...
You're her editor, try to take this more seriously!
Come on! Give me a break!
Just get over here!
This really does look like...
Niizuma-san, did you tell them I was trying to persuade you?
I didn't say a word.
Here's the issue with chapter 10 of PCP.
Thanks!
By the way, take a look at Crow.
Crow?
There's no text!
He's telling the story through pictures...
Apparently he redid this as soon as he saw chapter 8 of PCP.
He must have noticed that I'm changing my style...
"Look what I can do with just pictures... How far can you go?"
I feel like that's what he's saying...
B-but, will it be popular?
It's definitely an adventure.
But readers might find something lacking without the text and it might get fewer votes.
He wanted to show me this even
if it meant losing popularity...
What?!
The new Crow got even more votes than usual?
Yeah, I'm surprised too.
I expected it to drop...
But Niizuma was able to make readers find it novel and impressive.
Niizuma's above me in both talent and votes...
But +Natural isn't doing as well as I thought it would.
It's in 4th again this week, but only 9 votes more than PCP's 5th.
9 votes?!
So close!
Starting next week there will be three new series.
But after that, in issue 26...
PCP's 15th chapter will get the cover and color pages.
Color pages?!
Seriously?!
This is our chance to fight!
Let's surpass +Natural!
Okay!
We have to make our manga amazing for issue 26!
I'll start working on the color pages now!
What's going on...
Niizuma-kun and Akina-kun both agree...
Could they be getting married?
Niizuma-kun and Akina-kun?
The two of them as a couple... that's tough to buy.
So you want us to stop them?
I didn't say that.
Does Niizuma-kun agree?
Honestly, it seems like Akina-kun pressured him into it.
But Niizuma-kun seemed pretty sure about it afterward.
I see. Then there's no problem.
T-thank you!
Takahama-san's new series is pretty interesting.
Yeah, the courtroom battle idea
really works as a shonen manga.
Alright! Road Racer Giri!
My champion idea...
I can win with this!
Fukuda-san is amazing...
This is pretty impressive.
Takahama-san's representation
of a courtroom is great!
He must have studied hard.
Ally of Justice started in first place.
But the second chapter really dropped.
We really took it up a notch.
With all these new serializations,
NANDE!? could fall to 11th.
The wording at the end has the same feeling as +Natural.
Fukuda-san and Takahama-san really have a chance.
Well, with all these new series starting up...
Whatever you think, there's only one thing to do.
That's right, we have to do it.
We'll make the best manuscript yet!
Hattori-san?
We've been had.
H-have a look.
Something on the center page?
It's +Natural.
Eh?! +Natural...
W-what is this?
Why is Crow here...
When I struggle toward my dream
Those are the moments I love the most
I can feel our bond and will to fight
Our views overlap and electrify us
Let's improve ourselves, become what we should be
You can see the future in our path
My comrades don't agree with me
Our pride clashes
I can't let it go, I'll follow my heart from now on
I'm prepared
I'll charge right in
Unstoppable Pride
There's no other choice, this is what I love and this is what I'll do
I don't know what tomorrow will bring
But I know once again (just to get by),
We'll do our best
I know you're working hard, but is PCP ok?
Don't worry, Ashirogi-kun is always exceeding expectations.
I've outdone myself.
Next Time: Last and Cipher
Think of a way to fulfill the dream.