Mashiro-kun!
We did it!
PCP's first chapter was #1 in the rankings.
We're getting closer to our dream.
Everything will be alright.
I'm sure it will come true...
Our dream.
Hey, if I could be with you right now
Then I could keep my voice from fading
The goals I've set for myself seem too high to reach,
and I feel like I've lost my way
I'm relying on a broken compass and hiding in someone's shadow
If we keep letting go of what we have to find something else,
then I'm convinced we can never grow up
Never
Willpower and Decision
Are we clear?
I'm going to make +Natural into Jack's #1...
No... Japan's #1 manga.
I won't lose to PCP.
Don't worry.
We have an anime starting in April.
Oh, thats right...
Here,
Have a look at this.
The heroine, Mimiya Sayano,
makes her appearence in episode 16.
These are the four best applicants for the part.
I'll have Niizuma-kun to listen
to a few samples, and you...
This Azuki Miho...
I went to middle school with her.
Eh!? Really?
What a coincidence.
This girl... is Mashiro's girlfriend!
Girlfriend?
Yeah.
She visited him in the hospital...
Azuki Miho...
Mashiro Moritaka...
Takagi Akito...
Ashirogi Muto!
First place for the first chapter!
Off to a good start!
Yeah.
After this we'll have to work hard to keep it up.
About that...
We need to strengthen our characters.
But... Is it too much for her to be good at sports?
For a heroine thats fine!
Sure is!
Who is it?
It's from Miura-san.
Hey Mashiro-kun!
Were you really in middle school with Azuki Miho?
Yes...
Just how awesome was your class anyway?
You two and Akina-kun are writing manga.
And Azuki is a voice actor.
I must admit I'm impressed.
Um...
Why are you asking about Miho?
Because Miho-chan,
Is auditioning to be Sayano in +Natural!
What?! The part of Sayano?
What. You didn't know?
The audition is this next Saturday.
Wish her luck!
Later!
Azuki in +Natural...
Why...
Saiko...
What was that about?
You were talking about Miho?
Yeah...
Why would Miura-san ask
about Miho on the phone?
Azuki is auditioning for the
role of Sayano in +Natural
Sayano?
This girl.
The heroine of +Natural.
This is...
Iwase and Niizuma's manga!
She has an audition next Saturday.
So why did Miura-san call?
Well,
He's the editor for +Natural now.
He was just surprised to learn
that she is a voice actor.
Why would Miho apply for this role?
She needs to play Annojo Mai when PCP gets an anime.
Sayano doesn't show up until later in the series,
But there are no other major female characters.
And she eventually becomes the heroine.
But Miho is your heroine!
She can't do any others!
And the manga is by your rivals, Niizuma and Iwase.
It isn't right!
Mashiro, you have to stop her!
No.
This is a big role.
But she needs to be the heroine in your story...
In order for your dream to come true.
Work is work.
My job is to write manga.
Azuki is working hard to become a voice actor.
If that means playing a role in
Iwase and Niizuma's anime, +Natural...
It can't be helped.
What are you saying?
That isn't right!
Kaya-chan!
What?!
It's not your problem.
Thats terrible!
I'm just thinking of you guys...
I understand how you feel,
But it's not our place to interfere.
Aw...
You can't say that kind of thing in front of Saiko.
Huh?
I'm pretty sure he doesn't want
her to take that part either.
But it's Azuki's choice so he won't stop her.
Why not?
Because he's stubborn.
Stubborn...
I guess I can see that.
Sometimes he has trouble saying what he wants.
Azuki too.
That's true.
Why did she choose that role anyway?
Seriously.
"I can't be in Mashiro's rival's anime",
Is what I would expect her to say.
But she isn't that type.
Yeah,
It's work so she'll try her hardest.
It's her job so it's her decision.
Let's go see her tomorrow and talk to her.
Sure.
Welcome you two!
It's been a while...
Sorry to come on such short notice.
It's fine!
There's so much I want to ask you!
Come in!
A-ask?
I see...
How did you hear?
We happened to hear it
from the editor of +Natural.
Why did you apply for the role?
My boss is the one who
submitted the application.
I see...
Well, you got in.
Yeah.
When is the audition?
On Saturday,
At 1pm.
Where is it?
Near Shibuya station.
What are you going to do?
I don't think you should do it!
What if you actually get the role?
If you get the role of Sayano...
And our manga gets an anime...
What would you do?
That would be the same
voice actor for two Jack series.
They probably wouldn't let you
do ours in addition to +Natural.
What did Mashiro say?
As you might expect,
"It's Miho's job so Miho should decide"
I see...
I know him so I understand the way he feels.
But I don't want you to do it.
Takagi-kun...
There's no guarantee that we
will get an anime right away.
But you're supposed to be
the heroine for our story.
+Natural isn't the only anime out there.
It isn't right to do something that will
keep your dreams from coming true.
Don't be stubborn!
Be honest with yourself!
Kaya...
I know Mashiro would be happy if
you said that you wouldn't audition.
That's right!
If you tell him that I'm sure he'll be relieved.
And wouldn't you be happy if
he told you not to audition?
Right?
You're both so stubborn.
Anyway, you should just avoid
doing any Jack heroine parts.
Well,
Saiko is right to say that
your job is your own decision.
But...
I don't want you to audition if it's
only because he didn't stop you.
...Alright
I'll email him today and ask him about it.
Huh?!
But you already know
what his answer will be!
Kaya-chan.
This is all we can do.
It's up to Azuki and Saiko now.
Let's head home.
Eh?!
But this doesn't solve anything!
It's fine.
But!
See you later Azuki.
Azuki as Sayano...
Dammit!
...Azuki!
Are we too stubborn?
...Are we ... too stubborn?
I don't know.
Yes!
First page is done!
Keep up the good work!
Kaya-chan! Please quiet down!
Eh? Why?
I'm trying to motivate everyone!
You're making it hard to concentrate.
Mashiro-sensei,
Yes?
This panel on the third page...
Something about the angle
just doesn't feel right.
Let me have a look.
You're right...
I'll fix it right away.
Moriya-san is the same as ever eh?
No...
I think something is up this week.
Huh?
I can fix the mistakes I find as always.
But there are more than usual.
Really?
Yes.
Hopefully we can fix everything before we turn in the manuscript tomorrow.
PCP is in second place.
Crow is in third.
+Natural is in fifth.
YES!
Let's meet today at 6pm.
Understood!
+Natural's anime starts next month,
So we'd better not relax.
Second place is fine.
It's a good response.
It is...
But if Azuki plays Sayano in +Natural...
Is that really ok?
The audition is tomorrow...
Saiko...?
Huh? Oh that's fantastic!
Let's keep up the good work!
You forgot to close the copier...
Shoot... I wasted a sheet.
I...
I... told Azuki not to audition if she was
only doing it because you didn't stop her.
W-Why?!
I know it's not my place... I'm sorry.
No... thank you.
The dialogue here is interesting.
But what's wrong Mashiro-kun?
Your art hasn't but up to its usual...
Hattori-san! Mashiro...
I'm sorry,
I'll make corrections now.
I would like to say yes,
But I promised I would bring the
manuscript to a meeting in three hours.
So this should be good enough.
Sorry!
I can do it in two hours!
Let me have some time.
Saiko!
I'll help too... what can I do?
No, your dialogue is already fine.
Fixing this is my job.
If I can't do that I'm not a pro.
Saiko...
Azuki is working so hard for herself.
It isn't stubbornness.
Are we too stubborn?
I respect her and trust her.
If she doesn't back down I won't stop her either.
But was Shujin right?
Am I just forcing the decision onto her?
I don't know.
Mashiro-kun...
That line was so good.
Well, Niizuma-kun?
Did anyone stand out?
Everyone did well.
It's hard to choose.
Then, Azuki Miho...
But!
I don't think we should choose Azuki Miho-san.
Eh?! Miho is no good?
No good at all.
She's Mashiro-sensei's girlfriend.
I don't think he and Takagi-sensei would
like it very much if she were in our anime.
Is that so...
But she is a voice actor anyway.
Anyway don't mention that tomorrow.
Naturally.
Well good luck with the auditions tomorrow.
Good luck Miho!
Thanks.
Well, I'm heading out!
Take care.
Miho...
This might be unnessesary,
But It's important to follow
your heart when you're uncertain.
Being stubborn doesn't help anything.
Stubborn...
The audition...
Thats today.
Yeah.
What will Miho do?
I told you not to worry about that.
But...
The audition is at 1pm.
Really?
I'm so happy!
I'll work hard.
I'll definitely become a voice
actor and be in your anime.
It's so wonderful.
I'll wait.
I'll wait forever.
Mashiro-kun, do your best.
I believe in you Mashiro-kun.
Make our dream come true.
Ah! We're here!
Aren't we early?
Let's audition!
Good day.
Good... day...
Miura-san, what floor is it on?
Let's see...
The second floor.
Roger!
It's been a while...
Ashirogi Muto.
What could that pen name mean...
"A" from Azuki.
"Shiro" from Mashiro.
"Gi" from Takagi.
And "our dreams will come true"...
It means...
Their manga will get an anime.
And I will play the heroine.
That is our dream!
OHO! What a fantastic dream!
Is that why they got into manga?
So,
I came here today to decline the role.
You must be joking...
Hearing that...
Really makes me want to use you!
I'll make Sayano into the perfect heroine.
If you turn down the role
for personal reasons like that.
I won't forgive you.
Consider yourself warned.
I don't care.
Are all women this scary?
Yes...
Scary.
Oh!
Mashiro-sensei!
Let's Go!
Go where??
Let's just get out of here!
Okay!
Wait just a minute!
I won't let you...
Oh!
Mashiro-sensei is super cool!
Leave it to me!
I'll reject Miho-san,
And I won't let anybody complain about it!
Thank you Niizuma-san!
Thank you!
Love wins again!
I did it.
I'm happy though.
Even though I interfered with your work?
I had gone there today
to turn down the role.
We both came to the same conclusion.
We're still on the same page.
And...
You held my hand.
I'm sorry! That...
Sorry... I let go...
I feel like I can rely on you today.
Can't you always?
Well if it's not about manga
you can be unreliable.
And you're stubborn.
So are you.
We may be stubborn but
we're even bad at that.
How many times have we broken our
promise to not see each other.
It was an emergency.
Are you disappointed?
I'm very disappointed in you Mashiro-kun.
Yeah, I didn't want to hold hands
until our dream came true.
You really are the most
stubborn guy I've ever met.
Unforgivable.
Miura-san,
I would like to meet with
you after the audition.
Understood?
Y-yes
Quickly! Begin the auditions!
From Shinjuku I need to
take the Saikyo Line.
And you take the Chuo Line right?
Yeah.
We've only had five minutes together.
Can I go with you to Yakusa?
B-but... I have to work on the
manuscript when I bet back!
I'll just ride with you to Yakusa.
Then I'll go home.
What is this...
Azuki-san is so forward today...
Is it because I held her hand?!
Alright! Let's ride together to Yakusa!
You're really funny today Mashiro-kun.
I-Is that so?
We're supposed to stay away from each other.
But this keeps happening.
Yeah, but I'm happy about it.
It's the next station.
We've been together for 40 minutes already.
I was so happy...
it all flew by so fast.
Bye...
Mashiro-kun...
Next time we see each other...
Let's kiss.
What are you saying Azuki!!
Is this all because I held her hand?!
But how does that lead to kissing?!
This isn't like her!
So let's not meet again.
Until our dream comes true.
...When our dream comes true.
That's just like Azuki!
He can't be like that just from seeing her...
I told you, he's just happy
she didn't audition.
Something else must have happened!
What do you mean?
Don't tell me...
Just watch!
Idiot!
Don't...
Mashiro-kun!
Did something happen
between you and Miho?
I can see it on your face!
Eh? My face! No way!
Tell us what happened!
Oh nothing really.
Liar! I bet you kissed.
Kiss? No way! We didn't kiss!
Tell us!
Hands?
All you did was hold hands?!
That is just like you guys.
What are you, in middle school?
Shut up! We're just taking it slow!
Azuki Miho!
I won't forgive her!
I'll make sure she regrets
leaving my audition.
She'll never have work
as a voice actor again!
I'll drag Ashirogi Muto down!
No matter what it takes!
Now spill all of your ideas.
You know Ashirogi-kun
isn't just fooling around.
They're very serious.
You're on their side?!
Come to think of it, you helped
them make PCP didn't you...
I am +Natural's editor!
I believe in your talent!
Seriously.
Authors should compete with their content.
That's the best help I can offer.
Then give me another idea!
Hattori would have done
a much better job.
Well! Hurry up!
Ok... Where did we leave off last time?
You mean you don't remember?
Sorry!
PCP's third chapter is in fifth place.
+Natural is...
Fourth!
As long as we're above PCP
that should keep Akina happy.
Hattori, whats wrong?
PCP's third chapter did great right?
You should hurry up and tell them.
Yeah... You're right.
Chapter three is in fifth place.
Normally that would be great...
They have six months.
We'll see how it goes until chapter 25.
If their rating is low
by the seventh chapter.
I won't hesitate to cancel it.
After 25 chapters,
If it hasn't surpassed Crow and +Natural...
It will be cancelled.
This is no good.
At this rate they won't surpass +Natural.
We have to keep the rating up.
I have to do something.
When I struggle toward my dream
Those are the moments I love the most
I can feel our bond and will to fight
Our views overlap and electrify us
Let's improve ourselves, become what we should be
You can see the future in our path
My comrades don't agree with me
Our pride clashes
I can't let it go, I'll follow my heart from now on
I'm prepared
I'll charge right in
Unstoppable Pride
There's no other choice, this is what I love and this is what I'll do
I don't know what tomorrow will bring
But I know once again (just to get by),
We'll do our best
Our new serialization has finally started!
But we have some tough conditions!
With our rivals doing their
best, can we pull through?
Next: Every Night and Unite.
We'll have to work hard to reach our dreams!