Good morning.
My goodness... Sit properly while you eat, won't you?
That's bad manners.
There's a number of news items to discuss this morning,
but this is the headline that caught my attention.
"The miraculous pure love of voice actress, Azukyun"
Listeners Cry
Over her
Purity of
Love
Fans of Azukyun
shed farewell
tears over her
marriage
announcement
Her
boyfriend,
the popular
manga
artist
Mashiro
Moritaka
(24),
also called
live on
the phone
Revelation on the Radio
and her confession over the radio.
Pick Up
The promise they made in middle school not to meet until their dreams were granted—
She's a pretty girl, isn't she?
I-I'm going to work.
That's pretty early for you.
It's only 8 o'clock.
I have to do some stuff first, so I'll be late if I don't go now.
Thanks for breakfast.
Moritaka.
I'm not against it.
Against what?
Your marriage with Miho.
M-Mom!
I won't oppose it either.
N-Not you too, Grandpa!
Don't tease me!
I'm not.
You've become a real man, a proper hardworking member of society.
Marriage, huh?
yu
me
Dreams, dreams, dreams, dreams
As soon as I reach my goals, it all falls through again
So why do I run...
...and search in spite of that?
atta
We met after such a long time
watta?"
"Has the mood changed for us?"
So much time has passed
"It seemed like more fun back then"
We've lost so much
I already know that, though
Don't stop screaming, don't stop struggling
rou?
You've done enough for others
I still, still have something I haven't told you yet
Beyond each of my dreams lies yet another dream
Mic and Script
I was surprised too.
It was all over the news when I turned on the TV this morning.
And they called it "a pure relationship," right?
Too pure, maybe.
You're right.
Hey, Saikou.
What?! Enough about the news already—
That's not it.
This Month's Favorite Voice Actor Ranking
Voice actor
FAN MORE
Votes
Namba Kana
Ohtsuki Nanami
Azuki Miho
Majima Saki
Tanaka Mikan
Naka Yoshiko
Miho's rank went up!
I was worried for a while there, but it looks
like last night's broadcast had a positive effect.
Yeah, that must be it!
Miho managed to get her sincerity across to everyone.
Also, it's good for us that normal
people now know about this story.
Even if she does get picked for the part in Reversi,
they'll support her, just like they did on the news today.
Yup!
Can we really say that she got the job with her own skill if that happens, though?
She's taking the audition, so no problem there.
Ohtsuki Nanami
Azuki Miho
Majima Saki
Tanaka Mikan
But based on her popularity and
skills, and the buzz surrounding her,
Azuki's bound to get the part.
You're overthinking this.
Thanks to Azuki Miho, Reversi has an
amazing amount of attention on it right now.
Production and Conference room
Drawing
Post Production and Photographing
We should be able to hit the ground running.
Konaka.
Yes?
Satoru,
you've changed.
You used
to be more kind.
You just
went along
with it?
Ashirogi Mutou
We're going to hold auditions for the role of Naho
and choose the most suitable voice actress, correct?
Of course we're having auditions!
But at this rate, it's practically been decided already.
REVERSI
storyboard
All right, your manuscript looks good.
Thanks.
Weekly Shounen Jack
And also, both Volume 1 and 2 of
Reversi have another print on the way.
Weekly Shounen Jack
Great!
With this, you're selling about 830,000 copies per volume.
Just one more push until you reach
Zombie Gun's number of 1.05 million!
Right!
Anime Adaptation
Confirmed!
Ashirogi Mutou
You really do get more attention
when you have an upcoming anime.
There's that, but recent radio broadcasts have brought about a lot of positive attention.
By radio broadcasts, were you talking about Azuki's?
Yeah.
It seems that there's something in you two that
makes you stronger with each hardship you face.
You're exaggerating.
These two really are something else.
No, Azuki's strength is here, too.
They'll definitely move forward and achieve their dreams.
Right, Hattori?
Wh-What's wrong?
Uh, nothing.
At this rate, becoming Jack's flagship may not be just a dream.
That's what I was thinking.
Really?
Yeah.
The true flagship, huh?
Finally things are going our way!
I'll say.
Right. Everything's going our way now,
so Azuki will definitely get the role of Naho.
Anime Adaptation
Confirmed!
Congrats!
Ashirogi Mutou
Fair and square, by audition.
Well, I have to attend a meeting with the anime staff.
At this hour?
Apparently there's something urgent they need to make a decision on.
Urgent?
Is there some kind of problem?
It's not that big of a deal.
I'll call you as soon as it's over.
And that's our proposal.
It's a pretty drastic one.
Director Ehara has insisted that you let us proceed with this if at all possible.
B-But we can't decide on this without Ashirogi's input.
Of course.
Hattori, I'll leave the arrangements for that in your hands.
Huh?!
A public audition for the role of Naho?
Yes.
We'd like to hold a public audition for the role of Naho on the TV and Internet.
But why?
I proposed it.
First, we will narrow down the
candidates to 20 possible choices.
We'll then hold the public audition,
broadcasting it live on TV and the Internet simultaneously,
and allow viewers to have one vote each in a poll that will decide who will play Naho.
They can't do that!
Azuki definitely won't get the role that way!
Why?
There are still many critical opinions of her on the Internet.
That's even more true of the hardcore Azuki fans. They won't vote for her.
I also have my doubts as to whether this is necessary.
You mean, they won't vote based on her abilities.
No, that's precisely why we must do this.
Upon hearing that radio broadcast, I too was touched by your mindset.
That's why I must say this:
In this situation, even if Azuki Miho
wins the role through her skill alone,
in most people's minds, the
audition will merely be a formality.
That can't be!
I see.
This is what has been bothering me.
If we simply ride the changing tide of public opinion...
Mashiro, I...
will pass the audition.
Even so, I...
There's nobody who wants Azuki Miho to play the role of Naho more than me.
And there's nothing I want more than for her to get the role by her skills alone.
If you say that skill will be the only thing judged at these public auditions,
then I'll agree to it.
I'm telling you, there's a possibility they won't vote on skill alone.
That's right, Mashiro. You should think carefully about this.
No matter the result,
it's still better than people saying that
Azuki got the role through her connections.
Though there may be voice actresses
who surpass her in popularity and skill,
Azuki will rise above them.
No... If she doesn't rise above them, then she doesn't have what it takes to play Naho!
They said it's a public audition.
News
flash!
Media
Volume 4 "Turn"
Anime
starting
this fall!
Minadori Naho's
voice actress is...
Up to the open auditions!
Azuki Miho's going to win no matter what, anyway.
Yeah, there are some complicated situations going on with that.
Anonymous is desperate
Naho's voice actress will be decided in an open audition, right?
You betrayed us, Azuki Miho, you deserve punishment!
I really want to see how this will turn out.
Anonymous is desperate
They're busy flaming each other in the Azukyun thread, like usual.
Who cares? I'm gonna vote for Ohtsuki Nanami anyway.
Oh, you're a Nanamin fan?
It's just a big popularity contest anyway.
What are you frowning at?
What's this?
REVERSI Minadori Naho Voice Actress Poll
Valid votes
Option
st
nd
rd
th
Graph
Nanba Kana
Ohtsuki Nanami
Tanaka Mikan
Majima Saki
Azuki Miho
Arijima Aki
Votes
REVERSI Minadori Naho Voice Actress Poll
Miho's in 5th...
It's just a fake poll put together by
voice actress fans for the heck of it.
REVERSI Minadori Naho Voice Actress Poll
It's not related to the real poll at all.
Oh, good.
Hey, don't look at such misleading stuff!
Okay. I'm sorry.
If everyone thought and acted the same as I... as Satoru does—
Hey, wait until I say you can come in.
Sorry, Sis.
You don't look sorry at all.
What is it?
I was just wondering how many more times I'll be able to come in like this.
Wh-What are you saying all of a sudden? It's not like I've gotten the role yet.
This is when it counts.
This is a good luck charm for success in
studying, but it'll work for this too, right?
Thanks.
Oh, and it's dinner time.
Tada! For "winning"(katsu), we have tonkatsu, tonkatsu sandwich, katsudon, katsuo, and a big chickwin!
And some pasta for "passing"!
Geez, Mom. You're so superstitious.
And even when Dad gets home,
there's no way we can eat all this.
Sorry.
You don't look sorry at all.
This is all I can do for you.
Do your best tomorrow.
Mom...
Hey, Saikou.
Hmm?
For a middle schooler to dream of becoming a manga artist or a voice actress,
and actually make that a reality is a really hard thing to do, don't you think?
Yeah, I guess.
What's this all about?
Well, when you think of it that way, the dream you and Azuki share is impossibly hard to achieve.
Tomorrow, Azuki will stand before that microphone of dreams.
It's really amazing.
The microphone of dreams, huh?
According to that line of thought, we should be happy just to have gotten as far as we have.
A manga artist, a voice actress.
How many people have wanted to become either one, and have given up already?
What's with that?
It sounds like you're trying to tell me not to get depressed if she fails.
That's not it.
I believe she'll get the role.
I'm just reaffirming how amazing it will be to achieve that dream.
It's really amazing.
And like, what comes after is the best.
Are you teasing me or something?
It's Azukyun!
Do your best, Azukyun!
I can't believe you actually showed up, what with all your connections!
You betrayed us!
Go, Azukyun!
Don't mind them.
Right.
Open auditions
For actresses
Satoru.
Good morning.
I can't believe she showed up.
I wouldn't have.
It's going to be decided by the author, anyway.
Yeah, she's his girlfriend, after all.
What? That's pretty unfair.
Miho!
Are you okay, Namba?
You always catch me at my worst.
But I definitely won't lose to you in today's audition!
Yes. I'm looking forward to it.
Yeah, let's both do our best.
Good morning, Ms. Gouda!
Good morning.
Hello.
Oh, you are Azuki Miho?
Yes.
I am grateful to you for creating such a stage.
All I have to do is read my lines like normal, and I can win the role with all eyes on me!
That's exactly right.
Oh, Nanami.
It's been a while. I'm honored to work with you again.
Same here.
But I never thought you'd try out for the role of Naho.
I was also surprised to be chosen as one of the candidates.
I suppose it means I'm still needed around here.
That's right. You have to keep at it, Ms. Gouda.
Good to see you again, Namba.
And you.
Now everyone, let's play fair and have a good audition, okay?
Yes!
You decide who plays Naho!
Open Auditions
for the role of Minadori Naho!
The Reversi public audition!
Open Auditions
for the role of Minadori Naho!
It's finally starting!
Yes. In this program, you'll be able to vote for
the actress who will play the role of Naho in the anime Reversi, which will start this fall.
It's begun.
Later on, we'll tell you how to vote.
Now, let's begin—Or so I would like to say,
but first, please watch this informational video that will outline the plot of the manga.
And that's how it's going to work.
Open auditions
For actresses
Um, can I ask a question?
Yes?
The broadcast is about to start. Hurry up!
Uh, yes!
Would the first three candidates head to the studio?
The rest of you, please wait until you're called.
Number one, Tanaka Mika.
Thank you for your consideration.
Once again, you're all by yourself in the classroom this late?
So she's not just cute.
What is "Weiss"?
Thank you.
Editorial Department
Shounen Jack
Jack SQ
X Jack
"Oh, sorry"
"Huh? Satoru? No idea."
aaaaa"Oh, then  he probably went home by him
"Satoru... Staying alone in the classroom till late again?"
"Eh? What is 'Weiss'?"
Thank you, Tanaka.
It was a refreshing performance.
Yes. I could really tell that she was a pro.
On Air
Oh, Namba is up next.
Number 2, Namba Kana. I'll be
playing the role of Minadori Naho.
I hear she's the most popular one
among the younger voice actresses.
Thank you for your consideration.
And she's pretty skilled to boot.
Good morning, Satoru!
There's some parts of yesterday's math homework that I don't understand.
She's not the most popular for nothing.
Satoru, you're so nice. Not only do you let me borrow your notes,
Yeah.
but you also explain things until I understand them.
Huh? Satoru? I don't know.
Oh, then he probably went home by himself.
That's Gouda for you. She's excellent.
Satoru, you're all by yourself in the classroom again?
Yes.
What's wrong? You won't go home with your friends anymore.
Or with me.
And lately, you've changed.
You used to be more kind.
This lady is good.
Everyone is really good.
If everyone thought and acted the same as I... as Satoru does,
Will Miho be okay?
Of course she will!
Right?
the world would be a much better place.
Yeah.
Thank you for a passionate performance.
They're all really good. It's so hard to pick just one.
Mashiro...
Do we really have to wait till
our dream comes true?
Will you...
Will you keep waiting for me?
Now, Mashiro is the one waiting for me.
Next, Azuki Miho.
Your turn.
Okay.
Each and every word I'm about to perform
are words leading to my dream.
Number seven, Azuki Miho.
I will be acting the part of Minadori Naho.
Thank you for your consideration.
She doesn't have the script.
Then, please go ahead and begin.
It must be because she intends to move around while she acts.
Good morning, Satoru!
There's some parts of yesterday's math homework that I don't understand.
Satoru, you're so nice. Not only do you let me borrow your notes,
but you also explain things until I understand them.
She's really refreshing!
And this is a voice I've never heard Miho use before.
Yeah!
Your face is getting redder, Satoru.
I'm sorry. Thanks for teaching me this.
Azukyun is really good!
Anon in live chat
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Amateurs may not pick up on it.
Are you a pro or something?
Anon in live chat
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Are you a pro or something?
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Are you a pro or something?
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Are you a pro or something?
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Are you a pro or something?
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Are you a pro or something?
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Are you a pro or something?
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Are you a pro or something?
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Are you a pro or something?
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Are you a pro or something?
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Are you a pro or something?
Azukyun is really good.
But amateurs may not pick up on it.
Anon in live chat
Are you a pro or something?
I'm an amateur, but I think she's good.
See, even amateurs can tell.
No, it'd be near impossible to win against Nanamin.
On Air
Huh? Satoru? I don't know.
Azuki Miho is good.
Oh, then he probably went home by himself.
She's not bad.
Satoru, once again you're all by
yourself in the classroom this late?
Huh?
What is "Schwarz"?
That line was wrong.
Anon in live chat
What if she forgets her lines?
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
What if she forgets her lines?
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
Anon in live chat
What if she forgets her lines?
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
Anon in live chat
What if she forgets her lines?
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
Anon in live chat
What if she forgets her lines?
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
What if she forgets her lines?
Anon in live chat
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
What if she forgets her lines?
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
What if she forgets her lines?
Anon in live chat
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
That's wrong?
Anon in live chat
What if she forgets her lines?
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
What if she forgets her lines?
Anon in live chat
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
What if she forgets her lines?
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
What if she forgets her lines?
Anon in live chat
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
That's wrong?
What if she forgets her lines?
Anon in live chat
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
That's wrong?
What if she forgets her lines?
Anon in live chat
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
That's wrong?
What if she forgets her lines?
Anon in live chat
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
That's wrong?
What if she forgets her lines?
Anon in live chat
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
That's wrong?
What if she forgets her lines?
Anon in live chat
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
That's wrong?
It's not Schwarz, it's "Weiss"!
Anon in live chat
What if she forgets her lines?
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
That's wrong?
Anon in live chat
What if she forgets her lines?
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
That's wrong?
Anon in live chat
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
What if she forgets her lines?
Anon in live chat
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
That's wrong?
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
Anon in live chat
What if she forgets her lines?
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
That's wrong?
Anon in live chat
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
What if she forgets her lines?
Anon in live chat
Damn she's cute, too bad she has a boyfriend.
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
That's wrong?
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
That's wrong?
Anon in live chat
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
There go her dreams.
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
That's wrong?
Anon in live chat
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
That's wrong?
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
That's wrong?
Anon in live chat
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
She said "Schwarz"!
Anon in live chat
That's wrong?
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
That's wrong?
Anon in live chat
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
There go her dreams.
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
That's wrong?
Anon in live chat
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
There go her dreams.
Anon in live chat
She said "Schwarz"!
That's wrong?
Anon in live chat
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
There go her dreams.
Anon in live chat
That's wrong?
It's supposed to be "Weiss"!
Anon in live chat
There go her dreams.
Sometimes you say things I don't understand.
What's wrong?
You won't go home with your friends anymore.
Or with me.
And lately...
You've changed.
You used to be more kind.
You just went along with it?
What do you mean?
If everyone thought and acted the same as I... as Satoru does,
then the world would be a better place.
It's not too late.
We can remake it.
"Normalcy" and "common sense" are just shackles imposed by the people who run the world.
Thank you.
Th-That was some splendid acting.
Yes.
The mistake in the lines will have an impact on the vote.
Director!
What's wrong, Konaka?
We have a problem.
A problem?
Miho's acting was great!
It was way better than everyone else's!
Yeah!
We're sorry to interrupt the broadcast,
but Director Ehara has something to say.
Go ahead, Director.
I would like to explain something
about Azuki Miho's performance, which we just heard.
In the script where "Weiss" was originally
used, she said the name "Schwarz" instead.
What? Miho made a mistake?
However, this was our own mistake.
Their mistake?
We made the script based off of the magazine, Weekly Shounen Jack.
But in this section, there was a misprint by the magazine,
and it was corrected from "Weiss" to
"Schwarz" in the compilation volume.
The editing department just informed us of this.
Indeed, having "Weiss" there would seem strange for anyone who read the manga closely.
Since Azuki followed the original work in her performance, this will not count as a mistake.
That's such a relief.
Of course, the people who used "Weiss" will not be penalized.
However, we would prefer it if those who have yet to perform would use "Schwarz" instead.
The fact that they noticed a mistake in the script isn't the issue here.
What's more important here was Azuki Miho's acting.
We will now resume the audition.
The 20 candidates have all finished.
It's over.
That was tiring.
And now, what you've all been waiting for.
We will now begin accepting votes.
You have one hour from now to enter your votes.
For those watching on TV, press the D button on your remote.
Miho was really good.
But I don't think I did any worse than her.
Azuki Miho... I underestimated her.
Huh? Is that true?
You're too loud!
Azuki Miho's script copy didn't have comments
written on it. It looked like it hadn't been read at all.
I'm sure Ashirogi told her what part it was going to be ahead of time.
That's why she knew it was "Schwarz" instead of "Weiss"—
Do you really think Azuki's performance and attitude was that cheap?
Most probably, if you gave her any page number from the manga,
she could perform Naho's lines from it at the level of performance you saw.
Do you understand?
Yes.
However, a competition is a competition.
I don't intend to lose to anyone.
It's now time!
We received 191,728 total votes!
The announcement at last.
Thank you for all your votes.
A heroine will be born from one of you.
Who has won the role of the heroine?
And now, we will make the announcement.
The winner of the role of Minadori Naho, the heroine of Reversi, is...
This person!
Naka Yoshiko
Ohtsuki Nanami
Azuki Miho
Kitani Mai
She did it!
Azuki
Miko
With an overwhelming lead, Azuki Miho lands the role!
She did it!
Now she can get married!
Now then Azuki, please come up to the stage.
I'm so glad! I'm so glad!
Saikou, don't be so quiet!
Celebrate a little!
Saikou!
He's frozen stiff.
Mashiro, are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm so glad.
Yeah.
Everyone.
Congratulations, Azuki.
I hate to say it, but after that performance you gave I hold no grudge for losing against you.
That's...
Without a doubt, you have won the role
today based on the strength of your skill.
Please believe that.
Good luck with the Naho role.
Congrats, Miho!
Work hard on our behalf, too.
Thank you.
ro...
Why, I wonder?
Whenever I am close to fulfilling my goals, all effort becomes fruitless
We walk ahead, hold each other, and with little things
we support each other to reach what we promised
When we lack confidence, we put a hand to our heart
and reread the pages we assembled into a story
They lead up to today and continue into the morrow
We will always be ourselves
tto...
until the day that our dreams come true
Next Time
Preview
It's finally the last spurt!
I have no regrets about the path we've chosen.
How It Should Be and
How It Ends
Next time: How it Should be and How it Ends
We'll run through it all with our dreams!