Moritaka! How long are you going to keep Takagi waiting?
Sorry! Just a little longer!
Just tell him to go on ahead.
You've got no time to eat breakfast, right?
It's okay, I'll buy something on the way.
Really. You need to eat something before leaving.
Huh?
We're already seniors, huh?
Time just flew by.
Yeah, especially after starting our serialization.
Hey, what are you gonna do about college?
College, huh?
Well I did make that promise with my parents, so I need keep that in mind.
If TRAP  becomes a really popular manga, I may not go...
Our seventh chapter was 13th in the rankings, though...
There's no sense in rushing it.
And we already decided, right? We're going to continue with our current style.
All right, I'm done.
But you still have some left.
I'm full already.
Saiko, you've lost some weight since we started the serialization.
Yeah, my pants are pretty loose now.
But every minute spent eating is a minute wasted.
Let's go.
Yeah!
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Comedy and News
Oh, there it is!
I'm in the same class as Mashiro!
Mashiro Moritaka
Miyoshi Kaya
I'm in Class 3, huh.
Sorry, Takagi.
I couldn't be in the same class as you...
Oh, doesn't matter.
Eh?
Even if we're in different classes, we see each other every day anyways.
Takagi!
Editorial Department
Shounen
Jack
Jack SQ
TRAP 's in 12th!
It's up one rank from the early results!
And last week's case-concluding chapter got 10th, too.
At this rate...
Nah, that won't happen.
The new serializations start next week.
You've done nothing but sigh lately.
Ah, sorry.
Speaking of which, you haven't said a word about TRAP.
Well, you're  the editor.
That's cold. Aren't you worried about them?
I do worry.
It's okay to continue to push it as a mystery, right?
Probably, yeah.
What do you mean, "probably"?
I-I'm sorry. I'd feel more at ease if they had a better ranking.
I don't want them to be overlooked just because they have less experience.
If experience led to popularity, the rankings would be ordered by the authors' ages.
You're right! So what leads to popularity?!
Good sense, I guess.
G-Good sense...
Um, but isn't good sense something you're born with?
Huh? Where are you going?
For a smoke.
Good sense, huh.
In other words, there's only a paper-thin difference between a romanticist and a humanist.
I don't get it.
What's with the "humanist" thing, anyway? You're an otter.
Yes, I'm an otter.
I could forgive you as a human, but as an otter, I cannot!
Otters is pretty wordy, but it's really popular.
Yeah.
TRAP  is wordy, too... I wonder what's so different?
We also think that both Otters  and TRAP  are different from normal Jack fare.
Is it better to have more jokes, after all?
If so, then you just have to put jokes into TRAP.
But TRAP  isn't a gag manga.
Otters is a story manga too, though.
Oh, for real?
Yeah.
Well, comparing manga in the same genre can be difficult.
I think you should stick to the mystery conventions for TRAP.
But you could make it a bit more lighthearted.
Oh yeah, Miura said something similar.
Lighthearted, huh.
But that's pretty hard.
You need the sense for it.
Are you saying I don't have a sense for jokes?
Hmm... your face is pretty funny.
Please, just shut up already.
Yeah, yeah.
But it is pretty hard.
Saiko.
Miura's coming at 10, right?
Yeah.
Six more hours.
All right, I've decided.
Decided what?
I'm going to go out and buy as much comedy software as I can.
I've already thought about criminal psychology, so now I'll study humor.
If I do that, maybe I can figure out how to add in some lightheartedness.
I'll save the receipts.
Study humor, huh?
That's just like Shujin.
He says some pretty stupid stuff sometimes, but I really like how he works so hard!
What? You're researching humor?
Yes. I wanted to calculate the right amount of lightheartedness and fun to put in...
That's great, Takagi!
We're in sync!
Huh?
I also went around to as many bookstores as I could and bought all the books that had "Famous Lines" in the title!
Top 100 Famous Conversations
Study the conversations of the famous!
Wow, this many?
Thank you so much!
I was thinking of studying other genres after comedy, too!
But what gave you the same idea?
I thought of it after looking at Otters 11.
The manga's art is bad, but it's got good dialogue sense.
If you atone for your sins,
they will be forgiven.
I'm going ahead with that assumption.
Is living fun?
It's kind of pointless, but somehow, it's funny.
Polish your dialogue!
Takagi, you quickly put what you learn to good use.
Sunny Sunny Tale
If you do that now, we'll definitely rise in the rankings.
Let's make your next story with that in mind.
Yes!
All right, let's have our meeting.
Please go ahead.
You can't just plagiarize them, though.
Those two are getting so serious just to raise the ranking slightly...
You have to study them hard and make your own style.
I understand.
Then let's start with this page.
I have to improve my art, too!
Yes.
All right!
KIYOSHI Knights took the top ranking in the early results!
If this keeps up, the next team leader will be...
Yuujirou.
Don't get cocky just because KIYOSHI got the top spot.
Come on, it's not like that at all.
Don't worry.
Your face doesn't match your words.
Why isn't Miura telling us the ranking of the eighth chapter?
I can only assume it must be a ranking that's hard to say.
And I'm afraid to ask him myself.
Ugh, this sucks.
If this keeps up, we'll really need to rely on the dialogue from chapter 11 onwards...
How's that? We can't use it as-is, but...
I'll use it as a reference.
I've kind of figured out the basic rules.
Okay. I hope the rankings of chapter 11 onwards will go up with this.
So... our ranking for chapter eight was that bad, huh?
No, right now it's 9th.
9th?!
Since it still isn't official, I didn't want to tell you and have you celebrating too early.
Why did it go up?
Ah, KIYOSHI fell to 2nd place in the official ranking.
So close, Yuujirou.
But it lost the #1 ranking by a margin of 6.
That's passable, isn't it?
Yoshida, you're smiling.
The official ranking is still 9th place!
Is that so?
Even though new manga started their serializations!
Don't look so upset.
If their ranking went up even a bit, shouldn't you be happy?
Yes.
But why did it go up?
Detective TRAP Serialization Storyboard
Chapter 11 Revised Version
Figure it out for yourself.
Ah, yes.
Oh, hideout door placed 1st in the official ranking!
One Week Later
Well, the first chapter is especially well made.
The ninth chapter of TRAP got 8th place! It rose another rank!
Well then, I'll announce the official ranking of the 10th chapter.
A Week After That
Yes.
6th place!!
We did it!
It went up again!
So I guess that means for the next story, there was no need to polish the dialogue.
What are you talking about?
We have to aim even higher!
We were right to trust in Shujin's stories after all!
You're right!
Damn you, Ashirogi!
How dare your 10th chapter surpass my 3rd chapter!
Pen Attack!
Understood, sir!
Commencing the attack!
Take that, TRAP !
Yasu, you're fired.
We did it! Our second chapter is 5th in the survey!
I'm getting really pumped up somehow!
Sensei, you're bothering the neighbors! Please calm down!
Huh? Where's Hiramaru-kun?
Hiramaru Kazuya
No
Soliciting
Well, he said he was going on a trip or something...
Please don't look for me
Ashirogi's ranking went up, as I thought.
Unfortunately,
right now I'm in
serious mode
Yeah...
That reminds me...
I think Ashirogi will become my rival.
They had the same eyes as a super energetic manga protagonist.
Fukuda, Nakai, and Aoki were all serialized, and they're all trying hard.
Drawing for Jack just got a lot more fun.
I guess so.
However, the 10th chapter placed 6th.
Why? We haven't started revising the script.
Isn't it obvious?
It's because the case was resolved well!
It's getting established as a genuine mystery!
Oh, speaking of which...
I couldn't give these to you without checking the contents first, so it's taken some time but...
T-These are...
Yes, they're all fan letters addressed to Ashirogi Mutou.
You'll notice if you check the postmarks, but there are many more recent ones than from the beginning of your serialization.
This may support what Mashiro said about TRAP  being established as a mystery.
Awesome!
Are these all fan letters?
Yeah!
But now it feels like I'm under a different kind of pressure...
It's all right.
Chapter 14's storyboard is great.
Maybe we'll make a huge jump in the rankings with this!
Really?
The way he brilliantly solves the mysteries is really cool.
On top of that, there's definitely much more wit in the dialogue.
Mr. Takagi, since chapter 14 seems fine, please look over the summary of the short novels I read this week.
Oh, thank you.
I worked hard and read five!
Five? That's great!
Shujin, come here a minute.
Hey, can I take a look at your fan letters?
Don't scatter them around.
I know, I know.
What?
Shouldn't we be paying Miyoshi as an assistant, or something?
No, it's fine.
She's doing it because she wants to.
R-Really?
What are you two whispering about over there?
Oh, we're just talking about how you're such a great girl.
Right, right... and we were thinking of expressing our thanks for your help every day.
Thanks.
What? What happened?!
All right, we've expressed our thanks, so let's revise the storyboard!
Yeah!
You guys sure are motivated.
Well, yeah.
I'll think of something even better for our next series.
Go for it, Mr. Takagi!
And I'll support you even more!
Yeah, leave it to me!
Shujin and Miyoshi are giving it all they've got.
Oh, how reliable!
I know, right?
I should find a way to do that with my art.
Huh?
It really is difficult...
Wow, Mashiro's art is really something.
Mashiro.
You haven't been sleeping in school lately, so when do you sleep?
From about 5 AM until the last minute, at 8 AM.
Are you serious?
Actually, we may be in trouble with chapter 14.
Huh? Is the story no good?
No, I'm behind schedule because of stuff like the composition being too stiff.
Will you be okay?
I can make it if I stay up all night.
I won't let it cause problems for everyone.
Don't push yourself too hard. We actually have until Monday to turn it in.
Hey, great news! Chapter 11 is coming in at 7th place in the early rankings!
Manga
KIYOSHI Knights
Detective TRAP
7th place?! Really?
This means it wasn't a fluke that chapter 10 got 6th place!
This is the real thing.
I-It's Nakai.
Yes.
What is it?
Will you rewrite the storyboard for chapter six?
Why?
I think the main outline is good,
but there should be some more action.
The panels need to be flashier.
But Aida said it was fine.
Will you trust me more than him?
Expand on the action scenes and split the chapter into two parts.
Also, the readers might get tired of the dense dialogue.
Please be aware that this is a shounen manga.
Our 11th place ranking for chapter three isn't that great.
Please! Do it for us, for hideout door !
Okay, I understand.
I'll try doing what you suggested.
You are trustworthy, Nakai.
T-Trustworthy?
I trust you when it comes to manga, at least.
Should I ad-lib that part?
No, Sugita will follow up.
Oh, you're right.
Let's get started!
Okay!
An email? From who?
Azuki.
What did Miho say?
I have some unpaid work in the anime "Tomboy Ninja Squad". From about ten minutes in, I voice characters like the dango shop owner.
She got another part.
Awesome!
She also mentioned that she went to a post-recording session of the anime version of Jack's SKET DANCE.
Huh?
Just as a guest role, it seems.
SKET DANCE, huh?
They've gotten ahead of us.
I wanted Miho to make her Jack debut in an anime version of TRAP.
But it's proof that Azuki's been working hard.
So it's only right that I should congratulate her.
You're right. She did work hard for this.
But this is great. It seems like all of us have luck on our side.
Yeah, you're right.
Takagi, you said something cool!
I guess so.
Azuki's trying her best.
We'll aim higher as well!
Sorry, I fell asleep!
I thought so, since you weren't back when I woke up.
Don't make me worry.
Crap, it's already 7!
I haven't penned this in! I still have three pages that are only rough sketches!
And the assistants will be here at 4!
Sorry, Mom, but please call the school and tell them I'll be absent!
What are you saying? Go to school like you're supposed to!
P-Please! I'm really in trouble!
I haven't skipped school even once since becoming a senior,
so please!
Hey, Mashiro didn't come to school today...
He said he fell asleep after we left.
Really?
He's penning-in pages right now.
He's tired. He needs to rest.
Well, something like this happened during our serialization practice run with Hattori.
Chapter 15
Monday
Tuesday
Wednesday
Thursday
Friday
Saturday
Sunday
Monday
Tuesday
I'm sorry for missing the deadline.
Sorry.
It's fine. With this level of quality, there will be times when you're late by a day or two.
Maybe your ranking will rise even more!
You think so?!
I'll definitely give you the next one on Friday.
All right! Keep it up, you two.
Yes.
Lady Megumi...
There she is again!
Shut up, Miyoshi. That's getting annoying.
"Lady Megumi..."
That manner of speech... could you possibly be...
Is this... a surprise chance?
Isn't that Sugita's voice? He's so cool!
I don't know that guy.
Um, could you possibly be Takemitsu Shinzou?
We're also heading towards an anime adaptation, bit by bit!
I thought so! Actually, I was waiting here...
They're head to head! It's a tie!
Your 14th chapter and CROW are tied for 3rd place!
Tied with CROW... with Niizuma Eiji?
An anime adaption isn't just a dream.
CROW and TRAP  are tied?!
Even though KIYOSHI got 6th place, I can't celebrate!
6th place is still great, you know.
It seems your decision to change things was the correct one.
It suddenly jumped to 8th place.
Show it to me before Aida from now on.
Understood.
Looks like I've become less popular. How about I take a break for now...
I won't let you say that 9th place isn't popular.
Now draw.
Is it tied?
Yeah.
Though it's probably good news for you.
Yes, it is.
But...
But?
I don't want to lose to Ashirogi.
Honestly, I never thought we'd tie with CROW.
It's amazing!
Don't underestimate me.
Oh yeah, Hattori did tell the lead editor that we'd overtake Niizuma in three years.
He did?
It's been just about three years since that workshop.
We can make his words a reality.
No, surpassing him will be our thanks to Hattori!
Yeah, let's do it!
That's the spirit! We can do it!
I got us a front page color spread for the 20th chapter!
A color spread?! Awesome!
Your first volume goes on sale that day.
That shows just how much is expected from it.
The first edition of volume one is getting 100,000 prints, after all.
Why only 100,000?
It's rare for the first volume of a newly serialized manga to get that many prints!
The first volume of Otters 11 is being released on the same day, and it's only getting 60,000.
We've got more than Otters?
Well, 150,000 volumes of CROW  were printed recently, though.
150,000?
But the way things are going, TRAP  will need a second printing soon.
Really?
Yeah! We're aiming for 500,000 prints.
Surpass CROW !
No, while we're at it, let's aim for a million prints! And then an anime adaptation!
A million prints would normally happen after  it gets an anime.
Oh, really?
Of course!
If it's made into an anime, it'll be more well known, right?
I see.
Come on! Let's get to inking!
Is inking fun for you?
I want to try applying screentone, too!
Leave that to Ogawa.
Huh?
Hiramaru?
Hello there.
It smells nice.
Thank you, but it's instant.
Just the fact that a girl prepared it puts me at ease.
Anyway, you guys are really something!
Is this your office?
Ah, yes.
It must be hell, going through high school while keeping up with a serialization.
Well, we are splitting the art and the story.
I see. Niizuma is inhuman for being able to do both.
Y-Yeah...
I've been pissing blood.
B-Blood?
You should see a doctor...
I did.
But all he did was give me medicine and send me away.
They wouldn't hospitalize me!
If you were hospitalized, you wouldn't be able to draw your manuscript, right?
I want to rest.
Mashiro, can I talk to you for a minute?
Sure.
Mr. Ashirogi
I apologize for the sudden fax. I wish to warn you of a possible house call from Hiramaru, author of the currently serialized Otters 11. He has made a habit of escaping to other authors' houses, and has already inconvenienced three of them. If he shows up at your house, please contact the Shounen Jack editorial department immediately. Thank you for your cooperation.
Yoshida, Weekly Jack
If you lose popularity, that's it for you!
This fax just came in...
I had no idea. Isn't this job scary?
We should probably contact him.
I already did.
This is my dream job, though.
Hiramaru seems like the type who'd vent his stress like that.
Dream, huh? It's a nightmare for me!
I see.
This is Yoshida from Shounen Jack.
They've come to pick me up.
Well then, see you later.
"See you later"?
He seems rather used to it.
Well then, we'll get going.
We're counting on you tomorrow, too.
Mashiro, you've been redrawing your art for the past few chapters, haven't you?
The art has greatly improved.
Really?
Yes.
We've assisted you with various parts, but this rate of progress is stunning.
That's Mashiro for you!
I'm also happy to be working on TRAP !
Thank you!
The official ranking of chapter 15 was 6th place.
6th, huh.
And CROW holds steady at 3rd.
He's got another lead on you.
But we'll turn it around with chapter 20's front page color spread!
Yeah, that's the spirit!
Here.
I did a sketch of the volume's cover!
Yeah, this looks great!
It'll look even better once you color it in!
No one can compare with Mashiro's one-page shots!
5th place! We beat TRAP  again!
Yeah!
Yasu, it's all thanks to you.
Then give me a 2,000 yen raise for each good idea!
Actually, I was getting help from my friends and paying them 500 yen per idea!
But I really want 1,000 yen for myself!
You... you subcontracted my profit margin?!
I like that! I'll give you a raise of 3,000 yen!
Ooh, that's Godly Fukuda for you!
Chapter seven's at 10th place...
What's with that rough sketch?!
It's too vague!
S-Sorry.
11th place.
Hiramaru Kazuya
No Mr.Yoshida
No
Soliciting
Your first double digit rank.
It's time to get serious and do this work.
I am doing it!
Enough to piss blood...
All right, I get it.
The next time you turn in a manuscript, I'll take you out to a place with cute girls.
Mr. Yoshida, I'll give it my all.
I'll try my best this time.
That'll work for two weeks.
Chapter 18 UP
School Anniversary Day
Chapter 19 UP
Assistants in
The 16th page is done.
I should make it at this pace.
Oh, now I've done it. Miyoshi will get mad.
Takahama!
Hello.
Takahama, do you always get here this early?
Yeah.
Since we're headed the same way, you don't mind if I walk with you, do you?
Not really.
Mashiro's really amazing.
He seems really shy and cute.
He's probably dating someone.
What?
I think it's the girl who had a part in SKET DANCE.
Hello.
Oh, he's not here.
He's probably in the bathroom, or something.
His shoes are here.
It looks like he fell asleep.
He's dead.
I'm just kidding.
He's breathing.
Hey, you! There's good jokes and bad jokes—
But it's weird that he didn't wake up when you screamed.
Y-You're right.
Mashiro?
Mashiro, snap out of it!
Mashiro!
kurikaesu nibuku detarame na sekai
In this world, every day is dull and full of nonsense
urusakute mimi wo fusaida
I cover my ears, trying to mute the noise
nan no tame ni kizutsukeatteiruno?
Why do people hurt each other?
zetsubou ni fushita kokoro no sumi
In the contradictory, overlapping shadows
orikasanaru mujun no kage ni
on the recesses of my heart, fallen into despair
mune wo itamenagara
While carrying this pain in my chest,
ashita wo yumemireruno?
can I really dream of tomorrow?
tooriame no ato ni mitsuketa niji wo motte
Remembering the rainbow I found after the rain,
me wo tojiru Fly with me donna nagai yume mo
I close my eyes; come fly with me into my dream
iroasenai kimi to nara
If I have you, who shines so strong
egakidaseru kienai niji mo
I can envision an everlasting rainbow
deaeta ano hi ni mita tsukiakari desaemo
And even remember the moonlight of the night we met
utsuhidasu nandodemo
I can picture them... countless times
nandodemo
over and over again
Oh no, Mashiro collapsed!
Next Time
Preview
It was just impossible to keep up while still in school!
But that's his dream, and our dream.
Next time on Bakuman:
Sickness and
Determination
Sickness and Determination.
Can you stop a dream that's already been set in motion?