Whaddya think? Great, right?!
Yes, it's interesting!
For sure!
So cool!
What's going on?
Ashirogi submitted a new one-shot storyboard.
It's really interesting!
Hmm, let me see.
"Reversi..."
Reversi
Ashirogi
What kind of manga is it?
There's this black demon and white demon, and—
It's good, so just read it!
It can't possibly be better than Niizuma's Zombie Gun, though.
It's good!
And this battle between the protagonists is really well drawn!
Yes.
It's different from every other Ashirogi work
because they managed to make it into a standard battle manga.
And it's up against Niizuma's latest, a story with a zombie protagonist who fights against humans.
A standard battle manga with unorthodox elements.
Ashirogi's pushing their unorthodox style into mainstream!
Niizuma's incorporating an
unorthodox style into his mainstream!
So in other words,
these manga were born from the awareness
that Niizuma and Ashirogi have of each other?
They're a positive influence on each other.
I see.
Which will win?
It has to be Niizuma.
It's not about winning or losing!
Even if they both get picked up, they
won't be published in the same issue.
But if they get published one after the other...
Hey, you guys!
Yes?
We need three one-shots, and yet I only see two on my desk.
Come on, keep them coming!
Yes, Assistant Vice Chief!
For crying out loud...
yu
me
Dreams, dreams, dreams, dreams
As soon as I reach my goals, it all falls through again
So why do I run...
...and search in spite of that?
atta
We met after such a long time
watta?"
"Has the mood changed for us?"
So much time has passed
"It seemed like more fun back then"
We've lost so much
I already know that, though
Don't stop screaming, don't stop struggling
rou?
You've done enough for others
I still, still have something I haven't told you yet
Beyond each of my dreams lies yet another dream
Weekly and Monthly
Congratulations.
Reversi will be published in Issue 20, which goes on sale on April 17.
Thank you!
Yes!
We're sorry for pushing it on you.
We wanted Chief Sasaki to read it before he left.
No problem.
He was surprised when I handed
him a storyboard out of the blue,
but there's no reason not to
submit a manga as good as that one.
A standard battle manga that only Ashirogi can write.
I'm expecting great things from it.
Yes!
Can you put Mashiro on the phone?
This is Mashiro.
Niizuma's one-shot will be published in the issue before yours.
It's inevitable that your works are going to be compared as standard battle manga.
Yes.
The art quality, the readability of movements, the feeling of speed,
the double-page highlight scenes, and the panel layout variety.
Yes.
Sounds like I don't need to tell you anything.
Work hard and come up with a good manuscript.
Yes!
Niizuma
Eiji Ltd
Niizuma, Zombie Gun will be published in Issue 19!
Roger!
This is my first step towards world domination!
In the issue after that, Ashirogi's one-shot will be published.
Oh! I can't wait to read it!
This time though, Ashirogi's challenging you with a standard battle manga.
It isn't dark and disturbing?
No, it actually is. It's a pretty
ghastly standard battle manga.
Nice one, Ashirogi Mutou.
A ghastly standard battle manga! Nice!
Don't wear yourself out.
We still have plenty of time.
I know.
But I want to rank better than Eiji's one-shot.
Text received
Azuki Miho
From Azuki?
She got a main role!
What?
Azuki Miho
Mon
I've gotten a new role
I got the main female role
of Young Kick's Impromptu 12.
It's the soccer club
manager, Ai!
I got the main female role
of Young Kick's Impromptu 12.
It's the soccer club manager, Ai!
That's a pretty famous soccer manga!
Yeah.
But we've been beat.
Azuki's ahead of us now.
Let's make sure her first major role in a Jack work is from ours!
Yeah.
We'll turn Reversi into an anime and write in a lead female role for Azuki.
Mashiro Moritaka
Re: I've gotten a new role
Congratulations!
I'm even more motivated now.
I'll definitely catch up with you
and make our dream come true!
We'll make your future lead role in our anime
Mashiro Moritaka
Re: postscript
We'll make your future lead role in
our anime the most popular role that
voice actress Azuki Miho has ever
played! We'll make your future lead
the most popular role that voice
actress Azuki Miho has ever played!
the most popular role
that voice actress Azuki Miho
has ever played!
Yes. I'll be waiting.
The sample copy of Issue 19.
Niizuma
Eiji
New
one-
shot!!
45 pgs with
color spread!
Zombie Gun's on the front?!
This is the first time I've seen that done for just a one-shot.
It was the decision of our new Chief Editor.
It shows just how much he's expecting from Niizuma.
Special treatment?
Does that frustrate you?
Then you must surpass him.
The same Niizuma Eiji who ended CROW
after getting first place 20 weeks in a row!
Zombie Gun got first place?!
I knew it would get a lot of votes, but not this many.
Niizuma Eiji's really something else.
Well, he is aiming to become the best in the world.
Are you serious, Yuujirou?
Call me Team Leader!
Er, sure... Team Leader.
692 votes?!
It's the most votes a one-shot has ever gotten.
Eiji is just out of this world.
Yeah.
This is what Niizuma Eiji has to be.
Don't forget, our results aren't out yet.
So, please make a serialization storyboard for Zombie Gun.
Put everything you have into it and make it as good as you can
in the time you have until the committee meets.
Roger.
You seem quiet today.
Aren't you happy?
I'm happy and all pumped up.
Okay, then.
52 pgs with color spread!
Ashirogi
Mutou
New author's
one-shot
Part two
Th-This is...
That can't be right.
This is just...
W-Well?
Final results for Issue 20: Reversi is in 1st,
with PCP in 4th.
First place!
He said a new record's been set for a one-shot.
But Zombie Gun did that just last week!
Well, he said Reversi went past Zombie Gun's 692 votes,
setting a new record with 694 votes.
Wow!
Awesome!
I told you it was gonna be fine!
No you didn't, you liar!
I didn't? Well, I always thought we'd do pretty well, at least!
Hattori Akira
I'm gonna call Kaya!
I'll text Azuki, then!
Just you wait!
Huh? Where'd my phone go?
Who would've thought the record would be broken in a week?
They told me to take Zombie Gun to serialization.
The deadline for storyboards is next week,
so please don't lose motivation over this.
Is Reversi getting serialized too?
Well, Ashirogi still has PCP,
and it'd be hard for them to pull off two series at the same time.
If Zombie Gun's going to be serialized, then you want Reversi to be serialized as well.
I knew you'd say that.
I'll tell the higher-ups how you feel about it.
Thank you!
Oh, and we're done with the first
chapter of the serialization storyboard!
Would you like to take a look at it?
This is good.
It's even better than their one-shot.
It could be better than PCP,
or even more!
What's wrong, Yuujirou—I mean, Team Leader?
Niizuma told me...
To aim for the world and yet end up
losing by two votes is just ridiculous.
That's why I won't submit a serialization storyboard yet.
Or so he said.
What?
That's such a waste!
Team Leader!
This is Reversi's serialization storyboard.
Hey, give me a break here!
Niizuma and Ashirogi both doing two
series is completely out of the question!
Then, it'll be down to deciding which one is better: Reversi or Zombie Gun.
No, it won't!
In Jack's state right now, obviously Niizuma will be given priority!
It's not fair to give preferential
treatment to the author you're editing for!
Ashirogi can't even handle two weekly series in the first place!
Yes, they can!
How can you be so sure of that?!
Because there's two of them!
They already said they could do it.
Cut it out, you two.
This storyboard is good, no doubt about it.
We can't afford not to publish this.
They're already doing PCP!
Then, make them end PCP—
It's not that simple!
PCP's so popular that they're going to start a "Middle School" saga next.
Then serialize both—
Well, that might be too difficult.
He worked so hard on TRAP that he wound up in hospital, after all.
We can't let him push himself like that.
What is it, Heishi?
I have something to ask you.
What?
It's about Reversi's one-shot.
What was your intent when you had it published?
That doesn't matter. It's in your hands now, Heishi.
Then, as the Chief Editor of Weekly Shounen Jack,
Hisshou
Jack
I have a matter to discuss with the Chief Editor of Hisshou Jack.
Since we haven't heard anything yet,
I guess that means they didn't submit it to the serialization committee.
It's Hattori.
Hello.
What do you mean, "Is Hisshou Jack okay?"
What?!
Reversi's getting serialized in Hisshou Jack?!
Yeah.
It was the Chief Editor's decision that if Reversi was a monthly series, they could manage it
Best in
alongside their weekly series, PCP.
Reversi will be serialized...
Best in
the World
52 pgs with color spread!
Ashirogi
Mutou
New author's
one-shot
Part two
Yuujirou.
I'll submit a serialization storyboard for Zombie Gun to the committee.
You will?!
I've just realized it.
It was conceited of me to say I'd make the best manga in the world. I was wrong.
My opponent isn't the world.
It's Ashirogi!
Zombie Gun's opponent is Reversi!
SPIN!
Huh? Not PCP?
Because Reversi will be...
It doesn't matter what magazine it'll be published in!
Because Reversi is clearly better!
I was prepared to work myself to
death if we had two weekly series,
but I'm actually relieved that we'll be
running it monthly in Hisshou Jack instead.
It's the best possible outcome for us.
Right?
Yeah!
Best possible outcome, huh?
I'll try to introduce you to your new
editor for Reversi as soon as possible.
Oh, right.
If we're in Hisshou...
...that means the editor will be someone from Hisshou.
Of course.
I know it'll be tough for you to have two series,
but don't let it affect PCP, okay?
Of course not!
We'll work as hard as ever on PCP!
Good.
Hattori seemed kinda sad.
Yeah. To be honest, we wanted to do it with him, too.
It sounds pretty selfish to say that, though.
I know.
But...
I guess it didn't work out this time.
I know!
I know I shouldn't let myself get too attached to an author or a manga!
But... I wanted to be the editor of Reversi.
It'll be an amazing work!
It'll become a mainstay of Weekly Shounen Jack!
I know that cuz I've been with Ashirogi so long!
Niizuma said that, too.
That Reversi is clearly better than PCP.
Right?
That's jes' how good of a manga those two made!
We're just low men on the totem pole, though.
We have to follow whatever the boss decides.
I said I already knew that!
I'm just sayin', I wanted to do it...
Dammit...
I wanted to do Reversi.
Really, I should have come out to greet you.
Sorry for making you come all the way here.
I'm all over the place with starting up this magazine.
Nakano is now the Assistant Chief Editor of Hisshou Jack.
It's heartening to know that the Assistant Chief Editor will be serving as our editor.
Let's work well together.
Yes.
Hisshou's lineup is still weak.
We're counting on Reversi.
We're happy to be serialized in it.
We look forward to working with you.
At this rate, we'll only get one new manga serialized.
There's not much we can do about it.
The only good one out of this batch is Niizuma's Zombie Gun.
You're right.
But just one...
Maybe we should wait until next time and just serialize three at once.
What are you talking about?
We need to get out Zombie Gun as soon as possible.
Why don't we do Reversi?
What are you saying now?
We were concerned about Ashirogi doing two weekly series, so we gave it to Hisshou.
That's not my point.
Let's give PCP to Hisshou, and publish Reversi here instead.
W-We can't do that.
That's right! It's already been decided—
No, that might actually work.
It'd make us look better if we had two new series to publish.
We can't do that just for the sake of appearances.
Hisshou, which has a broader readership, can cover a greater range of material.
It's a better place for PCP.
Reversi got more votes than Zombie Gun.
And also, Niizuma is more focused on Reversi than PCP.
I want it to compete with Zombie Gun in Weekly Shounen Jack!
Hattori wants to edit Reversi more than he does PCP, as well.
Did Hattori say that?
I can tell without him saying so.
Because I'm his team leader!
Huh? You're in the middle of the serialization committee, right?
I'm telling you, get up here!
Well, I'm having a meeting with Ashirogi right now.
Bring Ashirogi to the committee with me?!
Why us?
Go.
You should go.
Let's get right to the point,
Hattori.
What do you think about Reversi going to Hisshou Jack?
Well, I think it's good that Reversi will get published.
And you, Ashirogi?
O-Of course!
We're grateful for that!
That's not what we mean.
Which one do you want in
Weekly Shounen Jack: Reversi or PCP?
"Which one"?
Just say what you truly think.
Which one do you want to do weekly?
S-Since they asked to serialize Reversi in Hisshou,
I don't really...
No.
Hattori, spit it out!
Please let me do Reversi in Weekly Shounen Jack!
Akira, you too?
I want to do Reversi weekly as well!
Please!
PCP will be serialized in Hisshou Jack,
and Reversi will be serialized in Weekly Shounen Jack!
Th-Thank you...
Sorry, it's gotten so late already.
It's fine. I'm just glad we got to hear your true feelings about it.
Me, too.
Mashiro, Takagi.
You have to make Reversi a mainstay of Weekly Shounen Jack.
No, it's already a manga that will definitely become a mainstay!
Yes!
We understand!
I'm sorry for making that decision without consulting you.
No, it was a good one.
Reversi's potential can best be harnessed in a weekly format.
It'll be more interesting for PCP to be in
Hisshou Jack with its greater degree of freedom.
Hisshou
Jack
The team leaders seemed to feel the same way.
Especially Yuujirou.
He's becoming more like a team
leader than I expected him to be.
Thank you very much!
It's too early to thank me.
If Reversi is canceled within 10 weeks,
they'll lose their spot in the magazine.
I'll turn it into the top manga!
For sure!
No.
The one at the top's gonna be Zombie Gun.
I won't lose to you!
That's my line.
Zombie Gun and Reversi.
I'm looking forward to the future of Weekly Shounen Jack.
Yes.
Heishi.
You've completely settled into the role of Weekly Shounen Jack's Chief Editor.
Thank you.
Oh!
So Reversi's going to be serialized in Weekly Shounen Jack now?
Yeah!
That'll really get you going, right?
Yes!
Finally!
Finally...
Huh? Ogawa?
He said that one of the manga he's working on is ending.
So, he's going to start helping us out again.
Ogawa, huh?
He's pretty reliable.
Yeah.
If we're doing two serializations, we'll have to pick up our pace.
But isn't this studio too small to fit in yet another person?
Nah, we can manage if we move the sofa.
Besides, I don't want to leave this studio.
You're right.
Yeah.
So, I decided to buy this place from my grandpa.
What? I'll pay for half of it, then.
It's okay.
This was my uncle's studio, after all.
I want to buy it.
I'm off.
Moritaka.
Come here.
What is it, Grandpa?
Are you still seeing that young lady?
Well, kinda.
I see.
Why did you ask that all of a sudden?
I'm going to give this to you.
Take it.
A notebook?
It's Nobuhiro's diary.
Huh?
Well, it's not quite organized enough to be called a diary.
It's about his feelings for a certain lady.
Huh?!
That's okay! I don't want something like that!
It's fine, I tell you.
Just read it at least once.
Um, well...
It's pretty interesting.
Interesting?
So my uncle sat next to Azuki's mom in middle school...
I will marry
Haruno Miyuki
Until that day, I'll write about
feelings towards her in this notebook.
And I think it would be great if both of us could
read this notebook together and laugh
when we get old.
Are these are the kinds of things he thought about?
Well, I guess he had a great imagination, in a sense.
No, this wasn't just his imagination.
He was really trying to do this.
It ends here.
Right...
He received a letter from Azuki's mom,
saying she was marrying someone else.
Haruno
sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year,
too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno
sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year,
too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year,
too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year,
too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year, too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year, too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year, too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year, too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year, too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
...or just write like 10 letters and get her to pick
which one she wants?...
???
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year, too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
...or just write like 10 letters and get her to pick
which one she wants?...
???
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year, too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
...or just write like 10 letters and get her to pick
which one she wants?...
???
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year, too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
...or just write like 10 letters and get her to pick
which one she wants?...
???
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
Haruno sent me a letter on
my birthday
this year, too. She must like me back!
My plan is set
for for now...
I also have to decide
what to say to her
when I propose...
...or just write like 10 letters and get her to pick
which one she wants?...
???
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
This is the last entry.
Manga artist... romance.
The things he couldn't do, and the things he wanted to do...
Gotta become a first-class
manga artist as soon
as possible!
I'll do them!
I'll become a mainstay of Jack!
ro...
Why, I wonder?
Whenever I am close to fulfilling my goals, all effort becomes fruitless
We walk ahead, hold each other, and with little things
we support each other to reach what we promised
When we lack confidence, we put a hand to our heart
and reread the pages we assembled into a story
They lead up to today and continue into the morrow
We will always be ourselves
tto...
until the day that our dreams come true
Next Time
Preview
Finally, we get two series!
Let's make both of them good!
Reversi may not last that long, though.
Next time: Drawn Out and All at Once
Drawn Out and
All at Once
Which dream will we choose?