Komane... zumi!
Well, it's a ripoff, so it's no good.
Don't do it, then.
Then, the next gag.
Kaya, hit me here.
Salmon Pink!
You prepared that?
Boring.
I know!
Next.
This is one I thought of based on Tanto's hairdo.
It's not a wig!
How's this?
Well, it's...
I dunno about that...
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Love and Denial
Editorial Department
Shounen
Jack
Jack SQ
V Jack
Akina Aiko confessed to you?!
Well, during our meeting yesterday...
What's wrong?
You haven't fixed the areas I pointed out.
That isn't like you.
I'm sorry.
Please let me know if something is bothering you.
If it's something I can help with, I will.
Am I appealing as a woman?
Er, what do you mean by that?
Do you see me as an attractive woman?
Is what she said.
And how'd you respond?
I said something like, "Boys your age would surely find you attractive".
You're an idiot!
You should take advantage of that to make her write better!
No way!
I can't use a 19 year old girl's feelings like that.
As I person, I can't...
But you, of all guys?
I could understand if it was Niizuma, though.
Those two don't suit each other at all!
Speaking of Niizuma, he said he's not reading Tanto.
I dunno about that.
That's  your catchphrase?
Uh, yes.
It actually becomes a habit.
It means something when you catch yourself doing it, right?
But, it's...
I dunno about that.
L-Look!
I-Indeed...
Okay, let's try putting it in several times per week.
Okay!
The seventh chapter got 12th place.
Thinking up the gags took a lot of time this week,
Even though it's stable,
so I didn't have time for the storyboard...
it's definitely not a good rank.
What?! That's not good.
Well, you can turn it in by Monday at the latest.
But you've always had it by Friday.
I'm sorry.
I'll definitely have it by tomorrow.
Oh, right.
Hattori told me to tell you something.
Natural  is already being fought over by the TV stations.
An anime adaptation?
Anime, drama,
and even offers for a live-action film, it seems.
Wow.
It's not even at the 10th chapter yet.
And... it seems like Niizuma's not reading Tanto  anymore.
Eiji, who said he was a fan of Ashirogi...
So the fans think Tanto  is no good?
Mashiro!
Does this mean that we'll be
finishing on Monday from now on?
Um, I think that's how it will go for a while.
Do you still need weekends off?
No, I'm good.
Orihara.
When a manuscript comes in, look over the whole thing first.
Oh, right!
Neither of them even giggled.
Akito.
Are you not sleeping tonight, either?
Yeah.
I dunno about two all nighters in a row...
I dunno about that...
Our rank isn't going up.
Ever since we added "I dunno" in the 10th
chapter, we've been at 12th place or worse.
W-Well, you just put it in.
Something like this will only show results if you're persistent!
Right.
Thanks for your work.
Saiko, how long can you wait for the storyboard?
I have some breathing room from the double issue,
but I'd say no more than a week.
Right.
Then it might be two to three days later than usual.
Fine, but wouldn't you have to put off the vacation we planned for your wedding ceremony in June?
If you don't leave yourself enough time...
I know.
My livelihood is depending on it, so I have to work hard.
Sorry, but I'm leaving early.
Yes, Miyoshi—I mean, Miss Takagi Kaya?
Akito just called and said he was coming home now...
He's been working all night for three days now.
You were hospitalized before, so I'm worried about him.
I get it.
I'll tell him not to push himself too hard.
Shujin's working his hardest.
But...
Because...
Yeah,
she's not a very cute
elementary schooler
But I guess taking them overseas
from a young age is spoiling them.
Meanwhile...
_
Metaru
Laboratory
Ah,
you're
going too
What!!
If you wait, we'll
definitely take
you to Hawaii
They'll take me
to Hawaii!
It seems that Niizuma doesn't read Tanto  anymore.
Dammit!
I can't think of anything!
Is he planning on going without sleep until our wedding in two days?
Crap!
Azuki Miho
Miho?
Sorry, are you still awake?
Yeah.
Only two days left!
I wanted to talk to you one more time before your vacation.
It's hardly a vacation; only three days and two nights at a hot spring.
In elementary school, you said you'd never get married!
Wedding Ceremony
Oh, did I say that?
You did!
Right.
Miho, back then...
Akito, Kaya, congratulations on your marriage!
I clearly and fondly remember when Akito and
Mashiro Moritaka came to me for a consultation.
It's been 5 years since then, and they have
produced one wonderful work after another...
I'm so jealous!
So why isn't Akina here?
Hiramaru, you're being annoying.
..they handed me The Two Earths.
Next, they aimed for the Tezuka Prize with A Hundred Millionth.
Then they debuted in NEXT with Money and Intelligence,
and finally got their first serialization in Jack, Detective TRAP.
From reading these works, I know these two have talent.
One day, they will become famous manga authors who will support Shounen Jack.
I believe in this.
He didn't say anything about Tanto.
Akito is a lucky man to have a wife like
Kaya and a partner like Moritaka Mashiro.
Eiji, and now Hattori...
I can only think they're disappointed in us.
Um... ah...
Akito, Kaya... th-thank yo—er, I mean, congratulations!
Hattori.
What is it?
Tell me up front.
Tell you what?
Aren't you really thinking that Tanto
doesn't suit us, and that we should quit?
You're serialized.
You can't quit.
If you do, it will cause a fuss.
You know what it means to be a new author with
two series that have been canceled quickly, right?
It won't go over well with Miura, either.
I don't even think Takagi will take it well.
Furthermore, Ashirogi is already labeled as a troublemaker.
If you do something that selfish, your contract may even be cut—
Tell me clearly!
Tell me to quit!
Saiko!
What?
Mashiro?
Mashiro, this is a celebration.
If you insist on having this conversation, let's take it outside.
Yes, let's.
Saiko and Hattori...
What's going on?
From his grim expression, something must be up.
The groom mustn't leave his seat.
Well, but...
I know.
You're not our editor, so you won't give us your opinion directly.
Are the rules of the editing department that strict?
If you have something to say, just tell me directly!
Are you going to do whatever I tell you?
You and Takagi just have to follow the path you chose and believed in!
That's what you've always done, right?
How far are you going to go to avoid saying what you think about Tanto?
You could at least give me some advice!
Just tell me whether you think it's good or not—
It's not!
Personally, I don't think it's good.
Ever since I saw your manuscript five years ago, I've believed that you can surpass Niizuma Eiji!
Let's get back to the ceremony.
Thank... you.
It's close, but I'm glad we chose Kinugawa.
We can take it easy.
I wonder what that was all about when Saiko and Hattori left the ceremony together.
That again?
When I ask Saiko, he kept saying "It was nothing".
Anyway, let's enjoy our honeymoon!
All right?
Oh, I like this show!
This may be a bit abrupt, but do you read manga?
Yes, I read a lot of it.
One Piece, Naruto, Inumaru Dashi, and CROW!
That's the one!
Our guest today is the creator of CROW
with an successful anime to boot,
manga author Niizuma Eiji!
Tada!
No way!
Hello?
Saiko!
Turn on the TV!
Huh?
Channel 2!
What's this all about?
We'd like to ask you what goes on behind the scenes of manga production.
Glad to answer.
Isn't it difficult to work on two
simultaneous weekly serializations?
Aside from sleeping, eating, and
going to the bathroom, I'm drawing.
So you're always drawing?!
Yes. I'm happiest when drawing manga.
Now then, we've drawn up what a
weekly schedule looks like for Niizuma!
Not just his work, but he himself is popular!
But still, aren't there times when you just want to toss aside your manuscript and have fun?
Is there a weak part of yourself that you're fighting against?
Like, you're your own worst enemy?
No, my enemy...
My rival...
is Ashirogi Muto!
Ashirogi Muto?
They are the manga authors I like most, and my rivals.
You don't know them?
Er, no, I'm sorry.
I'm not knowledgeable enough.
Well then, the next question...
What kind of music do you like?
Mashiro?!
Dammit!
Mashiro?
Azuki.
I want to quit Tanto!
What do you mean?
Tanto's no good!
It has no future!
What do you mean?
You want to quit it because of the promise you made me?
No.
Of course I want to fulfill the promise I made to you.
But right now, I want to quit...
because I want to aim higher!
I want to compete with Niizuma Eiji!
Niizuma Eiji was on TV.
He doesn't read Tanto  anymore.
Even though he said that, he just
clearly stated that we're his rivals!
Mashiro.
I also think you should quit.
If a person you think of as your rival will go that far for you, then you should quit.
I mean, isn't it frustrating?
Have you told Takagi yet?
I can't tell this to Shujin.
He's married and has to support his family.
I can't say "Let's quit!"
I can only say
that if it were me, I would quit.
And if we were married and you said you
wanted to quit, I'd agree without a second thought.
Thanks.
I'll talk to Shujin when he gets back from his vacation.
I want to thank you, too, Mashiro.
You've confided in me.
And by phone, too.
Right. We said we'd talk to each other about anything...
Yes.
We're maturing.
Our love is growing.
Talk to you later, then.
Try your best, and cheer up!
I love you.
Niizuma can speak better than I expected.
He might actually be popular.
He might be in demand for variety shows.
Two serializations and public appearances, huh?
It's kinda complicated.
Huh?
Well, there's no point in comparing them,
but yesterday, I got a phone call from Nakai's mother.
The guy who went back home to the country?
She thanked me again and again for looking after her son.
It was tough. He only got one serialization, after all.
It's all good if it sells, but we can't take responsibility if it doesn't.
We're in positions that control the direction of people's lives.
We should always keep that in mind.
You want to quit?!
Quit Tanto's serialization?
Yeah.
It's true that our ratings haven't gone up,
but we don't have to quit...
Before that, we should work on improving it.
That would be fine, too.
Then which one is it?
I can't be selfish.
I know you want to keep going.
I also think we can't surpass Eiji with Tanto.
I felt pathetic when I heard him declare that we were his rivals.
That was the final blow for me.
Hearing from Hattori that we could surpass Eiji didn't help, either.
Let's quit.
Quit? Are you serious?
I'm serious.
Actually, you were the one who said it first.
Don't act so surprised.
Have you thought about Kaya?
You're married now, Shujin.
Kaya said that you and I make the decisions about work.
I definitely didn't want to lose to Iwase when Tanto  was serialized,
but now losing is just a normal occurrence.
It's too pathetic.
But I don't think they'll let us quit just like that.
Huh? If the author really wants to quit, they have to let us, right?
Wha—
What're you saying?!
This isn't funny!
But we really feel like there's no future in this.
I'm at my limit for adding humor.
Miura, please tell us.
If the author wants to quit, will they let us?
Well, I'm saying...
I should take this to the higher ups...
Don't be ridiculous!
You wanted to be able to draw in the hospital, and now you want to quit?
There's a limit to selfishness!
Listen.
Tanto 's got the kids' vote.
It's important to us.
Even at its current rank?
Yeah.
You'll have to put in some work to get the ratings up,
but it's not in danger of being canceled.
The question is how to get it higher.
They say they're at their limit for jokes.
That's your  job!
A manga was canceled so that Tanto  could get in.
You should have more pride in your work.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
May I ask the Chief Editor for his opinion, as well?
Just give up.
You'll only get scolded.
Then I'll go get scolded.
Hey—
Saiko!
What is it?
I would like to quit the serialization of Tanto.
If you want to quit, then quit.
I have no need for authors who throw aside their work in the middle of a serialization.
You won't draw for Jack anymore.
If you are prepared for that, then you may quit.
Figured as much.
What's wrong?
Were you not prepared for that?
Prepared, huh.
What should we do, Shujin?
Should we stay fixated on Jack and keep going... or quit?
Hey, what are you saying?!
Of course you'll keep going!
I'm sorry, Saiko.
I want to beat Niizuma Eiji and
Akina Aiko in Jack, at the very least.
I also want to win against Niizuma Eiji.
But I can't do that with Tanto.
Is this talk about Niizuma coming from his declaration of you as his rivals on TV?
Yes!
Do you think you can win against him if you quit Tanto  and write another work?
It isn't that I think we can win,
it's that I want  to win!
Chief Editor, this is my fault!
Since they debuted, I've kept saying that Ashirogi Muto can overcome Eiji,
and again, recently, at Takagi's wedding...
Ashirogi Muto can overcome Niizuma Eiji?
Niizuma's proclamation, then this...
It seems there is a problem within the editing department.
Takagi, do you think that you can surpass
Niizuma Eiji with a work other than Tanto?
I don't think it's possible.
Excuse me, but...
I believe they have the talent to do so,
but they haven't been able to utilize it yet.
Vice-Chief!
Of course, I believe they can as well.
If they don't go mainstream.
Me, too!
I'm asking Takagi.
We'll beat Niizuma Eiji!
So please let us end Tanto !
Shujin.
The contract is for the full year, right?
How many more serialization committees are there?
Three more: the beginning of August, the
middle of October, and the end of December.
If you let us quit,
then Mashiro and I will definitely submit something to one of those committees
that can compete with Niizuma Eiji!
If we can't, then you can end our contract!
We won't draw for Jack anymore!
You said before...
that saying you're not being allowed draw what you like is admitting that you have no talent.
Then we'll submit something to one of those three committees
that the entire editorial department can approve of!
Is that fine with you, Mashiro?
Yes!
I see.
But it's not something that falls under my responsibility.
Your editor is Miura.
Miura, please!
Please!
Miura!
Let's win against Niiuzma!
Thank you!
They did it.
But... they raised the bar too high for themselves.
Now they really...
might not be able to draw for Jack any more.
toomawari wo eranda no wa
The reason I chose to take a detour
motto kimi wo suki ni naru tame datta n da
was to fall ever deeper in love with you
boku no namae yobu sono koe wo
I have a feeling I've always known
zutto zutto shitteta ki ga shita n da
what your voice sounds like when it calls my name
boku no yubisaki de egaita
With my fingertips I drew
subete no sen wa kimi ni tsuzuku kakehashi sa
many lines that make up a suspension bridge leading to you
Show me the way
Show me the way I'm sure our path
bokura no michi kitto
Believe in your way
your way connects us without any turns
hitosuji ni tsunagari
Show me the way
Show me the way It leads to the place where we promised
yakusoku no basho e tsuzuku
Show me the way
Show me the way I will never give up
akirametari shinaide
Believe in your way
your way Raise your gaze
sono hitomi wo agete
Show me the way
Show me the way and see that we're certain to meet again
bokura wa massugu deau sa
Next Time
Preview
Money
Intelligence
Appearance
We need to make our next work
Money
Intelligence
Appearance
Money
Intelligence
Appearance
Money
Intelligence
Appearance
something that can compete with Niizuma Eiji!
Money
Intelligence
Appearance
Money
Intelligence
Appearance
Money
Intelligence
Appearance
Money
Intelligence
Appearance
How about a cute female
protagonist who marries a manga author?
Nope.
Selfishness and
Advice
Next time on Bakuman:
Selfishness and Advice.
Sometimes detours and byways become the path to your dream!