Detective TRAP....
Honestly, I thought they would have a tough time in Jack,
but their ranking has settled down nicely on the surveys.
It looks like we all work well together.
Mashiro, snap out of it!
Hello.
Mashiro!
What?!
A-And now..?
Okay... okay...
All right, I'm coming now.
Miura!
What's wrong?
I-It looks like...
Mashiro collapsed.
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Sickness and Determination
It's been one thing after another for him.
The volume and the front page color spread...
Mashiro's been having to deal with more and more responsibilities,
but when we were together, we got too excited, and I didn't realize his condition.
For a high school student, it's probably the worst thing.
There's no point in agonizing over it.
Since he regained consciousness and was brought to the hospital,
he should be okay for now.
What's important right now is checking up on his condition.
Everything else comes after that.
Yes...
Yakusa Municipal Hospital
Miura!
Hattori!
Is everything all right?
We don't know yet; they're still examining him.
No, I meant you.
I-It's like you said... It's impossible to do this while still in school, after all...
Damn!
Thank you for taking care of my son. I'm Mashiro Moritaka's mother.
Examination Room
I apologize!
I-I apologize!
How can we possibly apologize for letting things get to this point?
It's all right... we still don't know what his condition's like.
And this is something my son chose for himself.
Who is the boy's guardian?
I am.
Please come in.
Doctor... is Saiko— is Mashiro okay?!
Takagi, calm down!
I'm sorry, he and Mashiro are a pair of manga artists,
and we're from the publisher.
Please let us know his condition as well, if you can.
I understand.
Everyone, please come in.
Thank you.
Katou, you go back.
But...
Leave the rest to me.
Yes.
So basically, you need to remove a portion of his liver?
Putting it simply, yes.
Surgery...
That can't...
Shujin.
Saiko!
Bring the manuscript here.
I've got to draw here in the hospital.
The front page color spread is the greatest chance we've been given.
I'll draw it here.
Okay.
I'll bring it here!
Wait.
Doctor, he's supposed to rest, right?
Of course.
He's tending towards malnutrition.
He needs plenty of rest.
He'll also need to be hospitalized for three months after the surgery...
Three months...?
Saiko!
H-Hey, what are you doing?
I'm going back to work.
People don't die so easily.
You won't die now, but your condition will worsen if you keep pushing yourself!
This isn't an illness you can recover from naturally.
You need to stay hospitalized and undergo treatment...
Then let me draw here!
We're being serialized in a weekly magazine.
For now, you need to rest...
You can't rest on a weekly publication!
Saiko...
I don't want to go on hiatus! Not when we've finally gotten popular...
I can't rest now!
Mashiro, we appreciate your determination.
But shouldn't curing your illness come first?
You of all people should understand.
This is different from a long-running manga taking a break!
Mashiro... is it true that you had only two more pages of chapter 19 to pen-in?
Miura!
Yes, probably.
For now, we'll leave 19 to the assistants to finish up.
We'll reconsider what happens after that.
Is that acceptable?
I want to pen-in the characters myself.
How long will it take you?
Three to four hours.
But I want to take a day to do the color spread that goes with it.
How's that, Doctor?
Stop this!
My son isn't a manga-drawing robot!
S-Sorry.
I was just trying to persuade him, but I got caught up in it...
It'll be fine, ma'am.
While he's in the hospital, I will
take responsibility and make sure he rests.
Thank you.
Surgery...?
Yeah.
I have to consult the higher-ups before deciding what to do next.
I'll contact you tomorrow.
I understand.
Yes, talk to you later.
Mashiro will have to be hospitalized for a while, it seems.
They'll tell us more tomorrow.
It's a hiatus, then.
That's...
Probably.
Even so, there's no point in us getting depressed.
What we should be doing now is finishing up the 16 pages of chapter 19 that are penned-in.
Let's make this the best manuscript so far.
Yes!
Damn. Why is Saiko...
Shujin, it's me.
Saiko?
Is it okay for you to be making calls?
I asked them to let me go to the bathroom by myself, at least.
More importantly, bring the manuscript to the hospital.
What?
I'll draw in the hospital.
I definitely won't let it fall behind.
We're pros, after all.
Saiko...
Kitashita Juuichi
Mashiro Moritaka
My hospital room is empty aside from one old guy.
I think I can do it without the doctor noticing.
It's much easier than Nakai doing it in the park!
Saiko, I'll be waiting.
I'll wait until you've fully recovered.
So...
What are you saying?!
We can't afford to drop the ball on this now!
If we stall for three months, we'll lose the readers we finally pulled in!
Don't you get it?
But...
I'll undergo the surgery.
That's the only day I won't be able to draw!
It's a color spread!
It's our chance to surpass Eiji!
What about repaying Hattori?
TRAP starts from here!
Saiko!
I get it.
I'll bring it tomorrow.
O-Okay. Visiting hours start at 3 PM.
At 3, okay?
Yeah.
Editorial Department
Shounen
Jack
Jack SQ
Mashiro said he wants to do the penning-in of the characters himself.
Right?
Yes.
But that'll be tough, realistically speaking.
And not only that; we have to rethink serializing a high school student.
Publish the finished 16 pages.
As for the other two pages,
we'll publish one of them with the announcement of the hiatus that begins next week.
Yes sir.
And listening to your story, it seems that Mashiro can't even touch a pen in the hospital.
Keep visiting the hospital and monitor the situation as much as you can.
It should be obvious, but the health of the author comes first.
Follow the doctor's orders, not the will of the author.
I understand.
It's definitely a safe surgery, right?
Yeah.
Are you absolutely, positively, 100% certain?!
They said it's a simple surgery, so there shouldn't be any problems.
But...
The surgery is two weeks from the 10th.
He'll be hospitalized for at least three months.
We'll probably be on hiatus during that time...
Well, that's how it is.
I know.
I know, but...
Saiko asked me to bring the manuscript to the hospital.
Of course you can't do that.
I said I would.
When I considered his feelings, I couldn't answer any other way.
Takagi.
Are you an idiot?!
If he's really your friend, you need to stop him!
What are you saying? That's pathetic!
Yeah, I'm pathetic.
But I don't want to go on hiatus either!
Our rankings went up, we got a color spread...
If I were in Saiko's place, I'd draw even if it meant dying!
Even so... you can't draw manga if you're dead!
And even if you don't die, it's a bad idea to draw manga while in bad health...
I want to have a long-running popular manga in first place!
No matter how many years it takes.
Akito Takagi
Incoming Call
Hi!
Azuki.
Stay calm and listen.
Yakusa Municipal Hospital
It's only natural that an assistant should take care of the author.
Well, there's no need to do that, and my mom should be here soon...
I already met your mom yesterday.
Ah, that's not what I mean...
Shujin, where the hell are you?
You were supposed to bring the manuscript at 3!
Mashiro?
Mashiro, it's me, Azuki.
The girlfriend?!
Azuki? Why is she here?!
Um, I'll be going then.
Ah, yeah, I'll leave the work  to you!
You don't need to emphasize "work" so much...
Oh, she looks like a doll!
I could never compete.
She bowed before I did!
She's really composed!
Mashiro.
I think it's okay for me to come in...
We're only supposed to meet after our dreams come true...
But you were going to meet me at my house a while ago.
That was... an emergency...
Right now, I'm moving quickly towards realizing my dream...
As long as I continue the serialization nonstop for a bit longer, I'll definitely...
Okay. Then, even though it's a
bit embarrassing, I'll speak from here.
We can at least talk, right?
Well, yeah.
Mashiro.
Yes?
You're going to wait until after  you recover to draw, right?
I won't let the manuscript fall behind.
Shujin, hurry up and bring it here!
Could he have...
If you don't say you won't draw until you're released from the hospital...
I'll hate you.
If you'll hate me for something like that, then go ahead and hate me.
I won't leave until you say you won't draw!
Go ahead.
I'll really hate you!
That's unfair.
You say that, knowing that I can't hate you.
Even though you can't, you're worse for saying you can.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Since I've liked you for eight years, there's no way I could hate you.
It's the first time she's said she likes me!
Eight years?
Yeah, since 4th grade.
Yakusa City Citizen Festival
Hey, buy me candied apples!
Absolutely not. You don't want to get more cavities, do you?
Miho, we're leaving.
Candied apples!
Mom, I really like this painting.
Pet
Bird
Week
It's well done. I like it too.
It's funny how it's spelled "Saiko" but read like "Moritaka".
Asakusa Elementary 4th Grade
Mashiro Moritaka
I thought it would look cool to draw
a lot of birds and greenery.
The background is the pond at Yakusa Shrine!
Candied apples!
Saiko, your art got put up again?
It's good, so whatever.
Don't you want to be a manga artist when you grow up?
Isn't your art too different?
The basics are what's important, stupid.
Come on, let's go to the cardboard boat tournament.
Yeah!
Ever since I saw that painting...
Ever since then, I was really interested in you.
Since I lived close to the school, I'd look for you on the way to and from it...
Then in 5th grade...
Stationary Shop
It's the compass my uncle uses!
You put ink on it and draw!
It's for pro manga authors!
We're just buying a compass for math, right?
Besides, it's 4,500 yen...
I really, really want it!
Yama, how much do you have on you?
I have 500 yen!
Saiko, are you listening to me?
Kaya, how much do you have?
About 150 yen?
I have 1,000 yen.
That's not enough.
I really liked how your eyes sparkled when you looked at the compass.
At the swim meet, I was watching you constantly, trying to convey my feelings.
That's when I first noticed her.
We went to the same middle school and both got placed in Class 3...
And then you...
So after our dreams come true, please marry me!
I couldn't believe it!
I was so happy I could die.
But if we die, our dreams won't come true.
I've always liked you, and you're irreplaceable to me now...
I want you to stop drawing until you're released, for my sake.
D-Do you... value manga more than me?
They can't be compared.
They're both important,
but if you put it that way,
then manga is more important.
M-Mashiro...
We met...
I'll draw the manga.
It'll be okay. Don't worry.
Shujin.
Yeah?
Manga is great!
Somehow, I feel just like Joe from Ashita no Joe  when he went to his final match.
Please, for my sake,
stop drawing.
The readers are waiting.
I have to draw.
Mashiro!!
So Azuki couldn't stop him?
I'm really pumped up right now!
Hurry up and bring the manuscript!
Okay! I'll be there in 20... no, 15 minutes!
I'm sorry for telling Azuki!
Ashirogi's going on hiatus?
That's unfortunate.
Yeah, right now the editorial department is topsy turvy.
I thought of a good story that won't lose to TRAP 's front page color spread.
I wanted to compete with them.
Well he's sick, so nothing can be done about it.
I want to visit him.
Which hospital is he in?
Um, let's see... I think it was Yakusa Municipal Hospital...
Yakusa Municipal, right?
I'm off!
H-Hey, Niizuma!
Since we've seen each other, you can come inside...
Yeah...
Moritaka?
He has a girlfriend, huh?
And such a cute girl, too.
I guess manga wasn't his girlfriend, after all.
I almost ran into your mom at the entrance!
These are the G pens.
I brought some crow quill pens and spoon pens, too.
Thanks.
I forgot the ink!
It's fine.
I have color pens, so I'll start with chapter 20's color page.
I'll finish chapter 19 by tomorrow, so if you take it to the office right away, we should make it in time.
Sorry.
Azuki... she's gotten more mature, or prettier, you could say.
Takagi.
Uh, yeah?
Why did you bring the manuscript?
You're the one who asked me to stop him.
Because I'm a guy, I guess?
Even you feel something when looking at him working so hard, right?
Speaking of which, this is the first time I've seen him while he's drawing manga.
LET'S HOSPITAL!
Niizuma, this is a hospital! Keep your voice down!
Ah, the receipt please.
Ashirogi, I'm here!
Niizuma!
You're working on your color page, aren't you?
Yes.
Niizuma, you can't run inside a hospital.
Yuujirou, we're leaving.
It isn't good to interrupt someone's work.
But I'm glad I came!
Takagi, here.
Uh, thanks.
See you.
Niizuma, wait up!
I told you not to run!
Yakusa Municipal Hospital Stop
Taxi Loading
Taxi Fare Chart
Destination                      Fare
That cute girl is Mashiro's girlfriend?
I would have thought she was Takagi's...
Are you an idiot?
She looks just like TRAP 's heroine, Ami.
Oh, I see.
I'm an idiot.
Yeah, I wouldn't think you were a Jack editor.
Well, she's cuter than Ami.
More importantly...
Yes...?
Miura, what the heck are you doing?!
What do you mean? I'm arranging a substitute manuscript for TRAP...
Mashiro is drawing the manuscript in the hospital!
What?!
I should get going.
I'm in the way.
Stay!
It'll be difficult with just the two of us here...
That's so mean!
No, it isn't you.
I'm just too embarrassed and can't look at your face.
Oh...
Takagi, can you stay until I leave?
I'll leave after all.
Shujin!
Saiko, hide the manuscript!
It's Miura!
No, we should show it to him.
Let him know we're still gonna make the deadline.
Really?
I guess so.
Come in.
Good to see you.
Chapter 20's color page is going well.
I'll finish penning-in chapter 19 tomorrow, and it can be finalized soon after.
I can draw in the hospital just fine.
I definitely won't let the manuscript fall behind.
Mashiro...
No, stopping him is my job.
Saiko! Call the nurse!
I'm fine.
Just let me draw—
It's no good!
Saiko!
Takagi, hurry up and call the nurse!
I'm fine...
Stop.
Mashiro is saying he's fine.
Takagi, when you brought the manuscript here, you were prepared to have him draw no matter what, right?
If you make him stop here, you shouldn't have brought it at all.
Azuki...
Mashiro, let's do our best.
I know you can draw without resting. I believe in you.
Let's make our dreams come true.
Yeah.
I-I can't tell him to stop drawing.
kurikaesu nibuku detarame na sekai
In this world, every day is dull and full of nonsense
urusakute mimi wo fusaida
I cover my ears, trying to mute the noise
nan no tame ni kizutsukeatteiruno?
Why do people hurt each other?
zetsubou ni fushita kokoro no sumi
In the contradictory, overlapping shadows
orikasanaru mujun no kage ni
on the recesses of my heart, fallen into despair
mune wo itamenagara
While carrying this pain in my chest,
ashita wo yumemireruno?
can I really dream of tomorrow?
tooriame no ato ni mitsuketa niji wo motte
Remembering the rainbow I found after the rain,
me wo tojiru Fly with me donna nagai yume mo
I close my eyes; come fly with me into my dream
iroasenai kimi to nara
If I have you, who shines so strong
egakidaseru kienai niji mo
I can envision an everlasting rainbow
deaeta ano hi ni mita tsukiakari desaemo
And even remember the moonlight of the night we met
utsuhidasu nandodemo
I can picture them... countless times
nandodemo
over and over again
Next Time
Preview
Mashiro collapsed?!
Serializing while in high school was too tough, huh.
My health is also kinda—
Hiramaru!
Next time on Bakuman:
Life-or-Death and Standstill.
Life-and-Death and
Standstill
I value my health more than my dreams.
Mr. Yoshida!