We really did it right this time.
Akechi's character turned out really good.
He makes a good rival. That improves the story.
It would be boring without Eiji and Iwase.
That's what helped us along.
Shujin.
This time we'll definitely do it.
Even if we don't win, it's fine.
We'll just start something new.
It's here!
Did we manage to beat +Natural?
T-this is Takagi.
You're in 4th. You passed +Natural!
We did it!
It's too bad.
Eh?!
We passed them right?
Crow in 3rd place was only 2 votes ahead of you.
That's what I meant by "too bad."
Two votes?
That's really close!
Can I talk to him?
This is Mashiro.
We didn't beat Crow, but we still passed +Natural. We won't be canceled, right?
Here's the chief editor.
Eh?!
This is Sasaki.
Thanks for always helping us!
I said that I didn't think you
could beat Niizuma-kun.
That was a bit rude.
N-no. You only said it to
motivate us to do better.
PCP is a popular manga.
I can't cancel something like that.
Ashirogi-kun. You've done well.
Please continue improving Jack with PCP.
Okay!
Hey, if I could be with you right now
Then I could keep my voice from fading
The goals I've set for myself seem too high to reach,
and I feel like I've lost my way
I'm relying on a broken compass and hiding in someone's shadow
If we keep letting go of what we have to find something else,
then I'm convinced we can never grow up
Never
Margin and Pitfall
So, next subject.
My superiors told me this.
People can get tired of a collaboration pretty quickly.
So Crow...
I understand that.
PCP could only do well at the end of the series.
I'll overtake them again.
That's right!
What a relief.
I was worried you might be
upset by losing to them.
Upset? Actually, I'm even more motivated.
I see! That's good!
Well, that's all for today.
Huh?
I'm going to stay here and think for a while.
Oh, I see.
Well, thanks for your hard work.
Would you like more coffee?
5th place was Ally of Justice.
7th place was Road Racer Giri.
Below that it's a close battle.
But PCP got 4th place.
That's true.
Takahama-san and Fukuda-san put in a lot of effort.
We can't let our guard down!
Yeah.
Let's do our best to stay ahead!
Huh?
Hattori-san?
This is Mashiro.
Eh? Yes.
Understood.
He wants to have a meeting tonight.
Huh? We haven't finished the manuscript yet.
He said something about really good news for PCP.
Good news...
Could it be an anime?!
I-it's a bit too soon for that.
Who cares!
Our manga is popular!
An anime is what we've dreamed about!
Anime...
Drama CD?!
That's right.
That's the situation, so I thought you should know.
Y-yeah...
What's wrong? Aren't you happy?
No, of course we're happy.
But... Crow and the others each got
animes. We're just getting a drama CD.
Because of the subject, it's pretty
easy for PCP to get a drama CD.
We've only been going for six
months, so this is pretty good!
Yeah, I get it.
We definitely want to do it.
They don't want to spoil the characters,
so it will be an original story line.
Let me know if you have any requests.
Voice actors.
Specifically for the role of Annojo Mai.
Is it okay if I name the voice
actor that I want for that role?
That's exactly the kind of request I want.
Just let me know who...
The person who does the voice on the drama CD...
When we get an anime, will that person still do the voice?
Anime?
Mashiro-kun, we aren't discussing an anime right now.
Ah... Sorry! It's a bit too early.
But if we do eventually get an anime.
As long as the drama CD does
well and you do get an anime,
the chances of keeping the
same voice actor are high.
I knew it! It was a good idea to stop
her from doing the +Natural role.
Huh? Well, who did you have in mind?
Azuki Miho!
Azuki Miho-san...
Ah, sorry. I don't think I know her.
It's fine! She's a talented
and dedicated voice actor!
O-okay. I'll pass that along.
It's going to follow the creators'
wishes as closely as possible.
If I get Azuki onto the drama CD...
We're almost there. PCP will definitely get an anime!
I heard about a drama CD opportunity.
Shonen Jack's PCP manga series. For the main heroine...
Annojo Mai. Have you heard of it?
I-I have!
The creators requested you for the role.
I'll do it!
Oi?
I'll definitely do it! Please let me!
I  heard  that  Ashirogi-sensei
wanted me to be Annojo Mai
on  the  P C P  drama  CD.
I  was  so  happy!
I heard that Ashirogi-sensei wanted me
to be Annojo Mai on the PCP drama CD.
I was so happy!
Congratulations!
"Ashirogi-sensei"...
that has a nice ring to it!
Congratulations! "Ashirogi-sensei"... that has a nice ring to it!
Yeah !
Ever since I started reading
Ashirog-sensei's
manga, I thought so too!
Yeah! Ever since I started reading
Ashirogi-sensei's manga, I thought so too.
Sensei...
Did something good happen?
Eh... PCP is getting a drama CD.
EH?! Congratulations!
That's amazing!
A drama CD?
How well do you think that fits with the story?
Since we work on the manga,
we want it to turn out well.
More of this?
Moriya-san, you're always working on
your own storyboard in your free time.
Unlike you, I want to get serialized.
What's it about?
We may be coworkers, but I can't tell you that.
But it's important for other people to see it.
You're not drawing something
of your own, Shiratori-kun?
Eh? Is that not okay?
It's fine...
But that seems like a waste.
I like drawing...
But I don't know what to write about.
Just draw and write about
something that you like!
Something that I like?
I'm home!
I'm home, Peace!
You're home early, Shun.
We're about to have dinner. Will you join us?
Yeah.
Hey Shun, you should work for dad's company.
I'm... not interested in cosmetics.
I like drawing.
If you were an artist, that would be one thing. But a manga artist's helper...
Saiko!
Huh?
Hey!
I hardly ever see you on the way to the studio.
We used to always go together.
Are you okay on time?
Yeah.
I'm used to drawing PCP now.
I can spare some time.
Remember when we came here in middle school?
We thought we knew everything back then.
Middle schoolers are all like that.
And in the first summer of high
school you kissed Kaya-chan here.
Eh?! How do you know about that?
Ha ha ha.
It's a perfect crime!
When did you dig this hole?
You dug it yourself. You're not fooling anyone, Akechi-kun.
You're taking it too far!
They're playing PCP...
????
What about it?
Maybe things are going too well.
It's been six years since we started writing for Jack.
PCP is definitely popular.
We have a drama CD, and Azuki will be on it.
When I write, I don't run out of ideas.
I finish things more quickly.
Well, I have more time too.
But there are things we still need to do.
We still haven't beaten Crow... or gotten an anime.
Anime...
You're right. That's the important part!
Yeah.
Seriously...
Why are they rushing things?
TV Animation Proposal
The final script for the drama CD is finished.
That was fast!
He's got the characters down pretty well.
But I think Mai should have more lines.
The crime itself though...
That's it.
He's good with characters and dialog...
But he isn't as good as Takagi-kun
when it comes to inventing crimes.
Eh?
Ordinarily, we wouldn't do this.
Even though you're working on the manga,
could you think of a crime for the drama CD?
That's fine.
Huh?
I'll think of a crime for the drama CD.
I want it to be really good!
But... do you really have time?
We're doing another series, so I have everything planned ahead.
I've got plenty of time.
I see. Well good luck.
Akito-san!
Now that that series is done, shouldn't you be going to bed earlier?
I'm working on the drama CD now!
Eh? The one Miho is going to be on?
Yup!
So you're writing a script for the drama CD?
I'm revising it.
I'm making the actual crime parts more interesting.
Akito-san, you're so cool!
What are you saying?
You've only just noticed my talent?
That's not it. The fact that you can touch type is so cool!
Kaya-chan, guess what else I can do without looking...
Squee!
Interesting... Are you sure this is okay?
You could use this for the manga.
We want it to be as good as possible.
When people hear it, we want
them to think PCP is amazing.
That way we'll be more likely to get an anime.
Well, while I'm here let's talk about the next series.
Good idea.
Well, I'll get back to my pen.
We've already done two series with Akechi,
so I wanted to do something different for this one.
That's true...
Wait, you've already got another idea?
Yeah!
Well, I'll be going.
Thanks for your hard work!
Um, will Takagi-sensei be here tomorrow?
I think so...
I want to have him look at my storyboard.
Eh?!
You wrote something?
But it isn't done yet...
This is bad! I'm the only person
not working on something!
Shiratori-kun has a storyboard?
Then I'll come over now!
This is really interesting!
R-really?
Rabuta doesn't trust people anymore.
And Peace can  read people's feelings.
It's simple but well-constructed.
I love dogs so I thought that would
be a good subject to write about.
His nose can tell the difference
between good and bad people.
And he can hear when people aren't being honest.
And when he licks someone, they tell the truth.
These are great ideas!
But right now, it seems like the dog is the hero.
That's no good.
In order to be more suited for Jack,
you need to make the hero stronger.
It's a good idea, so revise it a bit
and we'll show it to Hattori-san.
No. I want to get your okay first, Takagi-sensei.
Takagi-san, if I ever draw something, please look at it too!
Fine with me!
Awesome!
Shujin, you're pretty awesome.
In addition to the drama CD, PCP is getting a novelization!
A novel?!
Tanabe Ikki-san will be writing it.
Of all the light-novel authors,
he is the best for mysteries.
Oh, I've heard of him.
Of course, we'll have you check his work.
Is the novelization okay?
Of course!
Please do it!
A drama CD... and a novel.
Next will be an anime!
Anime again...
I need to make it clear.
Takagi-kun. Mashiro-kun.
Yes?
PCP will not get an anime.
WHAT?!
Why not?!
Maybe I should say it's best to assume that it won't.
Why?
We have a drama CD and a novel, why not an anime?
The drama CD and novel are different.
An anime is a big project.
It's expensive.
You can't do it without a sponsor.
PCP won't get a sponsor very easily.
Why not?
It's popular! Kids love it!
We even saw kids playing it in the park!
That's why!
PCP has received complaint calls.
I haven't shown you, but there are a lot of protest letters, too.
Children like to imitate the story.
Parents don't want their kids
imitating crimes and pranks.
You haven't had them do anything actually
harmful, but people don't understand.
No way...
It isn't like a battle manga.
You can actually do the stuff from the story.
But that difference is what makes it popular!
That's right.
It's realistic and totally possible. That is the manga's appeal.
But for an anime, that would be a big flaw.
Then, we can change the nature of the crimes.
Make them only do good things?
We can't do that!
Saiko...
That's what makes it interesting.
PCP is a popular manga.
We can't afford to change that.
Mashiro-kun is right.
PCP is the perfect Ashirogi Muto manga.
It's very popular.
Takagi-kun, you haven't done
anything wrong with the story.
I agree.
But if we can't get an anime...
Why are you so fixed on that?
It's popular, isn't that good enough?
If you don't get an anime, would
you feel like you've failed?
An anime is something that comes afterward.
It isn't something you plan for.
Yeah, but for us...
Shujin, it's fine.
It's not fine!
Hattori-san, let me be clear.
An anime... making a story that's good enough.
That's our dream!
Every since middle school, when we teamed up!
We both want to see our manga become an anime.
That's always been our goal!
This may be harsh.
Takagi-kun, you're the type to plan things out.
You've planned a lot for PCP.
But if you really want an anime,
you need to consider that in your planning too!
Plan for the anime?
It's true... I didn't include that in my plans.
I didn't think about it.
Staying with Jack...
Competing with Niizuma Eiji...
And now...
That's why it's good!
You never would have come up with this
manga if you had planned for an anime.
But now that you've said this,
next time I'm going to plan
for an anime from the start!
Shujin!
It's fine!
PCP is a popular manga.
We should focus our effort on it.
We're only 20 after all.
An anime isn't possible...
I guess I'm a little shocked.
I wasn't thinking about it at all. Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
PCP owes its popularity to you!
Hey Saiko,
Have you asked Azuki when she wants to get married?
What?
There's a big difference between 22 and 30.
We don't know how long PCP will run.
You don't need to worry about that!
Azuki-san, when do you want to get married ideally?
I can't send this.
It isn't something I need to worry about.
PCP is doing well.
But we haven't beaten Crow yet.
That's right. Eiji is writing two series.
But he does Crow by himself.
If Shujin and I both worked on it...
A second series might put us ahead of Eiji.
One more.
Like Shujin said, if we specifically make it to be an anime...
We do both have a little more free time now.
No. I shouldn't tell Shujin something like that.
We need to focus on PCP.
I was the one who said we were only 20.
We should see how things go, and then...
So right here is the focal point.
You want a big full-page panel for that.
Oh... I see!
That's about all I can help with.
Your art...
Shujin does seem to have more free time.
It won't be long now.
That should do it.
Thank you so much!
Before you head home, you
can work on what I mentioned.
Okay!
Hattori-san is coming later.
Want to have him look at it?
Eh? Yes...
Showing his storyboard to an editor...
Can I come too?!
Huh?
O-okay.
You guys are all working hard!
Moriya-kun, let me have a look at yours.
Please do!
What do you think of my work?
I would have to say...
It's too complicated. It isn't Jack material.
B-but kids nowadays...
Most importantly, it's difficult to understand.
Why do the humans help the city grow?
They don't have a reason.
Readers don't want to be preached at.
He's pretty tough...
Let's move on to Shiratori-kun.
Okay...
Please do.
This is interesting!
Interesting??
Next time, maybe!
Nobody ever recognizes art.
The dialog is pretty good!
I'm surprised!
You could submit this to Treasure... no, even Next.
That's awesome! Well done.
Or is it too early for that?
Hattori-san. I don't want to submit this.
Huh?
Why not? This is good enough to get serialized.
Yeah, this is a good chance!
But...
This storyboard isn't really mine.
What do you mean?
Before I showed it to you,
Takagi-sensei looked at it
and I revised it three times.
Three times?
Takagi-kun, is that true?
Yeah, he asked me to look at it.
I thought it might be too good for a first try.
Shiratori-kun.
Do you still have your original storyboard?
Yes.
Takagi-kun is really amazing.
I want to show this to my superiors.
But it will need to be marked:
"Idea and art by Shiratori Shun"
"Story by Ashirogi... no, Takagi Akito."
It's no good otherwise.
If it got serialized, it would be best
to have Takagi-kun write the story.
If Shujin starts working on another series...
But if that happens...
Takagi-kun, you've just gotten used to writing PCP.
So it wouldn't be right away, but would you think about it?
Eh? B-but...
That would be Mashiro's decision too.
Oh yeah, that's true.
Eh?
As long as it doesn't interfere with PCP...
I...
When I struggle toward my dream
Those are the moments I love the most
I can feel our bond and will to fight
Our views overlap and electrify us
Let's improve ourselves, become what we should be
You can see the future in our path
My comrades don't agree with me
Our pride clashes
I can't let it go, I'll follow my heart from now on
I'm prepared
I'll charge right in
Unstoppable Pride
There's no other choice, this is what I love and this is what I'll do
I don't know what tomorrow will bring
But I know once again (just to get by),
We'll do our best
If I do my best, can I fulfill my dreams too?
It's not impossible.
Don't turn away from your true self.
Next time: Step and Watch.
I can't give up on my dream!