Okay,
for today’s homeroom period,
Let’s talk about
this year’s Literary Fest.
I wonder what we’re
going to do this year.
I am looking forward to it, you know?
So Japanese schools have
Literary Fest too.
Every class and club
does something different.
Last year, we did an ensemble.
[Sakura, Shao Lang, and a Sea of Sand]
We all voted yesterday,
and the result for Class 5-2 is a play.
It’s a play!
I wonder what the story is going to be.
Class 6-1 is also doing a play,
But they will be doing
an ancient Japanese story,
So I thought,
how about let’s do a western play?
What do you think?
The dream that the card showed me…
That was Mizuki-sensei after all.
Besides, Kero said
what Dream showed was a prophetic dream.
Does it mean
something like what’s
in the dream will happen some day?
But
whenever I’m looking at Mizuki-sensei…
I always feel so schweeet!
So, the title of the play
you have all been waiting for…
SLEEPING BEAUTY
Then we will decide who play the role.
In order to let everyone
have a fair chance to play any role,
We will use the method of amidakuji.
Now then come up here
in the order of your class number.
Yes!
I wonder what role I’m getting…
Whatever role you are playing,
I will make the costume for you for sure!
To… Tomoyo-chan…
You don’t need to be so alert like that.
It will be very soon.
Let’s get back to our seats.
Shao Lan?
What’s wrong?
Mizuki-sensei said,
“It will be very soon.”
What will be?
I don’t know.
But she does have
something in her mind after all.
Okay, let’s reveal the results!
Sleeping Beauty is the story
of a sleeping princess…
who was woken up
by the kiss of a prince, right?
That is correct.
Then if I get to play the Princess,
and Shao Lang gets to play the Prince…
Oh, what a beautiful Princess!
I will wake her with my kiss…
Oh my!
I don’t wanna be the Prince.
Let’s see…
The Princess and the Prince are…
You’re playing the Prince?
I am sure you will play
a very cute prince!
I will ask the teachers
to let me make your costume!
I am really looking forward to this!
The play is the Sleeping Beauty, right?
Then the main character is the Princess.
Who is it?
Li-kun…
What’s up with that?!
But it’s all decided by amidakuji.
I will work hard on Li-kun’s costume too!
Because he is Sakura-chan’s co-star!
But now a girl plays a boy’s role
and vice versa.
Mizuki-sensei said everyone
has a fair chance to play any role…
Mizuki-sensei?
She appeared in what
Dream showed you, didn’t she?
Even that brat’s alert around her.
Who is she?
I’m sure I could sense power in her.
She has something real
powerful with her.
And so…
I’m going to the Literary Fest too.
What’s that all about?!
I’m going to check out that Mizuki-sensei
and watch you in action!
Kero-chan! You just wanna
go to the fest, don’t you?
That is so true!
So it is.
“I have this sword and courage in me!…”
“…I promise…”
“…I will break the curse
for the Princess!…”
This is so hard!
I wonder if I can do this right…
“O… Oh my!
I… I wonder what… this is…”
Li, you’re practicing too?
Are you okay?
You’re practicing over here.
Me too!
I’ve never played
a princess or a prince,
So I’m nervous.
Me too.
So, have you done anything
in Literary Fest in your school
in Hong Kong before?
Like twice…
What did you play?
I sang…
What song did you sing?
Sing it!
I don’t like singing
in front of people.
I see…
Sing it one of these days, okay?
Hello!
Yukito-san!
You guys having lunch break?
Yes!
Our teacher is absent today,
so we have a self-study period.
I was thinking of eating a little…
Why don’t we eat together?
Sure!
Okay, let’s eat!
Th… This…
All of these…
I hope it’s enough for three people…
May be not enough.
Come to think of it, isn’t it the time
for your school’s Literary Fest?
Th… That’s right.
What is your class doing?
A… A play.
Which play?
Sle… Sleeping Beauty.
Both of you are going to be in it, right?
What roles do you play?
Whatever roles you play,
I’ll make sure I won’t miss it.
Umm…
You coming…
Yeah. As usual of course!
Good luck!
Yes!
Yukito-san is coming to watch.
I gotta practice harder.
Li-kun.
Do you want to practice together?
There’re many scenes
I get to play against you…
I thought practicing together
might be a good idea.
But you don’t have time, do you?
When?
To practice…
Are you sure?
I don’t want to do bad either.
Thanks!
How about tomorrow morning
before school starts?
What’s going on?
Why are there so many alarm clocks?
They’re Father’s and Touya’s.
I’m practicing for the play with Li-kun
from today on…
I can’t be late.
It’s rare you are
practicing on your own…
I respect you.
Because…
Yukito-san’s coming to watch!
Since I’m not bringing lunch today,
I wonder what to eat for breakfast!
Onii-chan?
You don’t have morning practice
today, right?
Why are you up so early?
I happened to have woken up.
Is this mine?
Don’t eat it if you don’t want to.
I’ll eat it!
I wonder if he’s up early
in order to make breakfast for me…
Sakura…
When you caught a cold that one time…
Mirror!
This way I’ll be okay…
Wh… What about it?
You’re done?
Save some so that
I can have more later.
I’ll just make more later.
What about the medicine?
You don’t need to take it
unless you’re sick.
You aren’t Sakura, right?
Don’t do crazy things like that again.
What was he trying to say?
Could it be that
he knows I’m gathering the Clow Cards…?
It can’t be. If he knows,
he’d be scolding me already.
Mizuki-sensei…
I gotta hurry up to school!
Good morning!
You got here even before I did!
You’re so early!
Hey, since the weather’s so nice,
how about practicing outside?
I wonder what this is…
And like that,
the Princess walked towards the spindle…
…and tried to touch it with her finger.
Awesome!
You remembered almost all the lines!
The Princess doesn’t have many lines,
that’s all.
Okay, let’s skip
the scenes with the fairies.
Oh! What a beautiful Princess!
If I can wake the Princess
with my kiss…
I swear by this sword!
I will love this beautiful princess
of the forest of thorns
with all my heart.
And with this kiss…
L… Li-kun!
What?!
Wind Descend!
Key which hides the forces of darkness,
Reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release!
Fly!
What’s going on?!
It’s the act of a Clow Card!
But I didn’t sense it at all!
What card is this?!
I’m afraid, it’s Sand,
the card of the sand.
How do I turn it back?
First, we need to stop it from moving!
Li-kun!
Don’t come!
But!
Do what I say!
Yes.
Use Watery and envelop this area!
But it’ll fill this place up,
and besides,
that won’t stop it from moving!
Just do it!
Water, pour over the sand!
Watery!
Freeze!
Now!
Return to thy
form which thou should be!
Clow Card!
Li-kun!
Are you okay?
Yeah. Kinda…
Here.
It’s yours.
Why?
You were the one who thought
of how to capture it,
And earlier
you let me have the card, Cloud.
But you do understand
I’m fighting you
over the Clow Cards.
But this card is yours.
Here.
I’m not gonna give it back
if you regret later.
It’s almost time the others come in.
Thank goodness, the card was active
before school starts…
I wonder if it’s a coincidence…
Maybe it knows
only the two of us
are here at this hour…
Why?
Nothing.
I hope I’m just thinking too much.
It will be very soon.