All right! It cleared up
Really it’s like last night’s
rain was a lie
By the way Sakura
aren’t you up early for a Sunday?
Today I am having a picnic
with Tomoyo-chan at the wooded park
Why don’t you go along, Kero-chan?
If you are in the bag nobody can tell,
OK? OK?
I’m so glad the weather turned nice
[Sakura’s exhausting Sunday]
Good morning!
Good morning Sakura
You seem pretty happy monster
I’ll forgive you today
You really do seem
in a good mood Sakura
Today I am going out with Tomoyo-chan.
Eh?
Today’s chores are
all you aren’t they?
What?
You wrote it yourself last week and forgot?
Umm Umm
Rika-chan is having a piano recital
I was thinking I’d like to go cheer her on
Fine I’ll switch with you
Really?
In return next Sunday you are
doing all the household chores
OK!
Umm Umm…
Well I have work
I’ll take care of it
It has been raining a lot lately
so this much built up
Shall I help you a bit?
You have a meeting today don’t you dad?
It’s OK I’ll do it
Sorry
Leave it to me
I’ll leave this by the washing machine
OK
I’m leaving
See you later
I’m leaving too
Yeah see you later
I’m off.
Umm… Umm…
So that’s it?
I’m sorry
I completely forgot I had chores today
There is no helping it
I’m really sorry
Don’t worry about it too much
Good luck with your chores
Yeah! Thanks
Well I’ll see you at school tomorrow
Yes until tomorrow
I’ll bring a letter of apology on Monday
Well then shall we get down to work
Kero-chan how’s it going?
Just because nobody else is home
Why do I have to do something like this?
Wood? A tree?
This is a Clow Card
Huh? It stopped
Kero-chan! Kero-chan!
Kero-chan I found a Clow card
Huh?
He’s not here
Oh well
I’ll brag about it later
I’m spinning a lot today
I quit I quit I quit
Why should I must do such silly thing?
Oh yeah!
When this is done
I’ll have some ice cream with Kero-chan
I guess there is no choice
I’ll help a little more
All right. This is the last place
It’s covered in ink
This is also a Clow Card
I’m lucky today
To find two cards
I have to wipe it off
Towel Towel A wet towel
The phone
Yeah yeah I’m answering now
Hello Kino
Sakura
Yes? Dad?
Can you check if there
is a blue folder on top of the kitchen table?
There is
Sorry can you bring
that to the bus stop?
All my materials for the meeting are in there
I’ll leave right away
Kero-chan I’m going out for a bit
What?
See you later
Thank you!
Sakura-chan
Yukito-san
That was your dad right now right?
An errand?
Yes he forgot something so
You delivered it?
How nice!
A uniform?
There was a basketball game today
I was helping out a bit
Yukito-san isn’t really in any club
But sometimes he gets asked to play
just in games
He’s smart and can do anything
It’s wonderful!
Say Sakura-chan
Have you had lunch yet?
No not yet.
Won’t you eat with me? Over there
Big brother
Thanks
Three plates large helping
He eats three times as much as I do
Th… Three times?
You don’t have to hold back
It is my treat
Kero-chan is waiting for me at home
Kero-chan?
No Uh
It’s good to eat a lot
health wise
It’s tough on the allowance though
Yukito-san
Thank you Dad
I was able to see Yukito-san
I’m home
Kero-chan!
Thanks
I can’t spin anymore
I’ll make lunch right away
Kero-chan Kero-chan! Hey Kero-chan!
What? Lunch time?
What is this sound?
Sound?
I wonder if it is a thief
Sounds like downstairs
It couldn’t be a monster could it?
Would they come out at day?
They might be there and come out
It’s from the basement
In here
Well.
Open…
What? I can’t really see
What was that just now?
This is the branch from a plant
Why would something like that
be coming in from the basement?
This is the work of Wood
A Clow Card? Now that you mention it today
You left a card you found out
without writing your name on it?
But when I found it it was just a card
I had to answer the phone
That’s not good
The cards first begin to listen
to what their owner says
when you write your name on them
But it was in the house all this time
nothing has happened until now
Wood is a peaceful card
I can’t think of her
doing anything bad
Then why?
Ah! Kero-chan don’t let go
Kero-chan what should we do?
I’m in trouble too
What should I do?
I wonder who it is
If you answer you will know
If they see this it will
become a rumor all over town
They might see that you are a stuffed animal
that can sell too
I don’t want that
Y Yes!
Why did you answer?
It just slipped out
For the time being I’ll
Kero-chan?
Don’t to stuffed animals
No fair!
Umm this is
Hello
Oh my Tomoyo-chan
I was thinking I would help with your chores
Weeding the yard?
No
this is the work of the Clow Card Wood
Really?
My Sakura seal
it while you have the chance
OK, release!
Return to your rightful form
Clow Card!
How wonderful Sakura-chan
Oh!
Is something wrong?
There is no card
That can’t be
Isn’t it dropped
somewhere over there?
What about in the room over there
Oh yeah the basement
All right shall we go get the card?
Yeah
Sakura go up
Sakura!
It looks like it calmed down.
It seems that it was satisfied
after getting into the sunlight
Just what we should expect from Wood
The laundry!
Umm… Umm…
I have to do it again
from the beginning
Don’t be so down
I’ll do it too OK?
Do it again
What should we do about this?
Even if we try to seal
it just returns to normal
Isn’t it obvious?
We go to where the card
is and completely seal it
You mean into the basement?
Exactly
What is this sound?
It sounds like elephants walking around
No, it’s the sound of the house creaking
Wood is still growing
Even though it just calmed down?
It knows that there is light outside
If Wood is trying to get
all the way outside
The house will be destroyed
No!
This is a job for Card Captor Sakura
Why did you bring these clothes?
Today I was planning on filming
an episode of Sakura explores the Jungle
So you prepared this lunch too?
Looks like you can make it through
This way
Just a little further
Let’s hurry
What is that noise?
I wonder
Water?
The Wood card doesn’t make water
So the other card?
What? There was a second card?
Which means
So Rain was there
Rain?
The card of rain
Rain and Wood affecting each others
And created this jungle
Hey Sakura
OK
At long last
Rain! Wood!
That’s far enough for your pranks
How wonderful
Sakura here it comes!
What? It’s nothing much
Umm… Um…
Sakura it is just playing
Hurry and seal it
But…
At this rate
That’s it, Sakura, Watery!
Watery will turn
its rain water against it
Watery? Oh yeah
Card made by Clow
lend power to my key
Magical power in the card
transfer to this key
Give me power
Watery!
Water! Become now the chains that bind!
All right we got it!
Return to your rightful form
Clow Card!
You did it
All that is left is
the one responsible for
trying to break the house
Wood!
Wait a second!
What?
Just like I said she is a nice card
I guess wood and rain
get along well after all
Look at that
It’s a rainbow
My how pretty
Sakura
Once you have done this
you first make a card your own
Yeah I will keep that in mind
Well I am going to sleep for a bit
Good night
Sorry about today
No I am happy it
became a much better video
than filing in the forest park
Really?
Sakura! It’s terrible!
This means we have
to clean it all over
I’ll help too
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
I’m home
Good job on your chores today
We’ll eat cake later
If you don’t write your name on the cake
I’ll eat it
I did write my name