This feels okay?
Thanks, Sakura-chan.
I’m so nervous!
I hope I won’t say
the wrong lines.
Don’t worry.
You guys practiced so much.
Sakura-chan, you still
haven’t changed yet?
Tomoyo said she’s making
the costumes for Li-kun and me,
But she’s not here yet.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Tomoyo-chan!
I stayed up two nights to finish this.
Are you okay?
This is a costume
that you are going to wear!
I cannot allow any mistakes!
Now, let us get changed quickly!
Li-kun too!
[Sakura’s Pitch-Dark Literary Fest]
Too bad your father can’t make it.
He said he couldn’t leave
the excavation site no matter what.
This is really too bad.
So, you’re taking pictures. Yeah.
Father asked me to take them.
Sakura’s is the first class to perform.
It’s the Sleeping Beauty.
Come to think of it,
you did one last year too
Cinderella.
I didn’t need to remember that.
Why not? You looked so nice in that.
The president of the photography club
told me…
…that your pictures at
the Literary Fest sold the best.
That guy from the
photography club said that?
I wonder what role Sakura plays.
I’m really looking forward to it!
Who would want to invite
an evil witch like you…
Sakura-chan, you look so cool!
You look wonderful! Really!
Tomoyo-chan made an awesome costume,
that’s all.
Really, you look very nice in it.
Mizuki-sensei!
Really.
And you can move freely wearing it.
You’ll be okay even
if anything happens.
Eh!
Absolutely no way!!
Li-kun is so cute!!
You look so nice in it!
Not at all!
Why do I have to wear
this frilly stuff!
Because you are the Princess?
On top of that,
what’s this wavy hair?!
I absolutely hate this!
Just now I was looking at the audience,
and I saw Mr. Tsukishiro.
Yukito-san…
I am sure Mr. Tsukishiro has come here
in order to watch the Sleeping Beauty!
I bet the play has to be cancelled.
If the play is cancelled,
I am sure Mr. Tsukishiro
will be saddened by this.
We practiced so much,
let’s do it, Li-kun!
I’ll do it.
Yo! Tomoyo!
I’ve come to watch!
Welcome, Kero!
Now, let’s begin.
Thank you for your patience.
Class 5-2 will now present to you,
the Sleeping Beauty.
It’s starting!
One upon a time,
there lived
a King and a Queen.
Their kingdom is
prosperous and very peaceful.
However, for the longest time, the King
and the Queen did not have a child.
This is Tomoyo-chan’s voice, isn’t it?
One day, at last,
a Princess was born after
their many prayers.
Today is the celebration
of the Princess’ birthday.
Ladies and gentlemen, you may present
your blessings to the Princess.
Isn’t that a guy playing the Queen?
For the lovely Princess,
We fairies have come…
…to present our gifts.
Her beauty shall shine
like the brightest sun!
She shall have the sweetest voice
that would lose to no one!
I…
What a grand party it is today!
But I was not sent an invitation.
Who would want to invite
an evil witch like you!
An evil witch? I wonder who that is!
I am really sorry.
I was told that
you do not like merry occasions.
Right, right.
I do not like merry occasions.
But I hate even more
if I was being neglected!
So now, why don’t I also give
my blessings to the Princess?
With her beauty, her elegance,
and her gentleness,
the Princess shall be loved
by her people every day.
And then, on her sixteenth birthday,
she shall prick
her finger with a spindle,
And die!!
Mei Lin-chan is awesome!
During practice,
she kept saying she didn’t
want to play the bad guy.
She’s the type that can
just do the real thing right.
Oh no!
What a terrible curse
from that witch!
Th… This is too cruel!
Is there no way to break
the curse of the witch?
I still have not presented
my gift to the Princess.
The Princess shall prick her finger
with a spindle on
her sixteenth birthday.
However, she shall not die from it.
She shall only be asleep.
A true love for the Princess shall
break the spell of the witch,
And from the kiss of this person,
may the Princess be awoken!
Everyone’s doing’ great!
Tomoyo, you too!
Thank you very much!
That bratty girl playing the
evil witch was just perfect!
So,
Sakura and that brat still
haven’t had their turn yet?
They are in the next scene.
Having heard the curse
from the witch,
the King ordered
that all spindles be burned.
All the people in the kingdom obeyed
and destroyed all the spindles.
And no spindles exist in the country.
Sixteen years passed.
The Princess has blossomed
into beautiful young woman.
My dear Princess!
Yes, Mother.
He’s the Princess?!
Wow! He looks pretty good!
What is it?! Mother?!
Today is the party for
your sixteenth birthday.
Please hurry and get change!
Yes, Mother!
That’s a miscast!
The Princess returned to her room.
And there stood a spindle,
which should no longer
exist in this kingdom.
Oh, I wonder what this is!
This hu… hurts!!
Oh no! My Princess has died!
My lovely Princess!
No, that is not true, Your Highness!
The Princess has only fallen asleep!
Just as the gift I presented
to her sixteen years ago.
Now, let us wait for the one
who can wake the Princess!
It’s the next scene.
This will capture
all of Sakura’s heroic actions!
Oh? It’s her turn finally?
A long, long time has gone by,
and finally a Prince
has come to this kingdom.
Sakura! Sakura-chan plays the Prince!
Yukito-san!
Oh! She looks awesome!
I stayed up two nights to make it!
So, this is the mysterious castle!
We have been waiting for you!
Who are you?!
We are fairies.
We have been waiting for
a courageous young man to arrive.
What?
There is a beautiful Princess
asleep in this castle.
Under the curse of an evil witch,
she has been sleeping for a long time.
How terrible!
Is there a way I can save her?
You can, if you think seriously
that you want to save her.
I have this sword and courage in me!
I promise
I will break the curse for the Princess!
Sakura-chan looks so cool!
Good job! Good job!
Sakura is just too wonderful!
You have done well to get here, Prince.
You must be the evil witch
who cursed the Princess!
Everyone! Go get him!
Awesome! Awesome!
She’s just good at sports, that’s all.
Damn you, Prince!
I did it! I defeated the witch!
Oh! What a beautiful Princess!
The Princess can only be woken…
…by the kiss of the one
who truly loves her.
Kiss the Princess,
if you can truly love her.
Oh! Here’s the good part!
If only I play the Prince!
Don’t tell me
she’s really gonna kiss…!
This aura!!
Li-kun!
Oh no! This is…!!
Huh? What happened?
Did the lights go out?
Be careful! It’s a Clow Card!
This is Da … Li-kun! Li-kun!
Did you say this is because
of a Clow Card?!
That’s right!
Kero-chan should be in the
control room with Tomoyo-chan!
But…
Which way is the control room?!
Sakura…
Kero-chan! Tomoyo-chan!
Li-kun! Mei Lin-chan!
I’ve been running
but I don’t seem to be getting
anywhere… No one’s around…
Anyone will do! Just answer me!
Where did everyone go?
Am I all by myself?
Do your best, Sakura!
The only way to seal this card
is to realize that herself!
It’s no use crying.
Everyone’s probably scared
because of this darkness!
Li-kun said
this is the act of a Clow Card.
So, maybe I can do something about it!
Key which hides the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release!
I can’t use magic…
Calm down…
First, I need to think
what card this is…
It’s not ‘Black’… is it?
It’s pitch-dark… Could it be…
Dark, as in darkness?
I guessed right!
Sakura realized the nature of the card!
But…
It turned pitch-dark again…
Just by realizing the nature of the card
is not enough to seal it.
She’s gotta realize that herself!
If it’s Sakura,
she should be able to realize it!
It’s not like with Mirror
that I can just name the card…
I gotta think
what can I do in pitch-dark!
I gotta think!
But if it’s really pitch-dark,
I shouldn’t be able to see myself…
How come I can see myself…?
What?!
She’s being taken in by darkness!
At this rate,
she’ll be trapped inside darkness!
Sakura! Hurry up and notice it!
At this rate,
I won’t even be able to see myself!
Don’t cry!
It’ll be okay. It’ll all work out.
It’ll be okay for sure!
I’m shining!
I see! If I shine,
then of course
I can see myself in the dark!
Are you a Clow Card too?
That’s right. Since the time you broke
the seal on the cards,
I’ve been living inside your heart.
I didn’t know at all.
Because you never gave up,
You finally realized my presence,
And you let me out.
Now here’s a quiz for you.
What shines in the dark?
Light!
You guessed right!
You are… Dark?!
I’m glad you noticed Light.
She knew all along that
you would be able to seal me.
Of course, she’s the girl
whose heart I’ve been living in!
Now, you should be able
to use your magic.
Try sealing both of us together!
O… Okay!
Key which hides the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release!
Return to thy form which thou should be!
Clow Card!
We would love
to have you as our mistress.
Only Yue will be the Last Judgment.
Good luck to you.
Yue?!
Excuse me… ‘Yue’…?!
Yue is close to you.
But it’s going to be okay!
Because you have the invincible spell:
‘It’ll be okay for sure!’
It’s the same as the dream…
I’m so glad! You really came back!
Hey! That little!
Hey! I dare you getting all
out of hand like that!
What happened?
You didn’t notice, did you?
It’s a Clow Card.
It’s the card, Dark,
which only pulled those with
magic into the dimension it created.
I totally did not feel it…
To those with no magic,
it’s as though
time has simply continued on.
I can sense it…
The power of the moon…
Yue,
I guess the time for us
to meet will be very soon…
“It’ll be okay for sure,” right?