Sakura-chan,
you don’t really feel asleep recently.
Yeah, if it’s just a little,
I won’t feel too tired anymore.
This must mean
your power is growing!
Power?
Everyday
you become more cute,
pretty and confident.
So I don’t ever want to stop being
by your side to videotape you.
So I can help you
with all of your costume!
It is just too great!
Tomoyo-chan…
But when we are together
something dangerous might happen to you.
Compared with all I can get,
this is actually small price to pay.
Besides… whenever I am with you,
everything will be alright.
Re, really?
Sounds embarrasing…
You look very cute too
when you are embarrased.
Oh, Tomoyo-chan, please…
[Sakura, Tomoyo, and the Ball Trap]
– Everybody come here.
– OK!
Today there well be a b-ball contest.
Today well play basketball
and see.
That sounds like its gonna be fun.
Go!
Sakura-chan!
Sakura-chan go!
I did it!
Sakura-chan is really great!
Next,
Hiiragizawa and Li go!
Eriol-kun, Shao Lan-kun, go!
Let me have a chance.
Great!
That’s too bad, it just bounced out
He’s too focused.
Go! Go!
Calm down.
Just think about the basketball
going into the hoop.
Very great!
You just have to calm down
and think about yourself!
Then you can do it
Good!
Class is over.
Yes!
Really want to sleep.
Whenever I walk
it makes me even more tired
Clow!
Why…
How can you be right there?
You should already not be in this world!
I did a lot of impossible things.
But I couldn’t tell anyone,
including Kerberos and you.
Your power is used up
Although you can’t get power
from your new master.
So our disguise is
a big difference from
your real self, Yue
But
everything that is happening is
totally different then I expected.
It is very interesting.
I cannot tell you
that I really exist yet.
Temporarily forget this.
What? What? What?
Are you ok?
Did I fall asleep?
– Yeah.
– I went to sleep again?
Sorry if I bothered you.
Not at all.
What? I wonder how I got on
the other side of the fence.
Sorry to trouble you.
It wasn’t much.
Yuki!
What do you want Touya?
Because I saw that you didn’t come back…
Really?
Sorry.
He is… what kind of person?
You were thinking of Sakura-chan right?
No!…
Really? You’re not thinking of her?
You were thinking of Sakura-chan
You like Sakura-chan.
You still haven’t told
Sakura-chan this yet
I…
Sakura-chan has a very kind heart.
If you don’t tell her
then she won’t know.
But she has someone else that she likes.
That’s only because
you haven’t told her yet.
There are a lot of people
that like Sakura-chan.
Because Sakura-chan is cute
and also a kind person.
I know that.
You know that she likes somebody, who?
Hiiragizawa
I think Hiiragizawa isn’t who she likes
Sakura-chan only consider Eriol
as a friend,
so you can’t say she likes him.
You can say he likes her,
but he only looks at her
with friendly eyes.
You are a very good observer.
Because she is Sakura-chan.
I hope that
you can express what you’re thinking.
You don’t want
to tell other people what you feel
No matter what you’re thinking,
if you don’t say it
then you won’t be able to transmit it.
I’m done dressing,
will this do?
It’s too great!
I am going to go get my viedo camera!
Does this look alright?
– Yes.
– Really? Thank you!
No matter what you’re thinking,
if you don’t say it
then you won’t be able to transmit it.
I’d like to ask…
That is Clow-san’s aura.
I can feel it… it’s inside the school
That is Clow Reed’s power…
but,
Why did Tomoyo bring that brat here?
Because he came with me from
Tomoyo-chan’s house.
She was trying on clothes.
Did you eat food?
How could you eat food without me?!?
I also brought cake for Kero-chan.
– Really?
– Yup.
That’s great!
Tastes great!
Kero-chan you can really eat.
I am doing this for everybody.
What doing for everybody? You’re a pig!
You…
Actually she always helps me.
I can’t do anything.
It won’t be that way.
Li-kun has fulfilled his duty.
You have to believe in yourself.
Tomoyo, come here.
Let’s go?
ok
This hall is very scary.
Here we go again.
Your scared of ghosts right?
But…
It will be ok.
I’ve never seen a ghost before.
And I cant feel
anybody’s presence
Really?
Thank you Shao Lan-kun.
Shao Lan-kun?
Last time on the elavator,
he said that
I could call him Shao Lan-kun
and he said, “Can I call you Sakura?’
Really?
Right, Shao Lan-kun?
– Basketball?
– How could it just appear right here?
Its moving by itself!
Its probably a ghost!
No this isn’t a ghost.
Clow’s presence is growing
Lets go!
The basketball is gone.
It’s gone, really.
It flew into this classroom.
It’s ok, lets go to
a different room and look.
– What’s wrong?
– What are you doing?
I thought you wanted to go
to a different place and look.
I don’t think
that’s the right place.
This can also go to another classroom
What did you say?
How come this is now the music class?
How did this happen?
May be because the space
changed everything.
How did that happen?
– The basketball.
– I can feel a great power
Lets go over there and look.
– Tomoyo-chan!
– Sakura-chan!
Tomoyo-chan! Tomoyo-chan!
Tomoyo-chan!
How did we get back to this room?
It can’t be.
How could
she have disappeared like that?
Don’t cry.
Crying won’t help.
Hurry up and think.
How could we go back to room 5B.
Yes.
But what can we do?
Right! We can use the sword
card to slowly cut into the classes.
There’s no regular rules to follow
So we don’t know
what time shell be in room 5B.
So, how far the sword card
can cut is compared to its power.
If we don’t do it right,
then the walls that are too thick
Then well probably be stuck in the walls
Brat, have you ever learned how
to find people kind of magic?
If there is something that she
left behind then we can find her.
Oh, yes!
There’s Tomoyo-chan’s umbrella!
But Tomoyo is in that classroom
It won’t work! I can’t think straight or
I just can’t think of anything!
Tomoyo-chan. She said herself that
she’s not scared.
I have to hurry and find her out.
That’s Tomoyo-chan’s voice!
Wait for me, Tomoyo-chan.
I will keep on looking for you.
Right,
last time my shadow got caught was…
What’s wrong!?
Shao Lan-kun, Kero-chan!
Turn on the schools lights!
How come you’re saying that now?
– Please!
– Got ya!
O Key which hides the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me
I, Sakura, command you…
Release!
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura, thy new Mistress.
Shadow!
Shadow, go and find that persons shadow.
The song is coming from in there!
It’s in there!
Tomoyo-chan!
Sorry, you were here by yourself,
I bet you were scared!
No, Because I knew that
you would come and find me.
Tomoyo-chan
What’s wrong?
I felt someone over there.
Clow’s presence has disappeared.
Everything is back to normal.
Whenever she changes a card
her power goes up
I should be more careful.
I heard your song.
I thought it would be easier to find me.
When I saw that you disappeared,
I really wanted to cry.
But Shao Lan-kun said the crying won’t
do anything speech.
I would’ve cried really hard.
So I stopped crying
and thought about where are you
But I couldn’t.
But then I heard your song.
Once I heard it
I thought about where you were again.
Then I thought of the idea!
Thank you.
I should be thanking you.
Thank you for finding me.
But, still, I have this problem…
What?
Because we were separated,
I wasn’t able to videotape you!
Alright! Because you are so great,
I’ll let you videotape me
Thank you for offering!
That is no problem!
How should I pose?
Is this good?
How about this?
– Thank you, Shao Lan-kun.
– Why do you want to thank me?
Because you told me not to cry.
But it wasn’t just today.
So I really want to thank you.
– I…
– What?
No matter what you’re thinking,
if you don’t say it then you
won’t be able to transmit it.
Actually,
I…
To you…
You…
Sakura! Lets both go and be videotaped!
Now, I’ll give this to you.
Look I can pose this way.
This is my great pose.
This is really great!
Why don’t you put this on?
Then tomorrow at school I’ll
give you the tape for you.
Sakura, put your hand up a little more!