I guess I’m hungry…
I’ll have to apologize to
Kero-chan for eating without him.
Time to eat!
Yum! It’s good!
I know…
I know all about it.
The truth.
Onii-chan’s voice?
So, there’s no more need to hide it.
Onii-chan! And Yukito-san…
What you really are…
Onii-chan! You shouldn’t
be mean to Yukito-san!
– Sakura?!
– Sakura-chan?
CUT!!
What’s going on?
We’re making a movie.
A movie…
It’s for the cultural
festival at our school.
Oh! I didn’t know…
Well, let’s try that scene again
I’m sorry I got in the way.
I’ve got an idea
Hey, Sakura-chan
Yes?
Would you like to be in a movie
Y-yes!
[Sakura, Yukito,
and Disappearing Power]
You’re going to be in a movie?!!!!
Onii-chan’s class is doing it
for their cultural festival.
Sakura-chan is finally
making her film debut!
It’s really only a small part…
I’m sure I’ll be awful, but Akizuki-san,
from Onii-chan’s class, insisted.
I’m positive you’ll do fine!
So, what’s your costume like?
They haven’t decided, yet…
I see…
Do you think they’d let me help?
I’ll ask them.
Thank you!
So, what’s the story like?
Wait a second ~~
I have the script right here…
Meitan te Saigo no Jiken
(The Famous Detective’s Last Case)
Is it a mystery?
Yes. It’s set in the past,
around the Taisho era.
Onii-chan is the hero,
Yukito-san is the villain,
and I’m Yukito-san’s little sister.
But, if it’s set in the Taisho era,
finding sets around here must be hard.
Onii-chan’s class has been looking,
but they haven’t had much
luck finding a house they could use.
What kind of house are they looking for?
One with a large yard and a balcony…
This could be good.
I’ll have to make arrangements.
But you really surprised me.
You never said anything
about the movie, Onii-chan.
He probably didn’t want
you to know about it.
Oh? Why?
More tea, please.
Ok.
Oh!
Wait a minute, ok?
– Nice trick!
– Quiet, you.
What’s wrong?
I’m a little tired, all of a sudden.
It’s ok. I always get tired after tea.
Yuki…
Things can’t stay this way.
I know…
You…
Sorry for making you wait!
Ah, Sakura-chan.
Could I have some more tea as well?
Sure!
I’ll go get the cake.
Ok. Thank you.
Thanks.
You’re welcome!
Eh?
Is something wrong?
I must be imagining things…
What? You’ll let me film here?
I thought you’d say no, so I didn’t ask.
Consider it a gift for you, Ruby Moon.
Wow! Thank you!
However, I’d have thought you’d be
more suited to acting than directing.
But directing is the best!
I make the orders,
and everyone has to do
what I tell them! It’s so much fun!
I see.
Tomorrow everyone will be so happy!
Ok, back in a bit!
I’m sorry Spinnel.
You’ll have to stay out of sight.
I guess I can’t really avoid it, can I?
Is it really ok?
The new Card Mistress
may find out our secrets?
It’ll be alright,
if we watch what we say.
Sakura-san can be quite naive at times.
However, her brother is not.
He is very strong.
I have a use for him.
As well as Yue’s other form.
How are things over there?
My, you’re slow! Hurry up! I want
to start shooting as soon as possible.
Are those props ready, yet?
Sorry! Not yet!
Well, hurry up, then. We’re going to
need that in a bit!
You over there! Keep it up!
Hello. Are you an actor, too?
N-No. I wouldn’t have come.
But Daidouji said…
She asked you here to cheer Sakura on?
Sakura will be wearing
traditional clothes, right?
They should look good on her.
I…
CUUUUUUTE!!!! Looks nice!
They look really good on you! Wow!
SAKURA-CHAAN!!
You look so cute!
I knew you’d be perfect for the part.
Thanks for coming!
I’ll do my best!
You look very nice.
Do I?
This is your debut, right?
Yes! I do this scene and one later on.
This is such a beautiful house!
It looks like it should be in a movie!
Thank you very much.
So, three of you live here?
Yes.
I wonder who lived here before.
Three foreigners,
just like us.
Sakura-chan looks cute, doesn’t she?
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Tsukishiro-kun! Kinomoto-kun!
We need you now!
Ok!
We’re coming! Let’s go, Touya.
And this scene is…?
I told you before.
Weren’t you listening?
Listen this time.
Ok.
Calm down. You need to relax.
Relax?
Shall I fix your hair?
Sit here.
Thank you.
Eh?
I sense Clow-san’s aura from this chair
Is something wrong?
Oh? No… It’s a very nice chair.
It’s all I’ve had for a very long time.
Really?
Sakura-chan! We need you now!
Ok!
Sakura-chan’s right hand and
leg are moving in unison.
Is she really up to this?
Yuki?
Just a little tired.
And this early in the day, too…
Strange, isn’t it?
And then you give this to
your big brother, ok?
And look really sad.
Cut!
Ok, that’s all for this one!
You were very cute!
Really?
Yeah! Ok, let’s do the next scene!
All done!
Are you really finished?
Yeah…
But I was really awful…
No, you were amazing,
Sakura-chan!
And I was able to film “The Making
of Sakura-chan’s First Movie”, too!
I’m so happy!
Tomoyo-chan…
You were filming the entire time?
Ok, here it is!
Everyone else will be done
after the veranda scene, right?
Ok, Tsukishiro-kun, you will run
out here. Touya-kun will follow.
Tsukishiro-kun will
gaze out over the landscape
and Touya-kun
will confront him.
Any questions?
Nope, none.
Okay, let’s go!
Hey, stop that, Akizuki
I can’t help it! I’m so excited!
Ok, it’s up to you!
You alright?
I’m fine.
Action!
They’re starting.
I’ll go get some tea.
Can I help?
No, I’ll be fine.
I know who the criminal is, now.
Who was it?
That’s perfect…
I know all about it… You…
That’s it!
You…
Yuki!!!
Yukito-san!!
Yuki! Yuki!!
Sakura-chan!
O Key that holds
the power of the stars,
Reveal your true form to me.
By our contract,
I, Sakura, command you!
Release!
Open your Eyes!!! Yuki!!
Yuukii!!
YUKI!!
Yuki!
Yuki…
We should put him in a room to rest.
You…
Don’t worry, it’s no bother.
Touya…
I guess I fell asleep, again…
Something like that.
So… tired.
Yuki, if this keeps up,
you’ll disappear.
I won’t allow that to happen.
Why will I disappear?
When you lose track of time…
I know all about it… You…
Tsukishiro-kun! Are you okay?
Again…?
I’m okay…
Really, Akizuki-san.
Are you sure you’re not hurt anywhere?
Yeah.
I’m glad. Well, then,
let’s go finish that scene.
Yes?
I have something to say to him.
Without distractions.
O-ok.
This is bad…
I guess you bothered him too much.
What’ll I do?
At this rate,
I won’t become Touya’s most beloved.
I guess you’ll have
to live with it, then.
No! I don’t want to!
You’re really hopeless,
aren’t you?
But…
Eriol’s gonna be mad.
Sakura and
they are going to power-up.
I don’t think he’ll be too upset.
He might even be glad.
Yuki… I know all about it… You…
We’ve done that scene already…
No. Please listen.
I know you’re not human.
So you have no reason to hide from me.
We finally meet.
Your name is?
Yue.
Yukito wanted you to know.
About him and about me.
That is why I came.
That’s fine by me.
I heard you say you
wouldn’t let us disappear.
Yes.
Do you know what you’d have to do?
I know.
You can have my strength.
All of it.
You may never see your mother again.
It’s unfair that
I’m the only one who can see her.
However…
Without my power,
I won’t be able to protect Sakura.
Will you protect her for me?
There’s no need to ask.
I’d protect her, anyway.
I’m asking anyway.
Promise you’ll protect her.
Protect all of them.
That’s all you want for your magic?
That’s it.
It’s a deal then.
The two of you aren’t so different.
My power has returned.
Thanks you for your help.
You heard.
I’m sorry.
Because my power wasn’t strong enough…
you were disappearing.
And now Onii-chan
will never have his power back.
I’m so sorry.
It took almost all of Clow Reed’s magic
to create and maintain the cards
To think that a child
Like you has managed to do the same…
But…
It would hurt him,
if anything happened to you.
I promised him I’d protect you.
So, don’t cry.
Ok.
I’m sorry Onii-chan.
If you need anything,
I’ll help you.
I will protect you.
Ah! This aura!
It’s Clow!
Nobody’s here.
The aura is has gone too.
Yue’s power has returned.
And, now, Sakura will get even stronger.
Things are coming to an end.
I shall have to hurry.
So that’s what happened.
And your brother…?
He’s still asleep.
His classmates said they’d
send him home, later.
And, Yukito-san is watching over him.
He’ll be okay.
Thank you for being there.
Until tomorrow, okay?
Tomorrow, then.
Bye.
W… W… Welcome back! And how was the filming?
Onii-chan knew…
About you… And about Yukito and Yue.
WHAT???? I see…
So, he has no magic, now.
Kero-chan, did you know?
Did you know he was disappearing because
I wasn’t strong enough?
I knew.
Why didn’t you tell me?
Because there was nothing you could do.
What…?
You wouldn’t be able to support it.
All your magic is used in fighting.
Any more would completely wear you out.
And, so, there was nothing you could do.
I… guess I’m not good enough
to protect you, then
That’s not what I mean!
You’re always worrying about us,
and you are our friend.
There’s no one better!
Thank you.
You know, Kero-chan…
I was really worried
when I thought I might lose him.
It would be very hard to lose
my most important person.
Sakura…
You know, I don’t want to lose him
without letting him know I care.
I’m going to tell him…
how I feel.