Today, we’ll be cooking with oil…
…so everyone, put on your gear,
and let’s work hard, alright?
Enchanting Card?
It’s really popular now!
What’s this Enchanting Card?
For studying,
diets, or love.
There are all kinds of cards.
If you have the right card,
your wish will be granted.
They’re selling them at Maki’s shop.
I see.
Sakura, the oil is ready.
Yes.
Eh?
Sakura, are you alright?
I’m OK.
But when I look at that hot oil,
I’m scared…
If you don’t put
the croquette in the pot,
it won’t cook.
I wonder if I can do it…
Sakura.
You can do it.
You’re good at cooking.
I’ll try it again.
Sakura, the pot…
What do I do? What do I do?
What do I do?
I’m scared!
Are you alright?
Yes…
Everyone, when cooking with oil,
it’s very hot,
so please pay attention.
Right!
You’re not hurt, are you?
No, it’s nothing.
Mei Lin,
thanks for turning it off for me.
Kinomoto.
Um, next time I’ll be careful…
Where’s this Maki’s shop?
What?
[Sakura and the Enchanting Cards]
Thank you very much.
Huh?
H… hello…
Welcome.
Um, the Enchanting…
Enchanting…
Oh, you mean the cards?
We’ve got a lot of them.
Which one would you like?
L… L…
Yes?
That looks good, right?
Yep.
If you do it now, you should be fine.
Okay.
Sakura!
Are you okay?
Sorry about that…
No problem.
I’ll take care of it today, OK?
How come you’re so good at it?
Don’t worry,
you’ll be able to do this.
I wonder…
I’m home!
Welcome home!
I’ll take one!
Brother, don’t eat that!
Did you make this?
Dad did…
Then this should be fine!
What’s that supposed to mean?!
Good morning!
How did the deep-frying practice go?
I see. But I’m sure you’ll
get the hang of it.
Oh, Naoko, good morning!
Morning.
What’s wrong?
You look a little down.
Because today’s P.E.
is jumping practice.
But even though
I wasn’t able to do it before,
I’ll try hard today!
Go for it!
We’ll be rooting for you!
Okay!
Perfect as always.
Next, Li Mei Lin.
Okay!
Well, that’s to be expected.
Next, Yanagisawa.
Okay…
Naoko, go for it!
You practiced a lot!
You have the card and wished for this,
so you can do it!
Card?
Did it.
Pretty good.
It’s all thanks to the card.
Sakura…
Kinda looks like a Clow Card…
Is this one of the Enchanting Cards?
Yep. I was worried about
today’s jumping practice,
so I bought it yesterday.
Chiharu, you have one, too?
They really do look like Clow Cards.
Yeah…
Mei Lin, you want to see, too?
Oh, I have no interest in those cards.
Oh look,
it’s almost time to start class.
It’s so crowded.
You want a Cooking Card,
don’t you?
There’s also a Love Card, they said.
Thank you very much!
Mei Lin!
Sakura, Tomoyo, welcome!
Hello!
Mei Lin, you came to buy a card?
I… didn’t really…
You two also came to buy a card?
Yes.
Um, do you have a card that will help
me get better at cooking?
The Cooking one is, I think…
Sorry, I had them earlier,
but I already sold out.
I should have more tomorrow.
Excuse me…
I’m sorry, but you can
come back tomorrow.
I didn’t really…
Shao Lan has been mine for
a long time, so…
It’d be all right if they ran out
of these Love Cards, but…
For now, for now…
Really, me and Shao Lan
are doing fine, but…
It looks like a Clow Card…
You see, it’s not like
I’m trying to win your heart or anything…
See you later, Kinomoto!
What was that?
They look like Clow Cards?
The pictures and writing
are different, though.
“Whatever you wish for
will come true,” they say.
Today, thanks to a card,
Naoko was able to do the
jumping practice for the first time.
So, do you have one of those cards?
They sold out.
So I’ll pick one up tomorrow.
Sakura, I made some pudding.
Do you want some?
Sure!
Something wrong.
So serious?
A card that looks like a Clow Card,
huh?
Shao Lan!
What?
Lunch! Shall we eat together?
I was going to eat
in the cafeteria today…
I have done!
So, let’s go eat!
Wow, looks great.
Thank you.
Tomoyo, you’re good at cooking, too.
When you say that,
it makes me want to make more.
Next time,
I’ll make lunch for us.
So, shall we eat?
Sakura!
Yukito!
You eat croquettes?
Yeah. Your croquettes are really good.
Yukito, you like croquettes?
Yeah, I love them.
I see.
Now I have to try even
harder to make croquettes!
I guess I’ll have to buy
that Cooking Card…
Hey, why do we have
to go so far away…
Come here.
You…
Li-kun and Mei Lin,
you’re eating lunch, too?
Eh!
What’s wrong, Shao Lan?
I’ll introduce you, OK?
My classmate, Li Mei Lin.
Li’s cousin…
Fiancee!
Fiancee?
No, no…
Why’re you so nervous
all of a sudden, Shao Lan…
Oh, Sakura, Tomoyo!
Are you going to buy a card?
Yep.
We ended up buying more!
They still have them?
They have a lot today.
Really?
Yeah.
They have all kinds, don’t they?
This is the one.
The card to become better at cooking.
Sakura?
I feel the aura of a Clow Card.
Nope. None of these are Clow Cards.
But the aura was just here…
Maki!
Yes?
The card that was here,
what happened to it?
I just sold it.
What kind of card was it?
If I remember right, it was “Shot”…
“Shot”?
As in shooting?
Do you remember who bought the card?
I think it was one of
the girls in your class, but…
Was it Chiharu or Naoko?
Sorry, I don’t remember that much.
I’ll come back!
Sakura!
I lost again?!
We’ve got trouble!
It looks like
there was a real Clow Card
at Maki’s shop!
And someone from my class bought it!
Do you know which card it was?
Shot!
What?!
Shot?
This is bad! Shot is an attack card!
If it shoots and hits you,
it’ll really hurt you!
Find it quickly!
Right.
Chiharu and Naoko…?
I didn’t see either of them!
We’ll use Fly to go look for them!
Key which hides the power of darkness…
…reveal thy true form to me.
By the covenant,
I, Sakura, command thee.
Release!
Fly!
I don’t see them.
Where could they have gone?
Sakura!
Kero.
Did you figure out who has it?
Not yet…
Hurry up and find it!
Even if you say that…
Over there!
That Mei Lin…
Calling herself
my fiancee in front of him…
The aura of a Clow Card!
Naoko!
Sakura!
Could you show me the
Enchanting Cards you’re carrying?
Sure…
Is that all?
Yeah…
Oh yeah,
do you know where Chiharu went?
She said she was going straight home.
Thanks. See you later!
Sakura!
Hmm?
Not her?
Maybe it’s Chiharu…
Let’s hurry!
Right!
There!
Chiharu!
Oh, what’s wrong?
I’d like to see
the Enchanting Cards you’re carrying.
Okay.
Nope. N… Not… No…
Neither Naoko nor Chiharu…
Then who?
What’s wrong?
When you were at Twin Bells earlier,
was it just you and Naoko?
Maybe Mei Lin came out a little earlier.
Mei Lin?
It looked like she didn’t
even notice us, though.
Sakura.
Eh!
The little wench, huh?
We’d better find her.
Maybe it’s alright
if it hurts her a little.
I’ll go check Mei Lin’s house.
You two should go look for her.
Got it. Let’s meet back at school.
Sakura, let’s get moving!
It’s weird.
What’s up?
It’s Li.
Li!
The aura of a Clow Card…
I know, Mei Lin has it.
Mei Lin is holding a Clow Card?
I don’t know for sure yet, but…
It’s an attack card, so it’s dangerous!
Which card is it?
Shot!
Shot?
Fly!
Get on!
Hurry up and get on, brat!
Show me the direction…
That way!
At school?
With this card, Shao Lan’s heart…
Yes.
There!
She’s got it, dammit…
Mei Lin!
Shao Lan!
Why’re you with Kinomoto?
Mei Lin, that card you’ve got…
This?
That’s a real Clow Card!
No way!
This is an Enchanting Card I bought!
It’s a dangerous card!
Hurry up and hand it over!
What’s with you two?!
She’s really stubborn, ain’t she?
With this card
I’ll aim at Shao Lan’s heart!
Oh, no!
Li!
Brat!
Shao Lan!
Brat, behind you!
Shield!
Sakura, seal it quickly!
It’s not weak enough yet!
I’ve gotta do something,
or it won’t stop.
Shao Lan!
It’s only aiming at me!
When you get a chance, seal it!
But…!
Hurry!
Those attacks are
only going to get stronger!
Oh, no!
No!
That’s it! Li!
Got it!
Mirror, whatsoever
looks upon you, return it!
Mirror!
Now!
Return to thy true form, Clow Card!
Hey, using the Mirror card
to reflect the shot
back was a pretty good idea.
Oh yeah, where’s Mei Lin?
Over here.
Tomoyo!
When did you get here, Tomoyo?
I was able to capture
your victory on tape.
It’s ready any time.
I did it!
You’re doing fine.
Yes.
I wonder if the Enchanting Cards
granting all those wishes…
…was really because of the Clow Card?
It’s not incantations,
magic, or anything.
people keep trying hard,
they can do anything.
Sakura, this is a pretty good croquette.
All right, I can eat it myself!
No you can’t, Shao Lan, you’re hurt!
Li, how’s your injury?
It’s no big deal.
Shao Lan, we’re still
in the middle of eating.
Kinomoto!
For me?
Thanks for getting
the Clow Card this time…
…but next time we’ll win!
Thanks, Mei Lin!
I appreciate this!
But, Sakura,
you were able to make croquettes
this time, right?
Yep! But there’s still
room for improvement.
And Mei Lin gave me this.
I’m glad.