[Sakura’s first trial as a thief]
Not done yet?
Just a little more.
Wait just a bit longer.
My patience is about to snap.
Done!
Well, let me see
Here
Eh? Is that supposed to be me?
Yeah, I drew it pretty cute, huh?
I don’t have such a goofy face
Really? I think it looks pretty close
It doesn’t.
Look closely.
Don’t you think
my brow brings out my eyes?
Or perhaps it should be more smooth
Sakura, time to eat
OK!
Hey!
Listen to what
somebody is saying until the end
Later, OK?
Really…
This is me?
I won’t allow it
It looks great
What were you doing upstairs?
I was drawing.
Tomorrow for a special lesson we’re going
to the museum to draw
So you were practicing?
Yeah
Even so, you seemed pretty lively
That’s because if I don’t talk,
I can’t draw well
If you make noise like that in the museum,
they’ll kick you out
No they wouldn’t
But, try not to interfere with
the people who came to see the paintings
Will they really kick me out?
I don’t think they would do that, but…
I am the head of this museum
What we would like you to draw
Are the things on this floor
and in the courtyard
Tomoyo-chan, it really is quiet in here
Yes, it is very peaceful
That’s right
Well then, those who want to draw
in the courtyard, come with me
Tomoyo-chan, where are you going?
I thought I would draw this sculpture here
If you like, we can both draw it
Yeah
Chiharu-chan and the others left
Would you
rather have gone to the courtyard?
No. So, shall we draw?
Yes
Geeze
Shuu…
I’m sorry
Why, that Kero-chan
I’m done, how about you Tomoyo-chan?
Incredible
Tomoyo-chan, why don’t we go look
at the courtyard for a bit?
I want to finish my picture
Well, I’ll be right back then
I wonder how you get to the courtyard
What are you doing?
Let go! Let go!
Why are you trying to damage the painting?
Why would I damage it?
Then what is this?
That is my papa’s painting
It’s a picture papa painted of me,
but somebody changed it
They drew that woman over it
That’s impossible
Wait!
Why you!
Come quietly. So, come this way
Smile by Tenkai Tachibana
Sakura-chan
It’s already time for us to leave
Yes!
A picture in the museum moved?
Yeah, then all of a sudden
I couldn’t hear anything,
but only for an instant
It couldn’t be that, could it?
Something with a grudge
that goes beyond death
I’m sure that picture is cursed and
Was it that scary?
It wasn’t scary at all, at the time
Sakura!
You are sensitive to ghosts
or monsters aren’t you?
Which means, couldn’t it just be.
A Clow Card
Shall we go check together?
Yeah
Sakura-chan?
Good evening
Yukito-san
What’s going on? This late at night
Umm …Let’s see
I thought I would go look at the moon
There are a lot of stars out too
I wonder if Touya is home
Yes, he is home
Umm, about my brother
Sakura-chan is asleep upstairs.
I can’t see her tonight
Yukito-san
But, don’t stay out too late
Yeah
Swinging from depression to being happy.
What a busy person you are
I wonder if he thought I was rude
But, then he was looking out for me
But, then
How idiotic
Hurry up, Tomoyo is waiting for us
Yukito-san
Silent?
That means without sound, right?
Exactly,
It’s a card that hates loud things
That’s why we think
it’s in a quiet place like a museum
What is Silent’s power?
Today it only made the sound disappear
That’s not all.
When she goes shhh at the same
time as the sound goes away
At the same time, what?
I don’t really know
And you call yourself the beast of the seal?
She doesn’t really talk,
so I don’t know her personality
Sakura-chan
Come, let’s change
I thought so
These clothes are
more restrained than the usual
Yes, a cat burglar mustn’t stick out
I’m not really stealing anything though
But, you’re sneaking into a guarded museum,
so you have to dress appropriately
What’s that?
It’s the schedule chart for the museum guards
Wow! How did you get that?
I went back to the museum earlier
and picked it up.
Umm…
According to this,
it’s about an hour from now
when the guard comes to
where the problem picture is
We don’t have much time
Yeah
To be safe,
I’ll set my alarm for five minutes before then
Well then, mission start
I wonder what they’re doing
It’s suspicious
We’re plenty suspicious ourselves
They must be here to steal works of art
So it’s a thief?
What should we do?
We can’t leave them alone
Let’s have them leave
What do you plan on doing?
With this
Who are you?
What are you doing there?
Hurry and get out
Who is there?
Are you over there?
They seem pretty perseverant,
they aren’t running
That voice just now
It sounded like a child
There is no choice, do it
OK
Come out!
Listen well,
I am the protective god of this place
Leave now!
What do you mean protective god?
You’re probably the one defacing the pictures
It seems they are coming over here
That was not expected
Don’t move from over there
Umm…
Um…
It was a child after all
Ah, this kid
Do you know him?
Today in here
Hurry and help me
It seems that he’s waking up
Owl…
Are you OK?
Don’t panic
This is just a stuffed animal
But, earlier
That was just ventriloquism
I thought you were a thief
What a weird face
I was all surprised for nothing
I’m not a thief,
but what are you people doing here?
If you are the criminal
who defaced the painting,
I won’t forgive you.
We didn’t do that
We’re wonderful cat burglars
We wouldn’t do that
Cat burglars? That means
That’s not it, we just came back
for something we forgot
Well then, what about those clothes?
This is
Umm
Our hobby
As long as you aren’t the ones
who defaced the painting.
I’m in a hurry
Wait a moment, Yuuki-kun
How did you know my name?
I see, at that time
Yuuki-kun, were you really
trying to damage the painting?
I wasn’t trying to damage it,
I was trying to return it to how it was
My papa drew that painting
My papa is the artist Tenkai Tachibana
I know of Tenkai-sensei,
he has painted many wonderful pieces
But last year didn’t he…
Autumn of last year,
he died of his illness.
That painting was made last summer,
on what was the last family trip with papa
It was a painting he wanted to paint his best
as a memory of coming to the sea with me
Mama says it was her favorite painting too
And then,
somebody drew on top of it
On top of my precious memory with papa
How terrible! I know how you feel,
when my picture was drawn over
I was really angry
Yuuki-kun, we will help too
I don’t need it.
I can do it alone
What? When we are going
through all the trouble of
It’s ventriloquism
Don’t say that, let’s go together
Do as you like,
just don’t get in the way
What an unlovable child
That took more time than we expected,
let’s hurry
Yeah
I can’t use magic in front of Yuuki-kun
And we can’t scare him off
I’ll talk to him, and at that time OK?
It’s this picture
This is definitely Silent
The graffiti is still new
It’s oil paint so I should be
able to get it off if
You really know your stuff
It’s because I want to be a painter like my papa
I am sure you can be
But Yuuki-kun,
repairing oil paints is difficult
Why don’t you
leave it to the museum people?
I can’t leave it to them
Can you do it?
I can. I will fix it myself
If you speak too loud, the guard will come
Huh?
The courtyard?
It happened again
When I get close to papa’s picture
I am suddenly outside
This must be Silent’s power
When you make noise,
it throws you outside huh?
Good thing it didn’t do that earlier today
Can you believe this?
I think it’ll be ok if I came during the day
since a monster won’t come
What can we do?
A monster?
Say, Yuuki-kun .
This happened because you spoke too loud
during the day and just now
So, if you stay quiet,
Wouldn’t the monster not do anything?
So, we just have to stay quiet?
Yeah
But if it is a monster, I can’t get it off
Then are you going home?
No, we can get in from over here
Let’s go
If you use magic
you can blame it on the monster
It can’t be
At just that sound?
Quiet!
We don’t have much time
Ish…
Ish… Ish…
Damn it
It was just a sneeze
This means you can’t recite a spell
Isn’t there some way?
I’ll do it alone
Wait, Yuuki-kun!
The guard will be coming soon
If we get caught too
what will we do about Silent?
Who is there?
Don’t run! Wait right there!
He was caught
Here is bad too
Let’s hide
We have to help him
You’re the one from earlier today
Let go! Let go!
What should we do?
Oh yeah!
Shadow,
project me through the glass
Shadow!
It’s a ghost, let go of me!
Calm down
Here goes.
Hey, wait!
I did it!
Just what I would expect
That just leaves
Return to your rightful form
Here
Ah,
Thank you
Return to your rightful form
Clow Card!
That was a big success
Where are they hiding?
Yeah
Geeze
It’s terrible! The picture was changed!
It was no good after all. The guard saw me
That’s not true, look
It’s back to normal, papa
So you’re a girl
I’m sorry!
I call you Yuuki-kun.
No, I’m sorry too
The long hair is very cute
Yeah
Take care!
Thank you, both of you
Thank you a lot!
Bye bye!
She was trying her best for her father
Yuuki-kun, I mean Yuuki-chan
The heart of a child thinking
of the parent
Pretty good story isn’t it?
Kero-chan,
that’s pretty cool
The mission is complete and our plan is over
By the way, that was a pretty good
way to think of using Shadow
I remembered your shadow
So it was all because of me
It’s the aura of a Clow Card