It hurts!!
No! I messed up the cake again!
Mei Lin, haste makes waste.
If you stay calm, it should work.
Stay calm?
That’s the hardest thing for me
You know…
This is the result of Mei Lin-sama
trying to make a delicious cake for you,
Shao Lan-sama.
It is the thought that counts.
I’m sorry. I’ll clean up properly.
Oh! I’ll go get it!
Hello, this is Li.
Mother!
This is a cake…
Mei Lin-sama made it with all her heart.
But you know…
Shao Lan-sama,
I am sure you are a broad-minded person.
So are you going to bear
in mind such trivial matters?
But it’s not only this…
Say, she’d come hugging me
all of a sudden.
Shao Lan!
It hurts.
Hey! How many times have I told you
not to come hugging me all of a sudden!
What happened?
I don’t wanna go back!
[Sakura’s Farewell to Mei Lin]
Oh my! The pictures are very well taken.
Onii-chan said he took
it at the Literary Fest.
Your brother must be very good
at taking pictures.
It’s just the camera was good.
– Oh, Mei Lin-chan!
– Good morning!
Good morning!
Hey, I’ve got some pictures
from the play we did earlier…
Mei Lin-chan?
What’s wrong?
What? You’re going back?! When?
– Next week…
– So sudden?!
Li-kun!
Did you tell the teacher
that you’re going back to Hong Kong?
There might be other things
besides just taking attendance.
Let her know soon.
Shao Lan, you don’t care
if I go back or not.
There’s nothing I can do.
Auntie said you had to go back.
There’s nothing you can do…
Am I being a bother to you?!
Am I a bother being here?
– No, that’s not it.
– Shao Lan you jerk!!
– Mei Lin!
– Mei Lin-chan!
Mei Lin has to go back.
I have an announcement for everyone.
Mei Lin-san is transferring
back to Hong Kong next week.
This must be sad for her.
Bye-bye! Bye!
Mei Lin.
Mei Lin-chan!
Um… mm…
Why don’t you stay over at my house?
Fo… For what?
For what?
Umm…
Father is going to make
a really tasty cake!
Father’s really good at cooking,
so it’s gotta taste very good.
Besides…
Besides… I want to chat with you
about many things!
– Okay.
– Really?!
I’ll come over tonight.
Tonight…?
I’m sorry for borrowing Mei Lin-chan
all of a sudden.
Why did you ask her all of a sudden…
It’s true that I have lots of things
I want to chat with Mei Lin.
Besides, she’ll be so sad
having to part with you.
I’ll let Wei know about it.
Yuki, stay for dinner.
You’re on your own, right?
Thanks.
Sorry for bothering you all the time.
There you are. I’m home.
Sorry for bothering you.
You’re very welcome here.
Sakura has a friend over?
Yes, she’s staying over, she said.
Is it Tomoyo-chan?
No, I’ve never met her before.
She came from Hong Kong.
Hong Kong?
Oh, I’m so full.
Your father is really a good cook.
I feel envy.
Here. Thanks.
Come to think of it,
where’s that bath sponge?
Oh, Kero’s at Tomoyo-chan’s house.
Geez… Kicking’ me out
coz that girl is staying’ over.
Well, this is probably
much more fun for me!
I got so much to eat, and the food
is so good here. Isn’t that great?
Occasionally like that is good.
My my, I look real cool!
I hope Sakura-chan is having
a nice chat with Mei Lin…
Oh, this is so good!
This too!
This one too!
I’m so envious!
I’ll have to push myself
to finish them all!
This is so good.
It’ll be such a waste if
I don’t finish all of it.
You know,
Li-kun is a very good cook too.
I guess.
I don’t think Li-kun thinks that
you’re a bother, you know?
Because he’s always worried about you.
Whether it’s at school,
or when we’re capturing the cards.
I know.
I know that.
I know…
Two mailboxes? Which one is true?
I know.
It it’s different than what I want.
Hey, since when did you
start liking that guy?
Hm… Eh…
He was Touya’s classmate,
and he came over… And…
And you have a crush on him?
Wh… What about you?
For me… it wasn’t exactly
like a crush…
In Hong Kong,
I lived very close to Shao Lan.
Because I don’t have magic powers,
I didn’t need to study magic.
But Shao Lan and I did have
martial art lessons together with Wei.
Shao Lan-sama.
But Shao Lan doesn’t smile at all.
Nor does he like to play.
Like how he is now?
Even worse. I’ve never seen him
did anything fun before.
That’s why I’d watch him sometimes.
But, you know…
Is there something wrong?
The bird…
It flew away…
Auntie gave it to me…
It was my favorite…
Don’t cry.
Shao Lan-sama! Where are you going?!
I’m going to look for it!
So he went looking for it.
And then, the rain started to come down,
but still Shao Lan hasn’t come back.
Shao Lan…
Don’t worry.
I am sure Shao Lan
will bring back the bird.
Shao Lan.
Shao Lan…
This is the bird, right?
Hey! What’s the matter?
Are you hurting somewhere?
So there was such a story.
I guess from then on…
I’m not too clear too.
I’ve grown to like him a lot,
That why I love him.
But it’s not the same for Shao Lan.
He made a promise with me, but…
A promise?
I don’t have any magic.
Even if I stay with him,
I can’t do anything for him.
There’s no need for me to be here
to help him look for the cards.
Mei Lin…
I sense a Clow Card!
Sakura! I’m heading towards
where the Clow Card is!
Are you done yet?
Yeah. Okay. Gotcha.
Mei Lin-chan, you’re not going?
Maybe I shouldn’t…
Everything in the art
museum is doubled.
Could this be…
That way?
Let’s go, Mei Lin-chan!
But even if I go…
Mei Lin-chan!
There are plenty of things
that no one else but you can do.
Crap.
No! It is Twin after all.
What? Didn’t your house
become double as well?
Shao Lan!
Are you all right?
Even that old man!
Kero-chan! Sakura!
What have you been doing?
You’re late!
I’m sorry!
Shao Lan! You okay?
Watch out!
Jump!
Wind! Become a chain of admonition!
Windy!
Return to thy form which thou should be!
Clow Card!
How come?!
It won’t work
if you only capture one of the twins.
They have to be caught exactly
at the same moment!
At the same moment!
Jump!
What to do…
– Has to be at the same moment…?
– Right.
King of Thunder, descend!
I see!
Thunder!
That won’t work!
Just as I thought.
They noticed a gap in time…
If it’s not exactly
the same moment…
What? Exact same moment?
Even there is just a gap,
they will notice.
Wanna try one more time?
But is it gonna work?
We gotta try, if nothing else!
Mei Lin-chan!
Li-kun! You and Mei Lin-chan
might be able
to move just like the Twin.
can stop their action.
– Kinomoto-san!
– You can do it!
Because you’ve always
watched Li-kun!
But…
I… might be a bother…
Let’s do it! Mei Lin!
Got it!
Awesome!
Are you okay?
Now!
Return to thy form which
thou should be!
Clow Card!
I’ve never thought
of you as a bother.
I’ve never imagined that
The noisy bratty girl’s
gonna leave us.
She’ll be sad…
You didn’t forget
anything else, right?
Let me take care
of boarding procedures.
I’ll contact you
when we arrive.
Hey, do you remember
that promise?
Promise?
I love you!
I love you, Shao Lan!
I’ll be your bride!
Hey, wait a second! I…
Shao Lan! Is there someone else
you love more than me?
No, there isn’t, but…
So I’ll be your bride!
Because you’re
the one I love most!
Hey, listen…
I’ll give up
if you find someone you
love more than me.
But until that day,
I’m your bride!
– Okay?
– What do you mean “okay”…?
Okay?!
Do whatever you want.
Until you find someone you love most,
I’m your fiancee.
Mei Lin…
Mei Lin-chan…
We’ll see each other again, right?
Of course! I’ll definitely
come back to be near Shao Lan.
Mei Lin-sama! It is time!
Okay!
Thanks for helping me
with magic at that time.
See you again!
See you again, Mei Lin-chan!