Yay! Yay!
You seem to be enjoying yourself,
Sakura-chan.
Yeah.
What is this?
Seijou high
is having its culture fair this Sunday.
Oh yeah,
big brother has been home late
recently because of preparations.
Why don’t you come along with a friend?
Eh!
Perhaps you already got one from Touya.
No,
last year he gave me one,
but not yet this year.
Perhaps he is worried about the play.
Play?
Here.
With this you can eat what
ever you want at the stands.
Thank you.
Tomoyo-chan!
Sakura, you were just so cute
as you were lost in memory…
[Sakura, Touya, and Cinderella]
Hurry,
it’s almost show time.
Kinomoto,
the shoes are broken.
Try and do something about it.
Kinomoto-kun, you’re good.
Are you good at things like this?
Sorta.
Ha!
You’ll make a good husband.
Really, really.
Kero-chan would be jealous.
Oh yeah.
Eh!
Kero-chan asked me to get a souvenir.
Oh!
Hi.
Yukito-san, good afternoon.
A kimono.
Our class’s shop
is selling sweets,
so we did it Japanese style.
So, come in.
Welcome.
Eh!
What do you want?
We have lemonade and hiyashiame.
Then I will have hiyashiame.
Umm, I’ll have lemonade.
OK, wait one moment.
Yukito-san.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Delicious.
What is it?
I feel like somebody is looking at me.
Huh?
Would you like another?
Yeah.
It seems like he has been
in here for quite some time.
Eh?
Here.
My shift is over.
Shall I show you around?
Will you?
That’s heavy.
Really?
Kinomoto,
Are you sure
you aren’t a robot or something?
You’re too strong.
You guys…
Kinomoto-kun really is great.
At first I thought
he seemed a bit scary,
but he is pretty nice.
He has good looks.
He is the ace of the soccer team.
He is also good at cooking and sewing.
Don’t you think so too, Youko?
Eh?
Why do you ask me?
After all you are cute
and have a nice personality.
Yeah, yeah.
You are the president of the drama club,
and are good at taking care of people.
Wouldn’t you do well with Kinomoto-kun?
Geeze,
that has nothing to do with it.
I guess Youko really
does like Kinomoto-kun.
Yeah,
but there is a rumor all the girls
that have approached Kinomoto-kun
were rejected.
That Kinomoto-kun and Tsukishiro-kun
don’t have girlfriends
is one of the seven mysteries
of our school.
How cute.
You like such childish things?
But it’s cute.
You can have it
if you pass through five
of our regulars
and score.
Eh?
A hundred yen per attempt.
Here.
You are going to do it?
Yeah.
Wait just a bit.
Yes.
Go in!
Oh! Huh!
Eh?
Hey
There is no way our club members
can win against Tsukishiro-kun.
That’s not true.
Here.
Thank you.
You’re going again?
I need two more stuffed animals.
Tsukishiro!
Join our team.
I’ll think about it.
It’s just about time.
Time for what?
Time for play
Our class play.
We’re doing it in the gym.
Is my brother in it?
Yeah.
I wonder what role it is.
Ha…
Look forward to seeing it.
Umm…
Excuse me!
Eh
Are you in it?
Me?
Yes.
Woo…
What is your part?
Canned mackerel.
Eh!
Mackerel?
Canned?
Yep.
Seems like a pretty delicious role.
You’re right,
canned mackerel is delicious.
Next is the play Cinderella
by 2nd year D class.
Class D
is your brother’s right?
Why would there
be canned mackerel
in Cinderella?
Sob. Sob.
Long ago,
in a land far away
there was a beautiful
and lovable girl
named Cinderella.
Sob…
This voice.
Cinderella was bullied
by her mother and sisters
every day,
but was still a good girl
who worked very hard.
Bro… Brother
He’s …
Big brother?
Your brother seems very popular.
Are you cleaning well?
It is dirty over here,
useless girl.
Useless!
Hey, the miso soup this morning
was terrible.
Ah!
Were you trying to kill us?
Oh my God!…
There is a ball at the castle today.
Oh yes.
Yes, there is a ball.
The prince is going
to choose his bride.
From the girls that
come to the ball.
I will be joined
with the prince.
Me!
No, me.
It will be me.
La…
This seems fun.
Hey, be a little jealous.
Ah, I want to go to.
The three of us are going,
you stay home.
Have dinner ready too.
Ramen, we’ll have ramen.
Shall we go?
Yes, let’s go.
Let’s dance.
Woo…
I want to go to the ball too.
He doesn’t seem to
want to go at all.
Hello.
Wow
It’s Yukito-san.
Tsukishiro-san is popular too.
Yukito-san is wonderful.
You seem troubled,
Cinderella.
This is an invitation to the ball,
but why do you do this?
Because I am a wizard.
What is that on your head?
Canned mackerel.
A discarded canned mackerel
that gained magical power
over many years.
Why a canned mackerel?
There is a moral to the story,
treat things with respect.
The prince has arrived.
Eh!
I think you all know,
but today is a ball
to determine my bride.
Eh!
Big brother.
Youko,
your line.
Oh, what a wonderful young maiden.
Well then, shall we dance?
Weird play.
Huh!
Is something wrong?
Perhaps my imagination?
Cinderella,
I don’t want to let
you leave like this.
But if I don’t go make the ramen…
Please be my bride.
But the canned mackerel told me
to be home by midnight.
Something…
Feels strange.
Cinderella, I…
Prince.
Ah!
Eh!
Big brother!
Touya!
Ummm…
What’s going on!
It was a Clow Card after all.
We have to go somewhere
people don’t go.
Sakura-chan.
Li-kun!
What a great story, it made me cry.
Parent-child relationships
sure are great.
Kero-chan, it’s terrible,
the play my brother is in…
What?
Yeah. Yeah.
That is the Mist card,
it corrodes everything
that gets in the fog.
If you don’t hurry
your brother’s footing
will crumble too.
This can’t be.
It would be good
if you could gather Mist
all into one place to take care of it.
Gather it?
Ah!
Eh!
Youko!
Kinomoto-kun.
Touya.
Touya, let go!
You’ll fall too.
At this height
I will just be hurt a little,
so…
Touya
Gather? How can I gather it?
Oh yeah.
Shadows, gather all the fog within you.
Shadow!
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card!
Woo…
Wah…
Wind come forth!
Thank you.
Touya!
Youko!
Thank god.
Touya, are you OK? Not hurt?
Somehow.
Mic test. Mic test.
Even so it is unfortunate,
even though I brought my video camera
I missed your action.
Ha…
But it is good
it didn’t become a big accident.
Really.
Thank you.
For helping me.
I don’t remember helping you.
Yukito-san.
That was pretty exciting.
Your canned mackerel was wonderful.
Thank you.
Where is my brother?
He’s fine.
But he was called out
to talk to somebody.
Umm… I…
I love you.
Thank you, but I…
You have somebody you like?
Yes.
I had that feeling.
Sorry for crying.
Don’t worry about me.
Ah, they are doing a bonfire.
May I ask one request?
Dance with me.
It’s my brother.
Thank you.
Hey, Kinomoto-kun.
I only promised Youko.
A little too cool.
You should have told me
you were in the play.
You told her?
Yeah.
Shall we dance?
Eh?
Let’s go.
This will make a good video.