We went on a camping trip to the sea.
I swam a lot and it was very fun.
At night we did kimodameshi in the cave.
Are you writing a diary?
Yeah.
Let me see.
So this is when you went to the sea?
I wanted to go too.
What is this? July ,today is…
July?
Today is August, isn’t it?
Yeah.
You are writing about
previous months now?
Yeah.
Isn’t a diary something
that you write in every day?
I was busy with other things.
I finished my free research.
So then your homework is finished?
It isn’t finished?
Still a bit left.
What is left?
Umm… the math drills,
picture diary,
construction project,
and the book report.
You have that much left?
We have too much homework.
Hey, hey…
But I wrote this much in thirty minutes.
You don’t have the weather written.
That’s fine, it is all written
in old newspapers.
Hmm, you seem experienced.
Sorta.
Is that something to be proud of?
[Sakura and the summer vacation homework]
We’re now visiting Mt. Kumaya.
Hello sir, as we speak of Kumaya,
their specialty of sweet
bean jelly comes to mind.
This looks very good.
All right, now I just have
the weather left to do.
Newspaper. Newspaper.
Eh!
Dad, do you know where
the old newspapers are?
I got rid of them this morning.
What should I do?
What did you want to see?
The weather over summer vacation.
Will this do?
Eh?
I need it for my research.
I have couple months worth.
Here.
I don’t have the pressure readings,
so I wonder if it will do?
Yeah! Thanks Dad.
August 30th, clear.
Next is the math drills.
Huh? Where are my drills?
What?
Fourth graders are doing
such easy problems?
They are pretty hard.
Well then I can do them for you.
Eh?
Well, if my conditions are met.
What? What?
Sweet bean jelly from Kumaya he says.
Kero-chan really does like sweets.
It’s not my fault if he gets fat.
What are you doing?
Yukito-san!
The annual summer
tradition of our house.
Tradition?
She always is running
around on the 31st
because she hasn’t finished
her summer homework.
Big brother!
Is this a construction project?
Yes.
Last year was a paper made
savings box wasn’t it?
In the shape of a penguin.
But unusable.
Why couldn’t you use it?
There was no place to put in the money.
What is it this year?
A bird house, right?
Yes.
I bet this time
there is no entrance.
There is none!
You really forgot it?
I’m not good at these sort of things.
Shall I do it for you?
What?
Five of my chores.
Did you finish the homework?
Not quite yet.
I haven’t yet either.
You haven’t.
Yes, I have the math drills left,
what about you?
I haven’t decided on a
book for the book report.
Then do you want to go
to the library together?
Sure.
Well then, let’s meet at the bridge
in the penguin park.
OK.
Tomoyo-chan!
Let’s go.
The pool is closing today.
Summer is just about over.
Do you want to go play now?
No!
Tomoyo-chan, let’s hurry.
There are so many.
It wasn’t only our class
that had a lot of homework.
How about over here?
Forget it.
Today is an unlucky day.
But this is the only place open.
In this morning’s fortune it said that
dealing with females will bring chaos.
Chaos?
Done.
I am finished too.
I did half
of Sakura’s drills.
Thank you.
Which means the bean jam.
I’ll buy it tomorrow.
Shall we check our answers
off each other?
Yeah.
There is no need to check
the first half that I did.
It is perfect.
The answer to the first question is…
One thousand yen
Three hundred fifty yen.
Tomoyo, you can’t get
such an easy question wrong.
Let’s see, you purchase
5 pencils at 70 yen,
this is 350 yen isn’t it?
That’s why you pay 1000 yen
and get change.
I don’t know.
How ya doin? I like modayaki.
What is this?
What’s wrong?
No bean jam.
Why?!
The appointed book
The thinnest book of the ones we could
read was Little Pig Story, right?
Did you also read Little Pig Story?
No, I chose a different book.
Was it interesting?
Yes, very much.
Maybe I will do that one.
What was the title?
This one.
T… This one?
I guess I will read the
Little Pig after all.
Eh?
Oh, four copies are taken out right now.
Eh!
But there is one copy left.
Where is it?
It should be in the building.
There wasn’t any copy on the shelf.
In order to read it in the building
it doesn’t have to go past here.
So somebody in here is reading it?
Either that or somebody put
it back in the wrong place.
Let’s go look for it.
Yeah.
I bet it is delicious.
That bean jam.
That reporter on TV
really seemed to enjoy it.
Geeze, Sakura didn’t
have to get that angry.
What is it brat?
Don’t you understand this character?
The kanji are used differently
in Hong Kong and Japan.
Don’t get in the way.
I was heading this way too.
It is distracting.
Doesn’t it just mean you don’t have
enough power of concentration?
What an irritable guy.
Well you are studying,
so I will let you off for today.
Huh? I am sure I left it here.
Little Pig… Little Pig…
Sakura, what are you looking for?
Above you. Above.
I can’t find the book for the homework.
What is it called?
Little Pig Story.
Little Pig…
Ah, the brat had that one.
Li-kun did?
It was there.
Huh?
Where did he go?
Let me see that for a moment.
Did you find it?
I was told Li-kun has it.
Oh? I found it once.
Eh? I wonder if there are two.
It is strange.
Hey, don’t cry.
There it is.
Kero-chan.
It’s a Clow Card.
It is still close by.
This is…
Again.
There it is.
Is something wrong?
No.
In a place like this?
Li-kun!
Li-kun.
We are probably facing the Move card.
Move?
A card that exists to move things.
Sounds like a convenient card.
It is totally useless.
It can’t move very far.
It can’t move living things
or large things.
It really just likes pranks.
What a troublesome card.
If you don’t hurry and seal it,
then it will move again for fun.
Then I won’t be able to write
my book report either.
But I wonder where it went.
Ah!
Did you find it?
No, it’s just…
Just?
Just what?
I should have brought my video camera.
There it is.
Just a little bit further.
You can’t chase it with your eyes.
Chase the aura.
Eh?
Read the next place it will appear.
I can’t do that.
Sakura,
aren’t you able to sense
the card’s aura now?
But…
You can do it. Concentrate.
Good luck, Sakura-chan.
OK.
My first date with you…
Wait!
I love you…
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card!
All right, now I can do my homework.
So this was what the fortune was about?
You’ll catch a cold like this.
Do you want to go to my place to change?
Eh?
The chaos has already happened.
You need this book too, right?
I am almost done reading it.
Thank you.
Delicious.
Is it just you and Li-kun living here?
Yes,
his mother has entrusted
Shao Ran-sama to me.
His mother?
His father passed away
while he was young.
The rest of his family is in Hong Kong.
I see.
I finished reading it.
Thank you.
It seems you will be able
to finish your homework.
That T-shirt…
Wei lent it to me.
It is a cute T-shirt.
Did you buy it yourself?
No, that is…
Ni hao!
Shao Ran, I missed you!
Mei-Lin. Hey, Mei-Lin.
Why are you here?
Oh, a guest?
Isn’t this the T-shirt
I gave to Shao Ran?
Why are you wearing it?
This is, umm…
What is the meaning of this?
Why is another girl wearing it?
You’re wrong, this is…
Shao Ran, you’re terrible!
I said listen!
I can’t stand it! Just
when I am gone for a bit.
I wonder who she is.
I don’t know.
Listen to the reason, Mei-Lin!