Tomoyo-chan, is your leg okay?
I just sprained it a little, so…
Doesn’t it hurt?
Well, now,
but the teacher told me
not to enter the Marathon Competition.
That’s too bad.
Yes…
But with this,
I’ll be able to take as much video
footage of Sakura running as I like!
Last lap!
Okay!
[Sakura’s Long Marathon Contest]
Sakura-chan’s really fast, huh?
Tomorrow,
Sakura-chan will win
this year’s Marathon
Competiton too.
That won’t happen.
This year’s Marathon
Competition will be
Shao Lan and my one-two finish.
At school in Hong Kong,
the top two were always
me and Shao Lan.
It seems the first and second will be
from our class this year.
You’re fast, Li-kun!
Shao Lan!
Mei Li.
It looks like we’ll be number one
in the Marathon Competition!
Mei Li-chan, you’re good at marathons,
then?
Who told you I was good at it?
You’re going to be crying and
running way behind me, you know.
Why am I going to cry?
Crying because you’re jealous.
But, Mei Li have you ever
run long distance before?
Just like the previous group,
it’s 5 times around the track.
Make sure to set your
own pace as you run.
Yes!
Then get ready.
Set!
Start!
Fast!
You.
You’re seeing me run
and you’re amazed, aren’t you?
Did it!
Mei Li-chan!
No more…
Feels good!
Here.
Thank you.
Are you okay, Mei Li-chan?
It’s just that I’m not
in the best of health today.
I’ve never lost to anyone
but Shao Lan in a race until now.
Race? But you’ve only run a
100m race until now.
Huh?
Between a 100m
and a marathon,
even the way you run is different.
Why? It’s the same race.
How do you get fast
like Sakura-chan and Yamazaki-kun?
It’s definitely training.
Marathon training is ideal
at high elevations.
High elevations?
You mean like a tall mountain?
A marathon runner
trains on high mountains
like Fuji-san.
The tallest mountains
in the world
were first scaled by
marathon runners in training.
Eh?
There aren’t any tall mountains
like that in Tomoeda-cho.
World-class marathon runners are also
world-class mountain climbers, too.
It begins again.
Yamazaki-kun’s lies.
Is it a lie?
But training is important.
Uh huh! I’ll work on it.
Training, huh?
Gochisousama!
That reminds me, this Friday
is Sakura-san’s Marathon Competiton,
isn’t it?
Yes.
And you won last year, didn’t you?
What’s the start time for your grade?
Right after lunch recess ends.
That so?
Then maybe I’ll go watch, too.
Huh?
That day I only have
class during the morning.
Will Yukito-san come watch, too?
He’s in the same class,
so he doesn’t have class, either.
Where are you running?
Um, first once around the school,
then into Penguin Park,
then outside the park,
around the Sakura tree,
we pass next to the library,
then through the park again,
and back to school.
That’s a lot.
The whole way is 2.5km,
but I like running, so…
In your case, Sakura,
you train everyday, so…
Eh!
Don’t you run as fast as
you can every morning to school?
I slept in too late!
You say.
Yuki was impressed, too.
After all, you catch up to my bike.
Goshisousama.
Where are you going?
Marathon training!
You shouldn’t.
What?
Shao Lan,
don’t you want to win with me?
Mei Li-sama,
it’s better if you don’t exercise
vigorously right after a meal.
Eh!
You’ll get a stomachache.
I’ll be fine, already!
Stupid Shao Lan!
Sneeze!
My tummy hurts.
You’ll get cold.
Breathing method?
Rhythmically, like ‘su-su-ha-ha’.
And then, maybe you should
run more leisurely…
Leisurely?
Leave a little energy for the finish.
When you see the goal,
then use all that saved energy at once.
Thank you, Wei.
I’ll try it.
Give your thanks to Shao Lan-sama.
Shao Lan-sama wanted Mei Li-sama
to learn the methods of
long distance running.
Shao Lan.
I think I’ll be able to do it.
The top fourth grader has come in!
The top runners are
Shao Lan Li and Mei Li-san
of the 2nd group!
Shao Lan.
Mei Li.
Shao Lan-kun and Mei Li-san,
a very friendly one-two finish!
Kinomoto-san.
Today I’m a different me
from the one of last time.
I wonder if you can
keep up with my speed?
That’s some confidence, isn’t it?
I wonder is she has some kind of plan?
Sakura-chan!
Yukito-san!
Good luck!
I’ll cheer really hard for you.
Thank you very much!
Fourth graders…
Please report to the starting line.
Then we’ll be at the turning point.
Do your best!
Okay!
Don’t give up in the middle!
Good luck
Okay?
Yes!
Let’s go.
What’s wrong, Shao Lan?
Don’t run too fast
at the beginning.
Speed up at the turning point.
Okay.
It’s a one-two finish, okay?
Yes.
It’s almost start time.
How does it look from there?
Yes, this is ‘Air Above Tomoeda-cho’.
It’s good weather,
and the temperatures low.
It’s perfect for a marathon!
Then, let’s go!
Get ready!
Set!
The top’s the brat and that wench?
What are you doing Sakura?
Hurry up and drop them!
I’m not tired at all today.
This must be
because of the training.
And…
I’m with Shao Lan.
They’re not here yet?
Should be pretty soon.
This side is perfect!
Air Kero-chan, who’s top right now?
It’s that brat! Then that wench,
and Sakura is third!
Sakura! Go for it!
I can’t see them at all.
Too bad. I’ll wait at the park.
Sakura-chan! Go!
Weren’t they running way fast?
It was quite a fast pace.
She’ll falter at the end…
Go, Naoko-chan!
Well, let’s go after them.
Yes.
Wired?
Don’t you think it’s strange?
Yeah.
What’s wrong?
It’s been a while
since we turned around,
but no one’s going the other way.
Everyone’s so slow!
I don’t think we’ve
that much of a lead, though…
Me and Shao Lan are just too fast.
We have a tag along, too,
but…
They should be here soon.
She better be the top this time!
There they are!
What?
Sakura-chan and them have
already passed me twice.
That means that they have
turned around, then.
Yes, but both times they were
running in the same direction.
What?
Hey, was this road so long?
Mei Li!
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Sakura-chan!
Tomoyo-chan?
Why are you coming
from that direction?
Well, you won’t
be able to run now.
That’s not true!
The teacher’s supposed
to be riding a bicycle behind everyone.
Why don’t you have him
give you a ride?
No! I don’t want that! I’m going to
have my one-two finish with Shao Lan!
Hello!
That’s it.
I’ll wait here with you.
I’m sorry, but the teacher
already went on ahead.
But, the teacher on the bike
is supposed to be behind the last person
going back to school, right?
Yes, but just
a while ago the last person,
Naoko-chan, passed by.
What do you mean?
This is…
This poster, I thought…
I saw you run the same way twice,
Sakura-chan.
Is this a Clow Card?
I can feel it.
I do feel the presence of a Card, but…
Where is it?
It should be real close.
Here.
LOOP?
That’s right, it’s LOOP’s trick.
He connected your route and
made it into a circle, Sakura.
So it is a Card.
But I can’t see anything!
If you don’t figure him out,
LOOP won’t show himself.
Then we won’t be able to find him!
Even if we can’t see him,
there’s a way to find him.
You brought it with you?
Of course.
That’s Shao Lan!
Yokuteiyuchoku.
Shinkenshiho.
Kinmokusuika.
Raihushinchyoku.
Keimakuhiruki.
Denkoutai. Kyukyunoritsuga!
Oh, wow!
Moron! What are you admiring?
But!
Find it! There should be a seam
in the road somewhere!
It you cut that
then LOOP will show up!
Seam?
There has to be an unnatural place!
Even if you say that…
I’ll help you.
It’s there!
Umm…
Why is there a seam here?
Wired!
Found it!
Did you find it?
Yep!
You have to cut it with something.
When LOOP shows up,
you capture him before
he connects the road again!
But even if you say cut…
That’s it!
Key that holds the power of the dark,
show your true form to me!
This, Sakura commands!
RELEASE!
SWORD!
Return to thy true form!
CLOW CARD!
Did you do it?
Shao Lan was faster!
But Shao Lan was
definitely faster!
Sakura-chan and her
friends sure are late…
Maybe they took a wrong street?
No!
Even if you say no,
you still can’t run on that leg!
I’m fine!
I’ll stay with her,
so if you have someone come pick her up…
I’ll wait with you.
No! NO! NO!
Shao Lan and I are going
to do a one-two finish!
Mei Li.
Here.
Shao Lan.
The last fourth grade runner has come in!
Let’s greet them with a warm applause!
Shao Lan.
Thank you.
This time, I got hurt,
but if it’s just based on ability,
I would’ve won, ok?
Eh!
And even the Clow Card,
Shao Lan really captured it.
Next time there’s a race,
We’ll definitely beat you!
Then it’ll be a one-two finish
with me and Shao Lan!
The fight has just begun!
You’re troubled face is wonderful,
too, Sakura-chan!
I WON’T lose!
Eh?