[Sakura, the panda and the cute shop]
Good morning
Thanks
for your trouble
Well shall I get down to it
A new shop is opening
Thank you
You have a lot of cute stuffed animals
Is the store opening today?
Yes I am Maki Matsumoto,
The owner of this store.
Pleased to meet you!
I’m Sakura Kinomoto
Sakura is it?
Stop by on the way home from school.
By then the preparations should be done.
OK!
Umm…
Sakura-chan
A new store is opening did you know?
You mean the Twin Bells right?
Do you want to take a side trip?
You really love stuffed animals right?
Yeah.
I invited Rika-chan and Naoko-chan too
Won’t you come too?
I also promised Tomoyo-chan I would go
Let’s all go together
Yeah
It’s Tomoyo-chan’s voice
Tomoyo-chan is in the chorus club
She is really good at singing
and has won in competitions many times.
What a beautiful voice
Tomoyo-chan is looking for a pouch
I have been having trouble
because I don’t have a pouch the right size
to put camera batteries in.
I wonder if I should look for a notebook
Don’t you get excited in a new store?
Really
It looks like the store isn’t open yet
No it is
But it’s not cleaned up at all
I did it again
Welcome in
Ah you’re the one from this morning
Hello I brought my friends
I’m sorry it’s such a mess
Shall we help
But I couldn’t ask a customer to do that
But we want to see the cute things soon
Right?
Yeah I want to see them
Thank you everybody
I just moved to this town,
so there is nobody that I know.
You saved me.
So go ahead!
Thank you
In this state you can’t tell
what there is at all
Tomorrow I will have it,
so you can take a look around
Come over and see
Yeah, let’s come again tomorrow
It really is a nice shop
Chiharu-chan loves
stuffed animals so it is good
Yeah I’m really happy
Do you like stuffed animals?
Yes I love them
Hey tomorrow
do you want to come to my place.
I got a lot of new ones
How cute
I thought it was a soccer ball
You have a lot of different ones
Yeah
It’s like a safari park.
Yes.
I suppose it does in the living room
there is a bigger one.
I’ll show it to you.
What was that?
I’ll go check
What’s wrong Chiharu-chan?
The stuffed panda doll
It’s gone
A thief?
I wonder if they ran out from here?
Even though we came right after
we heard the sound.
It’s strange
How cool!
Nice shot
Poor Chiharu-chan.
I hope the catch the culprit soon
But they say there wasn’t any evidence
where the thief left the house
Actually I heard something that worried me
Worried you?
When I got home
and mentioned that Chiharu had been
robbed to my mother
A store where
if you shop there chaos ensues?
You don’t mean things
like being robbed and such?
Yes
Is that Maki’s shop?
I don’t know that far.
Kinomoto…
It was just a rumor in the toy business.
Forget I!
Kinomoto
Sakura-chan
Oh, no!
Welcome!
Hello!
What is it?
Maki-san that is Chiharu’s…
It’s happening again
Again?
The the previous town I opened a store,
the same thing happened
countless times
Rumors saying If you shop at that store
you will be robbed began to spread
They never caught the culprit
People suspected that perhaps I was doing it
Maybe I should just give up on this shop
You can’t mean that
It would be a waste,
this is such a nice shop
There was no way I could do it on my own
I was engaged
He was a designer
But he died in an accident
He loved stuffed animals,
So he always said
he wanted to sell animals
he designed himself in his own store
Maki-san
If I quit,
he would be sad, wouldn’t he?
But I can’t take any more
A Clow Card that collects
stuffed animals?
Why would there be such a silly card?
Don’t you think it has nothing to do with this
Check it out, Kero-chan.
You can tell a Clow Card’s
aura can’t you?
Well on a case by case basis.
If it is a card doing it,
I may be able to do something about it
Kero-chan, please!
I guess there is no choice
shall I go with you
Maki-san,
the tea you served early was very delicious
I would very much like to learn how to make it.
Can you teach me how to make it?
Yes sure!
OK, she managed to convince her.
Let’s look for the card Kero-chan.
The roundish panda is suspicious
So we need to find the panda
It was right here earlier today.
Aren’t you a cute one?
What are you doing?
The key is letting water you have boiled
once cool a little bit
I see.
Well I have to get back to the store
Maki-san
Sri Lanka used to be called Seilong,
so the stuff that is picked
there is called Seilong tea
Seilong was the name of a country?
I had no idea
And also milk-tea can have the result
of settling the stomach
If you aren’t quiet she’ll find us
The aura of a Clow Card
Where?
Under here
Got ya
No, it ran away.
Ran away?
Didn’t it just change over to another doll?
Did you know that
video editing
doesn’t mean cutting and splicing the tape.
Just dubbing the scenes you like,
can be editing.
But when you dub the video quality falls
That’s why you use a good camera with
good tape and a good VCR
Sakura-chan, if you don’t hurry up,
I will run out of things to about.
This isn’t it
This isn’t it either
That’s not it either
It’s not one of those either
No it’s not in those either
The picture in digital video
is the best after all
It is convenient that
the video software can dub it cleanly.
But there is the complex issue
of the artistry of it
Oh Yeah now that
I mention it recently camera batteries
have been able to last a long time.
It’s really convenient.
Until just recently,
you had to bring a mountain
of batteries for filming.
They were so heavy
I certainly do feel the aura
I wonder if it isn’t here anymore
That’s it!
That is the Jump card
At that time you take the inside of the lens
Somebody is in the store
Ah Maki-san!
Wait!
Maki-san!
Tomoyo-chan take care of Maki-san
I’m going too
That’s too bad
I won’t be able to video this time
It’s painful.
Jump Where is it?
Above!
It doesn’t hurt at all
It plans on running away
Wait right there!
Key that hides the power of darkness
Show your true form before me.
Under the contract I Sakura command,
Release!
Fly
Over there
Return to your rightful form
Ah hey
Tree luxuriating in green come to my aid.
Help me!
Wood
I caught it
That was horrible
What?
Did you already seal the card?
Tomoyo-chan I am just about to begin…
So I made it in time
What about Maki-san?
She is fine
What is that?
What is going on?
I don’t know
I wonder if it plans on chasing us
Here it comes
Let’s run away separately
Yeah
OK
Here goes
Our step size is too different
Sakura!
Strange?
Alright, seal it while you have the chance
OK!
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card!
Well done Sakura
It couldn’t hold out until the end
This one is aggressive but pretty stupid
Really?
Now is the hard part
Now?
Now we have to return
the stuffed animals to the shop
How cute
As a friend for the panda?
Yes so he doesn’t get lonely
But it is a mysterious panda
I was surprised when it came home
I was so surprised I fainted
Maki-san has cheered up
The store is doing well too
You even learned
how to make the delicious tea
Kero-chan,
you said there were no silly cards
that would collect stuffed animals
Well the Jump itself was
like a stuffed animal
Wasn’t it just looking for friends?
Sakura-chan, are you OK?
I’m sorry
It seems it isn’t just Jump causing trouble
for Maki-san