Tomoyo-chan!
Are you okay?
It’s coming!
This is…!
[Sakura and the Last Clow Card]
This is the card, Earthy.
You guys okay?
Both of you all right?
We’re okay.
Mizuki-sensei!
There’s no damage around
where she’s standing at all.
Why?
Use magic!
But in such a place…
Sakura-chan!
Use the Key!
But Yukito-san!
Use the Sleep card!
Release!
Sleep!
Tsukishiro-san!
How do I stop the earthquake?
You gotta seal Earthy.
I gotta do something!
I decided for myself that
I’d gather all the Clow Cards!
I gotta do something!
I’ll get in the air
and see what I can do.
Li-kun, I’ll leave the others to you.
Gotcha.
Thanks.
Fly!
Here I go.
Be… Be careful.
– Sakura…
– Okay.
Sakura-chan…
She’ll be all right,
Is this all Earthy’s good work?
Sakura…
Of all the scattered Clow Cards,
Earthy is the last one.
So if I get this one,
all the Clow Cards would be captured!
That’s as far as the cards go…
Kero-chan?
At this rate,
the whole town would be ruined!
Is this the disaster
that is caused by the broken seal?
No, the disaster isn’t
something that ordinary.
I told you at the beginning,
it’s not something like
blasting away the earth.
Then, this is…
This is all the good work of Earthy .
What should I do?
First, look for its true form!
That’s the true form of Earthy.
Watery!
It went back to its old form!
Alright!
Thanks.
Kero-chan, you okay?
Earthy can’t be
defeated by attack magic.
I can’t deal with that.
What should I do?
You must think of a way
to seal the last card
by yourself.
Me… by myself…
It’s coming!
Jump!
What can I do to turn
Earthy back to its true form?
As I thought…
There’s no damage around where
Mizuki-sensei is standing after all.
What’s the matter?
The trees don’t fall…
Nothing’s happening
where the trees are…
Could it be…
Sakura!
What are you gonna do?!
I’ll try capture the card!
But if you use the wrong card…
Let me try it!
I decided for myself that
I’d gather all the Clow Cards!
This is the last one!
Sakura… All right, I’ll go with ya!
– Let’s go, Kero-chan!
– Okay!
Tree! Grow dense
and become my aid!
Wood!
Does it work?
No…?
Now!
Return to thy form
which thou should be!
Clow Card!
Earthy … I did it!
What?
Kero-chan?
Wh… Who… are you?
It… It’s me! It’s me!
Kerberos!
Kero-chan?
You mean, this is your true form?
That’s right.
Because you captured
all the Clow Cards.
Thanks, Sakura.
But this doesn’t feel
like Kero-chan at all.
You look pretty cool.
I wasn’t in time.
If the last card
wasn’t Earthy,
I would’ve been able
to regain my shape earlier.
I wasn’t of any help at all…
Don’t say that!
Because you were with me,
I was able to capture Earthy!
Because you’re always nearby,
I was able to turn all
of them back to card form.
Besides,
I was the one who scattered
all the cards at the beginning…
– Sakura…
– Thanks, Kero-chan.
After this, there’s
only one person left…
Yue…
Tomoyo-chan!
Sakura-chan!
Are you okay?
Look! The last card!
All the cards have been captured!
This is wonderful!
– Who is this?
– Not again…
This is very cute!
Why do I have to get changed?
Today is the special day
for the completion
of the gathering of the Clow Cards!
When you do something special,
you must wear something special.
This is a must for filming
on a special day like this!
And so you called the van over?
Of course!
And on the way here,
we stopped by Li-kun’s,
and brought his costume here as well!
There, there, there, there.
This is the special filming of the two
who have all the Clow Cards.
But I’m glad that
all the cards have been gathered.
I guess so. And by the way,
good job.
Thanks!
Sakura-chan’s smile is so wonderful!
But Kerberos doesn’t seem happy at all.
Li-kun, do you know about Yue?
The other guardian of the Clow Cards.
The one who rules the Sun, Kerberos…
the Beast of the Seal,
and the one who rules the Moon, Yue…
the Judge.
They are the ones Clow Reed
created to guard the Clow Cards.
Like what things
does the Judge determine?
I don’t know.
As far as Yue goes,
none of Clow’s existing magic books
has described in detail.
You have the book that
stores the cards, right?
The golden beast on the front cover
is Kerberos.
And the moon
on the back cover is Yue.
There’s no moon
at the back of the book.
Then, like Kerberos,
Yue probably obtained
a physical body too…
Oh right!
Have you written your name
on the card yet?
No, not yet.
Then, right away, please do so!
Sakura. After you write your name,
all the cards are sealed away.
I believe you can accomplish anything.
Kero-chan?
– What’s the matter?
– I’ll write it now.
By the way,
Sakura-chan has some of the cards,
while Li-kun has the rest.
In this case,
who is the real owner
of the Clow Cards?
We’ll know very soon,
when he shows himself.
This is the Last Judgment.
Yukito-san!
Who is it…?
Yue.
Yue?
We would love to
have you be our Mistress.
But Yue will be the Last Judgment.
Good luck to you.
Yue?!
Excuse me… “Yue”…?!
Yue is close to you.
This is… Yue…
Then where is Yukito-san?
Tsukishiro-kun was Yue.
It has been a while, Kerberos.
I was careless.
The guardian of the Clow Card
had gotta be near
the owner of the cards.
You’ve been close
to Sakura for a long time,
being a friend of her brother.
Before you returned
to your original shape,
you hid all the aura of your power.
As Sakura and the brat
gathered the cards one by one,
I regained my magic bit by bit.
I sure sensed the aura of the Moon.
But… This lady has such
strong powers of the Moon with her,
so strong that I was deluded by it.
Even if you haven’t hidden your aura,
I might not even sense it…
Created alongside
by Clow Reed as a pair,
the other guardian of the Clow Cards…
…Yue, which means Moon in Chinese…
You know about him too, don’t you?
I was drawn to him during
the archery competition.
Yes, I know.
Wait a second, I don’t get it at all.
What’s all this?
The same as Kerberos.
Without enough magic,
I cannot regain my original shape.
Then, Tsukishiro-san is…
The false form of the other guardian?
This is the first time
I meet you in this shape.
The candidate chosen
by Kerberos the Appointer,
as Mistress of the Clow Cards.
Yukito-san…
But there is another who has
also obtained the Clow Cards.
Unable even to gather
all the Clow Cards by one person,
the Last Judgment is meaningless.
That’s not true.
I believe Sakura
can accomplish anything.
You are overly optimistic as ever.
You too, bad-tempered as ever.
Then, shall we begin… the Last Judgment.
What’s going on?
All the cards are gathered, right?
Doesn’t that stop the disaster
from happening already?
What’s this Last Judgment all about?!
That is…
First…
Li-kun!
Watch out! Li-kun!
I, Yue the Judge,
Shall conduct the Last Judgment.
With all the Clow Cards you have,
defeat me.
Li-kun!
What?! What’s this!
No one can interfere
in the Last Judgment.
No way!
God of Fire, descend!
Did that work?
Things such as that cannot defeat me.
Dammit! Wind…
Useless!
It surprises me that you obtain
Clow Cards with such level of magic.
Time!
Wh… Where?
Time is a card that serves under me.
This is the end.
Li-kun!
Brat!
Li-kun! Li-kun!
All my cards were taken…
Li-kun!
Watch out. He is really powerful.
Next is the proper candidate.
Sakura-chan!
It’s the same… Same as the dream…
Cards created by Clow,
There is one who desires worthy
of becoming your Mistress.
Chosen by Kerberos the Appointer,
A girl named Sakura.
To find if this girl truly qualifies
to become our Mistress,
I, Yue the Judge,
shall conduct the Last Judgment.
The Last Judgment…?