I found it first!
No, I found it first, brat!
Sakura, it’s coming your way!
Hold it right there!
Return to thy true form…
…Clow Ca…
Sakura, seal it!
Hurry, before
it has a chance to run away!
Eh?
While we’ve got a hold of it, hurry!
Return to thy true form… Clow Card!
You OK?
Oh, man.
What the heck?
Hey, calm down.
What happened? Don’t tell me that…
Kero, that speaking style…
Sakura, listen carefully.
And Li-kun has an Osaka accent…
Don’t be too surprised. I’m Cerberus.
W… what’re you saying?
Li-kun, don’t kid around…
It’s not a joke.
I’m Li Shao Lan.
Eh!
[Sakura and Kero and Shao Lan and…]
“Sa-ku-ra.”
Alright, Kero, Let’s go home.
I’m not him!
So he’s Kero and you’re Li?
That’s right.
What did this Card do?
What could happen to you two?
What do you mean?
Ah, this time that ain’t gonna happen.
Eh?
It’s just a switching of body and soul.
So, it’s not like someone got angry
and used this on you?
Not this time?
Nope.
So how did this Card do it?
Clow Reed, the guy who made the Cards,
did a lot of things.
Pretty careless, aren’t you?
What did you say?
You might be okay…
…but what about me
in this stuffed animal’s body?
Who’s a stuffed animal?
I’m stuck in this lame body,
that sucks.
What?
What’s so funny?
Sorry!
But still, nothing happened to me.
Why was it just you two?
We were holding onto that card together.
That’s when Change’s
power started working.
You didn’t know it was going to happen?
I’m the Beast of the Seal, right?
Of course I knew.
Then, how…?
I just forgot.
What?
Life is full of challenges!
Don’t mess around! You have to
figure out a way to change us back!
Don’t worry!
Just be patient until tomorrow.
Really?
After one day,
Change’s magic power will return.
Then Sakura can use the Change card.
However,
me and the brat
will have to do something then.
Do something…?
But still, can you do it?
I’ll do it. Tell me!
Tell me, Kero!
Tomorrow evening, you and me…
Yeah?
…tightly and in unison…
…hug each other.
Is that all?!
That’s not all!
Can you do that, brat?
Don’t look, I also feel nasty
‘Cause if you don’t…
…we’ll be stuck
like this for life.
No choice, then.
Anyway, we know how to switch you back…
But what do we do now?
About what?
You’ll be like this
until tomorrow evening, right?
Who is it?
Shao Lan, welcome home.
Yes.
What’s wrong?
You’re acting kind of shy.
Why don’t you come in?
I was waiting for you!
Come here, come here!
Will he give it away?
If you’re worried,
why don’t you tell Mei Lin the truth?
If she knew,
she’d never let me hear the end of it.
Then it can’t be helped.
It’ll stay like
this until tomorrow evening.
But still…
It’ll be okay.
If you stay patient…
Will he be able to remain patient?
Probably…
I’m making leftovers,
so why don’t you make soup?
Soup?
Wei is out today,
so we have to make it on our own.
“We?”
Well, I have to go buy some stuff,
so you get started, okay?
Hey! What the heck is going on?
A man’s gotta do what a man’s gotta do…
That’s dangerous, Li.
You never said anything
about leaving this room.
But if you leave this room
Someone will see you.
I can’t do it! I need some air.
You’ll catch a cold.
Li!
I’m home.
B… Brother…
Sakura, good afternoon.
Did you drop your stuffed animal?
Yukito!
It’s okay, it doesn’t look damaged.
Here.
Thank you very much.
Dad’ll be late today.
The three of us will eat together.
Really?
Have you prepared the food?
I forgot! I’ll do it now!
Sakura.
That stuffed animal’s face
is kind of red, isn’t it?
Maybe something got stuck on it!
I’ll take it back to my room!
Man, that hurt.
Sorry about that.
Well, gotta hurry up and cook.
Remember, Li?
You mustn’t leave this room.
Oh, Sakura.
Let me help with something.
No, you just sit right there.
That’s all right.
Why don’t I bring this to you?
Looks good! Well, let’s eat!
What’s up?
Something wrong?
N… nothing at all!
Of course not!
It’s soup made by you, after all!
I think so, I am confident in that.
You know, Shao Lan,
you sound kinda weird today.
Eh?
It isn’t like your usual…
I’ve been hanging around
Cerberus all evening.
He uses that Osaka dialect,
so it must’ve rubbed off.
Yeah, that must be it.
Cerberus, you mean that stuffed animal?
No!
I mean, that really
cool Beast of the Seal.
Shao Lan, you always
call it “that stuffed animal.”
Well, he has his good points, too.
This is terrible!
Oh, this is good, tasty…
…while drinking it…
I’ll get some tea.
Thanks. I’ll have half a cup,
and Touya, too.
I see.
Hey, over here. Over here!
Geeze.
Yes?
What’s wrong?
Oh, I thought I heard
something from the window.
Someone… hel…
Go away!
Isn’t that a cat?
Li…
Thanks. That was delicious, Sakura.
Really?
Ouch…
You awake?
That’s Kero’s bed.
It’s kinda small, but is it okay?
There’s nothing I can do.
What’ll you do tomorrow?
About what?
About school.
You wait here, and then…
I’m going, too.
I’m worried about what that guy will do.
I’m worried about you.
I’ll stay still. I promise.
Really?
I made it.
There’s no reason for you to be barely
getting to school on time all the time.
You’d better stay quiet.
I know.
Kinomoto, don’t be late.
Class is about to start.
Good morning!
That’s a pretty big bag.
This is… for gym.
What’s your bag for?
This? I just received a present.
Eh?
Today’s her birthday,
so I guess that happens…
Hey, instead of talking like this,
we should go to class.
Right.
You alright?
I’ll stay still. That’s my promise.
OK!
It’d be nice if
he would just stay quiet, too.
Good morning!
That kind of move?
I didn’t know.
Li, you know a lot about games.
That move was the
Cerberus Super-Special Attack.
So how do you use
that to defeat the enemy?
You hit the B button in rhythm and…
Truly terrible…
Yes.
Shao Lan,
since when did you
have time for games?
Oh, here and there.
Kero, you’re standing out too much!
Yeah, well,
they started talking about games, and…
How uncool.
Yeah, brat, I should just act dumb
if I want to be like you.
What was that?!
If you yell, someone will find us!
What is there to find?
Tomoyo!
Isn’t Li acting
a little strange today?
Actually…
Don’t say it!
Oh, Kero’s here too?
Um, you see, this is…
We’ve been discussing Card matters,
right?
Yes, yes!
Li’s use of language…
sounds like Kero.
That’s not right, Tomoyo.
It’s… you see… Right, Li?
I… I’m not nearly as cool as
that Cerberus is.
Here, pose please!
I thought so!
It’s no laughing matter!
That’s right!
I’m sorry. It’s just so unusual
to see Li look so relaxed
and Kero look so serious.
Weird, isn’t it?
I won’t get mad if
it’s just laughing.
We’ve got to hang in
there until this evening.
How nice, this friendly feeling.
Kind of like a wonderful
family get-together.
Anyway, I’m sorry about before.
I’ll keep quiet until this evening,
so you don’t stand out too much.
Got it.
Now that Tomoyo knows,
that’s more than enough.
I’ll take that!
It’s worse…
Sakura!
Sorry about that!
That moron!
Is there someone in here?
The homeroom teacher
should have confiscated this.
Oh, sir. Could you help me take some
of these things to the gym?
Man, that was some kind
of throw you made there.
Ok!
We have passed today safely.
What were you thinking,
doing that during P.E.?
Li is keeping quiet, so you should keep
your promise too, right?
Shao Lan!
Shao Lan,
you’re kinda weird today.
W… what?
Are you keeping something from me?
That’s just your imagination…
Why’re YOU answering?
Mei Lin. There’s no reason
I’d be keeping anything from you, right?
Really?
Of course!
Are you saying you don’t believe me?
If you say so, Shao Lan…
Where did Kero get that from?
Maybe he saw some weird drama on TV…
Wait for me in the classroom,
I’ll be there shortly.
OK!
Shao Lan…!
Thanks.
Mister Terada, phone call for you.
Oh, thanks.
Gotta get out of here…
All right, see you later.
Damn!
Oh no, this is bad!
What’s wrong?
This…
What’re you doing there, Li?
That’s Shao Lan? In such a body…
Didn’t he say
he was going to keep it quiet?
Li? Are you awake?
Sakura, maybe somewhere
a little more private…
Li, Li!
He’s not answering.
Maybe something happened.
The Change Card shouldn’t
have that kind of power.
Shao Lan!
Answer me, Shao Lan…
I won’t be able to go back like this.
Hey, brat! Snap out of it!
That’s not Li.
Eh?
Li doesn’t have a tag.
He’s not in the classroom either.
Where have I seen that bag…?
Oh yeah, Mister Terada
had that this morning…
Are you looking for something?
Miss Mizuki!
Oh, what a cute stuffed animal.
Do you know where Mister Terada went?
I think he went to one of
the shops by the station.
Thank you very much!
If you’ll excuse us… See ya!
Hey!
Good luck!
Hey, you sure
I can’t run on all fours?
You can’t do that!
Oh, I want to fly!
Got it!
Hey, Teacher!
W… what’s going on?
What happened with this?
I returned it at the toy store.
I was just heading home.
Shao Lan, where are you?
Where are you, Shao Lan?!
Not on the shelf? Maybe out front.
Sakura!
Get me outta here!
All right, now it’s my turn!
If it’s a game, leave it to me!
Have you ever played the crane game?
I should only need one try.
Right, just like that!
You found it, huh?
Oh,
that’s it. You’ve got the hang of it.
Too bad. You need to try again.
Try again?!
Looks like it…
I won’t be defeated! I’m burning up!
Man, would you treat
my body a little better?
It’s your fault that you suck!
You moron, it’s this clumsy body’s fault!
What was that?
Want to get it on right now?
Calm down, both of you!
Li, if you don’t do it,
you can’t go back.
Take these bodies and
exchange the souls within!
Change!
Good morning.
Mornin’. Yesterday was some kinda
ordeal for us, wasn’t it?
You… That speaking style…
Sakura is here.
This time, we got switched…
Eh?
Li, aren’t you Mei Lin?
No!
It’s not a dream!
Shao Lan, if you don’t hurry,
you’ll be late for school.
I am leaving then
It’s really the real Shao Lan, right?
Ah.
Yes.
Obviously Shao Lan is
the best Shao Lan there is!
Hey, let go!
But…!
Let’s go to school!
Hey, wait a minute, Shao Lan!