I am currently known as Eriol.
But I used to be called… Clow Reed.
Clow is dead!
Yue and I saw it!
But he is Clow.
Suppi?? You too!?
It’s easily proven right?
Akizuki-san… why?
O Key that contains the power
of darkness…
reveal thy true form to me.
By our contract, I,
Eriol, command you.
Release!
Return to your original forms…
Spinel Sun, Ruby Moon.
[Sakura and the Return of Clow Reed]
It’s the same as what I saw in my dream.
And that staff…
it looks like Clow-san’s.
Yeah… Clow made that staff.
Then… is Hiragizawa really
Clow Reed reborn?
If what you say is really true, why have
you been causing Sakura so much troubles?
You will understand soon,
Kerberos.
Clow…
Shall we begin?
The Sun and Moon are disappearing!
Tomoyo-chan!
This power is Clow!
What’s wrong?!
Clow…
Shao Lan-kun!
What have you done?
This town has been covered in darkness.
Everyone has fallen asleep.
What?
Why have you done such a thing?
I had intended for you to
fall asleep as well.
You’ve become quite strong.
Unless this darkness is ended by dawn,
everyone will stay asleep.
For how long?
Forever.
And how am I to wake them?
You must defeat my darkness
with your magic.
What!?
No way…
You’re wasting time on questions,
Sakura-san.
But
I can’t use my magic against you!
Then you will lose.
You may play for a while.
No you don’t!
Well done…
however…
Kero-chan!
Damn it…
Our master is quite powerful, isn’t he?
Yue-san… brother!
What’s wrong with him?
He’s asleep.
Him too?
Because he gave all his magic to me.
Clow.
This is the second time we’ve met.
The first time, I returned to Yukito’s
form against my will.
You caused that.
It was not yet time for us to meet then.
Why did you send us to a new master,
when you would be reborn?
Now that Yue’s here,
I shall have to make my entrance.
Yue-san!
You took all Touya-kun’s magic power, eh?
Your master must be weak.
It’s not her fault!
I was just too careless!
This time it’s for real.
Prepare yourselves!
Let’s go!
STOP!
Shao Lan-kun, please take care
of Tomoyo-chan and my brother.
Gotcha.
I still don’t understand
why are you doing this?
Both Eriol-kun and Clow-san
have helped me so much.
WHY!?
Before you hear the answer,
you must defeat my magic.
Morning is approaching.
Are you ready, Sakura-san? Or would you
prefer that they never wake up?
NO!
But… but…
It’s coming!
Sakura!
Shield!
Jump!
Sakura!
Hold it right there.
We are your opponents.
God of wind, come forth!
Are you ok?
Trying to cast magic
when you’re already weak?
That won’t work.
Shao Lan-kun!
Damn…
Sakura.
Shao Lan-kun…
If you wish to save
him and everyone else,
defeat my magic.
O wind, become the
chain that binds.
Windy!
Just like with Yue,
this cannot defeat me.
Fly!
Sakura!
Sakura!!
Damn you!
Out of my way!
Sakura!!
Hmm… it seems they’re
a bit stronger than us.
To protect their mistress.
Cards.
You were worried about me?
Thank you.
But what should I do.
There are still eight Clow cards left.
Are you ok, Sakura?
Maybe the card I need is within these…
Please lend me your strength so that
I may defeat Eriol and save everyone.
Card created by Clow,
listen to my words and be reborn.
I, Sakura, command you
She turned them into
Sakura cards all at once?
Her magic has gotten so much stronger.
Well done,
but not all the cards have changed.
Light? Dark?
They haven’t changed?
Light and Dark huh?
Why? What’s wrong?
Light and Dark
are the strongest cards.
Sakura’s magic isn’t strong enough
to change them yet.
Darkness is night
when everything sleeps…
and to wake…
you need
Light?
As the card said,
only Light can chase away Darkness.
Light can get rid of this darkness.
Alright! One more time!
O Card created by Clow!
Listen to my words and be reborn!
I, Sakura, Command you.
Light!
Light! Light!
No way!
At this rate…
everyone will fall asleep.
No! I can’t let that happen!
I guess it’s time for us to step forward.
Kero-chan. Yue-san.
Light and Dark are always together.
They should be together
when you change them as well.
But they didn’t
change the first time… or the second.
Light and Dark are the strongest cards.
We may be able to help you.
You two can?
But don’t they only respond to the staff?
Yup.
The staff is the only thing
that can change them.
Then how can you help me?
We can transfer ourselves into the staff.
Once we’ve been absorbed
we can help you change the cards
Will you be okay if you do that?
Can you come back?
They will be able to return
once you defeat this darkness.
And if I can’t change the card?
Like everyone else,
they will sleep in that staff forever.
NO! I won’t let you!
If I can’t do it
I’ll never see either of you again! Nooo…
If we don’t,
nobody will ever wake up.
Is that what you want?
Don’t worry.
You have your own spell.
“It will surely be alright”
Let’s do it!
Alright.
Cards created by Clow,
listen to my words and be reborn.
I, Sakura, command you.
Please… change!
I believe in the cards…
and in myself!
Shao Lan-kun?
I’m a descendant of Clow Reed,
I might be able to help.
But if it doesn’t work you’ll…
If the cards don’t change,
you’ll fall asleep too…
Don’t worry.
I’m sure you can defeat him.
Right!
Let’s go!
Yeah.
It’s alright.
“It will surely be alright!”
Light!
Oh my, it looks
like she’s beaten your magic.
Is this what you wanted Eriol?
Yeah, it’s finally over.
Shao Lan-kun!
You did it.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Kero-chan… Yue-san…
Thank you!
It was nothing.
We’re friends after all.
Tomoyo-chan!
Sakura-chan?
Are you hurt?
No, are you ok?
Yes, but what happened?
Brother!
It’s ok, he’ll wake up soon.
Sakura-san.
It’s over. I won’t harm her.
Over? What is?
They’re all Sakura Cards now.
These are the Sakura cards that
I made with the power of the Stars.
Well, you promised us an explanation.
Why were you bothering Sakura!?!?
The… they’re gone!
Sakura!
Shao Lan-kun!
Are you alright?
Sakura…
What?
I…
I really like you!