This dream.
I’ve had it before.
Who is it?
It’s not me.
Hey, Sakura. What’s wrong?
Hey, Sakura.
Sakura?
Sakura…
I was just worried because
you were having a nightmare.
Sorry, sorry. I just had a strange dream.
A strange dream?
I’ve had it before.
A dream about Tokyo Tower at night.
And then,
a boy wearing Chinese clothing appeared.
Chinese clothing?
Big brother.
Weren’t you having a nightmare?
I thought I heard
Your voice.
Brother…
It’s nothing,
I just had a strange dream.
I see.
It was just the moaning
of a monster after all.
What?!
Geeze.
I’m all stiff.
What is it?
Breakfast is ready, so hurry down.
[Sakura’s strongest rival appeared]
Geeze.
I’m not a monster.
About that dream we were talking about.
You have a fair amount of magical power.
That dream could be…
It could be a premonition dream.
A premonition?
It means you might meet
that boy in the Chinese clothing
in the near future.
Sakura! You’ll be late!
OK!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
See you later.
I’m off!
Ah, there he is! Wait up!
You eat too much for breakfast.
But!
Ah. Yuki!
Good morning.
Did you have a good dream last night?
Dream?
I don’t think it was a very good dream.
I could hear incredible
moaning even in my room.
Just like a monster.
Brother.
Was it a scary dream?
No.
It was more of a strange dream.
There are such things
as premonition dreams.
That is the same as what Kero-chan said.
Actually I also had a premonition today.
I dreamt that I had roasted
fish for breakfast.
And then there really was fish,
so I ended up having seconds
on rice six times.
You seem well today Sakura-chan.
I was with Yukito all the way to school.
That is good.
I also got this.
See you later.
Tsukishiro-san is always
carrying something to eat.
Yeah, it’s because he eats a lot.
Very healthy.
Right!
Good morning.
Good morning, Rika-chan.
Time to begin homeroom.
It seems everybody is here.
Today
I have a transfer student to introduce.
Well, come in.
A transfer student at this time is rare.
Sakura-chan, isn’t he looking at you?
This is Shao-Ran Li,
he came from Hong Kong.
Everybody try to be friends with him.
As for a seat, let’s see.
Behind Kinomoto is open.
Your seat is over here.
It’s like…
It’s like his stare is painful.
It is like your spirit jumps.
You just have to talk to somebody about it.
You feel like writing a passage about it.
Why?
This is the first time
I have met this person.
Why? Why?
Why?
I’m exhausted.
Just a moment.
Umm, what is it?
The king of gods commands,
gods appear from all directions.
Gold, wood, water, fire, earth,
thunder, wind, lightning, the new command.
The king of gods commands,
gods appear from all directions.
Gold, wood, water, fire, earth, thunder,
wind, lightning, the new command.
Soft thunder, spinning lightning.
Obey the command!
It’s right.
So you have a Clow Card after all.
Why?
This compass
was made to search out Clow Cards.
Hand them over.
Hand over what?
The Clow Cards.
No!
I promised Kero-chan.
I said I would gather all the cards.
Kero-chan?
You mean Cerberus,
the beast of the seal?
You know him?
If Cerberus is around
why would he have such a child
hold the cards?
Kero-chan doesn’t have
enough magic power now
and can’t get big.
That’s why…
Cerberus’ symbol is the sun.
Combining fire and earth.
Don’t you have either card?
No.
How long have you been searching?
Since April of this year.
You’ve been searching two months
and you haven’t gotten them yet?
That’s true but…
Why do you know about the Clow Cards?
It has nothing to do with you.
I’ll find the rest. Give them to me!
No!
I can’t.
I got these with Kero-chan.
I see, in that pocket?
Sakura-chan?
Sakura-chan!
Hand them over.
No.
Stop that!
What are you doing to my sister?
Big brother?
Are you OK? Sakura-chan.
It’s nothing. More importantly,
my brother…
I haven’t seen that stance before.
Is it a Chinese style?
Hey! They had some.
They had some meat buns.
Here.
Yuki?
They still had some at the stand.
And pizza buns, curry buns…
Does everybody want one?
I have five of them.
Sure.
Let’s see… One, two, three,
four, five. Perfect.
Here. A meat bun.
Here.
What was that about?
Well, I have to leave here.
See you later.
Until tomorrow.
Huh? Rika-chan’s house isn’t that way is it?
I think she is on her way to buy a present.
It’s a birthday.
Who’s?
The person she likes.
Eh?!
It seems the person Rika-chan
likes is older than her.
You need to try hard too, Sakura-chan.
Did you ask Kero-chan about
the transfer student?
No. I tried calling,
but he didn’t answer.
Kero-chan is good about
getting up on time,
but when he goes to sleep
He won’t be up until it is time.
That’s appropriate for Kero-chan.
Thunder.
I wonder if it is a rainstorm?
Umm…
We can stay out of the rain in here.
It’s not falling.
Kero-chan. Kero-chan!
Stop sleeping and wake up.
Lots of terrible things happened today.
Kero-chan!
Shao-Ran Li?
He is probably a member of the Li clan.
Li clan?
My master Clow Leed.
His father was English
and his mother was Chinese.
That is why in Clow’s magic
there is lots of mixed
western and eastern magic.
The magic you are using now
It is the magical arts made by Clow.
With the ancient magic
if you follow the rules
anybody can do a certain amount.
But there are only
a few magicians in the world
who can make entirely new magic.
Clow really was an incredible person.
Well, he had some problems.
Problems?
Nothing.
The Li clan is
where Clow’s mother came from.
I hear they are famous
in China for their magic.
So that boy is…
A very distant relative of Clow.
I heard a rumor that the
Li clan moved to Hong Kong.
I guess it was true.
So.
So I should have given these cards to him?
That’s not true.
You woke me by opening this book.
I said this when we first met,
but there is a seal on this book,
so you have to have
a good deal of power to open it.
That means you have the right
to use these cards.
Your name is already written on these cards.
You are their owner.
Hello?
Sakura-chan.
Tomoyo-chan.
Sky…
Look at the sky.
Yeah, I can see it Tomoyo-chan.
It is the same as earlier.
Since today has to do with thunder,
I made everything out of rubber
so as not to conduct electricity.
What about this bell?
That is also a material
that won’t conduct.
So why a cat?
That is because it is cute.
This is Thunder.
It seems strong.
Fly.
How brave.
You said the guy we were talking
about earlier had a compass right?
Yeah, it looked like it had all sorts
of characters written on it.
Clow said
that compass was passed down
through his mother’s family.
Alright, that boy might come
looking for Thunder.
You should catch the card before that.
OK, I’ll do my best.
How can I return it to being a card?
First you have to return it to
its original form.
Original form?
Here it comes.
Jump.
But what is Thunder’s original form?
Thunder is really…
Do you not know that either?
Li-kun.
Come thunder and obey the command.
It’s the same as the dream.
It looks scary!
You can capture Thunder
after returning it to beast form.
Don’t you even know that?
I was just about to explain that.
Are you stupid?
Windy can’t counter Thunder.
But there are cards I have caught
by hitting them with Windy.
I have been in Kansai long enough
that I can take being called a moron,
but to be called stupid…
Do you have the Shadow card?
Yeah.
All right.
Magic of impact obey the command.
Now!
Shadow!
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card!
So that is the rod of sealing?
But you really don’t know anything.
Hey! Don’t ask the impossible,
Sakura just started collecting the cards.
Who is this?
It’s Kero-chan.
What?
So this is the beast of the seal, Cerberus?
The golden eyed invincible protective beast?
Is this stuffed animal?
Kero-chan.
Anyways, it is impossible for you
to gather the Clow Cards
with that level of power.
Sakura-chan, are you hurt?
Sakura-chan?