[Sakura’s never ending day]
What we have here is a model
that was made of it.
The real one was made of
valuable things like gold,
silver, and ivory.
At Tomoeda elementary
every term we have a special lesson
where people’s parents
talk about their own jobs.
So, how was such a large pyramid
constructed?
Yes, today is my dad’s turn.
He is a college professor.
This is actually the first time
I have had a class with him.
I always thought archaeology
seemed difficult,
but it seems sorta fun.
In Giza
the biggest of all the pyramids
was said to have taken forty years.
There may be some that took longer than
that to build.
This pyramid is said to have used
2,700,000 stones.
Your father is wonderful.
Which means
he was a king with great power over the people…
Huh? I thought I had ten minutes left.
It would be nice
if class always felt this short.
The chime before lunchtime
never seems to come
and the one to end breaks always comes
right away.
Is it true that there is a curse of the pharaohs?
That’s a difficult question.
They say many people who
have disturbed the graves of kings
have been cursed.
But then pyramids were not always graves.
Eh?
There was one king in Egypt
who was said to have made
at least five pyramids.
Five?
Strange isn’t it,
to have five graves?
But then there are many pyramids
with people in them.
What were they made for?
You seem to like this sort of subject.
Yes.
If you are interested come over
to our house sometime.
I have even more interesting examples.
May I?
Of course.
Kinomoto’s dad really is great.
Kinomoto? Kinomoto?
Didn’t you notice by the name?
He is Sakura-chan’s dad.
What is that for?
I wonder if today’s talk was
a little difficult?
No, it was really interesting
and easy to understand.
That’s good.
What do you want to eat today?
Wasn’t it my brother’s turn to cook?
Touya says he has a test tomorrow.
So I’m doing it for him.
I see, well then…
Break is over already?
Breaks always seem to go by quickly.
Well, hurry up.
Yeah.
What is Sakura doing out at this hour?
This is the time when good kids
should be in bed.
All right!
Good luck on your test.
Umm, please take this.
What is it?
Sakura-chan.
A meat bun.
Ah dinner? Thank you.
Yuki, you’re hungry right?
Thank you, Sakura-chan.
It’s late, so go to sleep.
Good night.
All I said was meat bun.
Hurry and go to sleep,
I am turning out the light.
Well then,
good night.
Good night.
Tomorrow is the last part,
it was a long journey.
But Yukito-san is next door.
I feel all excited.
Kero-chan,
you started that game today didn’t you?
I actually planned on finishing
it in one day.
Your eyes will go bad.
Why is it ringing this late at night?
Where’s that bell?
Isn’t that the clock tower
at Sakura’s school?
You can really hear it.
Would it usually go off at this hour?
I’m sure that bell shouldn’t ring
after five in the evening.
Aren’t you mad?
But, that clock has never broke before.
I’ll be late!
You weren’t able to sleep well since then, huh?
Time to finish
my long journey.
I’m going.
Be sure to study well. Well then.
The data is gone!
How do you think you will do?
It’s hard to do this high pitched part.
I’m sure you’ll do fine.
I wonder.
Of course.
I haven’t practiced enough.
Relax.
Yeah.
Let’s see… Next is Kinomoto-san.
Yes!
Sakura-chan.
It’s the next phrase.
Over here!
I made a weird sound.
The rest was very well done.
It’s because you told me to relax.
But your performance was wonderful.
I didn’t think it was the same song.
I should have practiced more.
Huh?
Li-kun is practicing
even though the test is over.
Perhaps it’s because
he didn’t do well on today’s test?
But, it’s dangerous
to do that while walking.
I wonder if Li-kun moved
from Hong Kong on his own.
Now that you mention it,
I have never heard him talk of his family.
Look out!
Splendid!
Amazing!
Li-kun, that was an amazing shot.
Cheers to both your tests being over.
Cheers!
Delicious!
It’s because you tried hard.
Hey, did your test go well?
So-so.
I can’t stand it. I messed up one note.
Are you sure it wasn’t just one note, right?
No!
It’s not embarrassing to make a mistake.
But, even though the test is over,
practice the parts you couldn’t do well.
Yeah.
I did it!
Today I will be sure to save it right.
Save. Save.
I did it!
Kero-chan did you hear that?
Wasn’t your recorder test over?
Yeah, but my dad told me
to practice the parts I couldn’t do well today.
That’s your father,
he says good things.
I’ll practice at school tomorrow too.
All right, tomorrow for sure
I will clear the last stage.
This can’t be!
I am sure I saved it yesterday.
You saw me right?
Really?
Let’s see, today is… I’ll be late!
I have to do it all again.
I’m going.
Why? Why? Why?
Let’s do our best
on the recorder test today.
How do you think you will do?
I practiced yesterday so…
Just what I would expect,
then you will be fine?
It’s the same as yesterday.
We had a recorder test yesterday, right?
I had a toast with my brother
and Dad at home
after finishing the test.
Sakura-chan are you getting nervous?
That’s not it.
Let’s see, next is Kinomoto-san.
Yes!
Sakura-chan.
That’s Sakura,
she always does well at the key time.
Is it a familiar feeling?
You go to a place for the first time,
but you get the feeling it isn’t the first.
Or when you talk to somebody
you feel you had the same
conversation before.
But my memory is very clear.
That kid over there…
It is the same after all.
Which means?
It’s the same as yesterday,
after this Li-kun is going to
kick in a soccer ball that flies at him.
Oh, he really did come.
Huh? He isn’t practicing the recorder.
Don’t you think it is strange?
We had a recorder test yesterday too right?
It seems like it is just you and me.
The ones who have noticed that
we are repeating the same day as yesterday.
This is the work of a Clow Card.
Didn’t you feel it?
The aura of a Clow Card.
The card is over there.
Look out!
A little bit different from yesterday.
Li-kun that was an amazing shot.
It looks very good on you.
What is this?
I made it in the image of a fairy
that can fly in the night sky freely.
It’s impressive that you know
the location of the Clow Card.
That was…
The camera is ready.
Well then, let’s go.
I feel it,
this is the aura of a Clow Card.
Huh?
What?
I wonder what happened?
It’s the card of time.
Kero-chan, this is…
It’s Time.
Time?
The card of time.
It can freely control the flow of time.
The camera is ready.
People without magic power
can’t tell that time is being controlled.
Time
choses the biggest clock in town
and is playing with it.
So he’ll reverse a day again
like he did today?
He can only use the power to
reverse a day once per day.
And he can only use it at 12:00 midnight.
Twelve o’clock?
What if it hits twelve
and Time reverses the day again, like today?
We have to live through the same day again.
Another recorder test?
My battle will go again? Hurry and seal it!
But what if time is stopped again?
I have to hurry!
What is that?
Oh no! This time he has sped up time
just for the clock tower.
Oh!
I looks very good on you.
You did it on a fairy image right?
That’s right!
I am so happy you understand.
It really is tiring to repeat
the same day three times.
When can I go to the last stage?
Really, I have taken that recorder
test three times now.
Why do we have to go through
the same time again?
Isn’t it better to get out sooner?
But Dad, and my brother
had a toast after finishing the test,
and then reviewing for the test…
What are you doing?
Li-kun, is your face OK?
It hit him right as he turned around.
But the ball did go into the goal.
It was splendid.
Time is unified with the clock tower.
If you break the clock tower
with some attack magic.
It will return to a card won’t it?
You mustn’t do that.
Why?
Everybody in town relies on that clock.
I can’t break it.
Then are you satisfied to leave
the card like this?
Well, I can’t leave it alone…
But we can’t break the clock.
If you won’t break it
then we have to get close
without being noticed.
Oh!
He is in the clock tower.
He can see you easily
if you fly in using magic.
Oh!
No mistake, he is above here.
Return to your rightful…
Did you not make it in time?
Is it no good?
Look out!
Li-kun!
You
Hurry and use the Shield card.
Shield,
protect me from the time’s power.
Shield!
You did it!
All right!
The card’s power can’t pass into Shield.
He’s running.
Come forth impact!
You prepared for it?
Sakura, hurry!
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card!
Why?
The card becomes the property of the one
who returned it to normal.
I sealed it.
The one who sealed Time’s power is him.
It’s hard to accept, but the Time card
belongs to him.
It can’t be.
Good morning.
Now time will flow normally from today on.
That’s right. Although I never noticed.
Sakura-chan, what is the recorder for?
Wasn’t today the recorder test?
That was yesterday.
We have a sketching test
starting from the first hour today.
I forgot what day it was!