This castle was built
about 450 years ago.
The castle is now a museum,
but the grand hall,
the dining room, and the bedroom
were renovated to make them
look the way they were.
That’s so cool!
That’s so nice.
I want to live in a big house like that.
There are a lot of problems living
in a huge house like that.
Why?
Can you imagine how long it will take to
simply vacuum a house like that?
Besides, I’m sure you’ll get so lost.
I won’t get lost!
You’re not a princess to begin with.
You don’t know that!
If I live in a place like that,
I will become like a princess!
You’d be the last person to do that.
How come?!
How do you know something like that?!
In the meantime, a princess doesn’t
act so impolitely, you know?
You’re mean!
Touya. The bathroom is yours.
Okay.
But that must be nice.
[Sakura’s Mini Great Adventure]
Tomorrow’s a holiday. Let’s go somewhere.
Sakura, are you sure it is okay for me
to stop by your house today?
Yeah, no problem. Come!
Then, I will bring a cake with me.
Really? I’m sure Kero will be so happy.
Really?
Because the cakes
you make are really delicious.
Even I always wish I could have more.
I am glad that you like them.
Then, I will come by once I get home.
Okay!
Welcome!
Hello.
Come in. Come in!
Touya and Father
are coming home late today.
Kero, it’s Tomoyo.
Oh! You’re here!
You are very cheerful today, Kero.
He’s been like that
ever since he found out
you’re bringing a cake with you.
What did you bring?
Isn’t that a strawberry cake?
It looks great!
Hurry! Hurry!!
Not yet. You have to wait
until we’re done with what she needs from me.
So, what is it that you want me to do?
I was hoping that I can take your
measurements again for your costumes.
The ones you made me
have always fitted okay.
But you are in a period of growth.
Sakura, could you please
lift up your arms for me?
Oh, okay.
Sakura, you are the cutest girl,
so I must make sure.
Th… Thanks.
As I thought,
you are just too cute!
I’m so embarrassed.
You must not hang your head.
You are the world’s
only Card Captor.
To be able to film you
wearing this costume…
Let’s go!
I would be so touched!
Tomoyo…
All right, just hurry and let me eat!
I thought
I sensed something just now…
I did too.
It’s a Clow Card.
It’s here.
Inside the house.
Yes.
Key which hides
the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura,
command thee under contract.
Release!
Kero, stay with Tomoyo.
Got it.
Please be careful.
It’s from Father’s room.
A Clow Card?
Sakura?
Where… am I?
Huh?
Could I be underneath a chair?
An organ?
Did Father’s room
become this big?
Could this be… the Key?
Then that means…
I’m the one who has become small?!
It was that Clow Card’s fault!
Kero!!
Tomoyo!!
Sakura!
Sakura’s Key?
Really!
Leaving something
this important behind,
where did she go?
Yo… You know, I’m not food.
I was saved.
These are the flowers Father planted.
Thank you so much, flowers.
Thank you so much, Father.
It isn’t the time for this.
Without my wand,
I can’t use magic.
I can’t seal the card either.
What should I do?
Stay away from me!!
Where the heck did Sakura go?
I am worried about her.
But I have a feeling
that she hasn’t left the house.
I’m back.
Hello!
Oh no. It’s the brother.
Please hide!
Oh, oh, oh, okay!
Eh!
Hello. Sorry to bother you.
Hello.
Where’s Sakura?
Sh… She went out to buy something.
What’s she doing
leaving her friend behind.
She told me she would
be back in a short while.
Where the heck did you go,
Sakura?
That was scary.
You’re a Clow Card, aren’t you?
It was you who turned me
this small, wasn’t it?
I was almost eaten by
the cat and the mantis!
That is not funny!
Wait!
What should I do? What should I do?
What should I do?
I’ve got no choice.
Tomoyo, would you like cream and sugar?
I would like just cream please.
Thank you very much.
Not at all.
That’s right. I brought a cake.
It is in Sakura’s room.
I will go get it.
I feel dizzy…
I am fine now.
You deserve an Oscar award.
I was nervous.
Then, I’ll go look for Sakura.
Be careful, and make sure
you do not let them see you.
Okay.
Our bathtub was huge.
All right!
Ow ow ow ow ow…
What’s so funny!
Wait!
Hold on!
Where are you going already?!
Geez…
Where the heck did
Sakura go to buy stuff?
Touya looks like a monster.
That’s right! He looks so much
more like a monster than I do!
Where did the Clow Card go?
Touya’s here, and I can’t get out…
What should I do?
Touya, watch out!!
Just now…
I’m sure I heard Sakura’s voice.
That’s strange.
That’s impossible.
It’s too high for me.
What should I do?
If only Kero is around
at a time like this…
Kero!
That’s the act of Little.
Little? As in small?
Even the wand returned to the key shape.
Little not only made you small,
it weakened your magical power too.
How can I turn back to my original size?
If you bump into Little once again
you should turn back
to your original size.
I see. All right.
I gotta find Little as soon as possible!
But even if I found Little,
I don’t have the Key…
Tomoyo has it.
Tomoyo does?
I hope Sakura is all right…
Don’t!!
Sakura!
Tomoyo, the Key!
Ye… Yes!
Key which hides the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release!
Return to thy form which thou should be!
Clow Card!
I did it! I turn back
to my original size!
Kero! I… I’m so sorry!
Hang in there, Kero! Kero!
Here, please help yourselves.
Let’s eat!
This is good!
Delicious!
I am glad.
Tomoyo, you’re good at cooking.
Thank you very much.
Sakura could never make
anything this delicious.
I can! If I learn how to make it…
It is simple.
Really?
Yes. Let us make one
together next time.
But it’s really delicious.
We have two slices left.
Kero’s share…
Father’s share.
And there’s one more left.
Um… Um… I’m eating it.
On… Only this much?
I’m sorry…
Many things happened…
My cake… That’s right! Little !
Huh? Little ?
Lucky me!
I guess one can use
it like this too…
This castle is built
about 300 years ago.
You couldn’t say it, right?
Really.
What’s wrong, Sakura?
You’ve always like the program
about European castles.
You like big houses, don’t you?
I’ve had enough already.