It’s done!
Whoa… No matter how many times I try.
It always turns into Kero.
I’ll ask Rika
how to do it again later.
Kaho-sensei,
something weird happened
on Tomoeda again.
This time, Li Shao Lan
got controlled by some threads.
But
we don’t know who did it.
Same as last time.
I keep feeling Clow Reed, but
Kero-chan ensures me that
Clow…
has passed away long time ago.
What we could do,
is to develope our ability…
…to deal with sudden incidents.
So, I always carry
the cards around with me, but…
What else would happen?
– What is it?
– Eriol! Ah…
Is something troubling you?
Ah! It is nothing.
Is it OK if I stay with you?
Oh, it’s a letter.
Yeah, to Miss Mizuki Kaho,
who was my Maths teacher.
Is your current teacher Mr Terada?
Yup, Miss Mizuki Kaho
was here for the first semester
and now she’s out of the country.
She was amazing.
I wish I had a chance
to meet Miss Mizuki
Ah!
I’m still in the process of making it…
Is this what you bought the last time you
went into that store with sewing stuff?
Yeah, it is not so easy.
May I see it?
Eh? But, but, it looks weird
and nothing like a bear…
I don’t hate sewing so…
maybe I can help.
Don’t laugh.
I won’t laugh.
It’s something you put
a lot of effort into.
Thanks.
Eriol is really kind.
Over here.
If you make the ears
a little smaller
and move them up a bit,
would that not be better?
Since bears have
relatively small ears.
Is that right?
…then let’s take that out
Shall we try?
Thanks.
And… for the new ear…
[Sakura and the Giant Teddy Bear!]
It’s done!
Wow! It’s a bear!
It actually looks
like a bear!!
It’s all thanks to you.
Right!
I want to return the favour.
What would you like?
Anything is ok?
Yeah!
If it’s something I can do.
Then.
I am envious of the person
who will be receiving
that bear from you.
Eriol.
– Here.
– Thank you.
– Can I open it?
– Yup.
It’s a stuffed bear.
Yeah, and about
the name of the bear…
Ummm… if one give a
teddy bear with their name
on it to someone they like…
Let’s call it Suhama.
I love Suhama.
Suhama
in the old days was really big.
It was about the size
of 20 pieces of dadami.
The bigger the Suhama,
more delicious it was
So in the old days,
the higher class,
people always tried
to build huge barns
to make the largest
Suhama possible.
That’s why,
in the old days,
each town had their own barn,
size of a school.
where they can make the largest Suhama.
Suhama that holds
Japan’s record for being the largest
was made in Kyoto that is about
360 meters in length…
Don’t you want to like me too?
Hehehe, why are you mad? Hehehe.
Why did I buy this?
That’s no use
in making something like this.
if one give another the bear
with one’s own name on it.
another person
who get the bear
is supposed to like them back.
Why don’t you say
so from the beginning?
Why am I seeing her?
That’s a cute bear.
Ah, I’m about to eat lunch,
do you want to eat lunch with me?
Can you take this?
I don’t know why, but
I’ve been really hungry lately.
Don’t be shy and eat it…
Y… Yes…
Would it be OK if
I took a look at that bear?
It’s handmade.
Did you get it from someone?
So then you did it?
Wow, it looks great.
Are you planning to give it to someone?
Someone… to give…
Why?
Why can’t I not give it to her?
Ah!! this.
Why do I keep seeing her face?
The only time my face turned red
or my heart is about
to burst was when I met him.
Li.
Li-kun.
She…
Because of her heart is.
It feels
the same as when I met that guy
What is going on?
Yue…
One who bears Clow’s blood.
Reason why you feel
that way when you meet Yukito is
because you can feel
the presence of the moon’s powers.
– Moon’s powers?
– That’s right.
If you carefully look inside,
you’ll find what you really want.
What I truely want…
That is?
You figure out the rest.
When did I get here?
Oh yeah, I came
to return this to you
Since you worked so hard on it,
you should make sure
to give it to that person,
right?
On the hand?
Yeah.
but since Eriol lived
in England before…
I’m thinking maybe it was
just a different kind of greeting,
But, even though he’s
from another country,
Hiragiizawa is a
little different, neh…?
Like what?
Maybe, …mature, or careful?
I sometimes feel
he is like an adult.
Li also
is from a foreign country
They are so differnet.
Then again, Li was a
little weird today.
What was it?
During lunch,
he saw
my face and ran off.
I wonder if something happened…
I’m not sure,
but his face turned all red.
Oh, I see.
That’s because he met you.
Why does he run away
when he sees me?
Because you accept
everything so kindly.
It must be tough
for Li-kun as well.
Oh, by the way,
did you finish the bear?
– Yeah.
– Is it for Tsukishiro-san?
I have a favour to ask…
Haaa… It is embarassing.
You’re exploding with cuteness.
It’s good.
Why am I wearing the clothes
that you gave me,
coming to Yukito’s house?
The moment you are giving your
hand made bear to Tsukishiro-san
This is indeed a special day.
On a special day,
you can’t have yourself not look great.
Tomoyo, is that a new video camera?
Yes, last one broke,
so I got a new one
With this new digitial camera,
I can now record
Sakura’s image even clearer.
Toyomo…
Hurry up!
Now now, give the bear to him.
But I’m not prepared.
Fighting!
Yes?
– It’s me, Sakura.
– Sakura.
I’ll open the door now.
Sakura is too cute.
But wouldn’t
something edible been better?
Good evening.
Good evening. Hhh Ummm… this!
For me?
Can I open it?
Wow, did you make this?
Yes, it’s not the best
job in the world… but…
Thank you.
I’ll cherish it and take good care…
This is the best shot of the week.
I still think something
edible would have been better.
This aura… Clow’s?
Sakura…
Are you both OK?
– I’m OK, but Yue is…
– I’m fine…
Ara… He fell.
They seem to be struggling.
Especially Yue…
Are you really OK, Yue?
Really really ok?
Yeah.
That’s a relief.
Kero, look after
Tomoyo and Yue please.
O Key which hides the forces of stars,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura,
command thee under contract.
Release!
I can surely feel Clow’s aura.
I can’t use the card like this.
O Card created by Clow,
Discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
Jump!
Yukito’s house is getting demolished.
How can I stop this stuffed bear?
It’s moving by magic,
you have to find the source.
That’s it.
Sakura!
You have to find
the source of the bear’s movement!!
What’s the source?
Place where its magic is the strongest.
– It is ear?
– Cut it off!
Sword!
No good.
She can’t make it from there using Jump.
If she doesn’t use Fly…
But if she uses Fly to
fly away then the Sword will…
Right, Fly uses the wand
to grow wings on its end to fly away.
If she uses that,
then she can’t use the Sword.
Watch out!!
Please.
I have to use the Sword,
so help me fly in
the air without using my wand.
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
Fly!
Sakura…
SWORD!
She did it!
Again, it really is Sakura.
The card again changed.
Sakura did a great job
What’s it, Yue?
This…
same picture as when
I use the magic Clow cards.
What’s going on?