Hey, Sakura!
You’re an early riser today, eh?
Because today starts a new semester.
I’ll get to see everyone and…
…I can go to school
with Yukito-san again.
What? Your face is red.
Do ya have a fever?
No. I’m alright!
Thank goodness.
I thought you caught a cold
from falling in the water.
Tomoyo-chan!
I’m okay, but Li-kun’s…
Ni Hao!
SHAO LAN! I missed you so much!
Mei-Lin!
Why’re you here?
But who is that girl?
Who knows?
Sakura-san! Lunch is ready.
Okay!
Well then, I’m off.
Hey! Hey!
Weren’t you going to take this too?
Oh, that’s right!
Thank you, Kero-chan.
My, oh my…
[Sakura and the transfer student
who fight with her]
You’re early.
Ahem!
Is it going to rain today?
What did you say?
Neither of you has club today, right?
Yeah.
I’m early today too,
so I’ll make a feast for dinner, okay?
Feast?
Seems like you’re having fun.
Is… is that so?
It’s because today’s
dinner’s going to be a feast.
There’s that, too.
But… because
I’m with Yukito-san, so…
So there’s a feast at your house
tonight, Sakura-chan?
Yes! Father said it’s because
he’s coming home early today.
Lucky!
Speaking of which,
Sakura, did you see yesterday’s news?
What?
The one about the karate black belt
that was walking the streets at night
and got beaten to a pulp.
I saw that! The story’s that
the opponent was a little girl, right?
I didn’t know.
I thought for sure the suspect was you!
‘Cause you’re a monster, and all…
What did you say?
Morning.
Morning, Tomoyo-chan.
Sakura-chan, did you not catch a cold?
Nope!
Where’s Li-kun?
It seems he hasn’t come yet.
I wonder if he’s alright.
What do you think happened
yesterday, afterwards?
Shao Lan!
Why are there GIRLS here?!
No, this is… umm,
you know…
Shao Lan!
Who do you think that little girl was?
I dunno.
It’s Li-kun.
Li-kun, thank you for this yesterday.
Ok!
You don’t look well,
are you okay?
I’m starting Home Room.
From today on, it’s second semester.
Did you all do your
summer vacation homework?
Yes!
And now with this new semester,
it happens that
a new friend will join us.
Let me introduce you.
That person from yesterday…
Ah, you! I’ll introduce you to everyone,
so come this way.
And I even said, Let’s go together.
SHAO LAN, YOU MEANIE!
This is our transfer student
from Hong Kong, Mei Lin Li.
Li Mei Lin
It seems that she’s
Shao Lan-kun’s cousin.
Oh! She’s his cousin!
Right, Li-kun?
Shao Lan is my fiance, you know!
Don’t lay a hand on him!
Fiance?
Erm, no…
It’s true!
Eh?
I was so surprised.
After all it’s
“I’m his fiance! Don’t lay a hand
on him” all of a sudden.
But it seemed like Li-kun was
sorta depressed, though…
That’s true.
Yamazaki-kun!
That sure looks good.
Is it lunchtime for you too,
Yamazaki-kun?
Yeah. I thought I’d eat
in the cafeteria with Li-kun.
Shao Lan!
I made lunch!
Well, now! Let’s eat it together.
A moment, Mei Lin.
What? What is it?
Mei Lin!
What?
This is school, you know!
That’s why I put it in a lunch box.
If it was home, then I’d
pile it on a plate, right?
It’s not that…
Oh, you still don’t like
konyaku, Shao Lan?
It’s all right, there’s none in here.
It’s not that…
Don’t worry!
I was sure to make your
favorite shrimp shumai, Shao Lan.
You know!
Here.
Aren’t I good at cooking?
Yeah… well, sorta.
That’s not it!
Why in the world did
you come to Japan, Mei Lin?
Because you just won’t come home
no matter how long I wait, Shao Lan.
Because when I capture
all the Clow Cards…
Isn’t there some other
kid who captured them?
Just like it said in that fortune
telling you did in Hong Kong.
I explained it to you yesterday,
didn’t I?
It’s that kid, isn’t it?
What’s happened?
I just got this chill…
And so that’s the case.
To capture them all,
it’ll take some time.
Mei Lin, you should hurry up,
go back to Hong Kong.
Okay! I’ll help you Shao Lan,
so you won’t lose to that kid!
Leave it to me!
If we put our strengths together,
we’re invincible!
Totally invincible!
It looks like they’re
having fun over there.
Tha… that’s true.
Okay! Now gather ‘round!
Yes!
Today, it’s mat exercises.
We’ll do cartwheel practice.
Oh! Don’t!
Sakura-chan, for you something
like a cartwheel is easy, isn’t it?
Next.
Yes.
Yes!
Amazing!
She’s so good!
Eh!
Next, Kinomoto!
It’s your turn now, Sakura-chan.
Yes!
Just as expected of Sakura-chan!
Both Kinomoto and Mei Lin are amazing!
Okay, let’s have you do some
free style exercises.
You both don’t have to
overreach yourselves,
so do whatever mat exercises
you can do, okay?
Yes!
Amazing, huh?
Yeah, kinda.
Why?!
That was scary.
That brat’s fiance, eh?
And it’s not just during P.E.
All day long, I was being watched.
Like she was glaring at me.
Are you sure you didn’t do
something weird to that kid, Sakura?
Nope.
It’s done!
Okay!
Today’s supposed to be a feast!
I’ll bring you some later,
so wait okay, Kero-chan?
Din-ner… Din-ner… Fun din-ner!
I wonder what today’s main dish is?
It’s supposed to be steak.
Yukito-san! Why?
I heard that he was alone tonight,
so I invited him.
Itadakimasu!
Delicious!
Sakura-chan, your face is red.
Do you have a fever or something?
I’m okay!
It it’s for dinner’s sake,
even a 40 degree Celsius won’t bug her.
Huh!
Is this the incident you were talking about
this morning, Brother?
Nope, they say it happened again.
They had it on the news,
earlier, too.
At Tomoeda-cho
Park another incident
involving a black belt
in martial arts…
At the park?
Could you let me see?
They wrote it was a person
of Judo level 3rd dan, huh?
Was the suspect a girl again?
But why are people
doing Karate and
Judo being targeted?
It seems that no money had been taken.
According to the victim’s story,
it sounds like
they are testing their skills.
Touya-san, you’re a Karate student too,
so please be careful.
It won’t be a challenge since
I’m just without a belt level.
I’m an unworthy opponent, right?
Strange.
The girl is reported to be
in strange attire.
Strange attire?
Uh huh.
A girl in strange attire?
It always turns out this way, huh?
What? What?
And such a depressed face!
Heya! Let’s scoot and get that Card!
Kero-chan is so pumped up,
isn’t he?
It seems today’s dinner and
dessert were really good then…
That makes sense.
It is the presence of a Clow Card.
Yes, I feel it too.
Then the girl who
assaults martial artists,
wearing strange attire is…
…a Clow Card.
Mei Lin-chan!
The one they call the brat’s fiance?
You guys have come to look
for the Card too, then?
Then, you too…?
I’m going to capture it
and give it to Shao Lan.
The Card is Shao Lan’s!
What?
I won’t let you have your way!
Sakura is the ONLY Card Captor
I’ve approved!
What is this?
Your fairy godmother?
Let go!
Kero-chan is the guardian
beast of the Clow Cards!
This thing that looks like
a bath sponge is…?
Just let me see you say that
one more time, little wench!
Well, even if the guardian
beast is with you.
Shao Lan has me, so…
Shao Lan wins.
Eh?
That’s probably the girl
in strange attire
that they were talking
about in the news.
Oh, I don’t think she’s
so strange, though…
Sakura! That’s the FIGHT Card!
Eh?
What’s with it?
FIGHT is a martial arts
specialty Card.
So, it has an instinct
to challenge strong opponents.
I can’t do any martial arts!
What does that mean?
FIGHT is challenging the little wench.
Well, come get me!
Amazing!
You can’t even do
something this basic
and you’re trying to capture Clow Cards?
Shao Lan is going to capture
the Cards, after all.
You haven’t had enough yet?
Watch out!
Shao Lan!
I told you not to come!
B… but…
Are you alright? Mei Lin-chan.
It’s only that my foot
slipped a little.
Oh, so you aren’t working with the brat.
What do you mean by brat?!
Brat and Little Wench are good enough.
What did you say?!
You had Wei use it, didn’t you?
Really! And I TOLD him not to tell!
Wei told me because
he was worried about you, Mei Lin!
What do you mean?
It seems this little wench
can’t figure out the
location of the Cards by herself.
Well, it seems that she doesn’t
have any magic whatsoever, y’know.
Is that true?
That’s a real oddity in the Li Family!
Leave me alone.
‘Cuz it won’t work with me,
so I had Wei help me.
But even Wei couldn’t
figure out the exact location,
and I had a hard
time finding it.
Mei Lin!
Capturing Clow Cards
is not a game!
There’s the possibility of danger,
like earlier.
Earlier, I just let my guard down.
That’s all.
That letting my guard down might
be what costs you your life!
Li-kun is pretty cool, huh?
Compared to me,
he’s still pretty green, though…
Anyway, you go home first,
and with Wei…
Mei Lin!
Shao Lan!
Li-kun!
Shao Lan! Shao Lan!
I’m okay.
Sorry… because of me…
Don’t cry.
How dare you do that to Shao Lan!
Don’t!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Mei Lin-chan’s strong, huh?
But, can she win against
a Card created by Clow?
Mei Lin-chan!
What’ll we do?
At this rate, Mei Lin-chan will…
You have to hurry up
and return it to the Card!
What should I do?
Well, it is FIGHT, so…
The only way is to fight it and win.
Fight?
But I said that I can’t do martial arts.
But even so, there’s no other way
to return FIGHT to the Card
than to fight it and win!
But that’s…
It seems just like the time
with the POWER Card, a while ago…
Mei Lin!
Wait, Li-kun!
Leave it to me!
All power, come to this wand!
POWER!
You wait!
Sakura! Behind you!
Don’t come here!
Now!
To the true form return,
CLOW CARD!
That was wonderful!
It’s because you talked about POWER,
Tomoyo-chan.
Are you okay, Mei Lin?
Shao Lan.
How mortifying. Mortifying! Mortifying!
Mortifying! Mor-ti-fy-ing!!
But Mei Lin-chan, it’s all because the
Card was tired because you fought it…
It seems like you can do
a little something after all…
But! Shao Lan is going to
capture the Clow Cards!
It seems that this relationship
is getting a little complicated.
This is another one of those
crosses that a Card Captor must bear.
Is that so?
Oh… probably.