“Hey, hey.”
This fish over here is cute.
Sakura-chan looks like she is having fun.
Yes she does.
Sakura-chan loves athletic meets
and field trips.
I’m Sakura Kinomoto.
A fourth grader at Tomoeda Elementary.
Today is a field trip day.
We’re going to various places in groups.
Our group is at the aquarium.
I love the aquarium.
The penguin show is about to start.
OK.
“Sakura-chan, let’s go.”
Let’s hurry everybody.
She’s fast.
“Penguins, penguins, penguins.”
Sakura-chan really does seem to be
enjoying herself.
[Sakura’s first date]
That’s amazing.
How cool.
I want to swim with the penguins too.
Sakura is good at swimming right?
Here.
How cute.
My leg.
No! Penguin-san!
Penguin-san! Penguin-san! Penguin-san!
Sakura-chan.
We have to save the penguin.
Penguin-san! Penguin-san! Penguin-san!
What’s going on?
A penguin is drowning in the water.
But I can’t save it.
That guy…
Brother?
Sakura-chan, You drowned?
That’s not it Kero-chan
You weren’t listening.
Oh, sorry.
I was able to come out of your room
for the first time
In a while with everybody gone
So I just can’t calm down.
I see, so that’s what happened?
I guess there is no way you would drown.
Your athletic ability is
the only good thing you have.
What do you mean by only?
I won’t give you any hot cakes.
Ah, Sakura-sama.
But it being a penguin that drowned
Makes it even stranger.
The adults were saying that
It might because
the drain in the pool was open.
But that doesn’t quite seem right.
Here.
It was that kind of accident.
It was more…
more like something was doing it.
Like when you saw the Clow Card?
I’m home.
Oh, no!
Kero-chan, room. Go to my room.
Hide.
Come home.
Yeah.
Hey big brother,
you were at the aquarium today right?
It’s written right here.
Hey
Why were you at the penguin show?
What kind of part-time job?
Feeding the penguins.
Eh? How cool.
Not cool.
Why not?
Just because.
You’re terrible
Eating it without asking.
Those are the hot cakes
I bought with my allowance.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hurry and come in.
Sorry. Sorry.
It took me some time to get my shoes off.
Hello, Sakura-chan.
Yu… Yukito-san.
Hello.
That looks good.
Sakura, you’re a good cook right?
That’s not true.
Yeah. That really isn’t true.
Umm…
Yes?
Would you like
Some hot cakes?
Is it OK?
Didn’t you buy it with your allowance?
It’s fine.
I’ll bring it to my brother’s room later.
Thank you.
I can’t knock.
What should I do?
Thank you, Sakura-chan.
No problem.
What Sakura? You were there?
Umm.
How did you know
I was there when I didn’t knock?
I just got the feeling
You had brought them up.
Aquarium. Water.
Sakura.
Hey Sakura.
What’s going on?
I’m so happy.
Ah, Yukito-san.
Hey!
What are you going to do so spaced out?
What happened to your duty as Card Captor?
Yukito-san is more important than the cards.
Hey, hey.
Don’t you care of the penguin drowns again?
I don’t want that.
The poor things.
I thought I would die.
But this time might be a little bit bad.
If was obviously in the water that
the trainer woman
And the penguin were about the drown.
Yeah.
Did you see
who it was that tried to drown them?
No, not at all.
The water was just swirling around.
That was probably water,
the Watery card.
So that’s it.
So we just need to catch it
and return it to a card.
It won’t be so easy.
You can’t see Watery
when she is in the water.
Even if
you manage to draw her out of the water…
If she splits up all over the place
you can’t finish her off.
Something as shapeless
As water is tough to catch.
Watery is a high level magic
Amongst the Clow Cards.
The four basic elements
“Earth, water, fire, and wind “
Those are very difficult to use.
Above that,
Watery is an attack magic card.
She is very aggressive.
The cards you have are
“Windy, Fly, and Shadow.”
That won’t be able to do it.
Even if
You use another high level magic like Windy
You can’t beat Watery.
Windy is just too kind.
Windy.
Shadow.
And then Fly.
The cards I have are just these three.
How do you catch water?
I have to hurry and catch the Watery card.
You seem down, Sakura-chan.
No, not at all.
Ah?
It seems like the promised great trial for
An ally of justice has come.
It may be the work of a Clow Card after all.
But Kero-chan said it’s impossible now.
Ah…
Tomoyo-chan.
Yes?
Thanks for listening to me.
That smile suits you the best.
Oh yeah, I meant to give this to you.
It’s a new product made by
my mother’s company.
This one is yours.
And here is one for Kero-chan too.
Is it OK to borrow this?
Of course.
My mom asked us to tell her
How useful it is.
Thanks for worrying about me.
Well, until tomorrow.
Yeah, see you later.
But
If I combine all three cards, can’t I…
You can’t. You can’t.
No mater how you use the ones you have,
it would be impossible.
But the Watery card is
in there.
It’s a little frustrating.
I’m sorry…
Are you OK, Sakura-chan?
Yu… Yukito-san.
It’s dangerous to daydream like that.
Yes, I’m sorry.
Thanks for yesterday.
The hot cakes were delicious.
Oh, not at all.
You’re going home late.
Coming back from club?
Ah?
You’re in the cheerleading club, right?
Yes.
I heard from Touya.
He said he was hit by your baton
while you were practicing at home.
Brother…
Why did he tell Yukito-san.
In thanks for the hot cakes
Do you want to go eat something good?
What? Is it OK?
I found a restaurant with some good stuff.
I’ll meet you tomorrow at one o’clock
at the penguin park.
OK!
All right!
Yukito-san.
What, again?
Hello, this is Daidouji.
I can’t come to the phone right now.
Please leave a message at the beep.
Tomoyo-chan, this is Sakura.
Tomorow I have a date with Yukito-san.
We’re meeting at one o’clock.
I’m so happy.
I’ll call you again when you are home.
Could it be that I got the time wrong?
No, you’re fifteen minutes early.
Eh? Then you…
I mustn’t keep you waiting
So I came early.
Huh? This is…
Oh yeah,
you came here not too long ago.
We’re going in here?
Yes.
I see.
It was this aquarium.
This is perfect
I can check
If the Clow Card really is in here.
I will catch Sakura’s first date on video.
Let’s go.
Yes.
What a big fish.
Really.
I wonder if you can eat it.
Wouldn’t it be impossible alone?
I don’t think so.
They seem so natural.
What? Don’t modern kids even hold hands?
Mr. Stuffed Animal.
Kid, if you mess with me, you’ll regret it.
They’ve moved off.
See ya.
This is so cool!
I didn’t get to see this part last time.
Ah, because of the accident
at the penguin show?
So you probably
didn’t know there was a tea room?
While looking at the pretty fish.
Touya.
Brother?
Did you move from your job
with the penguins?
They are taking all the water out of the tank
and changing it.
Then Watery would be…
Good thing you don’t have to work
in the freezer anymore.
The penguin food was kept in the freezer
He said it was really cold.
It’s the same thing.
Now they have me making shaved ice.
The strawberry milk here is really good.
Shaved ice?
Ice?
Well then, we will have two of those.
Sure, sure.
Don’t you want a large serving?
You have large servings?
What? A date along with guardians?
Sakura-chan!
Watery?
Sakura, Yuki!
Sakura-chan.
Are you OK, Sakura?
Tomoyo-chan?
Oh yeah, where is Yukito-san?
Hey, are you all right?
I thought I would die.
Is this after all?
Yeah, the work of a Clow Card.
Watery was in here.
Did you see her?
Now that you mention it,
why are you two here?
Are you OK, Sakura?
Yes.
I guess that ruined our shaved ice.
Not at all.
Shaved ice. Shaved ice…
Ice? Oh yeah.
Yukito-san!
Thank you so much!
Thanks for your trouble.
Ah, thank you.
Is it really OK?
Leave it to me.
In here?
This is where the magic is strongest?
I’m getting off.
Hello, this is Daidouji.
Is it there?
Exactly, one level underground.
All right, well then hide.
Watery!
Come and get me.
Get out of the way, Kero-chan.
Fly.
Windy.
Nice work, Sakura.
If you harden the water, it’s easy to catch.
It’s because I heard from Yukito-san that
The food is kept in a freezer.
Thank you, Tomoyo-chan.
I’m glad I could be of help.
Well, shouldn’t it be about ready?
Return to your rightful form
Clow Card
But that was a good idea.
It was all because of Yukito-san.
Yukito-san.
Oh, my. Sakura has turned to ice now too.
All right. She’s with it now too.
Really show it to them next time Sakura.