Huh? That’s strange… this goes here…
and this here…
Something different…
Ah? Like this?
I get it!
I’ve got you now!
What’s wrong with you!?
I can’t get my head out!
What are those clothes for?
Tomorrow we’re having a bazaar at school.
Our class is running a cafe
to sell tea and candy
So everyone is
making uniforms like this.
Tomoyo-chan
designed that.
Ca…n…dy!?
I’m going too!!
I’ll go to the bazaar
and eat lots of candy!
Hey Kero-chan…
Tomorrow will be so much fun!
[Sakura, Kero and a Candy Encounter]
That’s
your suit for the bazaar isn’t it,
– Eriol?
– Yes.
What? What? What are you talking about?
– Welcome back.
– Welcome home.
I’m home, Eriol.
I’m home, Suppi!
Who are you calling Suppi?
But,
Suppi is so cute!
There’s a bazaar at school tomorrow.
My class will be
providing tea and snacks.
If you wish to come, you may have some
Really??
I’m going for sure!
Suppi, you come too!
– No.
– Eh? Why?
I don’t like sweet things.
Why are you laughing?
You’re the one
who told me to stay away from them.
I didn’t say never,
just don’t eat so much you’d become fat.
– Sorry for making you wait.
– Thank you.
Sakura-chan makes such a cute waitress!
Tomoyo-chan!? Hoe!
By the way,
what did you do with Kero-chan?
He’s hidden
in the woods out back.
Kero-chan.
Will he be alright there?
He just wants to have lots of snacks.
Yummy!
This is so great!
Lots of people have
come to the bazaar this year.
Really.
About bazaars,
the word bazaar
originated with the Nigerians.
At festivals they
used to call Zabaa, zabaa…
and so it was called Bazaa and
Whatever. Take this to table 3 ok?
In those times,
the most famous booths were…
Well done, Chiharu-chan!
Sure.
Well, he’s always the same.
Sorry for making you wait.
Thank you.
You were in charge
of decorating the class,
weren’t you?
Yes!
It looks very nice. Well done.
You two look very handsome.
Thank you very much!
You look very fine as well.
Eh? Um thank you.
What is it?
Nothing!
Two more orders please.
Ok!
Sorry for mak… ah!
– Good afternoon!
– Yukito-san!
Thank you for inviting me.
– You’re welcome!
– So… the food…?
B… Brother!
Well… ready to eat.
Ok!
Looks cute.
The outfit.
Teasing again? It was Sakura I meant.
Yuki, have you forgotten your glasses?
No I haven’t.
I’ll get you some more ok?
What is it?
Nothing, just an odd aura.
It seems that Sakura-san’s
older brother
has noticed me.
I shall have to be careful.
This is good!
Candy! Candy! Ca…n…dy!
Oh no, someone’s coming.
Sweet chocolate
and coo–kies! I must eat them quickly!
Suppi are you sure you don’t want any?
– Quite sure.
– Why?
I’ll eat them all
Do as you wish.
Ok, I’m going then!
Wait there
and we’ll go home together!
Chocolate and sweets…
Are very good to eat.
Don’t you know… it’s so much fun to eat…
something that is sweet!
There’s no one here.
I’ll finally get some peace and quiet.
Ah! That was close!
Time to eat some more!
Kerberos…
Who…?
This isn’t good…
this is not the proper time
for out meeting.
I’ll tell Eriol later.
You…
you…
have a big head.
My head is no bigger than yours!
If I am careless,
he would have figured out.
I can only tolerate!
Wow! A talking toy?
I’m not.
Ah, I didn’t know there
were such strange animals in Japan.
And you speak the human language too!
Huh, wait a minute. Your form.
Those wings. That tail.
That round face!
He figured it out.
A fairy?
No matter it is me, or snoopy,
under the body-borrow circumstances.
I know our magic
is hidden in these forms
and he can’t sense a thing.
But a FAIRY!?
How would you like to be called a fairy?
That must be it.
Wow this is the first time
I’ve met a fairy.
I’m Kerberos,
the magical beast created
by Clow Reed.
But I don’t really look like this.
My real form
is much cooler.
Cool eh?
Even with all his knowledge,
he hasn’t figured it out.
Oh well I might
as well keep the deception up.
So, what’s your name kid?
Spi…
I shouldn’t say my real name.
Su… ppi!
I have no choice.
Su… ppi.
Suppi? That’s a strange name!
Hahahah! SUPPI
How strange! Let’s be friends, ok
You are such a blockhead.
Huh? Something wrong?
No.
Might as well keep him happy.
I’ll tell Eriol about this later
Hey just a minute.
Shall we eat these sweets together?
Have you never had any?
You’ll like ‘em.
Actually I don’t like…
It’s ok, it’s ok.
Wait a sec.
You haven’t eaten it yet?
Come on, there’s plenty more.
Try this and this
and this and this…
This is good, too, and this…
Tasty?
What’s wrong? Do you not feel well?
Wasn’t that good?
Sweet things are so sweet! Hahahah!
More… more… and more…
Are you okay?
I want more!
Hey! What’s wrong Suppi?
I’m so glad you’re here Touya-kun!
Let go.
Don’t want to! Touya-kun!
– Do you want any more?
– Thanks.
– Me too!
– Ok!
I’m so happy!
Spinel?
Want more! More candy!
Thank you very much.
Found some.
Time to eat!
More!
He did this?
Let’s bring out more candy.
Good idea.
It’s gone!
Really? Where could it have gone?
Geez! Where’d he go?
Ah! It was just here! What?
Where’d…?
I just had it…
Why this happen?
Eh, all candies are gone.
Sakura’s going to think I did it!
Want more candy!
Yum! This way… ha!
Found you
Ready to eat!
Suppi!
I finally found you.
Want some?
Ready to ea…
Stop eating already!
Listen to me!
If you keep eating like this,
Sakura will get very mad!
What’ll I do if anyone comes!
Thank you very much for listening.
This is bad.
Hey, Suppi!
Why can’t I eat??
You meanie!!
What was that?
You’re so mean!!!
People are going to notice
if he keeps this up
That’s it
What’s going on…
Trouble!!
It’s bad!
Kero-chan!
I told you not to come in here!
No time for that!
Hurry and use SLEEP!
Make everyone
fall asleep quickly.
Why?
I’ll explain later! Hurry!
Ok.
Oh card Created by Clow.
Hear my words and be reborn.
I, Sakura, command you,
Sleep!
Alright!
Wait! Kero-chan!
Yummy!
Oh dear.
Meanie, go away!
No way!
Stay away!
Will you wait a minute!
What? That was Clow’s aura.
Kero-chan!
It’s no use. He got away.
It was you!
What?
You ate all
the candy at the stalls!
And knocked down a tree!
And the stuff in the staff room!
No! It wasn’t me! It was Suppi!
And Suppi is?
He looks like this…
wings… face…
tail…
This is him. He did it.
This is…
Kero-chan isn’t it?
No! It wasn’t me!
And you promised
to behave yourself!
I’m telling the truth!
When you tell lies, they soon
come back to haunt you!
That’s mean!
Where did you go, Suppi!?
You seem to have eaten a lot of sweets.
I guess you like them
don’t you Spinel
You and Kerberos
are more alike than you’d think