You look really good!
Thank you, Kero-chan
But, Kinomoto-Sakura,
without that kimono you look
completely different.
What do you mean!?
Alright alright, just joking.
Fine,
then I’ll just tell daddy not to buy any
food for you to eat then.
Now that’s too much!
Your kidding right?
I was just saying that you look so cute!
Your dress is really cute too.
You really are a hundred times cute!
So will you forgive me?
Dear and sweet Sakura!
It really looks good?
I’d dare to say…
Yes, nothing is
cuter then you, really!
OK, Kero-chan, it’s just too much.
I’ll bring back some food.
That’s great!
I really want to eat new years cake!
[Sakura and the Mysterious Fortune]
Happy New Years.
What are you looking at?
You are going to say my kimono
isn’t good looking, aren’t you?
No, it looks good.
For a monster…
What did you say?
What? The big new years
monster wants some food?
I’m not a monster!
Happy New Years, Touya-kun.
Happy New Years.
Sakura-san do you like your new clothes?
No problem.
Here, these are new year cards,
they’re for you.
– Thank you!
– No problem.
Will you guys wait for me for a second?
I am going to finish some work.
When I’m done we’ll go
together to the festival.
OK!
I wonder what everybody wrote to me!
Naoko-chans card has a picture.
Rika-chan’s card is very pretty.
This is Yamazaki-kun’s card!
It is said that on this very day,
at China
there was something
called a very big dragon.
There was 1 year and 1 day,
so they waited.
So it’s like that!
(Yamazaki-kun’s card has fake information
on it, so be careful, Chiharu-chan)
Fake? Really…
This is Tomoyo-chan’s card! Tomoyo-chan’s
words are very pretty, just like her.
Oh! This is Shao Lan-kun’s card!
Is it that brat from Hong Kong?
He isn’t a brat!
His name is Li Shao Lan-kun.
I’ll call him brat.
Shao Lan-kun is a very good person.
Before, we had a lot of disagreements.
But now Shao Lan-kun does
a lot of things for me.
So, I don’t like him.
What did you say?
Don’t eat the new year cards,
Monster.
Awww you called me monster again!
Let’s go.
Hurry up, monster.
Sakura-san, this year what new year
resolutions do you have?
Let me see…
I am going to help father
and not be too worried.
I also want to be on time
for school.
Still, still I want to be
better at some things.
And to do better.
How many do you want to have?
Hey, brother, did Yukito-san
really say that he’s going to come?
It’s strange for Tsukishiro-kun
not to keep his promise.
I’m going to go to Yukito’s
house to look.
You two can go home first.
Say hi to Tsukishrio-kun for me.
Yup…
He went late to school, too…
What’s up with Yukito-san?
It’s Tomoyo-chan!
Tomoyo-chan!
Sakura-chan!
Where? Where?
Sakura-chan!!!
Kinomoto-sensei…
Happy New Year,
Tomoyo-chan!
Happy New Year!
First let me get out my camera so I can tape you…
Last time, grandfather told me that
it was really too great
to be able to talk to me.
Me too.
Thank you, Sonomi-kun.
I only bought grandfather
a present for you.
He thanked me already.
It was you who told grandfather
to come and see us.
How do you know?
When we saw each other,
grandfather said it.
I told him not to say anything.
Oh yeah!
I brought my camera.
Lets go and take a picture
of them for New Years.
Sakura-chan, Tomoyo! I’m going to
take a picture, hurry up and come!
OK.
I’m about to take the picture!
OK, say “Cheese”.
I took the picture!
I’m very tired.
I bet the picture will be very pretty.
Because my mother’s camera is very good.
Also because you are very pretty,
I’m sure that it will be very pretty.
It’s already this late?
I have to go to work now.
You still have to go
to work on New Years?
Because today I said
that I would go work
So, you have to come
to our house and play ok?
Yes!
So, I guess I have to leave too.
I need to go home and do
some new year things
I want to help too!
Yesterday you already helped
Touya and me a lot.
You can not help it will be ok.
You go with Tomoyo and play.
Sakura-chan!
Remember to come to our house to play!
Yes!
Let’s go get some fortunes, ok?
Yes.
Excuse me, can we have some fortunes?
OK, hold on.
Eriol-kun!
How come you’re here?
Because the lady that was here is gone.
So I came to help.
Mizuki-sensei went abroad.
Still, I was surprised…
Do you know the shrine keeper?
I am the only one.
Now, were done talking hurry and choose.
Yup, yes.
I got 75.
I got 42.
Please wait a minute.
– I hope I get a good fortune.
– Same here.
Thank you for waiting for so long,
this is Daidouji-san’s.
Thank you very much.
– And this is Sakura-san’s.
– Thank You.
– What’s wrong?
– I got a good fortune!
The words on here are lucky!
That means…
An old day will come
and give me Sakura-chan.
And then I can make her pretty clothes!
What does that mean?
Sakura-chan, what does yours say?
What?
Your fortune
will come in your dreams.
That is a very weird card.
What’s wrong?
This fortune doesn’t have anything
really good on it.
That is the one you chose.
Is it right?
In my dreams?
What is that supposed to mean?
That fortune is
especially for Sakura-san.
We’ll see each other tonight.
Yuki! Are you home?
Yuki!
Yuki! Whets wrong?
Hey! Yuki!
– Yuki!
– Touya.
What’s wrong with you?
I really wanted to sleep.
I’m OK
How come you came to my house?
Your still asking?
Didn’t you say that you wanted to go
to the festival with us?
So we waited for a long time,
and we still didn’t see you.
Sorry.
That’s ok, if we hurry then
we can still catch up with
Sakura and the others.
Hey Yuki!
Sorry, I really want to sleep.
Yuki.
– I wonder who that could be.
– I’ll go see.
Thank you very much.
Yeah.
How come you guys are here?
Happy New Year!
But why did you come here?
We went with our family
to the festival and we were
on the way back home.
But Tomoyo-chan said that
we should come and see you.
So we came here
Oh My, two very cute guests.
Wei-san!
Happy New Year.
Thank you for coming over.
Happy New Year!
Come, Come, hurry and come inside.
I will make some tea.
But it’s not nice to just come in.
What are you talking about?
Right, Shao Lan?
Yup.
Since we were invited
why don’t we just go in for a while?
Right!
– Please come in.
– I’m coming in!
There’s something that
smells really good in there.
Really!
– I…
– Yes?
Thank you.
Yes.
– Thank you very much.
– Don’t mention it.
Cute! This is very well made.
This is really really good!
It really is!
Did Wei-san make these?
No, it was Shao Lan who made them.
You really know how to make these,
Shao Lan-kun!
Sakura…
– What?
– No, nothing!
Before, only family members
could call Shao Lan, Shao Lan.
So it’s like that?
This year let’s continue our friendship,
right, Shao Lan-kun?
Yup…
The food that your dad made
is really good.
This one is very good.
Having a new year is really good.
But if we could of gone with Yukito-san
to the fair then it would be very good.
What’s wrong with Snow Rabbit?
He said that he would come
to the festival with us today.
But, he said that tomorrow
he’s coming to our house!
I think that today he was busy.
Sakura’s power isn’t enough
to keep Yue from staying alive.
So, I could give her some of my power.
If something doesn’t change,
then Snow Rabbit will…
Kero-chan,
Kero-chan!
What’s wrong? So he’s coming tomorrow?
That’s great.
It’s a fortune?
That is very weird.
That’s what I was saying,
but I drew it.
But, isn’t it that place
where that lady used to be?
It could be because of her…
Why don’t you
go to sleep and see?
Yes…
I’m going to turn off the lights ok?
Good night, Sakura.
Good night, Kero-chan
Sakura-san. Sakura-san. Come…
The Clow key?
Come…
O Key which hides
the forces of the stars,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release.
Dream?
This is my very idea. Call it.
Wants me to call it.
O Key which hides the forces of stars,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Dream!
Am I flying?
It’s the moon tower?
What?
The sun, the moon.
They’re both gone!
Who is it?
Who are they?
I want to come here to fight.
I think this won’t be a problem for you.
I know, I’ve seen him before.
You are… You are…
Sakura! Sakura!
Whats wrong with you?
Sakura! Are you ok?
Did you have your dream?
I’m fine,
I just had a strange dream.
Thank you for worrying about me.
If you’re fine then that’s good…
What’s this?
Isn’t that the star staff?
How?
It’s not just that,
look at your left hand!
Clow Card?
No, you put it there yourself.
I think it was when you were sleeping.
Dream?
This is what I used in my dream…
So, dream gave you that dream,
that wasn’t a normal dream.
What did you dream about?
It was about…
I was flying over the city.
I was flying
and I saw a lot of different places.
But, when I got to the moon
tower the sky became dark.
The sun and the moon were covered.
Then it was all dark.
Then on top of the tower
I saw somebody.
Who?
It was too dark,
I couldn’t see their faces.
There was a person with long hair
and wings.
There was also a very huge dog.
That sounds just like me. That’s not all,
was there a Yue shaped person?
Then there was still
a boy with a dark face.
I think I’ve seen him before.
But, I don’t know…
This isn’t a normal dream…
You said you don’t know
who that person is.
But he was probably
a very important person
telling you there is no problem.
Sakura,
in your dream was
there anything very scary?
No.
So it’s like that,
don’t worry!
Because you are the powerful Sakura!
It’ll surely be alright right?
Of course! You still have me!
Do you think that
I will see these people
in my dream again?
At the moon tower…
I think that you might.