It’s hot.
And I can’t turn on the air
conditioning since nobody else is here.
No, that will just make me hotter.
I want to go to the ocean too!
Sakura-chan isn’t home, right?
School camping trip.
I wonder if something
on her desk fell over.
Eh? Yeah!
So Sakura is at the ocean right now?
[Sakura and the scary kimodameshi]
Sakura-chan!
Let’s play beach volleyball.
I’m coming.
Sakura-chan really is a good swimmer.
She was really looking forward
to this school camping trip.
She was saying
The sea, the sea, the sea, the sea!
Sorry to keep you waiting, let’s play.
Sorry.
It’s OK.
You know something
about beach volleyball…
It started a long time ago
On the beaches of Hawaii,
using coconuts.
With coconuts?
And you know, coconuts
are heavy and hard.
Yeah, they are heavy and hard.
I hear that beach volleyball
caused countless injuries.
Eh!
It’s a lie. A lie.
Is it a lie?
Anything Yamazaki says that begins
with “I hear” that is usually a lie.
It seems Li-kun is a good swimmer too.
Really.
He has been swimming
all around for a while.
Eh!
I wonder if he is
doing distance swimming?
You know about distance swimming…
Yeah, yeah…
Gather up!
Long ago in the Edo era
there was a certain samurai…
Yeah, yeah…
Chiharu-chan is used to it.
I hear she has been with
Yamazaki-kun since kindergarten.
They have been together a long time.
It’s wonderful to be together
with someone for a long time.
Yeah it is.
And therefore putting the honor of
their house on the line the two samurai…
Yeah, yeah…
Pull it with a heave-ho.
OK!
I never thought we would
get to pull in a fishing net like this.
Really. Really.
Right, Sakura-chan?
You seem all set.
Yeah.
It’s too bad I couldn’t
bring a video camera.
1, 2, 3.
Heave ho! Heave ho!
Come on, you can do it!
Heave ho!
Try your hardest.
Pull it in evenly.
Heave ho!
All right, just a bit more.
It seems like
we got a big catch.
Sakura-chan, you’re good.
I always do it at home.
Really.
She’s right.
He’s skilled.
Amazing.
You can’t give up Sakura-chan.
I don’t think that is the issue.
Today with fun with
the fishing and cooking.
Yeah.
What are we doing tomorrow?
I think it was kimodameshi.
Oh yeah.
In that cave.
The cave we can see from the beach?
Yes.
Now that you mention the cave…
Do you all know the old story?
Naoko-chan seems really into this one.
Yes.
You know, a long time ago a
group of elementary school kids
the same age as us came here
for a school camp trip.
The first day they swam
in the ocean and fished from the beach,
so it was like a fun school trip.
But…
On the next night they were
going to play kimodameshi.
That’s the same schedule as us.
I heard they did it
in the middle of that cave…
There was a small lake
in the middle of the cave
with a bridge over it…
That bridge ran to a shrine
in the middle of the lake.
For the kimodameshi
the students were to go in pairs
to the shrine and leave a candle.
Eventually one group went in
and no matter how long they waited,
they never came back.
The teachers and
other students got worried,
so the went to look.
In there they found…
What’s wrong?
Did something happen, Kinomoto?
Eh?
Sensei.
The door opened so suddenly
it surprised us.
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry about surprising you,
but it is past light out time.
Hurry and go to sleep.
OK!
It’s no good,
I am too scared to sleep.
I will tell them I am scared
and ask the teachers
if I can stay with them.
I wonder if they will laugh at me.
That doesn’t matter,
even if they do laugh at me.
It’s better than being scared.
What are you doing here?
Eh?
You surprised me.
I was surprised too.
You went over to that
cliff during the day, right?
I felt a strange aura from that cave.
A Clow Card?
No.
Then maybe a g-g-g…
Are you trying to say ghost?
I can’t tell what it is yet.
I felt a strange aura from the
cliff just a little while ago.
I think I just saw something.
Stop it!
Let’s talk about something else.
OK? OK?
You’re the one who asked.
You came from Hong Kong right?
Yeah.
With your whole family?
No.
By yourself?
Along with Wei.
Wei?
A person who has been taking
care of me since I was little.
He must be a nice person.
Why do you know that?
You seem somehow happy.
I’m going to sleep.
Wait. Li-kun!
If you couldn’t sleep
you should have woken me up.
I would feel bad doing that,
and I talked to Li-kun
on the beach anyway.
He walked me back to the bungalow.
Is something wrong?
No, it’s nothing.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
we are going to
start the kimodameshi
you have been waiting for.
Deep in the cave,
there’s a small lake.
There you will leave
your candle behind.
Got that?
Yeah!
It’s the same as Naoko-chan’s story.
It’s a common story.
Naoko-chan seems to be having fun.
In your groups split into
smaller groups of two or three.
The cave is a one way path
and ends at the shrine,
so you don’t need to
worry about getting lost.
Once you leave your candle,
come straight back here.
OK!
Well, let’s begin.
The first group.
OK.
All right, next.
Yeah.
OK.
It’s almost to us.
It’s OK.
I am sure there is a teacher
in there to scare us.
I hope it’s scary.
Kinomoto seems pretty pale.
Are you scared?
Are you OK?
I’m excited.
Naoko-chan.
Next. Next. Next.
We’re next.
It’s all right. Everything is fine.
OK, next group.
I wonder if Kinomoto will be all right.
It’s Terada-sensei.
See.
It’s fun to surprise Kinomoto.
Well, be careful.
Yes!
But it’s strange isn’t it?
Eh?
After the first Terada-sensei
there haven’t been any
teachers to scare us.
That’s right.
And I wonder why we don’t
pass anybody going the other way.
There should only be
one path through this cave.
It’s strange not to meet anybody
who has left their candle
and is on their way back.
It’s the same as Naoko-chan’s story.
Tomoyo-chan!
Naoko-chan! Naoko-chan!
It’s Chiharu-chan’s voice.
I wonder what happened.
Let’s go check.
What happened?
Naoko-chan disappeared.
What do you mean disappeared?
I don’t know why,
but she disappeared.
Right in front of my eyes.
Right, Rika-chan?
Rika-chan!
It’s the same, Naoko-chan
disappeared in the same way.
Chiharu-chan.
She disappeared.
This is the same as
Naoko-chan’s story after all!
Let’s go back and
let the teachers know.
What’s wrong?
Li-kun?
Tomoyo-chan and everybody…
They disappeared?
Yamazaki who was with me
also disappeared.
Is it a ghost?
A ghost erased Tomoyo-chan
and the others?
That’s not it.
Calm down and read the aura.
It’s the aura of a Clow Card.
Over there?
Yeah.
The problem is how to get close.
Can’t we use Fly?
We should get close
as quietly as possible.
So the card doesn’t notice us.
I’ll try it.
Envelop me and
carry me to that land.
Float!
Since we don’t know
our opponent’s identity,
we need to first find
its true form.
My compass can’t find
it’s exact position.
It worked.
Li-kun!
You’re disappearing too.
Calm down.
Since the card is acting
you should be able to
find it’s location.
Concentrate.
Can you let everybody disappear?
I’ll do it!
Over there!
Now!
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card!
It’s the Erase card.
So that’s why everybody disappeared?
Here.
This is yours.
Without you
I would have just been crying
and not been able to do anything.
That is yours.
Li-kun.
Bring out Float.
Sure.
We’ve waited kimodameshi for a long time,
I don’t remember anything about
what happened in the kimodameshi.
Me too.
It was the same for me.
I don’t remember anything at all either.
Was it a Clow Card after all?
Yeah.
Nobody remembers anything.
Why is that, Li-kun?
Erase also made their memory go away.
I see.
Thank you for yesterday.
It’s not like I’ve acknowledged you.
Sakura-chan! Li-kun!
Want to play beach volleyball?
Sure!
There is a history to beach volleyball.
In ancient Egypt there
is a saying that the person
who stays to the end
without dropping the ball
will have success in love.
Another pile of lies.
Those two resemble each other a lot.
Yes, yes.