Tomorrow, we’ll be meeting
at school at 7:00 AM,
and head to the rink by bus.
Everyone be sure to be on time.
Okay!
It’ll be cold there,
so wear warm clothes.
And don’t forget your gloves.
Okay!
I thought it was cold, but this…
Shao Lan, let’s hurry home!
Thanks for waiting!
Hey, wait up!
You know, Kero…
What happened?
Tomoyo, look.
There’s ice here.
Oh, ice is going to be slippery.
Sakura, are you hurt?
No.
I wonder if tomorrow’s skating
will go alright.
It’ll be fine.
You’re great at sports, after all.
Even though it’s your first time, I’m
sure you’ll get the hang of it quick.
I wonder.
I’m still a little worried.
But I’m looking forward to it!
[Sakura and the Cold Ice Skating]
I’m home!
Eh?
These shoes…
Welcome home, Sakura.
Yukito!
H… hello!
Dinner is ready.
Eh?
You made it today?
Dad made it before he left.
Dad left on a business trip…
It was very tasty.
Yukito is staying
at our house tonight…
Schweeet!
Maybe I should make something to eat…
Didn’t you just finish
eating dinner?
But Yukito eats a lot.
He might be hungry again.
He came to study for college
entrance exams, didn’t he?
If he eats too much, he’ll get sleepy.
I see…
Of course it is!
Then I’ll take him some more tea!
It’s cold tonight,
better make some HOT tea!
What’re you doing?
I thought I’d bring you guys some tea.
Arigato.
It’s late.
Go to bed and sleep.
Good night.
I made the tea and everything…
But I didn’t get to see Yukito.
Sakura.
Eh?
Thanks for the tea.
No… problem…
Better not catch a cold.
Good night.
Okay!
Good night!
Schweeet!
I’m so happy!
Okay, Sakura
Cut it out!
I’m gonna get sick!
Oh yeah,
tomorrow is the skating trip.
Good night, Kero.
Who… are you?
A dream…
What is it?
I had a dream.
I saw it before, too.
It keeps coming back.
It’s gradually getting clearer.
The moon is out.
It’s a full moon.
There’s someone with long hair there.
G… good morning!
Good morning, Sakura.
Go sleep some more.
What’s with making
breakfast so early?
You’re going skating today,
so Touya is making lunch.
Eh?
Your lunch is that one.
Just kidding, just kidding.
That’s mine.
This is yours.
Thank you very much!
It’s cold again today!
I’m off!
I don’t wanna skate
on a cold day like this…
Geeze.
You’ll warm up when we get there.
Usually
Mei Lin waited until the last minute
to decide to come.
She’s from Hong Kong,
so she must not like the cold.
Is that so?
Because Hong Kong is a warm place.
I read it in a book once.
It’s close to the equator,
so it has good weather all year long.
Wow, that’s great!
You know, you could live there
for a hundred years and
never see weather like this.
We’ll be at the rink shortly.
Okay!
She’s good!
Sakura!
All right!
How do you balance on these skates?
I fell, of course.
Are you OK?
Shao Lan!
Let’s practice together.
One, two. One, two.
Miss Mizuki is good at this.
Yep.
Yes.
Are you all right?
Yes…
Keep your feet about as far
apart as your shoulders.
If you keep it slow,
you shouldn’t fall.
OK.
OK, shall we try
it out together?
Yes!
Everyone’s trying hard, aren’t they?
Yeah,
we’re heading back in the afternoon.
Keep it steady, like that.
One, two. One, two.
That’s the way, Kinomoto.
As expected, Sakura learns quickly.
Shao Lan, are you OK?
It hurts!
And it’s cold!
You OK?
Cocoa, please.
I’d like a hot milk, please.
Mei Lin,
you want to eat lunch
with us over there?
If I take even one step from here,
I’ll break!
Are you OK?
I’m not OK!
I’ll come by later,
so let’s skate together.
Why is Japan so cold?
Let’s eat!
What’s going on?
My brother and Yukito
made lunch for me today.
That’s wonderful!
It’s almost a waste to eat it.
Let’s eat!
Miss Mizuki!
Wooo…
One, two. One, two. One, two.
Sakura’s got the hang of it.
That’s just like Sakura.
What’s going on over here?
Li, you’re missing out.
I’m so cold!
Come on out, you’ll warm up.
Look lively, and get out there!
Okay…
Actually, it is a bit cold.
By any chance,
is the thermostat broken?
No,
it’s been working normally…
Naoko, you look like
you’re getting sick.
It’s really cold…
I’m shivering too.
We don’t want you
to catch a cold,
let’s go back inside.
OK…
Sakura, Tomoyo,
you all right?
Yes.
It’s a little cold,
but I’m comfortable.
OK, we’re going inside.
All right, I did it!
It’s cold!
It’s so cold, Shao Lan!
If you’re cold, go inside.
Thanks!
All right…
Even if I go inside,
it’s still cold…
Cold, huh?
It’s a little too cold.
May I have a cup of hot milk?
Something warm, please!
Can I get a hot coffee?
Hey, Mei Lin,
you’ll catch a cold.
So cold…
Come on, stand up.
Mei Lin, what’s wrong?
Mei Lin!
Hey, everyone!
Come in from the cold!
What’s that?
Teacher…
Sakura…
Tomoyo!
What’s happening?
Everyone’s frozen solid!
Stay calm.
Is this because of a Clow Card?
Yeah.
You and I probably weren’t affected
because we have magic power.
This is the work of the Freeze card.
Freeze?
Eh!
Release!
Jump!
Eh!
Thanks…
Never mind that,
hurry up and seal the Card!
Yes.
Oh!
Look out!
Jump!
Oh!
Hey
Eh!!
Dammit!
No matter how much I fight it…
Eh!
Hey, snap out of it!
Do you want everyone
to stay frozen like this?
I’ll distract Freeze,
while you look for
a chance to seal it.
But… how…
It’s swimming in the ice.
When it breaks the surface…
That’s when it’s vulnerable.
Yes.
Wah!
Now!
Return to thy true form…
…Clow Card!
Huh? It warmed up again.
It’s hot!
Thanks, Li!
Where’s the teacher?
Miss Mizuki!
Would you take these to everyone?
Sure!
Here!
Thanks!
Shao Lan!
What’re you doing?