Who… Who are you?
[The Person Sakura Loves the Most]
What do you mean?
I know…
the truth.
And what will you do?
I know all about it.
The other you you’re
not ever aware of…
Another Yukito-san…
You… You’re really…
…not human…
the times I’m not aware of…
the other me takes over.
Everything of my past memory is a lie.
Not really… at least, everything
you remember since we met is real.
I’m not really sure what you are.
But, as long as we’re together,
that’s fine by me.
Thanks.
Wow… that was really good…
I’m so glad I saw it.
Kinomoto-kun was so cool.
Tsukishiro-kun too!
The girl who played
Tsukishiro-kun’s sister…  she’s really
Kinomoto-kun’s sister, right?
Really? She was so cute…
You did a wonderful job.
Th… thank you.
I’ve asked them to lend me the tape.
I’ll dub it and make it as my treasure.
T… Tomoyo-chan…
AHH!! KINOMOTO-KUN!
TSUKISHIRO-KUN! YOU WERE SO COOL!!
As usual, your brother and
Tsukishiro-san have gathered a crowd.
So it seems…
Thanks…
Ever since he gave
Yue-san his power,
Oniichan has been very tired.
I understand why he did it…
Without Yukito-san and Yue-san,
Oniichan would be very lonely…
The movie was very interesting
Thank you.
See you later…
Oniichan…
It’s ok… I’m just a little tired…
Sakura-chan!
Sakura?
You came as well.
I know, let’s go have some tea.
Ok!
Thanks for waiting.
Here.
Thank you very much!
Take it you…
Thank you very much.
Well, what did you like the movie?
Yes!
You were very cute, Sakura-chan.
not really…
The whole class thought
you were wonderful.
Have you toured the fair yet?
No, not yet.
How you would you like
to go together then?
Is that ok?
Yes. I’ll be your tour guide then.
I’ll be sleeping in the classroom.
You ok?
Just tired, don’t worry.
Don’t eat to much, monster.
I don’t eat that much!
Geeze…
I’ll take my leave as well…
You’re going too?
Yes. I have things to do at home.
I guess I’ll see you tomorrow.
See you then.
Take care.
See you, Li-kun.
Do your best, ok?
What is it?
I… it’s nothing…
Shall we go then?
Yes!
(The Milky Way)
The Milky way?
Our class put it together.
Shall we go take a look?
Sure!
Hiiiiii! Sakura-chan!!!
Thanks for being in my movie!!
You were the best!!!
What is it? Are you going
through the “Milky Way”?
y… yes.
OK!!! 5th graders coming through!!!
Wait a… where’s Touya-kun?
He was tired so he’s sleeping
in the classroom.
That’s too bad…
he’s been so sleepy recently.
Anyway, only 2 at a time…
Sakura-chan and Tsukishiro-kun,
you go first and your friends’ll follow.
Ok, lets go then. Move along.
Move along. Ok!
Two on their way in!!
Wow!! Great! Pretty…
It’s really wonderful.
Eh? Oh, sorry…
What do you think?
It’s pretty good isn’t it.
Yes.
There’s a really nice
bit just up here…
I want him to know how I really feel.
Yukito-san…
What is it?
I… Yukito-san…
I… I…
I love you Yukito-san!
I love you too, Sakura-chan…
but, the person you’ll love most
isn’t me.
You love your father a lot, right?
Yes.
And me?
I love you…
Those feelings are the same, right?
The way you love your father,
and what you feel for me…
are similar, right?
They are…
I’m like him very much.
Since you’re so young,
you’re confused about it a bit.
Yes.
You knew the whole time?
Yes. I was glad you considered me
a part of your family.
There’s someone you love, isn’t there?
Yes, there is…
It’s Oniichan, right?
Yes, it’s him.
I’m not sure what I’d do without him.
Oniichan seems mean sometimes,
but he’s really very nice.
Yes.
He likes to tease me.
Yea. But, even though I love him,
I don’t know how he feels…
I’m sure he feels the same way!
That’s why he gave Yue his power.
Anyway, he must love you
at least as much as I do!
Sakura-chan…
But, If he’s ever mean to you,
you call me
and I’ll punish him for you, ok?
ok… Thank you.
I’m sure you’ll find him…
the one you’ll love most.
And I’m sure he’ll love you the most too.
Tell me when you find him, ok?
And if he’s ever mean,
I’ll punish him for you, ok?
Ok.
What’s happened?
I can feel magic…
I wonder
if something’s happened to her…
To Sakura-chan?
You stay here.
Li-kun!
As I thought…
Yue-san?
Since my magic’s back,
I can’t be mistaken.
It must be Clow.
But he’s…
Dead.
Did you hear something?
Someone’s coming…
I know.
RELEASE!
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
Maze! Illusion!
Wow! Isn’t this great!
It’s like a planetarium.
Isn’t this different from before?
Maze and Illusion, huh?
Damn, it looks like I’m late.
I can do it.
The aura’s gotten stronger…
Yes.
Where is it coming from?
This way!
Wait!
Clow-san’s
aura throught here
it’s getting stronger.
There it is!
Sakura!
Where is she?
This way.
He cut through the maze…?
E… Eriol-kun?
Why… Eriol?
It seems you’ve found me.
You’ve transformed
two cards and found me.
You really have gotten stronger.
Please wait just
a little bit longer,
good luck.
The cards…
She’s stopped using them…
Sakura.
Sakura!
Are you ok?
What happened?
I don’t know…
but I remember seeing someone standing
inside Clow’s magic circle.
Who was it…?
It’s as you said…
What’s the meaning of all this?
Is this really ok?
Yes. Thank you.
Is it really ok for you to go without me?
Yes. Shao Lan-kun and
Tomoyo-chan are with me.
It’s really ok.
Thank you for today.
Take care, ok?
We will, good bye.
Good bye, then.
So it was Clow-san again?
You’re not hurt, are you?
No, Shao Lan-kun rescued me.
I guess we should get
some rest tonight, then.
Yes, that’s a good idea.
Well, I must leave you here.
I’ll see you tomorrow, then.
I want to thank you too, Shao Lan-kun.
Shao Lan-kun?
I’ll
walk you home!
Thank you.
But first?
What?
Could we go to the park?
You know, today,
I told Yukito-san that I loved him…
Oh? Did you?…
But… But he said…
the one for me wasn’t him…
He said “Your feeling for me,
are they like those for your father?”
I thought about it…
and I realized he was right.
But, there’s someone he loves,
really loves,
not like a father,…
The person he loves…
I love that person too…
and I’m sure that person loves him too.
So it’s ok that he doesn’t love me…
If Yukito’s with the person he loves,
then it’s ok.
Tomoyo told me that
when the person you love is happy,
then you can be happy too.
I think I’d be happy to know
that he was happy.
But… it seems that… for some reason…
I can’t help but cry…
But I don’t want to cry in front of him.
Because he’d know…
No… why am I crying…
I understand what he said but…
really… It’s good that he’s happy…
I know.
I understand.
Thank you.
Yukito-san said…
Someday I’d find someone
I really loved. And… and he’d
love me as much as I loved him.
I’m sure you’ll find him.
It’s ok.
You’ll surely find him.
Thank you.