[Sakura and elephant compare strength]
Morning.
Good morning.
Today’s lunch is extra special.
Sakura is going on a trip?
To the zoo she says.
Shall I help you?
No, I’m just about done.
Wait a second for breakfast.
Yeah
This is the Penguin park
inside Tomoeda central park
What’s this?
Good morning!
Oh, for you to come down alone,
it will rain today probably.
You’re wrong.
The lady in the weather report
said it would be clear.
Good morning, Sakura.
Is that mine?
I put in lots of your favorite things.
Yay!
Are you gathering at school?
Yeah, we are gathering at school
and going by bus from there.
If you are going through
the park be careful.
Why?
Eh… Eh…
I’m going!
That was surprising.
How could such a large emperor penguin
be flipped over?
Could it be a Clow Card?
I’ll ask Kero-chan when I get home.
How nice.
Sakura-chan!
Eh!
Yukito-san.
Good morning, you certainly are early.
Umm… Good morning!
Umm, aren’t you with my brother?
Today I’m the board monitor.
Today really is a good day.
What?
The penguin shaped slide
which was destroyed.
The mysterious thing about this incident
was that nobody was near the slide between
the break of dawn and early morning.
There is a lot of people.
It must be something very strong,
to flip that upside down.
You’re right.
I don’t feel the aura of a Clow Card.
Sakura-chan.
Yes?
Since you’re carrying a pack,
does that mean you’re going on
a trip somewhere today?
Yes.
It seems pretty big.
What’s in there?
A notebook for taking observations,
and lunch.
Did your dad make it?
Yes.
Your dad really is a good cook.
A gift.
The weather is nice,
we are going on a trip,
and I met Yukito-san.
Today really is a good day!
Huh…
Eh?
Strange?
Well then go off
and observe the animal
assigned to your group.
Do you all know your groups?
Yes!
Well then, group leaders come
and take the camera.
Yes!
Turn in the report on Monday.
Cooperate and do your best.
Yes!
Have lunch whenever
your group feels like it
Be back here at two o’clock.
Yes!
Well then, dismissed.
Tomoyo-chan.
You take care of the pictures.
Tomoyo-chan is an expert on cameras.
Sure.
By the way, did you all see it on TV?
About the emperor penguin?
Yeah.
Yeah, I saw it.
I wonder how they pulled
over something so big?
I wonder if it was a ghost.
If it were a ghost
it would be a really strong ghost right?
Perhaps the ghost of a sumo wrestler?
It would be nice if it were a scary one.
Eh? Why?
I like scary things.
There is the elephant, let’s go.
She’s fast.
Sakura-chan can’t handle
scary stories well.
But they are so fun.
Ah, there it is.
Where?
Right there.
So this is a sloth?
It seems pretty cute.
I wonder if it is related to a monkey.
Yeah, it must be.
We are in charge of the sloth.
Let’s do our best to observe it.
Yeah!
I wonder
if the sloth is like it’s name implies
and doesn’t move around a lot.
That’s not true at all, Li-kun.
A sloth is actually really swift.
It is always lazing about
like it doesn’t feel like moving…
but if it gets in the mood
a sloth is incredible.
Its speed
has been confirmed
at over a hundred kilometers per hour.
Incredible.
There it is Yamazaki’s sure
kill technique.
Yamazaki will lie for fun
at the slightest chance.
His lies are also ones that you would
normally know are lies right away.
Sometimes there are people
who are fooled though.
I wonder if we can see a sloth
that feels up to moving.
I would be nice if we did.
All right.
How big!
Hey,
they say these elephants
can do various tricks.
They say that they can understand
some human speech.
I have seen them on TV.
I saw them too.
They can do thinks like stand
on two legs when told to.
Yeah, it’s a really strong elephant
and even played tug-of-war.
Yeah, that’s right.
It was amazing.
Oh yeah, we have to make observations.
Let’s all do our best.
Yeah!
An earthquake?
It doesn’t seem like it.
It sounded like something very large
had fallen.
123, 123…
Oh yeah, what is Kero-chan doing?
He is staying at home today.
Kero-chan!
The elephant really is neat.
Really.
Did you write your report?
Just a little longer.
Good luck.
You finally noticed.
You said you were saying
at home didn’t you?
I had planned on that,
but your dad’s lunch smelled so good.
I just sorta floated in…
So that’s why the bag seemed heavy.
It wasn’t just my weight.
The lunch is big too.
If you had only asked
I would have brought you along.
I thought I would surprise you.
Sakura-chan was surprised
so it was a big success.
Yeah!
Sensei!
Umm…
What is it?
I made lunch,
will you have some?
It moved!
A little at 11:46.
It moved three times
in watching it for an hour.
Is that a lot, or a little?
Who knows.
Ah! It moved again.
it moved at 11:47.
For it two move twice in two minutes,
it might be up to it today.
There it is again.
Can you feel it?
Yeah.
It’s the aura of a Clow Card.
The animal’s cages were broken.
Penguins are fine,
but if some big animal
got out that would be bad.
Over there.
I am sure the keepers
and sensei are at the entrance.
What about you two?
We’ll be right back.
Li-kun.
Take care of this.
Nobody is here.
They all fled.
That is more convenient,
it would be a problem
if lots of people were around
when you use magic.
This way right?
I certainly feel a Clow Card’s
aura this way.
What card did this?
A card that would
want to break cages?
Something just crossed there.
What huge prints.
But I didn’t see anything.
Over there.
The elephants are afraid.
What should we do?
We can’t do much
when we don’t know what the card is.
Key which hides the power of darkness,
show your true form before me.
Under the contract,
I Sakura, command thee.
Release!
Windy!
The elephant was just about
to be really hurt.
But to throw an elephant like that.
What card is it?
I know!
Umm… Eh…
But.
If you don’t hurry and
save the elephant…
Wait a moment!
You are strength.
The card of Power.
Won’t you do a test of strength
against me?
Why a test of strength?
Power’s pride comes from
having a lot of strength.
There is the proof.
It’s coming this way.
See?
Aren’t you glad you used the Jump magic?
Don’t give me that.
If you don’t hurry and
test strength with it in a hurry…
What should I do?
Something you think you can win.
Here it comes again.
There is no way I can win against that.
If you don’t, it’ll continue like that.
Tug of war!
Power really is cute.
You’ll get hurt if you
underestimate her based on her form.
Kero-chan.
For the time being if it gets
dangerous you should let go.
Kero-chan!
Sakura, use a card.
Hurry and use one.
Close her in with Windy.
My hands are full, I can’t use it.
The elephant!
Go for it!
Good luck!
Time!
Could it be she won?
So it seems.
All right! All right! All right!
Thank you,
this is because you helped.
Sakura, hurry and seal her.
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card.
This card really caused a panic.
You did good.
I thought I would lose for sure.
It was close.
I wonder if the sloth is feeling up to it.
Hey Kero-chan, this card is…
Of course, if you use it,
you become really strong.
Sakura-chan, I have a request.
Eh?
Tomoyo-chan!
What are you looking at?
Sakura-chan.
Ahh! That picture!
Thank you so much, it’s a souvenir
Don’t show it to anybody.
Yes.
Good morning.
Good morning!
It seemed the zoo was exciting.
Are you OK?
Yes!
Is that a picture from yesterday?
Yes.
This is…
What should I do?
He might find out about the magic.
You really are strong Sakura-chan.
That is a trick photo.
There is no way you could do
this without using magic.