What’s going on?
Aren’t you getting up way too early,
Sakura?
Kero,
I was wondering if the recent incidents
are related
to these new cards
And also related to Clow…
Maybe…
If you keep feeling so gloomy,
you’re gonna start getting youself sick.
If strange things start happening again…
What’s gonna happen
if you’re not feeling well
You’re right.
If anything’s gonna happen,
I gotta do the best
I can with my cards.
All right! And on that note,
cheer up and go to school!
[Sakura, Shao Lan
and the Invisible Threads]
I’m leaving.
Well, it can’t be helped since
I got here so early.
Come to think of it,
Touya said they’re having
a morning game today.
Big Brother!
Yuki!
Yukito!!
Touya!!
Nice shoot!
That’s your nice pass.
Touya!! You are caught!
Hey you, stop it!!
I don’t mean being caught!
I’m in the middle of a game right now!!
Akizuki! I can’t move!
It’s starting already,
come on, Let’s go!
Great!
I’m glad that a new piano
is coming in today.
Yes, this way the choir
can resume practice.
Miss Tsujitani was glad about it.
It was such a mess.
– What happened?!
– The piano suddenly…
Watch out!
Why did the piano move all of a sudden?
I have never dreamed
that I would be chased by a piano
Me neither…
Do we not know
who is the one behind this?
I was sure
I sensed Clow’s aura,
but…
But Clow has passed away
a long time ago, right?
But it is no use keep thinking about it.
When anything happens,
I’ll still be cheerful
and everything’ll work out.
Right, right.
A smile suits best for you, Sakura.
Sakura! Tomoyo!
Hurry, hurry
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Let’s eat!
It testes so good!
Rika, this is good!
Thank goodness.
Let’s eat.
Really, this is good.
I would not believe this is home-made.
Rika, you’re
really good at baking cookies.
I’m glad
you like it.
Lately, you don’t seem cheerful,
Sakura…
Oh, I might have been mistaken…
That’s not it,
Rika. Thanks…
Excuse me,
I hope you don’t mind me
trying to finish up my sewing.
Cute bear!!
Rika, did you make that yourself.?
– That’s awesome!
– Awesome!
Rika, you really can make anything.
If you follow the instructions
in the book, it’s quite simple.
By the way, do you know
when a stuffed bear’s birthday is?
The day it is finished?
That would have been a good day.
But if you buy from a store,
you would not know
when it is finished, right?
That’s why
its birthday is the day
that you name the bear
and put a ribbon on it.
That’s quite wonderful, isn’t it?
Also overseas,
they said if you name the stuffed bear
you made with your own name.
And then give it to the person you love,
the two of you will fall in love
Is that so?
Fall in love…
Rika, you’re blushing.
No, I’m not…
Fall in love…
The girls are so cute talking about
a stuffed bear’s birthday.
You always look at me
with such scary face.
Did I do something
that displeased you?
No, you didn’t.
You were from Hong Kong, were you not?
I have just come to Japan,
would you mind
showing me various things?
Shao Lan Li…
Are you ok?
I’m fine!!!
So… Sorry about that…
What an interesting person.
Maybe you can help me out…
Good-bye!
– Good-bye!
– Take care.
I’m sorry, Sakura.
I can’t make it to the
handicraft store together.
It’s okay, Tomoyo’s coming with me.
Don’t worry about it.
Go home now, okay?
Then, I’ll see you later.
I wonder if Rika finished her bear.
Yes, during break time.
About bears, you know…
They were originally sea-animals.
Apparently, they used to swim
the seven seas in pursuit of salmon.
Is that so?
From Alaska and the
Arctic Ocean in the north,
to Antarctica in the south.
It was truly a great voyage
that spanned the world
On top of that, bears back then
used to able to dive deep into the ocean
That’s incredible.
Yeah. I’ve heard that
the white part on the neck
of a Japanese moonbear is…
a marking so that they
don’t lose sight of each other
in the dark depths of the ocean.
And the thing that caused them
to come up on land is…
No these lies again!!
…Because of the existence of a salmon
big enough to be mistaken for a whale…
Okay, okay, and?
They were lies?
So, shall we go?
Are you going to the handicraft store?
Yes, we are.
Do you mind if I come along?
No. I don’t.
I’m going too!
And the battle between the legendary
salmon and the bears…
was unfolded over the long time
period of fifty years…
Okay, okay, and then?
Mr.Terada…
What’s it?
Here.
Oh? It’s a stuffed bear.
It is very well made…
You really did a good job.
Hmm… Hm.
Would you minding having it?
This… for me?
Yes.
I’ll treasure it, Sasaki.
Thank you very much.
Are you mad at something, Li?
I’m not mad.
You are going to buy stuffed bears?
Did anything unusal happen that night?
If anything happens,
don’t just go alone, call me.
You might get caught in danger.
Let’s see. Bear. Bear.
There!
Thanks goodness,
I can buy it with my allowance.
For Tsukishiro??
Yes, What about you? Are you not buying?
For me,
For me, if the person I like most
can be happier
than falling in love with me.
I would like to keep this happiness
for this person the way it is forever.
You mean, it is okay even if
the person you like
doesn’t return the feeling?
If this person can return my feeling,
of course I would be really happy
But the greatest happiness
for me
is to let the person I like
have the most happiness
I’m sure this person you like most
is really happy as well
You think so?
Yup! I’m sure!
Thank you very much.
what did you buy,
Eriol?
These.
Threads?
Are you sewing something?
You can use threads in many ways.
Like what?
You can use them when roasting meat.
Is that real?
Yes, you can use them
like kite strings when
making roast beef.
Kite.
Oh? I see,
Li knows a lot too.
Not really.
How is it?
It’s hard…
Let me see. Let me see.
This is… a bear?
Somehow it looks more like Kero.
What?!
Is something wrong?
This…
This aura…
Clow’s aura.
Why did the brat come along?
Because I made a promise with him
that if anything happens,
I’ll call him.
Right, Li?
I guess he can be helpful sometimes.
What are you trying to say?
Anything’s better than nothing.
What??
Li?
– Li?
– Brat, what’s going on?
My body…
Move! Watch OUT!
Sakura!!
Something’s cotrolling him!
Like what?
This is Clow’s aura after all.
Could this be
Clow’s doing as well
But
Clow had passed away.
Watch out!
Tomoyo!
Get away from me.
I can’t.
I can’t leave you there.
Can’t we think of a way?
There should be something
controlling him.
If we can find out what it is…
But…
I don’t see anything at all!
Water dragon, come Forth!
Threads!
Cut them, Sakura!
O Key which hides the forces of stars,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release!
Sword!
She did it.
Li…
– I’m okay!
– Thank goodness.
Sakura, you okay?
Li, did you get hurt?
I’m fine but…
She fell asleep again.
It must be hard to create Sakura Cards.
I am sure that was Clow’s aura.
The aura of Clow Reed’s magic.
The threads can be used
for this too, Sakura.
Your spell was broken,
wasn’t it?
That was impressive.
The new Mistress of the Clow Cards.
Is that book interesting,
Spinel?
Yes, because this is a book
you left behind a long time ago.
A long time ago.
But why took all the trouble
to come to Japan?
Is it boring here?
No, not a bit.
It’s really fun, especially at school…
Besides, I found something nice.
You’re actually taking your time
instead of helping yourself
right to it as usual.
I’m suprised.
There’s someone of trouble around him.
Besides,
taking my time just makes
it even more tasty, right?
But…
couldn’t you just wear boys
uniform instead?
It doesn’t matter, does it?
And the girls’ uniform is so cute!
Beside, I’m not human.
Doesn’t matter if it is male
or female, right?
O Key which hides the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Eriol,
command thee under contract.
Release!
Return to your true form,
Spinel Sun, Ruby Moon.
Our creator, Eriol,
whose name from previous life
is Clow Reed.
What’s your intention
of coming here?
To make things interesting.