The rain that has been falling
in Tomoeda since last night.
…is not going to stop any time soon…
But why is this persistent rain
only falling in Tomoeda?
O Key which hides
the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true
form before me.
I, Sakura,
command thee under contract.
Release!
Why won’t it transform
into the wand?
Oh, you got up on time, monster.
You’re not fighting back.
Invite the snow-rabbit over tomorrow.
(Yukito = snow-rabbit)
Yukito?
Why Tsukishiro?
Yue is the one I need to talk to.
Um, do you know
if Yukito is coming over today?
Yuki? He didn’t mention.
Um, Can you…
um… um…
He’ll probably come
if you make something to eat.
Ok!
I’ll do my best at it today!
I guess I’ll ask him,
since it’s such a rare occasion
that the monster is cooking.
What did you say?!?
[Sakura and the Awakened Star Key]
That aura yesterday…
No, that shouldn’t be…
But…
This rain isn’t stopping at all.
They say it’s only falling
in Tomoeda and nowhere else
Maybe this is a
supernatural phenomenon!
About supernatural phenomenon… ,
The world’s highest mountain
was found in Antarctica,
and they said it’s
all because of penguins!
Penguins?
They said they had
some sort of strange powers,
and they could even fly!
Maybe they’re aliens!
And by the way,
they said some American mountaineers…
…even saw giant penguins
flying in the sky!
Bunch of lies again.
This rain is no ordinary rain.
But all the Clow Cards
have been gathered already…
How come…
Please have them.
Eriol…
A smile fits best on your face,
Sakura.
Thank you.
– Good morning!
Good morning, everyone.
– Good morning, Tomoyo!
– Good morning.
The situation has upped already.
The Key won’t
transform into the wand?
What’s going on…
And besides,
this rain…
All the Clow Cards have been captured.
I wonder why strange things
are happening again?
Maybe someone
who has power made it happen?
But I can’t sense any.
Maybe we just don’t notice it.
Maybe it is someone
even more powerful than us.
Someone even more
powerful than us…
Sakura…
Really?
Why is she with that brat!
Touya, you have really good eyes.
Yuki…
I…
There’s something
I gotta tell you.
– What’s it?
– I…
– About you, I…
– Touya!!
The teacher said
the meeting is starting,
so hurry and bring the printout.
Got it.
Yuki, stack yours up here.
It is heavy.
I can carry them myself.
Then…
– Akizuki…
– Call me Nakuru.
I can’t move.
Bye!
You don’t know, do you?
In that case, it is mine.
I wonder if it’s like Li said,
it’s because of
someone more powerful than us.
Sakura.
Eriol.
Thanks for the flower this morning.
Did your problem get solved?
Not yet…
But thanks for the flower,
I felt better.
I’m glad.
Did you buy that flower?
No,
it was from my garden.
That’s wonderful.
Next time, please come visit.
– Can I?
– Of course!
Thanks!
I’m going this way.
I’m turning here.
– Then, see you tomorrow.
– See you tomorrow.
Eriol is really nice.
– Thanks for the dinner!
– Thanks.
This was really delicious!
Thanks, Sakura.
Then I’m off to my part-time.
I’ll help clean up.
Sorry about that.
Thank you very much!
It’s still raining…
Because this isn’t just any rain.
Nothing. I’m leaving now.
Take care.
Back to your original form, Yue!
What? You look like you just woke up
and already having a bad mood.
Having two different personalities
between the true self and the false self.
It is rather troublesome.
Umm, Yue, have some tea…
This guy doesn’t eat anything…
But you love to eat sweet things.
Because Yue and
I have different eating habits,
and that’s simply what I need.
More tea.
Okay.
You send her out of the room
on purpose.
Because she isn’t aware of what
I’m thinking yet.
What do you think of this rain?
Looks like someone
purposely created this rain.
That’s what I thought.
The question becomes,
who is this… someone.
In the meantime,
the aura I felt yesterday.
I wanted to confirm it was his.
His…
That guy both you and I know so well…
Thanks for waiting.
– What’s the matter!?
– You got me!
You transformerd…
Just get used to it.
Kero,
I don’t know what’s going to happen.
I’ll leave Tomoyo to you, ok?
Please be careful.
– What??
– No, nothing… Hmmm,
Yukito doesn’t know
about you at all, right?
Right.
Then what about when you are him?
– I remember everything.
– I… I see…
This is making me so nervous…
In the end,
I still can’t imagine that
Yukito and Yue are the same person.
Yue is handsome,
but Yukito…
Sakura!!
Sakura!
Yue!
O Key which hides
the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura,
command thee under contract.
Release!
No! It doesn’t work after all!
Able to overpower me and Yue,
that means it must be…
Sakura!
Kero!
I can’t move!
Kero…
Sakura! Run!
Sakura!
Sakura…
This power…
I can’t breathe…
Tomoyo! Kero! Yue!
This feels terrible!
At this rate,
I’ll… Everyone will…
No!
This can’t happen…
I can’t… let this happen!
that magical formation…
It’s not the one Crow created.
That wand…
That wand holds a new power.
Neither the Sun or the Moon,
it is your mere power of the Stars.
Power of the Stars…
O Key which hides
the power of the stars,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura,
command thee under contract.
Release!
Firey!
Why?
The Key transformed into the wand,
but why doesn’t
it work on the card?
What should I do…
How do I save everyone…?
A new wand.
If this is a new wand,
maybe the cards too…
Card, I beg of you,
lend me your power!
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine
old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress
Firey!
The Spells changed.
Because the wand holds
the power of the stars,
it wouldn’t work unless I changed
the wording of the spell to “star”.
And besides, the card…
…has changed as well…
O Key which hides
the power of the stars,
reveal thy true form before me.
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form
and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
– Sakura.
– Are you okay?
I’m ok, oh, you know, the card…
Sakura.
– How is she?
– Is she hurt?
Asleep.
Is something wrong, Yue?
No.
Not bad.
To be able to create a new card
from a Clow Card
That’s impressive.