Mizuki-sensei…
There’s another person…
Who…?
The Clow Cards…
Who are you?
[Sakura, Kero,
and the Mysterious Teacher]
The alarm’s over here.
Didn’t you put it
over on the desk yourself
so that you don’t fall back asleep?
Oh, that’s right!
Geez.
You’ve had this doll
since before you woke me,
haven’t you?
Yeah, about a week
before I first met you.
Tomoyo made it for me for my birthday
and having become a 4th-grader.
It’s me.
I see. It does look like you.
Tomoyo’s real good at sewing.
Why is the doll wearing clothes like that
even before I was awoken?
Even before I become
the Card Captor,
Tomoyo said
someday she’d
make costumes for me
to wear for sure.
And so, she first
started with a doll…
It looks like it…
It’s like what’s in the dream.
There was a huge moon…
A full moon.
The Clow Cards…
…and Mizuki-sensei were there…
And now, there was also
a person with wings.
Has pretty purple clothes
and silver hair…
The clothes I was wearing
look very much like this.
I gotta go.
I woke up early too!
Yue…
Good morning!
You woke up early as planned.
The rice is almost ready.
Thank you!
Good. They look very nice.
Really?
Tsukishiro-kun is competing in
Japanese archery today, right?
Yeah. He’s representing
his school, he said.
There’re even adults in the competition.
It’s a really big one, I heard.
He must be good.
He seems to help out with the basketball
team and the soccer team as well.
I promised Yukito-san
that I’m gonna make lunch for him.
Oh, by the way,
is Onii-chan still asleep?
He said he has part-time today as well.
He got up early and left already.
Oh well.
And I was going to make him lunch
for a surprise too.
Okay, now that the side dishes are done,
let’s add those in.
Okay!
It’s done!
Good job.
Tomoyo-chan… Li-kun… Yukito-san…
Yukito-san… Me…
Oh no, I made too much.
Even it is one more prepared,
I’m sure Tsukishiro-kun will eat them all.
But for you to carry all of them
by yourself…
Don’t worry.
They’re coming to help
carry the food together.
Coming!
– Good morning, Tomoyo-chan!
– Good morning!
I am glad the weather is so nice!
Li-kun too!
Thanks for coming by.
When it comes
to capturing Clow Cards,
it’s easier if you’re around.
You’re right.
The lunch was just done. Shall we go?
I’ll go to get them.
You made lunch for me too, right?
– I must come along.
– Ke… Kero-chan!
What’s wrong?
It’s nothing.
It’s not nothing…
Sorry about that, Li-kun.
I’ll carry it
after we get off the train.
– I’m okay.
– But…
Still not there yet?
No, Kero-chan,
you can’t stick your head out.
We are getting there soon…
Told you it’s better to just stay home,
right?
I can always make you lunch
If you want.
I’m coming with you not
just because there’s lunch.
I just want to stay near you if possible.
It’s all about to end…
End? Are you talking
about the Clow Cards?
So, I’m almost done
with gathering all the cards?
It is almost over, Sakura-chan!
What is wrong?
No… it’s nothing. Sorry.
Yue, it seems that
it’s almost time for us to meet.
Li-kun, really,
let me carry it!
I… I’m okay.
Oh, there we are!
There’s a archery field in such a place.
There are rituals that
involve drawing bows as well.
Yukito-san!
– Good morning!
You guys came to cheer for me.
Yes! Umm… We brought lunch too!
He… Here it is!
You guys got up early for all this.
It must be tough.
No, not at all!
Thank you.
Oh, I gotta go. I’ll do my best.
We’ll cheer for you with all we have!
He looks wonderful dressed in that.
Yukito always looks so nice,
whatever he wears.
Don’t you think so, Li-kun?
I can sense the aura of the moon…
Tsukishiro-san won!
Yukito-san is wonderful!
What is the matter?
That is…
Mizuki-sensei…
Why is Sensei here?
But she is very skilled too!
Yeah…
Just as I thought, the aura of the moon…
Tsukishiro-san
has advanced to the final!
Yeah, but his opponent is…
Tsukishiro-kun…
My best regards.
Same here.
I don’t know who to cheer for.
Yukito-san, or Mizuki-sensei…
Neither of them
is giving away anything.
Whoever loses concentration
is going to lose.
Tsukishiro-san won!
She seemed to be
distracted by something,
and lost.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
– Congratulations!
– Co… Congratulations!
Thanks. But that was…
Oh well. I’m hungry!
– Do you mind if I start eating?
– Y… Yes!
– Let’s eat!
This is good! Did you make all of this?
Father helped me.
This is really good!
Oh, where are the cups?
In my back pack.
Kero-chan’s gone!
– What’s wrong?
– It… It’s nothing…
Where did you go… Kero-chan…
Hello.
You did notice me after all.
This is the first time
I saw you in this shape.
Yeah, I guess last time was
when that brat and I exchanged bodies.
I couldn’t use any magic at all,
I couldn’t tell.
I sense a great power in you.
On top of that,
it’s the power of the moon.
You work with the power of the moon,
don’t you?
Created alongside
by Clow Reed as a pair,
The other guardian of the Clow Cards…
Yue,
Which means Moon in Chinese…
Kero-chan! Kero-chan, where are you?
– Did you say anything to Sakura?
– No.
About the Last Judgment…?
I know about it.
But I didn’t mention that to her either.
My task here is something else.
What’s your task?
You’ll find out, very soon.
Geez, where did Kero-chan go?
I believe
Sakura can accomplish anything.
Same here.
Kero-chan!
Mizuki-sensei!
– What’s the matter with you?
– I thought
it’s better to talk in a quiet place.
Talk?
Kero-chan?!
That was such a surprise!
You were with Miss Mizuki.
That’s because you got out of the bag.
She noticed me earlier.
She is someone
with a great power after all.
And yet you feel schweeet or whatever
when you see her.
That’s because!
But… Not again.
So… Sorry!
Bear…
For me? Thanks!
Sakura-chan!
What are you doing?!
O… Onii-chan!!
You really do work part-time everywhere.
What a coincidence.
– For us to bump into each other.
– It really is!
Onii-chan?
There is no coincidence in this world.
There is only the inevitable.
See ya, Touya.
Work hard!
Let’s go before it gets too dark.
Oh wait, Sakura,
do you not have the lunch boxes?
Oh, now that you mention it…
You must have left
them somewhere back there.
I took them out when
we were eating lunch…
They must be around there somewhere.
Let’s go look for them.
Okay.
What Onii-chan said just now…
What did he mean by that…
And then what Miss Mizuki said…
Today’s last round,
did something distract you?
I just felt
like somebody was staring at me.
Staring at you?
– Tsukishiro-kun…
– Yes.
You…
Kero-chan, this aura…!
Yeah. A Clow Card.
On top of that,
it’s one that has very strong power.
Tomoyo-chan!
Are you okay?
It’s coming!
This is…!