A Clow Card…
I know…
…that person…
[Sakura’s Wonderful Xmas]
That person was…
Who?
Miss Mizuki!
I’m sorry!
If you sleep in the classroom,
you’ll catch a cold.
All right, let’s stop there for today.
Was that Miss Mizuki?
Are you feeling sick?
No, I’m fine.
Since the Quiz Competition,
you’ve been a little distant.
I’m really OK.
I just keep having this weird dream.
A dream?
A dream with a full moon,
a long-haired person,
and Clow Cards.
Other than that,
I really feel fine!
Please don’t push yourself, OK?
What’s the matter?
Hey, look at this!
Look at that!
That’s right,
it’ll be Christmas soon.
Have you decided what
you’re going to give everyone?
No, not yet.
How about you, Tomoyo?
I’ve already
decided on your present!
Thank you!
What should I do?
Christmas Day is also
Yukito’s birthday.
Alright, next!
What do I do for Christmas presents?
For Yamazaki?
I was thinking of giving him
something handmade, but…
…Yamazaki does that himself.
Yes.
He’s better than me at sewing,
cooking and just about everything.
Hi!
If it’s your present,
I’m sure he’ll be happy.
I’m still not very confident,
though…
Yamazaki.
Right.
Christmas present,
huh?
Oh, nothing…
What do I do?
About presents?
I’ve got Dad and
my brother figured out.
And I’ve decided on yours, too.
Umm…
But…
It’s Tsukishiro’s, right?
Yeah…
That’s great! Just like Shao Lan!
How about asking advice
from someone new?
Eh?
W… what do you want?
Mei Lin, you know…
You’re going to kidnap me,
and hold me for ransom!
You’re going to take
Shao Lan’s Clow Cards!
No!
It’s just… I wanted to ask your
advice about something…
Advice?
Christmas present?
You give one to Li every year…
I was wondering if you had any ideas…
Whether it’s handmade or bought,
there are all kinds, but…
All kinds, but?
Anything would be fine, wouldn’t it?
But!
It doesn’t matter so much
what the present is,
but the feelings that go with it, right?
Whether it’s something
you worked hard at making…
…or something you chose,
either way is fine, right?
Mei Lin!
And if he hates you,
anything’ll suck!
Does he hate you?
I don’t think so…
Then you’ll be OK!
Thanks!
Later!
Talking with her turned out well,
didn’t it.
Yep!
It really did work out.
Sakura…
…the bath is free!
OK!
Sakura, your bath…
Hang on a minute…
You just dialed it a minute ago.
You should just get it over with.
Here, just hit Redial!
Kero, you little…!
Just tryin’ to help…
Yes, this is Tsukishiro…
Um… um… I…
Sakura?
Yes!
Um, about Sunday,
the day after tomorrow…
Right. These amusement
park tickets from Chiharu…
That girl in my class.
We met her at the Quiz Competition…
Yes, I got them!
Um… Yukito, how’s your injury?
She got all hot and
bothered over a simple phone call
to a guy?
I really don’t get this “love” thing…
Is that all right?
Yes… yes… OK, this Sunday…
I did it!
I’m meeting Yukito at the
amusement park this Sunday!
I feel sad…
So, what should we ride?
Sakura looks so happy.
The clothes
I gave her look nice, too.
I’m a little worried
about Sakura, though.
You look more like
you’re spying on her.
But really, we can’t miss
Sakura’s Christmas date.
I have a duty to follow her, right?
That was fun.
It was!
What’s next?
Um… um…
Would you quit hanging off me?
Stop being so cold!
Hi!
Li. Mei Lin.
You guys came, too?
Back in Hong Kong,
we would go to the amusement park
every Christmas.
The two of you?
Well, with all
of Shao Lan’s sisters.
Eh?
Is that him?
The one you’re giving the present to.
Yeah…
So did you decide?
Yeah, all because I got your advice.
I’m kinda hungry.
I’m hungry, too.
Me, too.
So, shall we get something
to eat over there?
Sure.
Yes.
What do you want?
Eh?
Brother…
You can really find
a part-time job everywhere.
Of course.
Great!
The more you eat,
the healthier it represents.
Yes.
That’s true.
This brat.
Li and Sakura…
I want to eat too.
Right, we should have our meal.
This aura…
Pretty, isn’t it?
What kind of special effect is that?
It’s not a special effect.
That’s just a normal power line.
These aren’t ordinary flames…
A Clow Card?
Wait! It’s dangerous!
Time!
A card!
If you use Sleep,
you can put everyone out!
Hurry!
Key which hides the power of dark.
…reveal thy true form to me.
By the covenant, I,
Sakura, command thee.
Release!
Sleep!
Li!
Time takes up a
lot of my magic energy.
I just need to rest a bit.
But…
You’ve got to do
something about that fire.
Wind, be the chain that binds the flames!
Windy!
Sakura, Windy can’t
stand up to this one!
Kero, why’re you here?
Don’t worry about that now!
Windy is one of the
prime Elemental Cards Clow made.
But Windy isn’t aggressive
enough to win!
What Elemental Cards
do you have?
Windy and Watery…
So this has to be a fire card.
The Fiery Card!
Now you show your true form!
Fiery is an attack card.
That’s why you can’t
hit it with Windy.
The enemy of fire is…
Water!
You can’t hit it with just Watery!
Watery doesn’t have
as much power as Fiery…
So if they fight, you can’t win!
So what do I do?
Windy and Watery.
Use both cards at once!
Eh?
Using two Elemental Cards
together is impossible!
But if it keeps going like this,
Fiery is gonna burn down the whole park!
This is our best chance!
No! I won’t let you!
Everyone… the whole park…
And I’m going to capture all the cards!
Please, do your best
with me one more time!
Wind and water, work together
to contain the flames!
Windy!
Watery!
Two Elemental Cards working together…
Now!
Return to thy true form…
Clow Card!
You did it!
Fiery…
Good job, Sakura!
Kero?
Don’t worry ‘bout it.
Didn’t I tell you?
My symbol is the Sun.
To get the power to return to my true
form… you need to have the Fiery card
Can you return to your true form?
Not yet!
However…
A bit of my power is coming back.
As you capture the cards,
I grow stronger.
Right!
I’ll try hard from now on!
See that, loser? Sakura got another Card.
And it’s an Elemental Card,
to boot.
Even if your power is coming back,
you’re still a stuffed animal.
What was that, brat?
Wanna say that again?
As many times as you want!
Would the two of you cut it out?
Stuffed animal, stuffed animal,
stuffed animal…
It’s the best place,
but the hardest place to film.
Someone will see you!
Don’t worry, we’re pretty high up.
You guys caught a card while
I was sleeping?
That’s not fair.
I guess I got tired somewhere
along the way… Sorry.
But I’m glad the fire went out.
Yeah…
Um… Here…
For Christmas, and for your birthday…
For me?
Thanks. Can I open it?
It’s handmade, isn’t it?
Yes!
Thank you.
That’s not snow, is it? It’s glowing.
It’s Christmas, right?
My power’s coming back,
so here’s a special treat for ya!
Sakura?
I’d like to come back again next year.
OK.