Who? Who is calling me?
[Sakura and the mysterious magical book.]
Ah
It was this sound.
Sakura, breakfast is ready.
OK!
I’m Sakura Kinomoto.
A fourth grader at Tomoeda elementary.
My favorite subjects are PE and music.
My least favorite subject is math.
In short, a girl best known for her energy.
My family life is…
Good morning.
Why were you rampaging in your room?
I wasn’t rampaging.
Even so the stomping was noisy.
I was just walking normally.
Just from you walking
it sounds like a monster is stomping.
I’m not a monster!
This bully is my big brother Touya.
He is a junior in high school.
He goes to Seijou High
which is right next to my school.
He’s always picking on me.
Just because he is a little taller.
I can’t stand it.
Someday
I’ll be as big as a utility pole…
I’ll stomp on him.
Getting along well as
always in the morning.
This is my father Fujitaka.
He is a college archaeology professor.
He is good at cooking and sewing.
I love him.
Here you go.
It looks delicious.
Thanks for the food.
This is my family.
What? My mother?
My mother passed away when
I was three years old.
But I’m not lonely.
I have my father,
and even though he is a bully
I have my brother.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Thanks.
You’re leaving already?
Morning practice for the soccer team.
See you later.
I’m off.
Wait a moment.
Thanks for breakfast.
Are you done already?
Here is your lunch.
Where is my brother?
He left earlier.
Geeze.
Do you have club today?
Yes!
see you later.
Take care.
I wonder how far he went.
Ah, there he is.
Wait a second!
I thought you could
leave a little later?
But…
But my brother always
goes to school with him.
Ah, Yuki.
Good morning.
Hey.
Good morning, Touya.
Good morning, Sakura.
You’re up early.
Yes.
It’s because she ate
breakfast in five minutes.
You’re cheerful as always today,
Sakura-chan.
This is Yukito Tsukishiro.
He is a junior in high school,
in the same class as my brother.
He is such a kind, wonderful person
I can’t believe he is friends
with this barbaric brother of mine.
See you later, Sakura-chan.
Here already?
See you later.
Yukito-san.
He’s good.
Tomoyo-chan.
To give you a present in a parting wave.
He’s smooth.
Good morning, Tomoyo-chan.
Good morning,
Sakura-chan.
This is Tomoyo Daidouji,
my best friend.
She is intelligent, beautiful,
and the daughter of the president
of a big company.
You were so cute just now.
What?
You were clutching the candy
looking enthralled.
Umm, Tomoyo-chan.
I wish
I could have taken a video
or picture of it.
Are you listening?
Tomoyo-chan’s hobby
is taking pictures or videos,
and she takes a lot of me.
Oh yeah!
I just bought a new video camera.
Please let me film you again.
OK,
but
shouldn’t you film something
more interesting than me?
There isn’t anything cuter
Or more interesting
than Sakura-chan.
I’ll bring the camera tomorrow.
I suppose Tomoyo-chan may be
a bit strange after all.
Opening the mouth into an O shape
a boy’s face became visible.
Surprised aren’t you?
I wonder if it is a magical tangerine?
I wonder if that was me.
What a cute picture, what is it?
Well then, Kinomoto.
Yes?
Please read on.
I’ll tell you later.
From line twenty.
I wonder if it is a magical tangerine?
After all a butterfly came from it.
Incredible.
That’s amazing Sakura-chan.
How cool!
Thank you Miss Kinomoto.
Next we will do toss practice.
Everybody get your baton ready.
OK!
That dream worries me after all.
I’ll talk to Tomoyo-chan about it later.
Yeah.
Sakura-chan is really athletic
and good with the baton…
But she gets like that sometimes too.
Yeah.
I’m home.
Ar?
I’ll be home at nine.
Dad is going to be late.
Ah…
Is somebody there?
Dad and my brother aren’t home now…
It’s coming from dad’s office.
What should I do? What if it is a thief?
I’ll peek in from the door.
If somebody is there I will call the police.
Oh…
Nobody here.
What?
Oh!
It’s that book.
Strange?
A card?
Win…
Umm…
Win… Windy.
What is this?
How ya doing?
Oh?
Thanks a lot for waking me up.
An Osaka accent?
This book was in Osaka for a long time
so the accent stuck.
Where are the batteries? The switch?
What are you doing?
Where is the voice coming from?
I’m not a toy!
I am the beast of the seal Cerberus,
who protects this book.
Cerberus?
Seal?
Yes!
To make sure that the cards in this book
don’t do bad things
is my mission…
There are no cards!
Why? Why? Where did they go?
This?
Ah, this. This. This is it.
So, where are the other cards?
I read the windy.
Ya.
All of a sudden a wind came.
Yeah, yeah.
They all flew away.
I see.
What?!
Thanks for dinner.
Where are you taking that?
I’m going it eat it in my room while studying.
Well?
No good.
I can’t tell at all where the cards are.
Here.
That looks good.
The Clow Cards were in this book.
Clow Cards?
The Clow Cards.
When their seal is broken
chaos will spread in the world.
Those cards are special cards
made by a great magician
Clow Leed.
Each one is alive
and holds incredible power.
They all act as they like,
And normal people can do nothing
against them.
It is because of that
Clow himself made the book
and put me as the beast of the seal
on the cover.
Anyways,
we need to get back the cards.
So, I’ll have you help me.
Eh? Why do I have to?
You’re the one who
scattered the cards
with the wind magic.
But it’s your job
to make sure these cards
are sealed in right?
Well I just fell asleep for a bit.
For how long?
About thirty years.
Even so you call yourself
the beast of the seal?
A lot of stuff happens in life.
All right!
So that sound was snoring?
Anyways, since you opened
this book
it means you have some degree
of magical power.
What is your name?
Sakura.
OK Sakura, stand over there.
Eh?
Yeah!
Key of the seal…
There is one who wishes
the contract with you here.
The girl by the name Sakura.
Key, give power to the girl.
Release!
Sakura, take the rod.
All right!
It’s the birth of a Card Captor.
What?!
Impossible! Impossible!
It’s absolutely,
absolutely impossible.
Ahh, how fluffy.
It’s impossible for me to be a Card Captor.
Card Captor.
Hunter of the Clow Cards.
Doesn’t it sound cool?
I’m an ordinary elementary school kid.
Even if you tell me about chaos in the world…
I wonder who it was who
scattered the cards everywhere with this?
Who was it that was sleeping
without guarding the cards?
What an incredible wind.
Sakura!
What’s that?
It’s a Clow Card.
Ah?
That looks like the Fly card.
This is no time to be impressed,
can’t you hurry?
And do what?
Card Captor Sakura’s first job.
What?
Why in my pajamas?
Is that what the only Card Captor
in the world would say?
Something that big is impossible.
You trying to be cute?
Sakura, magic!
Eh?
The key, use it like I showed you earlier.
Key which hides the powers of dark…
Show your true power before me.
Under the contract Sakura commands you.
Release!
Listen Sakura,
the Fly card originates from the wind,
you should be able to catch it
with the Windy you have now.
I wonder.
Anyways, if we don’t get a little closer…
What should I do? It came at us.
Sakura, the Windy card.
Oh, no. Here it comes again.
Hurry and use the Windy card.
But like this…
It’s impossible.
Isn’t it a Card Captor’s job
to do something about that?
Something?
There may be something I can do.
What are you planning?
Sakura.
Sakura!
Wind
Please become the chains that bind.
Windy.
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card.
You did great, Sakura.
I thought I would die.
Just what I would expect
from my chosen Card Captor.
I never said I would do it.
The more you experience in life
the better person you will become.
Well, you went through
all the trouble to capture it,
go ahead and hit it.
What can this do?
Well, just try it.
Fly.
Well? Feels pretty good right?
Yeah.
I’ll be counting on you from now on too,
Card Captor Sakura
Yeah.
Eh?
But I haven’t said I would do it.