Who is that?
Who are you?
[Sakura and the Shrine of Memories]
Who could that be?
Oh? It’s only this early?
Taking a walk in the morning once
in a while is kinda nice.
But it feels good to be in bed too.
I’ve had that dream
when I first met Kero.
I also had it when I met Li-kun.
And then… I met Miss Mizuki yesterday.
Miss Kaho Mizuki…
What a mysterious teacher.
You think so?
Eh!
I’m sorry. Did I scare you?
No, I mean… Um… Good morning!
Good morning.
You get up early, Kinomoto.
I got up a little early this morning,
so I’m talking a walk.
I’m cleaning the premise of the shrine.
I’m the only daughter, so I got to do it.
Somehow, when I see Miss Mizuki,
I feel so sweet.
I’ll help you.
But how about your walk?
It’s no big deal.
Can I help too?
Eh!
Yukito!
Can I dump this here?
Sure. Thanks.
I’m glad I got up early.
Be careful.
As I thought, that teacher
is more than just ordinary.
He told me to be careful…
But as I thought, when I see Miss Mizuki,
I feel so schweeet.
You guys were a great help.
Thanks a lot.
These are chestnuts from our shrine.
Are you sure we can have them?
Of course!
Thank you very much!
It’s about time to go.
Sakura, you’re going to school, right?
Yes!
How about we go together?
Okay!
I’ll go get my bicycle.
Yay! I get to go with Yukito!
Kinomoto…
Yes?
It’s nothing.
If it is you, I’m sure
you will notice it yourself.
Oh?
G’morning!
Tomoyo, g’morning!
Good morning!
When you are all cheerful in the
morning, it usually means…
…it is because of Tsukishiro, right?
It’s only half.
The other half is… this!
Which is…?
You know…
This morning, Miss Mizuki…
I told you to be careful
with that teacher!
Li-kun!
But!
Shao Lan!
I was putting on my shoes
and you just left without me!
Oh. The chestnuts look good.
Do you want some, Mei Lin?
I can show you how to open it too.
For chestnuts, you pull it open here…
Like this…
Cool!
Mei Lin, do you like chestnuts?
Oh? The math teacher, Miss Tsutsumi,
is on vacation.
They said she’s taking a long vacation.
The substitute teacher is…
…Miss Mizuki.
That Mizuki?
Father, you know Miss Mizuki?
Is that Mizuki
from Tsukimine Shrine?
Yes.
So she came back here.
Hey, how come you know her?
When Touya was in middle school,
Mizuki was a student teacher.
Then, Touya and Miss Mizuki
do know each other after all.
‘After all?’
Remember I was late yesterday
and Touya took me home?
And he saw Miss Mizuki
at Tsukimine Shrine then.
Father?
Did Touya say anything?
Nothing.
But when he saw Miss Mizuki,
he looked so surprised.
Are you sure you
really sensed a Clow Card?
It appeared just once and woke me up!
This can’t be wrong!
Tsukimine Shrine…
I can sense it coming out from here.
Are you sure? But here again?
The Maze card I captured
yesterday was from here, you know?
Is this where that mysterious teacher is?
Yeah.
What card is it, I wonder…
All I know is that
it’s a pretty powerful card.
Li-kun!
I know that,
since it could wake me up.
What?
Where’s Mei Lin?
I left her behind.
‘Coz she hasn’t finished her homework.
She’s still doin’ homework at this hour?
Mei Lin just transferred here,
and she isn’t familiar with Japanese!
She couldn’t help it, you know?
How about that girl
who always takes videos of yours?
It’s this late already,
I can’t just call her…
In any case…
The card is inside this shrine.
This is strange. We should’ve been able
to tell its location right away.
It sure is nearby.
We’ve been searching inside
the shrine for almost an hour.
I’m sure I felt it before,
but now I couldn’t sense a thing.
I’m thirsty.
I wonder if there’s a vending
machine somewhere.
I want something to drink too.
Buy one for Li-kun too, okay?
Oh well, if I remember.
What do you mean?!
That’s my wallet!
I wonder where the card is.
It should be nearby.
It probably knows we’re here,
so it’s hiding.
But if there’s really another card here,
then that makes it the second one.
That teacher was here, wasn’t she?
Ye… Yeah. I saw her this morning.
I helped her sweep
the place and she gave me chestnuts.
You really didn’t sense anything
about that teacher?
I felt so schweeet.
Schweeet?
In any case, you could sense
something else too, right?
Ye… Yeah.
I guess people with powers are drawn
towards other things with powers.
You mean, me?
Because you have powers, that’s why
you can capture the Clow Cards, right?
But when I’m with Miss Mizuki,
it doesn’t feel scary at all.
Instead, I feel really happy.
Scary things
don’t always come
with a scary face, you know?
But you know, if you
think someone is nice
or if you like someone,
It’s nothing you can do
about that feeling. I feel sweet
whenever I see Yukito too.
I feel that way too…
S… So, you do l… like him…
a…after all.
Yo… You lie…
u… Y…Yukito too?
Since when?
Since Yukito transferred
into Touya’s school…
The third semester of Touya’s
freshmen year high school.
He became friends with Touya
on the first day of his transfer
and came by our house.
It…
It might have been love at first sight.
What about you?
Since the day I transferred here.
Love at first sight after all?
But both of us are
so much younger than Yukito…
There’s nothing we can do about it.
Because we like him so much.
Wa… Wait a second, Li-kun!
They had the juice I like!
Sakura!
How did that happen?
She was sucked into the tree!
This is… The card, Return!
Huh? Why did I fall asleep at a place like this?
Um… I came to the shrine to
look for a Clow Card with Kero.
I saw Li-kun,
and we were talking here…
That’s right!
I got sucked in by the tree!
Huh? There’s nothing…
The cherry blossoms are falling…
Li-kun?
Not him! I gotta hide somewhere.
Oh! That’s right.
Jump!
Touya!
Maybe he’s coming back
from his part-time.
What should I do
if he sees me?
Huh? Why is he wearing
his middle school uniform?
You’ve come to protect us today.
Thank you.
Today?
Good evening.
Did you come to worship at this hour?
Miss Mizuki…
It came to protect us,
so I came to say hello.
You can tell something is
dwelling in this tree, can’t you?
You see a lot of them,
don’t you?
Isn’t it hard for you?
To be able to see something
others can’t see…
I’m used to it.
Would you tell me your name?
Touya Kinomoto.
What year?
Grade 8.
Wa… Wait a second,
he’s in 8th grade,
that means this was in the past?!
I’m Kaho Mizuki.
I’ll see you tomorrow again.
Eh!
What’s going on?!
Return is a card that
sends people back to the past.
But it takes a lot of magical power.
It’s rarely put in use.
But then why did it act all of a sudden?
Most likely, this tree
is closely related to this shrine
and has stored up lots of power.
It’s probably returning
her these powers.
Also, it’s impossible to go
back with just the will of one person…
Someone must have
be waiting underneath the tree.
Besides…
Today is full moon.
You’re the student teacher
for our class.
That’s why yesterday you said
you’d see me tomorrow again.
I only recognize the uniform.
I didn’t know who’s in my class yet.
Then how did you know?
I just do.
It’s like you can see things
that other people can’t,
it’s hard to explain, you know?
I guess so.
This was the past after all.
I’m sure we’ll become friends.
Do you just know so too?
No. I have faith in you.
Touya and Miss Mizuki
really did know each other.
What happens if it goes on like this?
Before the past which Sakura is in
catches up with the present,
it’ll only go on like this.
Isn’t there something we can do?
There is. But…
Study abroad?
When?
Tomorrow.
Why didn’t you tell me?
If I told you, it would
bother you, right?
Both you and I will feel sad.
It all began under this tree.
It’s almost been a year
since you said, ‘I love you.’
They’re so far away, I can’t hear them…
I was really happy,
because I loved you very much too.
We had a lot of fun together.
I had a really good time.
Why are you talking in past tense…
Let’s say good-bye.
Why…?
Because… Because when we meet again
You would already
have someone you care about.
Same for me, too.
It’ll be okay.
Because when we meet next time,
you and I would
have become great friends.
I will come back for sure.
When the time comes…
What a beautiful full moon.
When a disaster befalls upon this world…
Eh!
Miss Mizuki!
But… I’m sure…
Sakura!
Kero…
Thank goodness. You really came back.
How did I…?
You gotta thank the brat this time.
Eh?
Sakura, that’s the true form of the card!
Return to thy form which thou should be!
Clow Card!
You did come back…
Li-kun!
The card that took you away
was called Return.
For Return ,
in order to stop the flow
of time by using the card Time,
a seal has to be placed
on the entire tree.
But it takes a lot of magical power
to use the card Time .
On top of that,
to stop the flow of time
in the past with magical power…
Li-kun, I’m so sorry…
Thank you so much!
Li-kun? Hang in there! Li-kun!
Yue…