Weird…
I was pretty sure…
I felt Clow’s aura here.
It’s like as if
nothing ever happened.
Hey Sakura,
there’s nothing
around here at all.
It’s raining.
This isn’t going to do
much right now.
Shall we retreat for now?
Sakura and her friends
are going home.
Is that ok?
It would seem that
you have a plan.
[Sakura and Friends’ Big Trouble]
I’m soaking wet.
I’m transforming.
Wait Yue, let me go first.
It wouldn’t be good if Yukito
saw me like this.
Hurry up then.
Umm Yue-san.
– Please come in.
– I’m ok.
But, you’ll catch a cold…
I don’t catch colds.
– Ah, I feel Clow’s aura.
– No good!
I can’t transform!
What?
I can’t transform to Yukito.
Now what will you do,
Sakura-san?
Why don’t you fold your wings?
I’m totally soaked…
Don’t do that! Here…
What’s going on??
I felt Claw’s aura again
and then…
We can no longer transform.
What shall we do?
Hmm… I don’t know…
I can’t think of anything.
Me neither.
Why don’t we try it one more time?
I guess.
It… it is no good…
Now what
Now what… now what now what??
What was that noise?
No… Nothing…
It was me…
Now what… now what… haaaao.
Now what. Now what. Now what…
Now go to bed…
Since we can’t do much about it now,
anyway, shall we get some rest?
Maybe tomorrow morning,
you can transform back.
Yeah…
Yue-san, Please sleep on the bed.
No.
I’m fine.
– But…
– No problem.
How come you don’t ask me,
Sakura?
Huh?
But Kero-chan,
you are… well…
Goodnight.
I definitely
can’t think of Yukito-san
and Yue-san being the same person.
But,
if Yue-san can’t transform back,
then what happens to Yukito-san
Sakura-chan.
To make sure that doesn’t happen,
we have to think of something tomorrow.
Shall we try again?
It’s still not working.
What about Yue-san?
It really doesn’t work?
Sakura-san, breakfast is ready…
Yes… yes…
Just wait for me.
Thank you for the food.
It’s sunday… I’m sorry.
No, that’s fine…
Well then, I’ll be back…
See you then.
– I’m leaving too…
– See you when you get back…
But what can we do to
bring Kero-chan and Yue-san back?
Stop eating snacks
so mindlessly
and think of what we can do.
Even if we are in a hurry,
it won’t do anything
Oh yeah, tonight is
your turn to cook dinner, right?
Don’t you have
a lot of things to do?
But…
Then should we not think about
this after you finish your chores?
If you don’t do them,
your big brother will nag at you.
I don’t know how to say.
I guess so,
ok let’s finish them.
Help me, Kero.
Huh? Why me?
Doing things
together will finish sooner.
Otherwise,
my big brother will be back.
I can’t handle delicate objects
with hands like this, in this form.
Would you please?
Ok,
then ask Yue too!
It is unfair
to just ask me.
Ok! Yue-san,
please take a rest here.
Ahhh! Why are you saying that!?
Why do I have to help you day after day?
Things you won’t make Yue do,
I won’t do either.
It would be better
to ask for Yue’s help too.
Rice washing Yue,
bathtub cleaning Yue,
laudry laying Yue, dusting Yue!
I think you should help out
with household chores too.
Hrm? I’m ok.
Since I’m cute!
Coming!
Kinomoto-san, package.
Do you have a stamp?
Ah, please wait a moment.
Here you go!
Here…
It will go bad,
so put it in the fridge.
Ok. Understand.
Keep up the good work.
Thank you.
What were you thinking?
I had something to ask you…
Dumping this I guess…
It is difficult to hold it.
I started the laundry.
Well done.
Why aren’t you making
Yue do anything?
Clow and you
both treat Yue too nice…
Take this…
No! Don’t do it!!!
Hrm, how can we get you cleaned up?
Do you have the Bubble card?
– Yeah.
– Use that card on me…
– Is that ok?
– But
since you shouldn’t overdo it,
make sure you wish sincerely
that you want
to clean me before using it.
I get it.
RELEASE!
Kero, here we go…
Go.
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
Bubble!
I didn’t know
I can use the Bubble card to do this…
Clow used to wash me like this often.
Then Clow-san made
this card for you, Kero?
That’s not it…
Clow used to use bubble
to wash me,
but also to wash his clothes.
Really?
Yeah, he was weird.
Also, he shut his sensitive sides away.
Then, I’m going over there to clean up.
Ahh, yes. Back then…
and then… and then…
was like this…
damn it…
Haaoo, what happened to the floor?
Yue-san, you cleaned it?
Thank you.
What about Kerberos?
In the washroom,
I just gave them a bath with Bubble.
Ah, Clow-san used
to wash Kero with bubble too, right?
How did you know?
Kero told me.
Yue-san…
You really care for Kero, don’t you?
Even now…
What make you think that?
Because,
you have this kind look
when talking about Kero.
My dad told me…
because he still loves my mom so much.
Even if he was to reborn,
he will end up loving her again.
You just seemed
Like my dad
when he talks like that
so I was just curious…
Ah, I’m sorry for
saying weird things all of a sudden.
We gotta hurry up and finish cleaning
and get you guys back
to your original forms…
Waaa! It is crab!!
A crab?
Its shell…
Protecting the insides.
Protect.
That is it.
Ahh!! That was a good bath,
I feel so refreshed…
I have an idea,
Kero.
Menu for dinner?
Not that,
just come with me.
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
Shield!
Shield, huh.
Try transforming now.
Right.
It worked!
I thought about Shield since
it is able to block off
magic and attacks.
Yue-san, please give it a try.
It worked!
Huh? Why am I over at Sakura’s house?
It’s already over. That wasn’t so fun.
So you decided to use the Shield card.
You are a careful person.
Shield is used
to protect valuable objects.
If the user’s will to
protect that object is stronger,
then the stronger the power of Shield.
It surely is,
Sakura…
I’m sorry,
I feel as if I’ve suddenly
barged in and burdened you.
It’s nothing.
Crab-goroke?
Well, it tastes so formal.
What did you say?
Touya! Sakura, it is really good.
Really?
Yes.
That’s good.
But it’s really a good thing
that you can return back, Yukito…
Hey, Sakura!
You haven’t eaten anything.
Shall we see test your
food for poison?
That’s not it.
Yuki, have some antidote
before you leave.
I said that’s not it…
It’s quite tiring to stay
large like that.
But stopping us
from returning to
our alternate forms.
It must be Clow.
What’s going on?