Today is the Tomoeda school athletic meet
There are kids
who seem to hate the athletic meet
because it is a pain
But I love it
[Sakura and the flowery athletic meet]
Sakura-chan, you really are fast
Thanks Rika-chan
Yukito-san!
You really are a fast runner
It’s because she has no other merits
This is lunch? It’s huge
I made it along with Touya
Dad says he’ll come right after his seminar
at the college
There is no helping it if he has work
My dad teaches archaeology at a college
He doesn’t just lecture.
He goes to excavations
and holds research seminars,
so he is very busy
In the afternoon there is a 100 meter
race for parents to participate in
It would be nice if
he made it for that
Yes
Members of the cheer leading club
please gather at the entrance to the grounds
Ah, it’s Tomoyo-chan’s voice
I repeat,
members of the cheer leading club
gather at the entrance to the grounds
Are you in that too?
Yes
I’ll take lots of photos
Take a picture of Yukito-san afterwards
Make sure to do it
Yeah, yeah
That 4th grader Kinomoto is a fast runner
Nobody can seem to beat her
Sakura-chan isn’t just a fast runner.
She is also very cute
Tomoyo-chan!
Sakura-chan!
Is that your outfit for this event?
Yeah
It’s wonderful
But if it had frills at the neck
and a big ribbon.
Your mom isn’t here yet?
She had a company meeting
and said she would rush here right after
Tomoyo-chan’s mother is the president
of a big toy company
Tomoyo-chan’s mother is really busy,
and there are days when
she can’t see her daughter
I also haven’t met Tomoyo-chan’s mother
So I’m looking forward to it
Now that I think about it,
Tomoyo-chan never talks
about her father
I have to go, please watch
I’ll be cheering for you from here
She really is cute
Yes.
You’re right
Well then, all set!
I must capture Sakura-chan’s exploits
on video!
Sakura-chan has gotten good
Well, if you compare her to before
When she joined the club
every time she threw the baton
she would catch it with her head
See
Next is the last morning event
The fourth grade obstacle course
Everybody please cheer
for the competitors
as they pass many barriers
Sakura-chan, good luck!
Sakura-chan!
Good luck!
Take your places
I won’t lose
Me too
Ready!
It’s down to just Sakura-chan and Lee-kun
Go for it!
Alright!
Your mom isn’t here yet?
Yeah, but I think she’ll be here soon
Then have lunch with us
May I? I’d be intruding on your family
Of course you can. The food would taste better
if we all ate together.
Thank you
Lee-kun
Do you want to have lunch with us too?
Why with you?
Sakura-chan!
We’re ready with lunch
OK!
I’ll eat with you
Eh?
Here, the egg is delicious
Your brother
and Tsukishiro-san made it?
It looks really good
Strange?
Ah, I’m sorry I was eating everything
No, it’s good to eat a lot
The lunch was just so good
When your food tastes good,
that is proof of good health
That’s right
Thanks for the food
Sorry I’m late
Dad!
Ah, I missed the cheerleading
club’s performance
I took a video of it
I also took a lot of pictures
Thank you
Sorry, Sakura
No, I am happy you ran to get here
I made these yesterday
I cooled them with the university refrigerator
It should be cold
Say, do we have some of this gelatin left?
There is some in the refrigerator at home
I’ll let Kero-chan have some when we get home
I’ll go throw away the trash
I’ll go too
Me too
Lee-kun missed out on the delicious gelatin
Tomoyo
Mother
What a beautiful person
Sakura-chan, let me introduce you
This is my mom
Eh!
I’m sorry, I’m Sonomi Daidouji
Thank you for always being
friends with Tomoyo
Not at all, she is always helping me out
You really are cute
You look a lot like a girl I once knew
I have heard a lot about from Tomoyo,
but I haven’t heard your last name.
Can you tell me?
Umm, it’s Kino
Sakura
Dad
Kinomoto-sensei!
Sonomi-kun
I never noticed because
the last name was different
When you were a student
it was Sonomi Amamiya
Sakura I should have known from the name
Nadeshiko said
she would give that name if she had a girl
I absolutely won’t forgive you
At that time Nadeshiko
was still a high school student,
and I had just become a teacher
Yes!
Even as a trusted teacher
you married a student,
and my precious Nadeshiko
Excuse me
I was looking over Nadeshiko
ever since kindergarten
So that she wouldn’t
attract any idiotic bugs
Even so,
for her to attract
such a dim witted bug
How can you be so cheerful
when you let Nadeshiko
die at only 27 years old
Because I promised not to cry
To Nadeshiko
Nevertheless, I won’t forgive you
Dad and Tomoyo’s mom knew each other
Parents participating in the 100 meter race
please gather at the grounds entrance
Sorry to keep you waiting
Dad,
you are taking part in the
100 meter race right?
Shall I go instead?
It’s OK.
I was ordered to take part by Sonomi-san
Where is the grounds entrance?
Over here
Should I ask the reason?
Or am I better off not knowing?
Sonomi
used to be Sonomi Amamiya
Huh?
Amamiya is your mother’s maiden name
Yes,
she was Sonomi’s cousin
My mom was the lone daughter
of a famous company president
Dad had just become a teacher
Even though they knew it would be tough,
my mother got married when she was sixteen
She worked as a model while going to school
That wasn’t the reason she got ill,
but there were various issues
with my mom’s parents
Sonomi cared a lot for my mom
since they were little,
and I heard she was the person
most against her marrying my dad
But in the pictures of
Nadeshiko at your place,
even the ones not from magazines,
she always looked happy
Even so, there are a lot of
flowers out today
My mom and your dad seem to
have known each other
Yeah
Huh, Tomoyo-chan
What? Mother?
Was your mother planning on participating?
No
Is your mom a fast runner?
I think when she was in high school
she was on the national team
Eh!
I absolutely won’t lose
Ready!
Good luck! Good luck!
Eh!
Your dad is amazing
He is fast
The most athletic one in our family
is our dad
Where are these flowers blowing in from?
We can’t see anything like this
Could it be a Clow Card?
It’s a Clow Card
Lee-kun, where are you going?
Where? Something terrible is happening
Really
It is in times like this we must remain calm
We have to take care of
first aid in the afternoon
Hey, wait!
Oh no you don’t We have to be ready
to help somebody if they get hurt
Let go! The Clow Card
They’re running
Mother hates to lose
I can’t move
We’ll drown in flowers
Are you going to use magic here?
Nobody is looking
Key which hides the power of darkness
Display your true form before me
Under the contract, I Sakura command you
Release!
Fly
I wonder if it really
is the work of a Clow Card
It is best to ask an expert
in times like this
Where were you carrying that?
Right now! Cerberus super special!
My sure kill technique!
What is it? I am sunk into sadness now
Kero-chan, big trouble!
No mistake, that is
the work of a Clow Card
So it is The school
is full of flowers already
For the time being, check out carefully
where the flowers are flying from
Eh!
Over there
I absolutely won’t lose
Somebody
help me!
I’ll be buried
Hurry and move to a higher place
We’ll hold this
Over there
Sakura-chan
You’re a Clow Card right?
Eh?
How are thing going over there?
This has gotten serious
Sakura-chan was suddenly invited to dance
It is a girl with curly hair right?
Yes
No problem, she loves fun things
What’s going on?
Sakura-chan, if you don’t hurry
and stop the flowers,
the school will be buried
Return to your rightful form
Flower?
Yep, it’s the Flower card
Your school was having
an athletic meet wasn’t it?
Flower gets happy when there is
fun or celebrations going on
Huh?
She was probably thinking
to add to things with flowers
So what can this card do?
It can put forth various types of flowers
That’s it?
Well, you got away without
any danger this time didn’t you?
We were almost suffocated by flower petals
Oh!
What’s wrong?
I forgot to take a video
Congratulations
What, Tsukishiro-kun and Touya?
With this much we could
make a lot of tea
Why do I have to clean after
coming to an athletic meet?
I hate this I hate this I hate this
It has been like this ever since high school
Because I didn’t want to let you have Nadeshiko
I challenged you countless times
But I always lose
It would be rude to you
if I lost on purpose
Because I knew
how much you cared for Nadeshiko
So I always tried my hardest
I remember it even now,
the house you moved into with her
Living together in that tiny apartment
Going to school with her even
though you were a new teacher
You made Nadeshiko’s lunch every day
didn’t you?
Both of you with the same lunch,
and then going home holding hands
It looks like they are
quarrelling over something
Sakura-chan
But
It’s OK
Flower. Bestow flowers upon those two
Why are you good at cooking anyway?
A nadeshiko flower
Nadeshiko was always entwined
with you With a smile
Even though I was really angry
she would just break down my anger
With her light attitude
She was spontaneous from the core
She certainly was a wholehearted person
I loved Nadeshiko the most
Nadeshiko loved you too
But
Nadeshiko seemed so happy
Ever since she married you
She smiled with
Her best face ever
How could she leave so soon
when she was so happy
I’m sorry
Why do you apologize?
I took all the time with Nadeshiko
from when she was 16 until 27 she was
That is what I hate about you
It must have been my mother
who was the girl I resemble
My mom often talked about
her cousin named Nadeshiko
It was because she wanted to have
it the same as Nadeshiko’s that
my hair was grown out like this
I guess lots of things have
happened to our parents
I wonder if he will tell me
about it sometime
Yes, I’m sure he will
But it seems your mom
She really loved my mom
Oh, but I love you too
Me too
Hey! It’s just about time
for the closing ceremony
OK!
Let’s go, Tomoyo-chan
Yes