Hey, have you heard?
There’s a Quiz Competition coming up.
Is that the one this Sunday?
Yeah!
You can only enter in pairs, right?
Oh, you’re going to
enter with Yamazaki, then?
Umm…
He keeps joking with his lies,
but it seems he’s good at quizzes.
How about you, Sakura?
Eh?
Quiz Competition, huh?
I don’t have cleaning
duty next Sunday…
Maybe I should ask Tomoyo.
I’m looking forward to it!
[Sakura and Yukito
and the Midday Moon]
Tomoeda Town Quiz Rally
Sakura? What’s wrong?
It’s this, right?
Tomoeda Town Quiz Rally.
Sounds fun,
doesn’t it?
It’s some kind
of trivia thing?
Let’s see…
This year’s Quiz Competition…
…is meant to encourage a greater
understanding of Tomoeda.
There will be a number
of questions each leading
To a hidden location.
We will present a magnificent trophy
to the champion.
A trophy!
Wah!
To promote teamwork,
we will only accept teams of two.
So you’re going with Yamazaki, right?
I’m a little worried, but…
Sakura, are you entering?
I’ll go root for you!
Me, too!
OK!
Tomoyo, wanna enter together?
I’d be delighted!
But
if I’m a contestant,
I won’t be able
to capture it on video.
To get nice shots of Sakura…
That’s my goal!
How about entering with me?
Eh?
Yukito!
You mean it?!
Isn’t that great, Sakura?
The Tomoeda Town Quiz Competition, huh?
Sounds like fun.
Yep!
I’m going to enter with Yukito.
What about you, Touya?
Part-time job.
We’ll win and bring back
the magnificent trophy!
I’ll be looking forward to it.
But don’t get hurt trying too hard.
OK!
Finished.
Oh, thanks!
I’ll wear this tomorrow!
That was worth three cleaning duties.
My power hasn’t returned…
Umm…
Good morning!
Good morning, Sakura.
Morning, Kinomoto.
One two… one two…
Mei Lin, Li…
Shao Lan and I are going to win
this tournament!
That magnificent trophy will be ours!
Where’re you going, Shao Lan?
Why do I have to be in this?
Good morning!
Yukito!
Sorry.
I was at a nearby shop,
and breakfast took longer
than I thought…
Let’s do our best today, all right?
Okay!
I’ll go get the booklet.
Me, too.
Wait here, Shao Lan.
Hey.
You’re entering with “him?
Yes.
You’re in this, too?
Let’s do our best, all right?
Oh!
Hey, where’re you going, Shao Lan?
No, it’s just that…
I can’t tolerate that…
I told you I’d be right back…
Good luck!
Everyone, good luck!
All preparations are complete.
Good morning, everyone!
Please have lots of fun here
in the Tomoeda Town
shopping district all day today.
And remember,
we have a magnificent trophy
for the winner.
It’s all mine.
And for all the participants,
we have thank you gifts…
…from the members
of the shopping district
Chamber of Commerce.
Now, to explain the rules.
First, there’s only
one quiz to solve at a time.
If you solve that,
you will receive a piece of paper
with the next goal.
That paper will lead to another quiz,
and if you solve that…
you’ll find out the next goal.
There are 10 quizzes at all.
As you pass each one,
you will get a stamp
in the booklet
that you’ve all been given.
If you get all the stamps,
you will get the paper
with the final goal.
There,
It looks like this.
A relief with
Tomoeda Town’s flower,
the Nadeshiko, on it.
When you find this,
bring it back here.
If you find and bring
back the relief by chance,
it doesn’t count.
There are plenty
of relief to go around.
No matter who finds them,
that’s the goal.
The reliefs are in all kinds of places.
They might be
in hard-to-find places,
so everyone, good luck!
Sounds hard.
We’ll be fine.
If we don’t even try the quiz,
we can’t advance.
Age doesn’t seem to matter.
I guess so.
Oh, and speaking of quizzes…
The very first quiz was made
by a Greek philosopher, you know?
In morning, I have four legs.
During the day, I have two legs.
And at night I have three legs.
What am I?
That was the world’s first quiz.
Yeah, yeah.
And the one who took
that first quiz was…
Yamazaki,
the answer to that quiz…
Eh?
A human.
When you’re a baby you crawl,
then you walk on two legs…
…and finally,
you use a cane to help you walk.
I see.
So, the first question.
Using 10 matches, we’ve made a star.
Using these same 10 matches,
make a different star.
Oh! I don’t know.
So if you know the answer,
go to that booth
and demonstrate it.
If you get it right,
we’ll give you
the paper for the next goal.
I don’t get it.
All right, let’s go.
Eh…
Do you know it?
I sure hope so.
Eh?
Brother!
But… weren’t you…
Part-time job.
That’s it.
Here.
Here!
Later, Touya.
We’re off!
Don’t make a mistake by hurrying.
We’ll be fine.
Cause I’m with Yukito.
Hey, hey!
I got it!
There!
The matches are
like stars in the sky!
That’s not it.
Why?!
Sakura, you’re fast.
Your store is the next goal?
So here’s the question:
In order to make water into ice,
you have to put it in the freezer…
…and wait for a while, right?
But there’s a way
to turn ice back into water instantly.
So how would you go about doing that?
Umm…
How about putting it in a volcano?
Wouldn’t that take some time?
Then, then…
Putting it in the sun?
That’s not it.
Eh?
Let me try something.
[KOORI]
Here’s ice…
Eh?
[MIZU]
Water.
That’s it.
That’s amazing!
It’s a field of stars!
That’s not it.
Why?!
Looks like we’ve got just one more.
Right!
You got it.
Yamazaki, you’re great!
The answer was pretty obvious.
You like these kinds of puzzles,
don’t you?
Yeah, I like it more
when the answers
just come to me like that.
What’s that about?
Chiharu.
Sakura.
Miss Mizuki, what’s going on?
There are a lot of Tomoeda
Elementary students participating,
so I’m helping out.
Hey, Chiharu,
how many stamps do you have?
Take a look. We’ve got all of them!
Looks like Yamazaki’s
team is the leader.
That’s great!
Kinomoto, how many do you have?
Right now, nine.
So then this is the last one.
Good luck.
Thanks!
See ya!
OK, good luck!
So, here’s the last problem.
Without putting your hand inside,
without tipping the beaker over… and
only using what’s on this table,
please get the ball out.
now, the two of you do
“rock-paper-scissors.
Eh?
Jan-ken-pon!
Aiko-de-sho!
This problem will be
solved by the winner.
Don’t worry.
If you think it over carefully,
I’m sure you’ll figure it out.
OK!
Um…
You are…
I’m Tsukishiro Yukito.
You helped us out with cleaning before,
right?
Yes.
How long have you lived in Tomoeda?
Since my first year of high school.
You live with your grandfather
and grandmother, right?
I love travel pretty much,
but they’re hardly ever home.
I see.
Yukito, you…
Yes?
I got it!
Here, I’ve got the ball!
Yes, that’s it.
I did it! Yay! Yay!
That’s great, Sakura!
Stamp, please.
Here you go.
Thank you very much!
Good luck.
Thanks!
All right, let’s go.
The last goal is…
Kinomoto?
Eh?
Be careful.
Because there’s a full moon today.
Sakura, fight!
Sakura?
I’m going for it!
The last goal is in Penguin Park.
The relief is there.
We’re off!
Later!
Let’s go.
There’s a place like this around here?
I didn’t know,
since this isn’t near
one of the playground areas…
It says the relief should be
right around here, but…
The moon.
Oh yeah, I guess you can still
see the moon during the day.
How pretty…
Be careful.
Because there’s a full moon today.
Sakura!
Sakura…
Eh!
Yukito!
Are you alright?
Does it hurt anywhere?
No…
Good.
Your leg…
Yukito,
I’m so sorry.
You’re hurt, aren’t you?
It’s because I spaced out…
I’m sorry…
It’s OK.
It’s fun just being with you.
Feel better?
Yes!
Oh yeah.
Actually, I fell on this.
Look.
Woo…
I wonder if everyone
else found their goal.
Well,
let’s do our best until the end.
Doing it like this… No!
This one for sure!
We’ve looked everywhere.
I see…
Sakura…
And they were just
behind Yamazaki and Chiharu.
And we got these amusement
park tickets, too…
I wonder where they went…?
They’re still not back?
Going to look for them?
Yeah.
I’m going, too.
Sakura!
Eh?
Where, where?
What were you doing?
Yukito got hurt,
and it was my fault…
eh!
I’m OK!
No you aren’t.
How about you?
Are you alright?
I’m fine,
because Yukito saved me.
Oh, man.
Sakura!
Alright
Are you OK?
I’m fine.
You waited for me.
Sorry about that.
Sakura.
Eh?
Your prize.
Wah…
This is perfect!
I needed one of these!
We got the same thing.
Yukito…