Ah! It’s pudding!!!!!
Since no one’s home,
Sakura’s left me
lots and LOTS of goodies to eat!
ALL MINE!!!
Mmmm…! So cold, so good.
This is the life!
I guess now Sakura should be enjoying
in the snow as white as this pudding.
Wow!
[Sakura and the
Snow Blowing Ski Class]
Let’s go! Next.
Good luck, Sakura-chan!
Tomoyo-chan!
That was great, Sakura-chan!
It’s not that great.
I just can move without falling.
But, you’re really good
Tomoyo-chan!
You’re good at both ice-skating
and skiing!
My mother’s had me in lessons
ever since I was little.
This is your first time, isn’t it?
Yes.
And you’re doing so
well after only an hour…
That is soo great!
Isn’t that Eriol-kun?
Amazing!!
Wow! You’re amazing, Eriol-kun!
Thank you very much!
You really can do everything,
can’t you?
You can even ski.
It’s not that hard.
You’re doing well, too, Sakura.
About skiing…
In ancient times,
they used to ski in sandals.
Sandals?
But, it must have been
very difficult to glide in sandals.
Even so, they managed it.
Right, Hiiragizawa-kun?
Yes. And they were a meter long too.
Wow! They had special
skiing sandals back then?
That’s not quite right.
They would load their baggage
on the extra length.
And if there was no snow…
They would be in big trouble…
So, they would do most of their
transporting while running very fast.
And they would have contests to see
who could run fastest in their sandals.
And so in the winter,
The sport of skiing was developed.
Isn’t that right?
That’s right.
Hoee!!
With Hiiragizawa-kun in on it,
I can’t be sure whether they’re
telling the truth or not…
At least the two of them
are enjoying themselves.
Of course, monkeys are best…
Shao Lan-kun!
Watch out!
Get out of the way!!!
He’s going to hit the tree!
Shao Lan-kun!
Are you alright?
Hiiragizawa…
You still have some things to learn,
don’t you…?
But I’m sure you’ll manage.
Skiing… and everything else.
You’ve said that before.
What do you mean?
Shao Lan-kun! Hoe!
Are you ok?
I’m fine.
What about you?
I… I’m ok.
I’m glad!
Skiing is fun, isn’t it?
Yes, you’ve improved a lot since
this morning, Sakura-chan.
You’re doing really well
for your first time, too, Naoko-chan!
Yamazaki-kun was helping me.
Does everyone know?
About skiing…
Give it a rest.
Is it really ok for you to spend
your free-time helping me?
It’s alright.
I like doing this.
Thank you.
Hey, Tomoyo-chan.
Shouldn’t we go help Rika-chan?
I think the two of them are
alright on their own.
I just remembered…
About snowy mountains…
Aren’t they spooky?
Do you know a ghost story
about these mountains?
No, I don’t.
Does anyone else have a story?
About a spooky ski resort?
About ski resorts…
Not lies… ghost stories.
Hiiragizawa-kun, do you know any?
Ghost stories?
I’ve heard there are
lots of ghosts in England.
Can you tell us a story?
Let me think…
Please don’t…
I think I remember one.
Alright!
Deep in the oldest mountains,
or so I’ve heard it told,
When the sky is darkened
with storm clouds,
A cold wind blows down
from the highest peaks.
Then, the snow rises up to blind you…
and Yuki-onna appears.
Yuki-onna is the wandering spirit
who comforts the souls of those
who freeze to death.
Isn’t that a Japanese story?
Yes, it is.
Why not tell one from England?
I thought this one would be better.
Hoe…!
Bu… but we don’t have to worry about
that here, do we?
One can never be sure.
It’s getting late.
Shouldn’t we turn in?
You’re right. It is late.
Well then, time to hit the sack.
Quite true.
Thank you, Hiiragizawa-kun.
It was nothing.
Please tell some more later!
Ok. I will.
Yuki-onna…
It would be wonderful to meet her.
I don’t want to.
She must be very beautiful.
I still don’t want to.
The story wasn’t really
very scary, though…
It was scary enough.
Do you not like scary stories,
Sakura-san?
You should have said something, then…
But Naoko-chan likes them so much…
Aren’t you afraid of anything,
Eriol-kun?
I am.
What?
It’s a secret.
Sakura-chan…
I can’t sleep…
Yuki-onna…
It’s very cold.
Shao Lan-kun!
Sakura…
What is it?
What?
I heard you call my name…
Oh, yeah…
Thank you for what you did today.
I was scared, so you pointed out
that it was time to sleep.
It was nothing.
You always say that.
But it’s not true.
Is that you really mean this?
What makes you say that?
I know you.
You’re a really nice guy.
What’s that supposed to mean?
It’s snowing!
Let’s go outside for a bit!
Ok.
Wow! Pretty!
Ooh. Cold.
That’s cute.
Look, Shao Lan-kun!
Isn’t it cute?
Oh, yeah. You made a stuffed bear,
too, didn’t you?
Have you given it away yet?
No… Not yet.
Yukito-san will be glad to get it.
No.
It’s not for him.
I was only attracted by his magic.
It’s someone else that I care for…
Who?
The person I really care about is…
I love…
I’m sorry!
I shouldn’t force you to tell.
I’m sorry.
We should go inside. We’ll catch a cold
if we stay out too long.
Ok.
Wow!
You’re doing good!
Ok. That was good.
You’ve really improved.
Next! Li!
Alright. You’ve improved, as well, Li.
Ok. From now on is free time.
Do what you want until noon.
Ok!
Kinomoto and Li,
you should be ready for
a higher-level slope.
Ok!
Alright, take care!
What do you think, Shao Lan-kun?
Shall we go further up?
No.
What was that about?
Li-kun is doing well.
He has improved much for one day.
He’s good at sports, isn’t he?
I think there’s more
to it than that.
Oh, snow!
It’s really coming down, isn’t it?
Yes.
Would it be better to stop for a rest?
I’d like to keep going.
I thought I’d try the next-level hill.
Will you come with me,
Tomoyo-chan?
I’ll wait at the bottom…
And film your triumphant finish!
Sakura-chan defeats
the Snow-covered Mountain!
How about you, Eriol-kun?
Is it ok for me to go with you?
Of course!
It’s really coming down now…
That’s true…
When the sky is darkened
with storm clouds,
a cold wind blows down
from the highest peaks.
Then, the snow rises up to blind you…
and Yuki-onna apears.
It seems a blizzard is on the way.
We should find shelter,
once we get off the lift.
It’ll be dangerous to ski…
We won’t be able to see much.
Hurry! Everyone,
get inside the restaurant! Hurry!
It reminds me of Hiiragizawa-kun’s
story, yesterday.
It does, doesn’t it?
Has anyone seen Sakura-chan
or Hiiragizawa-kun?
They don’t seem to have come in, yet.
Is something wrong?
They must still be up there!
What?!
No one’s there, and the door is locked.
Are you alright?
Yeah.
It’s gotten so dark…
and the snow’s too thick.
It’s almost blinding…
Yuki-onna…
HOE!!!!! No!!! Stay away from me!!!
I’m sorry.
I meant to say that it looks
like the weather in my story…
Oh…
I’m sorry. I didn’t think
my story would frighten you so much.
Perhaps I shouldn’t have told it.
It’s ok. I always over-react…
Don’t worry.
What?
An avalanche?
Hurry! We have to run!
But…
At this rate…
Everyone below will be
buried in the snow.
I have to do something.
But, Eriol-kun is watching me.
I could use Sleep…
No! He could be hurt while I was busy.
And, if I run away…
he’ll worry about me…
I’ll have to use that card!
Sakura-san!
Wait for just a minute, Eriol-kun!
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
TIME!
It takes a lot of
my strength to stop time…
I have to hurry!
Fi… ire… ry
I wonder if they’re ok?
I’ll go look for them.
Everyone else, wait here.
Sakura-chan!
Hiiragizawa-kun is with her, too!
Are you ok?
Yeaaaah…
What happened??
Sakura-chan!
She seems to have tired herself out.
We should let her rest.
Yeah.
What I’m afraid of is
causing you pain…
But it seems I can’t help that, can I?