It’s no good, I can’t get close.
Show it your perseverance.
Yes…
Eh!
Li-kun.
That’s dangerous, stop it.
Eh!
Li-kun!
Didn’t I tell him?
Come forth lightning, obey the command!
Now, Sakura!
Yeah.
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card.
Oh!
The card chooses the one
who sealed it’s power as its owner.
It’s hard to take,
but he did more this time.
It is impossible after all.
Eh?
It is impossible for you
to gather cards.
You have too little power.
What was that brat?
That was too bad, Sakura-chan.
Yeah, there is no helping it.
She is hiding her distress inside.
Umm…
[Sakura and Kero’s big fight]
Nothing good at all happened today.
Kero-chan, I wonder if it really
is impossible for me.
Kero-chan,
are you listening?
Hey, Kero-chan.
Kero-chan!
Why are you screaming,
after I was thinking of
a way to win against that brat.
Eh? That is what you were doing?
Sorry.
So, that way is?
Way?
I forgot it.
Geeze, and I was expecting something.
I really had thought of something,
but your idiotic voice
made me forget it.
I didn’t have any idiotic voice.
No, you did.
You’re wrong.
You did!
Huh!
I need a place
where I can relax and think
without being interrupted by Sakura.
I didn’t interrupt.
You did!
I didn’t.
If I said you did, you did.
I don’t care any more.
Good night.
Huh!
Just when I was about
to have a good idea.
Sakura, you moron.
I feel better after sleeping.
I’m not angry anymore,
come out Kero-chan.
Eh!
Kero-chan?
Where are you?
I’m in here.
Are you OK?
What are you doing in there?
How do you like it? I made it
last night after thinking it up.
Pretty good for being made in one night?
Now if I only had something for a sofa
or a nice table.
This is…
Where are the contents of the drawer?
Ah that stuff?
Over there.
Eh!
What are you doing?
Geeze,
you messed up the drawer.
My room that I went through
all that trouble to make!
It’s too cruel!
You are the one who was cruel.
Beast!
What was that?
If you aren’t a beast,
you are a monster!
What did you say?
I called you a monster
because you destroyed my room.
Monster Sakura!
Monster!
Geeze.
You seem one level
more the monster today.
Monster.
So that is why you have been
in a cross mood all morning.
I had to clean up after it all.
There were important things
in there too.
There was a letter
I got from you in there too.
Oh?
Damn it,
I can’t calm down.
Geeze.
Eh!
A gift from somebody?
I wonder if it is something to eat.
No.
Sakura will get mad at me.
No, I am angry too!
What is this?
It’s chocolate!
This is good!
I understand Kero-chan wanting
some privacy, but…
I am sure he didn’t intend anything bad.
But
then Kero-chan called me a monster.
Monster Sakura.
My, I would love a monster
that was cute like Sakura-chan.
Eh!
This chocolate really is good.
Great!
Kero-chan must have done this,
to make such a mess eating.
Isn’t this chocolate
with alcohol in it?
Geeze, he ate them all.
Eh!
Thanks for dinner.
Ah, Sakura,
have you seen a package
I left out?
It had chocolate in it.
Chocolate?
Yes, chocolate.
Well I am going to sleep,
good night.
Geeze, Kero-chan…
Where did he go?
You see?
I am really Cerberus,
I was protecting
that book the whole time.
In rain or wind.
Lots of terrible things happened.
You’re the only one
to listen to my story.
I feel kinda sleepy.
Do you know someplace
I could sleep?
Over there?
Oh, it’s a bed.
This is good.
Thank you.
Eh!
Sakura, you moron.
Where is this?
Are you awake?
Who is that?
I brought breakfast.
What is your name?
What?
Here.
Do you not like milk?
You’re a cat aren’t you?
No I’m not.
Oh, it’s over.
Oh no, I spoke.
You have an interesting meow.
Your name is Chau-chan right?
No.
It is Chau-chan!
Can you help me a bit?
OK, Mama!
Wait a bit, OK Chau-chan?
Chau? It’s not Chau.
No, no.
I left the window open all night
so he could come home any time.
Kero-chan is so obstinate.
Where did he go?
Hmm?
No, it’s nothing.
Huh?
I said it’s nothing.
I see.
I’m leaving.
I was thirsty
so this milk tastes good.
Well then, I am heading out.
See you later!
Chau-chan, did you eat it up?
That’s good.
Good boy.
Mama went out to work,
so it is up to Akane and
Chau-chan to look after things.
So this kid’s name is Akane?
Such a small kid
has to stay home alone?
Chau-chan,
your face looks a little dirty.
Stay still,
I’ll make you clean.
Isn’t this cold water?
Wash me with warm water.
There, all done.
Oh yeah! I’ll put on a ribbon too.
Where is this?
If I don’t do something in a hurry…
That is my Papa who is in heaven.
My dad went to a place
called heaven they say.
That is why
I have to watch over the house.
You’ll help me look over
the house too, right?
I got it!
Ah, Mama?
Yeah this is Akane.
Yeah. Yeah. I understand.
Good luck at work.
Yeah. Bye, bye.
Kumiko!
Papa?
You were alive?
Kumiko!
Papa!
Huh? Chau-chan?
Chau-chan?
Ha…
Kero-chan left home?
I don’t know,
but he hasn’t come back home.
Perhaps he got angry
because of how I reacted.
I am sure that Kero-chan
also regrets fighting.
The same as you are now.
I wonder.
Let’s go look for him, OK?
Yeah.
Even if we say that…
It’s too long.
Really.
Where should we search?
Sakura-chan. What are you doing?
Yukito-san!
Nothing at all.
He saw me at the worst
possible time.
I suppose this method
is impossible too.
I’m home.
I forgot,
I was supposed to make dinner today.
You do it on Sunday.
Why did you switch with me?
No reason.
There was just something I wanted to eat.
If you walk around with that spaced out
expression, you’ll fall over.
Eh!
Yuki was worried and called.
Yukito-san did?
Thanks, big brother.
I’ll answer that.
Hurry and go. Hurry and go.
Hurry. Hurry.
Where is it from?
A friend.
A very important friend.
Eh!
To Sakura, I am fine.
I’ll contact you again.
Kero-chan contacted you?
It was a fax,
but it had Kero-chan’s writing.
Do you know the phone number
it was sent from?
Let’s see…
The transfer data should be
On the top of the fax sheet.
Let’s see, 5,2,2…
I think I know the general area now.
As you can see a large
low pressure zone
is moving into the area.
Strong winds are expected,
so please be careful.
Next is the report for
the surrounding area…
What should I do?
I can’t leave her alone.
I have to get back to
Sakura’s place tho…
Eh!
Chau-chan, you can fly!
Eh?
Oh!
Chau-chau…
That’s amazing, Chau-chan!
I wish I could fly too,
Then I could
Meet my father in heaven.
Even if you can fly you won’t
meet people who are dead.
I understand wanting to
meet him though.
Eh?
Ha…
What is this?
I flew! I flew!
Look!
I can fly too.
That’s not it, she’s not flying.
This is…
A Clow Card!
Chau-chan!
Eh!
Join me over here.
Oh no!
Oh!
Akane!
Chau-chan, I can’t stop!
That is the Float card.
Give back Akane!
Chau-chan!
Stop!
If this goes on
you really will go
to where your papa is.
Damn.
Akane, wait for me!
I’ll show you my perseverance!
Oh, no. I’m falling.
Kero-chan.
Sakura,
you saved me.
But why are you here?
Tomoyo-chan searched for it.
Is that because of a card?
It is the Float card.
It is a prankster that likes
to make things float around.
If we don’t hurry and seal it,
Akane will be hurt.
I understand.
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card!
All right!
Akane!
Oh, no! I can’t stop!
Wood!
Mama…
Huh? Chau-chan.
Are you OK?
Oh! Chau-chau.
Well then, Akane-chan.
Yeah. Wait just a bit, Mama.
Chau-chau.
Miss.
You really will take Chau-chan?
Yeah.
Take good care of him.
Our new house won’t
let us keep Chau-chan.
If you get lonely
you can always visit Kero…
I mean Chau-chan.
Yeah!
But now
I can always be together with Mom.
I won’t be lonely anymore.
That’s good.
Yup.
Akane-chan.
Coming!
Bye, bye.
Akane’s mom
is changing jobs
so she can always be with her.
Yeah.
Chau-chan!
Bye, bye Chau-chan.
Bye, bye!
So, shall we go home, Kero-chan?
I haven’t decided to go
back to your place yet.
Are you still in a sour mood?
Look.
Ah, this is…
You made this?
Well?
Is is it a little too girlish?
No not at all…
I think.
This bed especially is pretty good.
You broke it!
After I went through all
the trouble to make it.
It wasn’t on purpose.
Wasn’t it just poorly made?
You’re horrible,
I think you are just too fat.
What’s that?
I’m not fat.
You are just clumsy.
Now you said it.
You monster.
Ah, you called me a monster again.
When all you have is dots for eyes.
What was that?
Giant monster Sakura!