Look! Look! That’s so cute!
Oh! That one is cute too!
So nice!
Mei Lin-chan is having so much fun.
I’m really glad she asked us
to go shopping together!
Yes.
Really,
that girl’s totally enjoying’ herself.
Kero-chan!
But girls really do like to go shopping.
I have to hide myself
everywhere you guys go!
It’s real tough, ya know?
Why don’t you consider how I feel?
I am really exhausted.
That’s why I told you to stay home.
But if you stay home, you might miss out
on the delicious food, right, Kero-chan?
That’s right!
I’m always where food is!
Geez, you love to snack
way too much, Kero-chan!
Hey! You guys!
Don’t just stand there!
Come on! Hurry up!
Now, let’s go!
[Sakura and the Sakura in the Dream]
=More and more and more,=
=I become greedy and spoiled.=
=From the way it’s going,=
=I wanna lock you up tight.=
=I made up my mind=
=at the mere sight and thought of you.=
=I wanna stay=
=like this next to you=
=for even just a bit longer.=
=I wonder if there isn’t=
=a terrible traffic jam somewhere.=
=I love you so much=
=that the brakes won’t work anymore.=
=Someone please,=
=read between my words.=
=Because I am no match for you.=
=Even just for now,=
=even just for one moment,=
=I wanna keep your heart=
=all to myself.=
=I’ve always, always, always watched you=
=and even pushed myself=
=wanting to catch up with you.=
=I love when you play jokes on me,=
=but I’m not a child anymore.=
=Even though I’m most easily scared,=
=I have the strongest feeling for you.=
=If you noticed,=
=there’d always be a familiar=
=scenery outside the window.=
=Your favorite slope=
=would pushed against your back.=
=The other side of me=
=can no longer turn away from you.=
Where should we go next?
Movie! Movie!
There’s a movie I want to see!
Kero-chan!
That game!
I’ve wanted to play
that game at least once!
But…
I wanna play! Wanna play! Wanna play!
You can’t! What if someone sees you!
In that case,
why don’t you play and lemme watch?
What? Me?
Good luck, Sakura!
Show me what you have!
You’ve been filming all this time.
Yes,
I must not let any of Sakura’s actions
slip through my camera!
Come on!
But!
What are you gonna do?!
Mei Lin-chan!
Don’t take your eyes off them!
I’ll take care of this side!
You do the other side!
Go! Sakura!
Sakura-chan and Mei Lin-chan
are working together so well.
Tomoyo-chan!
This is so sweet!
We won! We won!
What are you doing?!
You’ve waited for me.
I’ve returned from the navigation.
This is the last ring.
From now on, it is for our future.
It must be wonderful
to be able to stay
with the one you love forever.
Is that so?
It’s just gloomy to me.
Geez, Kero-chan,
you’re not romantic at all.
Mei Lin-chan,
don’t you think so too?
O… Of course!
Shao Lan, you think so too,
don’t you?
I’m going to buy something to drink!
Hey, Shao Lan!
Huh?
These…
are the Clow Cards I have.
Wh… What am I doing?!
Li-kun!
I am so touched!
Hey, Li-kun, Mei Lin-chan,
where should we go next?
There’s one place I’ve wanted to go
since I first came to Japan.
Wow! This is awesome!
It’s the first time I’ve done this!
You’ve never taken the train before?
I’ve never taken this train before.
Oh, I see.
Is something bothering you?
You’ve been staring…
Nothing’s really bothering me…
But I’ve been having a dream…
A dream?
Kero and I were
standing on top of this one building,
and we could see the
Tokyo Tower from there.
Do you dream about that every day?
No, only sometimes.
But maybe more often these days…
Oh, I dreamed about it
the day you came here.
A dream in which you appeared.
And then also…
the day I met Miss Mizuki.
A dream
which has that teacher in it?
We arrived!
We arrived! What’s wrong?
No, it’s nothing.
I’m sorry. Let’s go.
It’s huge!
Because it’s 333 meters after all!
It is really huge!
Have you been here before?
No, this is my first time.
But…
It’s the same as in the dream.
But what?
No, it’s nothing. Let’s go!
What’s wrong?
I thought I felt something weird…
There is nothing.
I wanna go to the observatory!
Li-kun!
Do you feel anything strange?
Not really.
Am I worrying too much?
Kinomoto-san!
Hurry up!
It seems Mei Lin-chan
keeps hurrying me today.
Because you look occupied.
She looks more like daydreaming.
She’s not occupied nor daydreaming.
She’s just worried.
No, she just needs to clear her mind.
This is it!
Hey, hey, it’s gonna close!
This is really high!
That’s the place I stood in my dream.
Did you see something cool?
Kero-chan!
What if someone sees you?!
There’s no one around!
So, what’s with
that confused look all day?
It’s the same as in the dream.
I haven’t been here before,
but it’s the same.
Well, that’s what
everyone called a dream.
But…
Would you like to join us
to buy something to drink?
I want an orange juice!
Kero-chan,
do you want a melon soda…
Huh?
What’s wrong?
Kero-chan…
Everyone’s waiting.
Oh! Wait, Li-kun!
May I take your order, please?
Onii-chan!!
Why are you here?!
Part-time.
But you said
there’s a soccer match today…
Yukito-san!
I’m doing part-time too.
But you told me
you’re helping out
with today’s soccer match…
Yukito also
Attend as a reserve player.
Because I want to be near you,
Sakura-chan.
Here’s the juice.
I want one too!
Kero-chan!
Yo!
Hello.
Hey, you guys, don’t try to
get Sakura into trouble!
Got it!
Wh… What’s going on?!
Because,
This is a dream!
This is…
… that dream?
Who is that person…?
Who is it?!
Mizuki-sensei…?!
What in the world is this?
What’s going on?
I…
don’t get it!
No problem
It’ll be okay for sure.
Gather yourself, Sakura!
Li-kun!
Under your left foot…
What is this?!
That’s a Clow Card!
Hurry up and seal it!
My magic can’t stop
time for much longer.
Key which hides
the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura,
command thee under contract.
Release!
Return to thy
form which thou should be!
Clow Card!
Li-kun!
Shao Lan!
I’m sorry,
if only
I’d noticed the card earlier,
none of this would have happened…
Don’t worry about it.
This is nothing for me.
This isn’t nothing!
Li-kun…
But just now, it was quite something.
Hey! What’s wrong?!
Kinomoto-san!
Sakura-chan!
Sakura’s totally unconscious,
and yet we could sense the card.
So I thought
this must be the act of a Clow Card.
But the card could not
be found anywhere…
Then Shao Lan noticed the card
was underneath your foot.
So, thanks for this!
It belongs to Shao Lan!
I’m sorry.
Dream …
So everything I’ve seen
after I entered the door was a dream.
Dreams created by ‘Dream’
What Dream shows a person
is not simply any dream.
It’s a prophetic dream!
Prophetic dream?
It’ll be okay for sure.