[Sakura and the mysterious broach]
Good morning.
Good morning, Tomoyo-chan.
You seem down Sakura-chan.
Couldn’t you sleep well?
A bit.
Are you worried about last night?
Yes.
Come thunder and obey the command.
You can catch Thunder
after returning it to beast form.
Don’t you even know that?
Are you stupid?
Windy can’t counter Thunder.
You did catch the Thunder card.
Sakura,
you performed your duty
as the only Card Captor
in the world perfectly.
It’s nothing so impressive.
So that is the rod of sealing?
But you really don’t know anything.
Anyways, it is impossible for you
to gather the Clow Cards
with that level of power.
But I don’t know what
would have happened
if Li-kun hadn’t given me advice.
Morning.
Good morning.
Good morning, Sakura-chan.
Rika-chan, good morning.
You seem down.
Rika-chan.
Thank you!
Rika-chan is mature and kind.
She is wonderful.
Umm.
Thank you… umm…
For yesterday.
It was because you told me
various things
that I was able to catch the Clow Card.
If you are gathering Clow Cards,
it is only natural
you should know that much.
Umm,
the clothes you were
wearing yesterday were cool.
Does everybody wear
things like that in Hong Kong?
Umm, in my dream
I saw a boy wearing those green clothes.
That’s why it surprised me.
That was the ceremonial clothing
passed down through the Li clan.
There is no way you could know it.
I didn’t know it. I saw it in a dream.
So you have enough magic power
to have premonition dreams.
Umm.
Li-kun.
Yamazaki-kun.
This is right after transferring,
but you are cleaning monitor.
Cleaning monitor?
To be the cleaning monitor means
to keep the chalkboard clean,
write up the day.
During the break you sing, dance,
and do various other things.
Japanese schools have something
like that?
Yeah.
Did the cleaning monitor have
to sing and dance?
They don’t.
Well for the time being
shall we clean the board?
When this is done you sing.
Yeah.
Sakura-chan?
Who?
Who is it?
Kinomoto.
Not getting enough sleep?
Umm. Well…
Well then get some rest when you get home.
Homeroom is over.
Well, that is enough for today.
Good bye sensei!
Do your homework.
Yeah!
Good bye sensei!
Be careful.
That dream again?
Something wrong?
No, it’s nothing.
It must make you nervous
to have Li-kun behind you.
Sakura-chan
do you have free time today?
Yeah, I don’t have to make dinner tonight.
My dad is at school until late,
and my brother has work.
Rika-chan said she found a wonderful shop.
Do you want to come along?
Thank you.
You’re cheering me up
because I was spaced out all day.
Thank you.
I just wanted to be with you
a little bit longer.
Going somewhere on your way home is OK,
but after you finish cleaning.
Y… Yeah.
Over here.
Do you like this sort of shop too,
Sakura-chan?
Yeah!
They have lots of wonderful things.
Sorry to make you come along.
Sakura-chan was feeling down today.
It’s fine.
I was wondering about that too.
How cute.
They really are cute.
I’m sure it would look good on you.
I want it, but…
But…
Are you going to buy it?
Yeah, I just got my allowance.
But this means no snacks for a while.
Then, I will get this one.
That one is cute too.
I wanted a broach too.
Well then, I will take this one.
It’s a pin broach right?
I am sure it would look good on you.
Kero-chan I have a guest,
so don’t come downstairs.
I got ya. I got ya.
Shall I help?
No, I’m fine. Go ahead and sit.
Sorry to intrude before dinner.
My brother and dad will be late today.
I will pour the tea.
Thank you.
Ah, it looks delicious.
My dad made them.
Let’s eat them together.
Thanks for the food.
Delicious.
Your father really is a good cook.
How cute.
It really was a nice shop.
Next time let’s invite Naoko-chan
and Chiharu-chan too.
Yeah.
It looks great.
You are very mature and pretty,
so things like that really suit you.
Rika-chan?
Rika-chan.
Rika-chan!
Sakura-chan.
What is it?
I just felt the aura of a Clow Card.
I smell pudding!
Without me!
More importantly,
Sakura-chan is in danger.
Rika-chan! Rika-chan!
Sakura!
Rika-chan is…
That is…
That’s the Sword card.
Rika-chan isn’t learning fencing,
so why?
The Sword makes
whoever uses it
an expert at swordplay.
This girl’s consciousness
is being controlled by Sword.
That can’t be.
Look out!
Key which hides the power of darkness,
show your true form before me.
Under the contract, I Sakura command you.
Release!
Jump.
If that sword hits you
it would be very bad.
The power of the Sword
depends on the heart of the person carrying it.
If it doesn’t want to cut you
it can hit you with the back of the sword,
but if it decides otherwise…
It can cut now.
But I can’t attack Rika-chan.
Then hurry and run away.
But… But… I can’t leave
Rika-chan like this.
Ri-kun!
You…
No!
What are you doing?
Sakura!
Are you OK?
Yeah, but Rika-chan is…
She almost got us.
You can’t hurt Rika-chan.
Everything would be OK
if she would only let go
of the sword for a second.
Sakura-chan!
What is it?
Tomoyo-chan and Ri-kun help me too.
That idiot.
It’s painful…
Be quiet and watch.
Display the form of the person
she thinks of the most.
Illusion!
Sensei…
Sakura, now!
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card!
All right!
She did it.
Rika-chan! Rika-chan!
She just passed out.
Sakura caught the card all on her own.
Sword is among the weakest of cards,
that was easy.
What’s that?
It’s painful…
Kero-chan!
Sakura-chan, I hear footsteps.
Stops.
Somebody is coming.
Kero-chan go to my room.
Is Touya here?
I came to return a CD I borrowed.
What’s wrong?
Are you OK?
Rika-chan.
Sakura-chan.
Sorry about yesterday.
For me to suddenly pass out like that.
But I don’t remember anything
after putting on that broach.
It’s strange.
Here.
Can I open it?
This is the one you bought.
I looked for your broach
as hard as I could,
but I couldn’t find it.
So…
Don’t worry about it.
It was my fault.
But… but…
But I really want you to take this.
The broach Rika-chan bought
is a card so I can’t give it back,
and I can’t tell her that.
I can’t explain it well.
Thank you, I’ll take good care of it.
Eh!
She isn’t asking anything
because I seemed troubled.
Rika-chan really is mature
and kind, and wonderful.
Good morning.
Morning.
What?
That brat was near our house?
He left right away though.
I guess I have to let him off this one time.
Have you chased away all the boys
that get close to Sakura-chan?
The only one allowed to pick on her is me.
You do have a sister complex after all.
Shut up.
It is just about the time she promised.
What did Sakura-chan need me for?
She said she had something
she wanted to give you.
In return for me telling you,
she has to make dinner tonight.
Picking on her again.
Why you…
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sakura-chan, you needed me for something?
Umm,
thank you for helping to
carry Rika-chan yesterday.
Thank you.
This is in thanks.
Really? Thank you.
Ah, chocolate.
I love sweets.
It looks great.
But you needn’t have worried about it.
Wait!
Here.
I can have this?
Thank you.
What did he give you?
Chocolate. Do you want some?
Sakura-chan!
Tomoyo-chan?
Because I couldn’t film
you getting the card yesterday,
I filmed a Sakura-chan
giving a present episode.
It looks like Li-kun likes
Tsukishiro-san too.
A rival has appeared in
both gathering cards
and in love.