I totally forgot
I’m supposed to cook dinner tonight!
Sorry about that!
Are you okay?
Ye… Yes!
Thank you very much!
You’re welcome.
I’ll see you again tomorrow.
Eh!
[Sakura and the Wonderful Teacher]
So she knows she’ll
see you again tomorrow…
Yeah.
What kinda person was she?
She was really pretty!
Hey!
Here!
Father made one for you.
Thanks.
He probably noticed it after all.
Since he was little,
he could see things
that other people couldn’t…
This jello is real good.
Leave some for me!
I’m late!
I overslept.
Today too.
G’morning, Sakura.
G’morning, Father.
You’re a little late. Hurry up and eat.
Bye. I’m leaving.
Take care yourself.
Thanks for the food! I’m leaving!
Take care!
There he is!
G’morning, Sakura.
Good morning!
You’ll fall
if you don’t watch where you’re going.
I’m fine!
Even when you said you’re fine,
you’d still fall into
a hole or something.
What did you say?!
G’morning!
You’re safe, Sakura.
The teacher’s not here yet.
Thank goodness.
You really just made it.
Eh!
I have an announcement
for everyone today.
Your math teacher, Miss Tsutsumi,
is taking a long vacation break.
So, from today on,
you’ll have a substitute math teacher.
Miss Mizuki.
My name is Kaho Mizuki.
Nice to meet you.
The person from yesterday.
She is pretty, is she not?
Yes.
What about Miss Mizuki?
You couldn’t sense it?
Sense what?
Oh, Shao-Lang! There you are!
Mei Ling.
You promised me that you’ll
eat lunch with me, remember?
He… Hey, hold on a second.
We just started talking.
What did you just start talking about?
It is about Miss Mizuki.
What is this? You want to leave me out?
It’s not that I forgot about you!
Then what?
You really didn’t sense
the aura on that teacher?
Aura?
She has a good amount of power in her.
It’s better to be careful.
That’s going to be a problem.
Miss Mizuki!
She came right next to us,
and I didn’t notice her at all.
You’re Shao Lan Li, right?
I am your new math teacher.
You’ll be in trouble,
if you don’t study carefully.
Isn’t that right, Tomoyo Daidouji?
And also, Mei Lin Li.
And, you’re Sakura Kinomoto.
Ye… Yes! Thank you for yesterday.
We meet again.
Miss Mizuki is so pretty.
She really is.
She’s nice and pretty.
I want to be like her too!
Then, maybe you should
buy a good-luck charm
from Tsukimine Shrine.
Why?
People said those charms
would grant anything you wish for.
Especially on love relationships.
Love?!
Mei Ling?
The charms might be very accurate,
but since my relationship with
Shao Lan is in the best shape,
it doesn’t make any difference.
I didn’t know they sell love charms
in this shrine.
Naoko knows a lot about these things.
Love… Yukito…
Now, let’s go.
Okay.
Eh!
What is wrong?
Somehow, I had a strange feeling…
I did not feel anything…
Maybe I just imagined it.
The place that sells good-luck
charms is over there.
Hold on, Mei Ling.
This place…
In order to heal the wounds between us,
we must get these charms!
That’s not what I mean!
Eh!
Ki… Kinomoto! Um… m…
This is…
Li!
Did you feel something
when you entered the shrine?
You felt it too?
Huh? Felt what?
Eh!
What’s that?
What is this?!
This was the shrine just now.
Yes, it was no doubt.
Wh… Where’s the exit…
Hold on! Sense it yourself!
Yes.
I sense a Clow Card!
Then, this is the act
of a Clow Card too?
It’s most likely the card, Maze.
I see. That is why,
it turned into a maze.
Well, leave the rest to Shao Lan.
Now, let’s get
out of this maze quickly
and buy our charms.
It’s not as easily as you think.
This maze won’t disappear
until those who entered it find the exit.
It won’t disappear
until we find the exit?
Weird!
Weren’t we here just now?
Come to think of it, the view
didn’t change a bit since just now.
This is strange.
But we should eventually find the exit
if we walk with our hands on
the wall like this.
Li, you brought the compass,
right?
Yeah.
You can use it to find out directions,
right?
Oh no!
This compass is made only
to look for Clow Cards.
But if we cannot think of
a good way,
we would never be able
to get out of here.
I thought of one useful thing.
Key which hides the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release!
Fly!
I’ll go look for an exit with this.
Hand it to you.
Yes.
Eh!
So there’s no way to search from above.
The Maze card is strict, don’t you think?
If we don’t something,
we won’t be able to buy the charms!
This pisses me off!
You can’t break it even if you do that.
But!
I get it! That’s right,
Mei Ling!
What!
If we aren’t able to look
for the exit from above…
Cut apart the object that
blocks our way! Sword!
Let’s try break it with this.
It worked!
It’s cut apart!
Eh!
So Sword doesn’t work either.
What’s going on?!
Mei Ling!
Sakura!
Tomoyo!
You okay?
Shao Lan.
Tomoyo!
Sakura!
Wind Descend!
Are you okay?
I am fine. Thank you very much.
It’s strange.
It seems that it has become
more difficult to look for the exit.
Oh no.
Where’s Mei Ling?!
Shao Lan!
Mei Ling! Where are you?!
Here!
Over here!
Mei Ling!
Wait there, I’ll save you!
Wind Descend!
What happened?
The space’s twisted,
so the wind can’t get to her.
Shao Lan!
I said I’ll save you for sure,
so don’t move about.
But how?
It seems there’s no other way
than to walk there.
Yes… Is that right…? I see…
Said she left school at the usual time.
I’ll go look for her around here.
Father, why don’t you stay put,
since she might call.
Be careful!
Shao Lan, hurry!
Just a bit more!
If we go in here, we would
not be able to see Mei Ling.
Turn back?
But look, once we get
out from the other end,
we’d be able to see her again.
Right. Mei Ling!
What?
We’re going to enter this tunnel.
You’ll be hidden from us,
so you gotta tell us where you are.
Get it?
How should I tell you?
Count slowly.
I got it.
Let’s go.
One. Two.
Three. Four.
Five. Six.
Seven. Eight. Nin…
Mei Ling!
Mei Ling! Mei Ling!
Where are you?
I told her not to move.
Father and Touya must be worried.
Anyway, let’s look or her!
Mei Ling’s waiting for us.
Ye… Yeah.
This sound…
We heard it too
when the maze appeared.
Who is it?
Mei Ling!
Shao Lan!
Thank goodness.
But how did you get here?
I was saved.
By whom?
Miss Mizuki!
I thought I felt a strange
aura in our shrine.
It turns out it’s because
this maze suddenly appeared.
I was really surprised.
‘Our’ shrine?
I’m the daughter of
the priest of this shrine.
Eh!
But thank goodness.
I decided to walk around
because I was afraid someone
might have got lost in it.
And then, I heard Li’s cry.
Didn’t you hear this sound?
When we first got lost in the maze…
I was trying to warn people
to be careful by making some noise,
but I guess it was a little late.
It has an interesting shape.
It’s been past down in
the shrine from a long time ago.
This works like a bell too.
Eh!
Poor girl, you’re hungry, aren’t you?
Then, let’s get out of here.
We’ve been trying to look for
the exit all this time, but it
was nowhere to be found.
Do you know how you can
get out of a maze?
We tried many things,
but it seems we are really in trouble.
Then, what about this?
But even though you break the wall,
it quickly…
It’s weird?
Now, let’s go.
This seems to be okay.
I guess it’s fine as long
as we can get out.
The walls aren’t turning back
to the way they were.
She can break through this maze.
She has some amazing power after all.
Here’s the exit.
We got out!!
We finally got out!
Thank goodness.
It’s starting to form another maze!
Turn it back to a card quickly!
Bu… But…
Don’t mind me.
Um…
In that case, I’ll turn around.
Sure that’s okay?
Hurry! It’s forming another maze!
Key which hides the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release!
Return to thy form which thou should be!
Clow Card!
U… Um… That’s…
I think it’s better
for you to have it. Here.
Sakura!
Touya!
What’ve you been doing?!
We got lost for a bit,
and then Miss Mizuki helped us out,
and led us towards the exit, and…
A lot of things happened.
Don’t scold her, okay?
Kaho…
You’ve grown up, Touya.
Eh!
I wonder what is wrong.
The charm store…
…is closed.
Here. Please have them.
Thank you very much!
You wanted that, right?
How did you know?
We didn’t say anything…
I just do.
My sixth sense.
See you tomorrow, okay?
See you tomorrow.
Be careful.
As I thought, that teacher
is more than just ordinary.
Wait for me!
See you later, Kinomoto.
Ye… Yes.
See you later, Touya.
Touya, you know Miss Mizuki?