What a gentle hand…
This hand…
[Sakura’s Dizzy Fever Day]
Sakura! It’s morning’!
It’s raining’ today.
You can’t skate in the rain,
so hurry up…
What’s wrong…
I feel kinda dizzy…
Dizzy?
You got a real bad fever!
You okay?
It’s better to skip school
if you’re sick.
There’s a poster I haven’t finished,
and it’s due today.
I left it at school so I have to…
Hey, hey!
Thanks…
Good morning.
You overslept again?
Our monster’s sure at a loss
on a rainy day.
That’s not it.
Good morning, Mother.
What’s wrong?
You’re very warm.
Don’t tell Father I have a fever.
Why not?
Father is going out of town, right?
The long-waited excavation
has finally succeeded.
He was looking forward to it.
If he finds out I’m sick,
he might not go…
Good morning.
Good morning!
Good morning, Nadeshiko-san.
It’s raining today.
Yeah, but I heard the
excavation site is sunny today.
Thank goodness!
Let’s eat!
I’ll be back next Saturday.
Okay. Good luck!
Then, I’ll see you later.
Bye!
Take care.
Just skip school today.
If I skip, I’ll make everyone worry.
But…
I’ll come straight home
and go to bed right away.
Now, let’s go, Touya.
We’re going to be late!
Sakura-chan.
You are not feeling well today?
No… Not at all.
But you don’t seem cheerful.
I’m fine!
Really?
That’s good.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Good morning, Tomoyo.
You don’t look so well.
Are you okay, Sakura?
I feel kinda dizzy…
You should have
just skipped school today.
I’m fine. I’ll be okay.
You have a fever, don’t you?
I am okay!
Maybe you’ve caught a cold…
Daidouji-san,
could you take Kinomoto-san
to the school nurse?
Yes.
I… I’m okay, Tomoyo-chan…
Now, let’s go.
Let me see.
It’s pretty high.
She did get a cold after all.
The fourth period has already gone by.
I suggest you skip the rest of the day.
But the poster…
We will finish it somehow.
But…
Don’t worry!
Mei Lin-chan! Li-kun!
I’m here! I’ll finish it for sure!
But…
Look, you don’t trust me?
That’s not it! But…
Then don’t say, “but…”
Shao Lan, Daidouji-san,
and I will finish it for sure.
And of course, in its best form!
Right, Daidouji-san?
Please do not worry about it,
and just leave it to us!
Right, Shao Lan?
So, hurry up and go home.
Thanks.
I’m glad you came.
You called me.
Within your mind.
It’s not something I usually hear.
It’s about Sakura-chan.
She…
It seems she has a cold after all.
So, take her home, okay?
She has already started
packing up to go home.
Kaho!
Why did you come back?
Because, there are certain
little things I need to do.
I am worried about you.
Let me walk you home.
It’s okay.
I can go home on my own.
Sakura-chan!
Such thick clouds…
Sakura…
Thanks.
Sorry to have you
bring my schoolbag here.
It’s okay. I hope Sakura’s
temperature goes down quickly.
But you know, Mizuki-sensei
Is quite a mysterious person.
I was so surprised
when you suddenly jumped
out of the classroom.
You could hear
Mizuki-sensei’s voice, right?
Even though she wasn’t nearby.
Not normally.
Today’s special.
Because it’s about Sakura, right?
If you need me for anything,
give me a call.
I’ll be right over.
See ya.
Sakura…
Take your temperature.
How’s it?
Here.
It’s not going down at all.
You already took the medicine but it
still doesn’t go down for some reason…
I’ll be right back.
Your brother probably
noticed me after all.
What’s wrong?
I sense a Clow Card.
You’re right…
You can’t get up!
Th… This is…!
A Clow Card?
Cloud. The card of the clouds.
Sakura! What are you doing?!
I gotta seal it…
If you go out in this condition,
your fever’s just gonna get worse!
But if I do nothing…
That’ll be a problem.
If Cloud spreads out,
it’d be impossible.
Then, I must hurry…
You can’t!
Your brother just
went to get food for you!
If you aren’t here,
it’ll turn in a big trouble!
You got it now?
Release!
Ho… Hold on!
Reflect my image
and form another me!
Mirror!
This way I’ll be okay…
Are you okay, Sakura?
Let’s seal the card
quick and go home, okay?
Yes.
Can you get up?
Wanna eat this?
Over there!
Cloud should be
inside that whirling storm!
Sakura!
Wind Descend!
Li-kun! Mei Lin-chan!
It’s the brats!
Th… Thanks, Li-kun.
You still go riding in the wind
in this condition?!
Y… Ye… Yeah, but the ca…
Idiot!
In that condition,
what if anything happens to you?!
But I gotta seal the card quickly,
otherwise it’ll cause
a lot of trouble…
Besides,
I’ve decided for myself
that I’d collect all the cards!
It’s coming’ again!
Thanks for the food.
You’re done?
Save some so that
I can have more later.
I’ll just make more later.
What about the medicine?
You don’t need to take it
unless you’re sick.
You aren’t Sakura, right?
We met before.
Did Sakura go out?
Umm…
Excuse me…
I kinda have an idea
as to what she’s been doing.
Can you not tell her
that I noticed?
It seems she wanted to
hide it from me anyway.
Okay…
Thanks.
God of Fire, come forth!
Is that… Rain?
They look similar,
but no, this is Cloud!
Return to thy form…
Sakura!
Mei Lin-chan…
Are you okay?
Return to thy
form which thou should be!
Clow Card!
We did it!! Shao Lan!
This is yours.
Huh?! Why?!
Now this is out of ordinary!
Li-kun…
In the end, all the cards
are gonna be mine anyway…
This is just for now.
Thanks.
I’m back…
Are you okay, Sakura?
Thanks.
You are welcome.
I had a lot of fun too.
She went back in safely.
Thank goodness.
And, why didn’t you go back in?
Her brother’s taking’ care
of Sakura in her room the whole evening.
Who knows when he’ll discover me
if I stay in there.
I’m worried about Sakura,
but I guess I have no choice
but to stay at you
two brats for the night.
What’s that supposed
to mean?!
It’s called telling the opposite.
In that case,
it’d be so nice if you’d come.
You’re so great!
What is this?!
What?!
This is painful…
This is painful…!
Onii-chan…
Geez, all because you
did reckless things.
I’ll go call the doctor.
Just hang on.
Mother…
Same as this morning.
This hand…
It’s Mother’s hand.
You’ll be okay now.
You came.
Yeah, I was a little worried
since this morning.
Get well, Sakura-chan.
Wh… Who is it?!
Father! How come?
Sakura seemed a little strange
this morning,
and that kept bugging me…
But it seems
I was just worrying too much.
No, you were right.
She had a fever,
but it’s gone now.
I see.
It must be hard to handle
this by yourself.
It wasn’t just by myself.
Because Mother came.
I see…
Good morning!
Huh? Father, how come…
I came back last night
for something I forgot.
I have to leave
again after breakfast.
Are you okay now?
Thanks, Mother.
Sakura, why did you say thank you?
Somehow, I had this feeling
that Mother was with me.
Breakfast is ready!
Okay!
You just recovered,
so you better start eating it,
monster.
I’m not a monster!
A monster can catch a cold too,
I guess.
I said I’m not!
Huh? What are you talking about?
No, it’s nothing.
Let’s eat!!