I am still sleepy.
Ah, I can’t!
I have to clean the yard.
Still sleepy after all.
Can I help you?
– Eriol-kun…
– Good afternoon.
Hello, are you returning home
from shopping?
Yes, I bought some ingredients
for dinner tonight.
Eriol, you cook your own meals?
So impressive
Sakura-san as well,
I’m impressed to see
you taking care of the various
chores around the house.
Allow me to assist?
It’s not too good.
There’s no need to reserved.
But if you return home late.
Won’t your parents be worried?
It’s alright.
Thanks.
[Sakura and the Panic Bicycle]
Allow me. Should I set it over there?
Yes. Thanks.
Are you all done?
Then let’s go back to the front.
– Thanks.
– Sakura.
Dinner’s ready!
Let me introduce you.
This is my father.
He is a college professor.
Hiiragizawa Eriol.
He transferred to
our school this September
and we ended up in the same class.
I’m Hiiragizawa Eriol.
I’m Kinomoto Fujitaka.
He lives nearby too.
He stopped by on his way home
to help me clean
Is that so.
Thank you.
Not at all.
That’s right!
Eriol, do you want to eat dinner with us
You helped me out
with the cleaning after all.
Yes please.
We have snacks inside as well.
Thank you very much.
I would very much like to
eat dinner with you as well,
but I have to return home and
prepare dinner tonight…
I see…
– Please invite me again.
– Sure, you bet.
Then, I’ll see you tomorrow in school…
Ok, see you tomorrow.
You have your work cut out for you…
Let’s eat!
Help yourself.
So good.
It would’ve been nice
if Eriol were eating with us
If he’s in the same class as you
that means he’s in the 5th Grade, right
He doesn’t look like it.
He’s very composed.
It’s because he’s nice and very mature…
He also does well in his studies,
and he’s a…
Good cook.
You seem to be sleepy a lot recently.
Are you OK?
Y… Yes!!
I woke up because the food is so good.
Can you sleep at night?
I’m getting my rest.
Really, there’s nothing wrong
so you don’t worried.
This one’s so delicious!
So delicious! This one too!
Who could it be?
I’m home.
Weren’t you supposed to be late
because of work tonight?
I just came to get something I forgot.
Have you eaten dinner yet?
I’ll be returning soon so.
– Sakura.
– What?!
Did you touch my bicycle?
Huh? Umm…
Oh, I moved it a little when
I was cleaning the yard.
Don’t ride my bicycle.
I won’t.
My feet can’t even reach the pedals.
Ah! The last piece of fried shrimp!!
Brother!!!
I’m leaving.
Good-bye.
Big brother, that’s so mean!!
You know fried shrimp is my favourite!!
Is Sakura’s father working this late?
He sure is a hard worker.
Your father made dinner tonight,
didn’t he?
What about dessert?
Yup…
You brought back
some dessert for me, right?
Wow, pudding!
It is pudding!
It is my beloved pudding!
That’s my Sakura-sama.
Pudding, Pudding, Pudding,
Pudding, Pudding, Pudding…
Sleepy.
It is probably because
you’re transforming
the Clow Cards into Sakura Cards.
It’s OK because today is Sunday,
but I’ll be in trouble
during the school week.
But with the magic power
you have right now…
Until all the cards
are transformed,
your magic and mental powers
will be drained.
– Hey Kero-chan.
– What’s it?
I’m getting a weird feeling
from the Clow Cards.
Weird?
Before, I would get a sense of warmth
and energy
from the Clow Cards
But now it’s cold.
It’s true!
The remaining Clow Cards are so cold!
Why?
Hmm, how can I explain
it so it’s easy to understand?
These cards, you see,
they move by the power
of the keeper’s magic.
Before you sealed the cards,
they were moving under
the supervision of the magic
left over by Clow Reed.
Magic is food for the cards.
Food?
So, after you become the new master
by collecting all the cards
after they were spread out…
My magic
was being cosumed?
That’s right!
But right now,
the Clow cards can’t be used
coz there’s an interference…
In other words,
the cards are still asleep
If it is in a sleeping state…
The food can’t be eaten…
If the food can’t be eaten?
What happens?
They become ordinary cards.
I won’t be able to meet
with the Cards anymore?
Umm… yeah.
I can’t let that happen.
I was finally able to become
good friends with them!
Therefore,
the ones that are transformed
to Sakura Cards are fine.
Since we just said that
the source of the Sakura Card
is your magic…
O Key which hides the power of the stars,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release!
Wh What are you planning to do?
I’m going to turn them
all into Sakura Cards.
Say what?
O Card that Clow has made,
I command you to lose your
old form and be reborn.
Under the new master, Sakura!
Sweet!
Lock!
Libra!
Song!
Voice!
Change!
Loop!
Dash!
Sakura!
Why are you being so reckless?
Your magic power is drained right now
so if you try to change them all at once,
of course you’re going to collapse.
I’m so glad, you’re all
still full of energy!
Sakura!!
That one, Dash.
What’s going on?
The magic has run away relentlessly.
I didn’t even use Dash, so why?
It’s because it’s impossible
to transform those cards all at once
That, and the fact that
the card was initated
without any reason
and Dash didn’t know
what to do so it went
into a panic state.
Considering your magic power
and precision at the moment,
you can’t use magic when
there’s no need for it.
On top of that,
transforming that many cards
into Sakura cards,
You idiot!
Of course,
I’m worried about the Clow Cards,
but if something happens to you
then the Sakura Cards
lose their magic as well.
In any case, we must stop Dash
and calm it down.
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
Windy!
It looks like Windy can’t catch up to it.
Oh! That’s right.
Hey!! What’re you doing
making a phone call now?!
But, I promised
Li-kun and Tomoyo
that I’d contact them.
Think about the time
and the place!!
[You have reached the
Daidouji Residence.]
[I am unable to pick up
the phone right now.]
[Please leave your message
after the beep.]
I guess Tomoyo’s not there.
I’ll leave her a message.
Listen when someone is talking to you!!!
Next is Li…
Hello.
Li-kun? It’s me Sakura…
What’s it?
We’re chasing a bicycle right now.
Without thinking,
I tried to change all the cards at once,
and Dash ran away…
And then…
I can’t understand
what you’re trying to say!
Anyway we’re in big trouble!
Where are you right now?
In the park, heading towards the library.
Alright, I’ll be right there!
Ok!
Look! You lost the card
because you were concentrating
on your phone call!!
Jump!
There it is.
No, you can’t do that!
Sakura!
God of Wind, obey my order!
Stop being so reckless!
Are you ok?
You came here pretty fast, kid.
I didn’t really.
Thanks for coming.
Is that it?
Thunder, come!
Damn.
One more time!!
Don’t! You’ll scare the card!
But if you leave it like that…
It’s my fault, if we’re calm,
I am sure Dash will come back
to us peacefully.
OK. I understand.
What’re you planning on doing, Sakura?
Using Fly, get in the air…
No,
following Dash in its panic state
is too much even in my true form.
Don’t think Fly would work either.
If we can somehow get ahead
so Dash can’ t go anywhere.
It might work!!
Loop, huh?
Yeah, but then you have
to transform another card.
This time,
it won’t end with you just fainting.
But it’s my fault
that Dash is like this,
I have to try and
turn it back into a card!
All right!
If you faint,
I’ll be sure and catch you!
Go for it Sakura!
O Card that Clow has made,
I command you to lose
your old form and be reborn.
Under the new master, Sakura!
Loop!
I see. Loop, is it?
But what’ll you
do about the frightened Dash?
WINDY
Don’t hurt it.
It’s alright.
You don’t have to be scared.
I’m sorry I fightened you.
It’s alright now.
You’re a good kid,
so stay still. Ok?
That tickles.
I’m sorry.
I won’t frighten you anymore so please,
turn back into a card.
Thank goodness…
You did it, Sakura!
Kero,
if there’s a reason to use magic
and if it’s little by little,
Then it’s OK to change
the Clow Cards into Sakura Cards, right?
That’s right.
I don’t know why strange events
keep turning up in Tomoeda
or why I can’t use the magic power
from the Clow Cards
But I’ll do my best
to change all the cards
And then,
when I’ve changed all the cards
and when my magic
becomes stronger,
I might find out
why all these strange
events keep happening.
Exactly!!
Allright! I’ll do my best.
Sakura!
What’s wrong?
Sleepy…
It’s because you overdid it!
Hey! Wake up!!!
I can’t go on without you…
Get a hold of yourself…!
I didn’t make it on time!
It just ended right now!
Who would’ve thought that
I would get a phone call from
Sakura while I was taking short bath?
I even brought the costume…
Well there’s no need to worry
because I was by her side.
At least… At least…
Let me get Sakura-chan’s
cute sleeping face on video!!
The batteries are running out!!
Really, I’m so careless today!
Get my cool pose as well!!
Sakura’s smiling face is so cute!!
Are you listening to me, Tomoyo?!
Really Sakura is…
Sakura is so ñute!!
Are you listening to me, Tomoyo?!
Being able to shoot Sakura like this
forever makes me so happy
Are you listening to me, Tomoyo?!!!!?