Who will you give it to?
Li-kun!!
N… nooo… way…
Why am I thinking about her?
This can’t be…!!
What’s wrong with me?
Why do I keep having
her images in my mind…
If your mind is calm,
then you will realize your inner truth
Inner truth…
What do you mean?
As for the rest of its meaning,
you’ll have to figure it out by yourself.
Inner truth… What is going on…
[Sakura, Shao Lan and the Elevator]
Good morning!
Good morning, Tomoyo-chan!
– Hi, Sakura-chan!
– Good morning, Rika-chan!
Look at this…
Teddy Bear Show?
How cute…
Sakura really like teddy bear, right?
Perhaps you will like to see it.
Love to see it!
We can all go to see it tomorrow.
Sorry,
I have a ballet lesson tomorrow
I can’t go.
Chihara-chan and Naoko-chan
don’t have time to go either.
You and Tomoyo-chan can go,
it’s already good enough.
I see… then…
thank you very much, Rika-chan!
Tomoyo-chan,
do you have anything to do tomorrow?
No, it would be nice
if we could go together.
Great!
Is it a teddy bear show?
– Eriol-kun, Good morning!
– Good morning!
Really?
Eriol-kun is really smart.
Oh not at all…
Then, Eriol-kun, let’s go
together tomorrow, okay?
Would that be too much
of a trouble for you?
– Good morning, Li-kun!
– Good morning…
Oh, Li-kun, lets go together.
It’s a teddy bear show.
It will be really fun.
Right!
Great!
Yes, yes, lots of bears, yes, yes, yes
Look at this, you could get a teddy bear
gift in the show too.
Everybody could be able to get one.
Can’t wait till tomorrow.
– Can’t wait till tomorrow.
– Right.
Sakura is very cute, isn’t she?
I… Me and her… There is nothing
It’s… really is… actually…
This kid is an honest person.
What am I doing?
This can’t be!!
Damn!
– Are you all right?
– I am okay.
That’s good.
Coming back from school?
Yeah…
You seem to be out of it.
Anything happended in school?
No… no…
I know, you must be hungry.
I guess it was me who’s hungry.
I am really sorry to
have you come along with me.
It’s not a problem.
Sakura invited me to have dinner
at her house tonight.
I felt improper to eat at Sakura’s
place even though she invited me.
I think
I will get her some cookies as a way
to say thank you.
That’s why I want to
buy some cookie bakery tools.
Oh yeah!
If you don’t mind, can you choose
some cookie cutters with me?
Me?
Did you find one?
It’s a teddy bear shape cutter.
Sakura likes it, right?
N… no… I really…
I choose this two.
But I think they are too big.
I think it won’t be a problem,
she eats anything.
If there are foods, she’ll be happy.
And…
If you are the one who make them,
she’ll definitely be very happy.
It seems like you like Sakura a lot.
Wha… You… I…
What’s up?
I like her…
Message one.
Hello, this is Kinomoto.
Before tomorrow’s meeting time
and place are decided, you’ve left.
Tomoyo-chan, Eriol-kun
and I have deci…
Message two.
It hurts…
Hello, sorry about that,
Kero-chan is playing videogame and…
It was you, who knocked me over!
What!!
Sorry… Oh,
we are talking about
the meeting time and place…
Tomorrow at ten am,
meet us at the train station’s
ticket booth, okay?
If you can’t get there during that time,
please tell me, bye.
Hello, this is Kinomoto.
we are talking about
the meeting time and place…
I discussed with Tomoyo and Eriol-kun
after you gone.
And the time is…
=This can’t go on forever,=
=I look up=
=at the blue sky.=
=A gentle breeze=
=goes by,=
=as I walk up the hill.=
=My usual serious face watches,=
=from far away=
=What has happened=
=to my pride?=
=I am devoted.=
=I can’t ignore her.=
=She’s mysterious.=
=I’ll just watch quietly from here.=
=It seems something=
=big waits.=
=I can’t ignore this feeling,=
=this strange feeling.=
=My heart beats like in a dream.=
=It seems that everyday=
=it gets stronger.=
=I won’t be beaten by her.=
=We spent so much time,=
=chasing down an orange bear.=
=It seemed like=
=Such a good idea, at the time.=
=When did she start=
=to mean so much to me=
=I don’t know why.=
=Kick away the asphalt,=
=and hurry home.=
=I can’t ignore her.=
=She’s mysterious.=
=I can’t look away=
=from her eyes today.=
=Why am I matching my pace to hers,=
=as we walk down the street?=
=I can’t ignore this feeling,=
=it’s a strange feeling.=
=As if my heart=
=has just started beating.=
=I won’t give up whatever happens.=
=But I have an idea!=
=I won’t be beaten by anyone.=
Those teddy bears are really cute.
Really…
I am very lucky.
I get to record Sakura’s cute moments
But if we could get to
see this show earlier…
Then the teddy bear
I made wouldn’t be that bad looking.
Oh yeah, Li-kun,
did you finish your yet?
What?
– The teddy bear doll.
– What?!!!
You bought the tools
in the store, right?
Eh… Li-kun, you bought
a teddy bear kit?
Did you give it to anybody yet?
The teddy bear show is over…
I want to hurry home before sunset.
Wait… Li-kun!
Li-kun!!! Wait!!!
What am I doing?
Why did you walk
that fast all of a sudden?
Hurry! Hurry!
What is going on?
It’s probably some minor
flaw in the elevator.
I’ll go get help.
Doesn’t work…
Same here…
Why is it like this?
For now, let’s wait till
the rescuers come and get us.
Tomoyo-chan and Eriol-kun
are probably on
their way to get help.
Someone will definitely
come and get us out.
So, don’t cry.
Do you want to sit down?
Standing like that
will make you very tired.
If you sit over there,
it will stain your pants.
– Let sit over here together.
– What!
Found it, here.
What is it?
Last night,
Yukito-san came over
my house to have dinner.
Thanks for the food!
You always invite me over to have dinner
I just don’t feel right…
So, today I want to give you this.
Here, cookies.
The cookie bag is so big.
The dinning table can barely hold it.
But… I was careless…
– It was really good…
– Kero-chan!!!
Kero-chan ate all of the cookies,
except this one.
Here, you can have it.
Since this is gift for you,
You should have it.
Then… I’ll give you half of it.
Here.
It’s very good.
It’s Yukito-san’s cookie.
It’s moving again…
Aaahh!!
Sakura!!
I used the Float card.
I am glad.
– Li-kun, Sakura-chan!
– Tomoyo-chan!
I am glad that you guys are all right.
Thanks!
I was very worried.
Really!
Good…
– Hello, is this Li-kun?
– Yeah…
Thank you for what you did today.
No, I didn’t do anything.
When Li-kun and me are
inside the elevator…
You yelled my name, Sakura.
I am really happy.
From now on,
can I call you Shao Lan-kun
instead of Li-kun?
Whatever you like.
Then, I’ll see you tomorrow in school.