Here.
Thank you.
You should have put
your bag in the trunk.
It’s pretty small…
Is this the place?
Yeah, about nine kilometers further.
This is my first time
going to a summer house.
Me too.
[Sakura and the rainbow of memories]
Sorry to intrude on your family trip.
Not at all.
Sorry to make you come along
on your summer vacation.
Not at all.
Yeah.
We don’t have any homework
over the summer holidays..
How nice. I am jealous.
I have this much.
You are probably going to run
around doing it all at the end.
We have to stop by and visit
Tsukishiro-kun’s place sometime.
You help around the house a lot,
and help out Touya a lot too.
I’ve never met your family.
I only have my grandparents,
so they get up early in the morning
and go to bed early.
Turn left here.
We’re really borrowing this place?
It seems they usually
spend summers here,
but this year they are going overseas.
Yay!
Sorry our summer trip isn’t overseas.
This place is wonderful too.
Dad,
thanks for bringing me along.
For the next two days,
I’ll be staying here.
I’m looking forward to it, Mom.
Hey! Did you forget I was in there?
Sorry, the room was just so nice
that I…
Oh, it’s pretty good isn’t it?
Right? So I was just so happy…
You were about to make me
into a sandwich.
That’s why I said I was sorry.
I will forgive you.
In return take care of my share
of the after dinner desert.
You don’t have to eat do you?
Well, yeah.
But, you like sweets.
I like a bit of luxury.
Doesn’t that just mean you like snacks?
All right.
The stove and faucets work.
OK, shall we go shopping?
Are you going somewhere?
To go buy groceries.
Do you want to come along?
Or, do you want to take
a walk until dinner?
I’ll go take a walk.
Now that you mention it, there was
a huge summer cottage near here.
Where?
Just a bit down the road.
Were you asleep?
No I wasn’t!
See you later!
Kero-chan, let’s go outside.
OK.
I was in the bag for so long,
the fresh air is nice.
Really.
It’s huge.
It is like Alice’s garden.
Alice?
Alice in Wonderland.
I saw it in a book.
Ah, that English story.
You sure know your stuff.
I am well educated.
Young lady.
Up here.
What a cute girl. Are you lost?
No, I am just taking a walk.
Where from?
From the summer home over there.
Did they have a girl your age?
We are borrowing it,
just for summer vacation.
I see. Are you in a hurry?
Would you like a cup of tea?
Here you go.
This is well done? Is that
because of your part time work?
From the steakhouse.
My brother really has worked everywhere.
It’s done.
So, shall we eat?
Thanks for the food.
Oh yeah, how was your walk?
It was fun.
I met an old man
at that big house.
He said he was out here
on vacation from work.
He treated me to some tea.
Didn’t you just gulp down
his tea without hesitation?
I didn’t.
Was the tea good?
The cookies were good too.
So you didn’t hesitate after all.
That old man invited me
to come over again tomorrow.
Go ahead.
It is good to make friends
at a travel destination.
Yeah.
Hello, this is Daidouji.
Ah, Tomoyo-chan. This is Sakura.
Sakura-chan?
I’m here too.
Kero-chan went with you right?
Yeah, it’s a really nice place.
I would have been nice
if you could come too.
The chorus club has
a national tournament.
It really was too bad.
Don’t worry about it. Good luck.
I’m cheering for you too.
Thank you very much.
There is a really big summer
house nearby.
There is a nice old man there,
he treated me to tea today.
Tomoyo-chan?
Nothing. Was it enjoyable?
Yeah, it was like
the tea party I saw in a book.
He told me to come over
again tomorrow.
That is wonderful.
Let me know about it
afterwards.
Yeah, my dad told me
I could too
Yeah, well then good night.
Good night.
Are you going to that old man’s
place again tomorrow?
Yeah, I’m going to go visit.
Don’t forget some snacks for me.
You are too glutonous.
I’m turning off the lights.
OK.
Good night. Pleasant dreams.
Good night.
I’m going out.
Ah. Sakura. I baked cookies.
Give them to the old man.
Thank you.
Say hello for me.
OK!
Are you going out already?
Yeah.
See you later.
I’m off!
Young lady.
Come on up.
Eh…
Over here.
Ah, over here.
Eh!
How cute.
Good afternoon.
Thank you for inviting me.
Thank you for coming over.
Is this a child’s room?
Yes it is.
A girl?
You can tell.
It’s such a cute room.
Is she here too?
Then can’t she join us?
She isn’t with us anymore.
She went to heaven some time ago.
I’m sorry. I…
You need not apologize
for anything.
So, smile.
A smile suits a girl best.
What is your name?
Sakura. Sakura Kinomoto.
Kinomoto?
May I call you Sakura-chan?
Yes.
Well then Sakura-chan,
would you like
to play here today?
Yes.
Let’s have some tea.
I wonder who is preparing the tea.
Is there somebody else here?
When you are like that
it is almost as if
my granddaughter has come back.
Was that child’s room
your granddaughter’s?
But she wasn’t good at tennis
like you.
Oh, shall I go get some cookies?
Ah, I forgot.
Here.
These are?
From my father.
Thank you.
My dad is a good cook,
so they are good.
You are here with your father?
Yes.
What sort of person is your father?
He is kind, a good cook,
a college professor,
he is also good at sewing.
Ah, he can knit too.
And then… and then…
You really love your father don’t you?
Yes.
Delicious.
Are you worried?
Huh?
About Sakura.
Was this your granddaughter’s too?
It was her favorite dress.
It really does look good on you.
You resemble her a lot.
Eh?
You closely resemble my granddaughter.
Will you accept this dress?
I can’t.
Please accept it.
I am sure my granddaughter
would be happy.
Would she really be happy?
Of course.
This is?
A picture my grandaughter drew.
A rainbow?
Because I liked to watch rainbows.
She drew it for me.
We could see a beautiful rainbow
from the veranda of this room.
It is a very kind picture.
She was a very kind girl.
What a nice old man.
But he seemed so sad.
Did you think of something
to return the favor?
I thought of a few things.
With such a big house
there is no point
to giving some present.
I wonder if
there isn’t something I can do for him.
Do you know something he would enjoy?
Ah, a rainbow.
There was a picture of a rainbow.
Rainbow? That’s it!
You stopped by?
Umm, I’m going home today.
That is too bad.
That’s why I have a small request.
Eh?
After I leave,
would you please go out to the veranda
from your grandaughter’s room?
I don’t mind.
Please do.
I understand.
I’ll make sure to do so.
Umm, I had a lot of fun.
So did I.
It was very fun.
Good bye.
Umm. Your grandaughter.
I am sure she went to a
beautiful place in the sky,
the same as my mother.
My brother told me that.
My mother was very happy
having married my father.
She must be in a
very beautiful place.
So, I’m sure your grandaughter
is also in a very beautiful place.
I am sure she is.
Well then, go out on the veranda.
All right, you can do it from here.
Rain,
cast a seven colored
bridge through the sky.
Rain!
Rain?
Grandfather! Grandfather!
Grandfather look, a rainbow.
Grandfather.
Sorry to make you stay with me,
Sonomi.
It was fun,
like playing hide and seek.
Putting out tea
and preparing cookies
without Sakura seeing me.
My great-granddaughter
seemed very happy.
I am glad I got to meet her.
Fujitaka Kinomoto
seems to be a good man.
He is the man Nadeshiko chose.
I wonder if Sakura
wanted to show me this rainbow.
But I wonder
how she knew there would be a rainbow.
I wonder if he saw the rainbow.
Ah, there is somebody there.
Where did you go off to?
It’s time to leave.
To the old man’s place.
Welcome back.
Ah, I’m sorry.
I’ll clean up right away.
Did you finish your business?
Yeah, I said goodbye to the old man.
Old man, she says.
But who’s summer house is that?
Long ago,
a young girl and her grandfather
would go together to that house.