What a hard painting
I should have picked
an easier one to paint…
Eriol-kun.
Sakura-san
Can I look?
Sure.
Great! Eriol-kun, you can really draw!
Thank you very much
I… I… I…
Y… yes…
li… like…
Sakura!
What’s wrong?
Someone is looking.
Who’s looking at you?
The person is looking at you, Sakura-san.
Me?
He is troubled too.
What a pity, last night.
What do you mean?
Just when you were
going to confess to Sakura,
Kero-chan suddenly appeared.
When do you plan to tell her next?
I won’t tell her for the moment.
Last night I was only thinking that
I have to tell her.
But before that, there is something
I must do first.
[Sakura and her Precious Friends]
I’ve made a promise.
Before I knew who the person I like was,
Mei Lin will still be my fiancee
So…
You want to tell
Mei Lin-chan how you feel?
I called her last night,
I said there were things
that we have to talk about.
What did Mei Lin-chan say?
She told me not to
tell her on the phone.
I told her I want to tell her in person
and she said she understood.
Really?
I really want to talk to Mei Lin.
And after that…
I’ll tell Sakura what I feel.
When will you see Mei Lin-chan again?
I’m going back to Hong Kong during
winter vacation…
I can’t wait that long!
Mei Lin-chan!
When you called her
she immediately came.
Mei Lin can’t wait until Christmas.
Mei Lin-chan!
It’s been a long time
since I’ve seen you!
How come you’re here?
I came to sort things out.
Right, Shao Lan?
How long are you staying here?
I still have to go to school so
I’m leaving tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Your leaving so soon?
So today!
Today after school
we can go together and play.
But,
you came to sort things out…
You’re still the same,
Kinomoto-san!
So after school
in at the front of the school.
That’s too bad,
I have ice skating after school.
– I have piano…
– Me too…
You have to have fun
with Mei Lin-chan for us then.
So, I’m going to go say hi
to the Terada sensei.
See you later!
Shao Lan! I’ll be right back
Who is it? I’m playing video games!
Why don’t you call another time?
Kero-chan, you’re playing
video games again?
Oh, it’s Sakura!
Call me later after
I play this game.
Today I saw Mei Lin-chan.
So I’m going to come home late
so if I open the door don’t worry
That girl is back?
But she said that
she is leaving tomorrow.
So today I want to talk with her.
Tell that girl,
even though the way
that I look isn’t very scary,
I can get her
to see how cool
I am in my original form next time.
Cooker… remember
to press the button.
Sorry that
I overheard you talking on the phone.
No, nothing private.
A new girl came in our class that
I’ve never seen before.
– With long hair…
– Her name is Li Mei Lin-chan,
she is an old student
After the school year
she went back to Hong Kong.
She sat where
you sit right now
She is Shao Lan-kun’s cousin.
So it’s like that!
We said that today after class
we will meet each other and play.
Be careful.
When it becomes dark, it is dangerous.
Thank you!
Why do you keep on smiling at me?
Because I get to see you,
that makes me very happy.
– Just because of that small thing?
– It’s not a small thing.
Being able to see you, I’m very happy!
Really?
When I saw you I was also very happy.
By the way,
Your the new Clow cards master?
Yes.
But there is still some problems right?
Yeah.
Are you ok? You look like a dummy…
– What dummy?
– Dummy looks is a dummy.
No need to say it, you already know.
But it’s no big deal.
You can stop looking like a dummy…
Today?
Are you going to tell
Mei Lin-chan today?
Tonight I’ll tell her how I feel.
If I didn’t tell her,
I’d break the promise.
I want to keep my promise with Mei Lin
no matter what.
Since you are that kind of person,
Mei Lin-chan likes you.
It opened again,
the store that sells juice.
That place’s drinks
taste really really good!
Really?
Why don’t we talk there?
OK.
What’s wrong?
Its Clow-san’s presence!
I feel the aura of strong magic.
What?
What is that???
Tomoyo-chan, Shao Lan-kun.
Are these the kind of
problems you just said?
Watch out!
King of thunder descend!!
– Are you ok?
– Yes.
King of thunder, descend!
Shit!
Mei Lin! Sakura!
It hurts!
– Are you OK?
– Thank you.
I can’t fight something that big!
There’s still so many!
How are we going to beat this?
Damn
if we want to beat them then…
If we use Wood,
it won’t affect them.
If I use Time, I will lose my power and
then I won’t be able to fight them.
The weather is so cold
how can I think?
Use that card!
Which card?
The one where you caught
at the skating rink.
When everybody was frozen!
Freeze!
O Key which hides the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract
Release!
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
Freeze!
It’s coming again!
King of Thunder, descend!
It worked!
This is because of
Mei Lin-chan’s idea!
Mei Lin, Sakura,
are you ok?
I’m fine, because
Mei Lin-chan helped me.
– Tomoyo-chan, are you ok?
– Yes.
Right! Mei Lin-chan are you ok?
Mei Lin-chan, are your hands ok
No problem, no problem, I’m very good.
I’m so glad!
Today it was because of that girl
from Hong Kong that helped.
There’s people coming.
Lets go drink some juice.
Yup.
But how come when it
happened nobody came by?
It is a place to jog.
Probably there is
something that scares away people.
Thinking about it,
before there
wasn’t any people.
Can he do that?
If he has the power
to control people then…
Power that controls people…
Mei Lin-chan,
I like you a lot too.
Why do you say that?
Because…
No matter what the problem you’re in,
remember me.
Yup.
Mei Lin-chan,
tomorrow, what time
will your plane come?
– 10 A.M.
– Really?
We have to go to school,
we cant send you off.
We’ll see each other later.
Maybe you can visit
Hong Kong over the summer.
Then we can see each other.
Yes.
What do you want to talk to me about?
If…
I have the person that I like.
I wanted to tell you.
Someone you like yourself?
Yes.
I see.
Is it Kinomoto-san?
How do you know?
Because you call her Sakura.
You will call girls by their names
and your sisters will have me.
So our engagement is over.
Thanks for the food.
– Where are you going?
– Daidoujii-san’s house.
I haven’t gotten to talk to her today.
– Your going by yourself?
– Shao Lan.
Wait, I’ll go with you.
– You don’t need to.
– Mei Lin.
It’ll be ok, I’ll take a cab.
Tommorow I’ll go from Daidouji-san
house to the airport.
See ya.
Let her go by herself.
It makes me mad to death!
I was the person
who liked Shao Lan the best.
I wouldn’t give him up
for any other person.
How come it ended up this way
I’m really mad
but I still like Kinomoto-san
I also like Kinomoto-san.
I know that she’s a good person.
That Shao Lan likes Kinomoto-san
isn’t a problem.
That’s how I’m thinking.
But I’m crying because of another reason.
Today I’m going to cry until morning.
I want to cry until I die. I want to
cry until I can’t cry
for Shao Lan any more.
– Are my eyes red?
– No,
you look fine
you look exactly as cute as you are
Shao Lan, are you
just going to stand there?
No… um…
Come and help me.
Have you told Kinomoto-san
that you like her yet?
No…
You still haven’t told her?
Kinomoto-san is that kind of person,
she won’t know unless you tell her.
If you weren’t so cute
then I wouldn’t care about Kinomoto-san.
But if you two don’t think about
it really good then I will get you!
Good bye, Shao Lan.
– Mei Lin…
– Come back to visit on holidays!
Mei Lin!
Mei Lin has a really good heart.
Yeah.
Mei Lin wrote me letters!
I got some too.
What did she write to you?
She said sorry for making my dress wet.
What did Mei Lin-chan write to you?
She said that I look like a dummy.
So she wants me to
act a little tougher.
But she said that my heart is too big,
so she’ll forgive me.
Still at the end there is something.
What it says,
I dunno,
but I think it is something very nice!
I am very happy!
Stupid Shao Lan,
hurry up and tell her.
I’m in Hong-Kong and the weather
is very good.
Mei Lin…
My most important friend,
Li Shao Lan.