– Good morning…
– Good morning.
Hey how did you know we have a test
at 1 o’clock today?
Really?
I see. That was a nice shot!
That’s great! What should I do?
I…
I really like you!
Good morning!
…Sakura-chan?
Sakura-chan!
Oh… Tomoyo-chan, good morning.
Oh! Good morning Li-kun!
Good morning…
g… good morning…
Everyone have a seat!
Okay.
I have some bad news for everyone.
Hiragizawa Eriol-kun is
transfering to England.
He will be leaving tomorrow,
so he’s not in class right now.
Sakura-chan…
I’m going,
are you coming too?
Yeah.
[Sakura and Her True Feelings]
This is the house where he lives.
Someone is inviting you.
Watch yourself.
Sakura…
I feel Clow’s aura.
Yes… I remember…
Yue and I did live here with Clow.
But you haven’t remembered until now?
He used magic to erase our memories.
Then how did you just remember?
I wonder why?
Come to think of it,
Eriol said yesterday “It’s finally over”…
If anything odd should happen,
Tomoyo, you…
I have my camera ready!
Tomoyo-chan…
Come on, lets go.
Be careful.
Welcome!
We’ve been waiting for you.
Now, please, come this way,
it’s all ready for you!
O… ok…
Wait right just a minute!
What’s waiting for us!?
Can’t you see it’s a tea party?
Nobody told me about this!
Have some sweets, then we can talk.
OKAY! Only Clow could be this nice!
Please, take a seat.
Don’t worry, it’s over.
Over?
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Now what did you wish to talk about?
What did you mean
when you said “It’s over”?
You said the same thing yesterday.
Yesterday, the last of the Clow cards
were turned into your Sakura cards.
My task is finished. That’s what I meant.
Task?
The cards
live off of
the magic of their master.
Without Clow Reed to support them,
they would have become regular cards.
You have saved them
with your magic.
And so…
You created problems
that would cause Sakura to use the cards.
It was my duty as the
reincarnation of Clow Reed.
I must apologize for what is to come.
Clow-san…
Wait a minute! Why didn’t you
just ask at the beginning!?
If we had, you wouldn’t
have tried as hard.
WHAT?!
Eriol decided that
this was the best way.
We didn’t know what
the new card mistress was like
and this would work no matter what.
Right, Sakura-chan?
Y… yes.
Do you get it now?
I GOT IT!
Thank you.
I understand it all now.
As the new mistress,
I had to refresh the cards with my magic.
That’s not quite all.
There were other things
I couldn’t predict.
What kind of things couldn’t you predict?
Uh. What kind of…
Don’t worry about it.
I’ll have to keep those a secret.
Actually, there’s another
guest you should meet.
I wonder who it could be.
I don’t know who.
She has been waiting to see you.
Please come in.
Ah!
Mizuki-sensei!
The shrine lady?
It’s been a long time.
Why are you here?
You knew? About Eriol?
Yes.
I met him while
I was at the University in England.
I heard he was Clow Reed’s reincarnation
and thought I might help him.
That’s how you got the bell
he made for the final judgment.
He asked me to deliver it for him.
Thank you very much.
You’re welcome.
Then… when I wrote to you about
the strange things that were happening…
I really wish I could
have told you the truth…
I’m sorry.
So, everything was Clow’s plan.
Not quite.
I’ll go fetch some more snacks.
Now that we’ve changed all the cards,
it’s time to PARTY! LET’S EAT!
Suppi eat too!
AHH!
He’s being weird again!
I’m not weird!
Why don’t you come in, Yue?
I still haven’t heard your answer
to yesterday’s question.
Why did we have to get a new master
if you would be reborn?
I’m surprised you haven’t realized…
Even though I have his memories,
I am not truly him.
He will never fully return.
That is why he left you two
to Sakura-san.
Even so… Even so…
Why couldn’t you have waited, Clow?
It’s not that I don’t like
our new master…
You like her a lot.
But…
Clow is no longer.
But, you still remember him.
You can talk to me whenever you wish.
About he who is so important to you.
Clow…
I am very glad I came here.
To meet Sakura, you and Kerberos.
But there were two things
I couldn’t predict.
The first was you. I could not predict
how your false form’s heart would choose.
I thought Yukito would have
fallen for Sakura-san…
The other was Sakura’s heart.
I couldn’t foresee how
either of them would react.
Yes yes I’m coming.
Yes, Li residence.
Oh my! It has been a while
since we heard from you.
Master Shao Lan,
there is a phone call from your mother.
Eh? From mother?
Hello, this is Shao Lan.
Yes.
And you?
Yes, the Clow cards have all…
Well done!
Next is… let’s see here…
Hey you know what? Yamazaki-kun hasn’t
told a lie since Hiragizawa-kun left…
That’s true…
Aren’t you glad, Chiharu-chan?
It seems a bit strange, I guess.
Sakura isn’t as cheerful
as she used to be, is she?
I wonder what’s wrong.
Do you have a minute?
Um… I…
I got a phone call
from my mother yesterday…
and…
the Clow cards have all been changed
and nothing strange is happening anymore…
Yeah…
Umm… I…
I’m glad I got the chance to meet you.
When I came to Japan,
all I could think of was myself.
My head was filled with the
Clow cards and becoming stronger.
You would do your best
and try your hardest for anyone.
I couldn’t do that.
That’s not true!
Ever since I met you,
you’ve been courageous and helpful…
I couldn’t have done it without you… and…
Thank you.
That’s all I wanted to say. See ya.
Shao Lan! Wait…
I…
I don’t know how I feel about you…
Mizuki-sensei has returned.
I saw her yesterday.
It seems she knew all about it.
About Clow Reed and all that…
damn, she could have said something…
Still, I’m glad.
He made my false form
Because of that
I met Sakura, and you, Touya.
Sakura-chan?
Did something happen?
Hey, Sakura… what is it?
Do you have a fever?
I’m fine.
You’ve been
so strange since yesterday…
what happened?
I really like you!
I like him too…
but only as a friend?
Is that all?
It seems different.
But it’s different from
how I felt about Yukito too…
Which feeling is it?
Well have you told her yet?
Yeah.
What did she say?
She hasn’t said anything.
What!? Why!? But today’s your last…
It’s ok. I told her how I feel.
It’s not ok.
Geez… how can you let her go?
I’ll talk to you later, Mei Lin.
Hey wait! Shao Lan!
It’s almost time.
Ok.
Let’s go, Wei.
(Touya’s part time job.)
Good morning, Sakura-san.
Good morning.
What’s wrong? You don’t seem happy.
I’ll get it.
Yes, Kinomoto residence.
Oh Tomoyo? What’s wrong?
Don’t you have choir…
I overheard Terada-sensei
talking about it…
Li-kun is going back to Hong Kong
on the 11 o-clock plane today!
He won’t be coming back! Sakura?
Are you listening?
Sakura-chan! Sakura-chan??
Shao Lan-kun is going back…
That can’t be true…
What I feel… to Shao Lan…
Sakura… card?
Shao Lan-kun…
I’ll check your luggage.
Ok.
Will she be mad
that I leave without telling her?
I wonder what her
answer would have been…
I hope it hasn’t caused her trouble…
Shao Lan-kun!
How?
I…
umm…
Shao Lan-sama…
here you go.
Can I have that bear?
=I am a dreamer=
=with power deep inside.=
=My world=
=is made from dreams,=
=love and uncertainty.=
=But something I couldn’t even imagine=
=must be hidden as well=
=Like a tree facing at the sky=
=I stare at you…=
=Wanna find out,=
=wanna realize…=
=“believing”, just with this…=
=everything can be overcome.=
=like singing a song,=
=like a miracle…=
=“missing” changes everything gradually,=
=for sure,=
=for sure…=
=will surprise me!=
I’ll see you again, right?