Morning!
You’re so noisy in the morning.
I’m not noisy.
A monster will shakes the whole
house by just walking around.
I’m not a monster!
Have you gained weight recently?
It’s fall, the season
for monsters to gain weight.
I haven’t gained weight!
It looks like you haven’t
gotten any taller, at least.
This sucks!
One day, I’ll grow big, and for sure…
I’ll squish him for sure!
[Sakura and the Book wih No Name]
Naoko!
Sakura.
It’s lunchtime, right?
Come eat with us.
Yes.
What were you reading?
I borrowed it from the library.
Is it a scary book?
No, it’s a fantasy novel.
Fantasy?
Do you like reading fantasy novels?
It looks interesting.
What kind of story is it?
There’s a dragon, and there’s
a turtle bigger than a mountain!
There’s a story like that from China,
you know.
Mei-ling…
It’s like the one about the
old man who saved his village…
…from a day long siege by 100 horsemen.
Hey, you know where Shao-Lang is?
He’s supposed to eat lunch with me,
but he isn’t around.
If you’re looking for Li,
he was heading towards the roof.
Oh, okay. Thanks!
Shao-Lang!
Mei-ling!
Why’d you disappear even though
you knew I made lunch for you?!
That’s…
Meanie, meanie, meanie, meanie, meanie!
It’s because I felt an aura!
By “aura,” do you mean…
A Clow Card.
Hey, is that any good?
How nice…
A used book store.
Hey, can we go check it out
for a few minutes?
Sure.
Naoko sure is a book lover.
Just a while ago she was praised
by Miss Midori for her reading.
That’s right.
Is there something wrong?
The aura of a Clow Card.
Where is it coming from?
From there I think.
Do you need to go find it?
Yeah…
Sakura, Tomoyo, what’s wrong?
Oh, nothing. We’ll be right there.
Is it alright about the card…?
There are too many people, anyway. We’ll
come back later tonight and find it.
As the Card Captor, right?
I made a new costume for you!
T… Tomoyo…
Huh?
There’s no name on the spine.
Please write the next
chapter of this story.
Sounds interesting.
I’ll get this!
It’s so cute!
I’m so happy…
Your happiness comes pretty easy.
Being with someone you love…
…and being able to take a video of her
wearing cute clothes!
I couldn’t ask for a better situation!
You’ll get a shot of
the super-cool me, too, right?
Are you playing around?
Huh?
You getting in our way again,
brat and little wench?
You’re getting in our way.
You’re too late, anyway.
Shao-Lang noticed the aura of a Clow Card
around lunchtime.
Sakura had noticed by then, too!
Right?
Yeah, but it was when
I was coming home from school…
Yay! Shao-Lang was first!
No way!
Sakura is gonna tell us
where the card is now!
Shao-Lang already knows!
Right, Sakura?
Right, Shao-Lang?
Yes.
Where is it?
Over there…
Just a cat…
I… it ain’t a normal cat…
What?
Fly!
Tomoyo!
Mei-ling!
I don’t taste good!
Let Mei-ling go!
Li!
What’s with this guy?
Eh?
It appears that it likes Li.
Might be the Big card.
“Big”?
“Big,” means enlarge?
Big can enlarge objects.
So where’s the card at?
Over there!
The card!
Hey, let me go!
Hey, quit interfering with Shao-Lang!
Get off of him!
There it is! Sakura,
that’s the Big card!
Sakura, seal it!
Eh?
It’s just a big fish!
Show me some Card Captor courage!
Return to thy true form,
Clow Card!
All right!
You did it!
Here you go.
Oh, geez.
It’s your fault we didn’t get that card.
Are you listening?
That was good.
This book leaves room for a sequel.
Oh, that’s right.
[Please write the next
chapter of this story.]
“Next chapter,” huh?
That’s right…
That card was going
to be Shao-Lang’s!
But what actually happened was…
That was just luck!
Now, now, you two…
If that big cat hadn’t
gotten in our way,
the card would be Shao-Lang’s!
If Sakura hadn’t sealed that card,
you might’ve been
eaten by that cat!
What was that?!
You little wench!
Um…
What’s wrong, Sakura?
Gh… h… h… g…gh…
A ghost?
Yes.
Ghost?
There’s nothing there.
Shuu.
“And so, the princess
didn’t know where she was.”
What’s after that…?
That’s it!
I saw it! I saw it!
Did you see it too,
Mei-ling?
Yeah…
Then it’s not a ghost.
Why?
Because you don’t have
that kind of perception.
Tomoyo, did you see it, too?
Yes.
Tomoyo doesn’t have
magic powers either.
Which means…
It’s not a ghost?
Exactly!
What a relief!
Eh?
W… what’s that?
A panther!
Did it escape from the zoo?
What’s that?
It’s got graffiti-like eyes!
Do Japanese panthers have wings?
I don’t think you’ll find that in a zoo.
There sure are a lot of weird things
wandering around in Japan.
That’s not really…
This could be…
“The panther, hippo
and the others grew wings…”
“… and they enjoyed
the experience of flying.”
“But that’s not all.”
“Other animals
and fish grew wings, too.”
Are these all the work
of a Clow Card?
The only one that could
do this is the Create card.
Create is the one
where if you write it,
it will become reality?
Right. It’s gotta be nearby.
But we didn’t feel it at all.
Yeah, there was only
the Big card’s aura.
Then again, with all this,
someone must be using Create
To make all these things appear.
I wonder if it’s okay to undo all this.
Anyway, it’s a pretty forgiving card,
so I think it’ll be…
Now what?
“And then, finally…”
“… growing wings…”
“… the very, very big King appeared.”
A… a monster!
This is bad.
What should we do?
We can only hope the person
using Create will stop soon.
Oh, no!
It’s heading towards the city.
At this rate,
it’ll crush a bunch of houses!
Lightning, come forth!
Why won’t it stop?
It’s too big.
What? Big? That’s it!
There’s a way!
What?
No! Definitely no!
There’s no other way!
I don’t wanna!
At this rate it’s gonna
wreck the city of Tomoeda!
But…
You mustn’t forget your responsibility
as the Card Captor!
I’m asking you, too, Sakura…
Tomoyo…
Okay. I’ll try it.
That’s great!
This will make a fantastic video!
Give me the size to meet this challenge!
Big!
All right!
That’s fantastic!
This is so embarrassing!
What’re you talking about, Sakura?!
Go and beat that monster!
Hey, you monster!
That’s it, that’s it!
I saw something like this on TV!
The hero stopping the disaster…
I never thought I’d see it for real!
Stay away from me!
Hit it with some kind of beam!
Fight with it
Can she really do it?
I don’t know if Sakura has any way
to beat a monster like that.
Sakura!
Eh?
Time to go to bed.
All right!
Whoever’s using Create has stopped!
Eh!
Sakura,
seal it before
it disappears completely!
Yes.
Return to thy true form…
Clow Card!
Good job, Sakura!
I didn’t know what would happen!
You’re still looking kinda big.
This is so embarrassing!
The book is… gone…
This is a big mystery!
Good morning!
Your bumping around
is noisy again today.
I’m not noisy.
A monster will shake the whole
house by just walking around.
What? No counterattack?
I can step on you anytime.
Eh?
Big!