It’s ok now.
I’m back to my old self.
I know.
I understand.
It’s because of Shao Lan-kun
that I cheered up.
[Sakura, Shao Lan
and the Tsukimine Shrine]
Good morning!
Good morning.
You’re up early today.
I just woke up.
Would you like me to get the newspaper?
Thanks.
I’m glad you’ve cheered up again.
You seemed a little sad recently.
Did I seem strange?
No… but I could tell.
I’m your father after all.
I’m really ok now.
Ok, let’s have breakfast then.
It’s pancakes today!
OK! Has brother woken up yet?
He has the day off today
and he’s been really tired lately…
so he won’t mind sleeping in.
I see.
Ever since he gave
all of his magic to Yukito,
brother has been very tired all the time.
Will orange juice be ok?
Yes!
It’s still a little cold
but going to school early
in the morning feels nice.
Yukito-san isn’t here…
This must be the first time
I haven’t seen him…
It would be very nice to see him…
but not as heart-pounding as before…
just nice.
I’ll have to thank Shao Lan-kun
for helping me.
I wonder what I could for for him?
There’s going to be a festival?
I should ask him to go with me
But he gets cold quickly…
That’s it!
Shao Lan-kun!
Good morning…
Want to go to the festival?
A festival!
There’ll be one this Sunday.
At Tsukimine Shrine.
Would you like to go together?
Oh, or are you busy?
I… I’m not doing anything.
Really?
Yay! So, 6 o’clock Sunday then! Promise?
I’ll go get some water ok?
I’m glad.
Her usual smile is back.
Because of you, it seems.
I… I didn’t do anything…
Ah! Eriol-kun, good morning!
Good morning, Sakura-san!
You’re here early.
I had something to take care of.
You seem very cheerful today, Sakura.
That’s not true.
I’m the same as always!
That cat always sits on the window sill.
I’ve never seen her move from that spot.
I’d imagine that she is still here today…
This is what I thought when I pass there…
and it’s really sleeping there.
Wednesday, 23rd.
Thursay, 24th.
Friday, 25th.
Saturday, 26 th.
That’s it for today.
Sakura-chan, homeroom is over.
What’s going on?
You haven’t been this bad since you
started changing the cards.
It’s nothing really.
Is it something you can’t tell me?
Shao Lan-kun…
Sakura-chan, today you promised we’d
go shopping right?
Let’s go. Bye!
Everything’s ok.
I’ll see you tomorrow in front of
the Shrine at 6, ok?
You saved me Tomoyo-chan.
No problem.
Is it almost finished?
I should be able to finish it today.
What Yukito-san said was true.
But, I was really
sad afterwards.
Shao Lan-kun helped me feel better
so I wanted to do something for him
I’ll do my best.
I’m sure it will be fine then.
Tomoyo-chan, thanks.
You’ve helped me a lot as well.
I really appreciate it.
If anything bad ever happens,
you come to me.
If there’s anything I can do,
I’ll help you.
As long as you’re smiling,
I have nothing to worry about.
I’m happy as long as you are.
Finally!
Finally finished huh?
Looks like I’ll make it.
Thanks for your help, Kero-chan.
Coming!
Someone… help me!
Shao Lan-kun?
Weren’t we going to meet
at the Shrine?
That’s true…
but… yesterday… you…
You were worried about me…
Thank you.
Wait a minute ok?
I’m almost ready.
Hey Kero-chan! Do you want to come too?
I’m too sleepy.
Okay, I’ll bring you back
a souvenir then.
Octopus-yaki, noodle-yaki,
and rice crackers with sauce.
OK!
I’m so glad you’ve cheered up, Sakura.
Uhm… are you ok now? You were so tired.
Yeah I’m ok. I finished it.
Finished?
Here.
It was my first try
so it isn’t very good…
For me?
You made it yourself?
Yeah. I guess you don’t want it…
Wait!
She was sleepy because
she was up late making this…
Th… thank you.
I’m the one who should thank you.
You were the one
who helped me feel better that time.
Let’s go?
Ok! We’re meeting
Tomoyo-chan at the shrine.
Brother and Yukito-san
will join us later.
It’s ok already.
He really seems like a part
of my family now.
Touya are you ok?
It’s just the usual. Don’t worry.
However, I’m glad Sakura invited me.
I know she didn’t feel
for me exactly the same
was as for her father,
but because of the way she felt,
she couldn’t find the person
she was meant to love.
I know it hurts her…
but it was for the best.
She was smiling…
but I’m sure she wasn’t
really happy to see me.
I’m sure she’s forgiven you.
She’s cheerful again.
That’s why she has invited you.
Tomoyo-chan!
Sakura-chan!
I’m so glad I get to take videos again
That scarf looks very nice on you!
I don’t see her.
Maybe she isn’t here yet.
It’s Brother and Yukito-san! Over here!
Good evening, Yukito-san.
Good evening, Sakura-chan.
Let’s go Yukito-san!
It’s very good that
she’s gotten over it so soon.
Yeah…
You still haven’t told her have you?
About how you feel.
If I told her, it would just confuse her.
She loved him for so long,
but he loved someone else…
She wouldn’t know how to react either.
She knows
what it’s like to be turned down.
If I told her how I felt,
she’d be too afraid of hurting me
to really think it over.
So… I won’t tell her yet
Li-kun.
Tomoyo-chan! Shao Lan-kun!
Coming!
Why did I have to
buy one for that brat too?
Why does he bother you so much?
I can’t afford to ignore him.
Why?
He’s too involved with
something important to me.
Oh brother!
What do you want?!
Don’t surprise me like that!
I’m thirsty, could you get some juice?
For Yukito-san and Tomoyo-chan
and Shao Lan-kun and me!
You want me to pay again?
We’ve walked pretty far,
so we’ll wait over there.
– So why do I…
– Thank you!
Hey wait a minute…
He’ll need help, so I’ll go with him.
Should I help you too?
We’ll be ok. Wait by the lake.
OK.
Hmph. Why did I have to buy
one for that brat too?
What is it?
You didn’t sense her coming just then.
You used to be able to tell
if anyone was nearby…
until you gave me all your strength.
And you’ve been so tired…
Yuki,
while eating lunch,
when you had finished yours
and were still hungry,
what did I do?
You have me all of yours.
It’s the same thing.
– Don’t worry about it anymore ok?
– Right.
This is the moon pool.
There aren’t any fish are there?
There’s a lake with fish that way.
They use this lake
to tell fortunes with the moon
so there aren’t
any living things in here.
You know a lot!
Mizuki-sensei told me!
Do you know how to tell fortunes well?
Yeah, she told me that too.
First, walk to the edge of the dock.
Clasp your hands.
Then look at the moon
reflected in the water.
Huh?
I’ve been quiet recently.
Clow-san’s aura.
Watch out!
Sakura-chan!
Oh key that hides
the power of the stars.
Reveal thy true form to me.
By our contract,
Sakura commands you.
Release!
Wood!
What happened?
A blackout
Aren’t the power lines
for the Shrine near the lake?
That’s where Sakura and her friends are!
Let me try to beat it.
God of lightnig, come forth!
It didn’t work.
But it did affect it.
It isn’t strong enough.
But… somehow…
that’s it!
Since you’re here to help,
I’m sure we can do it.
Alright!
Let’s do it!
God of wind, come forth!
Now!
Card created by Clow.
Listen to my words and be reborn!
I, Sakura command you.
Thunder!
I’m relieved.
I couldn’t have done
it without your help,
thank you.
Tomoyo-chan? Tomoyo-chan!
Yes! I’m alright!
Sakura!
Sakura.
Are you ok?
We’re ok.
The lights are all gone.
I guess the festival
is over for tonight.
But it just started… Oh!
Wait just a minute ok?
Hey Sakura!
Card created by Clow.
Listen to my words and be reborn!
I, Sakura command you.
Glow!
What’s this?
Pretty!
They’re not fireflies are they?
It’s beautiful isn’t it?
Sakura probably.
Sakura isn’t it?
The Glow card.
Li-kun?
You’re a really kind person.
I know you’ve never hurt Sakura.
And nothing would keep her
upset for very long either.
If you tell her how you feel,
I’m sure she’ll feel the same way
and tell you so in her own way.