I’m so sorry.
I set my alarm to a wrong time…
G’morning.
G’morning, Father.
G’morning, Touya, Sakura…
Oh? I thought today’s breakfast is my…
We just ate. This is yours.
It’s ready. Eat.
Thank you.
You didn’t sleep much
last night, did you?
From today on, let us do the housework.
The academic meeting
is next week, right?
Thank you. And thanks for the food.
[Sakura and Her Kind Father]
Here’s your lunch.
Oh? Lunch? This…
Somehow I felt confident today.
Thank you.
I won’t be as busy next week.
Don’t worry about it.
Isn’t it about time already?
Oh?! Then, I gotta go.
Take care.
I made lunch and did the dishes.
A perfect score today.
Oh? You’re leaving already?
Morning practice.
I’m meeting up with Yuki.
Wa… Wait! I’m going too!
Father, Keep it up at work!
Okay!
The total comes to 700 yen.
Can I have a bag for this?
Oh, you two are doing the housework?
Yeah. Father said he’ll be reading
A very important paper
at this academic meeting.
That’s why Touya and
I discussed and decided to do that.
We would do all the housework
so Father can concentrate on
work just this week.
When is the research announcement?
Next Monday. That’s why it seems
that now is the busiest time.
That is very nice of you two.
Teamwork from you and your brother.
It’s not that big of a deal.
Oh, how about this book?
Then I will take this too…
With this many, I think I will do fine.
Thank you very much.
But what are you doing with
all these books about flowers?
Recently, I have come
to a bit of deadlock…
I was thinking of
doing some research for a new motif.
Mo… Motif?
Of course!
This is for your costume design!
Eh!
Because you made all
the effort to wear them for me…
I must always put in
new thoughts and ideas.
Tomoyo…
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, I came to
pick up a pre-ordered book…
May I have your name please?
Kinomoto.
Yukito!
Touya asked you to get
it for him, didn’t he?
Yeah. His club practice
has gotten a little long.
It looks like your
father needs this book
in a hurry…
Oh, then it’s a
book Father pre-ordered.
Thank you very much.
Not at all. I heard from Touya that
you worked very hard for your father.
It wasn’t anything at all…
Here it is.
Thanks.
I’m sure everything will go well.
Because you put in all
these efforts to help.
See you later.
Yukito…
Father is working
late tonight too…
Sakura…
Did you fold the laundry?
Yeah, I finished
it a while ago.
Okay. Then, I’ve one
more thing for you.
What is it?
Can you bring Father
his midnight snack?
Okay!
Father’s still working,
so don’t stay in there for too long.
Also, it’s getting late,
so go to sleep!
I came to bring you midnight snack.
Maybe I’ll eat it now.
It’s good to take a little break.
It’s good.
Are you almost done?
I’m just about done gathering data,
but putting them
together will take a while.
I’ll be fine.
I’ll just have to stay at the university
for two to three days,
and I can probably
finish it at home on Saturday.
I give you and
Touya so much trouble,
next week after
the announcement is over…
Don’t worry about things like that.
Just concentrate on work.
Thanks.
So, what kind of people
are you presenting this to?
Are there going to be
lots of famous people?
How should I put it…
Those people attending
aren’t any famous people in particular.
Yes!
We live in a big world,
and it has been a long time
since human beings were born.
But what we know is
actually very little.
Living in different countries,
speaking different languages,
those people who lived
in different times
We hardly know anything about them.
That’s why this is what
I do for work.
Things about the ancient times,
about the ancient countries.
I want to learn about them,
research on them.
And then, I announce my result, because
I want to tell someone about them.
Rather than keeping something
you enjoy to yourself,
it’s more fun to let
everyone know about it, right?
Yeah!
Thanks for the midnight snack.
One more day of hard work
and it should be done.
Now, you need to get up
early tomorrow too, right?
Yeah. Good night.
G’night.
Goin’ to your father’s school?
Why don’t you come along too?
I don’t need to study.
I’m already so smart.
No, I’m thinking of bringing
him some snacks.
He’s staying there overnight and
probably even has a change of clothes.
Oh, maybe I’ll ask Tomoyo
to come with me too.
Tomoyo too?
Oh, she’s gonna bring cookies, right?
All you care is the food.
Okay, it’s decided!
Let’s go to the university on Saturday!
But I’m glad for you, Sakura.
Eh!
The entrance exams to the
university must be real hard, right?
You can get in without takin’ the exam,
aren’t you lucky or what?
What do you mean by that…
Universities are really big.
I wonder where your father is.
Um… The department of history
in the faculty of literature…
Let us ask someone.
Thanks very much for coming with me.
Not at all. I am happy to be
able to come with you.
Oh, that’s right. Thanks to the
books I bought yesterday,
I had a nice idea for your new costume.
It is very cute.
Do you need some help?
Um… I would like to get to
the faculty of literature…
Faculty of literature?
Yes.
Who do you need to see
from the faculty of literature?
Kinomoto from the department of history.
Oh? Professor Kinomoto?
Do you know my father?
Oh, you are Professor
Kinomoto’s daughter?
Yes, I’m Sakura Kinomoto.
You’re cute.
Hey, Sakura,
do you want to see your
father’s lecture?
Is that really okay?
Look, over here.
In this way, the ancient,
which spreaded agriculture
that originated from
Mesopotamia to Europe,
has a very important implication.
The widespread
knowledge of how to grow
wheat, barley,
and soya bean,
and even things
like pottery and ceramics…
…could be seen distinctively…
Your father is wonderful.
Professor Kinomoto’s
lectures are popular.
He made them really interesting.
When I first came
to this university,
I never thought history
is this interesting.
We are
Professor Kinomoto’s assistants.
We help him with various
research projects.
I see.
Um… Thanks for helping Father
out all this time.
Not at all.
We thank him for helping us too.
Lecture is almost over.
Now, let’s go.
Come in!
Professor Kinomoto,
your daughter is here.
Sakura?
Sorry for bothering you.
Hello.
Oh my God. Why do you come…?
We brought snacks.
Thanks for taking the trouble,
Sakura, Tomoyo.
I’m in here too!
Professor, we’ll be in the
data research room.
Data research room?
As you see,
just myself and these books are
already taking lots of space here.
The three of them use the data
research room next door.
They’re all staying behind
to help out with this.
It sounds like very tough work.
Not really, we’ll be fine.
Thanks to them,
things are wrapping up here.
Sakura, you guys also helped a lot.
I didn’t really do anything at all.
But I’m glad.
You work so hard all this time,
I was thinking what if you
can’t make it in time.
Sakura…
Father…
Maybe he is tired…
I’m sorry. I didn’t have much sleep,
that’s why…
Father is sleepy.
It’s probably because
of the all-nighters.
But Kero seemed to be asleep all along.
What are you talkin’ about?!
I was desperately hidin’!
I didn’t fall asleep!
Then what’s that mark of the basket
on your cheek?
But I wonder if there is
anything else I can help with.
Right.
How about bringing them coffee
to help them stay awake?
That’s a good idea!
Thank you very much!
It looks like Father isn’t in here.
It does not seem so.
Come in!
Oh, it’s Professor Kinomoto’s daughter.
Excuse me, Father wasn’t there.
He left the room just for a little bit
to talk to another professor.
I see. Oh, I brought coffee
for everyone. Please help yourself.
Thanks.
They fell asleep?
They are all tired.
I wonder why. Just a second ago,
they were…
Kero, this is…
It’s a Clow Card!
I’m sure it’s in this room!
There it is!
That’s Sleep!
If its powder falls on you,
you’d feel sleepy!
Then just now, when Father
was feeling sleepy…
There’s no mistake.
Sleep doesn’t care
and would make anyone fall asleep.
No way!
If I don’t seal it quickly,
Father will never finish his work!
Key which hides the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me!
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release!
Eh!
What’s wrong?!
I did not bring Sakura’s
new costume with me.
Watch out!
Tomoyo!
Jump !
Return to thy form which thou should be!
It went outside!
Everyone is asleep!
Crap!
Where is it?!
Over there!
Windy !
Return to thy form which thou should be!
Clow Card!
That hurts.
Did you seal Sleep?
It was a success, wasn’t it?
What’s wrong?
Father’s work…
Crap…
Maybe there’s a card I can use
to restore this back to the original…
Sakura…
I tried every single card!
But none of them worked…
It would’ve been nice if the cards could
solve any problem.
There are things even cards
and magics wouldn’t work.
Father…
Oh? Sakura?
What’s wrong?
I thought that you were sleepy,
so I brought you some coffee…
I’m sorry…
I’m sorry… for messing up your work…
There’s nothing you can do
if something is ruined.
Come on. Smile.
I wonder where is that coffee
you brought in for me.
Father…
Let’s go home together after
I’m done with the coffee.
Sakura, how long are you
gonna stay awake?
Your father has already forgiven you,
you know?
But…
Things about the ancient times,
about the ancient countries.
I want to learn about them,
research on them.
Father…
G’morning.
That’s early for you on a Sunday.
Where is Father?
He’s awake but he said he was
gonna tidy up his room.
Is it?
Touya?
You won’t have energy if you don’t eat.
Yes!
It hurts.
It’s hard to tidy up
since I have so many
things scattered around.
It’s okay.
Just leave them where they are.
Father… I’m really sorry!
Sakura.
If there’s anything I can do,
just tell me.
If it’s something I can do,
I’ll do it.
Please!
Sakura.
I thought about it last night,
but the paper for the
announcement is almost done.
But I ruined it…
I still have the contents of
the paper… in here.
If I work on it all day today,
I might be able to finish it on time.
But I need the help of a
capable assistant.
I’ll help you!
Then you’ll be my assistant for one day.
Let’s work hard together.
I’ll work hard.
I’ll do my very best for it!
Then, what should I do?
Tell me. Tell me.
You finished it.
Father…
Then I’ll be going!
Take care.
I wonder if Father
hasn’t gotten any sleep.
He was more afraid
of being tempted to fall
asleep like you did.
You’re mean!
Oh? You’re leaving already?
Morning practice.
I’m meeting up with Yuki.
Wait! I’m going with you!
He had a little bit of spare time.
If he had time for this,
he should’ve just rest for a little.
(Thank you, Sakura. Work hard!)
Father…
Hey! Wait for me!