There were many sheep
in the grassland.
They had white hair,
soft and warm.
This girl walked quietly
near the sheep,
because she didn’t want to
terrify the sheep.
But, when the sheep
found the little girl,
they ran away quickly.
Are you alright, Sakura?
I’m fine, I’m fine.
The girl’s voice made
the sheep more afraid.
And run faster.
They jumped over the fence.
Faster and faster.
The girl followed the little sheep
like she was dreaming.
She ran faster and faster.
One sheep, two sheep…
three sheep…
And finally
when the girl came
very near to the sheep,
she fell down…
Li-kun…
What’s the matter, Kinomoto-san, Li-kun?
Excuse me.
[Sakura’s Sheep Alert?!]
What? A gigantic teddy bear?
Yes, somehow, Clow’s aura
made the teddy bear grow huge.
It was really pretty scary.
Why did that happen?
Sorry, but it really
had nothing to do with me.
Next time, be more alert!
Okay. I promise.
Here you go!
These are newly introduced
by my mom’s company.
Please accept them.
Here’s one for Sakura
and one for Kero.
Thanks.
And here’s one for Li.
Ah!
I can use this to contact you later.
I feel sleppy…
I’ve been feeling sleepy a lot lately.
It can’t be helped.
The conversion of Clow cards
must have been tough on you.
And Kero, too.
Sakura Cards.
By the way!
After the conversion,
the magic of the Clow cards
will be completely yours, right?
Looks like that…
That’s
why those new Sakura card
deserve their
own characteristic pose!
Characteristic… Pose…?
Certainly! Certainly!
I really feel that you should
create one as soon as possible
For Sakura, so cute,
so beautiful, so elegant.
This should come ever so naturally!
Come!
Let’s practice!
All in all,
it’s been pretty tough
on you, hasn’t it, Sakura?
But
it’s also been pretty rough
on him over there.
Somehow…
I can’t seem to
eat enough these days…
As of late…
I have been strangely tired… and…
Sleepy…
Yuki…
Huh? Touya!
So your soccer meeting’s ended?
Touya…
Yes.
Ah!
Sorry!
What?
Yuki,
Well, you know,
you are well-liked and popular…
…even if you don’t know
you’re popular.
I…
If you don’t need me…
then you will become…
Why should I not need you?
You know what I mean, dumbass!
I… I…
I what?
I’m sleeping.
I heard your voice, Touya.
Ar, Touya,
the teacher was calling
for you earlier.
So hurry up, will you
Akizuki…
Nakuru!
You turned up here deliberately,
didn’t you?
And what’s wrong with that?
Later.
See you in class!
Just as I though, he knew
what I was thinking all along.
He’s pretty sharp.
You may not realize it,
but you do sleep a lot.
So, don’t interfere, ok?
…and we practice
my new pose all the way…
And?
How’s the pose coming along?
Is that a good pose?
I’m not sure, but…
Tomoyo is really enthusiastic,
isn’t she?
But,
why do I have to convert the Clow Cards?
And what does this piece
of paper have to do with all of this
Let me see…!
This…
My opponent is a magic user,
too, right?
Well… Well…
What’s wrong, Sakura?
So what if it’s
another magic users
Watch me trash them all the same!
Cheer up, will you?!
Yeah, I should!
Coming!
Good evening, Sakura.
Yukito!
Please come in!
Actually, I just came
today to deliver this.
Here…
Touya forget to take it with him.
Can you pass it to him?
Sure.
I can see Yukito one more time.
Don’t behave like that, okay?
Y… yes.
If this goes on…
he can’t return to his original form.
That’s because Yue depends on
Sakura’s magical power.
Yukito faints frequently
and his vonacious appetite is useless.
All these new things…
These new cards
who give their all for her
My symbol is the Sun
and my powers are self-sufficient.
But…
Its light fills me with strength.
So I’m not dependent on anyone’s power.
At this rate,
I will fade away.
and Yukito
will vanish along with you.
Sakura will be really sad.
In the last incident,
it was Clow’s presence that we felt,
wasn’t it?
I’m not sure.
But, if I’m not mistaken,
I think I felt the same presence too.
But these incidents are getting
increasingly dangerous.
The enemy is quite skillful…
Yes
But, Yukito…
Kero! Would you like some snacks?
Hoee! Oh.
It’s you, Kero.
Somehow.
I’m not used to seeing you so big yet.
I’ll change back to Yukito.
Yue! It’ll be terrible
if I get seen in this form!
Did I blank out again just now?
It’s really tough hiding
the truth from Yukito.
You’ve just been lucky to be able
to deceive Yukito for so long
What do you mean by that?!
Ah! Li?
Huh? The park?
Got it… I’m going now.
I expected it would end up like this…
Of course!
Not only is this going
to be a great video,
but to film it on this
beautiful night out in the park…
It makes my heart melt
just to think of it.
It’s a special evening dress, isn’t it?
I never did understand
what’s up with the two of you
Anyway,
do you see where this strange
aura is coming from?
You feel it too, Li,
Clow’s aura.
I sense a powerful magical aura,
but I really don’t
know if it’s Clow’s.
I would really want to see
who our opponent is.
– Is that so.
– Do you understand me?
It’s strongest
in the vicinity of the penguin
What’s matter?
Somehow… The penguin…
It seems different from
the way it used to be.
What?
What the heck is this?
This is pretty huge!
Who could have done this?
I feel it… Inside this hole…
Clow’s aura…
Guess we should go have a look.
Right!
So! Let’s witness the debut
of your new Signature Pose!
– Tomoyo!
– Let’s go! Sakura.
Let’s see the release thing
we did earlier.!
O Key which hides the power of the stars,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release!
Fly!!
Great! I’m coming, too!
What’s this?
King of Thunder.
Obey my order!!
Look here. You brat!
What were you trying to pull off?
In that case,
Get BACK!
Such power… Don’t tell me it’s Clow’s.
Just as I thought…
Clow’s aura…
Hey, Kero…!
Kero?
Hoe!! I’m so scared to be alone!!!!
A stuffed animal?
Isn’t.
this Mr.Sheep from my textbook?
Hoe! What’s Mr.Sheep
doing here, anyway?
It’s Sakura’s voice!
What’s happening? Sakura!
Damn!
Ah. That kid is really going at it…
Clow Reed’s spells.
Their forms are practically endless.
Flattery… That kid tries hard,
that’s his good point.
This hurts.
What should I do now?
Which card should I convert now?
If I use watery,
I’d be in worse trouble.
Firey will do me in as well.
How now?
Oh! That’s right!
O Card created by Clow,
Discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
Erase!
Well done.
The power’s aura… vanished.
– Sakura.
– Sakura-chan!
Are you alright?
Thank goodness.
Thanks.
I feel bad for making you worry.
What happened there?
Somehow, many sheep appeared.
Sheep?
Yes. They were stuffed dolls.
Dolls again… huh?
And how was it inside?
Indeed,
I sensed Clow’s presence in there.
But…
What do we do with this now?
Whatever we do,
we have to return
the penguin to its original position.
To move the penguin…
It’s Power card, isn’t it?
Let’s see you do your
Signature Pose Variation No.2!
Li-kun! Kero -chan!
Turn to look over there.
Why?
Just do it!
Don’t you ever… EVER…
look here, okay?
It’s so wonderful!!
I feel sleepy.
Sakura-chan!
Sakura.
Hang in there!
It’s been fun, hasn’t it,
Eriol?
Yes. Indeed.
It will get even
more enjoyable from now on.