We can’t catch up!
It’s definitely “Dash”!
When it’s about speed nobody can win it!
Then, can we really catch it?
Don’t worry!
It’s only good at short-range.
We’ve come to a clearing!
Windy!
Got it!
Oh no, if it keeps trying to get away,
it’ll get hurt!
What a pity!
[Sakura and the Injured Card]
I think it came this way.
Sakura, do you feel its aura?
I feel it coming from there,
but it’s really weak.
It was struggling really
hard against Windy earlier.
It’s just over this wall, huh?
Here’s your chance to catch it.
I must look like a thief.
Someone’s coming!
Over here, was it?
Yes, there was
a weird looking girl
coming out of the park.
A girl?
Right, and she had
a weird outfit on, too!
Weird?
I think it’s cute.
Shuu!
We’ll have to give up for now.
Dash is probably hurt,
so it can’t be too far from here.
Right.
Rei, what did you say?
Something came over the wall.
I think it was that cat.
Don’t be scared. Come here.
What’s wrong?
Are you hurt? Hang on a sec!
There you go.
What kind of animal are you?
I’ve never seen anything like you.
How cute!
The aura of that Clow Card…
That looks great!
But why baseball?
It’s your way in.
How’s your leg?
Excuse me! Could I get my ball?
Did you lose this ball?
Don’t you know
You’re not supposed to
play baseball in the park?
That’s right,
I’m in a baseball uniform.
Don’t worry, I won’t tell anyone.
Here’s your ball.
Be careful from now on.
I will. Thank you very much.
The plan failed, didn’t it.
That’s the way it is.
I’ll come back after school.
Thanks for waiting!
Here.
Thanks.
Actually, I thought of a new plan.
What kind?
This time… Over there…
She’s the one from this morning.
Ready!
Start!
Go for it!
Hello there.
You’re the baseball
girl from this morning.
You’re in the cheerleading club?
Yep!
Tachibana…
…your turn again in the 100 meters.
Okay!
Doesn’t look too good.
Ready!
Start!
So fast!
That’s great, Tachibana!
A personal best!
Really?
13.2.
That’s great, Rei!
Beat it by a full second! Wow!
Sakura…
So this Rei girl was
aided by the Card, huh?
Dash’s power is running fast, after all.
This just makes it harder to seal it.
Oh!
We meet again.
I’m home!
Welcome home.
You know, today I ran a great race!
Really? That’s great!
Your friends?
Oh, from Tomoeda Elementary, um…
4th grade class 2, Kinomoto Sakura.
Elementary School Track
and Field Tournament?
Yeah, I haven’t been running well lately,
so I didn’t have much confidence…
…but I turned things around today!
So you entered?
If I run like I did today,
I might have a chance!
You were really fast!
Thanks. It’s all thanks to Pee Wee.
Pee Wee?
It jumped in here last night.
It looks a lot like that stuffed animal,
if it were alive.
It was hurt yesterday,
so I put it in a cage.
Hurt?
It feels like my fast running today
was because of Pee Wee.
It’s the Card’s influence.
Weird, isn’t it?
That’s not it at all!
It’s your good luck charm, right?
Yeah. Sakura,
is yours like a good luck charm, too?
Um, a good luck charm
or a mascot, or…
Oh yeah! Do you guys
want to meet Pee Wee?
Eh!
Here’s our chance!
That’s right! I need to buy
some stuff for dinner!
Please let us see it next time!
O… okay…
Thanks for having us over.
Good luck at the Track
and Field Tournament, OK?
Come again.
Sure.
We were so close.
I can’t seal the Card
in front of Rei, anyway.
Maybe so,
but we can’t leave the card
with that girl either.
Yes.
I guess we have
to try to sneak in again.
But…
What’s wrong?
Don’t be scared.
Everything’s all right.
13 seconds flat?!
I did it! I did it!
Another school record, right?
Yep!
Fast, isn’t she?
They say she should win the 100 meters
at the next Track and Field Tournament.
Wow. She’s a 6th grader, right?
What’s her name?
Tachibana Rei.
She’s faster than the boys, isn’t she?
Speaking of the Track
and Field Tournament…
…they say she’s looking very good.
Oh,
Sakura.
W… what?
We’re going to the tournament next week.
Eh?
The cheerleading club is going to
The Track and Field Tournament to root.
Really…
Let’s go root for Tachibana!
Okay!
Rooting? “Rooting” you see,
comes from the ancient Roman
classics… In war, the sea would
overwhelm many boats.
When people cried for help,
an angel would lend a hand.
As more and more ships heard about this,
they’d cry out more.
Their cries for help became known
as today’s “rooting.”
Another lie.
It’s true. I hear that…
Working hard, I see.
Let’s call it a day.
Okay.
Sakura!
You’re in the cheerleading club, right?
You’re coming to the tournament
next week?
Root for me!
Okay.
Tachibana!
I’ll be right there!
Pee Wee’s gotten a lot better,
so come on over
to see him sometime.
O… okay…
Later!
I guess I can’t do it.
What’re you talking about?!
Let’s wait until after the Track
and Field Tournament to seal it.
Our best chance is
while it’s still weak!
I know that,
but Rei was saying that she’s
running well because of Pee Wee, right?
So let’s wait until after
the tournament to seal it…
If you wait until next week,
the injury will heal
and it’ll be harder than ever to catch!
Don’t worry, I’ll give it my all!
But, Sakura…
Let’s go home.
I understand how you feel, Sakura.
But if not for the magic,
none of this would have happened.
I know.
The Track and Field Tournament
is this Sunday, right?
Yes.
I need to make lunch, right?
I can do it myself.
I have some important things to
take care of at the University…
…so I’ll make your
lunch when I make mine.
You competing?
No, I’m going there to root
with the cheerleading club.
Who’s competing from Tomoeda?
A girl from the 6th grade.
Wow, that’s something.
Actually, last year, Touya qualified
to go to the Interhigh in the 100 meters.
You were in that?
Nope.
But he was good enough to.
He won the school
and the regional tournaments…
but he didn’t go to the Interhigh.
Why not?
Didn’t want to miss work.
Really sounds like Touya, doesn’t it?
Too bad, I would’ve rooted for you.
If you’re rooting for that girl,
I’m sure she’ll do her best.
That would be nice…
Hoo-ray! Hoo-ray! To-mo-e-da!
Tachibana’s about to run!
You’re right!
Wow…
She’s really fast.
Thanks for helping me, Shao Lan.
Shao Lan?
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
If you keep this up,
you’ll do fine in the tournament
day after tomorrow.
I’ll do my best!
All right,
everyone, one more time from the top!
Okay!
Day after tomorrow…
Looks like you healed up just fine.
That’s great!
You know, I set another
school record today.
Ever since you came here,
everything’s been going well.
Hey, Sakura…
you really should seal Dash
Before the tournament.
You can’t let
that girl think she’s fast
because of Dash’s power, can you?
Li-kun?
Over there… is Rei’s house!
Root for me, Pee Wee.
He must’ve found Dash!
I’m positive. It’s this house.
Oh, Pee Wee.
How funny!
That’s…
Don’t!
Dash!
Pee Wee!
Hold it!
Li-kun!
Li-kun, wait!
Lightning, come forth. Attack!
Sakura, seal it!
But if I seal it, Rei will…
Don’t you get it?
If she wins because of magic,
it won’t be due to her own ability!
Is that what you want?!
Can you really
congratulate her for that?!
Sakura!
Hurry up and seal it!
Rei…
What’s wrong?
Sakura!
Release!
Return to thy true form,
Clow Card!
You knew this card
was at that house?
Then why?
Pee Wee! Pee Wee!
Pee Wee, where are you?
You did the right thing.
So, see you tomorrow.
Bye bye!
She did it!
Tachibana made it to the finals!
That’s great!
She’ll be fine,
she practiced so hard.
Next up are the finals
for the girls’ 100 meters.
Be careful at the start.
Right.
Pee Wee…
Rei, go for it!
Ready!
She did it! She did it!
Li-kun!
Did you just use the Dash card?
Do you think that
6th grader got first place
with the power of the Card?
Huh? But…
You can’t use the Card’s
power in that way.
So I didn’t do anything.
Just a little encouragement.
It wasn’t magic,
Rei did it on her own.
The winner of the girls’ 100 meters…
…from Tomoeda Elementary School,
Rei Tachibana!
Go, Go, Ta-chi-ba-na!
Sakura!
Rei, congratulations!