Eriol, dinner is almost ready.
Ok.
What are you writing?
Can you understand it?
It’s been a long time
since we’ve seen her.
It’s almost over.
Sakura-san’s magic
has become much stronger.
She should be able to do it soon.
Hey! Hurry up or
your stew will get cold!
Ok, I’m coming.
Really, you two just
don’t appreciate the work
I put into things… hey…
Look! Look! Look!
[Sakura, the Past, and Clow Reed]
Damn! What’s with this snow!?
I guess that won’t work.
I can’t just keep running.
I have to do something about them.
All right, if you want
to play snow with me…
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
Snow!
Snow! Destroy all these little snowmen!
Sakura has managed to defeat us again…
Keep it up… for a little while longer.
Sakura-san.
Sakura-chan!
Tomoyo-chan! Shao Lan-kun!
Are you ok?
I’m sorry I missed it.
I made you a new costume too!
Promise you’ll wear it next time,
pretty please!
I’m not really sure whether
there will be a next time…
That’s okay!
You’ll manage.
That’s right, soon all of the cards
will be Sakura Cards.
It looks like you’ve become
as strong as Clow himself.
No way…
Don’t you think so kid?
Y… Yeah…
No… not yet… Clow
is still much stronger.
Why do you always have
to be so depressing?
I’m just saying what’s true.
Clow-san…
What’s wrong? Can’t sleep?
Yeah. Say, Kero-chan…
what was Clow-san like?
Why this all of a sudden?
I been thinking…
Earlier you said it’s good that
my magic is growing so quickly…
But Yue keeps saying “Not yet”
and…
Well, Yue still misses Clow a lot.
Don’t you remember him?
I’ve forgotten a lot over the years…
Is that so…
You know, it was a very long time ago.
You’re our mistress now.
But I’m not as strong as him yet!
I’ll do my best
when strange things happen…
But if Clow-san was here,
I’m sure he could do better.
I wonder if it’s really so good
that I’m your mistress…
What are you saying?
Of course it’s good!
But…
Clow was Clow and you are you.
There’s no point
in comparing the two of you.
Now stop worrying
about it and get some sleep.
Today reminds me
a lot of that day…
That day?
Oh! Did I say that out loud?
Since you reminded me of him,
I rememberd the day he died…
– The day Clow…
– Yeah.
It was about this time of year…
It was snowing just like today.
He didn’t seem very old
He’d just come to the end of his life,
or so he said.
Up until the end…
We never saw him die.
What is it? You look so surprised.
Could he still be alive? If he is…
Of course not… forget it, forget it.
There’s no way he would have left
Yue or me if he was.
But why then do we always sense his aura
when something strange happens?
Um… that’s…
could he have done
something before he died?
I should go and ask him!
Ask who?
Clow-san!
Eh? You’re going to use the Return card?
Yes, I’m going back
to the past to talk with Clow.
He might know something
about what’s going on.
But the Return card
requires a lot of magic!
If something were to happen…
Kero-chan said it would be ok
if we use the power of the cherry
tree at the Tsukimine Shrine.
Shao Lan: Still!
You shouldn’t risk it!
Thank you.
For worrying about me.
You ready?
Return!
I’m off ok?
Please be careful!
I’ll surely come back. I promise. I
promise on this spot that if I say a lie…
May a thousand needles prick me
till I die.
I’ll see you later then.
Okay.
Please, take me to a
time just before Clow died.
Clow-san…
Where is this?
Oh? Is that Kero-chan over there?
What is it, Kerberos?
Oh Yue…
Even though it’s spring,
this cherry tree isn’t blooming anymore…
That’s too bad.
I guess it isn’t time yet.
When will it be then?
At that time.
What’s that supposed to mean?
I wonder if it’s ok.
I wonder what Kero-chan
and Yue-san are doing?
They’re waiting.
Umm… Clow-san! I’m…
Please…
Is that better?
Geez, of course it is.
Kero-chan and Yue-san look so happy.
They both look very happy…
Did you sleep well?
Clow! Umm… I’m…
This is a quiet place
to rest during the day.
Umm there’s something
I’d like to ask you…
um… you see…
About the future?
Eh? Um… yeah.
What is it you wanted to ask?
Uh, well, you see, strange things
are happening and…
we always feel your aura
when they appear.
So I was wondering
if you had done anything?
If I will, I did.
If I won’t, I didn’t.
What’s that mean?
Clow! No, don’t use the Bubble card!
Stop… please… heh heh…
Oh dear.
It’s nice here, isn’t it…
Very peaceful.
And how are you?
Do you like these children?
I love them! Kero, Yue,
and the cards!
But… but I’m not you after all…
Please wait! Clow-san!
The summer is over so soon.
Each season passes into the next.
Have you ever thought
about how sad it is?
I have.
Because I am just like season
that passes into next very soon.
Oh! Clow-san!
Huh?
That chair
is the same one as the one
in Eriol-kun’s house.
Explain yourself Clow!
What does this mean?
It’s as I told you Yue.
I will leave this world today.
That’s not something to joke about…
I’m sorry, it is not a joke.
Why!?
It is my time.
Your time?
Impossible.
You’re the world’s greatest magician.
You made us!
Even so, everything must die, in time…
Even me.
Why!?
There will come someone
who will care for you in my place.
I don’t want anyone else.
Then this person shall
require your approval.
I wouldn’t approve of anyone else!
It won’t just be up to Yue,
You’ll have to approve as well,
Keroberos.
Are you serious?
You two and the Clow cards
used all my effort and magic to create.
So, I sincerely hope that you guys
will be happy with your new master
after I am gone.
That is my final wish.
Every life comes to an end at some point.
Even ours.
It is a part of being alive.
What happened to Kero-chan
and Yue-san?
That is why I’m glad that
you have become their new mistress.
But I’m…
No… but you’ll do fine.
Please take care of them.
Ok? Sakura-san.
I can’t do it!
I can’t become you!
I don’t want them to forget about you…
but… but I’m not you…
That’s what I expected.
You are you.
I don’t expect you to be me.
There are many things
that only you can do.
Only me?
We can’t live in the past forever.
The future is always ahead of us.
The winter is over.
A new spring has begun.
Don’t worry.
I am me, and you are you.
That is the way things
are supposed to be.
Are you ok, Sakura?
Are you hurt?
No.
Did you see him?
Don’t tell me you didn’t…
No… I met him…
But, I didn’t get a chance to ask him…
What were you thinking!?
But,
why was everyone at Eriol’s house?
Huh? Eriol, your classmate right?
That’s impossible! Clow died…
Oh, yes… I seems have seen him before…
You didn’t remember?
My member deteriorates…
Yue was at Eriol’s house…
But he didn’t say anything…
Could their memories have been altered?
But who would…
Clow Reed.
Eriol-kun!
What are you?
I am currently known as Eriol.
But I used to be called Clow Reed.