“This is a weird feeling.
As if looking through a binocular,
everything is small,” said Alice.
That’s right.
Alice who had become
about 10 inches tall,
her face lit up
when she discovered than
she can now walk through the small door
which leads her to a
beautiful garden on the other side.
Shortly, from a distance
there were footsteps
which grabbed Alice’s attention.
There she found a white rabbit
who was dressed up
with one hand in a white glove
and the other holding
a large pocket watch,
talking to himself
and running in a hurry.
“Oh the Queen…
I made the Queen wait like this
I’m in trouble,” cried the rabbit.
As it went by,
Alice started a conversation by saying
“Excuse me”
in a tiny muttering voice.
Use it as a bookmark.
Eriol-kun.
[Sakura and the Sakura in Wonderland]
Sakura-san,
what are you reading?
– This.
– Oh, Alice?
Yeah,
have you read it?
quite a while ago.
Isn’t it fun? Becoming little
and then big and all.
But it spells trouble.
Don’t come any closer!
Didn’t know my bathroom was this big…
Hoeee!! Don’t come any closer!
What’s wrong?
Oh it’s nothing.
Ahh, this is an English fairy tale
from where you used to live, right?
Yeah.
What’s England like?
Many days, it either rains or is foggy,
but I like it
because the old buildings
are still around.
Really?
There are many gardens and buildings
as illustrated in the book in real life.
Amazing!
Wow… I want to go there.
Shall I take you there?
To Alice’s wonderland…
Ahh… you can feel the love in the air…
Alice’s wonderland
must be England, right
Does that mean that Hiiragizawa-kun
is willing to introduce
Sakura-chan to his family?
Introducing someone to their family
is definitely…
You’re getting more and more jealous!
Home Room is starting!
Ok, thanks.
Reading week is almost at an end.
Can everyone
finish reading the books they chose?
Yes.
What a huge book.
It’s really interesting.
Do you want to read it too
Eh… but I haven’t
even finished reading this book.
and I read slow…
Wow… Yanagisawa… amazing.
Yes.
Oh you don’t say.
I liked this book myself.
Is that right?
I’ll be looking forward
to your book report.
Ok everyone has
to write a report upon
finishing reading their books.
Yes!
What should I do?
Want to stop by somewhere on the way?
Naoko-chan,
what about your piano lessons?
There isn’t much to do today.
What about you Rika-chan?
I’m going to the library
to finish reading this.
Then
should we all go to
the library and read?
Is that ok?
I want to finish
this book up soon too.
– Yeah.
– Ok then, let’s go.
Then shall I read another book?
I’m glad that
Tereda-sensei happens to like that book.
Yeah.
Eriol-kun!
Are you going too?
– Yes.
– Then do you want to go with us?
Ok, sounds good.
What are you reading,
Yamazaki-kun?
Alien transformed into a cat
and is targetting Earth?
– What’s that…
– I’ve read it before.
Wasn’t it fun?
But do you think it’s for real?
Cats who really are aliens.
It’s really true. Right now
2/3 of the cats
on Earth alone are aliens
On top of that
from space not just cats
but other forms like dogs or chickens
or penguins and other various
forms come to earth each year,
about 7000 of them every year
I wonder if there are such things
are goldfish aliens.
Of course!
It was thought for the goldfish alien
because they had to travel
with their suits
filled with water.
Small body,
but the space suit
are tens of kilometers in length.
Wow amazing.
And, that it is a famous story
that the octopus is an alien
You’re working hard.
Hong Kong and Japan
may have same Kanji characters
but the pronunciation
and the meaning could differ so.
I guess so.
Eriol-kun, you can read
without dictionaries?
Sort of.
Did you study Japanese?
– Yes.
– Wasn’t it tough?
I’m quite used to it
since there were people
who used Japanese around me.
Did you have Japanese
friends in England?
No.
Hoe? Then how…
I had some business a while ago…
I’ll go and return this.
Doesn’t Li-kun look angry?
Men are complicated.
Sakura-chan!
What’s wrong?
It’s nothing.
Sakura-chan
got sucked into the book.
What?
I can feel strong magic…
What do we do?
Hoe? These clothes.
Tomoyo-chan!
Where is this place
I was reading a book
at the library just now…
Then…
what else happened again?
I know… am I inside the book?
That’s right!
Over here!
Eriol-kun!
No, I’m the Cheshire cat!
Cheshire cat…
as in from…
Alice in Wonderland?
Yes.
Ahh… I got it! This must be a dream!
You’re wrong!
Then?
Eriol-kun doing something like that…
this is definitely a dream.
It isn’t. I actually like
to fool around a lot
Is that so?
But I have a tought time
trying to restrain myself
from being dragged into
you and Li-kun’s level.
My… level.
Yes.
Then why are you
so serious around me all the time?
Because there are people around you
who know my real self.
I can’t be revealed just yet.
Eh?
Well then… please take your time
in enjoying
– Alice’s wonderland in this book.
– Wait!
What should I do.
If this really is inside the book,
then I need to figure out
how to get out of here…
Must hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry…
Yukito-san!
No, I’m the rabbit.
(Yukito -> snow-rabbit -> rabbit)
Oh, I’m going to be late,
if I don’t hurry.
Where are you going?
Where the Queen is at.
Rabbit who is on his way
to the Queen in a hurry…
this is definitely Alice’s wonderland
in the book.
Must hurry, hurry…
Please wait! Wait!
That’s right…
Um… Yue-san?
It’s faster if I fly.
We’re here.
Sakura-chan.
It’s no use.
Huh? Where is Sakura-chan?
She went back to the classroom to
get something that she’d forgot.
Whew…
Brother?
I am the Mad Hatter.
Drink it?
Yes.
It’s good. That was good!
Oh wait,
if this is Alice’s wonderland,
then there may be potions to shrink me.
I better watch what I’m drinking.
Or it will be very troublesome.
So?
You just drank
the potion to shrink yourself
Li-kun! Thank you!
Hoe???? Why are there two of Li-kun!
I am Twiddle-Dum. I Twiddle-Dee.
Umm… hey Li-kun…
Do you know
how to get out of this world?
Do you want to know?
If you solve this riddle
then I’ll tell you.
Ok! Here is the question.
I have someone that I like.
I don’t have anyone that I like.
Which one?
Do you want this dumpling? Here…
Li-kun likes Yukito-san…
so… Yes!
Bing-bong! Correct!
Last Question
The person I like is taller than me.
The person I like is shorter than me.
Which one?
Since Yukito-san is taller…
TALLER!
Boo! Wrong!
How come?
But Yukito-san is taller than Li-kun!
It’s not Yukito-san?
Dissapeared…
I have to get out of this world!
But when I’m this small
finding the exit is going to be tough
Oh that’s right
Here it is!
Oh Key that hids the power of the stars,
reveal you true form before me.
I Sakura command
Release!
Please… change…
Oh card created by Clow…
lose your form and be reborn…
I command you…
BIG!
I did it! Hoeee!!!
I’m too big
What? A Leaf?
I’ve got to return to my original size.
Oh card created by Clow…
lose your form and be reborn…
I command you…
LITTLE!
Hoe? Where am I?
On the Chess board.
Tomoyo-chan.
I am Humpty-Dumpty.
I am in the middle of a chess game.
Hoe? With whom?
Kero-chan!
Kero-chan,
do you know
how I can get out of this book?
I am not Kero-chan.
You have interrupted my chess game.
Kero-chan…
I am not Kero-chan.
I am the Queen!
What’s going on, Kero-chan!
Call me your majesty!
Wait! I’m not done with you yet!
Ahh! Eriol-kun!
I am the Cheshire cat.
Even in the book,
Cheshire cat knew a lot…
Please tell me
how can I get out of this book?
There’s only one way out.
In other words,
you just have to find
the way you came in.
Huh? Where is the entrance?
You should know it.
Where?
Where did I come
into the book through?
That’s it! The leaf bookmark!
FLY!
Are you not going to listen to me?!
Sakura-chan!
Are you ok?
I barely escaped…
Sorry…
It changed…
WHat is it?
It’s nothing.
Thank you.
You saved me.