[Sakura and memories of her mother]
That day it had gotten really late,
so I thought I would go through the woods
behind the school as a shortcut
A firefly?
Eh!
Sakura-chan
Sorry
Naoko-chan, is that story true?
Yeah
Could you have just mistaken it
with something else?
No
Let’s not talk about this
I can’t handle scary stories
Hey, why don’t we go check
If that story is true
Club ends early today,
so let’s invite Rika-chan
and all go together
Umm Umm Umm!
What?
Isn’t there a cliff inside the woods?
It’s dangerous
As long as you don’t go next to
it everything is OK
But, what if a monster really did come out?
If we run away right away, it will be fine
But
Anyway, it’s OK
Our break is over, let’s go
Why does everybody like scary things?
Even though something scary might happen,
Why do we go?
Ah, Sakura-chan,
what’s wrong?
Tomoyo-chan
Tomoyo-chan, come along!
Yes Yes
Why don’t we go back?
It’s fine There is still light out after all
Yeah, yeah Nothing to worry about
Hey, it’s almost my mom’s birthday.
What do you think would be a good present?
Your mom likes making sweets,
so why not a cute cake dish?
A cake dish?
Sakura-chan, what do you think?
Ah, don’t worry about it
Now that you mention it,
this Sunday is my mom’s
This way
It’s crows
It was right here
Nothing is coming out
I wonder if it has to be night
Scary…
A long haired woman!
A misty form with pointed ears
A swirly thing with one eye
A pink monster with lots of fangs
A giant meat bun
What? I saw was a giant meat bun
I was really scared
What, Sakura, are you scared of ghosts?
I am
Even though you are fine fighting
the Clow Cards?
I just can’t handle things
I don’t really understand
I know where the Clow Cards came from
That’s sort of an indefinite reason
But, didn’t everybody see different things?
I wonder if there’s a card like that
It’s just about time for dinner
OK!
I wish you could hurry and
return to your normal form
and be my body guard
If you want that,
you’d need to get at least
the Fire and Earth cards
My true form is really cool
Cool?
EH!
It looks great!
You like noodles, don’t you?
Yeah
I love this picture
This is from when Mom was sixteen right?
My mother Nadeshiko
She worked as a model
since she was in Jr High
We have all the pictures of her
From magazines,
and the ones that Dad took
Mom really was pretty
Yes, the most beautiful
and kind person in the world
I was only three when my mom died,
so I don’t really remember her
My dad tells me
all sorts of things about her,
So I love my mother
If you don’t hurry and eat, it will get cold
Yeah.
If you don’t hurry,
you’ll miss the bullet train
Yeah, yeah
Are your dad and brother gone?
My brother is at work,
my dad is on a business trip for a seminar
My dad made pudding
You want to eat my brother’s along with me?
Yay! Pudding! Pudding!
Ah, I’ll go pick that up
Hello? Kinomoto residence
Tomoyo chan? What is it?
They went to the woods again?
Yes, Chiharu called me.
This time they went with other club members
They say it appeared again
The ghost
What happened? What happened?
What is the use of the Card Captor
whimpering over a thing like this?
But
Are you all right?
I’m not all right, but
There were girls who got hurt, right?
Yes, I heard that Chiharu went with
about five people
When the ghost appeared they panicked
And people were falling down
If it is a Clow Card, I have to catch it
Now there is the Card Captor that protects
the peace of the neighborhood
But, what should I do if it is a ghost?
Anyway, we can’t tell anything until
we check it out
Well then, shall we precede?
That is…?
Sakura!
Yeah! Fly!
Mom?
Is it really you Mom?
Mom!
What is that?
What’s wrong Sakura?
Kero-chan!
Mom…
Sakura-chan!
That’s a cliff!
Sakura-chan! Sakura-chan!
Sakura-chan!
Sakura is all right
Huh?
Are you awake?
Yukito-san,
Where is this?
It’s my house
Your?
Huh? These clothes?
The ones you were wearing are being washed
Ah, it was my grandma who changed you
Oh yeah, my brother mentioned that
Yukito lived along with his grandmother and
Um, thank you very much
You fell from the cliff
Do you remember?
No…
I see…
But it surprised me.
I was walking along the road
and Sakura came floating from the sky
So you
Where is Tomoyo-chan?
A group of women wearing sunglasses
came to pick her up
She was very worried,
but when I said I would contact Touya
she asked me to take care of it.
My brother?
Don’t worry
I’ll explain things, so he won’t scold you
Oh yeah, Kero-chan
Ah, that orange stuffed animal?
Tomoyo said
she would take care of him
So, rest a little longer
Yukito-san
Hmm?
I met my mother at the top of the cliff
I wonder if that was my mother’s ghost
A long time ago my brother told me
In order for a ghost to
appear they need a reason
I wonder why my mother was there?
But you know, if it was your mother,
would she put you in danger?
Mom
Sorry about this Yuki
No problem
Sakura-chan said she met her mother
In the woods behind the elementary school
Have you ever seen your passed on mother?
Yes.
But not behind the school though
It’s probably my fault
that she is afraid of monsters and ghosts
Ever since she was small
I would tell her things like
There’s a woman with a
Or There is a man with white hair floating there
So, that is how Sakura-chan
became afraid of them
She can’t see them, but it seems
that she knows they’re there
She would just start crying out
Do you still see your mother?
No, she wasn’t around any more
when I went to Jr High
I suppose it must be lonely for her
not to have her mother
I don’t think that’s it
It’s just natural to want
to see her if she could
Sakura-chan has her troubles too,
so try not to scold her for today
But, if you really think Sakura-chan
is so cute
you should stop picking on her
The only one allowed to play around
with her is me
Have you ever heard of a sister complex?
Shut up
Come in
Sakura-chan
Tomoyo-chan
Are you OK?
You took the day off
Yeah, I’m just fine.
My brother ordered me to rest
Kero-chan
I’m sorry that I couldn’t do anything
No. Thank you
It smells nice
But, I wonder what that light was
My mother was there In that forest
But everybody saw something different
You were the only one to see a woman
It might be best to give up on this one
I don’t know if it’s a Clow Card
or a real ghost,
but it has enough power
to defeat you and me.
It was me
who asked you to look for the cards,
but I don’t want to see you get hurt
Kero-chan
That was pretty cool, Kero-chan
I am always cool
But, I think I’ll go after all
Sakura
If it is a card, I have to do
something about it
If it’s my mom
A long time ago my brother told me,
Mom isn’t here anymore
Because I got big so she can relax
and went to a very beautiful
place above the sky.
That’s why
I want to ask her why she’s there,
and if she has something to say
Please be careful, Sakura-chan
Don’t fall off the cliff again
Yeah
Be careful of the unexpected too.
But, I wonder if it will
appear so conveniently.
It will There is no avoiding my hunches.
There it is
Sakura
Yeah
It’s Sakura-chan’s mom
The same as the picture,
But why can we all see the same thing this time?
Mom
Is that really you Mom?
Why are you here?
Mom are you lonely?
Do you want to be with me
Wait! on’t go Mom!
No! Don’t go there!
Kero-chan!
Sakura is
Mom! Wait, Mom!
Please, don’t leave!
Mom!
Sakura
Why? Mom
Why?
If it really was your mother,
would she put you in danger?
No.
Mom wouldn’t do this
She wouldn’t do this
Sakura
You’re not my mom
Who are you?
I have seen that pattern before.
It is a Clow Card after all.
That light!
Return to your rightful form
Clow Card!
You did it
It’s the illusion card
That’s why everybody
saw different things
What do you mean?
Illusion is a card
That shows people what
they want to see
It shows you various things
within your own heart
It’s only natural that
everybody would be different
Now that you mention it,
when we first came here I was hungry
And thinking I’d like to eat a meat bun.
The monsters that everybody saw
were what they thought would be scary,
if it appeared
Just all seeing Sakura’s mom
It was because we were all shown the photo,
And expected her to show up
And what threw you back?
Sakura’s feelings of happiness
from seeing her mom
It were just that strong
I’m so glad
That my Mom wasn’t here alone
I would be happy if I could see her
But, if she is in a beautiful
place in the sky,
that makes me more happy
You tried this hard.
Your mother must be put at ease
Well, she might have worried a
little about you this time.
I’ll be late!
In uniform even on a Sunday?
I have club
Thanks for breakfast
Happy Birthday, Mom
I love you
Well then, I’m off
I came because
I was a little worried this time
But she seems all right now