These are for the children,
and these are for the adults.
Please put them on
your hand before you go in.
Great!
Sakura-chan is very cute.
Excuse me, I would like
to buy #128 please!
[Sakura and Swimming Pool
and Big Waves]
Being able to videotape
Sakura-chan in a bathing suit
in the winter is very good.
It’s like I’m in a dream!
It’s very very fun.
We are very lucky because we get
to come here to go swimming.
Right, Tomoyo-chan?
You’re right!
Because I’ll be able to videotape you in
a bathing suit any time from now on!
I’m not coming here to swim only!
Wearing the swimming suit that
I made would be like a Sakura fish.
I’m too happy!
Sakura-chan! Tomoyo-chan!
Come over here and swim!
Yamazaki-kun, lets go swimming ok?
I’m going to let go ok, Rika-chan?
Go! Go!
Rika-chan looks like she really
knows how to swim.
That is because Sakura-chan
is teaching her since summer vacations.
Great! Great!
You can swim really
good by yourself!
Really?
It’s true, Rika-chan!
You really know how to swim!
She also knows how to swim underwater.
The way you swim is very pretty.
That’s because Sakura-chan
is a very good teacher.
It’s because you are a very good learner.
No, it is because you are a good teacher.
Swimming by myself, I couldn’t
swim at all! I swam very bad.
Shao Lan-kun and
Eriol-kun are really good!
They both swim very fast!
Hiiragizawa-kun and
Li-kun are the same
Because they are racing.
This kind of race is for time.
Before, me and Hiragizawa-kun
swam together.
But after swiming for a while,
Li-kun came.
So, Hiragizawa-kun
and Li-kun decided to race.
Why?
Because of what they’re
feeling in their hearts.
Nothing!
So, talking about swimming races,
The earliest time is in Britain
there were 2 gentlemen
that were racing at the Taylor River.
It was in the winter.
So it was very cold.
There was also a lot of fog
So they couldn’t see, and they
couldn’t hear so the results were urgent…
Yes Yes!
Lets go over to the pool ok?
So the most popular
was the batman’s umbrella.
Talking about how
to use the umbrella…
It is heard that, just opening
an umbrella can remove the fog.
Yamazaki-kun is the kind of person
that likes to make up stories.
Really.
So who won the race?
You can’t be too anxious.
You should stay calm. Then your potential
can get to the highest level.
But about swimming…
To protect the one
who is important to you…
You won right?
Why don’t you rest?
OK
Shao Lan-kun, will you come up here too?
Shao Lan-kun?
Shao Lan-kun!
Are you OK, Shao Lan-kun?
What’s wrong?
You were staring off into space!
Right! I heard that this place’s
cream soda is really good.
Do you want to go and try some?
Last time it was on the magazine.
It also said that it tastes really good!
That’s right!
Let’s go then.
Sakura-chan do you want to come too?
Ok, lets go?
Everybody wants a cream soda right?
Yeah, Cream Soda.
I also want a cream soda.
I do too.
Yesterday Kero-chan saw the
magazine that talked about cream soda.
Really?
I told him that
I am coming to swim here today.
He kept on begging me to bring him along.
I told him that Chiharu-chan will come, so
he couldn’t come, but he kept on begging.
So, Kero-chan kept on saying that
he wanted to come, maybe he snuck in.
I don’t think so!
She kept on saying,
“You can’t come”.
She underestimated me.
So, I snuck into her
swimming suit bag for a second.
Sakura-chan wouldn’t even
think that I came!
Because she didn’t let me come, she will
know the power of me!
Wait for me, Cream soda!
I’m so smart! I’m so smart!
Mommy!
Cream Soda, Cream soda,
Cream soda, Cream soda!
Do you want to order anything else?
Welcome!
Yukito-san!
Hello.
How come you are here?
I’m working here, Touya is here too.
Thank you very much.
Brother!
Sakura?
Watch out!
Touya-kun! I’ve came to help you!
You don’t need to!
I can do this by myself!
Stop it! Were here to work together!
So you can really help me!
Let go of me!
I don’t want to!
Your younger sister is also very cute.
What do you want?
Cream Soda!
– Me too.
Me too!
One cream soda.
This bar code can be used
for other things also!
That’s right, when you guys leave
then you can take off the bracelet.
I would also like a cream soda please!
OK!
He is…
Right! I would like
to thank you for last time!
No problem!
Yukito-san, you know Eriol-kun?
Last time I was in the schools yard,
I fell asleep and he helped me.
Excuse me!
OK! I’m going over there.
So it happened like that?
I just did what is right.
But helping a someone you don’t
even know is really nice.
Your are a very good person,
Eriol-kun.
Shao Lan-kun, how is it?
Does it taste ok?
Sakura-chan! Did you drink it yet?
It tastes really good!
Really?
Then I want to drink some too!
I’m going to drink!
Really Really good!
It tastes really good!
– Give me three cream sodas please.
– OK.
Akizuki.
Call me Nakuru!
Give me three cream sodas.
OK
Sorry!
The night before
I had a really good sleep.
But still, I am very tired.
Touya!
I’m OK!
I’m just not getting enough sleep,
so I’m tired.
Yuki.
Whatever I am about to say you
have to listen very carefully.
Last time you said the same thing.
Don’t care if I’m day dreaming.
Also, don’t worry if I sleep.
Stop worrying.
What do you mean by “I’m fine”?
I know, you are…
Yes, I’m done!
Thank you, Akizuki-san.
Why don’t you tell me later, Touya?
Be careful!
My roller blades go really fast.
They’re ok.
What’s wrong?
I saw something that looked really fun.
Where?
It already ended.
There is a person, why is he hiding?
It’s right there! It’s right there!
Sakura has a lot left.
The brat has a lot too.
But, the brat will probably notice me.
I should take that one.
I heard that there is also
an upstairs where they sell
apple pie that is also very good.
So, lets all go and see then.
Really?
It seems like it will taste good.
I really want to eat and see!
So after everybody is done
lets all go and try some.
When everybody is done eating.
What is wrong?
My Cream Soda is all gone.
Didn’t you eat it all yourself?
Of course not,
last time it was up to here.
Oh
When I was talking about apple pie,
it disappeared.
Order another one.
But, I remember that it
there was still some left!
KERO-CHAN!!!
Sakura-chan?
In here, it feels like hot water,
it is very warm.
Sakura-chan, do you want to come in?
Sorry, I have to go to the bathroom.
Me too.
I also have to go and get some batteries
for my video camera.
So, we will go to the pool first ok?
I get it, I’ll see you later.
Kero-chan!
I told you that you couldn’t come today!
But when I read about the cream soda,
I had to come and drink some!
How does it taste?
The one that Sakura bought was ok
I think it could have been better though.
You really are a food monster.
You wouldn’t know how I feel about food.
You are such a brat, stupid brat.
Who is a brat?
Kero-chan, when we were at home you
told me that you wouldn’t come.
But it was very easy
to sneak into your bag.
KERO-CHAN!
That feeling…
What is this?
How did this happen?
It seems like a big wave!
What happens?
Let’s hurry and get out of the pool.
How can a wave become so big?
Is there something
wrong with the machines?
No…
Rika-chan!
Rika-chan!!!
Sakura, this is…
I feel his presence.
Eveybody get out of the pool!
How did this happen?
I’ll come right back,
you stay there and hang on.
Rika-chan!
You can’t go in.
It’s not safe to go play in the pool.
But my friend is going to drown!
If someone doesn’t hurry
then Rika-chan will…
Calm down, hurry and think of something!
Touya, look over there.
Are you ok?
Shit, if it stays this
way then it won’t do.
I have to hurry.
What should I do?
If I don’t hurry then Rika-chan will drown!
The reason she’ll drown is because…
Because there is water!
You can’t.
At this place, there will be
a lot of people that will see you!
But…
Over there!
Right!
Release!
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
Watery!
Rain?
But it is an inside pool.
I did it!
Rika-chan!
Are you ok?
I’m fine.
I’m so glad.
– I’m glad.
– It scared me to death.
Are you okay?
Eriol, if Sakura didn’t help
and use her Clow cards,
you would have stopped the wave
So what was the point of doing that?
You will soon find out.
Today was very weird.
It’s good that Rika-chan is ok.
I want to thank you
for helping me to swim.
Sasaki-san,
will you be scared of water later on?
No, though it was a little scary.
Sakura-chan,
will you still help me swim?
Of course!