Thank you very much.
Fettucine and spinach pasta.
Okay!
I got done with all my shopping!
[Sakura and Another Sakura]
I’m back!
Welcome back, Sakura.
Yukito?
Touya, what are you doing?
Can’t you tell?
I’m getting a haircut.
I just happened to stop by.
With this, I don’t have to pay.
Must be nice!
Getting a haircut from Yukito.
Sakura, you want a cut too?
Eh?
But maybe you want go to
a salon for a proper cut…
Because you’re a girl…
Please!
I’ll just trim a
little for you, okay?
Ye… Yes.
Clean up after you’re done.
I’ll help too.
I’ll do anything !
Someday,
I’m gonna wear one of these too.
Hey, Shao Lan, wait!
Eh!
What’s wrong?
Kinomoto!
Could she be running away because she
knew she did something bad?
This pencil case is cute too.
I’ll get this one.
Which one should I get…
Sakura?
What is it…
Whoa! Who did this?!
What is it? You look happy, Sakura.
How is it? Yukito cut my hair.
You didn’t look any different at all.
After all, Yukito can really do anything.
Besides, he’s so nice and
he’s good at sports. Schweeeet.
Sakura, come help!
Okay!
I guess girls are hard to understand.
You’re good at cleaning up, Sakura.
Not really.
She’s not like this normally.
She’d break things here
and there like a monster.
I can’t tell if she’s cleaning
or moving things around.
When this is done,
let’s make dinner.
How about I cook?
Eh!
I always eat here for free…
I’ll help you.
Thank you.
Today’s a really nice day.
I guess we won’t be
eating dinner tonight.
Eh!
Why not?
If Sakura cooks,
you can’t even eat the things
supposed to be edible.
What did you say?!
Touya,
where’s the ingredient
for the pasta?
Oh, it’s here.
G’morning, Tomoyo.
Good morning.
It’s gotten cooler
little by little.
Yes.
You seem cheerful.
Listen. Listen.
I had a lot of good times yesterday.
Oh? Did you get a haircut?
Ye… Yeah. Could you tell?
Yukito cut it for me yesterday.
I am glad for you.
But you know, Kero said
he couldn’t tell any difference.
I can notice even
if you had the slightest trim.
G’morning!
Good morning!
G’morning…
Sakura, you know…
Did something happen?
Kinomoto!
Ye… Yes!
You can’t misbehave like that!
Eh!
You were going to steal something,
weren’t you?
I saw you yesterday.
You messed up the stuffed
dolls yesterday.
Right, Shao Lan?
What are you talking about?
Sakura, were you at the
stationery store yesterday?
No. I did go out to buy pasta,
but I stayed home since then.
Just as I thought,
I mistook her for you.
That’s right. Sakura wouldn’t
do something like that.
Did something happen?
We saw someone who
looked a bit like Sakura.
Me?
That’s not it.
I’m positive that was Kinomoto.
Shao Lan saw her too!
Be careful.
What does he mean?
What could he mean by ‘be careful’?
Sakura.
Thank you very much.
Don’t worry about it,
Sakura.
They say everyone in this world
has someone who
looks just like him or her.
Eh!
Oh, there’s this story too…
It’s called a doppelganger.
The another you.
They say if you meet
the other you, you die.
Did Li mean by that
when he told me to be careful?
Sakura!
It was her!
You are not feeling well.
Tomoyo, did you know?
If you see another you, you d… di…
You mean, you die?
Do not worry.
That is only a superstition.
But… But!!
What is wrong?
I saw her!!
Sakura!
Oh, there she is! Sakura!
What is wrong?
Eh?
Was that you who were
being mean to the little kids
In the park?
I didn’t do anything like that.
Sakura has been
here with me all this time.
See, here is her ice cream.
She was wearing
the school uniform…
It was that girl just now.
Someone who looks just like you?
She was mean
to the little kids,
and she made a mess at the stores.
So it looked like
it was you who did those things.
At this rate, bad rumors
will be spreading around the town.
Besides, they say if you
see another you, yo… o… yyou’ll die.
A doppelganger…
Were you scared when you saw her?
No, rather than scared,
it was more like a strange feeling.
Could it be a Clow Card?
All right. Let’s tell a fortune.
Tell a fortune?
It’s the perfect opportunity for this.
I’ll teach you how to tell fortunes
with the Clow Cards.
Pay attention, okay?
Okay.
First of all, mix the cards
with your left hand.
Okay. Put them back together,
and then divide them into
3 piles with your left hand.
Using your left hand again,
put them back into one pile.
In the same order?
No. In any order you like.
And then, pull out the cards
one by one from the pile, and
arrange ten cards here.
First, one card at the top.
Next, put one by your side.
Put the next one below on the left.
Again, by your side.
Close your eyes and repeat after me.
Cards created by Clow,
answer my question.
Reveal the true form
of the one who stands in my path.
Okay. Flip over the card at the top.
Windy .
Just as I thought!
Eh!
The cards are trying
to tell you somethin’!
What do you mean?
Windy is a card that represents
‘communications,’ and ‘information.’
It’s telling you that
a Card has noticed that
you’re collecting them.
The cards I’m going to capture
from now on, do they all know about me?
Probably except for those
that haven’t been awakened
and are still in form of cards.
Then, that girl is
a Clow Card, after all.
That’s highly possible.
Flip these 3 cards over.
That card can be associated
with these 3 cards.
Shadow. Watery. Illusion.
Go on!
Lastly, look at the very bottom
card in the remainin’ pile.
What is it gonna tell me?
What the card has its eyes on now.
Flower ?
Peach…
Peach blossom…
Touya!
Sakura?
You’re late.
Did you have club activities?
Sakura…?
But then why does it remind
you of your brother?
I don’t know!
It just came up in my head!
Do you know where
your brother is right now?
I don’t know.
But somehow, I think it’s this way!
Sakura’s magical power
has grown stronger again.
This way.
This is Touya’s bike.
All right. He’s nearby.
What is it that you dropped?
There’s nothing.
Go deeper.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
It’s further in.
What’s wrong?!
No!! I couldn’t sense
the card anymore!
But you could tell until just now!
Somehow, I sense
a lot of people around here.
But there’s no one around here.
I can feel something not very nice too.
Oh! Those must be ghosts…
Those ‘not very nice’ things
must be drowning out
the trace of the card.
What should I do?
It’s deeper inside.
Deeper.
What should I do…
if anything happens to Touya…
Dammit.
If only I regain my original form,
then I can tell
its location right away.
Touya…
Sakura…
Hey brat,
what are you doin’ here?
I followed the trace
of the Clow Card here.
What’s wrong?
That’s…
That’s made to
look for Clow Cards, right?
Ye… Yeah.
Please!
Please use it to find Touya!
That way!
Touya, I’ll be right there.
So, where’s that thing you dropped?
You were looking for it, right?
I’m fine. I’ll keep you
company until you find it.
This is bad.
Looks like I can’t stand up.
Hey, I look for the thing
you dropped for you,
so I’m not gonna let
you use Sakura’s image.
It just doesn’t feel pleasant
for someone like her
to turn into ghost.
When did you find out
I’m not your sister?
At first, I thought
I’ve mistaken you for Sakura,
because you look
so much like her.
But soon, I realize you’re
not a living human being.
There are a lot of
them in this forest.
They probably still have things
to finish up in this world.
How about I keep you company until you
find the thing you dropped?
After you find it, you should go.
Go where?
My mother’s there too.
Say hi to her for me.
Down there!
Fly !
Touya!
He’s okay. He’s still alive.
He just lost consciousness.
You hurt my brother!
Windy!
Magic doesn’t work?!
Sakura, use an offensive card!
Watery !
Just as I thought,
neither restraining magic
or attack magic works…
That means,
it’s a special card!
Special card?
You can’t turn it back
with the common cards.
What am I supposed to do?
You have to guess right
the true form of the card.
For a special card,
if you name it correctly,
it loses its power and
turns back to a card.
Idiot!
That’s stupid of you to get close!
You are the sister.
That’s right.
You did cruel things to my brother.
Think what card it is!
Illusion. Watery. Shadow.
Keep thinking of those 3 cards…
She is imitating me?
Like Shadow,
it moves the same way with me.
Like Watery, it reflects many things.
But like Illusion,
it’s not the real thing.
You are…
You’re the card, Mirror,
aren’t you?
I’m sorry.
Return to thy form which thou should be!
Clow Card!
Touya!
But then, you did a good job
in recognizing it’s Mirror.
She imitated me.
It’s like she moved with me on purpose
to make me recognize it.
I guess she was sorry before she
was turned back to a card.
Yes.
I could have walked
downstairs and eat.
No, because you hurt your foot too.
Hey, that guy.
Oh, um… this…
It was lonely making
food by myself,
so I brought the stuffed
doll with me…
Touya…
Eh!
I’m sorry.
Nothing. I’m just sorry.
Did she put something in here…
Hello!
Falling down a cliff,
it’s very unlike you.
Things happen.
You told me you always saw things
in that forest.
Is this because
of something you saw?
When I woke up,
it’s already gone.
I guess I just didn’t feel it.
That must be it.
You’re so nice.
Delicious! Did Sakura make it?
Just shut up.
That was too bad.
I missed out on shooting
your heroic epic.
It looks so good!
I wanna eat Tomoyo’s cake too!
Those cards that will stand
in my way trying to hurt me…
Even from now on,
they might still come out.
They might.
Hey, you told me when we first met,
‘When the seal of the
Clow Cards is broken,
a disaster will bestow upon this world.’
What is this disaster?
I don’t understand it,
but is it like bad things
will be awakened
And they will blast
away the earth?
No, no.
Things like that aren’t gonna happen.
Then, what kind of disaster is it?
To some people, it might not
even be any disaster at all.
I’m glad.
I’ll do my very best
to gather all the cards.
In order to prevent
the cards from doing bad things,
I’ll gather them all for sure!
If it’s you, Sakura,
it’ll be all right.
Let’s bring these to
Touya and Yukito.
Okay.
But to some people, when
compared to blastin’ away the earth,
it could be somethin’ even harsher.