G’morning!
G’morning.
Good morning, Sakura.
Tomoyo, g’morning!
Did something nice happen?
Eh!
Because from the moment you came in,
you looked joyful.
Tonight,
Yukito is staying over at our house.
He has to plan the
athletics meet with Touya.
Oh, I see.
Who did you say is staying over?
I said it in such a soft voice already.
After all, one can hear the name
of the person one likes
under any circumstances.
Is he coming over tonight?
Hey, hey, who is ‘he’?
He is…
What? What?
What are you guys talking about?
Sorry for interrupting…
Wh… What is it?!
Daidouji…
Yes?
Our music teacher, Miss Tsujitani
wanted me to let you know…
…that she needs you to stay behind
in the music room after school.
To practise for the competition?
Yes.
Everyone in the choir has to stay behind.
This is not easy at all.
Hey, can I come watch your practice?
The song you sang to me yesterday
was a really nice song.
I want to hear it again.
Please come!
Oh! We want to go too!
I want to hear Tomoyo sing.
Yeah!
Oh! I can sing very well too.
Then, would you like to join the choir?
I don’t mind joining,
but I don’t know any Japanese songs.
Oh, speaking of the choir…
Did you know? They said it came out…
Wh… What came out?
A ghost.
[Sakura and Tomoyo and
the Wonderful Song]
Last night, there was this girl
from the choir who stayed late.
They said she left something
in the music room,
and so she went back for it.
In that really dark room,
where nobody should be there,
someone inside was singing!
Tomoyo, did you know about it?
I thought you would be scared,
so I did not mention it.
Thank you.
The song is pretty even
it was only played on the piano, right?
Yes! It was a wonderful song!
Oh!
What is the matter?
Everyone, why don’t we listen
to this wonderful song one more time?
I feel something weird in this room.
You noticed it too?
There’s something in this room.
Could it be a Clow Card?
What is it?
Is there a Clow Card in here?
I can’t quite tell yet.
It… It could be a ghost…
Let’s check it out.
When?
After everyone is gone.
At night?
At night?!!
Is there something wrong,
Kinomoto?
N… No… m…
I just thought… it’s scary at night…
I’m sorry.
So, a singin’ voice
from the music room.
That isn’t a ghost, is it?
Stop it!!
Talk about a song coming
out from the music room,
isn’t that like the
seven mysteries of the school?
But, I’m sure
I could sense a trace of a card
in the music room,
and even Li-kun said so too.
Okay! Then in order to
jump ahead of the brat,
we’ll sneak into the school tonight!
No!
You’re the one who lose if
it turns out to be a Clow Card!
But even if the music room incident
is due to a card,
there are still many other
scary stories about the school!
Didn’t we go there
for Shadow?
That’s why I said no more!
Hey! Hey!
Besides, Yukito is coming over tonight.
I want to stay here all night.
Oh, your tea is getting cold, isn’t it?
I’ll go pour you a new one…
You want another cup, don’t you?
He… Hey, Sakura!
Geez…
They should be back anytime now.
Yukito…
They are late, aren’t they?
Ye… Yeah.
Oh, I was going to pour some tea.
Should I pour it out for you?
I’m fine. It’s not something
I can’t do myself.
I’m home.
There you are.
Welcome home.
Sorry for bothering you.
You’re very welcome here,
Tsukishiro.
He… Hello.
Hello. I’m staying over tonight.
O… Okay!
Yukito will be with us today…
U… m… Would you like some tea?
Can I?
Thanks.
Oh, I want one too.
After.
Totally different attitude.
By the way, Sakura…
Did you know the story about
the music room in your school?
Oh, that story.
Hmm? What happened?
It seems somehow,
people heard songs from within
their music room at night.
Songs?
Also, they always
last for about an hour.
We have students staying
late at school
to prepare for the athletics meet.
I see.
Those who heard it were the officers
from the student council
who stayed the latest.
They thought it was the wind at first,
but they listen more closely
and it was definitely a song.
And they wondered where
it was coming from,
so the members went to check it out.
And it was from Tomoeda’s music room.
What time did it happen?
They said it was around
10 o’clock at night.
Um… No one’s there at that hour, right?
Yes.
That’s why there were
rumors around the school.
That maybe it’s a ghost.
But I heard…
It was a very beautiful voice.
I kinda want to hear it.
I’m going to the school tonight!
What? Did somethin’ happen while
you went to pour the tea?
Yukito said he wanted
to hear the ghost’s song.
Is that why?!
That is why.
You don’t have the right motive,
but I’m fine with it as long as you are.
It’s the Card Captor’s call!
I found it!
Yukito…
Hey, are you listenin’?
Tomoyo, you’re not scared?
Not particularly.
I am more worried about
not being able to capture
your best shots.
By the way, did you hear the singing.
in the music room when…
you stayed for practice?
No, I stayed behind after school,
but it was only till 7 o’clock.
Then only that girl who forgot her stuff
and those high school students heard it.
Some students in Seijou High School.
Stayed until 10 o’clock.
It is exactly 10 o’clock right now.
So… Somehow…
It is scary after all.
Hey!
Umm…
Li-kun. Mei-Ling.
You scared me.
You scared us too!
In your costume with a sword,
you’ve come to look for the Clow Card,
right, brat?
Who’s a brat?
You are a brat for the fact that
you only lived for 10 years.
And you came along too.
I followed him here.
He said I couldn’t come.
You shouldn’t have done that.
If something happens,
someone with no magical powers like you
can’t win.
Then, what about her?
I need to record it.
I should have brought my video camera!
That’s why we’re not coming to play.
Next time, for sure…!
Did you hear something?
Is that… a song?
Guess the rumor was for real.
Where is it comin’ from?
The school building over there.
Let’s go!
Wait!
Those brats are cuttin’ ahead of us!
Let’s hurry, Sakura!
It isn’t a ghost, is it?
Just go, even if it is.
After all, it is here.
I could hear it clearly from back then.
But I still can’t tell the exact place.
Hey, it isn’t a ghost, right?
Hey, hey,
it’s not, right?
This song…
What’s wrong?
I seem to have heard it before.
You know it?
Yes, but I cannot tell what song it is…
It’s not the one from
the seven mysteries, right?
I do not think so.
But you could have been wrong too.
Just as I thought, I…
Hey,
aren’t you all ready to
record the voice on tape?
That’s right.
What are you recording it for?
Someone wanted to hear it…
The snow ra…
I heard that the voice is beautiful.
Let’s get going.
Sorry.
I thought I was gonna die.
Just as I thought, I know this song.
It’s from the music room.
Card Captor, pull yourself together.
If you can’t capture the card,
that means you can’t
record the song either.
O… Okay. I’ll do my best.
It’s from here after all.
Oh?
I have heard this song before too.
This song!
No more guesses. I’ll just open the door,
and let’s find out.
Hey, hold on!
It’s gone!
I cannot hear the voice either.
All because you suddenly opened the door!
But!
But thanks to you opening the door,
I could hear the song clearly.
Did you recognize the song?
Yeah. That’s the song you sang for me,
wasn’t it?
That was the song I have been practicing
for the national competition.
Why is it the song from Tomoyo’s practice…
There it is again.
It’s coming from above.
Let’s go!
It moved again.
This voice…!
This sounds just like Tomoyo’s voice.
I see now. This is…
Song!
I was just about to say that!!
What can Song do?
First of all, the card, Song,
is a card that sings.
What else?
It listens.
Anything else?
That’s it.
Then, why is it Tomoyo’s voice?
The card, Song,
can copy the voice
of the one who sings better than anyone.
Tomoyo is good at singing.
I’m good at singing too.
If the card copies her voice,
it’s gonna get so ill.
What did you say?!
Because you yelled!
But!
It’s here.
But I don’t see anything.
Because Song can’t be seen.
Then how am I supposed to seal it?
Hang on!
Tomoyo, are you still
practising this song?
Yes, because the higher
notes were still unstable.
That’s right.
Song!
Because our perfect Tomoyo
will win no matter what,
Song is working hard in its practice.
While Tomoyo practises her song
in the music room, at the same time…
The card has its own practice too.
But we just can’t leave it as it is.
If we don’t something,
the rumor will just get worse.
They might recognize
it’s Tomoyo’s voice…
What should we do?
Hey, how about this?
Let me do that,
I’ll sing in front of the card.
Having heard my perfect singing,
even the card…
Well, as we put that thought aside…
Tomoyo, bein’ the one whose
voice was copied,
if she would sing the song
in the most perfect manner,
that even the card is satisfied,
it will show itself…
I sing?
You will do fine.
Even when you sang it yesterday,
it was really nice.
I’m sure you can do it.
I understand. I will do my best
and be confident.
Twinkling in the night sky
is a distant golden star,
Look at that!
the same color as the
little bird I saw
in last night’s dream.
In this sleepless night,
I sing a song alone.
Let us sing tomorrow
as we ride on the wings of dreams.
Now, Sakura!
Return to thy form which
thou should be!
Clow Card!
Good job!
Well done, Tomoyo, Sakura.
Tomoyo, it was really wonderful.
Don’t you think so? Li-kun?
Yeah.
I guess she’s as good as I am.
And puttin’ that thought aside…
after all, only the original
copy of Song would work.
Thank you very much.
Oh no, brat, you couldn’t
do anything this time.
You still have plenty
of things to learn.
You stuffed doll.
I dare you say it again!
What is the matter?
I brought my tape recorder along,
but I forgot to record Song’s singing.
But then its voice
is the same as Tomoyo’s voice,
isn’t it okay to just have her sing?
But the duet was really wonderful.
Then why don’t you write
your name on the card,
and have them
sing together?
And I was just gonna say that!
S-A-K-U-R-A
All right! I wrote it down.
The tape recorder is ready.
Okay.
Hey, how about
I sing with them too…
Puttin’ that aside…
Tomoyo, thanks.
I will sing the best
I can with the card.
Okay.
Deliver a supreme
singing voice to us!
Song!