=Someday,=
=I’ll become a wonderful person.=
=I want to bring happiness=
=with my own magic.=
I was so nervous.
It was wonderful.
Not bad,
but not as good as me.
This karaoke mic turns out really well.
It’s from your mother’s company,
isn’t it?
Yes, but it is not for sale
in the stores yet.
It’s nice to have one
when watching the cherry blossoms.
It’s nice for parties!
You know, about karaoke…
Next, it’s Tomoyo-chan’s turn!
Okay.
I love to hear Tomoyo-chan sing.
Don’t you, Mei Lin-chan?
I guess so.
I mean only Daidouji-san
can rival me in singing.
=When I am lonely,=
=I seek warmth.=
=I trace far into the distance=
=my dear memories.=
=Holding her beloved child=
=in her arms,=
Tomoyo-chan is
really very good at singing.
And she has such a beautiful voice.
=This song is dedicated to you…=
[Sakura and Tomoyo’s Vanished Voice]
That must’ve been nice.
I wanted to go see
the cherry blossoms too!
I could’ve pretended
to be a stuffed doll!
Then you couldn’t eat anything, you know?
No way!
That’s just too painful!
Thanks.
Hey,
if you return to your original form,
will you be able to go
see the cherry blossoms during the day?
Even more impossible.
Hey, how does your original form
look like?
Reeeeal cool.
Like how?
So cool that it’s impossible
to describe in words.
What’s that?
Well, when you finish gathering’
all the cards,
you’ll find out.
Fine…
But at that time,
you might need to
deal with that guy too…
For next week’s strawberry hunt,
everything you need
to bring is printed here,
so make sure you
show your parents.
Yes!
Let’s eat lots of strawberries!
Okay, that’s it for today.
Good-bye, Sensei.
Good-bye.
Hurry up!
Okay!
Tomoyo-chan,
do you have club practice today?
Yes.
Me too.
Let’s go home together afterwards!
That is…
Shao Lan, let’s go home together!
Wei asked me to go
buy something for him.
I’ll go with you!
I’m not going to play you know.
Sakura-chan.
In order to prepare for the competition,
I might need to stay late.
The set piece this time is hard.
The song you sang
at the cherry-blossom viewing?
No, it is a different song.
Are you singing a solo?
No, it is a group singing.
But I have
a solo at the beginning…
If I do not perform well,
it will affect
everyone else’s performance.
And also,
it is a song that I love very much.
Don’t worry!
I’m sure you’ll sing really well.
I will do my best.
See you later!
Kinomoto-san!
Is Daidouji-san going
to the choir practice?
Yes.
Daidouji-san…
I think she’ll be having a hard time…
Help her through it, okay?
Hurray! Hurray! To-mo-e-da!
Have you heard the new song
the choir’s been practicing?
No.
Tomoyo-chan said she’s practicing
a new song for the competition.
Tomoyo-chan’s singing is wonderful.
She said she might have to
stay late for practice today as well.
Oh, after club practice is over,
do you want to see their practice?
Yeah, I’ll go.
I’ll go too!
Sakura-chan!
Yukito-san!
Cheer-leading club practice?
Yes!
I’m glad it’s not a baton this time.
Even if that fell on your head,
it wouldn’t hurt.
Onii-chan!!
You’ll be okay even
if you got hit by a baton.
Sakura’s head is as hard as a rock.
It is not!!
Yukito-san,
you’re wearing this uniform…
I’m helping out the soccer team.
He’s helping out
with our next match.
Oh, we gotta go.
Later, rock-head.
Onii-chan!!
See you later!
Pass it! Pass it!
Touya!
All Right!!!
I… I’ll go get it!
That went very far!
Sakura-chan’s all full
of spirit today as well!
Oh, It’s Tomoyo-chan’s singing.
Her voice is so beautiful.
Clow Card…
What’s wrong? Daidouji-san?
Daidouji-san! Daidouji-san!
Daidouji-san!
Tomoyo-chan!
You… can’t speak?
No way!
Please take care.
Please excuse us.
And then, Tomoyo went home?
The bodyguard ladies
came to pick her up.
And they went straight to the doctor.
That’s what the maid said
on the phone just now.
It seems she still hasn’t been
able to speak after all…
That is probably
the act of the Clow Card
you sensed then.
You sensed it, right?
If only I’d noticed
it a little earlier
and sealed it…
Cheer up.
If you’re like this,
Tomoyo’ll be sad too.
She can’t speak…
which means…
No doubt about it.
It’s the act of Voice card.
Voice?
It liked Tomoyo’s voice,
so it stole it.
That’s mean!
What Mizuki-sensei said…
Could it be about this…?
I’d like to meet
this teacher for once.
Tomoyo!
You couldn’t speak?
Even though the doctor
said you didn’t catch a cold…
How about a fever?
Are you cold?
Are you in pain anywhere?
Is that right?
I’ll skip work tomorrow.
I’m so worried.
[I am okay.]
You are not okay.
I could tell you must be scared
when something like this happen.
Because you’re my
one and only daughter.
Saitou Mioko-san.
Here!
Tanade Ryouichi-kun.
Daidouji-san is
not feeling well today.
Her mother called saying that
she will be absent today.
Tomoyo-chan…
What happened?
Li. Why are you here…
I… I was worried about you…
I just think, I
…might have found a Clow Card…
Daidouji is absent
because of the Clow Card.
Tomoyo-chan,
for the competition this time,
was practicing so hard for
the solo she has at the beginning.
If she can’t sing well,
The rest will be wasted.
It’s not just about the competition.
What if she loses her voice from now on?
Tomoyo-chan!
It’s no use crying.
You must think of a way
to seal the Clow Card.
I’ll think too.
I… just… wanted to capture the card…
Thanks.
In… In the meantime,
we should go visit Daidouji-san
and see how things are going.
Li-kun! Tomoyo-chan’s
house is not that way!
How are you feeling?
You still can’t speak, can you?
I’m sorry.
It’s all because
I didn’t notice it quickly enough.
[Sakura-chan, please cheer up.
Seeing your sad face
makes me feel sad as well.]
Tomoyo-chan!
I’ll capture the card
before the competition.
I promise!
Hello!
Oh, we haven’t met before.
I’m Shao Lan Li.
I’m Tomoyo’s mother.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, Sakura-chan, please sit.
Please let me help you.
Oh? Thanks.
[You are always watching Sakura.]
Wh… Wha…
I… I’m not…
What’s wrong, Li?
It’s nothing.
Did Kerberos mention anything
about the Voice card?
He said, “The Voice card
likes Tomoyo-chan’s voice,
so it took it, right?”
It’s not nearby.
He said Voice is not going to stop
until it finishes
collecting all the voices it likes.
Said it’ll also hide from
those whose voices are taken
so that they can’t get them back.
So if we want to seal Voice,
we must find it first.
I have no idea at all
how to search for Voice!
[Please cheer up.]
Compare to me, you must
be feeling even more terrible.
This is the second time for you!
It’s always you Tomoyo-chan.
Last time I got you involved
in the Song card too!
Song!
We can use Song!
That card has copied
Daidouji’s voice, right?
If Voice could
hear the voice
it has stolen
coming from somewhere…
It might come out
to steal it again!
Deliver the most supreme singing voice!
Song!
All right!
Return to thy form which thou should be!
Clow Card!
Tomoyo-chan!
Sakura-chan…
Thank goodness! Thank goodness!
Thank you very, very much.
Next is the Tomoeda
Elementary School Choir.
Tomoyo-chan has a solo, you know?
I can’t wait!
When it comes to singing,
Daidouji-san is my only rival.
So there’s no way she can lose.
Where’s Sakura-san?
I’ll cheer for you with all I have!
Because you went
through all that trouble
to bring me back my voice,
I’ll do my very best.
Next is the
Tomoeda Elementary School Choir.
I will sing from the bottom of my heart.
Because I am dedicating this song to you.
Please go listen to it.
=Sunshine dances between the clouds,=
=and pours into the plains…=
=The season has just begun.=
=run up to the voice of my friend.=
=And there, as I turn to her,=
=is always her smiling face,=
=where the brightest sun always shines.=
=As I walk in the street=
=in the freezing winter,=
=you encourage me naturally,=
=and helped me so many times.=
=Like you… Just like you…=
=I want to be someone=
=who can give courage to others.=