Why?
How come?
Yukito-san…
[Sakura and the Last Judgment]
Sakura…
I wonder if Tsukishiro-san knows that
Sakura has been gathering
Clow Cards all along.
No, I don’t think so.
Yue is the Judge.
He is not needed
until the Last Judgment.
His false form shouldn’t
know of his existence.
So…
Snow-rabbit simply thinks
(Yukito = snow-rabbit)
he’s a normal human being himself.
But you woke up
because she scattered
all the cards, right?
But he has come to Tomoeda
much earlier.
Someone…
Someone has wished it
so happened, perhaps?
There is no coincidence in this world.
There is only the inevitable.
Same as the dream.
Candidate of the
Mistress of Clow Cards.
Now,
with all the Clow Cards you have,
Defeat me.
No way… I…
I can’t!
Jump…
Jump.
Yuki… to… san…
Sakura!
Now, I shall conduct
the Last Judgment.
I can’t!
I can’t fight you, Yue-san.
Right now, you look different, But…
You are Yukito-san after all!
If you keep running away,
you cannot win against me.
No!
If Sakura gets help from anyone,
she loses right there, right then!
But at this rate, she’ll…!
Sakura should be able to convince Yue.
I believe in her.
If you don’t act serious,
this will be the end.
I gotta… I gotta do something.
A card that won’t hurt Yue-san…
Wood!
Not good!
Wood carries the attributes of the Moon.
You do not even know such a thing.
This is the end.
– You have lost.
– I lost…?
Right. You lost.
The seal on the cards
are broken once again.
On top of that,
the disaster befalls upon this world.
What is the disaster of the world?
What’s going to happen?
That is, to forget.
If the candidate chosen by
Kerberos the Appointer…
…cannot defeat Yue the Judge,
The Clow Cards, and everyone involved
with the Clow Cards will forget…
…the feeling of “love” towards
the person they love most.
What?!
The Clow Cards treasure most the person
who sealed and signed on them.
But if this person does not qualify as
the Master or the Mistress,
In order not to grieve,
the cards would forget the person
they love most.
Forgotten…
Everyone’s feeling of loving someone
the most would be forgotten…
Even mine…
…would be forgotten…
I can’t…
I definitely can’t…
…let this happen!!
You have broken the magic that
was backfired at you.
Still, I will not say
that you did not lose.
Only Clow Reed is able to defeat me.
Dammit!!
I can’t… Everyone would forget…
They’d forget the people they love…
A dream?
Good morning!
Good morning.
Good morning, Father.
Good morning…
Is there something?
No, it’s nothing.
Good morning!
Good morning, Tomoyo-chan!
Class is going to start!
– Good morning!
Mihara-san, the Japanese
class material for the first period.
Please get it ready now.
Miss Midori will be here soon.
That’s right.
Hey Chiharu-chan,
Yamazaki-kun calls you “Mihara-san”?
Yeah,
it’s not like
we know each other very well…
Can you come here for a second?
Yes.
Can you hand these
to your class teacher?
Yes.
– Good morning.
– Good morning!
– What?
– No, it’s nothing.
No one is here…
Sakura-chan!
That person…
He is…
That’s it! He is…
…the person I love most!
She broke it!
Mizuki-sensei!
I’m glad you noticed it!
The bell…
This bell is left behind by Clow Reed,
in order to give you a second chance.
Its task is over,
so it vanished.
There will not be another chance again.
I got it.
Living in a world without the feeling
for the person you love most,
That is too harsh!
I’ll do my best!
I can do it!
It’ll be okay for sure!
Now, lift up your wand.
What is this?!
A new power.
Release!
The wand changed!
Wind, capture the one before you!
Windy!
Useless. Windy serves under me…
Impossible!
Yue-san,
you must like Clow-san very much.
Therefore,
I’m sure you understand how sad it is…
…to forget the feeling
for the person you love most.
I’m still a kid,
and I’m not nearly
as powerful as Clow,
But… I’ll work hard at it!
Rather than being the Mistress,
I would like to be your friend.
Close your eyes.
Do it now!
Judgment complete.
I, Yue the Judge,
Accept Sakura as the new Mistress.
You are…
I predicted the chances around you,
And little by little
made the inevitable happen.
You came across all of them,
And completed the story
with a happy ending.
Thank you very much.
Could you be… Clow-san?
Then, is this wand yours?
No, You were the one
who created that wand.
Neither the Sun or the Moon,
It is your mere power of the Stars,
which resides in the wand.
Even though it only emits a small
amount of brightness at the moment.
The power of the Stars
keeps shining on their own.
Please treasure that power.
Hey!
Sakura-chan!
I did it!
You’ve been staying around
the whole time.
I guess.
Did you know Tsukishiro-kun isn’t human?
Yeah.
All is well.
Sakura is the new Mistress.
But with that level of power,
It is impossible for her to convert
all her cards.
You may be right.
For the time being,
I think it’s better for us
to return to our false forms.
Sakura!
Kero-chan! I did it!