Summer is almost over.
Hey Sakura
What?
Is it really okay that
we have so much free time lately?
What are you talking about?
Because of that,
we had lots of time to play,
didn’t we?
Yeah, but…
Huh? What are you doing?
I got a letter from Miss Mizuki,
so I’m writing her back
That lady went somewhere
oversea to study, didn’t she
Is she doing fine?
Yeah, she said she’s
studyng hard.
But thanks to her,
you’ve officially become
the Mistress of the Clow Cards
I’m real glad for that.
Why?
Isn’t it obvious?
If that brat had
become the Master,
I’d have lost all
my confidence to live.
Don’t say that!
Li worked hard at it too!
By the way, what’s he gonna do?
Has he gone back to Hong Kong yet?
Not yet,
but he said he’d be going back soon.
With this much free time every day,
it’s getting boring!
I don’t have any free time
because I have school tomorrow…
Huh? What’s wrong?
The summer vacation homework
were still left in the school bag!!
What??!
Gotta finish Maths exercise,
Japanese exercise,
Picture Diary.
and then there’s independent research,
and… and…
Can you finish them
all in one night?
It’ll all work out!
It’ll be okay for sure!
This is not too good.
Kero, help me please!!
I helped you last year,
and you got mad at me!
Yeah, but now…
Oh, by the way,
I’m on duty tomorrow!
Oh no!
I gotta get up early tomorrow!
You’ll be fine!
I’m sure you’ll
get all of them done.
[Sakura and the
Mysterious Transfer student]
Good morning!
Did you finish your homework?
Yeah!
Good morning, Mother.
Are you okay, Sakura?
Good morning, Father
Good morning
Today’s only the opening ceremony
but you’re up quite early.
I’m on duty today.
I see.
From today on is the 2nd semester.
Work hard, okay
Thanks for the food.
Even if you go this early,
Yuki won’t be there.
That’s not it!!
I’m going now.
Humm, I hate Maths already.
Come to think of it,
who’s on duty with me today?
Yukito!
– Sakura!
– Good morning!
Good morning!
Oh, you’re really early today.
I’m on duty and so…
But you’re early too.
I got up early to buy breakfast.
Because lately,
no matter how much I eat,
I’m still hungry…
Maybe I bought a little too much.
No… Not at all!
To be able to eat a lot…
It’s the proof of good health, right?
Yup!
Oh, I’ve to go now.
okay, See you later.
Yukito is the
false form of Yue…
Sakura!
But, but but,
Yukito is Yukito after all!!
Good morning!
But, no one’s here yet anyway.
On duty, on duty, on-duty.
I even finished the summer vacation
homework somehow.
Writing the class journal,
changing the flowers.
Let’s make everyone’s desk clean.
On duty, on duty, my…
Good morning, Li.
Good morning
So you heard me…
I see, I’m on duty with Li today…
Because all the Clow Cards were captured
before summer break
we haven’t seen each other
for a while, you know?
– Yeah.
– How was your summer?
– Did you go anywhere?
– No.
– What about the beach?
– Didn’t go.
So, are you really
going back to Hong Kong?
Yeah.
Since the Clow Cards
already have a new Mistress,
I have to explain to Mother.
I see…
It’s not like we’ll
never see each other again.
Tha… That’s right.
Thank goodness
– Good morning.
– Good morning, Tomoyo!
– What’s wrong?
– Lately,
there has not been many occasions
for you to wear my special costumes.
I still have so many,
many, many costumes
that I would like you to wear for me
And then, to film you in these costumes…
It would have been so great!
– Tomoyo…
– So great!
– Good morning!
Thanks for the letter.
Did you get my reply?
Yeah, I got everyone’s
reply already.
Oh yeah,
I got one from Miss Mizuki too.
She replied you too.
Is she doing well?
Yeah, she said she’s studying
hard in England.
Do you know who’s
our class teacher
for the 2nd semester
Come to think of it,
who could it be?
Tomoyo, do you know?
Yes, I saw our class teacher just now.
– Who is it? Who is it?
– Teacher is here.
Get to your seats!
It is Mr Terada!
So,
summer break ended yesterday,
did all of you bring your homework?
Yes!
Today, I’ll introduce you
to your new classmate
who’ll be studying with us.
Now, Come in.
He seems kind.
This is Eriol Hiiragizawa
from England.
I hope you’ll all get along
I’m Eriol Hiiragizawa.
Nice to meet you.
Your sear… Let’s see…
That’s it.
How about the one next to Li?
Hello.
What’s this?
Did I meet him somewhere before?
Miss Kaho,
class 5-2 has a new student today
It’s a boy named
Eriol Hiiragizawa.
He seems kind.
But…
For some reason,
I feel like this is
not the first time we met
Same here.
Hi… Hiiragizawa??
I’m so sorry that I scared you.
Thank goodness.
Is it all right
if I sit next to you?
Somehow I also feel that
today is not the
first time we meet.
It is strange, isn’t it?
We might have met before.
We might have met before
in our previous lives
Do you mind
telling me your name?
M… My name
is Sakura Kinomoto.
What a beautiful name of the flower
that blooms in spring
May I call you Sakura?
Yes, Hiiragizawa.
Please call me Eriol,
Sakura.
That’s like
a promising development
in a girl’s comic
Keeping an eye
on Sakura like that…
Li, did something happen?
Because you’ve been
having such a difficult face all day.
Li has a new thing
to worry about today, right
Wha… Th… Th… That’s not…
If there’s anything
I can do
let me know.
You helped me so much
when we were
gathering the Clow Cards.
This time I wanna
be of help to you.
But you’re
going back to Hong Kong soon.
I can’t go yet.
I’m still staying here.
– Really?
– Yes.
I see now! That’s great!
Thank goodness!
Ice-cream bars
over there are very good.
I’ll go buy some.
Because a new rival
seemed to have appeared.
If you went back to Hong Kong,
it would be like giving her up, right?
I said that’s not it!
Thanks for waiting.
Here, Tomoyo, Li.
– Thank you very much.
– Thanks.
Touya Big Brother!
Don’t do that, Touya!
You want some too, Yuki?
I’ll buy you another one, okay?
It… It’s okay. No need.
What’s wrong, big brother?
A new student came
to our class today.
We have one too.
But what about it?
Touya!! I was looking for you!!
Oh? You must be
Touya’s little sister!
Yes! I’m Sakura Kinomoto.
I’m Nakuru.
Nakuru Akizuki.
Just as I thought,
you’re so cute!!
Hey! don’t be such a…
Later, Touya! See you tomorrow!
– Ice-cream.
– She took it…
– Is something wrong?
– Nothing.
Thanks for your ice-cream!
Oh! It is raining…
Oh no! The laundry!
This is the last basket.
Just leave it there.
I’ll put them in afterwards.
Thank you.
Then I’m going to my part-time job.
You have part-time today?
It’s written on the board.
Then, what about dinner?
No, thanks.
Oh no,
I bought dinner for 3 persons…
Transfer student?
What kinda person?
His name is Eriol Hiiragizawa.
Aerial?
What kanji is that?
It’s not a kanji!
E-RI-O-L.
He’s from England.
England…
No!!!
So, what kanji is that?
Forget it!
You weren’t listening at all.
…and now the forecast
in your local area.
What incredible rain.
And it was so sunny
in the afternoon too.
What?
What’s in that drawer?
The book of Clow Cards!
What?!
Kero!!
I might be troubling you
from here on
but if it is you,
it will be okay for sure
This voice…
This is Clow’s voice…?
– Sakura
– Kero,
Clow’s voice
came from the book…
Clow’s voice?
What’s this?
SA-KU-RA?
My name?!
what does this mean?!
Kero,
did you sense that just now?
Yeah, I sensed it too.
What’s this aura…
The rain in Tomoeda
will continue to fall.
It’s a limited area raining.
It’s cloudy in the surrounding area.
where the rest of the area
will enjoy another sunny day.
This isn’t just
any normal rain after all.
So… why this?
Mysterious rain in Tomoeda!
This’s also Card Captor’s
call, Right?
My, it has been so long
since the last filming!
Kero?
Be careful.
I sense very powerful aura.
But all the Clow Cards
have been gathered.
What’s this?
– Kero! I’ll leave Tomoyo to you!
– Okay!
Sakura!
Sakura! What’re you playing?
Use magic!
O, Key which hides
the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura,
command thee under contract.
Release!
Why?
Watch out!
Are you okay, Sakura?
Kero, the key…
This aura…
Impossible.
It can’t be… But…
Sakura! Are you ok?
Sakura,
invite the snow-rabbit over tomorrow.
(Yukito = snow-rabbit)
Yukito?
Why Tsukishiro?
Yue is the one I need to talk to.
Yue…
I want to check with him
on something.
Why doesn’t the new Key
turn into a wand?
And
this aura…