How beautiful.
This must be…
[Sakura, Yukito, and the summer festival]
Must be…
It must be?
Umm…
What a rude person you are.
What kind of voice is that
to have when you see somebody’s face?
It was because you were
so close all of a sudden.
You can’t sleep in forever
just because it’s Summer vacation.
I was just about to wake you up.
So, it must be what?
I forgot.
You surprised me,
so I forgot what it was.
Hey, hey. Dreams are important.
Especially the dreams of those
with power have a high chance
of being a premonition.
You have to remember them.
Yeah.
The breeze feels nice,
doesn’t it Kero-chan?
Summer is almost over.
So, did you finish your summer
vacation homework?
Eh!
Today it is my turn to make dinner.
What should I make?
I foresee hell on the last day
of summer vacation.
OK, we have cabbage and flour, great.
Today I will make okonomiyaki!
Yay! Okonomiyaki!
Well, I’m going grocery shopping.
If you’re making okonomiyaki,
I want modayaki!
Modayaki! Modayaki!
Moda…
OK, the one with soba on top, right?
Modayaki.
I bought the soba, and the sauce.
A festival?
It ends today?
I’ll invite Tomoyo-chan
and check it out.
Maybe I’ll take a side trip.
He isn’t here after all.
Too bad.
Sakura-chan.
Eh!
Over here.
Good afternoon.
Yukito-san!
On an errand?
Yes! But I am finished already.
Would you like to have some tea?
May I?
Yeah.
I just got some good snacks.
Ah, wait a second,
I’ll go over there now.
I am glad I took a side trip.
Here.
I made it a little thin.
Touya told me that
you like thin tea.
Thank you.
Umm, why were you on the roof?
Because the weather was nice.
Where is your family?
On a trip.
My grandpa and grandma
get along really well
And are on a summer trip.
Just the two of them.
This time it is to Atami.
I see.
So Yukito-san is alone.
I wonder if he is lonely.
It’s good.
Yes.
Delicious.
Right?
It was a really cute dog,
this time they are going
to let me give it a bath.
It would be good
if she doesn’t hate the bath.
It’s this late already?
I have to go home.
Is it your turn to cook today?
Yes.
Shall I walk you home?
Eh!
You pack looks pretty
full and heavy.
And I have something
I have to give back to Touya.
I’ll take you home.
Is it OK?
Yeah.
Today really is a good day.
You would eat it in a time like that.
That’s right.
So I ate the gelatin
in the refrigerator.
But it was my brother’s.
So it was you who ate it after all.
B… Big brother.
You really surprised me.
It was because you were walking
without looking where you were going.
Umm, it’ll be done in just a bit.
But is it OK to stay here?
Stay and eat. You’re home alone,
aren’t you?
Well then, I’ll help out.
Should I grate these?
Yes.
Oh yeah, did you know
there’s a festival?
Yes, I thought I would
invite Tomoyo-chan and go later.
Just the two of you?
Yeah.
Umm…
I’m going too.
Why?
Because I want to.
Eh?
May I come too?
Yes! Then I will go call
Tomoyo’s place and ask her.
You’re worried because
there are many people at the festival,
and it’s dangerous to come home so late.
What a kind big brother.
Shut up.
Tomoyo-chan said she could.
Well then, the four of us will go.
Yeah.
Do you know the place?
Yes. It was the Tsukimine shrine,
wasn’t it?
Yes.
My hand slipped a bit.
Eh?
This is how okonomiyaki has to be.
Maybe I will wear this one.
I wonder if this one is better?
Going out?
There is a festival.
That is good.
A present. Be sure to buy one.
Yeah.
It looks very good.
My dad made it for me last year.
Your father really can do anything.
I brought my video camera.
You must let me film you.
Umm…
Over here.
Let’s go.
Do you want that red one?
Yes.
Mister.
Ah!
Here.
Thank you!
How cute.
Sakura-chan is cute too.
Do you want one too, Touya?
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
What shall we do next?
Umm, umm… the ring toss.
It was over there right?
Let’s go check it out.
OK.
You should have done it
too, Tomoyo-chan.
Aren’t you bored just watching.
No, being able to film
Sakura enjoying herself
is fun enough.
Eh!
Chiharu-chan! Yamazaki-kun!
Hey.
Sakura-chan.
Good evening.
Good evening,
did you two just come?
Yeah, I heard from Naoko-chan.
Naoko-chan likes these things.
Shrines and temples.
And scary stories too.
Naoko and the others didn’t come?
Naoko-chan and Rika-chan
have piano lessons today.
I see.
Ah, how cute.
Now that you mention it,
do you know the beginning
of water balloons?
In the beginning of the Edo era
it was like a normal feature
to the common people.
Did that have rubber that long ago?
This is rubber isn’t it?
Yes.
Yeah, that’s why long ago
they made them out of glass.
At last it starts to get suspicious.
Glass?
Well, then they couldn’t
play with them like this.
No, it seems they went to
great measures to figure out
how to play with them
without breaking the glass.
Eh!
It’s a lie. A lie.
What was that?
He hit it.
You’re very good.
Did you get these all
on your own Li-kun?
Well, yeah.
That’s impressive.
May I have these?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Speaking of shooting games,
a long time ago…
Yes. Yes.
Yamazaki-kun, I want that one.
If you get it for me,
I will bring you some
home-made cookies tomorrow.
We have to go pray.
Eh? Why pray?
That I will survive.
What was that? You’re horrible!
They really do get along well.
Chiharu-chan and Yamazaki-kun.
Yeah.
Isn’t it good that you got
that water balloon
from Yukito-san?
Yeah.
Eh?
Did he hear that?
You hear the name of
the one you love
no matter the situation.
Umm…
Yukito gave this…
Something about me?
Do you have some business
with my sister?
Yay!
That’s it.
Sakura-chan,
don’t you want that one?
You like rabbits don’t you?
Yeah.
Really. It’s cute.
Yes.
Wait!
One more time.
Quite a competition.
You’re right.
Shall we go somewhere else?
I will watch their splendid
competition from here.
Eh?
Sakura-chan, don’t worry and go ahead.
But…
It’s not often that there’s a festival.
Well then, Sakura-chan.
Sure.
I wonder if we are behind the shrine?
I wonder if they are fireflies?
But there isn’t any river near here.
Shall we go look?
Yes.
Ah!
This is…
It is the same as
the dream this morning.
They’re beautiful aren’t they?
Yes.
Almost like snow.
Yukito-san.
What?
I…
I got it.
Eh!
They couldn’t come to a conclusion,
so the man running
the stall gave them two.
It was a climactic battle.
Really.
Eh?
Is this for me too?
Yeah.
Ah!
If you don’t want it, give it back.
I want it.
But I wanted to be left
like that a bit longer.
Oh yeah. There was a
shaved ice stall over there.
Let’s go.
I’ll treat you in thanks.
Touya, you come too.
Sakura-chan. Tomoyo-chan.
Sakura-chan?
Something is bothering me.
Let’s hurry.
Well come soon, go ahead of us.
What is it?
I saw it in a dream.
The same as this.
Could it be?
Release.
Return to your rightful form.
Clow Card.
Glow.
Just like Kero-chan said,
that dream was a premonition.
The continuation to the “It must be…”
I said in the dream was “…a Clow Card.”
OK, Cut.
So it was a Clow Card after all.
I couldn’t tell at all.
I didn’t feel an aura either.
It seems Li-kun didn’t notice either.
Yeah.
But because of this card was
really happy.
Thank you.
Shall we get going?
Yeah.