All done
Big Brother, breakfast is ready!
– Dad!
– Good morning!
Good morning!
What’s that? Calendar?
A really old one…
That’s right.
Nadeshiko had it
when she was still a model.
Say, is it alright if I keep this?
Of course.
Alright!
Thanks!
Breakfast is done so
come down when you’re ready!
OK!
[Sakura and the Calendar of Memories]
What’s it?
That’s Mother’s…
Yeah! Her calendar.
I found it while
I was cleaning the room earlier.
Brother, your brithday is written here
It is written there because my birthday
comes one every four years.
Years when his birthday
wasn’t written on calendars,
mother used to big signs.
My birthday is written here too!
Thanks Mom.
– Thanks for the meal.
– I’ve to go too.
Goodbye.
I’m off!
Good morning!
Good morning, Tomoyo.
Did something good happen?
Can you tell?
I can guess if it’s about you.
It was a calendar that my mother used.
I see.
Calenders you see,
A long time ago,
there were written on the ground…
but as it was written on the ground,
the wind would blow over it
and the rain would fall on top of it
making it disappear.
Or a wandering dog or cat would
walk over it making
the markings unreadable,
so it was troublesome.
Therefore,
in order to help preserve the calendar
employment for the so called
Calendar Watch was created.
There he goes with lies again.
– He has a creative imagination.
– Good morning.
Good morning.
Hiiragizawa, you know too, right?
About the calendar.
You know, Hiiragizawa-kun
isn’t like you so he doesn’t lie.
I know about it very well.
In ancient Europe,
everyone yearned for a position
in the Calender Watch.
And then, anyone who tried
to deface the calendar
would be severely punished, right?
Yes,
there are many account of the calendar
in history books.
The most
famous calendar
has to be the one in Egypt
which spans 100 km.
That’s probably the working
of extraterrestrials.
I think we’ll be good friends,
Hiragizawa-kun.
Likewise.
– So, it is true?
– I don’t think so.
It looks like Hiiragizawa-kun
and Yamazzaki-kun are the same type.
It must’ve been hard
for people back then.
Why don’t you try playing with me?
You’re doing very well, Touya.
You’re pretty good, Touya.
I don’t think I’ve
heard that piece before…
It’s a piece that
my mother composed.
It’s a very beautiful melody.
– Yuki…
– What’s it?
– I… I
– That’s so great!
So great, so great!!
Touya, you’re so good
at playing the piano!
Ah, Tsukishiro-kun.
The archery club president
was calling for you.
There was something he wanted
to ask you about the contest.
Thanks.
Then I guess I’ll be leaving, Touya.
There’s so many thing written here.
I wonder if this one’s for work.
Brother’s birthday is here.
Tomoyo’s mother’s birthday!!
If I had known about it earlier,
I could have given her a present.
I’ll remember next time
and be sure to give her something!
Grandfather… Mom’s?
That means, he’s my
great-grandfather?
I wonder what
he was like…
– I’m home.
– Welcome home.
– Dad, dad…
– Yes…
Today is Great-grandfather’s
birthday, right?
Yes, it seems so.
Hey,
mom gave him presents, right?
Mother’s presents
were always hand-made.
But I thought Mom
was bad at cooking and sewing…
Yes, but mother
put all her effort into making them.
Hey, is Grandfather still?
He’s very lively,
but I still haven’t had
a chance to meet him.
Why not?
Because Grandfather
cherished Mother with all his heart.
I’m
the bad guy
who stole Mother away from him…
My Dad is not a bad guy!
I don’t
remember anything about Mom at all
…but she always
looks so happy in the photos!
And if you two weren’t here,
I would’ve never been born…
…and I wouldn’t be so happy now!
Thanks!
That’s it!
Is it alright if
I make something for Grandfather?
A hand-made present like Mom used to do!
Something I made might be no good.
– Of course not.
– That’s good.
Ah! I might not make it
even if I start right now!
If you do your best,
you could have something
made by tonight.
But we won’t be able
to get it to him by tonight.
It is alright.
There’s a person who will be able
to deliver the present.
Grandfather will surely be happy.
Is it alright like this?
Yes, now bind it here and here.
– Ow!
– Are you OK?
Yeah, I’ll do my best.
It’s all done.
It’s all done, done done!
It’s all done!
Hey, hey,
how did Mom deliver her presents?
She sent a letter and some nadesico
flowers with the present.
Flowers!?
Hoe!! The flower shops is closed already!!
That’s it.
I’m home.
Play the organ for me!
It’s great Grandfather’s birthday today!
Play that melody
that Mom composed
and record it to tape!
Please play for us.
I see, then today is.
Kero, Kero!!
What are you going playing around?
I wanna make some flowers!
Great-grandfather’s birthday huh?
But you told me before
that I can only use
the Sakura cards
when I really need to.
Can I use the magic
to make some flowers?
Do you really want to make them?
No matter what happens?
Go for it…
If these are your true feelings,
then your magic won’t rampant again.
O Key which hides the power of the stars,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Release!
Flower!
You did it!
They all understand.
Dad, Mom, and my brother,
they understand that I’m happy…
Calling for me
was a good idea, Teacher.
Grandfather’s birthday… is it?
Nadesico gave him one every year.
Birthday present.
Home made gifts to which
even empty words cannot be made to
lie in describing their looks…
and a letter written describing
her happiness
after getting married to
teacher Kinomoto, and…
…nadesico flowers…
This is something Sakura made,
not just anybody.
So I’ll have it delivered
to grandfather tonight!
Thank you.
I see.
It was ok to ask Tomoyo’s mom…
I hope Grandfather
will be happy with me…
Yes, Kinomoto Residence.
Ah, Sonomi kun.
Thank you for yesterday.
Sakura was happy as well.
Eh?
Grandfather?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No, I’m sorry that I called you
out on such short notice.
Not at all.
Please sit.
I’m sorry I didn’t come by more often.
How many years has it been?
This is the first time since
we gave you the letter of
invitation to our wedding.
Has it been that long already…
I got it,
from Sonomi-san.
It was a heart-filled letter.
Nadesico was so happy,
and now Sakura
is happy as well…
Can you deliver this to
Sakura and Touya?
In return for the gift.
They’ll be happy to receive it.
You…
There’s something I’ve been meaning
to tell you for a while now.
Thank you.
And,
I’m sorry.
I knew it all along.
You were the one Nadesico chose
and that you would make her happy,
more than anybody else…
But…
Nadesico-san
was still sixteen…
On top of that,
I was a new, naive teacher.
So I didn’t know how much
pain I could possibly cause.
It was only natural
that you wouldn’t give your precious
granddaughter to someone like that.
No, I was just being stubborn.
I was so lonely when
she left me all of a sudden.
I wish I could have told her as well,
that she had chosen a great partner
My grand daughter
was the happiest in the world.
I’m sure
she’s listening… somewhere.
I’m home.
– Welcome home.
– What’s this?
Ah, this is for you and
Touya from grandfather.
Saying thank you for the birthday gift.
Is grandfather here?
Where? Where?
No, a runner delivered it.
Ah, is that right?
But he was happy for me.
I’m glad.
Can I open it?
Of course.
Yours is the one on the bottom.
Why don’t you try it on?
What is this?
What is it this time?
Ahh, it is the clothes
from the time we went to resort.
Putting it aside,
and not even saying a word.
Looks good.
I wonder if Grandfather acknowledged…
How mother was happy,
– and how we’re all happy…
– Yes.
Do you think we will get
to meet Grandfather someday?
Of course.
That’s great, right? Mom.