Are you ok?
Yeah…
I’m just a little sleepy…
You don’t have a fever.
I’m just a litte sleepy,
so,
both of you,
go to work and go to school.
I’m ok.
Really.
Then I’m leaving now. ok?
Bye.
I’ll skip club today
and come home.
I’ll come home
as soon as possible too.
Geez,
things start happening again,
don’t they…
[Sakura and The Dangerous Piano]
Your brother noticed me after all!
On top of that,
he’s mad at me!!
Hey, Sakura.
You’re just playing sleepy,
aren’t you?
Hey, Sakura!
I can’t open my eyes at all…
Sakura is absent today.
I wonder what’s wrong.
Li,
would you like to go visit Sakura
at home today
Wh… Why me?
I’m sure Sakura will be happy.
You’re good at this,
Hiiragizawa.
Really.
Awesome,
Hiiragizawa.
I am used to making these.
– Do you make them often at home?
– Yes.
How many people are in your family?
Two. No,
three people
Oh, I see…
I wonder if Sakura’s doing okay…
Sorry to keep you waiting
The store was so crowded,
so it took a little longer.
Let’s eat.
Are n’t you eating
a lot more than usual?
I’m just more hungry than usual.
Even though I ate five times
more than normal for breakfast.
Yuki…
I think you don’t realize,
so let me tell you…
About you, I…
I jump!
Nakuru’s awesome!
That’s so cool!
Challenging the basketball team,
that’s awesome!
She look like Tsukishiro!
Touya!!
Did you see me?
Akizuki is awesome.
But she isn’t in any school clubs.
She’s like you.
You mean not being
in any school clubs?
Not only that…
– I slept well!
– You sure did…
3 o’clock already?!
Tomoyo! Li!
Sakura!
How’re you feeling?
I’m totally fine!
Just a little sleepy.
That’s right,
she slept like a pig.
Kero.
Oh right, we made these
in home economics lesson today.
The cakes look good!
I made this one,
Li made the others.
Thanks…
The one the brat made
is just okay.
What did you say?!
Bring it on anytime!
Take it easy.
So, the Key
wouldn’t transform
unless you used a new spell?
But why were you so sleepy today
that you couldn’t not even get up?
Like the wand,
the cards have to take a new form.
Yesterday,
when Sakura used her magic,
a new magic formation appeared
that is different from Clow’s…
Look.
Only the card Firey has changed,
Right?
The back of the card is different too.
The key transferred into the wand,
but it wouldn’t work on the card.
And so I thought, maybe the card
had to be changed too…
You changed it with your own power?
I don’t know…
No, Sakura herself
created this Firey Card
from the Clow Card
A card that I created by myself…
Then, this is no longer a Clow Card,
But a Sakura-chan Card
created by Sakura-chan, isn’t it?
Fighting against something
even more powerful
with her own Sakura-chan Card…
That’s splendid!
Calling it Sakura-chan
Card is a bit…
Then how about “Sakura Card”?
That too…
Then being sleepy…
Up until now,
she’s been using Clow Cards
that were created by Clow,
Of course, Magic Powers are
needed from the person who use them…
But other than that, Clow’s powers
residing in the cards
were the source of magic.
so it wouldn’t be nearly as tiring.
But the new card
was created by Sakura’s own magic.
That’s different.
And so I became really sleepy.
Last night when you were
caught in danger,
neither Yue or I
were able to do anything.
Don’t worry about it.
I’m okay now.
No, this isn’t something.
I just don’t worry about.
I wouldn’t worry
about it if we were in our false shapes,
but both of us were in our true forms.
You were in your true forms?!
The only people
who can freeze both Yue and I…
… are Sakura, who is the current
Mistress of the cards, and…
…Clow Reed.
Miss Kaho,
a mysterious event happened again.
Somehow,
I now have the star wand and a new card,
Oh, a new card
being one that
was created from a Clow Card
That was what Kero said.
But at that time,
neither Yue or Kero were able to move.
And the only one who could do
such a thing to them was Clow,
Kero said.
But…
Kero-san…
But Clow has passed away
a long time ago.
Eriol…
Sakura
Did you notice I was watching?
You play very well.
Thank you very much!
Oh, this is the song
Tomoyo has been practising in the choir.
Tomoyo
That’s wonderful!
I heard you were practicing
the song and I remembered it.
You have a wonderful voice.
Thank you very much.
That’s right! Tomoyo,
how about you sing
while accompanied by Eriol?
– Now?
– You can’t?
I don’t mind.
=When I am lonely,=
=I seek warmth=
=I trace far into the distance=
=my dear memories=
=Holding her=
=beloved child in her arms,=
=a mother sings=
=a lullaby under the sun=
=Someday,=
=in the clear blue sky,=
=everyone can fly freely=
=as high as possible.=
=Fly freely…=
=With flowers blooming=
=in those hearts.=
Awesome! Awesome!
That’s wonderful, Tomoyo!
Eriol too, thank you!
You are not leaving yet?
I was thinking of
going home with Tomoyo.
Daidouji is still in the music Room?
She’s practicing
for the next competition.
She’s staying really
late to practise.
No one is here anymore.
It’s a solo competition.
I heard the song
during lunch break.
It was a really beautiful song.
Eriol was playing
the piano for her…
It was wonderful.
What’s matter?
Nothing.
Did Kerberos say anything after that?
About Clow?
Kero said he didn’t
know either.
because Clow
should have already passed away
long time ago.
What in the world is happening…
It is Tomoyo’s voice…
Tomoyo!!
Sakura!
– What happened?
– The piano suddenly…
WATCH OUT!!
Why did the piano
move all of a sudden?
Clow’s aura…
Sakura…
Watch out!!
Get out of here!
We can’t get away
if we stay in the room!
– Right. Tomoyo!
– Okay.
Hurry up.
Did the piano just
move all of a sudden?
I started to practise
the song for the next competition,
and suddenly…
King of Thunder, DESCEND!!
– Thanks.
– I wonder if we are ok now.
It’s moving again.
It simply looks
like it would not let me go…
I see.
Tomoyo, would you help me with this?
Yes!
We might be able to do something.
=When I am lonely,=
=I seek warmth=
=I trace far into the distance=
=my dear memories.=
=Holding her=
=beloved child in her arms=
=a mother sings=
=a lullaby=
=under the sun.=
=On the cheek of the infant playing=
=in the dreamland…=
=…are the dimples of happiness…=
It is coming.
O Key which hides
the power of the stars,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura,
command thee under contract.
Release!
– It is here.
– Right!
O Card created by Clow,
discard thine old form and be reborn.
Under the name of Sakura,
thy new Mistress.
Song!
=Even after woken up from the dream,=
=there is still a smile.=
=Such as seed of kindness=
=remains in the heart=
=When a nervous heart…=
=It’s better…=
It is not moving.
Thank Gooddness.
Song turned into a Sakura Card too!
Just now,
I’m sure
I sensed Clow’s aura…
Sakura
Sakura!
Hey! Hang in there!
Things seem to be getting interesting.