Ah, Tomoyo-chan,
isn’t that the strawberry house?
It seems so!
This entire place
is the strawberry house!
This is so cool!
This is where we’ll pick
our strawberries in the morning.
And you can eat while you pick!
It’d be nice if we end up
with lots of strawberries!
I’m sure Yukito-san can eat a lot
If he had come!
I’m going to bring him some as gifts.
Yu-ki-to-san.
Kinomoto-san.
He… Here!
If you’re so slow,
you’ll get left behind.
I’m sorry.
Come to think of it,
are there strawberry hunts
in Hong Kong too?
You know, about strawberry hunts…
Strawberries were originated
from South America.
In the old days,
it’s not easy to eat strawberries.
It is because
Strawberries used to be different
and had legs to run around,
so people weren’t
able to catch a lot of them.
And for those people who wanted to eat
strawberries no matter what,
they would chase
after the strawberries,
which is how the name
‘strawberry hunt’…
Okay, okay, okay…
In order for them not to run,
strawberries were somehow
changed to what they are…
All these lies…
That was a lie?
I could tell right from the start.
[Sakura’s Merry Strawberry Hunt]
You will be using these containers
to pick your strawberries.
Okay!
Let’s do our best!
I promised Kero that I’ll bring
lots of them back as presents.
Oh, so this is the strawberry
park Sakura’s going’ to.
What?!
You can eat while you pick?!
So that means you can eat non-stop?
This is so good!
It’s no use just drooling
over these pictures…
The more I see,
the more the feeling of vain.
Sakura, hurry back!!
In the afternoon,
we will show you a video in the materials
room separated from the rest of the park.
It will focus on
how to make strawberry cakes
and desserts.
We will then follow some
of the examples
and put them in practice.
I hope you will enjoy it.
Yes!
Make cakes and desserts
with strawberries…
I wonder how it’s done.
Let us try to make some then!
Now this gentleman
will lead the way into the house.
And make sure you take
class notes afterwards, okay?
Okay!
Let’s go!
Oh, are you okay?
Yu… Yukito-san!
Sakura-chan?
Why are you here?
Good afternoon.
Isn’t that Sakura?
Onii-chan! What are you doing here?
Why are you in here?
I had it written clearly on the board,
that I have no school today
and I’m going to work part-time.
And so, I came along.
Yukito-san is here…
What’s wrong, Sakura-chan?
Oh yeah!
Do you like strawberry
cakes and desserts?
Yeah. I like them.
They’re teaching us how
to make them here!
I’ll do my best at it!
Umm… Would you like… to have some?
Of course!
I must get going!
Good-bye.
Sakura-chan is full of
energy today too.
Yeah, I guess she is.
I’ve gotta pick lots and
lots of strawberries!
It seems Sakura-chan
really loves to go on
school trips and camps.
But she seems especially happier
than usual today, don’t you think?
This is the place
the house supervisor mentioned before
– the materials room.
He said it was converted
from an old storehouse.
Let’s eat a lot.
Hey, what’s wrong, Shao Lan?
Let’s hurry!
Strawberries! Strawberries!
Strawberries!
How is it going? Did you pick a lot?
Yukito-san!
What’s wrong?
I want to pick tasty strawberries
but they all look
tasty to me.
Those tasty strawberries
First, you want to look for
very green leaves on top.
Then, the whole strawberry must be red,
without any white around the calyx.
You know a lot.
That’s what they told me.
Something you have to know
when you work here.
Oh, hold there.
This is what you should do
when you pick strawberries.
Hold the strawberry from underneath
and put your fingers
over the green calyx.
Then, break it gently on the stem.
I… I see…
What a nice shot!
To… Tomoyo-chan!
Li!
Are these… for me?
Yuki, it’s break time.
We picked so much!
It will be fun from now on too.
We’ll be making desserts
with these strawberries.
Maybe I’ll make some
and bring them to Mr. Terada-sensei.
Then I’ll make some for Yamazaki too.
Then I better pray again.
Why?
To make sure again
that I’ll be okay afterwards.
What did you say? Geez!
What did you mean by that?!
But it’s the first time I make it,
so I’m a little worried
how it’ll turn out.
Me too.
Here. ‘Aaaahh… ’
I’ll eat it myself.
That’s great.
Mei Lin, did you make
them all by yourself?
That’s right. I made them
the best I could
just for today.
Here. Say ‘Ahh… ’
I said I’ll eat it myself.
They look so good!
Don’t they? Wanna try some?
Are you sure?
Please help yourself.
Then, I’m eating!
Tastes so good!
Mei Lin, you’re really good at cooking!
I guess. No dish is ever
too hard for me!
I wish I can cook
as well as Mei Lin.
Then, for Yukito-san, I can…
Hey, have you heard?
They say the plans
for the afternoon have changed.
Why?!
I heard they couldn’t open the door
to the materials room
for this afternoon!
No way!
Strawberry desserts…
Where is the materials room?
Oh, it’s that storeroom along
the path we took to get here.
They really couldn’t open it?
Lem me go take a look.
I will go with you!
Shao Lan?
I wonder why they can’t open it.
It opens!
It seems everything is ready.
Then we should let the instructor know,
don’t you think?
Be careful!
Can’t you sense it?
It feels strange in here…
Sakura’s new class teacher
is called Mizuki-sensei, right?
You knew her before, right? Touya…
Or should I not ask?
I’ll tell you later.
Come to think of it, what are
Sakura-chan and the others
going to do this afternoon?
The materials room wouldn’t open, right?
Yeah. They couldn’t open the door
somehow, it seems…
Sakura-chan, she was so
looking forward to the afternoon.
It’s no use. It won’t open at all.
Leave it to me!
Don’t do it, Mei Lin!
It hurts…
Are you okay? Mei Lin-chan?
I can sense… a Clow Card.
I’m afraid, it’s the card, Lock.
Lock? Like a padlock?
And it has placed
a lock in this building.
What’s worse, this is a special card.
Even I don’t know to capture it.
A special card means not even
Windy, Watery,
and Firey would work…?
That’s right.
Oh no!
I have an idea.
How about asking Kero-chan
for some suggestions?
That’s right!
Condensed milk, condensed milk.
Double the sweetness!
Kero-chan’s not picking it up.
Just when we have a problem too! Geez.
We are in trouble.
This is the place!
This is no use.
It won’t open after all.
This is too bad.
Anyone over there?
Isn’t that Mei Lin-chan’s voice?
Are you in there?
Help us! The door won’t open!
We’re all trapped in here!
Don’t call the others.
But if it’s just us, we can’t get out!
But do you think
it’ll really open if
they try to open from the outside?
Besides,
if you call other people here,
we can’t use magic.
And then, she won’t be able to seal it.
Rika-chan and the others have left.
If we don’t hurry,
the teachers will get here.
Before that happens,
we must find a way to solve this.
But how?
If it’s a lock,
the right key should open it.
In order the open Lock,
there must be a magical key somewhere.
That’s possible!
It’s just like that time with Maze.
Because we’re within
the card’s domain like last time.
It cannot tell where it is.
What should we do?
In the meantime, we have
no other way but to look for it.
They were locked in?!
Yes.
Let’s go!
I’m going with you!
Geez.
What a troublemaker.
Have you told your teacher yet?
No, Mizuki-sensei isn’t around.
Chiharu-chan went
around looking for her
but couldn’t find her anywhere…
I cannot find it.
Geez,
where is it already?!
It’s not here either.
People are coming!
Watch out!
Mizuki-sensei?
Gimme your hand!
Li-kun!
Just now I saw
Mizuki-sensei outside the window.
What?!
It seems she was trying
to tell me something…
This is it! This!
If I try this on the lock…
They’re okay.
Kaho…
It’ll opens now.
What’s wrong?!
You can’t get away!
Before Lock hides away,
hurry!
Release!
Return to thy form
which thou should be!
Clow Card!
Hey! Sakura!
Onii-chan!
Are you okay?
Thank goodness,
Sakura-chan.
Are you okay?
Sorry to make you guys worry.
With this, we can probably resume
the original plans for the afternoon.
But…
This is all messed up.
If everyone helps clean up,
it’ll be okay.
Right?
Right!
Huh? Where’s Sakura-chan?
She is outside.
I’m glad the materials room opened.
Yuki…
What is it?
Forget it.
Sakura-chan!
Hmm… These are…
Are you sure?
Yes!
Thanks, Sakura-chan.
It tastes really good.
In other words,
it was a really fun outing.
I was really happy. Yu-ki-to-san!
Oh, I’m glad for ya.
So, how about some presents for me
who stayed home and behaved so well?
Don’t tell me
you gave all that dessert
to that snow-rabbit guy…
(Yukito = snow-rabbit)
Ac… Actually that was it.
How dare you?!!
I… I didn’t forget about you.
But Yukito-san
was enjoying it so much,
I couldn’t ask him
to save some…
so…
Unforgivable!
You’re such a fool!
I’m so sorry!