To your house?
Yes, I’m having trouble with something
Sakura-chan,
can you come to my house tomorrow?
I’m happy to be going to your house,
but what is the trouble?
I’ll explain that tomorrow
I wonder what happened to Tomoyo-chan
I can’t breathe!
It’s nothing
Don’t do that Kero-chan
But the air in here
It’s just a little longer so bear it
I’m at my limit already
Just a little longer OK? OK?
It’s at the one after next so hold on
[Sakura, Tomoyo, and the big house]
This is strange. I think it is in this area
What? Can’t you find Tomoyo’s house?
Well, let me see
It should be in this area
She said it was right after the bus stop
Somebody will see you
There isn’t anybody around here
Huh!
What is it?
I found Tomoyo’s house
Eh? Where? Where?
Ummm…
What are you doing, Kero-chan?
Take a look
All of this?
Hello Who is it?
This is Kinomoto
Ah, welcome I will open the gate now
Eh!
Sakura-chan
Hello
Welcome
Hey Tomoyo
Hello Kero-chan
So, come this way
Woo…
This really is a big house
Young lady
Young lady?
Where shall I bring the tea?
Bring three to my room
Three?
Please take care of it
Amazing!
Amazing
Your room is really, really big
Is this your room over here too?
Yes
What do you use it for?
Eh?
Sakura-chan really is cute
Here, right here
The way the skirt flutters is wonderful
Ah, I am really cool too
Are you in the middle of making this?
I thought I would have you wear it
It looks pretty flashy
and nice Looks easy to move around in
But I feel sorta bad
having you make clothes for me
all the time
Not at all
I will film you in the clothes
that I make for you
It makes me happy
By the way,
what was the trouble you mentioned?
Actually
Oops
Come in
Mother, welcome home
Hello
Welcome
Sorry to intrude
I heard you came over to play,
so I rushed home from work
Why don’t we have some tea outside?
I bought some delicious cake
Eh?
Kero-chan
Cake?
So, let’s go
Ah, can you take that tea to the yard
Yes
Cake! My cake!
This aura
The cake from this shop is really good
Do you like cake?
Yes
That’s good
Nadeshiko also loved sweets
She said sweets went into another stomach
She would eat
this much cake all on her own
my dad said that too
She had a metabolism where
she wouldn’t get fat no matter how much she ate
That would be really nice
So, eat up
Thank you
How is it?
It’s very good!
You’re working hard
Yuki?
It shows that you have
worked at a gas station,
it suits you
Hello, Tsukishiro-san
Hello
I heard you were cleaning today,
so I brought something
Thank you
Well then, shall we have some tea?
The weather is nice, so let’s eat outside
Huh? Where is Sakura-chan?
At a friend’s place
At Tomoyo-chan’s house?
Which mean’s that mother
we met at the athletic meet
It’s Sonomi-san’s house
It’s OK.
Sonomi wouldn’t do anything
that would hurt Sakura
I swear it
You really do resemble Nadeshiko
Really?
Yes, Nadeshiko really was cute
Sonomi-chan
Hey, Sonomi-chan
Sonomi-chan, yesterday
Sonomi-chan, look
I want to tell you Sonomi-chan,
I am getting married
To Kinomoto-sensei
What’s wrong?
I just remembered something unpleasant
Say, can I call you Sakura-chan?
Yes
You are in the cheerleading club right?
I have heard you are
very athletic
Not at all
That is totally different
from Nadeshiko
When it came to athletic ability
she had no speed or coordination
What happened next?
Then Grandpa said,
for your next birthday
Nadeshiko?
Nadeshiko!
It seems I fell down
That’s dangerous Nadeshiko!
Don’t do that!
I’m fine Just a little further
I’ll go. Come down
Just a little further
You’re OK now
Nadeshiko!
Are you alright?
Yes
I’m sorry
I thought an angel
had fallen from the sky
Yes, that was when they met!
What do you mean by angel?
How disgusting
Sure Nadeshiko was cute like an angel, but
Excuse me
Umm You know my father right?
That’s right
Umm Umm
What sort of person was my dad?
Ah?
Dad talks about Mom a lot,
but he won’t tell me much about himself
My dad’s relatives are all gone,
and I don’t know any of my mother’s.
That’s why. That’s why
Your father was a horrible person
Umm…
He was cool, and kind.
He was a good cook,
and could do anything
If you look at him
as the person Nadeshiko loved,
he was a horrid, horrid person
Yes, to mention his faults
is to say he had none
That’s about it
Keep it secret that I said that
OK!
Dad?
A cold?
No, I’m fine
I wonder if somebody
is talking about me
Yes, and then he suddenly
There is a call from the main office
Oh, my
It’s me
Yes. Yes.
That’s a problem. Wait a moment
I’m sorry, this looks
like it will take a while
We will be playing in my room
I’m sorry
Not at all Thank you for the cake
Shall we go?
Sakura-chan! Let’s have dinner later!
Absolutely! Promise!
OK!
Your mother really is a wonderful person
Thank you
I’m sure my mom would he happy to hear that
Cake!
You left only me out
I was the only one who didn’t get any cake
You looked like you were
enjoying the cake, Sakura
I’m sorry, Kero-chan
I was watching you from
this room the whole time
Sorry to keep you waiting
This is your portion
Yay! Yay! Cake! Cake!
Yay! Yay!
Thank you
Anger over food is a scary thing
Great!
Geeze, there is a Clow Card’s
aura in here,
so it was sad being alone
Clow Card?
So there is
That’s our Kero-chan
The trouble is from this box
Actually I haven’t been able
to open this box
Did you lose the key?
I have the key right here
You can’t open it even with the key?
It’s the aura of a Clow Card
It’s faint, but I feel the aura
of a Clow Card from the box
Really
Please watch
We tried to open this box of
my mother’s for the first time in a while,
and it was Like this
This certainly is because of a Clow Card
I thought that might be so
That is why I called you
There is something very important
to my mother and me in here
It is in the box,
so it isn’t as if we have lost it,
but it is very important
All right! I’ll give it a try
I like both you
and your mom
I’ll try my best to open it
Sakura-chan
Well then, I will prepare
to video it right away
But what sort of card is it that
makes a box unable to be opened?
No matter how much I look there
isn’t anything strange about it
What is it?
Sakura
Yeah
Shield! It is the shield card
You saw a barrier like thing
just now, right?
I didn’t see anything
Those with magic power can see it
Why would it be on this box?
Could it be the card knows that
Tomoyo-chan is my friend
No, this one has good character,
it wouldn’t do something so bad
Shield exists to protect important things
It tries to protect the most
precious thing it can find
The contents of this box
must be very important
How can I return Shield to being a card?
That’s easy.
You have a sword that can
cut anything don’t you?
Oh yeah I should cut Shield with Sword
If Shield is cut, it will show it’s true form
Then you seal it without waiting
Card made by Clow, lend your power to me
Send the power held in a card to this key,
and give me power
Sword
Now!
OK!
Return to your rightful form,
Clow Card!
You did it Sakura
How heroic
What is it?
I should’ve had you wear this outfit
It opened
Thank you
Well, I was here, so it’s only natural
Can I look inside?
Yes
Oh no
Come in
Sorry about earlier
It opened
Yes
But how?
The spring was caught in the keyhole
So that’s why the key went flying
What a beautiful bouquet
This is
From your mother’s wedding
A bouquet of cherry blossoms
Nadeshiko loved cherry blossoms
She said ever since she was small that
She would name a daughter Sakura
Sakura?
You are that Sakura-chan
Oh yes.
I will make dinner tonight
If you have something you like,
let me know
Yes
The dining room is this way
Umm…
Tomoyo, give me a hand
OK
I’m doing nothing but hiding today
That is Tomoyo’s precious thing?
Yes
What is inside?
An eraser
An eraser?
Why is something like that so precious?
Because this is
We are sitting next to each other starting today
Pleased to meet you
Don’t you have an eraser? Here.
If you want it, you can keep it
This is the first thing I ever
received from Sakura-chan
Did you say something?
No, nothing
Tomoyo
Yes
Take care of my portion too
Yes, take care of the room until then
Yeah! Make lots of tasty things