Right, I’ll tell her later.
Because there are too little of
clow cards that can talk.
– There wasn’t any problem?
– Your father came in for a second.
I see. Thank you.
I’m very tired!
You did very well.
Today you transformed
four Sakura cards without a breath!
That is true.
But I don’t know with this speed,
when I will transform
all of the cards.
You can’t,
Don’t even think about transforming
all the cards at once again!
But if I don’t hurry
then the cards well lose their power.
I don’t want that to happen.
They won’t be losing
their power anytime soon.
This I know.
– I would like to ask…
– What?
There is someone coming!
Hurry and go back! Hurry and go back!
Yes.
You still haven’t slept?
Hurry up and sleep.
You are a big monster.
Hurry up and sleep then.
Tomorrow I have to go to school early
Change into your pajamas then.
[Sakura, Card and Present]
Sakura, I’ve been thinking.
Does your brother know
what we are doing?
I’m gonna be late!
Are you listening? You brother he…
Tell me later.
I think that
so you should be…
he also has some powers
Yeah brother is very talented.
Piano, Drawing,
but he still loves me a lot.
Thats not what I’m saying!
Calm down!
If he knew then he would ask me
a lot of questions.
Good Morning Dad, Brother
Morning, Sakura-san
MORNING Brother!
Amennn…
Hurry up and eat.
Oh, it looks like
somebody is hungry.
You should save some food
for other people.
Because you are a monster.
How mean of brother!
He probably knows but he’s not saying anything!
It’s something that he would do!
It’s what Kero-chan thought.
I’m leaving!
Be careful.
It’s very cold!
It’s a Christmas Tree!
This years who should I give
Christmas presents to?
Tomoyo-chan, Chiharu-chan,
Rika-chan, Naoko-chan,
and Dad, Brother
and Yukito-san
It seems like there’s
someone I’m missing.
– Who is it?
– Hey.
Do you know what you’re getting for dad?
Not yet. What should I get?
Dad really wants a money bag.
So he can use it.
Alright, I am going to
buy a money bag for dad!
– Do you have enough money?
– Is it expensive?
It’s more than you can afford.
I really want to make dad happy,
but I don’t have enough money.
What do I do?
I’m also getting dad
a money bag for a Christmas present.
– We can give it to him together.
– Really?
I’m thinking we should go buy it today.
I want to go too!
Yukito-san isn’t coming?
What’s wrong?
Then at 4:00 I’ll come here
and wait for you.
I’ll see you at 4.
Morning.
Morning Yuki.
Hey Yuki, Yuki…
Touya, morning
You came here early?
Because I am very tired.
So I came early to sleep.
Yuki, Yuki,
– YUKI!
– What…
If you keep on acting
this way then you will fall.
Yuki, you are…
– GOOD MORNING!
– What do you want?
I really wanted to see you, Touya-kun!
You saw me yesterday at school.
But I haven’t seen you
in the last 12 hours!
Did you sleep well?
– Stop holding on to me! Let go!
– I don’t want to!
Morning!
Shao Lan-kun, you wrote
my name on the board?
Yeah.
Right, Mei Lin-chan wrote me a note.
She wrote…
She wrote this. What does this mean?
It means my very good friend.
I have to hurry and write her back!
Right,
does Hong Kong celebrate Christmas?
Do you give Christmas presents?
You give them to your good friends.
Then I’ll give a Christmas
present to you!
But my allowance is very small
so I can only give small things.
What?
Um… I…
Talking about Christmas presents…
Before they kept Christmas trees outside.
Then on top they put a lot of good food.
But outside is so cold,
won’t the food freeze?
Right,
That’s why they made frozen food.
Cake is also ice cream cake…
I will look around.
Where will Sakura-san play?
Do you want me to help
get your dad’s present?
Brother is going is waiting for me.
Sorry, but I can’t go shopping with you.
I’m also going to be busy
so don’t be worried!
Doing what?
Because its about to be Christmas!
I have to get a present for you!
Christmas Present! I’ll make a very good
video tape of Sakura-chan
I have to hurry and finish taping!
You don’t really want to make that…
I’m leaving now!
I also have to hurry and
write this stuff down.
Shao Lan-kun, you can put this board back
to the classroom then you can go.
I’ll be done writing soon.
I’ll write then.
Writing those words down is easier
I’ll write the words ok?
You go buy Christmas presents…
So, excuse me.
See you tomorrow.
Bleh, why didn’t I say it?
A very pretty piece of music
Thank you very much.
This is a thank you song.
On a mountain there was a place.
I want to go there for Christmas.
So today I’m playing this song.
That’s incredible.
It gives warm feelings…
Its really great that you can
play such a great song.
Playing this song is to thank
even the little things.
Small Thanks?
I’m playing this song
to thank the flowers,
water and air.
You can only use this kind
of thanks with the piano
Flowers, water, air?
It’s not for people.
It’s only for things.
You can go by yourself?
Last time I went to sleep
I was very tired.
So don’t worry…
Yuki.
– What?
– I really want to tell you,
– You are…
– Touya-kun!!!
Let’s go home together ok?
How come you came here again?
Were you thinking of me?
– Of course not!
– So, I’ll see ya tomorrow.
Hey! Yuki!
– Are you happy now?
– What did you say?
She left already.
Shao Lan-kun!
I thought you left early.
I was doing something else.
Shao Lan-kun, what are you doing?
Nothing…
Your brother still hasn’t come.
Bye-bye!
Shao Lan-kun!
What?
I want to ask you,
what does it mean
to thank the flowers, water and air?
I’m sorry, asking you
such things all of a sudden.
No problem…
I want to thank
someone in some kind of way.
Though, I don’t really understand why…
Sorry!
– This is…
– Clow-san’s presence!
I’ll go look and you can stay here.
No you can’t, I want to go too.
But I thought you had to wait right here.
Your brother will be worried.
You’re right…
Oh yeah!
O Key which hides the forces of darkness,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract
Release!
Mirror!
Mirror-san, I need your help again.
– Yes.
– That’s great!
I…
Please go with my brother to buy stuff.
– I…
– You can’t?
– No, it’s not that.
– Thank you.
Hey, lets go!
When can I tell her?
Eh!?
Go with her brother to buy stuff?
I can really feel it,
it’s Clow-san’s presence.
It seems like something isn’t right.
Is it coming?
Were you waiting for long?
Shall we go now?
You’re not Sakura are you?
I…
It’s that direction, right?
If I go there now,
then you’ll be troubled right?
Let’s go together and buy stuff.
Yes.
Jump!
King of thunder, descend!
– Thank you!
– It’s coming!
It’s coming again?
I don’t know how to defeat this.
You can’t use that,
so how are we going to defeat this?
Sakura!
Right! That card!
O Key which hides
the forces of the stars,
reveal thy true form before me.
I, Sakura, command thee under contract.
Mist!
It worked.
Hey, are you ok?
Yeah I’m fine.
What’s wrong?
I know what it was. Right!
Will he be at the piano?
Shao Lan-kun, sorry I have to go now.
What?
Don’t worry, I won’t tell Sakura.
I bought this when we were
buying dad’s present.
Thank you for coming with me today.
I shouldn’t give this to you so early.
But this is your Christmas present.
This is for me?
Your hair is really long right?
Thank you very much.
I should be thanking you.
Thank you for always helping Sakura.
Sakura! How come you came home so late?
Where did you go?
You made me worried.
Sorry, Sorry!
You’re back?
I want you to listen to this.
You want me to listen?
Yup.
What is that?
This is all of the cards present!
Thank you to all of you for helping me
out when I’m in a bad situation.
I want to thank all of the cards
for always helping me out.
Later you will help me with a lot more.
I…
Before, I wanted to tell you something
What?
You are always helping us
and changing us to new cards.
We really would like to thank you.
All of us like you a lot.
So whenever you need our help,
please call on us.
Ok!
Huh? Was that ribbon there before?
Sakura, can I ask you a question?
What, Kero-chan?
You don’t know how to play the piano.
So how did you get that song?
Eriol-kun, will you play the piano,
I want to give that song to somebody!
I thought what should I
get for the cards?
But it was Eriol-kun who helped me.
– Oh I see!
– What do you mean “Oh I see”!
I spent a lot of work making that!
You can’t even play the piano
but you used your heart instead.
Thank you.
All of us really like you,
so keep working, Sakura!!
Yup!