[Sakura’s wonderful friend]
Sakura.
I can’t eat any more.
Who was it that set
the alarm to seven o’clock?
Weren’t you going to wake up early?
Huh? Osaka accent?
There is nobody with
an Osaka accent in my family.
The TV…
isn’t on.
Which means…
What is it?
A stuffed animal?
You’re still half asleep.
Hey, wake up.
Oh yeah, the guard of the Clow Cards.
Finally awake?
I’m the beast of the seal Cerberus.
Oh yeah,
A book Clow Card
I found in our basement,
I don’t really understand it,
but there were magical cards inside.
I scattered them
and I was asked by
this Cerberus to gather the cards.
What a nice morning,
Card Captor Sakura.
I keep saying,
it’s impossible for me.
You’re too modest.
You see,
You’ve already got back the Fly card.
Look. Look.
And it was terrible.
Breakfast is ready.
OK!
Good morning, brother.
She came down after
only being called once.
I wonder
if it’s going to rain today.
There was somebody to wake me up today.
Huh?
The alarm clock…
Good morning, mom.
Good morning.
Good morning, dad.
It looks good today.
Well, better than the monster’s I suppose.
Well dad, let’s eat.
Thanks for breakfast.
You really are early today.
I have morning cleaning duty,
Monster.
Welcome back.
Here, a present.
Well, I’m leaving.
Modern children sure are busy.
My dad and brother have school too,
so if you wait a little
you can turn on the TV.
Your dad is still a student?
He is a college professor.
Don’t leave the room
while anybody else is home.
Everybody would be shocked.
Fine.
Ah!
It’s already this late?
I gotta hurry!
I’m leaving!
I’ll take a little detour.
I came to Yukito’s place.
Yukito isn’t here.
What?
You were here?
Good morning, Sakura-chan.
Good morning.
You’re early.
I have cleaning duty.
How commendable.
Oh yeah.
Want to decorate your classroom?
Is it OK?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Take care.
Thank you so much!
I’m going.
Today is a good day.
Yay! I’m first!
You’re early, Sakura-chan.
Good morning, you’re early too.
Good morning.
Did you have some sort of duty too?
No,
I had something I wanted to show you.
A video?
Last night I filmed
something very interesting.
Ah?
What was that?
This is a close up.
Huh?!
What’s wrong Sakura?
Is it a Clow Card?
Where? I’ll fight you so come on!
Uh, oh.
My, he looks the same.
It was stuffy in there.
Why did you come with me?
I thought I would check out
the daily life of the Card Captor.
May we please be introduced.
He says his name is Cerberus.
He doesn’t seem to match the name.
He seems more of a Kero-chan.
Really.
Don’t call me like a frog!
I am the beast of the seal
who protects the Clow Cards,
Cerberus
Clow Cards?
Here I go.
Here.
And therefore Sakura
became Card Captor Sakura.
How wonderful.
The Card Captor protecting the city
From the chaos of the Clow Cards.
How cool!
Something so difficult
is impossible for me.
No, Sakura-chan can do it.
Can I please
see you use magic?
Yeah, yeah. Go ahead.
But…
I don’t mind. I don’t mind.
Nobody is looking, so go for it.
Key which hides
the power of darkness.
Show your true form before me.
Under the contract,
I Sakura command you.
Release.
You can use magic with this rod right?
But I need a card.
Here you go.
When did you get that out?
So, do you have a special pose?
Why?
A special pose and magical phrases
are the key to a magical girl.
Bye!
Goodbye!
Good morning.
Good morning…
What’s going on?
Sakura-chan.
Look at that.
Oh!
What is this?
I don’t know. It was like this
when we got here this morning.
Huh?
I wonder who did this prank?
But I suppose we have to clean it up now.
Uh, oh…
Good morning, Tomoyo-chan.
Good morning.
This looks pretty bad.
What could do this?
Could it be that this is
the work of a Clow Card?
It is the work of a Clow Card.
So it was.
Geeze, it was really tough to clean it up.
But because of that class was shortened.
I was happy about that…
But
what kind of
Clow Card would mess up school?
I don’t know.
Anyways Sakura,
this is a job for the Card Captor.
Why?
If this is the work of a Clow Card
you have to catch it.
That’s why I say it’s impossible.
I wonder who it was
that scattered the cards?
Well then we will go to school tonight.
Tonight?
Night is no good.
Why?
Because, school at night is horrible…
Ah!
I won’t. I won’t. I absolutely won’t.
But there are cards
that will only move at night.
The school at night might be dangerous.
Tomoyo-chan.
So I’ll come too.
We must capture
Sakura-chan’s heroism on video.
Why?
It’s because that is my hobby.
All right!
Tonight the three of us will attack.
Now that it has been decided
we need to hurry to perfect
a special pose even more.
Yeah! We’ll start training right away.
Ah!
I’m scared.
It’s fine. It’s fine. I’m with you.
I don’t think it’s fine.
Did I keep you waiting?
No, I just got here.
Strange?
Let me introduce you.
These are my bodyguards.
Ah…
Well then miss.
Yes. If I call you, come and pick me up.
That’s incredible.
There aren’t many elementary school students
with bodyguards.
Oh, elementary school students
who can use magic are even more rare.
That may be true.
More importantly, come over here.
Oh!
What is this?
Well, let’s change.
Why?
Sakura,
you’re going to catch Clow Cards now right?
Yeah.
When you do something special,
you have to wear special clothes.
What?
Exactly!
If you don’t dress appropriately
for a Card Captor
you may lose to the card on spirit.
I’m so happy you understand.
So, change Sakura.
I have hats too.
So, so. Go inside.
How wonderful, Sakura-chan.
It’s embarrassing.
It’s nothing to be embarrassed about.
Oh yeah, I have one for Kero-chan too.
For me too?
It’s cute and matches Sakura.
Really?
I don’t feel any tension.
Uh!
I wonder what that sound was.
What’s wrong?
Ah…
This is the aura of a Clow Card.
Oh!
Oh…
Calm down.
But… But…
Ar!
It’s chasing. It’s chasing us.
Sakura-chan.
Yes!
Look.
There is nobody there but a shadow.
Shadow?
Look out!
Kero-chan, is that a Clow Card?
That is…
That is the work of the Shadow card.
Kero-chan, you go with Tomoyo-chan.
Leave it to me.
Key which hides the power of darkness.
Show your true form before me.
I Sakura command you.
Release.
How wonderful.
Wind, become now the chains that bind.
Windy.
Eh!
Use the Fly card and run away
for the time being.
Fly.
It’s horrible!
It looks like the Shadow card
gathered the shadows of all the students.
It’s impossible for Sakura
to fight against this many.
Isn’t there some way?
The student’s shadows would disappear
if hit by light.
That would leave just the true Shadow
which she could just hit with magic.
But it’s night now.
If that’s it, then leave it to me.
Oh?
Oh!
That’s why I said it was impossible.
What should I do?
Hey! Let go.
Ar… r… aar…
Help me!
Ar?
Uh?
The shadows are gone.
Sakura
The shadows disappeared.
All but the main one will disappear
when hit by light.
It is impossible to call the sun,
but I can turn on the lights at least.
Thank you, Tomoyo-chan.
Sakura. That is the main one.
All right.
Now, Sakura!
Show the results of your training!
Wind, become now the chains that bind.
Windy.
Return to your rightful form. Clow Card.
She did it!
Just what we would expect
from Card Captor Sakura.
How wonderful.
Chiharu-chan,
have you seen Tomoyo-chan?
I saw her going into the A/V room.
Thanks.
Tomoyo-chan.
Thanks a lot for yesterday, this is in thanks.
Oh?
Huh!
I’m so glad it filmed well.
You even filmed this?
Of course.
I wouldn’t let even a second
of Sakura-chan’s heroism escape.
From now on when you go to catch cards
be sure to call me.
Eh?
We must leave the exploits of the Card Captor
for posterity.
Tomoyo-chan.
And then…
Leave your costume
for each time to me too.
Next time I’ll put
on more frills and a ribbon too.
Er…