A dream?
It’s this dream again.
Kero-chan and I…
I know…
I know that person.
Mizuki-sensei…?
[Sakura and
A Snowy New School Term]
Kero-chan…
You’re finally awake.
What were you doing…
The alarm’s been going
off all this time,
and you wouldn’t get up!
And you call yourself
a 5th-grader today.
That’s right!
I’m Sakura Kinomoto.
I’m a 5th-grader from today on.
I still don’t like math.
But I love P.E. and music.
Basically, I’m an energetic girl.
Oh, talk about something unusual…
No matter what cards you’ve gathered
or how much magic you’ve gained,
You’re still a sleepyhead.
And you captured these many cards
during’ spring break too…
These are the Clow Cards
where I get my magical powers.
Good morning!
Yo, monster.
O-onii-chan!!
Your alarm’s been going off
like that and you could still oversleep so much.
You’re a monster all right.
I said
I’m not a monster!
Good morning.
Good morning, Father.
Good morning,
Let’s eat!
From today on, Sakura is a 5th-grader,
and Touya is a high school senior.
Yeah.
Sakura, do you guys swap classes?
No. The entire class stays
the way it was
and moves on to 5th grade.
So you’ll be in the same
class with Tomoyo-san.
I’m glad for you.
Um… What about you?
Are you and Yukito
in the same class…
We swap classes,
but Yuki and I are in the same class.
Then, are you still going to school
with Yukito in the morning?
I guess.
Then, I’ll be leaving.
Okay.
Good luck on the academic presentation.
Oh, also, if anyone calls,
please ask him or her to call the hotel.
We’ll do that even if you didn’t say so.
Thanks. See you later.
Bye! Good luck!
O… Onii-chan?!
You’re mean! You left me behind.
Can’t be late on the first day
of a new school year, you know.
Yuki!
Yukito-san!
Yo!
Good morning, Touya.
Good morning, Sakura-chan
Good morning!
Huh? Where is your bicycle?
I got a flat tire yesterday
when I went to buy things.
You could have called me
and I would’ve fixed it for you.
I stopped by
a bike store on the way back
and had them look at it.
Touya, you’re on duty today, right?
It’s okay if you just go ahead.
Okay. Then, I’ll see you at school.
Sakura-chan, are you in a hurry too?
I… I’m not in any hurry at all.
Then, why don’t we go together?
Okay!
You’re a 5th-grader now, aren’t you?
Ye… Yes!
It’s a little late, but…
Here.
For your birthday
and having become a 5th-grader.
It’s for me?
Thank you very much!
Good morning!
Good morning, Tomoyo-chan!
I am so happy that
we are in the same class again.
Me too!
Oh? Could it be a present that you are holding?
Yeah. It’s from Yukito-san.
I see. He is still good at it.
Good morning.
Good morning!
Hey, I wonder who is our class teacher.
Oh yeah. We change teachers.
Mr. Terada was kind and fun.
He was so nice.
What’s wrong, Rika-chan?
Oh… nothing.
I was just wondering
who is our new teacher.
We… We made it.
Good morning,
Li-kun, Mei Lin-chan.
Good morning.
Did you guys oversleep?
I had a nice dream,
so I didn’t want to get up.
What kind of dream?
I was on a date with Shao Lan!
A date?
The teacher’s here.
Oh! It’s Mizuki-sensei!
What’s with Kinomoto-san?
She seems to be in schweeeet mode.
What’s that?
Good morning.
Good morning!
I am your new class teacher,
Kaho Mizuki. Nice to see you again.
I wonder…
I wonder if that’s Mizuki-sensei.
So you will do your best
in your schoolwork too, right?
Yes!
But that…
Okay.
The first period is a free period.
How about a game?
What are we going to play?
That’s right.
Let’s go outside.
What do you want to play?
Dodge ball! Volleyball!
Soccer!
Then, we’ll play dodge ball.
Everyone, let’s go outside.
Yay!
Something
really pretty is coming down.
And it’ll accumulate a lot.
Cherry blossom?
Snow?
It’s a little late,
but…
For your birthday
and having become a 5th-grader.
Yukito-san! Yukito-san!
I brought some potato chips.
I wonder…
It’s spring already,
and it still snows.
Sakura, do you want some chips?
I got a watch from Yukito-san!
Hey, are you listening?
Guess I’ll eat it all
while you’re in schweeeet mode.
I’m so happy.
You’re happy, but I guess
you don’t forget your chips either.
Anyway, the new class teacher
is that mysterious one?
I’m sure
I could sense special powers in her.
It feels like she has something
real powerful around her.
Maybe because of that,
she could sense the cards.
Something really pretty is coming down,
and it’ll accumulate a lot.
Is snow in spring going to
accumulate that much?
What’s wrong?
It’s nothing.
Oh, it’s about time
to get ready for dinner.
What is it for today?
It’s cold today,
so we’ll have stew.
All right!!
I’m back!
Oh, it’s Onii-chan.
Hey, Sakura!
What is it?
Hey, get me a towel!
A towel?
Why?
So much snow!
It was really bad.
I couldn’t ride my bike at all.
It accumulated that much?
Yeah, almost meter.
Yes, it is almost like
we are surrounded by walls of snow.
It’s totally white around here as well.
This is strange for April.
I wonder…
Could this be…
It’s the act of a Clow Card!
Then, the Card Captor
will be in action, right?
This time,
I have a costume just right for you.
I am looking forward to film you in it!
There is snow on everything.
Everything besides
the roof is all buried.
With the snow this widespread,
I can’t sense anything this high up.
Let’s get down.
Sakura-chan!
Sakura!
Help!
I guess I’ll help you.
This is the act of Snow.
Li-kun! Mei Lin-chan!
How come you guys
are standing on top of the snow?
Thanks to Shao Lan’s magic.
You can use your Float card, you know.
Oh, that’s right.
Brat! Even if you didn’t mention it,
I was just gonna…
Snow It’s the card of the snow.
Yeah.
But I couldn’t sense anything at all
Even though it is so near.
Me neither.
Oh, but Mizuki-sensei said
something really pretty will
come down, and…
She seems to know
it’s going to accumulate this much.
You’re saying
she knows from the start
this is because of a Clow Card?
I couldn’t quite tell…
After all, that teacher
isn’t just anyone.
But Mizuki-sensei
is kind and pretty.
And she makes me feel schweeeet.
It’s coming down again!
Tomoyo-chan! Mei Lin-chan!
At this rate… At this rate…
I cannot shoot your video!
This way!
It’s after us!
This snow contains magical power!
Let’s move away from them!
Fly!
Get on!
Hurry!
Shao Lan! Good luck!
It’s gonna catch up to us!
At this rate,
the whole town’s really
gonna get buried by the snow.
We can’t just run away from it!
Bu… But!
God of Fire, come forth!
You did it!
Not yet.
This is bad,
if we can’t use stronger fire.
It’s coming again!
Damn! It’s so persistent!
What should we do?
All right. One more time.
What’s wrong?
What is it?
The watch is gone!
Your watch,
you mean the one you got today?
The watch Yukito gave me
was so precious to me…
He gave you something?!
How could they!
Fire! Melt away all the snow!
Firey!
Incredible.
After all, girls are
scary when they get mad.
Sakura, that’s the true form of Snow.
Return to thy form which
thou should be! Clow Card!
I lost my watch.
The watch he gave me
was so precious to me…
He… Hey…
The watch Yukito-san gave me…
Don… Don’t cry.
In… In… In… In the meantime, I’ll
go check on Tomoyo and that girl.
He… Hey!
Don’t cry.
I’ll look for it
with you until we find it.
Thanks. You’re so nice.
Good evening.
Mizuki-sensei!
Oh, that’s a cute outfit.
This is… um…
You don’t need to be so alert.
I just came to give Kinomoto-san
to give back something she dropped.
This is yours, right?
Yes!
But how do you know it’s mine…?
I just do.
Thanks for everything today.
Now, you should go home.
Good night.
Thank you very much.