This is LAN Xi.
The big city where I grew up.
I remember every stop here.
Every street.
The shape of each sunny days
and also the rainy ones.
At that moment in time,
we were around 16-17 years old.
Without a smart phone.
Without whatsapp or voicemail.
Here's your Bao Zi.
Time passed slowly.
It was a long summer.
An old song was playing over and over again.
Some people will always carry in their heart.
Tu Xiao Yi, be more realistic.
Who's still look at such shallow mangas?
In mangas, you have to give the reader more pleasure, do you understand?
Since I'm the company's president,
you should be like a loyal Golden Retriever
and be calm and proud.
If you don't want to draw me a wolf cub, then you should draw me a puppy.
Will you continue drawing for me?
If you keep drawing your original manga,
I will no longer invest in that.
Once you're an adult,
it's good to act as one.
But you can lose sight of yourself.
I remember when I was 17 years old.
Such an insolent youth.
But also a simple and realistic one.
Good morning my audience.
Today is September 1, 1999.
The return of Makao is in 11 days.
On this splendid morning,
I will share a new song by Pu Shu, "New Boy".
Gramps, I'm going to school.
Be careful.
Good morning.
Here's one bowl of tofu buns.
Owner, are my Bao Zi done?
Oh, yeah.
You're still playing? The old man will kill you.
I'll carry the Bao Zi.
Hey, my Bao Zi!
Tu Xiao Yi, wait for me!
Get on the bike quickly.
Hurry up, the bell is about to ring.
3rd year class 1
Your average for the last semester are the worst.
Look at your notes.
Aren't you ashamed?
Now we must raise your average with blackboard reports.
Yao Zhe Tian.
It doesn't matter if it's by studying or on the blackboard.
Being on the committee,
You must be a good influence for others
and also for yourself.
Understood?
Keep laughing.
Amazing.
You get here late just after the beginning of class. What were you thinking?
Why not come when classes ends while at it?
And you dare to sneak into my classroom.
Did you think you could do it?
You two, when you are not looking at mangas or playing video games,
You're always getting here at bell time.
Not even dogs can catch up after class.
In what course do you think you are?
Are you deaf?
Do you think the school is your house?  Impolite.
How did your father teach you?
I...
Oh, it you, Jin Xuan.
Now try not to be late anymore.
It doesn't matter.
This year you're trying to get into a university.
If you have a problem, you can come and tell me.
Do you feel good being in the last row?
Do you want me to put you up closer ahead?
Being close to you? I'm afraid you wouldn't get used to that.
You two, why are you still standing there?
Go back to your seats.
So he's Qi Jin Xuan.
Do you know him?
Who doesn't?  He's the son of the director of education.
Master Chen?
My mother wants me to focus on the exams.
She doesn't want me to make more blackboard reports.
Look if...
No.
The exams are important.
But so is the honor of the course.
Tu Xiao Yi.
Will you be able to go to the university if you draw all the time?
Yao Zhe Tian still has to do her dance training.
All right.
This semester you will help her with the blackboard reports.
At least you will be useful.
Ah, g... good.
Wait!
Your pencil.
Thank you.
Making blackboard reports with Yao Zhe Tian...
A blessing after the disaster, eh?
Shut up!
If you strive now, in the future you will shine.
Everyone remembers that.
This year...
You just have to remember 2 things:
The final exams
And that all the other things are not important.
Silence silence.
We started the class.
Anyone causing a disturbance will come to my office after school.
Did you hear?
He has...
However,
our teacher Chen said
that this year
we only have 2 things to remember.
But
things and people that he says are not important
are more real and clear than exams
and they exists in my life.
Yao Zhe Tian, ​​wait.
Yes?
I want to talk about the blackboard report.
Don't be so cocky!
2vs1. I was afraid you would say that we are bothering you!
And we even let you have some time with the ball.
All right.
Wait for me here.
I'll go drop my dance shoes.
Ok
Hey, you.
Oh?
You're calling me?
Now it's 2vs2. We are even, right?
What's 2vs2?
Why are you giving me the ball?
Boy, can you play?
Enough of this nonsense.
Quick, just pass the ball.
That's right.
Boy
Thanks for your help.
Just pass the ball!
Hey, take it!
Catch it!
Behind you!
Take it!
That's right!
The last point, we can't let that score.
This way!
Over here!
Here!
The ball has no eyes, it's not my problem.
You're the one who doesn't have eyes!
I'm fine.
He said he's okay, let's continue.
Wait!
Let me try the last shot.
No matter what, don't let that score!
All right!
If he scores, I'll eat the ball.
All yours!
Here, eat it.
Well played, see you tomorrow.
Ok
I didn't know you knew how to play basketball.
I just pretended to know, I only know how to draw.
Did your parents make you draw?
I only have gramps now.
Oh
I just like doing it. I was drawing just by seeing the covers.
Do you like it?
I like it ever since I was a kid.
So your family wants you to become a painter?
I don't want to be a painter, I like to draw manga.
Are you planning to enter an art university?
I probably can't, I have such low grades.
Art colleges needs at least 200 points.
So it's beyond my reach.
Oh
I really envy you.
You have something that you really like.
I have not.
What?
What did you say?
I said that
It's good that you have something that you really...
like.
In that instant
I knew that I really liked someone.
My cloudy sky looked like it opened in a corner
and that a dazzling light appeared.
It's adolescence.
It awakened like that.
Qui Jin Xuan.
Jin Xuan.
Wait wait.
How are you?
Now more than ever, I want to will give you private lessons.
Don't bother yourself.
It's nothing.
Now, remember when you go back to tell your father
that I will not charge anything for giving you private class.
It definitely doesn't violate the rules.
The ministry of education prohibits any paid private individual class.
Tsk
I mean, you better keep
being the teacher who is in the last line.
I'll tell my father when I get back home
that you are a teacher who thinks about the students.
It would be a shame if you are not a director of the education ministry.
Oh, no, no.
Jin Xuan.
Jin Xuan!
Hey, Jin Xuan.
Also, bring this to your father.
Why are you two still here?
Teacher, we are doing the blackboard report.
The blackboard report?
Next time try doing it
while not hiding.
Qi Jin Xuan.
Back off!
Qi Jin Xuan!
They will see it tomorrow, what should we do?
It doesn't matter.
First let's think about cleaning it.
Let me.
Better leave it to me.
Now let's finish the rest.
Ok
Soda?
Yes
What do you want?  I'll get them.
-Bei Bing Yang -Jian Li Bao
2 different brands of soda.
-Then Bie Bing Yang -Jian Li Bao is fine.
Can't you have a little more coordination?
-Yes - No
What do you want?
Cola.
Say...
Yes?
How about you draw that?
What do you mean?
Draw that on the blackboard.
Ah, are you sure that old Chen won't get mad?
Doesn't he get angry every day?
He doesn't care about anything other than the final exam.
Speaking of that,
I can give you particular help.
Particular?
No... don't waste your time.
Ha, another old Chen.
Only thinking about the final exam.
All right.
I...
Well, I'll take you to a special place.
The iron tower of the mountain.
Ok
Hold on firmly.
Wow.
How high we are.
Get up.
It's my first time seeing LAN Xi from so high.
LAN Xi is so beautiful.
Look, a cloud of fire.
It's nice.
This is the first time I'm so close to heaven.
Oh, it’s over.
Isn't it late?
When my mother comes back and doesn't find me, she's going to question me.
Hey, Qi Jin Xuan.
I'm not sure if Yao Zhe Tian should returns alone.
How about we accompany her home?
I don't know who's not sure.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Oh, you have secrets.
Then I'll wait for you.
It's not like this.
I was just telling Qi Jin Xuan
that we will accompany you home.
Let's go you two.
Right, Qi Jin Xuan?
Qi Jin Xuan.
All right.
Hey Yao Zhe Tian? What university are you going to go to?
I don't know.
Maybe I'll go to a trade school.
Or maybe one for math or doctor.
Since I don't know much.
Any place is strange to me.
So many universities that you can choose.
Is there none that you like?
I don't know these universities.
How will I know if I like them or not?
My parents said that
If your grades are high
then you can go to the best universities.
And as to which one,
We
we will get well organized.
Why are you worrying?
Tian Tian.
Mother.
Why are you here?
They are my training partners.
Hello, miss.
Mother.
Where's dad?
In his class a couple of students did something bad
so he went to fix the problem.
Look at what children do now...
They don't study anymore.
We don't known what they are thinking.
It's already getting late.
They...
They just accompanied me home on the way.
Ah, yes yes.
Miss, you don't need to thank us,
We were just passing by.
I was forgetting to thank you.
Hey?  Are you also in her dance class?
We dance Yang Ge.
Hehehe
Miss, it's getting late.
We are leaving.
Goodbye Miss.
Go Go.
Didn't you say it was just in your way?
This...
Miss, it was this way...
Here...
Goodbye Miss.
They dance that...
They're also adding points.
It would be nice if we could look up some information about universities for Yao Zhe Tian.
Tian Tian, ​​the magazine that you like to read, I already ordered it for the whole year.
Tian Tian.
Oh, I'm coming.
Get over yourself and don't give up !!
It shows
everything
that will
be in the
exam!
Wow, that's soo good.
Who drew it?  They have talent.
Really!
This is more interesting than love stories and other things.
Hey, does it look like Slam Dunk?
It's very good.
Yes Yes
I really like Rukawa Kaede.
Tsk, you're in love.
Oh, shit!
Did you draw that outside?
It's Incredible!
Why did you draw the big gorilla?
That Tu Xiao Yi never study.
He only knows how to draw these things.
The origin of everything, it's quite deep.
Master Chen, it seems that finally the board could get the first place.
Students!
They can't look only at the notes,
I always wish they could also use their intellect and art.
Well done!
That can encompass everything.
Hey, yeah yeah.
Who could mark Sakuragi and Rukawa?
Coff coff, silence.
The blackboard report this time...
Yes.
It has something special.
We'll keep it.
But,
also pay attention.
The blackboard reports should not be done with so little content.
There must also be good content on the board.
Then for the blackboard competitions,
we must get the first place
to bring honor to our class.
For our blackboard report
I definitely didn't pick the wrong person.
Amazing!
Qi Jing Xuan.
Can...
you help me find information
about universities?
You did not spend that many days with Tian Tian
and you already want to go to the university?
Shut up, what are you saying?!
I just think that...
Don't you think
that there are many people who want to know about universities?
I'm not kidding.
What was I saying?
Oh
If we put those infos on the board, surely someone will see them.
Right.
As well...
We can meet old Chen's needs.
What do you think?
You're really putting a lot of efforts.
Hey, you even put some English.
Are you listening?
If you have skills, better worry for yourself.
How about we make a bet?
If you win, I'll help you.
All right.
Hey, Tu Xiao Yi,
don't you know how incredible he is with Tetris?
Hey, do you want to try or not?
Ok
Ehm, Tu Xiao Yi.
We didn't see each other for more than 10 years.
You finally thought about calling me.
Where are you?
I resigned.
Now I'm in LAN Xi.
When can we meet again?
You resigned?
Why?
Wait,
I'll call you back in a little while.
Hey hey
Hua Sheng.
Recruitment at the manga office.
Qi Jin Xuan.
Did you bring all that?
Did you bring so many?
That's good.
Take it, this one is for you.
Oh?
Yes.
Thank you.
She gave it to me.
Yes, I decided...
I will draw manga.
Did you choose?
Yes
Look.
All right.
I think that this time we can present these universities.
What do you think?
Yes, I think it's pretty good.
This is also good.
Hey, Qi Jin Xuan.
Don't take a picture, give it to me!
No, give it to me!
Get me a copy too!
Give it to me!
There will be a mock exam.
Anyone is allowed to make mistakes.
If you do, it's not going to influence your scores.
It would just be bad luck.
But for my parents, there is no such thing as luck for the exam.
They only want the best for you.
They wish the best for us?
They only care about their standing.
When have they ever thought about what we're thinking?
You got some blood!
Let me see, it's very deep.
It will become infected if we don't clean it.
It's okay.
No...
You don't have to bother.
Don't move.
Let's go.
I better put a bandage on it.
Don't bother yourself!
Qi Jin Xuan.
You...
Again, getting angry out of nowhere.
Let's go.
What are you drawing?
Has your anger gone?
Someone left you a note.
A note?
Who?
I don't know.
I found it on the blackboard.
What university can I go to if I get 300 points?
Don't you feel that you've accomplished something?
Are you talking about the blackboard or the score?
About the blackboard, obviously.
Are you comparing points with her?
That's what it seems.
You should leave a comment book.
A comment book?
Yes.
Hang it on the blackboard.
That way she shouldn't have to leave notes.
Hey.
Hey!
Yes?
It's already going to be the winter holidays.
Let's take her out to play.
We? With Yao Zhe Tian?
But...
I don't know if she can come.
I gave you the opportunity, everything depends on you.
You're not lost, right?
Yes.
We'll get there just after we get up this steep road.
Go ahead.
Hua Sheng.
Why are you so heavy?
Try a little more and then it's all down hill.
Go down hill !!
Why isn't Yao Zhe Tian already out?
Ah
Hey...
We're not at the wrong place, right?
Even though he makes mistake about your house,
he wouldn't be wrong about Yao Zhe Tian's house.
What are you staring at?
Call her to come down.
Me?
Yao... Yao...
How do I do that?
How are you usually calling Hua Sheng?
Just do it like that.
Oh...
Wait for me!
This...
Hey, Hua Sheng.
What are you doing?
He always calls me by throwing stones.
I'll look for a stone for you.
This is...
Quickly, call her.
Hey.
Yao Zhe Tian.
Yao...
Shh.
Hey, go wait over there.
This is a good one.
Hey, Hua Sheng.
This way.
Ok
Oh
Come back early.
If you go with the girls,
You must be careful.
Take this, it's cold outside.
After the 8th, it will be the Chinese new year.
The year is almost over.
You really have to follow the calendar.
Ah!
You said that you would only say two words.
Can't I?
Say professor,
how about helping her with her lessons?
Ok, ok.
Come back early.
When you come back, we'll go over everything again.
Go.
Oh, wait.
All right.
I'm here.
Hey, aren't you cold?
I'll give you my gloves.
What about you?
Oh, it doesn't matter.
I still have my pockets.
Qi Jin Xuan.
Aren't you cold?
How about I give you my gloves?
Shut up.
I can also put my hands in my pockets.
I'm fine.
Let's move on.
Hua Sheng.
Let's go.
You really don't want my gloves?
Shut up, let's go.
Ok, I'm going.
Tu Xiao Yi, Qi Jin Xuan handles it better than you.
Then you better get off and run.
Hey, I'm complimenting you.
Insolent!
How much farther is it?
What are you hurrying for?
I fear that Tu Xiao Yi can't follow us anymore.
Who can't follow anymore?
I'm always ahead of you!
Be careful, don't wet your shoes.
Don't worry.
Wow, how beautiful it is over here.
Hey, Qi Jin Xuan, it's snowing.
Hua Sheng.
Be careful, Yao Zhe Tian, ​​I'm going to help you.
An avalanche!
Where are you?
I can't see anything.
You two...
Hey, the water's frozen.
Hua Sheng, what are you doing?
Careful, careful !
Pull me up carefully.
It's good.
I'm fine.
Hua Sheng.
What an idiot.
I told you not to step on it.
We're here.
Waa.. we finally arrived.
Mother.
Look closely, be careful what you step on.
Jin Xuan.
You're back.
Hi miss.
Hello Hello.
Look at you.
You didn't tell me you would bring friends.
I didn't prepare anything.
I will go prepare something.
Come come, enter.
It's a long way, isn't it?
No no.
Come come, you don't need to be so polite.
Consider it as your own home.
Come look, I've never seen these things before.
How come?  They are on TV all the time.
Let me try, let me try.
Hua Sheng, don't break it.
Don't worry.
Hey, that's it.
Wow.
I was wrong, don't follow me!
Here, take one.
Jin Xuan, come pick up the food.
Here I am.
Don't move.
It's delicious.
Eating again.
You're hungry now, aren't you? Over here, it's fine.
Sit down, sit down.
It's just normal food.
Don't be so polite, eat.
Miss, you should also eat.
Ok
Qi Jin Xuan, I didn't know that you knew how to cook.
There are many things that you still don't know.
This is good, this too...
Qi Jin Xuan.
Why does your mother live all the way here?
Do you need to ask?
Surely they are divorced.
That's ok.
You're not mistaken.
When I was little,
My father abandoned the both of us.
Then when I grew up a little,
he came back for the divorce process
and he took me into custody.
Saying it was for my sake.
But I wanted to continue to be with my mother.
Be a peasant for life.
I feel it's good to live in the countryside.
Did you notice?
All your toys are planes.
They are things from my past.
My mother told me that when I was a kid, I always wanted to be a pilot.
Definitely.
Look at this picture.
Such a big hat.
Do you still think about being a pilot?
That's a childhood thing.
Now I just want to become independent
and help my mother.
I heard my father say
that pilots go to a secondary schools every year to do a special training.
You just have to pass the physical.
Really?  So it's not hard?
You can get approved!
Hey, look at this Qi Jin Xuan, he looks like a fool, look!
Let me see.
What a fool, look!
What a fool !
Give it back!
Tu Xiao Yi, catch it!
Goodbye miss.
Miss, we're leaving.
Goodbye, wait...
Remember to eat breakfast before going to school.
Don't worry about me.
Ok
Be careful.
Miss, it's not necessary to accompany us.
It's the first time Jin Xuen brings some friends home.
This boy, ever since he was a kid, is so sensible.
But being that sensible makes me worry more.
It means that I was not that good at raising him.
I hope it won't matter where he's going.
He can have friends like you accompanying him.
Don't worry, we will accompany him forever.
We were young...
We thought that if we said forever,
then it will be like that.
As if when we say 'see you',
we would see each other again.
Hey, shall we go?
I'm coming.
Where did you come from?  You scared me!
Hey wait!
Why did you put it in?
I'm done.
What will happen if she sees it?
What's the matter?
Surely she will see it.
Shit! Shit!
Then help me open it.
I beg you.
Don't be so direct with everything, ok?
Then pray that she accepts you.
Pr... pray?
Don't you have a more normal way?
Let's go.
Don't go!
You just kill and don't clean up?
Pay attention.
A team of education inspectors are about to arrive.
Please make your preparations
and put your best behavior to greet the inspectors
for our school's honor.
They are coming.
Still not here yet?  Try to act more normal.
Good teacher Chen.
Hey, let me tell you...
What is this?
Yao Zhe Tian's mother came to look for old Chen.
Come come.
Director Qi.
Over here, over here.
We already obtained the paper to add points.
Lately Yao Zhe Tian's notes are not stable.
I wish to cancel all extracurricular activities.
Master Chen.
But the city's art performance, Yao Zhe Tian can't miss that.
And the blackboard reports?
The blackboard reports...
Ah, Director Qi.
Master Chen, it's good to see you.
Oh, this is...
Oh, she's Yao Zhe Tian's mother from our course.
She's a university professor.
Oh yeah, Qi Jin Xuan is in your course.
That's to say that I'm also the father of one of your student, Master Chen.
This blackboard report is not bad.
The information is new and very specific.
Director Qi, you're right.
That blackboard report was made by Yao Zhe Tian.
She puts a lot of effort into the study and course work.
Our Jin Xuan is also excellent.
He plays basketball very well.
During the semester, Jin Xuan also changed a lot.
How How, I see...
It's because you know how to teach, old Chen.
Your students really have talents of all kinds.
He can play basketball and Yang Ge.
Yang Ge?
Director Qi...
I say miss Yao,
aren't you mistaken?
He said it himself.
What's wrong with it?
Director Qi.
How about we go to the meeting room and continue the talk over there?
This way.
Hey, director Qi.
Qi...
Miss Yao...
What are you looking at?
Listen well.
The blackboard reports have yet to take the first place.
Master Chen.
From now on, I can do the blackboard reports by myself.
By yourself?
Tu Xiao Yi.
I haven't seen you put much heart in your studies.
So why are you paying so much attention to the blackboard reports?
Look at what you're drawing every day.
Right.
I already understand why.
Hey, I think he drew Yao Zhe Tian.
Good, very good.
I had you make the blackboard reports
but you were doing these things instead, huh?
Shut up.
Can't you show some discipline?
Discipline!
You're not putting any effort into the exams!
Aren't you going to put any?
Master Chen.
I'm sorry.
That drawing, it was me who asked him to draw it.
I never really paid attention to the exams.
I like looking at these things.
Can't I have it?
It doesn't matter who wants it.
The exams are almost there, you know?
You're not being reasonable.
Yao Zhe Tian.
Starting today,
don't worry about the blackboard reports.
Concentrate on your notes
and also on your performance.
Those who come to withdraw their exams:
Huang Bo, Li Bao Qiang, Zhang Shu Qi.
Stop drawing.
Come.
We're going to the arcade.
Well, you want something to happen, right?
I'll walk with you because tomorrow I'm leaving.
It's true.
I decided to become a pilot.
Tomorrow I will go and register.
Before I leave, come with me to the arcade.
Qi Jin Xuan, you...
I'm going too.
K.O. again.
Qi Jin Xuan, you're really good.
Want to give it a try?
No, you play.
Try it.
I'll teach you how to play.
What do you mean, 4 eyes?
You said you would let us play!
What do you mean by this?
When did I say I was leaving?
I was wrong, Qiang Ge.
I was wrong.
It's Hua Sheng, why is he here?
Say that again!
Hua Sheng.
Hey? Tu Xiao Yi?
No wonder.
So you had someone watching your back?
I will hit you all!
Hey, Hua Sheng, I will solve my own thing by myself.
Don't disturb my friends...
Hua Sheng!
They...
Qiang Ge.
The one in the back is someone important.
His father... is the di... di... director of the education ministry.
No no no...
We are bullies
What do we care about the education minister?
Move away!
Hit him!
Be careful !
Four eyes...
Hua Sheng!
You brat!
Let's go!
Tu Xiao Yi, hurry up!
Qiang Ge, your nose is bleeding.
Pursue them!
Don't let them escape!
My bike...
Go, quickly!
We'll meet with them later.
Let's go!
Divide and pursue!
Where?
I can't run anymore.
My feet are going to split.
I'll carry the bike in my hand. I'm faster than you.
My vision is fading...
Let's go find the other two.
Ha...
Shit.
Where did the two of them go?
No...
We must go and look for them.
Tu Xiao Yi.
Wait for me!
Will you really go...
and never come back?
It's late.
Go back home.
You know I shouldn't talk about that.
I...
I will not go back to school.
Then we will not see each other anymore,
Right?
I don't know.
Qi Jin Xuan.
Can't you watch where you're going?
Sorry mister!
Here they are.
Tu Xiao Yi.
If you don't want to go to the university,
then I won't go either.
There's no difference between myself
and the bullies we just met.
Go away.
Tu Xiao Yi, Tu Xiao Yi.
Back off!
Hey hey!
Where are you going?
Tu Xiao Yi, Tu Xiao Yi !
I'm giving you the opportunity.
The rest is up to you.
That drawing, it was me who asked him to draw it.
Then pray that she accepts you.
On that night...
All our relationships were over.
It was the first time I felt my heart beat madly.
I didn't have enough courage
and I was already destroyed.
After that, Qi Jin Xuan didn't show up at school anymore.
Yao Zhe Tian became quieter.
And myself? I decided to quit the exam.
Do you plan to enter an art university?
It's good that you have something that...
you really like.
This is for you.
Recruitment at the manga office.
Notice
For best performance, the third-year
blackboard reports will be paused
for the next semester.
Master Chen, I decided to quit the exam, I'll go draw instead.
No matter what you choose, I want you to be able to move forward.
I know that in Master Chen's heart,
the final exam was the most important stop for the future.
But it's not a stop for the train of life.
We are all going in our own direction, driving to a different place.
See you, my adolescence.
Thanks senior.
Thank you Xue Zhang, I'm the President of 2nd Year class 4,
can I ask you to copy the contents of your blackboard reports for our course?
Many people like your content.
You strove hard for those blackboard reports.
2nd year class 3
I wish you luck and that you can stay first forever in any job.
2nd year class 4
But no slap in the back, try your best, strive!
Every week I have to go up to the 3rd floor just to see your blackboard reports.
Your blackboard reports are too good, Xue Zhang's notes are probably great!
Surely you can enter your first choice university, try your best!
Try hard!
Hua Sheng.
When the rainy season ends,
It will be the time for me to leave for Shen Zhen.
Tu...
Wow, that's a great city.
I also want to go.
Do mangakas make money?
When you earn good money, don't forget about me.
Now in my life, I can see the goal with my own eyes.
On the other hand, you...
You are still doing something that you like.
I only know how to do this.
Oh, right, did you really quit?
Yes, I resigned.
I'm drawing my own manga.
Yes, I'm rooting for you.
Take advantage that you can still choose.
Go do what you really want to do.
Not unlike those years...
On Wednesday at 4pm at the
city hall there will be a
demonstration of art and culture.
Except for those in third year,
all other classes must arrive
on time to participate.
What are you carrying your backpack for?
Let's go.
All right.
Yes Yes.
She's my student.
Yao Zhe Tian.
It's only because I came
that your backpack got wet.
It's okay.
I was already getting annoyed.
Here's some ginger tea.
Oh, ginger tea.
Be careful, it's hot.
Thank you.
Are you still drawing?
Yes, I still draw.
And I plan to continue drawing.
That's why I decided to go to Shen Zhen.
It's a small manga company.
Maybe for me it will be a new beginning.
Wait, you're not going to participate in the final exams?
Yeah.
But...
I didn't think that
someone like me
was so bad at it.
When I decided not to go to the final exam, in my heart I felt a little...
bit of repentance.
It's good that this magazine...
Magazine?
My magazines!
Ah, this is bad
Everything is wet.
I just took them out today.
They are all wet.
Your...
Did you get them out of the mailbox?
Yes.
What are you looking for?
Oh, no... nothing.
I sneaked them out and I still haven't read any of them.
They're all wet.
It's the first time I sneak them out behind my mother's back.
Now I ruined them.
They got so wet, even if I return them, she will notice.
What is this?
It seems that there's a letter.
Wait.
Do you know what it is?
I don't know what it is.
It's all blurred, you can't see anything.
Maybe...
It was a gift from the magazine.
I think it's not good anymore.
Throw it away.
Drink some ginger tea.
Don't catch a cold.
Yeah.
How spicy.
Tu Xiao Yi.
I always want to do something right.
But it's not always what I end up doing.
If only this morning I hadn't taken out the magazines.
There wouldn't have been a need to return them in time.
It's like with us...
You have to remember
that If you have something that you really like
then make it shine.
If you like someone
make them shine as well.
Although even if in the end you can't be together,
It doesn't matter.
Why?
You'll probably like that person.
You'll shine for liking him.
You found what you really like.
I won't give up.
University wish list and career.
Psychology
Education
I wish everyone to shine in their own way.
Yes, Hua Sheng, don't cry.
When I get there, I will call you.
You have to take care.
Tu Xiao Yi.
This is for you.
Keep it as a memento.
Yes
Thank you.
You don't need to go further, right here it's good.
Tu Xiao Yi.
Don't forget us when you get to the big city!
Be a genius!
Tu Xiao Yi!
Try hard.
Help me give this to Tu Xiao Yi.
Tell him It's from you.
Why?
Just give it to him.
Right then I knew...
From that moment I knew
that the magazine that Qi Jin Xuan gave me
opened the way to go make mangas at Shen Zhen.
I think that
If that summer would have been a little longer
maybe I would have said "see you"
If at that moment I had said "I'll see you"
then...
would it have been possible to find each other again?
Where are they?
How are they?
I already miss them.
Wow, you're missing a lot, Tu Xiao Yi, you won't be able to win.
No, I haven't lost yet.
You have, It will be the end of the day if you continue trying.
Well, I'll help you this time, but
when you become mangaka, you have to draw a story about us.
Mom!
Mom, look!
It's LAN Xi, it's really good looking!
It was drawn just now by a guy.
I told him that he drew well and he gave it to me.
Mom look!
Mom, what's wrong?
Nothing, I just remembered something from before.
Come on, Mom will take you to eat some crystal cake.
Ok
Faster Faster!
Don't run so much, be careful or you will fall.
Mom, I want to learn how to draw.
Well, if you have something that you like to do, go for it.
Ok
If you have something...
Yes,if...
If at that moment he would have told us "see you later"
Would we have been able to see each other again?