Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Let's see...
Goku-sa, look at this! Gohan is already
solvin' problems as difficult as this!
I can't wait to see what kind of great
scholar he'll become in the future!
Yeah, I'll bet!
Mother... Father...
Try taking this on!
Makankosappo!!
H- he avoided it! W- what kind
of bastard is he, with such speed?
You pierced through this armor
quite easily. That's quite a technique.
If I had taken that head-on,
I would have been out!
That doesn't mean anything
if I don't hit you!
To think that you would
inflict injury upon me!
You're going to pay for this!
I'm through playing around!
It doesn't mean anything
if I don't hit you!
All right!
Wow, I did it!
I lost a great deal of time
to Old Lady Snake there.
If I don't hurry up,
things will get nasty!
Oh, no you don't!
Hey, we meet again!
It sure is big!
I wonder how long
this beach goes on for.
Mother...
Chichi!
I brung some of my special-made porridge.
Eat some of this,
you'll feel better, Chichi.
Nope.
You ain't eaten nothin'
for a whole week now, have you?
Come on, just eat this.
I'm not goin' to...
Gohan...
Huh? That's what I made!
I've come back to the starting point.
All right, then...
This is an island!
Beyond there is Mother!
All right, then!
Makankosappo!!
This one looks like it's the best.
All right, then...
Thank you!
Move it, move it, you're in the way!
It's finished!
I did it! I did it!
All right, now...
All right, here I go!
It's okay, I'll be back right away!
I'm just going to go see
my mother for a little while.
That should be good enough...
--The kid!
--It couldn't be!
Rain?
There's a storm coming!
I can't turn back now!
I've got to tough it out!
Got to tough it out!
It's okay, it's okay. I'll get through...
I'll get through the storm soon enough!
Ah, this is bad! If this keeps up,
I'll be swamped! And I can't swim!
I... can't swim! I can't swim!
That dirty brat!
Where the hell did he go?
Gohan, what about your
training with Piccolo?
Have you forgotten about
the crisis the world is in?
Eight months remain
until the Saiyans arrive.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org