Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Looks like Freeza is
out and about, all right.
And so then, right there,
I told him...
Wait, hold on now...
What's this?
--What was that!?
--What's going on!?
W- what was that explosion just now?!
V- V- V-
Vegeta!
Damn!
Hey!
Where are the Dragon Balls?
Look at all of you,
lined up so loyally!
If you don't want to tell me...
...then you don't have to tell me.
Lousy small fry.
You can swear your allegiance
to Freeza from the Other Side now.
Damn it all, Freeza...
Seeing as how Ginyu stayed behind,
the Dragon Balls must
be around here somewhere.
In any event, those Earth
punks can locate them
with that strange
device of theirs.
They should be here
very shortly now.
Until then, I'll see about changing
into some new battle wear.
So, this is what it's like to have
a body with a power of 180,000?
However, I think my previous face
was more handsome. Right, Jheese?
Absolutely!
I- I've got to go faster, or Kuririn
and Gohan will get killed!
That way? No, this way!
Ribbit... ribbit... ribbit...
Damn it, I can't keep my balance
very well in this body.
You know, there's something very unusual
about the medicine Kakarrot was using.
Not only does it heal injuries,
but it completely restores
one's strength as well.
The only ones in my size
are the older models, huh?
We're almost there, Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san, there it is!
G- got it! So that's
their spaceship, huh?
So, you've arrived, Earthlings.
It's no good if they realize I'm here.
I have to suppress my battle power,
the way they do.
Let's hurry and find them!
No one else seems to be here.
Kuririn-san, wait!
According to the readings
on the Radar,
the Dragon Balls aren't inside
the ship, but away from it.
Where are they, Gohan?
Let's see... this way.
Right over here.
Here they are, Kuririn-san, here!
Yeah, looks like something
was buried here, all right.
Why would they put them here?
Okay, let's dig them out!
Right!
Here's one! I found one!
There's another one over here!
Hooray! Here's another!
Looks like all seven are here after all!
So that's where they hid them, huh?
We've got them all!
Good. Now just summon
that Shen Long thing.
l'll put you two away,
and then have my wish of eternal life
and youth given to me!
We did it!
Hey, Gohan, what's that
on your face?
Well, what about you,
Kuririn-san?
Hurry up and summon it,
would you!?
We sure worked hard for this, huh?
Yes. Now Piccolo-san and everyone else
can finally be brought back to life.
Do it already! Summon it!
Okay, here goes. We've come such
a long way for this moment.
Let's have ourselves a look at what
the original Shen Long looks like!
Right.
Come forth, Shen Long,
and grant me my wish!
The incantation is as simple as that?
W- what's wrong?
lsn't something supposed to happen?
What is this Shen Long?
H- h- he's not coming out...
Shen Long isn't coming out. Why not?
Why isn't Shen Long blasting out of there?
Maybe the incantation is a little different.
--Shen Long, come forth!
--Those dirty punks! What are they doing?
--Please grant us our wish!
Maybe his name isn't Shen Long.
That's strange.
Kuririn-san, someone
is coming this way!
Hey, I can feel two Ki!
Is it those two Ginyu guys?
If so, does that mean
that Father was beaten?
Things are turning
for the worse again!
They're evil Ki!
There's no mistake,
it has to be those two
from before!
W- what happened to Goku, then?
We've got to suppress our own
Ki and take cover, Gohan!
Right!
The Dragon Balls have been dug up!
What's going on?
How did anyone know
where they were buried?
Goku!
It's me, it's me!
You sure surprised me!
I thought, " Ginyu! It must be
that Ginyu guy coming!"
I didn't know you had beat him,
and convinced his pal
to come over to our side.
Are you the one that found
the Dragon Balls here?
How did you know
where they were?
What are you talking about, Goku?
I used the Dragon Radar
to find them, of course.
Radar, did he say? Damn,
they've got something like that?
So, have you gotten
your wish granted then?
That's the funny thing.
It didn't work.
Shen Long won't appear.
I can't figure out why.
The password may be different
from what we use on Earth.
So, it didn't work, huh?
Goku, is something wrong with you?
Something about you...
It just doesn't seem right.
And how come you're wearing
that Scouter, or whatever it's called?
You really want to know?
Kuririn-san!
That isn't Father!
Kuririn-san, run!
So, there's another one of you, huh?
I didn't get any reading on my Scouter.
Apparently you can control your
battle power all the way down to zero.
What do you think
you're doing, Goku?!
It's not Father!
That isn't Father there!
I- if that isn't Goku,
then what's going on?
He looks just like him!
I don't know,
but I can just tell.
I've switched bodies. This one was
so much stronger, you see.
What!?
H- he's switched bodies?
That's right.
Red Magma of the
Ginyu Special Corps, Jheese!
And I am... Commander of
the Ginyu Special Corps... Ginyu-sama!
D- damn... This unfamiliar body
makes it hard to read Ki, as well.
" Unfamiliar body?" That's right!
If I ain't used to this body,
he shouldn't be used to my body, either!
You've switched bodies?
That's impossible!
I think I'll test it out right now.
The incredible power of a
better-than-180,000 battle power!
D- don't do it, Goku!
You're being controlled somehow!
You've been hypnotized or something!
Whether he's actually switched bodies,
or has just been hypnotized,
Kakarrot's strength
would still be the same.
Things are getting
worse and worse!
I'm going to keep increasing
my power even higher and higher!
I hope you're ready!
Commander Ginyu! That other
bastard followed us here.
What?
I've found you!
You've done well
to make it this far.
I should have made
the wound more severe.
K- Kuririn, Gohan, listen up!
That ain't me!
He's taken over my body!
You mean, it's true?
I- i- it can't be!
That's Father?
Yahoo!
Yum, yum!
I couldn't stand that!
That guy is Ginyu!
Don't hesitate to take him down!
There's no way he can defeat
you at your present levels!
Go on, start beating on him!
S- start beating on him, you say?
Fool! You think I cannot defeat them?
This was originally your body!
It's battle power is over 180,000.
There's no reason why that
would have changed!
You'll see, once you give it a try.
That's my body there.
How do you even expect to use
its Ki well, let alone Kaio-ken?
If body and mind ain't completely united,
you won't get any great power!
Your lies won't work on Ginyu-sama.
I'll show you what my
battle power is right now!
Jheese...
Yes, sir!
Jheese! How high is my battle power?
Just how high a battle power does Ginyu have,
now that he has stolen Goku's body?
Moreover, will Goku be able
to get his own body back?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org