Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"I am Son Goku's Son!! Gohan
Returns to the Battlefield"
Kaio-sama!
Are you all right?
Such tremendous power! Still not yet?
Hasn't Shen Long granted the wish yet?
We're counting on you, Shen Long!
Once those who were killed by
Freeza and his ring are resurrected,
the Grand Elder should return to life, and
Planet Namek's Shen Long should appear.
This is the only means by which Goku
and the others can be saved now.
Shen Long...
Father, hang in there!
This is terrible! In three minutes, this
planet will undergo a giant explosion!
Full power!!
What!?
l- It can't be!
Is something the matter?
Father-Father's Ki has disappeared!
What did you say!?
How could Father lose?
Then Son-kun is... ?
Did you see that? My 1 00 percent power!?
How about that!? That's what you get!
There was no way someone like
you could have beaten Freeza!
There's nothing else we can do! You
realize that, don't you Gohan-kun?
If we don't escape from here right now...
Gohan-kun!
Bulma-san,
take Piccolo-san and return
to Earth ahead of us.
What are you saying, Gohan-kun!?
Freeza intends to wipe out all Saiyans.
That means if I return to Earth, then
Freeza will go to Earth next!
You're not, by any chance...
H- Hold on!
Wait!
Gohan-kun!
I am my father's-Son Goku's son!
And now I... I will take on Freeza!
You can't! There's no way you can win!
I'm sure Piccolo-san would
say the same thing.
Bulma-san, take care!
Gohan-kun!
Gohan-chan! Gohan-chan!
Chichi-san, our Goku can't possibly be beaten!
He's must surely be winning against Freeza!
He's right, he's right!
On the other hand, don't matter how bad
Goku may be thrashin' on what's-his-mug,
once the whole planet blows up, he ain't...
Enough of that!
I'll thank you not to be sayin' such ill-fated
things! My Goku-sa won't be dyin' so easily!
I'm sure he's comin' home in good shape!
I'm sure... I'm sure he's comin' home!
Oh? Sorry about that.
What is the meaning of this?
Have we returned to life?
There's something strange about this!
What's with the ground shaking?
Not to mention the sky being dark.
What in the world is going on?
W- Where am I? Am I alive again?
Hurry, Shen Long! There's no time!
The sky! What's this?
Is this an indication that the planet
is just about to explode?
It looks as though it would be best for
me to get away from this planet.
If I get caught in the blast, I'll lose
even more power sharply.
T- This can't be!
Now, you'll have to face me!
You surprise me! To think you still
had the power to fly so fast.
Just what you'd expect of a Saiyan brat!
You... I'm going to defeat you!
You're going to defeat me, you say?
Are you thinking of fighting me, Freeza,
in your exhausted condition?
You for one are aware of my
overwhelming power, aren't you?
You're so miserable, you Saiyans.
Even when outclassed, you still
can't keep yourselves from fighting.
It's fine with me. This saves me the
trouble of going to Earth.
So then, last of the Saiyans, come at me!
What do you think you're doing?
Weren't you going to defeat me?
Or is it that before my overwhelming power,
the only thing you could do was run?
Why, you... !
Now then, what manner
of death do you desire?
J- Just a little longer. If I can detain Freeza for two
minutes, he'll be gone, together with the planet...
I have succeeded. Whosoever was
killed by Freeza and his ring on Planet
Namek have been returned to life.
Thank you for service.
So then, farewell.
He did it!
He did it! Everyone has been restored to life!
What about the all-important Grand Elder?
How is Planet Namek's Super Shen Long?
They're all right. They should be
all right. The sky is dark.
That's proof that Super Shen Long and the
Grand Elder are back alive. I'll verify it now.
How is this so? Why... why am
I in the mortal world?
Great! It's just as I figured!
All right!
Kaio-sama, hurry! You have hurry
and to tell him your intentions, or he'll... !
That's right! The Grand Elder's
measure of life will once again... !
I know!
Grand Elder of Planet Namek! I am
the Kaio over the Northern Galaxy.
Kaio-sama...
I want you to listen closely to
what I'm about to say.
Just a little bit more time...
Where did all that spirit you
had a moment ago go?
I know! I just thought of something nice!
I think I'll put you into the
same grave as your father.
What do you think? That must make you happy!
You should be grateful for my kindness.
Okay, that put a little bit
more fight into him.
That kid! What is he thinking!?
So that's it!
I've figured out what you were after!
You're stalling for time, aren't you?
That must be it!
You've realized that this planet only has a few
more moments of its life span left, haven't you?
Y- You...
You, who killed Father and Kuririn-san...
I can't allow someone like
you to go on living!
Masenko!
Hmph. It has to be like this, or it wouldn't
be enjoyable. Just like a Saiyan.
However, I'm done playing around. You've
gone to such trouble, so let me show you...
...my 100 percent power, which is
what killed your father!
Father... Piccolo-san...
You're finished!
What!?
F- Father!
Why haven't you escaped?
I thought I told you to get away!
B- But...
- GO!!
- Right!
Father...
You undying freak!
Goku rises again from the brink of death!
Can Kaio's wish reach the Super
Shen Long Polunga before the
destruction of Planet Namek?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org