Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"A Super-Huge Genki Dama
- I'm Playing My Last Card!! "
It's no good. Not even with
Goku's 20x Kaio-ken.
How can it be? That didn't have
much effect on him at all!
He wasn't bluffing this time either!
H- He really hasn't been using
any more than half of his power!
Ow, ow ow! Where am I?
Let's see... I was a frog, and
the frog was me, and Kuririn was there...
Um, and Son-kun might have been there...
Enough! What's taking Son-kun so long?
Just take care of those aliens, already!
This planet really is the worst!
I've found you! This is your fault!
You won't get away with it!
Unbelievable! Goku's Kamehame-Ha
just now had incredible power!
Y- Yeah...
Why, then?
Why is it that Freeza has barely
taken any damage, then?
Father's Ki has dropped considerably!
To think that a guy like that
could exist in this world!
It's utterly lost.
It's just as Kaio said. No matter what,
we should have kept our hands off of Freeza.
T- That was a close one!
How!? How does that lower life
form Saiyan have such awesome power?
This is the first time anyone has
done this much harm to my body!
You damn Saiyan!
That one... hurt.
It hurt!!
Father!
Monkey!
What happened to all that energy
you had a moment ago?
K- Kaio-sama, what is happening?
He's being beaten! Goku is taking
a one-sided beating!
- H- He's what!?
- H- He can't be!
F- Freeza is frighteningly strong.
That twenty-power Kaio-ken was
beyond Goku's limits after all.
What's wrong? Have you finally
used up the last of your power?
How dull. And here I thought I'd found an opponent
I could get somewhat serious over.
I really have lost a great deal of power. Looks as though
that 20x Kaio-ken had its price, all right.
Indeed, the Saiyans are a lower
life form, whose only talent is in fighting.
Every last one of you are fools.
Killing you off was the right decision.
It's... all over...
Kakarrot, you disappoint me!
Is that the extent of your power?
Where has your Saiyan pride gone?
- I ain't no Saiyan!
- Are you still saying that!? You're
a Saiyan unlike any other!
Vegeta, none of that matters now.
Team up with me...
You are a Saiyan! You have the fighting Saiyan
people's blood flowing through you!
Do you not feel the anguish?
The man who destroyed Planet Vegeta,
the world where you and I were
both born, is this same Freeza!
Does it not wound your pride as
a Saiyan to be battered about by him!?
Saiyan... pride?
Your father, Burdock... as well as
my father, King Vegeta...
Kakarrot, you are the last
remaining Saiyan!
He wants to kill every last Saiyan.
This is because he fears the birth
of what is said to be the strongest
warrior in the universe,
the legendary Super Saiyan!
If I could have, I would have killed him by my own hand.
And then I get killed like a rag doll!
If you understand my anguish,
then be sure to kill him by your hand!
I... don't understand what
it is you're thinking.
I hate that sort of thing!
But I won't let you die easily.
I still want to have some fun, you see.
Vegeta, I was raised on Earth, so I don't
know anything about being Saiyan.
But I can at least understand your grief!
You're talking nonsense again.
I must not lose. I must not lose,
not to the likes of Freeza!
Stop messing with me!
What!?
Don't fool...
...with me!
Why, you!
That was kind of close just now! Looks like
you've got a bit of fight back in you.
But you Saiyans are
still lower life forms.
I can read what you're going to
do next as you attack.
You will forever be unable to beat me!
F- Father!
Looks like this is it.
You'll be wanting to die
pretty soon, right?
I'll put you out of your
misery right now!
What's that? What's the matter?
It's Bubbles-kun! It sounds like
it came from the house!
- What's the matter, Bubbles?
- Gregory!
It looks like there's someone in there!
...Ah, yum! Yum!
- Look at all this food!
Yummy, yummy!
Who are you guys!?
ReaCoom!
Butta!
Jheese!
Ghurd!
Together we are...
The Ginyu Special Corps!
It's missing something, huh?
Maybe because the
Commander isn't here.
We haven't done this in a while, either.
No, it has to be the gravity!
Okay, let's try it again!
Together we are...
The Ginyu Special Corps!
All right! That one went well!
We nailed it!
Okay, from now on,
that's how we'll do it.
W- What's the deal...
with these guys?
I can't take it any more! I'm going!
W- Wait!
- How come? Father will be killed!
- Goku is about to do something!
But what? What can he hope
to do with such little remaining power?
What's this? What are you trying to do?
Ah! A Genki Dama!
What? A Genki Dama?
T- That's right. The Genki Dama, a last-ditch
technique he learned
from Kaio-sama.
The foliage and animals on this planet, as well
as ourselves, and even microorganisms...
He takes a fraction of the Genki,
the basic energy of life, from every
living thing, and apportions it to himself.
And then... and then he creates
a ball of energy, and attacks with it!
What!?
Damn, Kaio. You kept that
back from us, didn't you?
B- But will it work against Freeza?
There's a far smaller number of living
things here than on Earth!
What choice is there!? Goku
has to realize that too! Are you
saying there's another option left!?
All we can do is gamble that this works!
I can't beat Freeza with just
the energy from this planet.
Those planets in Namek, I only
need a little from each of you...
Share some of your Genki with me!
T- This Genki Dama is the
last thing I wanted to use.
There'll probably be too much force to it!
It will be hard not to squash the planet itself!
But if I don't wipe out Freeza here and now,
the universe itself could be torn apart!
I don't know if this is going to
go right or not, but it's all I can do now!
What's this you're doing?
You're still thinking of trying some
kind of nonsense, are you?
What can you possibly do, as
worn out as you are?
G- Goku...
Can you really beat Freeza
with a Genki Dama?
W- What's this I'm sensing?
l- It's...
G- Genki Dama...
l- It can't be... !
A Genki Dama, loaded with
the hopes of the universe.
Will this turn out to be
Goku's very last card?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org