Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
K- Kuririn, you handed it over
pretty easily, considering, huh?
You had to work so hard to
get that Dragon Ball, too.
He said that was the last
Dragon Ball, so it's all over now.
If I hadn't handed it over,
we definitely would have gotten killed.
The fact that the two of us
are even alive like this...
...is nearly a miracle.
Besides, we're probably still
okay handing over that Dragon Ball.
I'm sure that the Dragon Ball
that Gohan went looking for...
...is the one that Vegeta hid
to keep that Freeza bastard
from gathering all seven of them.
That's right! Gohan-kun must have
found that Dragon Ball already,
and now he's heading back!
That means things aren't going
the way Vegeta had hoped, are they?
Mm-hmm. As long as Vegeta
doesn't find Gohan, they are.
He is late, is he not?
Y- yes, sir!
It has been four hours.
What could Zarbon-san be doing?
Seeing as how he has not returned,
he has either fled,
or he has been killed.
If I had known this would happen,
I should have brought the Ginyu
Special Corps from the start, huh?
Yes, sir! C- concerning that,
according to a message we just
received from Planet Freeza,
preparations for the Ginyu Special
Corps' departure are complete.
Is that so?
I look forward to it.
Now then...
I have no need of cowardly
men, like yourself.
Be gone.
Ginyu Special Corps, launch!
What exactly is happening
on Planet Namek!?
W- what's this!?
There's an enormous power
headed for Planet Namek.
Is it Goku?
There are five of them. Is this...
...t- the Ginyu Special Corps!?
The Ginyu Special Corps?
Mm-hmm. They are the evil overlord
Freeza's special private squad.
The Ginyu Special Corps
have always operated
in the shadows of Freeza's
rule over the universe.
I don't know about " Ginyu," or whatever,
but we'll put those guys down
"g-iny-ood" and hard!
That was funny, that was funny!
Kaio-sama, how was that pun-?
Kaio-sama...
The Ginyu Special Corps-
a fearsome squad of evil.
Each one of their powers might
be higher than even Goku's.
And there are five of them.
For some reason, it feels like
my body has suddenly become lighter.
All right, one more burst!
Something's coming from straight ahead!
It's a very strong Ki...
Vegeta!
All of a sudden, there's a strong
battle power in front of me...
l have to mask my Ki...
The presence just disappeared.
Impossible...
I'm sure it was around here.
Vegeta! Hurry and get out of here!
Who's there!?
Come on out!
I know you're there!
If you don't show yourself at once,
I'm going to blow this whole area away!
H- he wouldn't!
What's the matter!? Huh!?
All right, I wonder if I had better
jump out and fight Vegeta. But then...
Gohan, there's no way we can
match up against Vegeta now.
l have to protect this precious
Dragon Ball at this point.
You don't intend to come out, huh?
All right... as you wish,
I'll blow you away!
Rats!
W-
Wait!
Please, don't let him find this...
I- it's me!
Kakarrot's son, huh?
Kakarrot's son, huh? I thought
that perhaps it might be you.
There were other Earthlings here.
You being here isn't all that surprising.
A Dragon Ball!
D- don't tell me that's!
This? I got it as a present from
that bald-headed friend of yours.
Y- you... killed Kuririn-san...
didn't you!?
If you'd like me to,
I wouldn't mind going back now
and killing him for you.
Be grateful.
To celebrate me getting all of the
Dragon Balls together, I let him live.
A- all of the Dragon Balls?
Hey, what's that you're
holding in your hand?
T- this is a clock!
Heh, a clock?
With science that can only make
a clock as huge as that one,
I'm impressed that you could
make it to this planet.
N- nobody asked you!
By the way, is that
Kakarrot bastard here, too?
No, he's not!
We didn't know there would be
bad guys like you here!
Is that so?
That's too bad, huh?
The three of us...
...are the last of the Saiyans.
When you get back to Earth,
tell him something for me.
Tell him I said that I will
come to Earth before long,
and this time, I will blow
both you and the Earth away.
It's around time for you to be
missing your mother's milk, isn't it?
Hurry back to Earth, now.
That hurt!
But still...
...the Dragon Ball is safe!
Dammit! Isn't he back yet!?
Kuririn, I've taken down the house,
and returned it to its Capsule.
Isn't Gohan-kun back yet?
I- I don't see him yet.
I sure hope he wasn't
discovered by Vegeta.
Vegeta has found out
about this place.
We have to change
locations, fast.
What is Gohan doing!?
Hurry! Hurry!
Kuririn-san!
He's here!
Kuririn-san, I found this!
You did it! We've been
waiting for this!
Gohan-kun, way to go!
Gohan, I'll fill you in
on the details later,
but we have to hurry
and get away from here,
or things are going
to get dicey.
I know most of it already.
Vegeta found me, too.
But I managed to hide
the Dragon Ball somehow,
so I got away without
him finding it.
Y- you were lucky, too, huh?
Kuririn, Gohan-kun,
let's just get moving.
--Right.
--Yeah.
This is the lake.
The Dragon Ball is submerged in here.
Once I pull it out...
...l will have all seven
Dragon Balls together.
Take that, Freeza!
As of right now,
the universe belongs to me.
That's strange. lt was definitely
submerged in this area.
lt's gone!
lmpossible!
lt was him!
The place where I ran into that kid...
...was exactly halfway between here and
the cave where those Earthlings were!
Why, that miserable brat!
But how did he search
for the Dragon Ball?
This is a clock!
That was no clock!
lt was radar!
Damn it!
You Earthling punks!
Play me for a fool, will you!?
You'll pay for this!
Damn it all!
Damn it all! Damn it all!
Where are you, you punk kids!?
Come on out, or you'll be sorry!
Dammit, they've disappeared, have they!?
Damn it all, I can't sense
their presence, either.
Those brats are able to control their
presence all the way down to zero.
I can't find them like this.
Those rotten Earthlings!
That was an insolent stunt to pull!
But they are sure to come after the six
Dragon Balls that I have at some point.
And when they do...
It's okay.
He won't find us here.
Hold on a minute.
I can't even set up the house
in a place as tight as this, can I?
Please don't ask the impossible.
There aren't too many caves
like that last one, after all.
We just have to put up with it
until Father arrives, Bulma-san.
Huh? You mean, until Son-kun
gets here, a lady such as myself
is going to have to stay here, in a place
that doesn't even have a bathroom,
together with you guys?
Oh, you don't have
to worry on that point.
I'll be taking Gohan with me,
and we'll be going to
Grand Elder-sama's place again.
Huh? How come?
What is this!?
You mean you're going to be
leaving me here all by myself!?
Please bear with us. Once Gohan
meets Grand Elder-sama,
there's a chance that he will gain
enough strength to rival even Vegeta.
Freeza's secret weapon,
the Ginyu Special Corps,
had at last gone into action.
Goku was also headed
for Planet Namek
while continuing to train
under 100-times gravity.
Vegeta was seething with anger.
And Kuririn and Gohan had taken
off to see the Grand Elder.
A grand three-way battle intertwining
good and evil was about to begin.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org