Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
P- please listen to us!
We come from a planet called Earth,
and in no way do we mean you any-
I don't want to hear anything
you invaders have to say to us!
Invaders? W- w- wait
just a minute, would you?
There's nothing sinister about us,
I tell you! We're not invaders!
Shut up!
Hold on a minute!
Those boys are right!
You talk too much for men!
You're not popular with the girls, so-
Stop standing around and do something!
Gohan, we're fighting.
Right.
Yee-ow-ow-ow!
Hey! What did you do that for!?
Don't move!
I- I really will kill you.
Zeshin, let's hurry and kill them.
These guys have to be Freeza's men.
Y- yeah...
W- we have to kill them, huh?
W- what's happening!?
Zeshin! Bad news!
We've gone into a meteor swarm!
What!? Damn...
Hey, keep an eye on these guys! If they
try anything funny, shoot them right there!
Kuririn!
Now's our chance!
Save me, quickly!
Y- yeah. Gohan...
Right.
No! No! No!
Absolutely no way!
Oww!! Oww!!
I haven't even stuck you yet.
My, my, Goku is positively
hopeless over this sort of thing.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
I told you, I haven't stuck you yet.
Good grief. For someone who's
always doin' push-ups and sit-ups,
what are you so upset over
somethin' as small as this for?
Chichi...
Hmph! How embarrassin'.
Compared to the sufferin' Gohan went through,
that pain should be nothin' at all.
I'm goin' to go pace a hundred times
in front of the shrine for Gohan-chan's sake.
Chichi...
And stickum...
What are you doing!?
Hurry it up!
Right... but...
Any ship that goes into a meteor
swarm like this won't last long,
no matter how tough it is!
If we don't hurry,
we won't be spared, either!
But that's why we can't just leave
these needy people like this...
Who are you calling needy people!?
Are you okay?
All right!
W- who are these guys?
Somebody help!
Oh, no!
Take care of things here!
Geez, you two are just
too nice to others...
Hey! What kind of piloting is that!?
Which one is-? Damn!
I can't stand to watch this! Move it!
What are you doing!?
Let me do this. I'm a pro
at this sort of thing, after all.
How can we trust you!?
W- we don't need your help!
Letting me do this is better
than getting everyone killed, right?
Let's see... this and this controls
the ascent, and this is left and right.
Which one is the speed control?
Hurry up and tell me!
You don't want to die, do you!?
T- the keys on the left side.
Okay.
Awesome!
Looks like we somehow
managed to pull through, huh?
W- what is this?
Don't you trust us yet?
How can we ever trust you!?
Your pals are the ones who
destroyed our planet, after all!
What do you mean, our pals?
Hmph, don't play dumb!
You guys are Freeza's
men, aren't you?
Freeza?
Bulma-san!
Help me out here, Kuririn.
These kids still seem
to have us all wrong.
We don't have anything wrong!
We were convinced when we saw
that barbaric power you have!
Barbaric, he says?
That's mean.
I will admit that those
two are barbarians,
but I am a sincere person,
who loves peace and justice.
N- now hold on...
How can we believe
what you're saying!?
Hold it!
Z- Zeshin...
Guys, it's okay for you
to put your guns down.
Why, Zeshin!? These guys
are Freeza's men!
Their pals are the ones
who killed our moms and dads!
If they were Freeza's men,
they wouldn't have saved us.
They would have just suddenly come
attacking us, and have killed us all.
That's right. Before,
they came without warning,
and killed Dad and Mom without
saying anything, didn't they!?
Maybe so, but...
Dad! Mom!
You've got a nice look in your eyes.
Bun...
Thanks for believing us.
Then again, those guys sound
just like Saiyans, huh?
Say, by any chance, did the guys
that attacked you have tails?
Tails? No, they didn't have those.
I- I see. Then they weren't Saiyans, huh?
Which would mean that there are
other bad folks out here in space.
So, what happened to your planet?
Our planet was peaceful,
and a very easy place to live.
Until they came!
Those guys appeared before
us without any warning.
They said they were going to
deliver our world to Freeza-sama,
and that we should be thankful.
And then they suddenly started killing
our dads and moms like they were worms.
They were going to kill all
the people who were on the planet,
and turn it over to Freeza!
I'm surprised you guys survived.
The adults who realized what Freeza's
scheme was had us escape in spaceships.
But all of the other spaceships were
chased down by Freeza, and shot down!
So this mirror-clad spaceship
is the only one that survived.
Mirror-clad spaceship? I see,
so the mirrors reflect outer space.
That explains why we couldn't
see the shape of your ship, either.
So where are you guys going now?
Do you have any destination?
Yeah, there's a planet where our dads
used to travel to on business long ago.
We're sure that they will take us in.
Is this planet far away?
Not to worry. We'll get to that planet,
no matter how many years it takes.
Hang in there, all right?
Yeah. You guys, too.
Right.
Okay, let's go. We've lost quite
a bit of time, so we need to hurry.
Oh, that's okay, isn't it?
Planet Namek isn't going anywhere.
Planet Namek? Are you guys
going to Planet Namek?
That's right. You know it?
We passed it about two weeks ago.
If you go straight in the direction KS-162,
there should be quite a shortcut.
Huh? You mean it?
Y- yeah...
The direction KS-162, right?
Thank you! Come on, we're going.
Bye-bye.
Oh, but that shortcut is...
Well, they're gone.
They were nice folks, huh?
Bun...
Okay, we'll hurry on, too!
All right! Guys, let's go!
Take direction KS-162
and head to Planet Namek.
That's a bit of a relief, huh?
What's the matter?
Oh, I'm just worried about the other
bad aliens those kids talked about.
But they weren't the Saiyans, right?
However, the Saiyans did have allies.
They've got nothing to do with us.
Well, I'm going to bed.
I'm completely exhausted.
However, Kuririn's concerns
were by no means off the mark.
Eighteen days after Vegeta left Earth...
All right, here...
Something is coming!
Is it Freeza-sama?
It couldn't be! He just left!
I- it's an older model.
It's a soldier.
That signal is Vegeta-sama's.
That's strange. We didn't get
any word that he was returning.
Could something have happened to him?
Hey, this is the control room!
Vegeta-sama is arriving!
Fall out to greet him at once!
He's here.
There's just one pod,
all right. Where's Nappa-san?
What's the matter?
He's not coming out.
H- hey, his life signs are awfully low.
What?
He's using the life-support equipment!
This is bad! Hurry and take him
to the treatment center!
W- w- what is that!?
An earthquake?
B- Bulma-san, has something
happened to cause this shaking!?
You guys make light of outer space,
so that's why you're so
surprised by something like this.
This is a shortcut, so it's
going to be a little bumpy.
How can she sleep through
a situation like this?
I- it's settled down.
That was mean, Bulma-san.
I didn't think that you
would try anything like this!
No, you misunderstand, Bulma-san!
How would you know!? You're a student
of that Old Man Turtle, too, after all!
Poor Kuririn-san...
Look at that!
We made it! We've arrived
at Planet Namek!
That was fast, huh?
It's only been about ten days.
That's what a shortcut will do for you.
Is that really...
...Planet Namek?
Sure it is. Isn't it obvious?
Just like those kids said.
Bulma and the others had arrived in no time.
But was this really Planet Namek?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org