Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"Attack, Goku!! An Enraged Freeza's
Second Transformation"
Incredible! He's holding his own
against Freeza!
No, he's doing better!
You really are incredible, Piccolo-san!
Just what the hell has happened? It hasn't been that
long since he was defeated on Earth!
We might actually be able to get out of
this without dying, Gohan!
Right!
Beat that Freeza, who killed so many of
us, using the power of Nail-san!
What kind of training has Piccolo undergone?
That's the way, stick with him until I get better!
Kaio-sama, with Piccolo powered-up as
much as he is, can he defeat Freeza?
If he doesn't beat him for us, we're screwed!
So fast! And I should have the
advantage of speed!
Kuririn-san...
How can this be? You mean, he hasn't
been taking this seriously up until now?
What's the best step for me to take now?
What should I do?
Damn you for making us rejoice prematurely!
Nail-san...
Piccolo! What kind of guy is this Freeza!?
Piccolo...
Kaio-sama?
I told you, they have touched that
which should not be touched...
Piccolo...
Sorry about that just now. I didn't give
you enough credit.
But you are capable of more than I imagined.
I decided to show you some true power.
Which is to say, my true power.
There's no end to his power!
Was I really planning to fight against him?
So will I. Let's make this genuine.
What's that?
You're saying you haven't been serious
up until now?
I didn't realize that Namekians told
fish stories.
You'll find out very soon.
You worthless fool! To have to resort
to bluffing at this stage...
l- I get it!
Piccolo's been fighting with that heavy
turban and mantle on all this time?
Now realize the fury of all the Namekians
who were killed by you!!
Piccolo's Ki is getting stronger again.
This strength is the real thing!
He can win! Piccolo-san can win!
Piccolo! We're counting on you!
The situation has changed again!
You've removed those heavy garments
and made yourself lighter...
which is supposed to mean your speed
has become even more polished?
We'll have to see.
It will take more than this to satisfy the
fury of the Namekians!
He did it!
Gohan!
Kuririn-san!
Nail-san!
Nice going, Piccolo-san!
That's the way!
At this rate, Kakarrot may still be in time.
In which case, I may get out of this alive!
And now to finish you off!
Has Freeza... ?
You don't suppose... ?
Look there!
As tenacious as I expected.
You seem to be laboring under some false
impression concerning my true power.
What!?
Did you really think that what I just showed
you was serious?
You couldn't have known I'd transformed
myself, could you?
Transformed, you say?
I will allow you the same thing I gave to
Vegeta and the others...
A feeling of absolute terror towards me.
All right, first I will instill a sense
of hopelessness.
A hopelessness from knowing that nothing
you can possibly do will help!!
Every time l, Freeza, transform myself, my
power substantially grows!
And I still have two more
transformations remaining!
Do you know what that means?
What's this?
Impossible!
Gohan, what did he just say?
Freeza can transform two more times.
Now getting married is completely out.
So then, let me show it to you.
You guys should feel honored. You're the first
ones I've ever shown this transformation to!
Watch carefully now! Here comes
Freeza-sama's second-stage transformation!
I apologize for the delay. Now then, shall we
begin the battle once again?
Y- You monster!
H- He hasn't changed all that much, has he?
Idiot! Try probing what his latent power is!
It's completely different from a moment ago!
Yet he's settled down again, and he's
regained his presence of mind!
He's also lost the damage that Piccolo-san
had inflicted on him!
Damn it all! What's going on out there? That
Ki of Freeza's has gotten stronger again!
At this point, even once I completely recover,
I might not be able to beat him. Now what?
Freeza is a super-monster
beyond imagination!
You had such confidence in your speed
earlier, did you not?
So then, shall we have another look at it?
You bastard! If you've got the power, I've got the speed!
You won't catch up to me in this lifetime!
l- It can't be!
My goodness, it has been too long,
my little toddler.
Piccolo-san has lost his speed advantage
over Freeza!
Does that mean Freeza's power has gone up
that much?
Don't lose, Nail-san!
Thank goodness, you aren't dead! I'll heal
you right away!
That's right!
There's still that trick!
It's all over now, isn't it?
Piccolo...
Shall we put an end to this play, then?
D- Damn...
You have realized that, unfortunately enough,
the speed you took such pride in
is of utterly no use against me now,
have you not?
I would have you give up now!
S- So fast!
Piccolo-san!
They're impossibly fast! There's no way
he can dodge them!
Piccolo-san...
Piccolo!
Stop it!
Gohan!
Gohan! Dammit!
Wait!
What are you doing, Vegeta!?
There's no sense for you to go!
B- But if I don't...
Listen here, at this rate, we're all going to be
killed by Freeza!
Never mind him, you blast me half-to-death!
Do it now!
Once I get that kid to heal me, and rise
from a near-death state one more time,
I'm certain to be able to become a
Super Saiyan!
Having transformed a second time, Freeza
has become even more powered-up.
Piccolo faces a great pinch, as Gohan leaps
to his aid. How will this turn out?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org