Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Dammit... l've got a bad feeling
about this. Hurry! Hurry!
C- Chaozu...
Who's going to play with me next?
I- it had no effect at all!
Chaozu won't be able
to rest in peace like this!
Looks like his death was for nothing.
Chaozu!
Be grateful! I'm going to send you to meet him
again in the Next World soon enough!
Y- you'll pay for this!
You're definitely going to pay for this!
Incredible!
You can't be too careful
getting near him!
Tenshinhan! Get him back
for Yamucha and Chaozu!
Hang in there, Tenshinhan!
The only thing driving Tenshinhan
is his determination.
He's fighting on determination alone.
More trouble with this?
What on earth is the problem!?
Hey! Can't you get any closer!?
T- this is intense!
Out of breath already? You should
start seeing the Next World soon.
At this rate, Tenshinhan-san
will be done in, too.
I've got to do something!
Stop!
We've got a slight, momentary opening
on him when he moves to attack.
We'll watch for that moment.
Got that, Gohan?
Yes...
That's a good strategy.
I hope it goes well for you.
Are you sure you should be looking away?
You'll miss your chance.
You sure are confident.
But you won't be able to stand there
with that stupid look on your face
once Son Goku arrives.
Oh? And who is that?
Your ace-in-the-hole?
You just look forward to it.
Tenshinhan-san!
Looks like this is
the end of the line for you.
I'll put you out of
your misery right now.
See you in hell!
Now! Scatter, Kuririn, Gohan!
Yeah!
You're finished! Die!
What!?
Gohan! Now! Shoot him!
Gohan!
Take aim!
I'm scared!
You dirty brat!
No!
We missed him!
Our timing was too late!
I- I'm sorry... Uncle Piccolo!
You really did a number on me.
You've shortened your lives even further.
Fine! I've decided to change the order
in which I'm going to kill you.
Brace yourselves!
What the matter, Kami-sama?
It looks like my life
will only last a little longer.
Death... death is close at hand.
Which means... don't tell me!
Piccolo is going to be killed.
And so will everyone else.
W- what about Goku?
I still cannot sense his presence.
Goku, hurry! Hurry, Goku!
That was some awesome speed oni!
Hang in there oni!
Guys, sit tight!
C- Chaozu...
You guys aren't too bright
to be making me angry.
I'll get you two together!
What do we do?
That brat!
Well now, which one will
I amuse myself with first?
I'll leave the Namekian there alive,
but barely breathing.
We have to find out more
about the Dragon Balls from you.
You're lucky, Piccolo.
They think that you're the only one
who knows about the Dragon Balls.
It's all the same. They're planning
to kill us all, in any case.
All right, we go on the offensive first!
We're going to attack him!
Crafty...
Here goes!
Uncle!
Uncle...
We don't need any cowards like you.
Go on home to bed, right now!
Tenshinhan-san! Are you dead?
Piccolo, now what?
Is there anything we can do?
No.
I didn't think he was going
to be this big a monster.
He goes far beyond
the Saiyan that came earlier.
It's too late for regrets
to do any good now!
Here I come!
Tenshinhan-san!
C- Chaozu...
Ten-san...
Chaozu!
Ten-san, I'm sorry.
I didn't do any good.
Chaozu...
Tenshinhan-san...
Ten-san, I'm sorry...
Chaozu!
Chaozu, I will avenge you!
And then I'll be coming.
I won't let you be lonesome
all by yourself!
This... this will be my final...
...Kikoho!!
Did he get him!?
You gave me a start...
It didn't work at all against him!
Don't tell me he's immortal!
N- no!
Miserable fool!
He could have just lain there,
but he instead used up his power
and died for nothing.
I- it can't be!
Not Tenshinhan too!
This is awful. It's a nightmare.
How can everyone be dying, one after another?
Goku! Get here soon!
Goku! Goku!
Please! Goku!
Goku?
They've been saying that for a while.
Hang on...
Another one has been taken care of!
Your turn comes next!
Let's go down on the ground and fight.
He's far more used
to mid-air fighting than us.
It'll all end up the same,
no matter where it happens.
Writhe! Writhe!
Here goes!
--H- he's coming!
--Father!
Wait, Nappa!
W- what is it?
Why don't you let me get them?
Don't be hasty. There's
something I want to ask them.
This Son Goku person you're
talking about is Kakarrot, isn't it?
That's right. What of it?
To think that you are
falling back on Kakarrot...
He couldn't even stand against Raditz.
What good will it do you
when he gets here?
He won't be the same as he was back then!
He's sure to be much, much stronger!
Don't you look down
your noses at Son Goku!
But for all that, he's not here, is he!?
Are you sure he hasn't
gotten scared and run away!?
H- he'll be here!
Father will surely be here!
He's going to take care of you guys!
That reliance of yours is something else.
Interesting. We're going
to wait until he gets here.
Ah, that's lame! Let's put
these guys away right now!
However, only for three hours.
We won't wait any longer than that.
That's absurd! I'm going
to play with them right now!
Nappa! Didn't you hear what I said!?
S- sorry. I got carried away.
That's how it's going to be. Your lives
have been extended somewhat. Be grateful.
Be reasonable. This is his
first actual fight, after all.
I'm the pathetic one
for expecting anything from you.
Get out of here, you coward!
Be that as it may, the way
that huge guy just got timid-
does that mean that Vegeta runt over there
is even more ridiculously strong?
How can that be?
I'm just itching to do something here!
Let's get them, right now!
Just wait. Three more hours.
Wait three more hours,
and you'll be able to watch
a magnificent, hellish show.
Vegeta's scheme is appalling.
What exactly will this
hellish show in three hours be?
ls he saying that the extinction
of earth will happen in three hours?
Will Goku arrive in time?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org