Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Jheese, how high is
my battle power now?
Yes, sir...
What's wrong?
Jheese, hurry up and tell me!
I- it's 23,000.
What's that?
I can't hear you!
23,000!
There, you hear that!?
Just 23,000! That's all!
Why?
W- why, you ask?
23,000?
You say it's just 23,000!?
That's my body there.
You see, unless your mind
and body are united,
you can't put out any great power!
Kuririn, Gohan,
you can beat this guy now!
I- impossible!
T- this is impossible!
I- it's true! We just might
be able to beat him like this!
Let's go, Gohan!
R- right!
Now, Gohan!
What's the matter, Gohan!?
Father...
Gohan!
What's the matter, Gohan?
I- I'm sorry. For a moment,
he seemed like he really was Father.
I- I know what you mean.
I feel the same way.
But that isn't Goku. It's Ginyu!
Got it?
Gohan... Kuririn...
Okay, it won't happen this time.
Here we go!
Jheese!
What are you doing?
Why don't you fight!?
Y- yes, sir!
Whoa!
You're going to face me!
Vegeta!
You mean that lousy Vegeta
is still around?
You expect such a wimpy
attack to hurt me?
W- why!? This body is supposed to
have a power greater than 180,000!
Didn't you hear what Goku said before?
You can't use that body very well.
Why don't you just give up now?
G- give up? You expect me,
Ginyu-sama to give up!?
Don't be ridiculous!
Kuririn... Gohan...
For someone such as yourself to even
consider picking a fight with me...
...takes a lot of guts!
Babble as much as you want!
How did you manage
to hide yourself!?
There wasn't any reading
on my Scouter!
You guys rely too much
on your Scouters!
If you were to fight against
those guys from Earth,
you'd figure it out for yourself!
That is, assuming
you don't die here first!
Don't be ridiculous! The Ginyu Special
Corps is made up of only
the most super-elite
warriors in the universe!
There's no way a monkey
bastard such as you
could ever stand
a chance against me!
So you say, but you're
actually afraid of
my renewed battle power,
aren't you?
W- what?
Take a good, long look,
with your precious Scouter there.
Afraid, you say?
Me? Afraid of a battle power
such as yours, Vegeta?
I- impossible...
Dammit!
It's broken!
Do you really think
it was a malfunction?
W- why, you!
Every time I recover from
being near death, I grow stronger.
I've also overcome
the limits of ordinary Saiyans,
and I'm still getting stronger!
Actually, I've just now
realized something-
This growth in power is not just due
to some kind of gift that I have.
Which means, I must be getting
very close to becoming one myself!
A Super Saiyan!
W- what?
S- stop talking nonsense!
A Super Saiyan is the mightiest
of all warriors,
delighting in death and battle!
Kakarrot may not be cold-hearted
enough to become one,
but I'm different!
I- i- impossible!
Attaway, attaway!
We're really hitting our stride!
L- looks like we're going
to beat him, huh, Kuririn-san?
I- impossible! How can I,
Commander of the Ginyu Special Corps,
be beaten by these guys?
G- Goku,
Sure enough, it was useless
trying to stop you,
and now you've become tangled up
in things better left untouched.
Goku, soon you will realize the hidden
terror possessed by Freeza.
It's not too late, even now.
Depart from that planet
as quickly as you can!
I- if Dende... can just make
it to where they are...
You Namekians really
are very stubborn.
You have absolutely
no chance of winning.
I do not want to use
my energy needlessly.
Dende...
I wonder how much longer I will
be able to view Namek's scenery.
I hope it is until Dende
reaches the Earthlings.
W- when Grand Elder-sama dies,
the Dragon Balls will also disappear.
Before that happens, I have to hurry
and meet up with those people.
Oh, no!
Gohan!
This is strange.
It's like suddenly, it seems
like he's gotten much stronger.
Watch yourself, Gohan!
R- right!
Impressive. Looks like he's starting
to get used to my body.
This ain't good.
From here on out,
I'm not going to be pushed
around by rubbish like you guys!
Here it comes!
The Ginyu Special Corps'...
I haven't done this
by myself very much,
but there's got to be something
good for me to say here...
Oh well, maybe I'll just skip it
this time and leap right into battle.
I- I- I wasn't finished yet!
I won't be beaten
by that flimsy blast!
This one will be even harder!
Gohan! Get out of the way!
Goku!
F- Father...
Yow-ow-ow!
H- how did you manage
that in your condition!?
I- it's just like you're doing.
I'm starting to get used to this body.
I'm going to fight, too!
Y- you may have become
partially used to it,
but you still can't generate
its full power.
We've got to eliminate him,
before he completely masters my body.
With the three of us,
we can beat him!
Kuririn! Gohan!
Right, Father!
Y- yeah!
There's something strange
about this, huh?
I- I feel the same way.
I- it's a little odd to think that
I'm about to attack my own body like this.
Vegeta! There's no way we're going to be
beaten by a monkey bastard like you!
Babble on all you like!
It does not change the fact that
you are no longer a match for Vegeta-sama!
Now then, how about I show
you my true power?
S- s- spare me-
Vegeta! You didn't
have to go that far!
You just keep on spouting that soft-hearted
nonsense of yours, Kakarrot!
You'll never become a Super Saiyan!
I'm the only one who has that capacity!
What? You, a Super Saiyan?
Haven't you taken care of Ginyu yet?
All right then,
I'll dispose of him for you!
Move it!
I- incredible!
Now, to finish you off!
Why, you...
T- that's enough!
Don't kill him, Vegeta!
Die!!
You fool!
I- it can't be!
Change!!
What?
Once again, Ginyu's signature technique,
the Body Change, bursts forth.
What is Ginyu's target?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org