Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
There, there...
Y- Yamucha...
Pu-erh!
Hey, Pu-erh!
Stay with me! Hey!
Pu-erh too, huh?
My, my, the sofa is going
to be all full at this rate.
Come on, Bulma, take heart.
What are you talking about!?
How can I be calm with Yamucha dying!?
You don't have to worry about Yamucha.
This is the first time
Yamucha has died, right?
We can always bring him back to life
with the Dragon Balls, can't we?
That's right! That's right, isn't it?
Yes, that's right!
You dirty old man!
What a pathetic Saibaiman-
ending in a draw!
What did he think he was doing,
against scum like that!?
Hey, clean that up.
He's dirtying up the place.
That pile of filth.
You dirty bastard!
Get back, everyone!
Let me show you
the results of my training!
Go!
What is that-
slow-moving blast?
We'll be caught in the blast!
It's got tremendous energy,
but almost no speed at all.
It's like it's saying,
"Get out of the way!"
You did it!
He did it! He did it!
H- hold on, B- Bulma...
L- let me go...
I- incredible!
Kuririn, are you okay?
Yeah. But I missed one of them.
Burn in hell!
Just what you'd expect from Piccolo.
l shudder to think about him
becoming my enemy again someday.
Thank you, Piccolo-san.
Don't get the wrong idea.
You think I would save you?
I was just warming up for the marvelous
battle that is about to get underway.
Assuming that's the kind of
fight it turns out to be...
Well then, as you wish, how about
we put an end to the games?
This means it's time for the real thing!
lmpossible! lt had hardly
any effect on him at all!
They were hit dead-on!
I- I did that at full power!
So that's what a Saiyan is, is it?
Please let me handle them. I'll put all
five of them away in the blink of an eye.
Do as you like.
However...
...do not kill the Namekian.
We'll need to get him to tell us
about the Dragon Balls afterward.
Yes, understood.
Now then, entertain me
the best that you can. First off...
I'll start with you!
Let me handle this!
Piccolo-san!
Looks like this is
going to be somewhat fun!
What?
T- the ground is shaking!
I- it's no use!
Ten-san!
M- my telekinetic powers aren't working!
T- this can't be!
Piccolo-san!
Stand firm, Gohan!
B- but!
Control your Ki!
Don't let yourself be
browbeaten by this level of Ki!
R- right!
S- still, I had no idea
it would be this bad...
Hmm? Is that-?
The Snake Princess' palace.
W- what was that just now?
Beats me.
If memory serves, that was the
midpoint of the Serpentine Road.
All right, everyone, just you wait!
Chaozu! Be careful!
H- here he comes!
Now then, which one of you
shall I take care of first?
Tenshinhan!
Get out of there!
Ten-san!
Hmph! What fragile folk.
Now to finish you!
You filthy bastard!
Tenshinhan-san!
That's one tough bastard.
He's still alive.
W- what power he has!
Dammit! Tenshinhan!
Wait!
He's had it! Leave him alone!
Don't interrupt!
I can't see the bottom
of the hole! Unbelievable!
What an incredible energy wave!
C- Chaozu!
Was he done in just now!?
Chaozu!
Don't worry!
I'll send you to him soon enough-
in the next world!
D- damn...
Nappa! Look behind you!
Chaozu!
Why, you!
When did you get back there!?
Come on, let go!
Why, you... why, you... runt!
Come on!
Chaozu! Get away from him!
Chaozu-san!
Look at him.
Look at him! Don't turn away.
This is what fighting is.
You're a persistent one!
Chaozu! That's enough!
Get away from him!
T- Ten-san...
Thank you.
W- what are you saying... Chaozu?
Get away from there!
Get away from there, now!
I enjoyed... being together...
with you...
Chaozu! What are you thinking!?
Farewell, Ten-san. Please don't die.
D- don't tell me... you're-!
Farewell. Farewell!
Stop! Chaozu!
Farewell!
Chaozu!!
Blowing himself up
and taking them both out-
that was a pretty drastic thing to do.
For a little squirt,
that was nicely done.
That was a worthless thing to do!
Nappa, he sure gave you
a lot of trouble, considering.
I- i- it can't be! How can he
be unfazed!? T- that's awful!
Chaozu even gave up his life!
Chaozu has already been brought
back to life with the Dragon Balls.
He can't be brought back
to life again! Dammit!
You're going to pay for this!
It looks like you still don't
realize how fearsome we are!
The only thing you have
coming to you is death!
The warriors are falling, one by one.
ls there anything that Tenshinhan
and the others can do
in the face of the Saiyans' powers,
which are far greater
than they anticipated?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org