Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"Showdown!! The Embodiment of Flame
in a 20x Kaio-ken Kamehame-Ha"
That's our Freeza-sama! He's just
playing with Goku! Such composure!
W- Who the hell are you!?
W- Who, me?
He's a frog! A frog, I tell you!
CHAN-GE!!
T- Then, this frog is...
B- Bulma-san?
Haven't I been saying so all this time!?
I'll send you all to hell!
I'll never get anywhere like this.
Your body is mine!
CHAN-GE!
What!?
Piccolo, watch out!
I... I can't... move... !
Piccolo-san!
P- Piccolo-san...
W- What happened?
My hands... my feet... my body...
My cheek... !
Yea! Yea, yea! I'm back in
my original body!
Ow, ow! T- Thank goodness, Bulma-san, but it's very
dangerous here! If you don't take cover soon...
Enough already!
Bulma-san!
Get over here and save me!
This is getting ridiculous. You can
entertain me a little bit more, if you like.
What a technique!
As I told you, If I had to, I could destroy
this whole planet.
I am the one who destroyed
Planet Vegeta.
l- I've had it.
I can't win.
W- What did he do?
H- He's cut the whole planet!
N- Never mind that, I have to wonder
if Goku is planning something.
It looks like he's starting to take a
one-sided beating!
- He's got no plan!
- The fact is, Freeza's power is greater
than we could have thought!
You don't have to worry. I wouldn't kill
you instantly with something like that.
D- Dammit...
Otherwise, I wouldn't be able to
placate my anger.
So, how about Goku?
Even using his upper limit of a 10x Kaio-ken,
is Son being defeated, Kaio-sama?
On top of that, Freeza seems to only
be using half of his power!
T- That can't be!
This is why I told him that no matter
what happens, he must not
set his hand to Freeza.
He has lost!
So, then...
What can I do to cause you the most pain?
Should I break your arm? Rip off your
ears? Or perhaps I'll slit your throat.
T- The only thing I can do is pull up to a
20x Kaio-ken somehow!
My body may not be able to
handle it, though.
But if, like he says, he really is only
using fifty percent of his power now,
there ain't nothing else I can do...
It's much too late for you to start
agonizing. You're the one who
started this, after all.
You will become my toy, until I
grow tired of you!
What's the matter? If you don't resist a little for me,
I will find you unresponsive and get bored!
Hey, hey, the fun is just beginning!
It's much too soon for you to
be going to bed!
It's no use!
How does it feel to become a fish?
Kuririn!
- Goku-sa!
- G- Goku!
- Chichi! Where are you!?
- Old Man Turtle Hermit! Oolong!
O- Old Timer!
Chichi!
Goku-sa! ...Goku-sa! ...
- Father!
- Gohan!
Father!
W- What!?
- Father!
- G- Goku!
For the future of Gohan, Chichi, Earth,
and Planet Namek...
I absolutely must not lose!!
Fifty percent power, he says... Whether
those words are a bluff, or whether they ain't,
all I can do is stake everything on a
20x Kaio-ken!
Ka... me...
ha... me...
HA!!
Damn it to hell... !
Now that even his twenty-fold Kaio-ken was of no use,
is there any chance of victory left for Goku?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org