Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Just a little farther till we're at
Kame House. Hang in there, Gohan.
Right.
H- hey, over there...
T- that's the direction
we just came from.
What could it be?
It's awfully bright. A star?
No, it doesn't appear to be a star...
This can't be!
T- this is impossible!
W- what is that? There's
a tremendous Ki rising up.
Father's Ki hasn't risen again, right?
N- no. This nasty feeling
is coming from the other one's Ki.
And you know, that's an incredible
amount of Ki. What's going on!?
F- Father...
Gohan!
I- I'm going back.
I'm going back.
G- going back? You mean
to where Goku is?
I can tell... Father is in trouble.
He's going to die if this keeps up...
What are you talking about, Gohan?
There's no way Goku- your father
is going to die, is there?
Besides, even if we go back there,
we can't do anything against
a guy with a Ki that incredible.
Yeah, I know.
Even so...
Even so!
I absolutely have to go back there!
Hey!
Wait up, Gohan!
How about it, Kakarrot?
You're finished now!
What's going on!?
A Great Ape?
A Great Ape monster?
Let me give you some good news.
A Saiyan who has become a Great Ape
has ten times more battle power!
Goku, there's a great ape monster
that comes out during the full moon.
You must not go outside. As long
as you stay asleep, you'll be safe.
I- I'll make it so that
tail of yours never grows back.
It's something of a nuisance.
S- so that's it!
l finally get it!
H- how awful...
The monster that crushed
Grandpa to death...
...and the monster that showed up
at the tournament grounds,
and busted everything up...
...that was me!?
l'm sorry, Grandpa.
This guy is incredible.
l'll probably have to use up all of my Ki,
or I won't be able to beat him.
Once I die, and go back over to the
Next World, l'll go apologize to you.
What is that monster!?
I- it's outrageously huge!
That monster's clothes're the same
as the Saiyan's! Is he that Saiyan!?
I'll show you, Vegeta!
I'm going to feed you your fill
of me and the earth's Genki Dama!
You're at last going to use
the Genki Dama, are you?
Still, with your body
as ragged as it is,
this is going to put
too much of a burden on it.
K- Kaio-ken!!
What's the matter?
Can't you even get away?
Die!!
What is it?
Is anything appearing?
I'm starting to see some light.
Goku's Ki has subsided.
Goku-sa has won, right?
--Goku!
--Son-kun!
Goku-sa!
I- is he dead?
No, he is not dead.
What the hell has happened?
I- impossible!
You mean the Saiyan has transformed,
even without the moon!?
It's hopeless now! There's no way
he can stand up to that monster!
What about Gohan-chan!?
What's Gohan-chan doin'!?
Where's Gohan-chan!?
There's someone else there...
It's Yajirobe!
What is he doing!?
Come on, Yajirobe!
Why aren't you helping Son-kun!?
Hey!
G- Gohan-chan...
Chichi!
Father!
Goku, he's your son, all right.
What's the matter, Kakarrot?
Can't you manage anything!?
H- he's so fast
for as big as he is!
I don't have enough time to mentally
focus so I can create a Genki Dama!
And even if I went to a 5X Kaio-ken,
it wouldn't be any use against him!
Hmph. If you're not going to come
at me, then I'm coming after you!
I- I just need ten seconds!
I need some time to concentrate!
T- that's it!
Tenshinhan, I'm going
to borrow your technique!
Taiyo-ken!!
Now, while his eyes
are blinded by the glare!
M- my eyes! My eyes!
All right...
At this distance...
T- the Land...
...the Seas...
...and...
...all living things...
Each of you, share with me
just a little bit of your Genki energy!
l beg you!
Dammit, that was an insolent stunt!
J- just a little longer...
Just a little more,
and I can form a Genki Dama...
W- what's he doin'?
He's starting to get
his sight back.
Still, at this distance,
l'll be able to launch the Genki
Dama before he can attack.
Dammit!
Where are you!?
Where did you go!?
It's useless to run away from me!
I can sense your presence!
Dammit!
l've gathered the Genki energy together.
Why, you!
He found me! Please,
let there be enough time!
I-it's done. I've collected the
Genki energy from all earthlings.
All right!
Take this!
W- what was that?
What happened?
I- I never expected him to attack like that...
T- that was an awful miscalculation.
What a development... The Genki Dama
I worked so hard to make has vanished...
Hmph, you're a tough bastard.
But you appear to be
near your limit. I can tell.
H- he's got me. There ain't
no way even I can win now.
I used up most of my Ki
on that Genki Dama.
Now what are you going to do!?
Goku's Ki is shrinking fast!
F- Father!
Hurry! We're almost there!
Whoops! Sorry, sorry!
Looks like I carelessly stepped
on you and crushed your leg.
Well, this time, I'll
carelessly crush your heart.
This is the end for you, Kakarrot!
Even if you were to come back to life again,
this planet won't be here when you do!
D- damn...
I'm utterly defeated...
I never imagined there'd be
this much difference in our power...
I'm glad there was someone
so strong... but if I die...
...it'd be so frustrating...
Die!!
That's what you call
the weasel's last fart...
Now, I ain't even got enough
strength left to blow my nose...
D- do as you like...
W- why, you!
Kakarrot!
How dare you...
how dare you scar my face!?
I'm going to squeeze you to death!
Having been wounded,
Vegeta was burning with anger.
Will Goku be crushed
to death like this?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org