Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
''The Incredible Destructive Force of the
Genki Dama!! Who Will Survive!?''
All of you sneaking around like this,
you're like pestering flies!
Aren't you done yet, Son Goku!? Haven't
you completed the Genki Dama yet!?
That Freeza creep is quite
thoroughly pissed off!
I- it's no good! This is still going
to take some time!
Shoot it! Shoot it, already!
I- it's no use...Just a little longer...
For someone too stubborn to die...Are
you still hanging around here?
I'll show you the power of someone
too stubborn to die!
Piccolo-san...
Piccolo may be intent on dying.
He probably used up the greater part of
his power in that blindside attack.
He's risking his own life to buy time for
Goku to finish the Genki Dama!
Piccolo-san!
Wait, Gohan!
Goku, please hurry!
That was useless.
Didn't you get it when I told
you it was useless?
Apparently, you wish to die early.
Goku! Hurry...hurry and complete
the Genki Dama!
Piccolo...
-Tenshinhan... -These guys pushed Vegeta
around like he was a baby! Be careful!
Here goes!
Oh, look out!
Save me!
You guys,
Attack! Attack, I say!
That's easy for you to say!
They're even...stronger...guys than ...Vegeta was!
Dammit, I'll do it!
What?
You're weaker than we thought, aren't you!?
What!?
We can win this!
All right, me too!
I get it! It's not that they're weak, it's
that we're strong!
This is the result of our training! The fruits of having
received Kaio-sama's judicious training!
They're better than I thought.
Hey, if we get serious, they'll be no problem!
Hey, ReaCoom, shake it off!
Nice! This is how it ought to be!
I am totally up for this!
ReaCoom Body Attack!!
All right...!
Hey!
Ginyu Special Corps' Red Magma, Jheese!
Ginyu Special Corps' Blue Hurricane, Butta!
Now!
Goku, isn't the Genki Dama ready yet?
Still longer, Goku? I've just about
reached my limit.
Just a little longer...
Just a little longer, and it will beat Freeza...
As you wish, I'll kill you first.
Those guys, they scraped that together
with what little Ki they had left!
That there should still be some flies
there that had not run away...
You folks really are good at
annoying someone...
This is as far as it goes! I'm going to
trash you, along with the whole planet!
Goku! Still not yet!?
Okay, it's finished!
Do it, Goku!
Father!
O- oh, crap!
Get down!
I- I'll just take this and...
I'll take this and...
Oh, what's this!?
H- he did it! Goku beat Freeza...
He beat Freeza!!
Yeah, he really beat Freeza!
He did it! He did it!
-He beat him!
-Goku did it!
Has Freeza-sama lost?
I- impossible!
It's a lie!
Goku has won!
He did it!
Kuririn-san!
Yo! You all right?
Y-yes!
It's all completely changed.
Yeah.
Where's father?
Where's Uncle Piccolo?
The super-giant Genki Dama finally detonates!
Has Freeza really been laid to rest?
And what of Goku? What of Piccolo?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org