Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
This is bad...
this is definitely bad...
There aren't supposed
to be any other Saiyans.
W- who could it be?
Now there are three more, yes?
Hold them with care, Dodoria-san. It appears
that Vegeta is after them, as well.
Freeza-sama, Kewie, who is
pursuing Vegeta, has just landed.
And as for those two large
power readings that appeared earlier,
they suddenly disappeared,
and remain so.
We are searching the area
where the readings were located,
so we should soon discover
what their source was.
Well, the issue here is the disposal
of Vegeta, who has defied me.
In that case, you need not worry.
Kewie should now be heading
after Vegeta to deal with him.
Those two have always hated each other,
and their abilities are roughly the same.
In any event, Vegeta is not
likely to come away unscathed.
Vegeta, you're not
getting away from me.
I've found you, Vegeta.
I'm under orders from Freeza-sama!
Are you reading me, Vegeta!?
Now I can kill you out in the open!
Don't make me laugh, Kewie.
You think you can kill me?
I'm waiting here for you,
so get here fast.
What are you, blind?
Take a good look at your Scouter.
My battle power is clearly
higher than yours!
We can't stay here,
in any case, can we?
I'll leave the Dragon Balls up to you.
Okay, well, I'm going
back to Earth, so good luck.
Bulma-san, just a minute.
What should we do, Gohan?
S- should we go back
to Earth now, too?
After all, it looks like
we've got one more foe now,
and even if we do have
the Dragon Radar...
Oh, I mean,
I'm fine and all,
but it wouldn't be right if anything
were to happen to Gohan.
B- but Kuririn-san, if we do that,
then he'll get the Dragon Balls.
Well, if we yield the Dragon
Balls to him this time,
we could always use them next time.
That would be okay, as long as he doesn't
kill Shen Long, like Piccolo did before.
Kuririn-san, someone is coming!
I- is it a Saiyan?
N- no, it's not Vegeta.
This Ki is weaker.
This should be the area
where the readings disappeared.
Must be Namekians.
Who is it?
Probably Namekians.
T- they're not Namekians!
Hmm? W- what is that?
Those aren't Namekians!
Who are they!?
That doesn't matter. We were ordered
to just kill anyone who was on this planet.
Look at what they're wearing!
Those are just like what the Saiyans
were wearing. Yet... they're not Saiyans.
I haven't a clue what it means,
but I've got a bad feeling about this.
R- right... Any way you look at them,
those are not friendly faces...
Gohan, build up your Ki while
keeping your presence masked.
Right.
Do you see that? These guys are common
trash, with barely any battle power!
They're just tourists.
We won't get to have
any fun if they run away.
Take care of their spaceship first.
All right.
Oh, crap!
Our spaceship!
These guys are so unlucky to have
come here at a time like this.
Gohan, release your Ki.
These guys aren't all that tough!
Hey, did you hear that?
Not all that tough?
Does he mean us?
W- what kind of battle
power ratings are these!?
Let's do it!
Right!
Hey, nice, nice!
That was not nice!
What are we going to do about that?
Is something the matter, Zarbon-san?
Yes, Freeza-sama. It is about
the search that was ordered earlier.
It would seem that they
are no ordinary people.
Their battle powers rose momentarily,
then once they had defeated our pair
of scouts, their readings disappeared again.
Ho, that is curious. It does not
appear to be Vegeta, either.
Correct, the readings
are different from Vegeta.
Their battle powers
were both around 1500.
1500, you say? We could leave them alone,
and nothing would come of it,
but their attitude does not
seem to be very good, does it?
The next time they are found,
eliminate them.
All right, just a little more...
Goku-sa...
Chichi...
What are you doin'?
Oh, you know, I was bored, so...
Really... How about you realize somewhat
that you were seriously injured?
If you don't lie there quietly,
you're goin' to open your wounds up again.
Ow! Yow-ow-ow-ow!
Don't be so rough!
Yow-ow-ow-ow!
That hurts! That hurts!
Never mind that, I wonder
if Gohan-chan is okay.
I hope he's washin' his hair,
and usin' that rinse.
His hair is so shiny and all,
so he has to look after his cuticles.
Is he usin' his hair dryer?
His hair dries out so fast,
and he has to take care of it right...
Gohan...
It's hopeless! It's all over!
We'll never get back to Earth now!
Uh, Bulma-san, for the time being,
let's get away from here.
It's dangerous here. Someone
even stronger might come along.
That's right. Those many Ki
that we sensed weren't Namekians,
but appear to be friends of Vegeta,
so we need to go hide somewhere.
Things will work out somehow.
I'm sure the Namekians
will repair the spaceship for us.
How nice that you can be so optimistic!
Bulma-san...
Hmph, you're finally here, are you?
You imbecile.
It looks like the time has come
when we can finally settle things
between us as fellow rivals, huh?
But it looks like
you've let yourself go.
You've got no chance of beating me
with that battle power.
Fellow rivals, you say?
Well, let me show you
a little something.
When I was on Earth, I learned
something interesting from them.
What, how to run away quickly?
How to control my battle power!
H- how to control your battle power?
Take a good look at my battle
power rating on your Scouter!
I- impossible! You and I have
always been evenly matched!
You idiot! I have been fighting
in actual combat constantly.
The battle on Earth was such
that it nearly killed me.
Did you think I would remain
equal with you forever,
as you just sat around
in comfort at Freeza's place!?
19,000... 20,000... 21,000... 22,000!
What happened, Zarbon?
I- I think it was a malfunction,
but the rating on my Scouter, which was set
on Vegeta, had just risen above 22,000...
22,000, you say?
That really was a malfunction.
Your Scouter is an older model, after all.
I'll find out his true
rating for you on mine.
What's his rating?
T- this is absurd... Could my newer
model be malfunctioning, too?
He's gone up to 24,000...
If he's at 24,000... Are you saying that
his battle power is even higher than ours?
I- it couldn't be. His battle power
would just barely reach 18,000.
It is nothing to be surprised about.
Vegeta has been fighting
on the front lines, you see.
He probably came upon
some sort of new skill on Earth.
But...
It is only 24,000. If the
two of you fight together,
it is a rating that you can
sufficiently beat, is it not?
Vegeta probably wants to obtain
eternal life with the Dragon Balls,
the same wish that I have.
Unless he does so, there is no way
that he can prevail against me, you see.
Vegeta never has been
respectful toward me.
He went to Earth without my orders,
and he even appears to be
after my position for his own.
Though I must say,
this is brash of him.
To think that he would come out
in open treason against me...
W- wait, Vegeta! I just had a great idea!
Let me work with you. I can lend you a hand.
I- I didn't like Freeza-sa-
I mean, Freeza before this, either.
T- that doesn't sound bad, does it?
If you team up with me at that battle power,
I think we could somehow
manage Zarbon and Dodoria.
Spout more of your worthless lies, will you?
You are one thoroughly disgusting bastard!
It's no lie, I tell you!
Believe me, Vegeta!
Oh! Freeza-sama!
What!?
Miserable fool!
No matter how much
his battle power had risen,
nobody could stand up
to being taken unawares by that.
You wish.
What an utterly pathetic strategy,
coming from someone like you. I'm astounded.
W- when did you manage to-?
Having an elevated battle power means
that my speed has been elevated as well.
In other words, you have now
gotten me thoroughly angry.
Die!
That was one foul firework.
V- Vegeta's 24,000 rating
is the real thing, all right.
He did in Kewie
with no trouble at all.
It is of little import. Now,
we search for the fifth Dragon Ball.
Thanks to their Scouters,
they'll know exactly what my actions are.
Even if I were careless enough
to get too close to them,
l might be able to take
Zarbon or Dodoria,
but there's still no way
l can beat Freeza.
Judging by the transmissions I heard
over the Scouter between Freeza and his men,
these Dragon Ball things don't work
unless you have all seven of them together.
All right, I'll search out
just one of them.
Once they have gathered
the remaining six,
I'll look for an opening
and take theirs from them.
lf things go right, and I get
them all, l'll gain eternal life.
Once I do, defeating Freeza
will no longer be just a dream!
There is a reading of around
ten Namekians in that direction.
Very well.
It would be nice if they had
the fifth Dragon Ball.
Please make sure not
to let your guard down.
It would seem there are some mysterious
others out there, in addition to Vegeta.
Yes, sir.
Now, let us be going.
With him gone,
l'll be number one.
The whole universe will be ruled
by Vegeta-sama the Saiyan!
Bulma-san, we have to
hurry a little bit more,
or they're going to
find us out here!
You guys can fly, right?
Take me with you, and fly.
I wish we could do that, but we're
walking to mask our presence.
Flying through the air requires a lot of Ki,
and the enemy will know where we are.
Bulma-san, there's a good place.
It will be hard to find us in that hole.
H- how long am I going to have
to live in a place like that?
Kuririn-san...
Do you sense any Ki over there?
You're right. It feels different
from the Ki we felt earlier, huh?
It could be the Namekians this time.
Hide! There's another Ki coming
this way from that direction!
What is this Ki that is coming toward
them at top speed? ls it Vegeta?
Or is it Freeza and company?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org