Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Big Brother...
Mm-hmm, this one's dead.
Really?
You can tell if he's dead
or not by doing that?
Of course you can! You're five already,
and you don't even know that?
I did so know!
It doesn't look like he's carrying
anything worth any money.
Big Brother, over there!
All right, we will reap something!
Awesome!
That's mine...
Did he die again?
He doesn't look injured, huh?
You're right.
He's coming around.
--Um...
--I'm Rom.
Nice to meet you.
I'm his sister, Chiko.
Who are you?
I'm Son Gohan.
How old are you?
Four.
Hooray! You're younger than me!
Where are we?
This is our cottage.
Not bad, huh?
Where did you come from?
I don't know. I think it
was a desert somewhere.
Well, no matter. In any case,
as of today, you're one of us.
It might be rough, but don't cry,
the way Chiko does.
" Mom! Where have you gone!?"
I don't cry anymore!
Um, I...
Listen, from now on,
you have to call me Big Sister.
There's no need to be shy.
Without any parents,
we all have to help each other.
What's the matter? If you want
to tell us something, speak up.
I'm sorry. It's been a long time
since I talked to anyone.
I can't speak that well.
About two years ago,
there was this gigantic tsunami.
It swallowed up the whole city!
It was scary!
This place is packed with
kids like us that don't have homes.
Um, but I...
Uh-oh, they're making
their regular stop.
Regular stop?
Uh-huh! Hurry!
Hurry! They'll catch you!
Wait here. Once I take Chiko across,
I'll be right back for you.
Come on...
Take that! You guys can't catch us!
Dammit!
They make sure to come here
once every day.
Who are they?
The guys from the institution.
They're trying to catch us
and toss us in the pokey.
Is that a scary place?
According to the folks
who escaped from there,
they were picked on every day,
and got smacked with slippers.
You can't come out of there for the
rest of your life, that's for sure.
On top of that, they cut
your nails every night!
Let go of me! No! Oww!
Stop it! You're hurting me,
I tell you!
Piegero!
She doesn't want to go. Cut it out!
You again!? Come on, now!
Why, you-!
Stop that!
You children up in the tree,
come on down here!
If you do, you'll get new clothes,
a clean room, and a hot meal!
Really?
Dummy! Don't be fooled!
We don't want any of that!
Get out of here!
So then, do you plan to go on
living in a place like this forever?
You think we're about to
put ourselves in your care!?
We'll go on living
by ourselves just fine!
Yeah! Yeah! Get out of here!
Get out of here!
Yay! And don't come back!
We have a new kid?
Apparently, he got shipwrecked
out at sea, and washed up here.
I'm Son Gohan.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, this boy is still little,
so give him a comparable share of food.
Look who's talking. The same
goes for you, doesn't it?
I guess so.
Well, anyhow, as a fellow person without
any family, let's stick together.
Come on over, come on over!
Delicious stuff!
Welcome by, son.
I'll let you have them cheap.
Yow!
Yow-ow-ow-ow!
What's the matter, son?
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
--All right, now!
--Okay.
It hurts! It hurts!
What's the matter?
It hurts!
Where does it hurt?
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
So, it's you guys! Hold it!
It hurts!
You bastards!
Hold it!
You hold it!
Dammit!
Thieves!
Hey, you!
Hold it!
Take that!
Why, you-! Hey!
See? That was pretty fun, wasn't it?
Uh-huh!
Even without parents,
children still grow up!
Yeah, yeah!
Well said!
We're growing up fine, huh?
What's the matter?
Hmm? Nothing.
What's the matter? Need to pee?
What are you doing?
Standing watch. We've been causing
trouble all over, after all.
Sometimes there are people
that come after us at night here.
What is it, if you didn't
come out here to pee?
I'm not an orphan. I have a mother,
and I was actually on my way home to her.
Oh, so the little boy has a home, huh?
I'm sorry, I just couldn't say anything.
There's nothing you
have to apologize for.
I guess I jumped to the wrong conclusion.
Where is your home?
In a bamboo grove on Mount Paozu.
Mount Paozu? That's pretty far, huh?
--You know it?
--Yeah.
Please tell me the way, if you would!
You got it. I'll show you tomorrow.
Thanks!
Say, is your mom nice?
I wouldn't say that.
Everyday, she tells me to study,
study, and it gets annoying.
Being annoying is okay,
as long as she's around.
Yeah, yeah!
Do you go to school?
I go to a cram school.
Do you like to study?
There's stuff I like,
and stuff I don't like.
Yeah, yeah, that's right, huh? I hate
gym and math, but art is my best subject!
For me, it's science.
--What about you, Ena?
--I've never been to school.
Oh, that's right. The tsunami
happened before Ena started school.
Do you guys... want to go to school?
Not especially. Who needs studying?
If you go to the institution,
you can do all you like.
No way, that place smells like medicine!
Yeah, that goes for me, too. No way.
And someone who's escaped
from there ought to know!
I know! How about we all drive
to Gohan's house tomorrow?
Cool!
That will be fun! Let's go, let's go!
Not yet?
Not yet.
They're late today.
Maybe they've given up.
They're coming, they're coming!
Here they come!
Hey, wait!
Hurry up!
O- oh, no!
Hey, get out!
Ow! Ow!
Chiko!
Come quietly!
Damn!
Gohan, this way!
But everyone else is-!
Just come on!
--Piegero!
--Gohan!
Piegero!
What are you doing!?
Hey, you!
Piegero!
Why!? Huh?
Why!? Why did you do that!?
Why!?
It's for the best!
They're still...
...just little kids...
and already they're delinquents.
They're too young for that!
You're no ordinary kid, huh?
You're incredibly strong.
Are you going back there?
No. There's nobody there, even if I
did go back. See ya. Respect your mom.
Thanks, Piegero-san.
Say, is your mom nice?
l've never been to school.
Respect your mom.
What is your mission!?
Say it!
To defeat the Saiyans, and to save...
...the earth!
We're going back!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org