Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Dammit!
Don't worry, you're just
entangled in them.
Just wait until evening,
and you'll get loose all on your own.
Who are you guys?
Is this not Planet Namek?
It doesn't have any
fancy name like that!
This scummy planet is like
a big trash heap in space.
It doesn't have any cities, or people,
or anything decent to eat or drink.
We were forced down on this planet
when we got caught in some cosmic tides.
Our spaceship was smashed up, and we were
at our wit's end when you folks showed up.
We were going to swipe your spaceship
and get out of here right away,
but unfortunately, there is a gigantic
cosmic tidal current in the way,
and we couldn't move.
So, you're saying that you were
just killing time up to now?
That's right. While you were out,
we probed you to find out about Earth,
the secret of the Dragon Balls,
and even what Namekians looked like.
Then, the lake, and the giant,
and the ice cave were all...
Illusions that we made you see.
W- what kind of despicable joke is this!?
It was pretty thrilling, wasn't it?
Get bent, you bastards!
A- as hectic as things are right now-!
Don't be mad. In exchange
for taking your spaceship,
we just let you have a bit
of a dream, didn't we?
It's better than being killed, right?
Yeah, we aren't the barbaric
type. We're more gentle.
The cosmic tidal currents
move just a little bit each day.
But once in a very rare while,
an opening appears in them.
An opening?
Yeah. And this fog
is our indicator of that.
As long as this fog
is out, we can escape.
What are you doing!?
We're going to search
for the Dragon Balls.
We never thought anything
in the world could be so amazing.
This time, you guys stay here.
You'll wait until someone else
comes down on this planet. Later!
J- just a minute!
Hey!
Bulma-san, what are you doing!?
Hurry and go after them!
Are you saying I should get
our stuff back by myself!?
W- well, the way things are...
Hey, by the way, you do know
how to fly this, don't you?
It's simple. You tell this thing
to fly, and it flies, all on its own.
That's amazing.
Okay, let's take off!
Open the door!
Hey...
What's the matter!?
Open the door!
All right! They don't know
how to open the door, do they?
--How are you coming, Gohan?
--No good!
They're squirming all over,
and I'm getting nowhere!
Kuririn-san!
D- darn it!
All right, now!
Kuririn-san...
All right...
What is this?
If we don't hurry it up,
the fog is going to lift!
Why didn't you make sure
to look into this?
Shut up! We just need to bring
the girl with us, right?
Huh? Ah, h- hold on...
We did it!
Yahoo!
Come on, open it!
We can't afford to dally around! Once the
opening in the cosmic tidal currents closes,
there's no telling
when it will open again!
L- listen, let's all
go together, like friends.
You're saying you want to come with us
back to our planet? It will take 50 years.
Huh? 50 years!?
Hurry it up!
Hurry, or else!
A- all right.
" Piccolo"
All right!
So, there's a password, is there?
Take care, now. There is food
to eat, if you're not too fussy.
Like snakes, and lizards.
They can be pretty good,
depending on how you cook them.
" Piccolo!"
What!?
Whew, you're here at last.
I hate snakes.
D- damn it, if that's
how it's going to be...
Oh, wow, they're
weaker than I thought.
You're right.
I told you, we're not barbarians,
like you guys are.
Oh, no!
The fog is about to lift! We have to hurry,
or the tidal opening will close! Let's go!
Thank you. If it weren't for you,
we wouldn't have known how to
get out of here. See you later.
Bulma-san, where is the
opening in the cosmic tide?
I can see it now. It's where
that gas is blowing through.
It's almost closed!
It's all or nothing.
Here we go!
We got through!
We've slid in safe!
Now, we have to make up for lost time.
Destination: Planet Namek.
Full speed.
How strong those guys were!
They were too much for us.
I wonder when the next one
will come down here.
At that moment,
Vegeta was hastening along his route toward
Planet Namek from a different direction.
l won't let Freeza
have it his way any longer.
l will make sure I get the
Dragon Balls, just you watch!
Say, Goku-sa...
W- what?
It's been a month already, huh?
Y- yeah...
I forgot to give him
some nail clippers.
I'd send him some if there
were a delivery service.
Y- yeah, I guess so.
That's too bad, huh?
Y- you were standing guard, huh?
34 days after blasting off from Earth,
Bulma and the others had finally arrived
at their destination of Planet Namek.
We made it!
There it is! There it is!
Wow, it sure is pretty.
It's the real one this time, right?
No question about it. The computer says
that this is the genuine Planet Namek.
We got here four days
later than we planned.
It's just like those kids said.
It's a good thing
we took that shortcut.
Everything turned out
all right, didn't it?
I guess so. Now, we're going to land,
so sit down and fasten your seatbelts.
There's going to be quite a jolt.
Commence landing
in a suitable location.
We did it! We've landed
on Planet Namek!
We're here!
Hang on, now. I'll examine
the composition of the atmosphere.
I made sure to install some sensors.
Wasn't that prudent of me?
We'll be lucky enough if there's
some level of oxygen here,
but I also prepared
some atmospheric masks,
though that will limit
our time out there to roughly...
This looks sort of like the place
where I trained with Piccolo-san.
Yeah, where we first
fought the Saiyans, right?
I suppose a place that was similar to his
home would instinctively be more settling.
Piccolo-san...
You guys don't ever learn
from your previous lessons, do you!?
How can you just waltz
on out here like this!?
You sure are as scary as ever.
For crying out loud. Well, it's okay,
as long as there are Dragon Balls here.
Please...
Look! I'm reading them!
Hooray! Now we can finally-
What are you doing?
Oh, I was wondering if we weren't being
tricked again, so just to make sure...
It's for real, I tell you!
Yow! All right!
Hooray!
--Hooray, hooray!
--Hooray, hooray, hooray!
Kuririn-san, there's a strong
Ki coming from over there.
A Ki?
You're right.
I'm sensing a lot of them.
Yeah, and they're all
incredible Ki, too.
W- what does it mean?
Oh, come on, what are you talking
about? Those are the Namekians.
With Kami-sama and Piccolo
being as strong as they were,
it's not at all strange that
the Namekians from their home
would have incredible Ki, too.
But still...
Those Ki do feel
a little bit evil, huh?
It's okay, I tell you. Kaio-sama said that
Namekians were gentle by nature, didn't he?
There are four Dragon Balls
gathered together in that direction.
Come on, let's go meet the Namekians.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, you're right.
They must be Namekians.
I shouldn't have
gotten so jittery, huh?
H- haven't we seen
that someplace before?
It's a Saiyan spaceship!
I knew it!
It can't be!
Again? Are you serious? How?
Gohan, mask your presence!
We'll be detected!
R- right.
I- it's Vegeta.
He's the only one it could be.
Dammit!
Has he already healed?
Come to think about it,
he knows about the Dragon Balls, too.
What do we do? It's hopeless. The only thing
we can do now is return to Earth, right?
Isn't that so?
Let's hurry back.
If that guy gets
the Dragon Balls, it's over.
Bulma-san, please contact Earth and tell
them about this, then go on back by yourself.
Me and Gohan will stay here
and try to collect the Dragon Balls.
But...
It's okay. We'll have
the Dragon Radar.
Isn't that right, Gohan?
Right.
All right.
Once I get back to Earth, I'll bring
Son-kun on board and come back for you.
The round trip will take a little
over two months, though. Wait for us!
It's okay! Two months
will pass like that!
I mean, it's only 60 days! 1440 hours!
86,400 minutes! 5,184,000 seconds!
Right!?
R- right. A little more
than two months, right?
Freeza, you bastard! I won't
let you snatch them away from me!
I should be able to handle
everyone besides Freeza,
but I don't stand a chance of winning
if I fight him head-to-head.
Whatever happens, I have to get the Balls
away from him and gain eternal life.
Tch! To think I'd be stuck
using a Scouter again...
This way, huh?
He's brought Zarbon and
Dodoria with him too, has he?
W- what was that?
S- so now what?
Mm-hmm... Mm-hmm...
Right. So tell that
to Son-kun and the others.
Do you read me? Just don't
tell Chichi-san. Got that?
Right... right... mm-hmm...
I already told you...
are you listening to me?
No, tell everyone
but Chichi! Sheesh!
Right! Got it!?
We're counting on you! Goodbye!
Good grief...
What's the matter, you two?
Huh? What?
W- why is there
another one coming?
T- that's what l'd like to know.
Here it is, Freeza-sama.
Oh, very good, very good.
Now there are three more, yes?
At last, the evil hidden hand,
Freeza, appears.
Will Gohan and Kuririn indeed
be able to collect the Dragon Balls?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org