Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Father...
Father... Father...
Stop picking on my father!
R- run! Gohan, run away!
Father...
All right, I've decided. I think
I'll go back to where Mother is.
Ain't I gotten to...
Kaio-sama's place yet?
I wonder if Goku has arrived
at Kaio-sama's place
and is getting his training yet.
Uranai Baba-sama told us that even
once we gather the Dragon Balls,
not to bring him
back to life for a year.
Mmm... And one year is right about
the time when those Saiyan guys
are supposed to arrive here on earth.
I wonder if he'll be able to
defend earth against the Saiyans.
Bulma-san, aren't we there yet?
There's no doubt that he's
along this direction somewhere...
We have to find Tenshinhan-san
and them quickly,
and climb up Karin-to Tower.
Yamucha-san might already
have arrived there.
Earth's fate is in the balance.
Hey! It's time to eat!
Come quick, Tenshinhan! I've got
some top-notch cooking ready for you!
Ten-san, it's incredible!
How is it that there's so much?
I hired these guys to
make it all, of course!
I had nothing but first-rate ingredients
brought together! Right?
Must have cost some money.
Don't worry. I just finished a pretty
good job. By the way, Tenshinhan,
how long are you planning
on doing all this?
Until Ten-san beats Son Goku.
Cut it out, cut it out.
Things are peaceful now.
There's no use in getting any stronger.
And for that matter, you're strong
enough as it is in the first place.
I am not so strong.
When I met Son, I learned that
the world was a large place.
And it's not just Son, there's sure to be
other strong guys out there in the world.
That is why I train.
How about, instead,
you team up with me
and we hold up banks or something?
We could make a real bundle!
If we did, then you could eat as
much of this delicious stuff as you want!
After all, from now on,
money is everything!
Money talks in this world! As long
as we have money, we'll be happy!
Aren't you eating?
Ten-san, let's eat up!
That's more like it!
There's no need for you to hold back!
Go on, baldy, chow down!
R- right.
Y'know, Tenshinhan,
holding up banks is fun!
Just by shooting off your gun,
everybody gets the jitters!
Yeah, let's do it!
If you teamed up with me,
there's nothing we'd have to fear!
We'd be invincible!
Chaozu, training!
He's really got himself a hard head.
Ten-san can even
break rocks with his head!
That's not what I meant...
you stupid bastard!
I- I didn't mean it!
Son, just what sort of
training are you doing?
--Oni?
--Hey there! What are you doing, Pops?
What am I doing, oni?
I was asked by Great King Yama-sama
to clean this road oni.
I'm going to Kaio-sama's place!
Oni!? You're going
to Kaio-sama's place?
I've never seen a daredevil
dead person as big as you oni!
Is there still a long way to go?
Of course there is!
From what I've heard,
you're still only about halfway
to the halfway point oni.
Still only halfway to halfway!?
It is pretty long then, huh?
Oni?
Hey, what's the matter oni?
I need a little break!
Oni.
If you want me to take you part
of the way, I can give you a ride oni!
Get on back of here oni!
Really? Yahoo!
Ready, Pops!
All right, here we go oni!
Chaozu!
Ten-san, you did it!
No. I still have much more
to do than just this.
O- oh, no!
How could I have done that?
l messed up the control over my power.
At this rate, it will
reach where that kid is!
Hang in there, hang in there!
T- this is a big one!
And I can't stand earthquakes!
Tenshinhan!
Ten-san!
I've located Tenshinhan!
Where the hell have you gone!?
I made it!
I'm cold!
Huh?
Oh, my! Have I done it again?
Apparently, he's within those mountains.
That's just the kind of place you'd
expect Tenshinhan-san to be training!
I'm really sorry
I've been a bother to you.
I'll go back to the
Kame House for now.
That will be great. Please give
Muten Roshi-sama my regards,
and tell him that we are continuing
to train as he would expect of us.
Yes, you certainly are.
Okay then, take care of yourselves.
--Be careful.
--Farewell!
Chaozu, now we can devote
ourselves to training.
She's an odd person.
Such pretty flowers!
They smell nice!
Stupid bastards! I've been
looking for you, you know!
You're trying to get rid of me,
but I won't have it!
Now cut out that stuff already,
and get over here!
Keep out of this!
B- bullets!?
I- impossible! To think
that Son could have died!
But Goku is training
in the Other World.
And we need to be sure that we can
keep up when the two Saiyans get here.
Kami-sama is going to be
training you, after all!
Ten-san!
It's something better than I could
have hoped for! We'll go immediately!
Ten-san, we can train!
What's more...
What is it, baldy!?
Hey, Tenshinhan...
If you're trying to run away from me,
I'm not about to let you.
I don't care if you're going to
Kami-sama's place or anywhere else,
I'm going to come with you.
l'm going to have Kami-sama
train me through-and-through!
Son, let's make sure
we meet again!
Kaio-sama, I'm Son Goku...
Oni!
Yow! Kaio-sama, you're training
is as tough as I expected...
Ee-yow!!
W- where is this place?
I wonder if I've arrived at Kaio-sama's
place without even realizing it.
That smells good!
That fruit looks delicious!
Just where exactly
has Goku fallen into?
And as Umigame was anxious about,
and the Turtle Hermit was
unable to offer a reply to,
will Goku and the others be able
to defend earth against the Saiyans?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org