Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Yeah, that's right, short stuff,
do as much as you can.
I, ReaCoom-san, will let you
match up against me, okay?
Darn it!
Ultimately, we're not
going to get a turn, huh?
That's okay.
Taking out those two runts wouldn't
give us anything to boast about anyhow.
G- Gohan...
That's pretty good.
How about this, though?
All righty...
Masenko!!
Did you see that?
Yeah, for just a second,
his battle power was over 20,000.
Gohan...
Wow, you're good, you're good.
You made my handsies smart.
Now then...
Take this!
G- Gohan!
Oh, my. Is something the matter,
Goku-chan's wife?
Gohan-chan is in a terrible fix.
Gohan-chan...
My Gohan-chan...
Cheer up, Missus. Gohan-chan
will be fine. My Bulma said so.
Is it ready!?
Oh, is that you, Chichi-san? Have a look
at how wonderfully this is turning out.
You wouldn't think that I put it
together in just two days, would you?
I'll tell you, this second one
was a lot easier than the last one.
I even nailed down the right
location for the speakers.
All I need to do now
is a test flight.
Just you wait, Gohan!
Ma is comin' to save you right now!
Hey, Chichi-san, won't you let me
explain how to use it before you go!?
Just which one of these
is the startin' switch!?
Hey, just a minute, I say!
G- Gohan!
There, didn't I tell you so?
Gohan-chan!
Still alive?
Good, good!
Magnificent, Ginyu-san.
I would not have expected you to bring me
all seven Dragon Balls so quickly.
It was worth it to call in
the Ginyu Special Corps, all right.
It gives me, Ginyu, no greater joy
than to have you say so, Freeza-sama.
This means that I am about
to acquire eternal life.
What wonderful joy.
If you would like, shall I
dance the dance of joy?
P- perhaps you could
do that next time.
Really?
Who would have thought the immortal
youth I dreamed about would come true?
Even I, of all people,
am starting to get excited.
The birth of the perfect and everlasting
ruler of the universe is about
to happen, isn't that right?
Now, Dragon Balls, give me,
Freeza-sama, eternal life and youth!
W- what was that?
l've got an odd feeling of uneasiness.
No doubt about it,
the hands of evil will be extended toward
Grand Elder-sama in the very near future!
Forgive me, Earthlings. I have
a duty to protect Grand Elder-sama!
Darn it...
Father!
You got up, did you?
You got up, you got up!
I won't be beaten.
Not by you.
I won't... be beaten...
What have we here? Did you
mean for that to be an attack?
N- nothing is happening, huh?
Have you become immortally young yet?
N- no, I do not believe so.
W- why?
G- go on, take it.
Even if you do get
the Dragon Balls together,
you guys won't be able to get
your wish granted anyhow.
As I recall, when I took the second
Dragon Ball, that is what the Namekian said.
I thought he was just
being a poor loser.
" You guys." That is exactly
what he said. " You guys."
There has to be some sort
of passcode for these!
A secret passcode to grant wishes,
that only the Namekians know!
A password! A place! Or perhaps
a way of arranging the Balls!
We will have to ask
a Namekian for it.
A Namekian? Are there any of them
still surviving anywhere?
T- this reading is from
Vegeta and company.
It's possible that Vegeta
or the others know what it is.
I- in that case, I must stop
my men from killing Vegeta!
Have a look at Point 8829401.
There are two readings which
I believe could be Namekians.
There is also a reading
that is approaching that point.
We have not once attacked this area,
so they must be survivors, yes?
Well then, I will go there at once and force
them to tell me how to get a wish granted.
That will not be necessary.
I will go ask them directly.
After all, I am more accustomed
to dealing with these people.
Ginyu-san, please stay here
and keep watch over the Dragon Balls.
Yes, sir, understood.
Please leave everything to me.
Now, to go flying...
I won't be beaten...
G- Gohan...
I have to... defeat you guys...
for Piccolo-san... Yamucha-san...
Tenshinhan-san... Chaozu-san...
Or I can't bring anyone back to life!
All right, here I come!
ReaCoom Bomber!!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go! Go!
Whoops, I'm over here!
Have you finally
reached your limit?
D- don't get up anymore, Gohan...
Darn it...
I- I am... Father's...
...S- Son Goku's... son...
You wont... you won't...
Oho, you still have enough energy left
to be spouting that sort of nonsense, huh?
I don't know what planet you're from,
kid, but this is surprising.
Your opponent is too much for you, huh?
I won't be beaten!!
Whoa!
He's just about ready to croak.
He doesn't have any battle power left.
Of course not.
His neck has been broken.
Gohan!
P- pathetic little brat... And here
I thought he'd gotten a little better...
Gohan-chan...
Yo, are you awake?
Are you all right, Missus?
Gohan-chan is... Gohan-chan is-!
Oh, my...
Sheesh...
These guys were all
just worthless scum.
I don't understand why Freeza-sama expressly
called in the Ginyu Special Corps for this.
Well, nonetheless, I guess I should
finish off all three of them.
What's that?
It's a ship. It's landing.
At last, Goku had touched down.
Goku, rescue the desperate Gohan and friends
from the devilish hands of ReaCoom!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org