Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
It's been six months
since we parted company.
It looks like you've
gotten a little better.
Now then, how about I start
training you properly?
Come at me!
One more time!
Over here!
Do not lose sight of your opponent!
I can't see anything that fast.
You don't see it. You feel it.
That's easy for you to say...
If you've got enough time to whine,
think about what you should do instead.
Then move.
We've only got six more months!
When you're not eating or sleeping,
you will fight me!
Set your mind straight!
You can't mean it. I'll die.
Then get stronger!
Even stronger than me! And...
...stronger than the Saiyans
who will be coming in six months!
Now, come on!
The end still ain't in sight?
Pretty fired up.
Kami-sama,
Just how long will it be
until you train us?
Yeah...
We've already been here for two months,
and yet you haven't taught us anything.
We want to get stronger, like Goku.
Please give us the same
special training that you gave Goku!
Goku's special training, huh?
I...
...taught Goku...
...absolutely nothing!
What does he mean!?
If that's the case, there's no reason
for us to've come all the way here at all.
It's 'zactly the same as
training down on the surface.
Tell us, just what kind
of training did Goku do here?
Okay?
We just want to get stronger.
Getting stronger... is knowing enemy,
and knowing self.
Do that, and what you
should do come naturally.
Knowing the enemy,
and knowing oneself?
Enough of your smart-aleck talk! I know
better than anyone what my strength is!
I don't need to be told!
Sure about that? You not know self.
You not know weaknesses.
What? Are you calling me weak?
You want to try me!?
Everyone, come.
W- what kind of room is this?
Past. Present. Future.
All intersect here.
You go on time journey now.
Goku trained here too.
What? Goku did?
Intriguing. Let's go, then.
Let's go!
I ain't going.
I'll wait for ya's here.
Those want to go, enter circle.
Close eyes slowly.
Where are we?
A tail?
It's a Saiyan.
What?
What happened here?
These happened during
some kind of battle.
The people on this planet appear
to like fighting something fierce.
I'm raring to take them on.
I'm ready to have a go at them.
I'd like to try out my strength.
Come on, let's go.
All four of them together
have a battle power of 1507.
None of them appear to be
all that strong, huh?
It'll kill some time.
What do you say we rough them up?
There's not a single
person around, is there?
Maybe they're scared of us.
If this really is the Saiyan's planet,
we definitely should not
take them lightly.
Chaozu, let's go.
Right...
Ten-san!
Chaozu!
Ten-san, help!
--Chaozu!
Why, you-!
Okay, who's going to face us next?
I will!
Tenshinhan, be careful!
Okay, now it's your turn.
Hold on, Tenshinhan!
Sokidan!!
Get out of there, Tenshinhan!
I got them!
That didn't hurt one bit.
This time, all three of us
will go at them!
It looks like we took care of them.
Those guys were incredible.
Chaozu, I have avenged you.
He vanished!
--Kuririn!
These guys are invulnerable!
Where did they disappear to!?
Kuririn!
--Kuririn!
Let's go save him!
Dammit!
At this point, I'll let them have it,
even if it costs my own life!
That's it. That's more like it.
Otherwise, it's no fun.
We've laid two of you to rest.
Who's going to be third?
What!?
Before you do that,
let me show you to your graves!
This is our last chance!
An extra-large Sokidan!
Those guys were awful! It's almost
like they were undying monsters!
We beat them...
I- I'm alive...
Where are we?
We're alive! We're saved!
'Course ya are! You've just been
standing there the whole while.
Your minds went on journey.
Kami-sama let you have
valuable experience in minds.
How'd it go with the Saiyans?
What's wrong?
What're ya keeping quiet for?
The Saiyans that you saw were still
only half as strong as full-fledged ones.
They don't even compare to the strength
that Saiyans who are now
heading for Earth possess.
You mean, they're even stronger?
How about it? Do you feel
like running away now?
All right!
I'm keeping at it!
Ten-san!
I'm going at it, too!
I'm going to train here for the next
six months to defeat the Saiyans!
Me too!
What's that!?
Is that your defense!?
Concentrate harder!
I'm just itching to kill you!
The Saiyans' power is terrifying.
The fated time is drawing ever nearer.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org