Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"Piccolo's Self-Confidence! 'I Will Be the
One to Defeat Freeza' "
I'll do this by myself. You guys stay out of it.
It's senseless! Not even Piccolo has
a chance of winning against that guy!
Piccolo-san...
Piccolo's Ki has increased considerably since
he left his training here. What's going on?
In that case, Kaio-sama, are you saying Piccolo
has the potential to win against Freeza?
No...
They have touched that which should have remained
untouched. Freeza's power is unmatched.
If Piccolo is beaten, Kami-sama will also die.
If that happens, our chance at resurrection
will probably be forever lost.
Piccolo, you have to stick it out until
Goku has recovered!
That is the issue, isn't it?
Leave this to me, he says. He doesn't
understand how terrifying Freeza is!
He'll realize it soon enough.
Piccolo-san isn't the kind of person who
doesn't know his opponent's strength.
But Gohan, Piccolo hasn't...
I'm sure of it! Piccolo-san has a
chance of winning!
A chance of winning?
There's no way he can win! Even though he may have
shown up, our situation hasn't changed a bit.
But Piccolo-san is...
This Ki is Piccolo's. Piccolo has been
resurrected! But this time his Ki is different,
more incredible than ever!
H- He looks just like Nail-san, but is this
Piccolo fellow also a Fighter-type Namekian?
You appear to be quite sure of yourself.
But soon enough,
that surety will shatter and give way and
turn to your begging for your life from me.
Enough from you.
Take this!
He did it!
Way to go, Piccolo!
Struggle though he might, there's no
way he can win.
I hate to admit it, but all I can do is escape
and wait for another chance.
I'm not stupid enough to just wait around
to be killed by Freeza.
Well, come on out! You've got greater
power than that, haven't you?
Piccolo-san!
You're not that bad. I mean, you were able to
dodge that from close range by a hair's breadth.
Vegeta!
Where are you going? Don't tell me you
need to go pee, now.
Dammit!
Vegeta...
It won't do to have the prince of the warrior
race Saiyans sneaking away with his tail
tucked between his legs.
However...
No matter what you may try, your destiny
is to be killed by me.
You just sit still and wait for it.
Once I kill the Namekian,
your turn comes next.
Sorry for the delay. Now, show me the
power of that onfidence you hold.
You are a fool not to feel my terror!
Gohan! Piccolo has greater power than
we can imagine! We may be able to hope
for something here.
Right! Piccolo-san will do it!
He's your sensei, after all, right?
Right!
N- Nail-san!
Could it be?
Piccolo-san...
Piccolo-san!
Do not be upset.
It will take more than that to kill him.
But I will show you how I'll take him apart!
You fought well, for a Namekian. I'll give
you credit for that. But it's over.
The fun stops now.
Damn.
Piccolo-san!
We are now completely out of Namekians.
What!?
Piccolo-san!
Don't take me so lightly.
G- Gohan! We might be able to win!
You could be right.
With Piccolo and the three of us, this
could turn out all right after all!
Okay then, it's decided!
Stay out of this!
I thought I told you I'd do this by myself.
But...
We can contribute at least something.
Leave this to me.
That fool! This is our one chance
to defeat Freeza!
He's no match for Freeza's
power just by himself!
You filthy maggot!
Haven't you realized it yet? We can see
through your every move!
What!? What do you mean "we"?
What does this mean?
Piccolo!
Piccolo...
Piccolo's Ki has surged yet again.
What's happening!?
You've become a giant, and you're using
both hands, yet this is the best you've got?
That voice...
I know! What if I were to fight using only
my left hand for you?
Something like that cannot possibly work
against me, can it?
Surely you see there is no way you can win.
I have merged with Piccolo.
What!?
l- I knew it!
By doing so, my power has increased
several times over.
Unite with me.
I am the... last Warrior-Type Namekian
left on my world.
What? Unite with you?
That's right. If you do, your current power
will be increased several times over.
What incredible power! What an unbelievably
fearsome power this is!
Is this what uniting with someone is like!?
Awesome!
Impossible! I don't believe it!
I have obtained the ultimate power!
Piccolo-san!
Piccolo!
Impossible!
What!?
He did it!
Why, you... !
Nail has merged with Piccolo, but can
Piccolo defeat Freeza?
And what about Goku?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org