Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I shot down Dodoria!
I easily beat Dodoria, who took
such pride in his own power!
Even l'm surprised
by how much I've improved.
It truly seems that my battle
on Earth was not in vain.
Be that as it may, Dodoria
did say something curious...
I see now. Those runts I was chasing
earlier were Earthlings, weren't they!?
I do indeed sense two large
powers getting farther away.
Of course they couldn't be Earthlings,
but it's still disturbing.
Maybe I should go
look into it, just to see.
Whatever the case, I have to get rid of
even the small fries that stand in my way.
The cave that Bulma-san
is hiding in is right over there.
For this being a planet you've never been to
before, I'm surprised you remember so well.
What's that!? Something is coming!
It's incredibly fast!
Hide! Quickly!
Right!
We'll be found if we stay here, won't we?
Never mind, just hurry up
and suppress your Ki!
All we can do now is leave
our fate up to heaven.
Will it be someone like
that monster from earlier?
Dammit, how did they know where we were?
Both of the power readings have
disappeared. What's going on?
Over in that area,
all of a sudden...
K- Kuririn-san! O- over there!
V- Vegeta! T- then he is
on this planet, after all!
How can he be here!? This is the
absolute worst thing that could happen!
He's still looking.
He wasn't wearing
one of those Scouter devices.
And yet, how is it that
he can tell where we are?
D- don't tell me he has
the ability to sense Ki!
If that's the case,
then this is bad.
We might be able to extinguish our Ki,
but this kid still has a faint one.
Damn. Was I mistaken?
Is it because I'm not yet used to using
this power sensing technique?
Maybe I shouldn't have
destroyed that Scouter.
I'm sensing a small power.
It's no mistake this time.
Let's check it out.
He's coming this way!
lt's hopeless!
He's going to find us!
It's near that rock over there.
At this point, all we can do is fight.
Even though we know we'll get killed.
Let's go!
Right!
Now!
Tch! It was a fish?
Oh, well. Right now, the first order
of business is to get the two-
no, even just one of
the remaining Dragon Balls.
Once I've hidden it,
Freeza and the others will no longer
be able to get all seven together.
Then I'll find the chance
to take the five
that Freeza and company
have away from them.
Their having lost
their Scouters means
that luck has shifted
in Vegeta-sama's favor!
W- we're saved!
I thought it was completely hopeless there.
Lucky for us, huh? We have
that guy in the water to thank.
Anyhow, let's get back
to where Bulma-san is,
while keeping our presence
as masked as we can.
You said it was right close by, right?
Yes.
We didn't even fight, and I'm already
exhausted. I'd like to get some rest.
I, uh...
To be honest, I'm starting to think
we shouldn't have come to this planet.
It might not be fair to the late
Yamucha-san and the others,
but far from bringing
everyone back to life,
it looks like we're just going
to be adding to the deceased.
You mean, us?
Look! Kuririn-san, over there!
Yeah, right, right.
Bulma-san!
Huh? She's not here.
I'm sure she's hiding
deeper inside the cave.
Bulma-san!
It's us! Where are you!? Bulma-san!
A Capsule house!
What were you guys
taking it so easy for!?
While leaving a young girl like me
alone in a place like this!?
Taking it easy, she says...
W- what's with the small-size
Piccolo-looking kid there?
By any chance,
is that a Namekian?
It's okay.
Has something happened?
For now, just let us in, please.
We'll fill you in on the details.
Oh, right!
I just got some delightful
news from my dad!
He said that Son-kun had
blasted off for Planet Namek here!
And that he would arrive
in just six days!
You see, apparently, my dad
rebuilt the Saiyan spaceship
that Son-kun came in as a baby!
What's more, he said that Son-kun was
doing some incredible training inside it
along the way.
F- Father?
Yahoo!!
Yay! Hooray! Hooray!
Incredible training along the way?
All right! All right!
We've found some hope!
Next up, I'll do this for 30 minutes!
Huh? Is it already time
for the next item on the schedule?
That's strange...
What's going on here?
W- what's that?
Goku, can you hear me?
Ah, it's Bulma's daddy!
What on earth is going on?
Part of the exterior of the
spaceship has been damaged.
A meteor or something must have hit it.
lf you keep going like this,
you'll slip off course.
W- what's going to happen!?
You won't be able to go to Planet Namek.
You'll become lost in space.
I can't have that!
Go outside and repair it.
Repair it!?
Mm-hmm, it will be easy.
lnside the repair box, there should be
some material and a powerful adhesive.
Wow, so this is space, huh?
Goku, don't panic. You've
got a lifeline, don't you?
That's right. I just have to
reel myself in, huh?
You know, this speed is amazing.
Yikes, I'd better hurry.
Oh, that gave me a start.
Goku, the soles of your boots are magnets,
so you can stand up and walk around.
Oh, yeah?
Ha-ha, it's true!
This is terrific!
Oh, that must be it.
All right, there it is.
Let's see... This is the glue, huh?
Let's see, the course deviation
caused by that damage is...
Oh, what's this!?
All right, that does it.
It was easier than I thought.
Goku, this is bad! You have to
make a course correction right now!
Goku, your position right now
is at SU-83 by 643-XY.
If you keep going the way you are,
you're going to collide
with the star Alpha HZ at 653-XY.
I can't understand anything as
complicated as that! What should I do!?
Oh, just do as I instruct you to,
and it will be easy.
Hurry and get back inside the spaceship.
All right, you got it.
Huh?
I'm stuck here.
Come on, now!
This is bad.
I can't get loose.
All right, one more time...
Goku, what are you doing?
There's no time!
That's easy for you to say,
but my feet got stuck with
the glue, and I can't get free!
What did you say!?
What do I do!?
Tell me!
G- Goku!
Goku-san!
I don't want to die out here!
All right, all I can do now
is count on this...
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!!
Whew! This is incredible power!
I get it, this is the result
of the 20 G training!
He did it! He did it!
I- it's no use!
Goku-san!
All right, I'm sure of myself now.
This time, full power!
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!!
He did it! He did it! He did it!
That much force from 20 Gs.
If I raise the Gs even more,
I'll become even stronger!
I feel it! Larger-size powers!
They number about twenty.
No question about it,
it's a Namekian village.
They probably have
one of the Dragon Balls.
Freeza and his men don't have Scouters!
No matter what action I may take
now, they won't know about it!
Sure enough. And since
the villagers are still alive,
that proves that Freeza and the
others haven't been here yet!
W- what's this?
It's an alien!
Is the one called Elder here? I've come
to take your Dragon Ball off your hands.
W- what?
I am the Elder. Would you tell me
why you want the Dragon Balls?
Never mind, just hand it over
quickly. You have it, don't you?
Leave us. I cannot allow you
to have it. I can sense evil in you.
Then die.
Bang!
Elder!
Planet Namek was in
the worst of circumstances.
At length, Vegeta had also set out
in search of the Dragon Balls.
ls their only hope to await
the arrival of Goku?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org