Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
We're going to change
the location of our battle.
Suit yourself. It will
all end up the same.
l should have guessed.
He's following
with confidence to spare.
Gohan...
Hey, Gohan!
--Yes?
--Let's hurry back to Kame House.
Let's stop worrying about him already.
We've left the fate of the earth up to him.
It's okay, Gohan! I'm sure
Goku will come through for us!
Come on, let's go. Show your
mom that you're all right.
Right.
All right, there won't be any
people or animals around here.
I see...
You've chosen here to be your
gravesite, have you?
You should be thrilled.
A lower-class warrior
such as yourself
is about to be toyed around with
by a super-elite, after all.
Saiyans have their warrior ratings
examined right after they are born.
When they do, the scum that have
lower ratings, such as yourself,
are sent off to planets that do not
have terribly formidable opponents.
In other words...
You were a left-behind!
And as a result,
I was sent to Earth here?
I should be thankful.
But what's more...
Even a left-behind might be able to overcome
an elite, if he tries desperately enough.
An amusing joke.
Now then, allow me to show you
a barrier that you cannot overcome,
no matter how hard you try!
What's the matter, Kakarrot!?
You can do better than this, can't you!?
When you defeated Nappa, you had
to have been doing better than this!
Let me see it!
I should have expected as much...
He still ain't
the least bit serious,
but his speed and techniques
already surpass my own.
Show me what you've got! Or have you
already used up all of your power?
You got it.
I'll show you!
Kaio-ken!!
If that's the limit of what you've got,
then I'll be greatly disappointed!
What a powerful bastard!
And yet,
even though I'm in this kind of trouble,
I'm starting to get excited.
I don't see a thing.
What's the matter?
This is because
you got violent with it!
What, are you blaming someone else!?
Well it's the truth!
No, no, that's not why, Sis.
It's not because
the crystal ball is broken,
it's because the terribly
fierce power of their Ki
is concealing them from even
the spiritual powers of your crystal ball.
Then, at least they're
still fighting, right?
Probably.
I know! If I use
that thing, I can tell!
How about it?
There are two large
readings to the west.
Just two?
He's smiling. Has he given up,
and adopted a defiant attitude?
Or is he poised because he can raise
his battle power up even higher?
What's the matter!?
Finished already!?
You seem to be at your limit.
In that case, let me show you
something, as your dying gift.
The overwhelming power
of a super-elite Saiyan!
Let's see it!
That smirk of yours is going
to disappear very soon.
What a Ki! It's as if
the whole earth is shaking!
As before, images from the site of battle
have been completely broken off.
A- as of now, there is no way for us
to be able to conceive what is happening,
or indeed if it has all ended.
" What Will Become of the Earth!?"
Now then, changing the schedule a little,
we now join this discussion of " What will
become of the earth, and what is left for us?"
They ultimately don't
know anything, do they?
Hey, if you're going to sleep,
go sleep at home.
Shut up.
Give me another.
Eh? That's your tenth one!
Do you have any money?
Tenshinhan is dead and all...
I don't have any need
for this money anymore.
Hey, are you all right?
B- by the way, do you have
a place to stay? If you like-
I can hear it.
W- what?
Can't you hear that sound!?
W- what are you going on about?
H- hey, look!
W- what is that!?
T- the crows are fleeing
from something!
It's like there's a typhoon!
The trembling of the
atmosphere has stopped.
A- all the clouds
have been blown away, too.
It's over, Kakarrot!
You fool!
Behind you!
Kaio-ken times two!!
All right, nice going.
Way to avoid it.
Damn... What power and speed! I can't
even keep up with him with a 2X Kaio-ken.
I guess I ain't got much choice.
Even if I wreck my body,
it's better than dying.
I'll have to raise the Kaio-ken to 3X.
I intentionally made that one
easy to dodge for you.
It wouldn't be any fun to have you
die on me so easily, after all.
They came close by, so I can't help but
come take a look at 'em, but what's this?
Both Goku and that bastard're so strong,
it's like l'm havin' a bad dream here!
Now then, I wonder how long my body will
hold out once I raise the Kaio-ken to 3X...
What's the matter,
Kakarrot!? Come get me!
Either way, I have to do it.
Ain't no way I can win like this.
Have you lost everything up your sleeve?
Looks like you picked the wrong opponent.
I was the number-one most powerful
man, even among the Saiyans.
No matter how much training you've done,
you're still just a left-behind.
Looks like your time of death
has been extended by only a little bit.
T- this is bad. That Saiyan bastard's
overwhelmin'ly got it over him.
l'd best be gettin' outta here now,
while I can, huh? Yeah, l'd better get goin'.
lt won't do no good
for me to be here anyhow.
May my body withstand this!
Times-three Kaio-ken!!
No! You can't go any higher
than 2X, Son Goku!
Although, there's definitely
no way he can win like this.
I never imagined he'd
have that much strength.
He may not be able
to win this fight.
W- what's going on?
H- has something happened?
I think it's probably Son-kun, but this
battle power reading is rising incredibly...
--Goku!
--Goku-sa!
17,000... 19,000... 21,000...
It can't be!
W- what?
lgnoring Kaio's warnings,
Goku uses a times-three Kaio-ken.
Will Goku's body be able to withstand
a battle power beyond its limits?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org