Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"The Death of Dende... Come Forth! Intense,
Wide-open Power!"
That's Freeza's true self? He's smaller, more
simple-looking, and less formidable...
He's become an excellent example of why
you don't judge another's ability by
outward appearances!
Everything he's looked like up until now
has been cute by comparison!
D- Damn it to hell!
After all the trouble you went through to
revive me with the Dragonballs! I'm sorry...
There's simply no way I can save the rest
of you now. Damn...
Piccolo-san...
Freeza, you've finally shown your true form,
have you?
Even supposing Son Goku recovers,
Freeza now has the power to destroy the
universe as we know it.
This could be the point of no return!
How can this be? Freeza's Ki has risen
once again!
Dammit...
"Bang."
What?
Dende!!
I didn't see it coming! A- All I saw was some
kind of flash!
T- That's not possible!
Now, there will be no more revivals.
Dende...
Someone just died. Who was it? Damn!
I can't tell what's going on any more!
Dende's been... k- Killed...
H- He...
He saw that we were being revived by
that Namekian...
That's why he was first...
Damn you...
H- He vanished!
Y- You fool!
J- Just where...
Over here!
How did he... ?
I made you a promise, didn't I?
To show you a terror even greater
than Hell's.
However, for that Namekian child there to
not be able to experience this...
it seems a shame, doesn't it?
I'll just have to let you guys take his share.
You bastard!
Take this!
You're not getting away!
Did you get him?
H- He's vanished again.
T- That's impossible!
You ignorant fools!
He's behind you!
What!?
As he said...
Get out of the way!
Worthless idiot!
O- Once again...
I couldn't see... him move... or attack...
But he... Vegeta saw it!
Why? Have his abilities gone up that much!?
Thanks!
You saved me.
You've got it all wrong. I didn't do it
to save you.
I thought I'd show you guys something good.
S- Something good?
Don't tell me you... you think you
can beat him?
You might say that.
You can't possibly...
You guys are in our way.
Pull back and watch very closely!
Such confidence, Vegeta. Or perhaps you're
so frightened, something has snapped?
You just keep on smirking like that, while
you still can.
What stands before you...
is that...
which you fear most!
A Super Saiyan!
Super Saiy... an?
What's this "Super Saiyan" business
he's talking about?
As always, your jokes go too far.
In that case, I'll show you the abilities I
possess, now that I have become
a Super Saiyan!
Is this Ki Vegeta's? He's had an
incredible power-up!
A- Awesome!
What's this? Why is he so powered-up?
It's like he's a different person!
What the hell happened to him?
W- When a Saiyan recovers from near-death,
their power goes up several times over!
What!?
Gohan, let's put our money on Vegeta,
and take shelter for now.
Right!
You know, to think that suddenly, someone
could have achieved this much of
a power-up...
You can see it for yourself. This is exactly
why Vegeta purposely came close to dying,
then got himself revived by Dende.
S- So that's what he was doing, huh?
He was right...
And now, Vegeta really is incredible!
With any luck, he might actually take Freeza!
Right, Gohan!?
W- What? What happened?
They're both the same as they were before.
What...
No, they aren't, Gohan. Try sensing
Vegeta's Ki. It's calm now, but
unbelievably huge!
Incredible! I can't believe his Ki is so full!
Yeah. Vegeta really might be able to beat
Freeza at this point.
I'm supposed to think that somehow you've
powered up quite a bit.
You dare say! Just be grateful you don't have
a Scouter with you!
If your Scouter were to read my battle rating
now, you would run away from here in tears!
The reason being, my power has now become
even greater than yours!
Brace yourself, Freeza. This time, for sure,
you are going to meet your end!
What's the matter? Are you too frightened to
say anything? Well, Freeza-san?
Okay, okay. I get you, I get you.
If you mean everything you said, then I've
decided to see for myself the power of this
so-called, legendary Super Saiyan,
the strongest warrior in history.
Don't you mock me!
I see you!
Kakarrot won't even get a turn!
l- Incredible!
He's completely got Freeza on the run!
No!
V- Vegeta's... h- Had it!
P- Piccolo-san...
What's the matter, Freeza!? You can't defeat
me by running away!
What? L- It can't be! Where is he?
There's no way I... a Super Saiyan like me
could have lost sight of him!
What!?
Im... possible...
I raise my speed in earnest for just a
moment, and you can't keep up, can you?
And you call yourself a Super Saiyan?
l- It can't be...
How can he toy with Vegeta, with all his
power and speed?
He really is an unthinkable beast after all!
F- Father!
A little longer... a little bit longer, and I will
have recovered!
Overwhelming speed and power-
and yet, it's still not enough to match
Freeza's ultimate power?
What will be the fate of Vegeta, now that he
has been shown his limits?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org