Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
''Transformed At Last!! Son Goku,
the Legendary Super Saiyan''
It's all completely changed.
Where's Father?
Where's Piccolo-san?
Father and Piccolo were right nearby. You don't think
they got caught in the middle of it, do you?
They couldn't have been!
I don't feel their Ki...
That's just because we've lost
our powers of concentration.
Piccolo was there with him!
They're not about to die!
Kuririn-san, over there...
P- Piccolo-san!
-It's Goku!
-Father! He's alive!
-We did it, we did it!
-Just like I told you, right!?
Damn! With barely any Ki left,
we can't fly very fast!
-Father!
-Piccolo-san!
-Piccolo!
-Father!
-G- Gohan...
Hey, Goku, are you okay?
Piccolo-san!
Gohan, you must have been worried.
It was incredible! That Genki Dama!
Wasn't it huge!?
That it was. It had the hopes of everyone
in the universe packed inside it, after all.
I was afraid the two of you had died...
You expect us to bite the dust so easily?
Now we can head back to Earth with
our heads held high.
I didn't think I was ever
going to be able to...
What's that?
I- I just wanted to give it a
shot once, y'know!
Marriage.
Goku did it!
With the Genki Dama I taught him!
He really did it to that Freeza with a
super-giant Genki Dama!
Freeza-sama beaten by that monkey scum!?
T- that can't be!
-Never!
-I don't believe it!
Goku won!
And we're going to stick it out too!
With Piccolo-san still alive, we
can all go back to Earth.
All right! Let's go!
Charge!
Purple Comet--
--Zed Crush!
W- what was that oni?
Order up!
Oh? We have so many guests today oni!
Jheese! Butta! ReaCoom!
Yeah, we won, we won! We beat
the Ginyu Special Corps!
Dammit! We can't just leave it like this!
It's no use, oni! It's easy to drop down here into Hell,
but crawling out is very difficult oni!
Nothing is impossible for ReaCoom-sama,
of the Ginyu Special Corps!
ReaCoom Jump!
You fought well! You guys have
improved more than I thought!
To think that you could so easily kick around those
training partners I took the trouble to call here...
Training partners?
To tell the truth, in order to give you
some training in actual battle,
I made a request of Yama the Great to
have the Ginyu Special Corps sent here.
Given their powers, it isn't likely they'll
be able to climb out of Hell.
Well done, well done!
Your training partners have parted and run
away! Your training partners have parted!
Good joke!
Shall we go home? The spaceship I came
in can get us back to Earth in five days.
I'll see Mother!
We'll see everyone!
Ouchie...!
I completely forgot! Bulma-san!
Don't scare me like that! I thought that maybe
Freeza had shown up again, you know!
I- in some senses, Bulma-san is
even scarier than Freeza!
Ooh, ow! Don't make me laugh
so much, I ache all over!
You know, Planet Namek has
endured something terrible.
However, this should allow the Grand
Elder-sama, and all the others who
have died, to rest in peace now.
H- how is it you know about the Grand Elder?
What is it, Kuririn?
Freeza!
He took that huge Genki Dama head-on,
and yet he's still alive!
I- it can't be!
Goku!
P- Piccolo-san...
P-...P-...
PICCOLO-SAN!!
Wha...no way!
Kaio-sama, what is it?
Piccolo's been...Piccolo's been done in!
But I thought Freeza was
supposed to be dead!
Freeza is a frightful one!
More so than I had imagined!
Piccolo! Hey, Piccolo!
Free...za...!
Even I questioned whether or not I
was going to die this time.
I, Freeza-sama, nearly died!
Run...Kuririn, Gohan...!
There's a spaceship very near the
location where I first arrived.
Take Bulma and get yourselves away
from this planet, now!
Gohan, snap out of it!
I will fight! I'm going to avenge Piccolo-san!
Get the hell out of here! You guys are in my
way! Do you all want to die together here?
-G- Goku...
-Father...
You think I'm going to excuse you?
I'm not letting a single one of you go home alive!
Kuririn-san!
Kuririn!
Stop it, Freeza!
Goku!!
A- and this time?
Kuririn...
Shall I do the little brat next?
Y- you're going to pay for that..
How dare you...How dare you!?
How dare you...How dare you...!?
W- what!?
Gohan, take Piccolo with you and get yourselves
back to Earth. He's still barely alive.
Go home now, while I still have
some sliver of reason left!
Right!
Goku's fury has gone beyond its bounds.
What can Goku's transformation mean?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org