Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Brr...
H- hurry it up! Are you trying
to freeze me to death!?
You can't ask us to do that.
He's right. If we melt it too fast,
this whole cave could collapse.
I get it! I get it already,
so just hurry it up!
Ah, man! I'm sure this cold
is no good for my skin!
If my beauty is ruined because of this,
it would be a serious loss for the universe,
wouldn't it, Zarkuro-san?
Huh? Where could he have gone?
Bulma-san, just a little more.
We did it! The sixth one!
One more to go!
Hooray! Hooray!
What?
What is this!? I thought you were
going to keep this from happening!
If you're going to complain,
tell us later! Let's just hurry!
Kuririn, do something, quick!
Wah! Oh no!
Left! Left! Go left!
All right!
Ho, ho, not bad.
But they're finished now.
I guess we can relax now.
This is no time to relax!
Vegeta-sama, as powerful as you are,
you sure must have had a hard time of it.
As busted up as this
high-quality rubber protector is,
I'm surprised you came
back to us safely.
It would take quite a lot
for it to end up like this.
What in the world happened
to you on that planet Earth?
Is Freeza-sama around?
N- no, he has departed.
He's already gotten
tired of this planet, huh?
Um... Kewie-sama...
...said that he had something
to speak to you about,
and that you were to come to the training
room when your treatment was finished.
Ha! You tell him that I said " I've got
nothing to discuss with the likes of you."
B- but...
Vegeta-sama... um...
you've forgotten your Scouter.
I don't need that thing.
You can have it.
It's no good... I ain't able
to control my power at all...
Damn...
I've had it.
I ain't even able to perform the Kaio-ken
like this, let alone a Genki Dama.
Hurry up and do something!
Gohan, up there!
Right, understood!
An outlet?
Lucky! There's an outlet!
I see an outlet!
You're right!
That was close.
Okay, one more to go.
Right.
Say, Bulma-san, don't you think
this is a little bit strange?
What?
N- nothing, really.
Never mind.
It's almost time, huh?
Yeah.
It's just ahead.
We're nearly there.
Isn't this where we were before?
What's the matter?
We'll leave you behind.
It looks like the Dragon
Ball is in that lake.
There doesn't seem to be any doubt.
It has to be inside that stone figure.
Judging by all the other
events we've had up to now,
it doesn't look like this
is going to be easy, either.
It would be a relief if Lychee-san
or Zarkuro-san were here, huh?
What are you worrying about?
This one out here is going to be a simple
affair compared to the others, isn't it?
I don't see you
going out to get it.
One more to go.
One more, and then Kami-sama
and Piccolo can both come back to life.
Right.
But Bulma-san...
And once that happens,
the Dragon Balls will be restored,
and we can return to Earth,
and bring Yamucha, Tenshinhan
and everyone back to life, can't we?
Then we can all go back to our regular lives,
and Earth will be at peace, won't it?
Am I right?
Then I can put some makeup on, and go back
to being the usual beauty that I am, can't I?
Don't you boys forget that you're
on a mission to save Earth.
A- all right.
One more to go, huh? One more, and then
Piccolo-san will come back to life!
K- Kuririn-san!
Help me! I can't move!
W- what's wrong, Gohan!?
Geez, this is no time to be
playing around, Gohan-kun!
I can't move! It's like I'm being
held by an incredible power!
Gohan!
There he is. Over there.
W- where?
What was Goku-sa doin'
in a place like this?
D- don't tell me he was
training in his condition...
He's so reckless...
l'll head for Earth
first thing in the morning.
l'm going to smash them
to pieces for sure this time.
No, before that,
l'll go to Planet Namek...
Yo, Vegeta. I heard you had
yourself a rough time of it.
They said that both
Raditz and Nappa died.
To whom do the supposedly invincible
Saiyans owe the pleasure of this grief?
Get lost, Kewie. I don't have time
to entertain your inconsequential chitchat.
Now, just listen.
Freeza-sama is cross with you for the actions
you guys took without his permission.
He can't complain
about it if he's not here.
Now,
remove that filthy hand of yours.
Still, Freeza-sama is a magnanimous
gentleman. I hear he's going to forgive you.
That's because you've
discovered something wonderful.
What?
He was thrilled when he found out he might
be able to gain eternal youth and life.
What did you say!? Then, the place
that Freeza-sama departed for is-?
Planet Namek.
Damn it! He listened in on our
conversation over the Scouters, huh?
l- l have to beat him to it somehow,
or l'll be that bastard's toady forever!
I understand that you wanted those
Dragon Ball things to gain eternal life too,
but you'll have to give that up now.
Once Freeza-sama has his wish granted,
he's planning to exterminate the Namekians.
That bastard!
Hey! Vegeta!
Vegeta-sama!
Give me that!
It turns out I need it after all!
Vegeta!
I won't let you do this!
Those belong to me!
W- what are you doing? If you try anything
perverted, you're going to answer for it!
We're through playing around now.
Playing around?
Yeah.
That's right.
Sure enough, you guys...
...aren't Namekians!
That's right!
You're just now realizing it?
What!?
You don't mean-!
I- it can't be...
Are you sure you shouldn't
be rescuing him?
Those are man-eating nautili.
He'll be eaten if you leave him there.
Gohan!
Bulma-san!
What's this? This world isn't
Planet Namek? Then, just what is it?
And who is this "Freeza"
that even Vegeta is afraid of?
The situation grows more tense.
What fates will everyone meet?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org