Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I am bored to death.
I've had it. This is still
only the seventh day, too.
We've still got twenty-some days to go.
I should have installed hibernation devices.
Are you guys image training again?
Nice for you to be able
to pass the time.
Wow, you're not bad!
You sure are strong.
You've inherited Goku's blood, and you've
been trained by Piccolo, after all.
Still, I was surprised by how many
techniques you have, Kuririn.
Listen...
It's fine for you
to train inside your heads,
but the room is starting to get pretty
messy, so would you tidy it up for us?
There's a lady present.
B- but Bulma-san, you're the one
who made it messy over there.
We've cleaned up our own messes.
I'm busy here! I've got a lot
of things to think about.
You guys are just passengers,
so that's fine for you.
I thought you just got done
saying that you were bored.
You hush! I wish you would show a little more
consideration toward a delicate lady.
So busy, so busy...
As a lady, I sure wish she wouldn't
stroll around in her underwear.
Oh, not again.
Four more.
Son-san, you mustn't do that!
Nurse, I'm all better now.
Goku is immortal, you see.
Did I just do something? Must be my age,
but lately, I don't even know what I'm doing.
Oh, for heaven's sake...
These sponge cakes are delicious.
Of all the...
Doctor!
How many times must I say it
before it gets through to you?
If you keep doing that,
you'll never get to go home.
As you can see, I'm all-
It should hurt. You were very severely
injured, after all. Get back to bed.
S- sorry.
You there, Grandpa Glad-hands,
give him a hand.
" G- Grandpa Glad-hands" ?
My word, " Grandpa Glad-hands," huh?
My, my...
" Grandpa Glad-hands" !
At your service.
Where is his wife,
who is usually with him?
Oh, she probably went to the roof
to look up at the sky again.
Gohan-chan, are you doin' all right?
I told you over and over
to send me a letter every day,
but you haven't sent a single one...
Come back to me soon,
safe and sound.
Say...
By the way, I've been wondering
about this for a long time,
but about that Saiyan, Vegeta,
who ran away- where did he run away to?
What do you mean, where?
Well, the Saiyans' planet
was lost a long time ago, right?
Oh, right. He had taken
an awful lot of damage,
so I think it would have to be
a civilized planet somewhere.
Could there be such a place?
Earlier, Son-kun's brother
mentioned something, remember?
He said that, " We exterminate those
who live on planets with good environments,
and then sell them to aliens."
Do you think that maybe Vegeta went
to one of those aliens' planets to get treated?
If he did, then when he comes back to Earth
would depend on where that planet was.
If it were far away,
then it would buy us some time.
You know something, that's one terrible
fellow who has set his sights on Earth.
T- to think that it would come to this...
--What was that just now?
--Something flashed, huh?
It wouldn't be Planet Namek, right?
It's too early for that,
to say the least, isn't it?
Huh? Something is approaching.
But I don't see anything.
B- Bulma-san!
Flying saucers!
Leave them to me!
Counterattack!
You got them!
It's too soon to celebrate. Look!
It's a spaceship.
It's coming closer and closer!
I can see that. It's coming
straight toward us.
Is that!?
We're going to hit!
Do something!
H- how could they turn
in the same direction!?
W- we're done for!
Where could we be? It looks
like the inside of a spaceship,
but even so, there isn't a soul around.
I have no idea what's going on here.
There may be some weird
aliens hiding from us.
You're right.
They might suddenly-
...pop out, like this.
Gohan! Don't scare us like that!
I- it looks like it's safe to go
outside. Let's go have a look.
Here goes!
Maybe I should have stayed
on Earth after all, like Yajirobe.
Oh, no!
I forgot to put on
some pants first.
Huh? But you are
wearing them, aren't you?
These are my shorts.
Ah, oh well.
Let's hope you don't
embarrass mankind.
Kuririn-san...
All right, let's go.
Gohan! Don't push!
Gohan, watch yourself! It looks like
there are some booby traps in here.
Remember, you two! Men are to protect
ladies at all times! Don't forget that!
There should be a doorway
into the main room somewhere-
A wall like this will be
easy to take care of.
Kame...
hame...
K- Kuririn!
Kame...
...hame-Ha!!
Must be nice for you guys,
being able to perform Bukujutsu.
I get the feeling that they want to
eliminate any intruders, no matter what.
Is this a Saiyan spaceship?
Beats me.
Suppose Vegeta were to suddenly
appear from over there...
C- cut that out! Look,
I'm starting to get goosebumps!
I wonder if that man Vegeta is recovering
from his injuries somewhere right now.
I'd appreciate it
if he'd just die.
K- Kakarrot... remember this... I will
definitely go back there to settle the score!
Say, I get the feeling
that we've been walking around
the same place in circles for a while now.
There wasn't anything
that looked like a door, huh?
There's one!
It looks like the real
door is down here.
Yay!
Damn... They sure built
this thing to be convoluted!
All right, let's try going in here.
Kuririn, be careful.
I know.
Outer space!
I thought we were dead!
I- I'm getting hungry...
My tummy is grumbling, too.
Something smells good.
Y- you're right.
Wow, that looks delicious.
It might be a trap!
It sure is a spread!
Be careful when touching anything.
You won't catch me falling for that!
Bulma-san!
Help me!
Bulma-san, your
reflexes are so slow!
It's you guys who are
the unusual ones!
We're coming
to help you out now!
Please move away from the cage!
What is this!? Who set
this childish trap!?
Don't move!
Bulma-san!
Why, you!
Stay back!
I'll be shot!
Kuririn-san, they're all children!
D- don't shoot! We're not your enemy!
Is there an adult here that I could speak to?
Never mind about me! Give these
kids a good hard spanking!
B- but...
Don't dawdle around! Hurry up!
Okay then...
Kuririn! Don't offer
any more futile resistance!
Just hurry and surrender, already!
B- Bulma-san...
K- Kuririn-san?
W- what should we do?
Ominously, these children
have suddenly appeared.
What exactly is the true nature
of this mysterious spaceship?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org