Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Kakarrot...
Yow-ow-ow-ow!
Okay, let's find the remaining
Dragon Balls quickly, and go back to Earth!
Saying " do it quickly" is one thing,
but as spread-out as this place is...
We'll find them for sure, you'll see.
Thank you very much, Zarkuro-san.
Come to mention it,
where is Lychee-san today?
He said he was staying home
because he had some work to do.
That's strange. One of the Dragon Balls
is moving toward us rapidly.
What is that?
What are you doing!?
The Dragon Ball is inside that thing!
Hurry up and go get the Dragon Ball!
Y- you can't mean that. Let's just
wait until the tornado disperses.
That tornado isn't going to disperse.
On this planet, tornados
roam around the desert forever.
Snap to it. I'm going to be
taking shelter, okay?
What are you doing!?
Hurry up!
A- all right.
Gohan, we're going to release
our Ki toward that thing.
Right.
All right...
Kienzan!!
Masenko!!
Stop that! If you do that,
you're going to destroy the Dragon Ball!
B- but...
What are you doing!?
Clumsy, clumsy, clumsy!
Stay away! Stay away! Stay away!
This is why I said I didn't
want to come to Planet Namek!
Bulma-san!
This is why I said I couldn't
go from the start, you know!
There's no way a delicate young lady
like myself can go looking for Dragon Balls!
You're not serious!
Without that Dragon Ball, Piccolo-san
won't be coming back to life.
There it is!
I did it!
All right...
Masenko!!
Gohan!
Gohan-kun!
I got it out.
You did it!
Yahoo! That makes
four of them! You did it!
Sure enough, this is
the best outfit for me!
This one is that way,
no doubt about it.
It sure is dark.
I can't see a thing.
Shall I make us a torch?
W- what was that just now?
This isn't a forest, it's a bird!
Aah! Help!
Look at that incredible castle!
We've got no choice
but to jump off!
It does look like that's
the only thing we can do.
Y- you're kidding, right!?
If we don't act fast,
we're going to become bird food.
All right! All right, already. But you guys
are responsible for catching me!
We know.
Remember this well, you trash...
There aren't going to be any more miracles...
Be sure to enjoy yourselves until then...
I can't beat that Saiyan like this.
Say, the Dragon Ball is right nearby.
Okay, Bulma-san, you keep
a lookout, if you please.
I- it'll be okay, right?
He's sound asleep, after all.
Kuririn-san, have you found it?
No, not yet. What about
you, Zarkuro-san?
I haven't found it.
Geez, where exactly have you hidden it?
There it is!
Here goes.
Ready, set...
Safe!
Okay, let's get back, quickly.
I've looked everywhere I can think of,
but I have absolutely no idea where he went.
Good grief! My darlin' Gohan-chan
is off strugglin' hard on a distant planet,
and what is his father, Goku-sa, doin'!?
He never does anythin' a parent should!
N- now, now, Chichi, you don't
need to get so worked up...
Goku must have felt terrible that he
couldn't do anything, all here on his own.
No, he's not gettin' away with it!
Makin' others worry about him like this...
If he doesn't get back here soon,
I'm goin' to turn this sweater into hankies!
You won't get away from me!
Bulma-san, are you sure
this toy can fly?
You just hush! If I say it
will fly, then it will fly!
I told you, we should have
run away down the stairs.
Stop all of your complaining
and do something about that guy, now!
I guess we've got no choice.
--All right, Gohan, let's go!
--Right!
Hold it, hold it, hold it!
Oh, man!
Enough, already!
I did it! I really am
a mechanical genius! Amazing!
Kienzan!!
Masenko!!
We got him!
We're saved!
For goodness' sake, you guys
are nothing but trouble for me!
If I weren't around, we wouldn't have
gotten a single Dragon Ball. You're hopeless.
You don't say...
Now there's only two left.
At this rate, we should be able
to go back to Earth soon, huh?
That would be nice...
Huh!?
It's almost time...
All right.
You are now healed.
You may open your eyes.
Unfortunately, we were not able
to regenerate your tail.
No matter. It will
grow back in time.
Vegeta has recovered at last.
The fearsome battle is about to begin again.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org