Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Damn you...
This is for Yamucha!
Why, you-!
I- incredible!
You dirty brat!
I don't even have
to dodge this one!
W- what!?
H- he defused it
with just a kiai shout!?
D- d- dammit!
This is for Tenshinhan!
How!? How does Kakarrot
have this much power!?
What!?
And this is for Piccolo!
Dammit!
Awesome! You really
are awesome, Goku!
Yeah!
Dammit!
I see... Impressive, you really
are extremely tough, huh?
I am an elite warrior
from a distinguished family!
I'm not about to be looked down upon
by a lower-class warrior like you!
You'll pay for this!
I'll kill you!
You miserable fool!
Cool that head of yours!
If you'll compose yourself
and think about it,
you'll find he's not the kind of opponent
that you can't take, Nappa!
Calm down!
You're right!
Thanks to you, my eyes
have been opened.
That simple-celled fool! At this rate,
it looks like I will have to step in.
It's true, I was pretty upset. Now it's time
to show you what I'm really made of.
Are you ready for this, Kakarrot!?
That's more like it.
I can't wait!
Talk tough, will you?
He's not just talking tough. He's got
assurance and absolute confidence in himself.
G- Goku...
Father...
Son-kun, pound that guy
into a pulpy mass!
H- hey!
Hey! Don't be so rough with this!
Who cares if a crystal ball
or two gets broken!?
It's an important tool of my trade!
With Kami-sama dead, and us not knowing
whether the earth will be destroyed or not,
you can just stuff your trade!
How dare you say that!
Now see here!
Would you two quit it!?
It doesn't matter, does it?
Yeah! While you two are at it there,
Goku could be getting done in.
Rubbish! Son-kun is
obviously doing all right!
You think he's going to lose
to those guys!? No way! No way!
Don't hit my crystal ball!
Hey, shut up, already!
Give that here!
A little brother does not take
his older sister's things!
I see you!
Whoo! This is a lot
better, ain't it?
This is a lot better, huh?
I'm going to put a stop to that
irritatingly smart mouth of yours!
You're finished now!
What kind of guy is this!?
He countered at that close range!
That would have been trouble
if I'd taken that one head-on.
I- impossible! That was- that was my greatest
technique, and you brushed it aside!
You really are one tough bastard.
You should have taken at least
a little damage from my Kamehame-ha.
--We ain't getting anywhere like this.
--Enough! Get down here, Nappa!
You're getting us nowhere!
I'll take care of him for you.
What!?
You're pathetic!
To think that I would have to trouble myself
to take action against Kakarrot there.
He's finally coming forward, huh?
Even that big guy is scared of him.
Father...
D- dammit...
T- to think that I should have to
yield your execution to Vegeta...
But brace yourself! Your life will only
last for a moment against Vegeta!
He is a warrior gifted enough to take upon him
the name of Planet Vegeta, after all.
Since he ordered me to,
I'll leave you to Vegeta.
But I won't be content
to withdraw like this.
Oh, no! He's going
after those two!
It's no use!
I won't make it in time!
Kaio-ken!!
What!?
What just happened?
Goku! How did you-?
I doubt he'll be able
to fight anymore.
Take him, and disappear
from the face of the earth right now!
What was that just now!? For an instant,
his speed and power suddenly increased!
G- Goku, how did you do that?
Was that a technique you
learned from that Kaio person?
Yeah. It's called Kaio-ken.
By controlling all of the energy within
your body, you can momentarily amplify it.
If you do it right,
your speed, power,
destructive and defensive forces
all increase many times over.
T- that's awesome!
Even after getting
that much stronger,
you can become many times
stronger than that!?
Yeah.
What are those guys talking about?
Goku, that was mean of you!
This is no time to be playing around.
If you have something like that up your
sleeve, then use it right at the start!
Sorry, but I can't do that.
If I don't restrain my Ki just right while
I'm controlling it, I could wreck myself.
In short...
You have done well to master
the Kaio-ken technique,
which even I could not handle,
to this degree. However,
I must stress once again that you must not
overuse Kaio-ken at your current level.
If you mishandle your control,
you will end up ruining your body.
Do your best to limit
yourself to 2X power.
Remember, using Kaio-ken
any higher than that
will place too great
a burden upon your body.
In other words, your body won't
be able to keep up with the Kaio-ken,
and it will bite back
for what you're doing to it.
Understood clearly.
--...and that's the story.
--I- is that right?
V- Vegeta... h- help me...
T- thanks...
Not at all.
W- what are you doing,
Vegeta!? Vegeta!
I don't have any use
for Saiyans that can't move!
W- what a Ki!
F- Father!
W- what's going on!?
Die!
V- Vegeta!
W- what a beast!
He even killed his own man!
Gohan... Kuririn...
Both of you, go back
to Kame House right now.
R- right...
Gohan, you heard him.
Let's go, now.
B- but...
Gohan, he's just too terrible.
We won't do any good being here.
On the contrary, our being here will
distract Goku, and we'll just be in his way!
Really, Father?
Sorry, yeah. His strength appears
to be even greater than I thought.
O- okay, I understand.
Oh yeah, Goku, as long as you're at it,
could you fight in some other place?
It would be wrong to mess up
everyone's bodies,
in case they ever come back to life.
They ever come back to life?
With Piccolo dead, Kami-sama is dead, too.
The Dragon Balls
have disappeared forever.
I hate to say it, but nobody
is ever coming back to life again.
I know that...
Kuririn-san, you don't think-?
What?
I'll go into the details later.
T- that is, if you're able to beat him, Goku.
lf I can beat him, huh?
Right. In any case,
I have to beat him.
What are you doing? What happened
to all that energy you had before?
Did you get scared, and now you're
discussing how you're going to run away?
Now then, to change locations
and give it my best, I guess.
Just let me take care of this.
Goku, I feel bad about always
leaving our fate up to you.
Don't you dare die now, my friend.
Right.
Father...
Gohan...
Once your daddy comes back alive,
let's go fishing again, okay?
Okay.
Looks like you know that it
won't do any good to run.
We're going to change
the location of our battle.
Suit yourself. It will
all end up the same.
Father...
Vegeta... Has there ever been
a foe this powerful before?
The curtain now rises
on a fierce deathbattle,
with the fate of the earth
and our friends at stake.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org