Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Hang in there, Gohan!
Grand Elder-san's place is just ahead!
Right!
l might have said that once we have the
Grand Elder draw out Gohan's dormant power,
he would rival Vegeta, but to be honest,
l doubt we can expect that much.
That bastard really does have a gift.
There's no end to how strong he's becoming.
After having Gohan made stronger,
all we can do is wait for Goku to get here,
and then have all
three of us fight together.
9999...
10,000...
Amazing! I'm hardly tired at all!
I've surprised myself!
Now then, all right,
that's all for my training.
With the time that's left, I'll rest up.
I have to get used to
regular gravity again, too.
I did it! What agility!
I'm so surprised! I'm so light,
it feels like I ain't even here!
Whoo! Light! Light!
So light, so light, so light, I say!
And strong, and strong!
After building myself up this much, I'm sure
I'll be able to withstand a 10X Kaio-ken!
" Shampoo"
I'm almost to Planet Namek, huh?
All right, let's do this! Let's do this!
Whew, that was refreshing.
Now, all that's left is to sleep tight.
But let's take a moment
before doing that.
Let's see... here it is.
Huh? My mistake.
This stuff is bitter, after all.
Let's see... here it is,
here it is, this, this!
Bulma's daddy's specially-made sports drink!
Goku had not realized
that at some point along the way,
he had obtained a level of power
that went beyond Saiyan limits.
Almost there. Almost there,
you dirty punks!
Gohan, it's coming into view!
You see that tall mountain
there? That's where he is.
All right, we're in the home stretch!
G- Gohan, there's a Ki!
There's a Ki coming from behind us!
I- it can't be!
I- it couldn't be... Vegeta!
Gohan, I'll use all of my
strength to stop him here.
You go on to Grand Elder-san's place!
But...
Hurry up! Go get yourself made stronger!
Okay?
Right!
All right...
In any case, I have to try.
What speed!
Yo.
I- I'm impressed that you discovered us.
Of course I did. I'm in a completely
different league than you are.
Now, why don't you return to me the Dragon
Ball with the four stars that I had hidden?
You've made a mockery of me!
W- what in the world
are you talking about?
Don't play dumb. I'll make
you talk soon enough.
This is incredible!
What's that?
That mountain where
Kakarrot's son fled to...
There's something else there.
That's where you've
hidden the ball, is it?
It is not!
Wait!
You have a tremendous amount
of dormant power, don't you?
Are you not an Earthling?
Excuse me, but could
I ask you to hurry?
They are here.
What is this place?
Wait, Vegeta!
Please wait!
Leave here.
Looks like you want to die.
H- he did it!
Gohan's Ki has risen!
So that's it.
Kakarrot is here, is he?
All right, today's the day
when we settle things!
Come on out, Kakarrot!
What!?
I- it's you!?
What did you do in there!?
Why has your base power
risen so sharply!?
It's true,
your battle power seems to have risen to
a level incomparable to what it was before.
Even so...
...are you telling me you want to
exchange blows with me at your level?
Very well.
Grand Elder-sama!
D- Dende...
Y- yes?
Go tell everyone at once... There is a large,
mysterious power approaching Namek.
Grand Elder-sama!
Quickly!
R- right!
L- listen, Grand Elder-sama says that
there is something approaching this world!
--Huh?
--What!?
Grand Elder? Who's that?
I- it's true! There really is
something up there!
I- it's an incredible power!
I- it's Goku!
Goku has finally gotten here!
What?
I'm not so sure. It doesn't
feel like there's just one...
I- it couldn't be!
1... 2... 3... 4... 5...
No doubt about it!
Freeza has called in
the Ginyu Special Corps!
Damn it all!
You guys, hand over your
Dragon Ball to me, now!
N- no way! We won't do that!
I promise you, once I gain
the power of immortality,
in no way will I
do anything to you!
Hurry, or there will be
no undoing what will happen!
Y- you think you can fool us!?
If we do that, we'll be
playing right into your hands!
Listen to me closely,
you dirty bastards!
This Ginyu Special Corps that
Freeza has called in has five men,
each of which is as strong as me-
no, probably even stronger!
They're going to use the
latest Scouters to find me,
as well as you guys,
and then come kill us at once!
T- that can't be true!
Can't you sense their power!?
There's only one path we can take!
The only route we have is to make
me immortal, and have me defeat them!
What he's saying might be true.
There are indeed five great
evil powers out there.
Well, let's make Gohan immortal!
He might have the power, but he's
utterly lacking in tactical experience!
B- but then... if that's the case...
why the hell did we even come here!?
The Dragon Balls can
grant you three wishes.
You guys will be sure
to have your wish granted.
Three? Not just one?
T- three?
Y- you guys!
Why do you keep repeating it!?
Snap to it!
Who knows if there's
going to be enough time!?
L- listen, we really... we really
can have three wishes granted, right?
Come with me!
But we're going to make sure
you keep your promise, you got that!?
Wait for me!
Damn it!
Fly as fast as you can!
It looks like they've left, huh?
Yes. But even if it works out, their
chances of winning are extremely low.
Nail-san...
Nail...
You go on as well. You want
to help out some, don't you?
But...
If it's about me,
I'll be all right.
My life should still
hold out for a little while.
Understood.
So, you have arrived at last, Ginyu
Special Corps. I have been waiting for you.
Aren't we there yet!?
They've already landed!
Just a little farther.
Why does this have to happen to me?
W- what in the world was that!?
Huh?
Bulma-san, I'm taking
the Dragon Ball with me.
All right, hurry! This way now!
H- hey, what exactly is going on!?
Gohan-kun!
Hold on! Explain what's
happening before you go!
Do you know the kind of trouble
I've had to go through!?
For crying out loud!
Really, when it comes to
those guys, I've just about-
Huh? Wasn't that Vegeta
with them just now?
ReaCoom!
Butta!
Jheese!
Ghurd!
Ginyu!
To-geth-er we are...
The Ginyu Special Corps!
I- I have been expecting you.
The tense situation was
starting to change rapidly.
Who exactly are the Ginyu Special Corps,
whom even Vegeta is afraid of?
To whom will go the Dragon Balls,
along with their wishes?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org