Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Elder!
Dodoria-san! Wait!
Begin by killing
these three younger ones!
Dammit!
I'll dispose of all three
of you within ten seconds.
Don't be ridiculous! You think
you're a match for all three of us!?
Huh? Do l think I'm a match
for you? What an amusing joke.
What!?
Come on!
It's hopeless! He can't defeat
that guy with that kind of attack!
You now understand that it is useless
to try to defy us or run away, I trust.
In any case, come back
down here, please.
So you have finally grown
cooperative, I see. That will do.
You have destroyed
my precious Scouters.
May I have you produce your
Dragon Ball, by way of apology?
I have no choice. But promise
me that no matter what,
you will not lay a hand
on the children!
Yes, yes, we ought to have done it
this way right from the beginning.
W- what monsters
these guys are! How awful!
Why, those-!
H- hey, Gohan! Don't go
getting any funny ideas.
T- there's simply no way we can
stand up to those guys, okay?
Yow-ow-ow... With twenty times the gravity,
you get twenty times the pain!
Now, take this, and get
out of here at once.
Well done.
While I am at it, let me also
have you tell me the locations
of the two remaining Dragon Balls.
Don't be ridiculous!
We Namekians don't sell each other out,
even if it means our own lives!
Now, we had an agreement!
Leave here at once!
Oh dear, not you, too.
There is absolutely no one on this planet
who will speak about their friends.
I guess I will have to have you die...
along with the children!
W- what did you say!?
Why, you-!
Elder! Elder!
This isn't what we agreed to!
You promised you wouldn't do anything
else if I handed over the Dragon Ball!
But unless I have all seven Dragon
Balls, it is meaningless, correct?
You have destroyed our Scouters,
so we will need to have you tell us
where the remaining two are.
I told you, I'll tell you about
the others over my dead body!
Is that how badly you want to die?
In that case, I will do as you wish.
What!?
Freeza-sama, will we possibly be able to
search for the Dragon Balls without Scouters?
Kill all three of them.
Yes, sir.
T- that's dirty!
You guys run! Run away!
Right!
I'll show you the pride
of the Namekian people!
C- Cargot!
Control yourself, Gohan!
Control yourself.
There's nothing we can do! Hey!
Cargot! Cargot! Cargot!
You didn't even have a chance
to show us this " pride" of yours, huh?
It won't even be any fun
to smash a little kid like this.
Well, all the same, die!
Stop!!
Gohan!
What? Your buddies? Where?
Does that teach you?
W- who the hell are you!?
That idiot!
I am going to take you down!!
What did you say?
Kuririn-san!
You dumbass! Run! Hurry!
Hurry!
Right!
They do not appear
to be Namekians, do they?
No, sir.
Damn it!
After them!
Dodoria-san, catch them!
Gohan, fly as fast as you can!
If he catches us, we're finished!
Right!
Fools! Do you think you can escape?
It's no good! He's faster
than us! He'll overtake us!
They are quite fast,
aren't they, Freeza-sama?
They also seem to have more
battle power than the Namekians.
Who in the world could they be?
In the way, to be sure. That
mountain is in the way, you see?
Now our visibility has become
much clearer, has it not?
Huh?
Gohan!
Oh, crap!
Damn!
Dammit, let go of me!
Let go of me, you!
I'm not going to make it in time!
Gohan! Get out of here!
Hurry! He's coming!
Damn, these sure are
nimble little guys!
Kuririn-san, let's land and fight him!
We can't! He isn't the sort of foe
we can do anything against by fighting!
Just fly as hard as you can!
Damn, if this keeps up, we've had it!
I've got to do something!
That's it! Gohan!
Gohan, from here on, don't look
in my direction! Close your eyes!
I have an idea. Got that!?
Right!
Take this!
Taiyo-ken!!
My eyes! My eyes!
My eyes!
I did it! It worked!
Why, you-! My eyes!
Gohan! Hide now, while we can!
Right!
W- why, you rotten-!
W- where did you go, dammit!?
Where are you!?
Where the hell did you go!?
Come on out, dammit!
W- what did you do, Kuririn-san?
Oh, I just blinded him a little bit.
It's okay. He doesn't have his
Scouter anymore, after all.
However, will they indeed be able to escape
the hands of this brutal pursuer?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org