Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"Freeza's Terrible Declaration! I Will Defeat
You Without Using My Hands"
W- What a Ki!
Mid-air battle or ground battle, which
are you better at?
Which, you ask? I guess ground battle.
- Where are they going?
- They're just changing locations.
They're probably moving to someplace
where they can fight to their heart's content.
What incredible guys!
Father...
This means we're going to fight on
the ground, where I'm better at it?
- I'm getting good service.
- Or is it... you're that confident?
When you look at me this way,
I'm very kind.
I know! How about I offer you
another great service?
Great service?
I will keep myself from using
both my hands!
- How's that?
- Both hands? How very generous of you.
So then, can I start us off?
Of course.
Whatever you like.
Ah, I've finally perfected it.
- Well, she sure seems to be in a hurry
to depart.
- Yes, indeed!
Why are you dawdlin' around!?
Tell me! When exactly can we leave!?
While we're all down here like this, my
Gohan-chan is... !
S- See here, Chichi-san! Calm down!
Yes, indeed!
What are you doin' durin' all this
commotion!? Dirty old man!
Not at all, Chichi-san!
Yeah, converting this from a single-seater
to a five-seater is quite a chore.
Ah, that reminds me, I haven't decided
where to place the stereo speakers.
We don't need that stuff! Hurry up and
make this thing go!
The biggest issue there is the
energy, you see.
The difficulty is, in order to fill up this
spaceship with energy, it's going to
take a little time.
So?
- How long's it gonna take?
- Well, I just started a moment ago,
so... I don't know.
WHAT!?
You know, guys...
How come we have to go to
Planet Namek too?
That's the place where Piccolo was born.
On top of that, Vegeta and other, even
more terrifying guys will be there!
Yamucha-sama!
l, Pu-Erh vow to go and strike down
Yamucha-sama's enemies!
Please just sit tight, okay?
You're not gonna live too long, are you?
Come on! To think, me, goin' to Planet
Namek? Don't even kid 'bout that! I'm
gettin' out while I still...
Thinking of running away by yourself,
huh? Not going to be that easy!
Oh dear, what's the matter? Have you
finished attacking?
Your motions are too slow!
There, and now from the left.
Next, from the right!
Right! Left! Right!
And the final one, left!
He's strong! Got great speed too,
as big as his talk.
- G- Goku...
- Father!
It's strange. Here I am fighting someone
so incredibly strong, and I'm
giddy with excitement!
If you're not going to come at me, then
I'll bring it to you again!
You know something, I'm glad I met you!
I was getting so bored, and the creatures
on this planet are all so weird anyhow...
Ah, sorry, sorry! I've hurt your feelings!
You're an exception!
When I first saw all of you clustered
around, I was all freaked out, but you
alone were different!
That's enough! Who would ever expect
me to die here among all these frogs!?
Ah, so gross!
You seemed to have a lot of promise,
so I'll let you be my friend!
Do you want to eat some too?
For a frog, you're really eating this stuff,
huh? Well then...
Would you eat some of this, too?
It's been a long time since I
laughed so hard!
Overall, you really do seem to understand
what I'm saying.
Say! If we had a translator device, I bet
I could talk to you!
I'm so clever!
It's finished!
That was easier than I expected.
Indeed, the word impossible doesn't
exist for a genius like me, Bulma-sama!
- Here goes!
- Switch on!
Go on, try saying something!
Don't be shy!
CHAAN-GE!!
W- What's this? What is it?
You're the first person I'd encountered in
some time, so I tagged along, hoping some
kind of chance would come around...
...but to think that I'd be able to
Change so soon...
W- What am I doing over there!?
Just what is going on here!?
You have my gratitude, little miss. It's
enough that I want to dance the
Dance of Joy!
However, this is one unsightly form!
Well then, how about I set out to find
a stronger body?
Who would have thought he could have
possibly done this much?
Dammit... I can't get free... !
I thought you weren't going to use
your hands, right?
The service time has run out.
Well, let me offer my service, if you want
to call it that, by giving you some advice.
Advice?
You put too much faith in your own strength.
As a result, you leave yourself wide open to attack.
My thanks.
Incredible! Goku's super power is such
that not even Freeza is able to appraise it.
With his pride injured, will Freeza's
anger explode?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org