Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Die!!
P- Piccolo-san!
Get out of here... Gohan...
Piccolo-san!
W- why did you... save me?
I- I told you to get out
of here... Hurry, or else...
D- don't die! Father will be here
soon to beat him for us!
Please, don't die!
Miserable fool! My killing order might have
gotten switched around, but oh well.
Either way, it will all
turn out the same.
One Ki is rapidly growing smaller.
l- is somebody dying!?
K- Kami-sama...
I- it looks like my life is about at its end...
G- Goku didn't make it in time...
H- however, at the very end, Piccolo
surpassed even me, Kami... I'm so pleased...
Kami-sama!
W- what a pitiful tale...
Imagine, Piccolo Daimao,
of all people, protecting some kid...
Nothing could be worse...
U- Uncle!
Gohan... you're the only one
who ever spoke decent to me...
T- this last year that I
spent with you wasn't bad...
Uncle!
Don't you die, G- Goha-
Uncle!!
Mister Popo, I leave
the rest to you...
Kami-sama!
Kami-sama!!
G- Gohan...
Interesting!
You want to fight?
Masenko!!
T- that's an incredible Ki!
700... 1200...
2400...
Battle power 2800!?
Sure enough, these guys can alter
their battle powers intensely!
2800, huh?
Gohan!
For a kid, you can do
some amazing things, huh?
My arm tingles a little.
His battle power just plummeted.
It looks like he used up
all of his power just now.
T- they're too strong...
T- they're just too strong...
--Let go of me!
--See here, Chichi Calm down!
--Let me go, I say!
--Come now, Chichi-san...
Let me go!
--H- hold on, now, that's dangerous...
--Come on, calm down, okay? It's not safe.
T- that's dangerous like that! Stop that!
Aren't you spirited?
--Uranai Baba!
--Sis!
Goku just passed by Karin Tower.
But will he be in time?
I know! Even without a TV,
we can always watch what's happening
using Baba's crystal ball!
Don't be ridiculous! You want to use
my sacred crystal ball to do that!?
--What are you doing!?
--Never mind, just come on inside!
Piccolo-san, I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to avenge you.
Gohan! Run!
Get out of there!
Pipsqueak, I'm sending you
to the Next World for sure this time.
I don't have the strength
to run away anymore.
D- damn it all!
I can't wait to see the look
on Kakarrot's face...
...when he sees his own son
smashed to a pulp!
Kinto Un?
What is that?
Father!
G- Goku!
So you've finally shown up, huh?
G- Goku! We've been
waiting for you!
Father!
What have you come
all this way for, Kakarrot?
Don't tell me you're here
to tell us some nonsensical joke,
such as you've come
to defeat us, or something.
Piccolo...
Piccolo-san died to protect me.
Tenshinhan...
Yamucha...
Shocked over your dead
idiot friends, are you?
Come to think of it, there was another,
puny little guy, that went to pieces.
He had more power than you'd
expect for such a runt.
Naturally, he was no
match for Nappa-sama.
ls that so? Even Chaozu?
And Kami-sama, too... Damn...
There's no need to grieve for them.
You'll be joining your friends soon.
After going through all the trouble
to come back to life,
you just had to stroll on by, huh?
His battle power is rising
higher and higher.
W- what? You want to die already?
Here's something
by way of greeting!
He's fast!
Gohan, over here.
Kuririn...
G- Goku...
Sorry I'm late.
Way to hang on, you two.
Each of you eat half of this.
I- isn't that a senzu bean?
K- Karin-sama still has them, huh?
Mm-hmm. This is the last one.
T- then, you eat it.
That's all right.
I ate one before I came.
N- no, you save it in case you need it.
Even if we recover,
we won't be much help to you.
Don't worry needlessly.
If you don't eat it,
I'm throwing it away.
Here.
Thanks.
Gohan, you too.
Kuririn, you've gotten a lot
stronger, huh? I can tell by your Ki.
I thought I had, but to no avail.
I'm no use against them.
They're too strong.
I- I just stood by
and let everyone else die...
Gohan, I hardly recognized you,
too. You sure trained hard.
Mm-hmm. Piccolo-san trained me,
but I wasn't able to do anything.
With Piccolo-san dead, we'll never
be able to use the Dragon Balls again.
No one is coming back to life.
Let's avenge them- the three of us!
With you joining us, Goku, we might
be able to deal with one of them!
Hey, Goku, you trained under some
incredible guy named Kaio, right?
Yeah.
But I'm going to fight them by myself.
You guys stay back and watch, so you
don't get caught in the middle of it.
B- by yourself!?
No matter how strong you are,
Goku, that's crazy!
Their strength is far greater
than we can even imagine!
H- he's right, Father!
G- Goku...
Father!
Let Goku handle this!
B- but...
I've never seen Goku
show that much anger.
W- we've got no place
getting in his way.
Remember, you're going to be
paying me a viewing fee for this.
Goku!
Goku-sa!
Where's Gohan!?
Gohan!
G- Gohan is alive!
T- thank goodness...
Chichi! Goku and Gohan
are fightin'! Keep it together!
Son-kun, hang in there!
Beat those Saiyans!
P- Piccolo!
Even Piccolo has been done in!
Which means we can no longer
use the Dragon Balls!
T- then, nobody is
coming back to life?
What's with that look
on your face? I don't like it.
Is this how badly you want me
to effortlessly kill you?
You're going to pay for this!
Father, you're incredible!
Battle power 7000...
8000... impossible!
What is Kakarrot's battle power!?
Higher than 8000!
Higher than 8000!? There has to be
some mistake! It's a malfunction!
Don't worry, I still won't be using
the Kaio-ken technique on you.
Kaio-ken?
Shut up!
There's no way you can
stand up to Nappa-sama!
What?
H- how did he do that just now?
W- when did you get behind me?
Why, you!
For as big as you were talking,
you ain't all that great.
W- what did you say!?
I- I'm not all that great, am I!?
That's right. I could tell
from your attack just now.
Why don't you tell me...
...exactly what it is
that you can tell!?
Strange... His battle power is completely
different from when he fought Raditz.
Over here!
D- did you see your father's moves?
But he's amazing.
What's going on?
How did Kakarrot get this much power
in such a short amount of time?
Why, you!
That punch just now
was for Chaozu.
Goku is strong!
But will Goku be able to protect the earth
from the hands of the Saiyans?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org