Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
How audacious it was for them to attempt
to inflict even one injury upon me.
Such extreme examples of those
who did not keep their places.
Now then, Grand Elder-san,
it would appear that there is
still one foolish individual
out here who does not know his place.
I believe that if this gentleman
were about to be killed,
you would soon change
your mind and tell me
how to have the Dragon
Balls grant my wish.
You will also regret not
having spoken up sooner,
while you were still unharmed.
If you like, we can spare
your life right here and now.
You've probably already realized this,
but Grand Elder-sama has only
a short time left to live.
It would be bad for you and I both
if we were to fight here,
with him caught in the middle.
We will change our location.
I do not anticipate the extent
of our fight to be that great,
but very well.
Anywhere you like.
My apologies, Nail.
Please find a way to hold out
long enough for Dende to
reach the Earthlings.
At this point, the fate of our
planet rests in their hands.
C- Commander Ginyu!
What are you laughing about?
How can I not laugh about this?
I didn't think anyone could
be as strong as you.
So why laugh?
Because I'm happy to have found someone
much stronger than even I, Ginyu-sama.
Yes, yes! Such strength!
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
It's been quite a while since
I've been so happy!
I'm so glad to be alive!
W- what!?
Jheese...
Y- yes, sir.
S- so that's it!
Commander Ginyu...
Take care that you do
not drop my Scouter.
That's it, all right!
How far away are you going?
This is far enough!
There is no need to distance ourselves
any farther than this, is there?
I suppose not.
My, my. Those who wish to
die certainly account
for a large number
of this planet's inhabitants.
How troubling.
This is amazing! Your battle
power has risen to 42,000.
I see now. You certainly are quite
different from the other Namekians.
I am surprised. It is
a wonderful battle power.
You certainly live up to your
classification as a " warrior-type."
I wish you were among my ranks.
Well, shall I inform you of the
battle power rating which I possess,
to use as a reference as
you begin your fight against me?
My battle power rating is...
530,000.
However, naturally I do not intend
to use my full power against you,
so you need not worry.
What!?
I know! What if I were to fight
using only my left hand for you?
That might make it more enjoyable.
Enough!
No, this will not do.
Here I stretched out my neck for you
so that you could not miss,
and this is all you have?
On the other hand, this is about
right for someone at 42,000.
Oh my, that was impolite of me.
I will return it to you.
You should not be straining
yourself so, should you?
I think it would be best for you
if you spoke, before you get killed.
This is a surprise!
You can regenerate?
Although, while you may be back in one
piece, your situation has not changed.
It appears that you cannot
regenerate your energy, as well.
Your battle power has dropped.
My, my. After having been
shown how mismatched you are,
you still wish to continue?
I have no idea what the people
of this planet must be thinking.
I will not allow you...
I will not allow you to...
W- what is this?
What is going on here, exactly?
Does this planet have something
personal against me, or something?
This time, l've had it for sure!
Lucky! lf I can just
make it into that cave...
Just a little farther...
I- I made it! I'm saved!
Huh? Have I been saved?
This is so mean of you!
This is it! This time for sure!
Farewell, everyone!
Yow!
What? What happened?
Here.
Stay back! You pervert, grabber,
idiot, monster, whatever you are!
Bulma-san!
G- Gohan-kun! T- then...
How could you, Bulma-san?
How terrible. There
wasn't even any warning-
What have the two of you
been up to?!
No sooner do you show up suddenly with
Vegeta and take the Dragon Ball away,
then you take off with
him to someplace else!
Now, I want to know
just what's going on!
Do you think you can just leave
a delicate lady unattended out here
in such a dangerous place,
and get away with it?!
B- b- but didn't we just
rescue you from that dinosaur?
B- Bulma-san, at any rate,
we need the Dragon Radar!
If everything works out, we may still
be able to get our wish granted!
What's this? You still haven't
gotten our wish granted?
I saw from the Radar all seven Dragon
Balls had been gathered in one place.
I was sure you were the ones
who had gotten them together,
and I was on my way to meet you.
And now what do I hear?
Unbelievable. What sort of
goofing-off have you been up to?
G- goofing-off, she says.
Scratch, scratch...
Bulma-san, pardon me for a second.
Kuririn-san, I've got it.
It's that way!
Okay, we're off!
Hold on! Tell me
what's going on!
We're in a hurry right now,
so we'll explain later.
Bulma-san, please wait
for us back at that island.
Huh!? You've got to be kidding!
You expect me to walk back from here?
How can you?
This is so mean of you!
Oh yeah, Father has arrived!
R- really? How is he?
Has he gotten much stronger?
Gohan, let's hurry!
Right!
Son-kun, huh?
I didn't think he would turn
out as handsome as he did.
With Yamucha as my boyfriend,
all he and I have ever done is fight...
Maybe I blew it.
Wha- wha-
What are you doing?!
What the?
Y- you're not a...
Super Saiyan...
...b- but I've still taken a liking...
to that strong body of yours.
T- taken a liking?
S- sure enough, Commander Ginyu
is planning on doing that...
Amazing! How was he able to find
that much power in his condition?
H- here it comes...
C- Change!!
H- how come...
I'm... over... there?
I've made an exchange,
your body for mine.
Y- you did what?
Commander Ginyu!
Here's your Scouter.
All right, we're returning
to the ship.
Freeza-sama may be on
his way back, as well.
Yes, sir!
This body is even faster!
I... can't... move!
So this is the reason
why he injured himself...
Oh no! At this rate I, I mean,
he and Kuririn will meet up!
Dammit, not only am I
unfamiliar with this body,
but with this wound,
I can't fly so well.
On top of that, if I manage to
safely get back to Earth,
l'll probably just get
Chichi angry at me again.
L- look at the face l've got now!
l'm done for!
What's this? Goku and Ginyu
have exchanged bodies!
Flying toward Freeza's spaceship
in search of the Dragon Balls were
Gohan, Kuririn,
Vegeta, and Ginyu!
The battle revolving around the Dragon
Balls has taken yet another radical turn!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org