Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"The Two Superpowers Collide! A
Fistfight Where Both Turn Serious!!!"
Sit tight, Gohan! Your Ma is comin' to
save you right now!
Say there, Chichi-san, won't you
please re-think this?
Planet Namek will be dangerous for you.
He's right! Let's leave all of
this up to Son-in-law!
My Bulma-chan is there with him.
It will be fine!
No! I'm goin'! After all, you can bet
Goku-sa ain't makin' Gohan-chan do
his homework properly!
Yajirobe!
I've brung a message from Karin-sama.
'Parently Piccolo got to Namek all right.
Piccolo!?
If he hangs around with the likes of him,
Gohan-chan will become a delinquent!
I can't dawdle around any longer!
Let go of me! Let me go!
The repairs to the spaceship aren't
likely finished yet!
- That kinda thing takes a lotta time!
- That's right!
Ah, here, everyone's all together!
The third time around, I could handle
it without even looking at the blueprints.
Well, Chichi-san, the repairs on the
spaceship are finished. I can have
you take off any time.
l- Is there something... ?
There's no other way, is there? We can't
very well let Chichi-san go alone.
At this point, we all go together...
Listen here! If we all put our efforts
together, we just may be of help to
Goku and the others!
Why d'ya need me too!?
You seem to be much stronger than
I thought. I'm a little surprised.
To think that there was someone in the
world who could reach even higher than
Commander Ginyu...
- But you are still no match for me.
- Maybe not. But we just don't know!
I know!
Right back at you!
He's escaped from my Kiai-Ho!
Damn!
Hurry and come back up! It'll take more
than that to beat you.
That rat has incredible speed as well.
So, now what do I do?
He can't find his opponent by just feeling
out their Ki, the way we can.
He's always used his eyes to locate me.
All right, let's make use of that!
W- What's wrong?
Goku still hasn't come up!
It's okay! Father's Ki hasn't
diminished one bit!
You know, it's been a while since I've
done this. I wonder if Old Man Turtle
Hermit is doing okay.
Ka... me... ha... me...
Ha!
Okay, just like that, just like that!
What's the matter? Not ready yet? And
here I was about to deliver a final blow...
I guess we're just about ready.
All right, here goes!
Off you go!
Here he comes!
That's not him!
And the other!
This way?
No!
Father!
A great success!
Huh? He ain't the least bit affected?
To think that you could do this much.
You're the first one aside from my father
who I've had to dust off after.
This might be the first time I've ever been
this excited. How shall I dish this out?
You got me! I thought that would have
at least had some effect on you.
I think I'll torment him a little...
That bastard! This is telekinesis!
Dammit!
Okay, if that's how it is...
You are impudent!
- What is this!?
- It's like a whole island!
An island is floating there!
Goku!
This is the end for sure.
- You've fallen for it!
- Oh, hell!
I... can't... move... !
This serves you right!
When I miss, you're finished!
If I don't somehow find my way out of this... !
We're just about at Game Set! Are
you getting tired of this?
- What!?
- You might die this time, huh?
Gohan!
Ah, Piccolo-san!
- Goku...
- Father...
What kind of guys are these!? Freeza's
just playing around!
If he felt like it, he's got the power to
destroy this whole planet.
And yet, seeing as how we're
all still alive here...
- It means he really is just playing around?
- What a punk he is!
Piccolo-san, what about Father... ?
There's no use worrying! That jerk hasn't
gotten serious yet either!
Look over there!
Father!
That was a little too close. I'll have to
be on guard against that attack.
Didn't I tell you earlier? Don't bust other
people's planets up so much!
Goku... But how?
At the moment of the explosion, he
escaped from being bound up in
there at super-speed.
He did something that incredible?
In that instant?
They're freaks! Both of them, dammit!
- You're a persistent one! Even I am
starting to get annoyed.
- So am I.
I think I'll put an end to all this warming up,
and finally get serious about this.
Me too.
A clash of technique against technique!
Explosive power versus power!
However, to Goku and Freeza, is this no
more than simple warming up?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org