Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Where are you!?
Where did you run off to,
Vegeta!?
He couldn't have gotten
away that fast.
He must be hiding somewhere.
Have you not found
him yet, Zarbon-san!?
If you disgracefully allow him
to escape you like this,
I will have you take
responsibility with your life.
Fool! Go ahead and search
outside as much as you like.
1... 2... 3... 4...
There are indeed
five of them here.
Not only have they
healed my injuries,
they're going to have every last one
of their Dragon Balls taken from them.
But I can't get away
carrying all five of them.
What's more, it doesn't look like I have
the time to calmly think this over.
All right...
Please, let this work!
Hey! You fell for it!
I'm still inside the ship!
What was that!?
D- damn it all!
Now!
Where is Vegeta!?
D- do not tell me that Vegeta
is after the Dragon Balls!
All right, and now for me!
T- the Dragon Balls!
That bastard!!
W- where is he this time!?
Freeza-sama, is he still
inside the spaceship?
Look for him!
Y- yes, sir!
lf I were to unwisely
escape through the air,
Freeza would overtake
me in an instant.
What disgraceful behavior!
Not only did you allow
Vegeta to escape,
but with the Dragon Balls, as well!
There is no way that
he could have run away
with all five Dragon Balls
in that short moment!
I will search the inside
of the spaceship,
so you are to thoroughly
search outside!
Yes, sir.
You are prepared to
answer for this, yes?
If you are unable to bring
Vegeta back here in one hour...
Y- yes, sir!
Let's see...
It's around here.
T- this is awful...
Vegeta must have done this.
Who's there?
Is someone there?
Oh...
And after they had grown
this many of them...
I'm sure they should have
fallen around here somewhere.
There they are!
That's magnificent control,
if I do say so myself.
Take that, Freeza.
I've finally gotten
your Dragon Balls!
Now, including the one that
I sunk at that village,
I only need one more
to have all seven.
A strong battle power!
Is that Zarbon?
No, the battle power
is lower than Zarbon's.
I- is that!?
Just you wait, Gohan!
Once you go to
Grand Elder-sama's place,
you'll become much,
much stronger!
He's that Earthling!
W- why is he here
on Planet Namek?
What's more, he was holding
the final Dragon Ball.
Just how far is luck
going to go my way!?
That's the last one.
People of Planet Namek,
may you please rest in peace.
Now then, I have to hurry
and look for that Dragon Ball.
Huh? This way?
It's not inside a house?
I get it. Not even Vegeta would
find it if it's in the lake, huh?
Here it is!
Here it is, here it is.
9995... 9996...
9997...
After I've done 10,000 of these,
I'll do 60-times gravity.
I'm on it...
9998...
9999...
10,000!
W- what is this?
I can't move my body at all...
Dammit...
That was fast!
I'll be there real soon!
It looks like that Earthling is
after the Dragon Balls as well.
But I'm going to take that
one that you're holding.
Then I will have all seven
of the Dragon Balls!
Dammit! Where the hell is Vegeta!?
If only I had a Scouter,
I could easily detect him!
If it keeps going like this, I'll have
to surrender my life to Freeza-sama.
Is that Vegeta!?
No, that's the guy who rescued
that Namekian kid.
But he's carrying something
that looks like a Dragon Ball.
Vegeta!
I've finally found you!
You're mine now!
There's a huge battle power following me.
It looks like Zarbon has found me.
What an annoying bastard.
But this is a good opportunity.
I'll take care of him for sure this time.
He'll be full of confidence in himself
after our previous battle.
His guard ought to be down.
It will take more than this!
This is crazy, Goku!
Bulma's daddy...
You're going to die, suddenly jumping
to 100-times gravity like that.
I- I was doing it at 50-times gravity...
Are you sure the machine ain't broken?
Don't be absurd!
My machine is flawless.
B- but still...
Just a moment.
W- what's this?
l figured it out, Goku.
The gravity device control
has become unstable.
lt's because your spaceship has
entered an intense magnetic storm.
W- what do I do?
lt will take another hour before
you're through the magnetic storm.
A- an hour?
I ain't going to last that long!
ln any event,
you have to turn off the gravity machine's
switch without a moment's delay.
T- that's easy for you to say...
Huh?
Well if it isn't Kuririn!
Don't startle me like that!
I- isn't this dangerous,
Bulma-san?
If you're outside leisurely
reading a book,
they're going to find you.
What are you talking about?
If I stay inside that cave
all the time, I'll-
Huh? Could that be... a Dragon Ball?
You got it!
Native Dragon Balls are gigantic, huh?
The Grand Elder was quite understanding.
Oh, right, right! Bulma-san,
is Gohan inside the house?
I'd like to take him to the
Grand Elder's place, too.
He went to go find another Dragon Ball.
Huh?
It showed up on the Radar.
Remember, near that village
that Vegeta attacked?
Huh? Really?
A Ki! It's heading this way!
It's right next to us!
It's Gohan-kun.
That was fast, huh?
N- no, it's not Gohan!
V- Vegeta!
Oh, crap! I was so ecstatic over becoming
stronger that I didn't notice his Ki!
This is an unexpected place
to run into you, huh, Earthling?
I didn't think you guys had
the civilization it took
to make it all the way
to this planet.
Looking at that Dragon Ball that
you're so carefully holding onto,
it appears our goals are the same.
Listen, before I take that Dragon Ball from
you, there's something that I have to do.
But you'd better not get any funny ideas,
like running away with that thing.
It won't be just you- that woman
will end up dying as well.
He's here.
W- who is that?
Judging by his face, I wonder if
he isn't a champion of justice...
T- this is the worst...
Once again, a battle to the death
was about to begin.
What fate will Kuririn
and the others meet?
And what about Goku?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org