Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Looks like Kakarrot
has decided to lay low.
What a coward.
F- Father is not a coward!
D- dammit...
What's become of you, Goku!?
Hurry, Kinto Un!
Go, go, go! Go!!
At this point, it looks like we'll have
to fight them with just the three of us.
You know what to do.
Let's go with that plan.
Y- yeah.
First, I draw his attention
as much as I can.
I'll find an opening, and grab his tail,
the Saiyans' weakness.
Once his power fails,
and he can't move...
I- I rush him as hard as I can.
That's right.
Watch yourself!
What are you all mumbling about?
It won't do any good.
What can you guys do against me?
We'll show you what we can do, right now!
All right!
Here goes!
He's started charging me
all of a sudden!
Keep his attention!
Now!
Why, you-!
Gohan!
We did it!
You fools!
I- impossible!
P- Piccolo-san!
Whoa, don't you die, now.
We still have to have you
tell us about the Dragon Balls.
I- it can't be!
Hell of a miscalculation, huh?
Did you think we would leave
our weak spot untrained forever?
That's too bad. The best
that this planet had to offer,
and this is what happens
to him after one blow.
P- Piccolo-san!
Shake it off! Piccolo-san!
Piccolo-san! Piccolo-san!
I- it's hopeless now...
Now then, while he has gone beddy-bye,
I think I'll toy around
with the little squirts.
I'll start with Kakarrot's son.
Hey, you've inherited
the blood of a true Saiyan.
You'll be able to amuse me
for a little while, right?
You know, your old man
is pretty cold, huh?
Letting his own son die like this...
Dammit, what's going on here!?
The TV isn't showing anything!
Come on, come on, come on!
It's no use.
I'm sure that things
aren't going so smoothly
that they can provide us
with a TV broadcast.
Y- you don't think that everyone
has been killed already, do you?
Don't you say anything
dire like that again!
C- Chichi, what are you doin',
gussied up like that?
T- those are Lunch-san's...
I can't take it anymore!
I'm goin' to rescue Gohan!
D- don't be ridiculous! If you go now,
you're goin' to be killed!
I don't care! I'm goin'
to die together with Gohan!
H- hold on, now!
Chichi! Calm down!
Let me go, Pa!
Let me go!
Let go of me! I- I'm goin'!
Pa! Let go of me! I'm goin'!
I'm goin'! I'm goin'! I'm goin'!
Now see here, Chichi!
You're goin' to get killed!
--I'm tellin' you no!
--I'm goin' to go rescue Gohan-chan!
--Come on, re-think this!
--I'm goin' where Gohan is!
Chichi!
Tenshinhan...
Yamucha...
Son-kun...
l believe in you.
l'm sure... l'm sure you're
going to save the earth.
Hey now, don't you snuff it just yet!
Amuse me a little longer.
That's more like it!
Stop!
Ho, at least his moves are pretty good.
You dirty brat!
Bounce around, will you!?
Let me show you
something I've been saving.
Kienzan!!
What a worthless technique!
Nappa! Get out of the way!
That idiot! Can't he tell
what kind of technique that is!?
D- damn!
W- why, you-!
How dare you wound my face!
Away with you!
K- Kuririn-san!
Now to finish you!
Y- you bastard!
A- are you awake already!?
Looks like you're having
a hard time with them, Nappa!
Don't you... don't you
look down on Earth, Saiyan!
W- w- why, you! Now I'm mad!
I was holding back against you,
since we can't kill you
because of the Dragon Balls.
But don't get too full of yourself!
You're the one
who's too full of himself!
W- what Ki is this!?
T- there's an incredible Ki
coming this way from far off!
I- it's true! A- an amazing,
yet familiar Ki!
N- no doubt about it.
I can feel it.
You guys are all just spouting
nonsense! What is this!?
It could only be him.
It's Son Goku!
Just a little farther, Goku.
Hurry! Make haste!
It's Son Goku! Son Goku is coming!
I knew he was sure to come!
Damn that bastard,
making us wait for him!
F- Father! Father really
is coming! Hurry!
G- Goku...
Kakarrot?
Where is he?
These guys have the unusual ability
to sense someone's presence.
Is it Kakarrot?
Let's see...
I'm close. I can feel them.
There are two enormous Ki,
two even more enormous Ki,
and one small Ki...
That number ain't right.
Has somebody died?
Kinto Un, please hurry faster!
Vegeta-sama!
Is what these guys are saying true?
Is Kakarrot really headed this way?
I don't know whether
it's Kakarrot or not,
but someone will be here
in about four minutes.
Someone with a battle power of 5000.
Five- five thousand!?
That's impossible!
lt's definitely a reading
that makes it unthinkable
that this is the same
Kakarrot as before.
What's more, these guys
are able to alter their readings.
That means it's at least 5000.
T- that can't be! It must
be some kind of mistake!
It's unusual to see this guy panicked.
Nappa! Kill them! If all four of them
team up, it could be a problem for us!
It will also serve
as a warning to Kakarrot!
What!?
But what about the Dragon Balls?
I don't care! I have an idea.
If we go to Planet Namek,
the home world of that Namekian,
I'm sure that there will be Dragon Balls
that are even more powerful.
I thought they were
just worthless stories,
but if Kakarrot really
has come back to life,
then those legends are true after all.
I get you. But Kakarrot being 5000
has to be a mechanical malfunction.
Well, it doesn't matter. It doesn't change
the fact that I get to kill them all.
I'll start with you!
P- Piccolo-san, run!
I'll stop him one way or another
until Father gets here!
What!?
After all, if you die, Piccolo-san,
then Kami-sama dies too,
and the Dragon Balls will...
You're talking nonsense! There's no way
you can stop him by yourself!
Stop me, you say? Me?
I- if this keeps up,
there won't be any going back...
I- it's no use... I can't move...
Don't make me laugh, you brat!
No!
I- incredible!
D- did he get him?
Why, you brat!
This is where it ends!
N- no!
Goku...
Die!!
Who- who are you?
They're sour!
Piccolo leaps in to rescue
Gohan from his pinch.
What will be Piccolo's fate?
Hurry, Goku!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org