Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Stay with it, Kuririn...
Gohan can't control this Ki...
T- t- there it is!
Is this-?
A Genki Dama...
You did it...
Hit him... with that...
I can't make another Genki Dama...
Make sure you hit him... please!
Y- you got it! I'll try.
Let me take care of it.
He's so strong! He should be fairly
worn out from fighting with Father, too...
You're a tough little runt, but you
appear to be nearing your limit.
Gohan-chan, fight!
Fight, Gohan-chan!
W- w- what are you sayin', Chichi!?
Gohan's no match for that guy!
Gohan, get out of there!
Gohan-chan...
Chichi, are you-?
Pa!
Chichi...
They've vanished!
Gohan-chan?
Uranai Baba, hurry up
and show me Gohan-chan!
A- all right! All right!
I'll try! Let me go!
You've got a ridiculous amount
of strength for a woman!
Kamehame-Ha!!
Is that your last-ditch effort!?
Darn it!
One more!
Damn! With my skill, I can't hit him
when he's moving around like that!
You don't hit him with the
Genki Dama by using your eyes.
You sense out his evil Ki
and shoot at that.
W- who's there!?
I am Kaio, the one who taught
Son Goku the Genki Dama.
K- Kaio-sama?
Everything will be
decided by your one shot.
Know that the ball of that Genki Dama
is filled with the hopes of the whole earth.
The ball is filled with
the hopes of the whole earth?
No matter how many of you scum gang up
on me, you're still no match for an elite.
It looks like once you realized
that, it was already too late.
S- sense out his evil Ki
and shoot at that... So that's it...
Kuririn, we're counting on you!
You'll only get one chance.
I'm done playing around.
You think you can get away!?
F- feel it!
Feel his evil Ki!
K- Kuririn!
H- he's fixin' to do somethin'.
That's a humungous amount of Ki.
lf you're gonna get him,
then get him, already!
Watch closely, Kakarrot!
This is the end of your foolish son!
I've got him!
What're ya doin', ya dimwit!?
Hurry up and hit him with that!
W- what?
T- that idiot!
Damn it all!
W- what is that!?
Hit him!
It missed!
W- what happened!? How could
my crystal ball crack!?
G- Gohan-chan!
It's hopeless now!
Bounce it back, Gohan!
Gohan, that thing is on our side!
As long as you don't have any evil in you,
you should be able to bounce it back!
You did it!
Yahoo!
We did it!
We did it, Goku!
Turtle, do you have
any quick-drying glue?
Glue? Hmm, I seem to remember
having some around here somewhere...
What about Gohan-chan!?
Uranai Baba, can't you do something
about the crystal ball!?
Chichi! Stop that!
Pa! Gohan-chan is still
alive! So's Goku-sa!
Y- you're right. But how are we goin'
to get to where Goku and them are?
All right, Chichi-san,
I'll take you there.
Really? But how?
In my airship.
Bulma-san, thank you!
If I were to ever have a husband
and son who were in trouble,
I would rush to their side,
no matter what. That's human nature.
All right, I'm going too.
I'm going, too.
K- Karin-sama!
Father...
You guys finally got him, huh?
Time and again, I thought
we were done for.
You two sure are a mess.
We're not as bad off as you.
T- the Saiyan!
It's okay. He's dead.
We can relax, now.
Damn it all, he was one horrible fellow,
but we could at least dig a grave.
You mean, a grave for you guys?
T- t- that's impossible!
He took that Genki Dama dead-on!
You put me through quite
the awful experience, huh?
E- even I thought I was
going to die from that one.
I may have taken
quite a bit of damage,
but I still have enough power left
to take care of you trash.
After I've killed you,
I'll wait until I've recovered my strength,
and then thoroughly destroy this planet!
Just keep on going straight.
Bulma! For Karin-sama to deign
to give you directions...
...is an extremely magnanimous
thing for him to do!
It is? He looks like
an ordinary cat to me.
Y- you guys dare to make me, Vegeta-sama,
use up nearly all of my power?
Never mind that you ganged up on me,
against trash like you, it wounds my pride...
Would you die, already!?
D- dammit... Dammit!
G- Goku!
Damn it! Coming from me,
that destructive force was pathetic!
All three of them
are still barely alive!
I- I've taken more damage than I thought...
I- I have to put them all away quickly...
...and then recuperate...
T- this brat has...
...re-grown his tail!
H- his tail? That's right... In the past,
Goku's tail suddenly grew back, too...
If he were to transform,
that would be a problem!
Gohan's tail has
once again grown out.
Could this be a symbol
that the fate of the earth-
that the fate of mankind-
is to be saved from extinction?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org