Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Okay, Vegeta-chan, now it's our turn.
You two little pipsqueaks there,
give Vegeta-chan a hand.
Use as many dirty tricks as you need to.
Hey, ReaCoom! Don't kill the little ones!
We're going to kill them, after all!
Leave a little treat for us, too!
Dammit!
Why, that jerk!
Ginyu...
...Special Corps...
ReaCoom!!
Hey, what's going on here? Vegeta-chan's
power level just rose to upwards of 30,000!
Get down!
More! More! More!
H- he got him.
Incredible... He ended it all in one instant.
Vegeta has ridiculous strength, all right.
Hey, it couldn't be, right?
A- a Ki! H- he's alive!
That guy is alive!
H- he couldn't be... N- no way...
Hi!
H- he's taken hardly any damage at all!
That's enough for the warm-up exercises.
ReaCoom is trying to look cool,
and we're getting all dusty over here!
Our cleaning bill
is going to be outrageous.
W- what kind of monster is he?
How is it that we have to get the Dragon
Balls back from someone like this?
Whoops!
That was close, that was close.
I almost screwed up.
I have to make sure to
deliver these to Freeza-sama.
Planet Namek.
Environment: moderate;
culture level: low;
practical resources: none;
scouting industrial space,
commercial space, and residential space.
Such a worthless planet, huh?
Perhaps I will make it a planet for exiles.
There are any number of planets
like this one in the universe.
I doubt there would be any value
in going to the trouble of developing it.
I will be acquiring the Dragon Balls shortly,
so I will have no further business here.
I know. As we are leaving,
I will turn this planet into fireworks.
F- fireworks?
Yes. To celebrate my eternal life.
A big, flashy " boom."
Are there any other planets we can sell
for development at a high price?
Y- yes, sir, I will investigate at once.
Dragon Balls... how delightful...
Well, should we get started?
ReaCoom Kick!!
V- Vegeta-san!
Good! That's pretty good, Vegeta-chan!
You're better than I thought, huh?
ReaCoom Elbow!!
He got him!
Speed Up!!
Yoo-hoo!
Way to go, ReaCoom!
Whoo! Whoo!
Thanks, guys!
V- Vegeta-san...
What's the matter, Vegeta-chan?
You can't possibly be
finished after that, right?
You're still pretty spirited, huh?
Good for you!
Hey, now, are you okay?
Don't tell me you've kicked
the bucket already, have you?
D- did he get him?
Okay...
Nice, nice, that's more like it.
There's the reason why Freeza-sama
adored you so much, long ago, huh?
But why would you turn your
back on him, Vegeta-chan?
ReaCoom is the same as ever, huh?
He's got a nasty personality.
What a freak!
Don't you have any techniques
with more panache than that?
If not, then it's about time
I killed you. Is that okay?
Y- you monster! Damn it...
To think he'd be this strong...
lt's almost as though he's
treating me like a toddler...
lf it keeps going like this,
l'm going to get killed by him...
G- Gohan...
Yes?
I- if Vegeta gets done in, then it
will be our turn to get killed next.
M- make no mistake,
there's no way we can beat him.
I'm sure that not even Goku could.
At this point, it's all or nothing.
Let's charge him!
Right!
All righty...
Your life is mine!
There it is!
ReaCoom's 18th final pose.
Poor Vegeta-chan. The life
of a flower is so short, huh?
Okay, I'll finish you with this.
All right... let's go, Gohan!
Vegeta doesn't have the strength left
to avoid ReaCoom's quick attacks.
Right!
ReaCoom...
...Eraser Gun!!
Vegeta-san!
Move! You're in my way!
W- who asked you to do that!?
Y- you idiot! If you had time to rescue me,
why didn't you attack ReaCoom!?
For crying out loud, your softness
makes me want to vomit!
The ground's surface has been blown away,
and the planet's shape has changed...
What a terrifying beast!
That sneak attack just now
was a pretty good one.
Coming down from directly
above shut my mouth.
As a result, my teeth are messed up.
I think I might be a little bit mad.
Hey, Butta, Jheese!
Let me take out these
two little squirts, too!
Do you mind? Okay?
Do you mind?
What choice do we have?
Okay, fine! Do as you please.
In exchange, you're going to treat us
to chocolate parfaits later!
Okay! You heard him, maggot-kun.
Big Fire Toe Attack!!
Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san! Kuririn-san!
M- my bones...
How can this be?
With just one hit...
this is what happens to me...
He's too much...
I- is this allowed?
And after having Grand Elder-san
raise my power, too...
I- I'm no use at all...
S- shake it off, Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san!
F- frankly, we're finished...
We're powerless against them, and if
we run, they'll catch us right away...
And the Dragon Balls
have been taken from us...
There's nothing good about this...
Tch! Aw, man... I couldn't help
myself, and hit him too hard.
I was planning to play around
with him a little more, but too bad.
Now then, for the next
little pipsqueak's turn...
Darn it!
G- Gohan...
I- I'll do as much as I can!
Just you watch me!
This should be interesting.
Darn it...
ReaCoom is an incredible foe.
Will Gohan be able to get through
this greatest of pinches?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org