Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
What should I do for training?
W- what should I do to train?
To begin with, you don't need
to do anything. Just live.
Live?
Right. Try surviving all by yourself
without anything happening to you.
If you can survive without incident
for six months, I'll teach you how to fight.
Six months, by myself, in this place?
No way! I'll die of loneliness!
You won't be lonesome.
This place is teaming with beasts
that are thirsting for blood.
No, don't do this!
Don't leave me here!
Right now, you don't have
time to be spoiled!
But...
Survive somehow for the next six months,
and make yourself tougher,
both physically and mentally.
Do not forget that you hold the key
to earth's fate in your hand.
Believe in your own power.
And learn some way to
effectively draw out that power.
But I...
See you later.
Oh, right, right.
Don't think about trying
to escape from here.
This place is surrounded by nothing
but expansive hellish desert.
In other words,
it's a world of death that's enough
to make this place look like heaven.
Wait! Where is there any food?
What about baths?
What about a bed? What about books,
and notebooks, and pencils, and...
You think there's any of that
arranged for you here, sonny boy?
Oh, no!
That's horrible!
If you have to blame something,
then blame your own fate. The way I do.
Wait!
I'm scared!
Don't leave me here!
Kami-sama look strange.
Something wrong?
Sure enough, there's something different
about Piccolo from how he was before.
He's still unmistakably evil,
but I sense that the devious abrasiveness
he had in the past is fading away.
Popo thinks so too. The old Daimao
not make Son Goku's son strong.
What made me clearly realize that there
was something strange about Piccolo...
...was that when Son Goku's
brother Raditz was killed by him,
his spirit went right
to the Other World.
Up until now, whenever anyone
was killed by the Demon Clan,
their spirit had been
unable to pass beyond,
and they drifted through the air,
as they suffered.
Did a guy named Raditz wash up here?
Yeah, he was here all right.
And yet, since Raditz had
gone to the Other World,
Piccolo is clearly different
from how he was before.
You mean Piccolo has good heart?
Perhaps he realizes it too.
My life- and thus Piccolo's life
-has only one more year left in it.
One more year?
Whether it's because
Piccolo will be killed
by the Saiyans that are
to arrive in another year,
or whether it's because that is when
my lifetime will run out, I do not know.
Kami-sama...
My death means death for Piccolo,
and Piccolo's death means death for me.
Even being Kami,
it is not a pleasant thing to know
the time when one's death will come.
He has to be sensing it too.
Maybe he just wants to leave
something of himself behind,
even if it is to Son Goku's son.
Then, possibility of
using Dragon Balls...
This next time will be the last one.
I'm scared!
Ee-yow!
Wait up!
You didn't have to go
around my neck like that.
I had no idea at all that Gohan
was as strong as all that.
He is my son, after all...
That's right! I don't have to run
along the entire road at all, huh?
All right then!
At this rate, I'll get there in no time!
That was close, that was close!
That's hell there beneath the clouds.
" Son Goku has...
unfortunately... been killed."
I wonder if the shock
will be too much like that.
" Um, I'm terribly sorry,
but Goku will not be returning,
and has entered his eternal sleep."
Then again, he is coming
back to life, huh?
That's it! I'll do it cheerfully! Yeah!
" Goku died, but he's coming back
to life right away, so don't worry."
Kuririn!
G- g- good afternoon.
What are you doing out here,
mumbling to yourself?
W- well, you see, um...
as it happens...
Heya! It's been a while!
G- good afternoon...
That's nice of you...
Aren't you together
with Goku-sa and the others?
Yeah, um, the truth is,
Goku has d- d- ...
...d- d- d-...
What?
...d- don't worry, he says!
What's that?
So he is goin' to be late?
Yeah, um, yes. The truth is,
the late Goku will not be returning...
He said he's not comin' home?
Er, no, he'll be
returning to us very soon...
I don't get what it is you're sayin'!
Now, now, it's no good
to stand here talkin' like this!
Come on in the house!
Come on, come on!
I can't wait to see
my grandson's happy face!
I ain't even seen him
in a over year now.
I bet he's gotten a lot bigger, huh?
l can't handle this. I can't tell them.
Not that he won't be back for a year...
Nobody's told me anythin',
so I called the Kame House earlier,
but nobody was there.
Y- yeah, come to mention it,
everyone's gone off to some
uninhabited island somewhere to play.
That must be it.
You wouldn't be able to reach
them there... would you?
But Goku-sa and them will
be back by nighttime, yeah?
Y- yeah... I suppose...
Goku-sa aside, Gohan has his studyin',
you know? He can't just skip it.
You know, Goku-sa can't
do anythin' as a parent!
Don't go gettin' so jumpy, Chichi.
This is Goku we're talkin' about.
He'll be sure to bring
him home. Just relax.
Really? You're right. Good.
They'll probably be comin' back hungry,
so I better go make some dinner.
Um...
I should be heading on back soon...
B- but why? You just barely
got here, didn'cha?
You could wait here until
Goku-sa and Gohan get back.
At least have some dinner first!
B- but I have things to attend to...
Look, don't worry, don't worry.
Mother!
Help! Somebody help!
I can't get down!
Come on, come on,
they're goin' to burn!
Eat up, eat up!
Before long, Goku will
be bringin' Gohan home!
I can't stand for this any longer!
Ogre spirits.
One crazy dancer drink.
Sure, sure...
Here's my check.
Thanks for coming.
Here's your change.
10,000... 20,000... 30,000...
40,000... I'm 10,000 short.
I beg your pardon.
H- how creepy!
...and so, he said he does not wish
to be brought back to life for one year.
I see. And I should tell
this to the Turtle guy?
Yes. Please be sure not to forget.
Goku is a curious one, huh?
He still wants to become stronger?
Damn... that guy lied to me!
He said I wouldn't get hungry,
but here I am, hungry!
I'm scared and cold!
I'm so hungry I could die!
Apples! Some apples fell down!
How lucky!
Oh well...
Yuck, they're sour!
I want some juice or something to drink!
I want to eat shao mai dumplings!
I want my mother's curry!
Dirty brat! Give me trouble, will you?
I'm scared!
Now listen, this is the last
time I lend you a hand..
From here on, if you
are unable to survive,
then that's all you're worth as a kid.
Exhausted, Son Gohan sleeps.
There's no way
he could have known
that one of his moments
of destiny was drawing near.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org