Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"Fear Me!! Freeza Does Battle With a
Third Transformation"
What?
DIE!!
G- Gohan!
Full power!
Hang in there, Gohan!
Thank you, Piccolo-san!
Quite strange. That little one should not
have such a battle power.
After recovering from near-death,
it is as if he is a different person altogether.
That's it! The little one is a Saiyan!
But whose child is he? Twenty years ago, with
the exception of Vegeta, Nappa and Raditz,
the Saiyans were supposed to have been
exterminated.
So whose is he?
He doesn't look like either Vegeta or Nappa...
So he's Raditz's child? There is something
there that reminds me of him.
T- That blast that just got bounced back...
You've gotten stronger, Gohan. I'm so glad.
But it was no use. I put everything I had into that,
and it still didn't connect against Freeza!
That brat...
He is indisputably drawing closer to
becoming a Super Saiyan.
You!
You must have figured it out!
After coming one step away from death,
when we Saiyans recover, our
strength increases!
Now listen! Before Freeza makes his final
transformation, you must render me half-dead!
Well? Do it now!
The blood of the Saiyans must be
completely cut off.
Not because I believe in ridiculous legends, such as
the Super Saiyan, history's greatest warrior,
but because I do not feel well with
them around.
It is the principle of it all, with the little
one and Vegeta growing stronger so quickly.
If I injure myself, there will be no
effect! You must do it!
B- But my power isn't enough to
bring you to near-death!
Don't worry. I'll lower my battle power as
low as it will go. Your power will be enough.
We're just lucky that Namekian kid down
there can heal people instantaneously.
No matter how much I may hate you,
how can I?
Besides which, it's just about time for Goku
to recover.
Kakarrot is a lowest-class warrior! He won't
get any stronger than that!
Very well.
It would be a simple matter to blow
you all to pieces in this current form,
but before I kill you, I will have you witness the terror
of an ultimate power, even more frightening than death!
Ultimate... what now?
H- How can it be?
I do you a great service! You will experience
a terror even greater than that of Hell's.
And so, gaze upon my final transformation!
My true form!
You rotten...
P- Piccolo-san!
If you do it now, there's still time. Hurry!
What!? What's wrong with this planet?
It's all over! I'm going to die here!
If I'd known Son-kun was coming, I could have
left searching for the Dragonballs up to him!
Gohan-kun is a fool! Kuririn is an idiot!
I hate you, Son-kun!
Freeza's Ki is rising again. Am I going
to get out of here in time?
Hurry up! This is the only way!
It can't be...
Dammit!
There's no other choice!
That's not good enough! You have to
shoot a stronger Ki!
Can't you even do that, you
good-for-nothing fool!?
T- That's good...
I'm at last going to become... a Super Saiyan...
W- Why did Kuririn-san shoot Vegeta?
G- Gohan! Get out of here!
Right!
Are you okay, Piccolo-san?
I can't say that I am...
I know! It's all right, we can heal those injuries!
There's a Namekian named Dende that can heal injuries!
I'll go get him.
Gohan!
Kuririn-san, where's Dende?
What!? You say you can't heal me?
T- That's right!
You're saying you could heal the
others, but not me?
You killed many of my friends as well!
I cannot heal someone like that!
Y- You brat! So long as you don't
heal me, Freeza will not be beaten!
I won't!
H- Hurry up... I'm starting to
lose consciousness...
I... I... I...
I'm going to save the other one.
Damn...
You... brat...
Vegeta and the other Saiyans gain a whole lot
of strength once revived from near death.
You knew that, didn't you?
Y- Yeah.
And so, he had me blast him on purpose.
It sounded like he was sure he could beat Freeza!
So that was why?
Dende!
Vegeta!
They said... you can heal injuries. Is that true?
Y- Yes!
Dende...
I see, so that's it!
Unbelievable! Do I have the same ability?
No. You, like Nail-san, are a warrior-type.
More importantly, Dende, I know how
you feel, not wanting to heal Vegeta.
For now, without him, there isn't anything
we can do!
He...
He's just like Freeza! He's also killed
so many Namekians!
Go heal him for me.
I can beat Vegeta now, but I can't
possibly beat Freeza.
What now? Freeza is...
He's finishing his transformation!
Ah, hell. All this time, we should have
masked our Ki and hidden somewhere.
If we had done something like that, he would just
blow us away, planet Namek and all!
He doesn't have any more use for this planet!
T- That is one impossibly huge Ki.
T- The incredible beast is about to appear!
Dende, please! Heal Vegeta!
Dende...
We can see him now!
You little turd!
You just be grateful that I didn't kill
you right here!
So that's Freeza's battle power?
Looks like he's revealed his true self.
Freeza, or anyone else, bring it on!
I have now become a Super Saiyan!
So this is Freeza? Such an incredible Ki!
At last, Freeza completes his
third transformation.
Is there any hope left for Gohan
and the others?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org