Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"The Curtain Rises Over the Ultimate
Battle!! I Am Going to Defeat You"
For all the Saiyans who were killed by you...
...as well as for the Namekians here...
I am going to beat you!
Such drivel.
It utterly sickens me how you worms can
share this consciousness among yourselves.
A worm is a worm.
Your legend will not be fulfilled.
I don't have anything to do with this
Super Saiyan stuff. Still...
I am going to defeat you!
How is the situation on Namek?
Vegeta has died.
W- What's that!?
Vegeta, did you say?
That's right. He was killed by
Freeza, and easily so.
Even though he served as Freeza hands
and feet, working exactly as ordered,
in the end he was betrayed and killed by
him. What a shame!
It was his pride as a Saiyan, I suppose.
So that's how terrifying a guy this
Freeza is, then?
They touched that which must not be
touched. That which must not be touched!
Damn it all! Not even Goku is a match
for a rat like that!
So, what about Goku?
He intends to fight. It seems that, no matter
what, he's determined to defeat Freeza.
Goku!
G- Goku...
He's got such power under wraps.
Goku, when did you find all that power?
I implore you, Son Goku, defeat him, and
give me another chance to challenge you!
You guys, get away from this place!
We're in the way here!
Gohan! Hurry up!
Gohan!
Father!
Father, don't die! Let Freeza have it!
- So fast!
- Father...
I get it. He can't sense Ki!
- Father!
- Gohan!
It's incredible! It's too incredible!
That got him for sure.
T- This is a Saiyan? So many of these
insects have overestimated their own
power, and defied me up until now.
I've never seen a Saiyan able to take
things this far!
Over there!
H- Has something happened?
D- Don't tell us Son has... ?
He's putting up a good fight.
These Saiyan are strange ones. Or perhaps
this is limited to Goku,
There's no limit to his strength. He's a
different person from when he trained here.
He really is impossible to understand, indeed.
- Such an unusual guy...
- Such an unusual guy!
Ah, that was good!
But it's no use. I can't walk any more!
I'm going to die here. Without ever
getting back to Earth...
...without anyone to watch
over me... quietly...
It's true what they say, beautiful women
do die young.
That's enough! Who would ever expect
me to die here among all these frogs!?
Oooh, yow.
Now, then...
He's not that bad...
You're an impudent one!
What's this?
l- It's an eruption! What's it doing there?
- Father!
- Gohan!
If you go, you'll just get in the
way. Have faith!
Goku isn't as green as all that!
- Father...
- Son...
That's far enough.
I wonder if he's burned up. What a
disappointing way to end the scene.
Goku!
Oh dear, you didn't have to come all
this way. I would have come to you.
I'll kill you quickly.
That was close, that was close!
If I'd fallen in there, I would've died!
Here goes.
Son!
Son! Behind you!
I'm not going to keep falling into the
same trap like that!
Don't go messing up other people's
planets so much!
What will you do once you break it!?
Frightening powers tear the land
and rend the sky.
However, Goku and Freeza display
nothing but confidence on their faces.
Is this decisive battle just getting underway?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org