Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I- it can't be!
Change!!
This is it! I can get
my own body back!
Let me get there in time!
What?
O- out of the way!
You bastard...
How dare you... interfere!?
Ow-ow-ow-ow...
Looks like I'm back to normal.
W- what happened? What the hell
did Kakarrot do just now?
What was that light?
Did Goku jump between them
in order to stop Vegeta's attack?
I can sense Father!
Father is... Father is back
in his own body!
What?
Are you sure, Gohan?
S- so then, that Ginyu bastard
is now over there?
Damn!
I'll Change with you for
sure this time, Vegeta!
I ain't going to let you!
What!?
Ka...
me...
That rotten Kakarrot...
ha...
me...
Ha!!
Damn, I've taken terrible damage...
I can't control my Ki...
Father!
G- Goku!
That was pretty stupid of you.
You won't get in
my way any longer.
T- this is bad! If we allow him to take
over Vegeta's body now... it's all over...
I'll take that body of yours!
Chan-
What!?
Impressive, Vegeta.
He's getting himself busted up,
just like he did against me.
He's planning on trading
places with Vegeta!
What's the matter?
Finished already?
That's right! You...
...are finished!
Stop, Vegeta!
You fell for it, Vegeta!
T- this is it.
Change!!
N- now what happened?
Ribbit... ribbit...
Ribbit... ribbit ribbit ribbit...
I- I did it!
G- Goku! Are you okay?
Father! Hang on!
Y- you really did quite a number...
on my body, didn't you, Vegeta?
Never mind that, explain to me
what happened to Ginyu.
That guy that ran away is a frog.
And that frog-looking thing
over there is now Ginyu.
What?
Ribbit... ribbit...
I don't know how you did it, but
I'm still going to mash you underfoot.
Leave him alone, Vegeta.
Now that Ginyu is like that,
he can't do anything.
Oh, all right, you can go.
I pity you when I think
of the life ahead of you.
Goku!
Father!
Hey, Goku, don't you have
a single Senzu left?
N- nope, I've really had it.
There's no reason why I couldn't vaporize
you bothersome guys right now.
What?
Vegeta, you dirty, lowdown...
I- it's all right.
He can't kill us just yet.
You're right. There's still
the matter of the Dragon Balls,
as well as the fight against Freeza,
and I'm going to need everyone's power,
especially yours, Kakarrot.
Come on.
W- where to?
Inside the spaceship.
Bring Kakarrot with you.
W- what are you going to do to Goku!?
I'm offering to heal him.
Why should we believe you!?
Fine, suit yourselves.
You can croak right alongside Kakarrot.
Damn it...
K- Kuririn-san...
K- Kuririn, it's all right.
It's all right?
Vegeta's enemy right now
is Freeza, not us.
B- but...
Let's go, Kuririn-san.
Hurry it up. We don't know when
Freeza will be coming back.
In here.
You go first.
This will treat Kakarrot's injuries
and restore him to full power.
W- with all this?
A needle!
N- no way!
I hate needles!
Let go of me, Kuririn!
I don't need any medical attention!
You think I would treat you with something
as uncivilized as a needle, you idiot!?
R- really?
Oh, Father, how pathetic!
Vegeta, what is this, anyhow?
It's called a Medical Machine.
In short, it's like a healing capsule.
By immersing oneself
in this special solution,
one's energy is restored to them
in a short amount of time.
So that's how...
After l've defeated Freeza,
l'll kill you guys nice and slow.
By that time, make no mistake,
l will be a Super Saiyan!
How about you speak to me, already?
Just telling me one simple
thing is enough.
How do I get the Dragon Balls
to grant my wish?
All you have to do is tell me that.
Y- you expect me... to tell you?
You do not need
to say anything else.
Well? Do you still want
me to continue this?
Up yours!
My apologies, Nail.
Bear it just a little while longer.
Very soon, Dende will arrive
at the Earthlings' location.
Please, allow my life to last
for at least that much longer.
J- just a little farther. Grand Elder-sama
said they were in the Maima region.
The Medical Machine in this room
is the older model,
but knowing Kakarrot, he should
be fully rejuvenated before too long.
The older model?
I destroyed the newer model.
H- he's not going to drown
or anything in there, right?
T- this sure feels good.
Now then, let's get you two
some battle wear.
You'll do better by them,
as far as protection goes.
Battle wear?
You mean like yours?
That's not how I want
to picture us.
Boy, their civilization
sure is ahead of Earth's.
It sure seems like it.
Take off your clothes
and put on that undershirt.
Hurry it up.
Freeza is coming.
Say, Gohan, if Vegeta feels
he needs even our help,
it must mean that Freeza
is awfully strong, huh?
It scares me.
Now for your battle jackets.
Luckily enough, there are some
smaller sizes here,
for use by those from
Planet Litt.
How do we put these on?
I can get my head through,
but my arms won't fit.
Just force them on.
Those are soft enough that if you pull
on them, they'll stretch.
Back on Earth, even when
I turned into a Great Ape,
my armor didn't break, remember?
Yet they can still stand
up to a shock pretty well.
Wow, you're right!
Are the gloves and boots
made of the same material?
I suppose.
This is incredibly light!
I barely feel any weight at all!
It's awful slimy of you guys
to be wearing stuff this nice.
What do you say, Vegeta?
Is something the matter?
I- it's nothing.
I wish I had armor more
like Vegeta's style.
The shoulder area seems a lot
easier to move around in.
This is an older type. There weren't
any that fit me in the regular sizes.
However, these don't seem to be in the way
at all, Kuririn-san. I can move freely!
Are you sure you're all right?
You don't need to
concern yourself about me.
Well, if you say so.
So, what about Goku? How long
will it take him to heal?
Good question.
Knowing him, he should be fully
healed in around 40 or 50 minutes.
Gohan, I'm going to go see
Grand Elder-sama.
I know that Freeza is probably there too,
but if we can't get the password
to summon Shen Long,
there's nothing we can do anyhow.
I- I'll go too!
No. I can handle this myself.
You wait here.
Goku and the others regroup,
preparing themselves for
the coming conflict with Freeza.
Who is it that will be able to summon
Shen Long from the still silent Dragon Balls?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org