Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Huh? When did I happen
to get down from that cliff?
Last night, I was looking
at the moon, and then...
And then, I don't remember anything.
Oh, well.
I need to wash my face.
Something sure is weird!
Huh? Wha-? Huh?
It's gone! My tail!
I wonder if it got pulled off
while I was asleep.
Huh?
My clothes have changed!
Huh? That's strange.
Don't come over here!
Huh? A sword?
Stay back!
Don't! I don't want
to do this, you know!
Why are they just after me!?
I don't taste very good!
Help!
Oh, I'm so hungry!
Ain't there anything to eat?
That's a picture of a vimana,
from the Nemurian civilization!
It's just like the one
that tried to catch me.
A 3-S Series prototype. This is
an incredibly old capsule robot.
Who's there? I was
sleeping so pleasantly.
I- it spoke!
Who is it that's there?
M- my name... is Son Gohan!
Don't talk so loudly. Sand will fall down
here at even the slightest vibration.
I'm Son Gohan.
Son Gohan...
Mister, what are you doing here?
That's no business of yours. Turn off
my switch and leave here at once.
Leave here?
There is an exit behind me.
All right!
I'm saved!
Wait! Turn off my switch before you go.
Sorry about that.
Thanks, mister.
Mister!
It's no good going that way!
Y- you fool!
Don't talk so loudly!
I can't get down from there.
Is that any of my concern?
But...
I told you not to turn on my switch,
didn't I? I wish to remain asleep.
But still...
Hurry up and go.
I can't get down from there! I'll die!
Don't cry!
Don't cry. That exit is the only one.
If you want to survive,
jump down from there.
You don't mean it!
Why are you acting like such a baby?
If you stay here,
you'll just be buried in sand.
Hurry up and go.
Are you gone?
Ah, Son Gohan! My switch!
Turn off my switch before you go!
He left without turning off my switch.
I'm just wasting my energy like this.
Mister?
Y- you're still there?
Mister, your visual sensors
are damaged, huh?
I'll fix them for you.
S- stop it!
Stop! Mind your own business! I don't
need visual sensors any more! S- stop!
Can you see now?
There's no point in you doing this.
Hmm, you're still a child, aren't you?
I'm surprised that someone like you
would be in a dangerous place like this.
Right, see? There's no way I could
jump down from that place, you see?
Unless you want to die here,
you should be able to.
But Mister, if you'd
just cooperate with me!
Do not turn to me!
And don't turn on my switch again.
You got that?
Now, turn off my switch, and then get
out of here. I wish to sleep quietly.
Hurry now, turn off my switch.
Mother...
Is it okay if I eat all of this?
I can still eat more and more!
Mister!
Wake up!
Again? I told you not to wake me.
T- there's a scorpion!
There's bound to be one
or two scorpions around.
I'm scared.
Turn off my switch. Don't make me
say the same thing over and over.
--But...
--Hurry up.
Oh, I am so hungry!
I wonder if I can eat these clouds.
It's me. I'm hungry.
Cut it out already. Don't turn on
my switch over such trivial things!
But...
There's no reason for there to be
anything to eat here, is there?
Scorpions and snakes are about all
the things you can eat around here.
Don't cry!
I'm hungry!
Don't use such a loud voice!
You'll be buried too.
A- all right, but just this once.
Let's see. At this time of year,
inside this cave...
Go search all the deeper corners.
Right.
Ah, I've eaten! I've eaten!
I found some, I found some!
All of this.
Then you don't need me anymore, right?
Turn off my switch.
But I can't eat these raw.
You won't be able to survive
in these plains like that.
Mister, you have a cooking system, huh?
I read so in a robot picture book.
You're a 3-S type all-purpose
capsule robot C-6, right Mister?
It says in my picture book
that you're quite a superior robot.
W- well, I guess so.
Shall I fry those up for you?
Open up my head.
Right.
Set it down inside.
--Close it.
--Right.
What kind of flavor do you want?
Chinese-style? Western-style?
My mother's style!
How should I know what that is?
It's done.
Yow-ow-ow...
Mister, it's too hot.
Am I to blame for that as well?
" I humbly accept this food."
How is it that you're
in this sort of place?
This is yucky.
I'm lost. I want to go back
to my mother's place,
but I don't know what I should do.
That is rough, huh?
It's not possible for a little kid
like you to cross the desert.
Having said that, it will be even harder
for you to live in this desert.
Mister, what is it
that brought you here?
An accident.
An accident?
It was an investigation
into excavating these ruins.
No sooner had I found this place than,
hmm, I ended up like this.
The ground around here is not very firm,
so earthquakes are constantly occurring.
I've been here in the sand ever since.
This Nemurian temple was
a great discovery, wasn't it?
How do you know about that?
It said so in a picture book.
Anyhow, there might be someone else
who comes searching the area
that helps us out, huh?
It's been eighty years now
since I've been buried in the sand.
Hey, what are you doing!?
I'm going... to get you...
out of here, Mister!
Stop that! I want
to stay with this city!
Mind your own business!
Leave me alone like this!
You can leave here together with me!
Don't worry about me.
I can store up energy and leap
out of here all at once. Stop!
I'm losing my balance!
Watch out!
Get out of here, quickly!
The cave is collapsing!
--But...
--Hurry and get to the exit!
You don't want to die, do you?
You come with me too, Mister!
That's all right. I will turn out okay.
I'm a superior 3-S type, after all.
Hurry and get going!
There, it's settled down.
Go now, while you can!
Don't cause me any more trouble!
Right...
Now, summon up your courage
and jump with all your might.
What's the matter? Son Gohan!
Jump! Jump, I say!
All right!
I have to turn off your switch!
You fool! Don't come back!
Mister!
Son Gohan...
It appears you're okay, right?
The exit has been blocked.
Son Gohan... listen to me...
Open up my head and connect
the blue wire to the red wire.
--Do it quickly.
--Right.
If you don't hurry,
the ceiling is going to come down!
Dammit, my energy is
beginning to leak out...
I've connected them!
Damn it all!
Mister!
Power at full!
Now, Son Gohan!
Mister!
Take care of yourself.
Mister!!
Mister!
Mister...
This is all my fault!
Son... Gohan...
Thank goodness!
You're still alive!
More or less. But it appears
that my energy is all used up.
Never mind about that,
hurry up and go on.
Mister!
Don't cry, even when you're all alone.
You can't rely on anyone else
around here if you're going to survive.
No!
Hush, would you? I can't
take any more. Be... quiet...
Mister?
Mister!
Wake up! Mister!
Mister, wake up!
Mister!!
Goku and Gohan- what sort
of adventures await them next?
The Saiyans are closing in
with every passing moment!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org