Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
A Ki! There's another unknown Ki
coming this way from over there!
Hide! Gohan! Bulma-san!
W- what, now?
Come on, hurry!
What in the world is it?
I'm always impressed by how
you guys know these things.
Shh! Keep quiet.
It's coming this way.
Could we have been discovered?
I don't know.
They're here!
T- they're gone.
Thank goodness. It looks like those
people weren't coming after us, huh?
B- but, what exactly
was that about just now?
What's the matter with you guys?
B- Bulma-san, could you check
something with the Dragon Radar?
W- what?
W- when you examined it before,
there were four Dragon Balls together, right?
What are they doing now?
All right, I'll check.
All four of them are moving.
Which means...
R- right, no doubt about it. Those guys
just now had the four Dragon Balls with them.
I- I knew it.
You don't say.
Gohan!
Yes?
Gohan, did you see him? The weird one,
flying second from the front?
Yes. I sensed an incredible
power from him.
The moment I saw him, I froze.
That guy might be even more
ridiculously powerful than Vegeta.
I- it looked like there were
some other amazing guys in there,
but that guy was in
a whole different league.
Stronger than Vegeta?
It couldn't be! Just who is he?
I- I don't know, but I think
he's one of Vegeta's pals.
They were all wearing
the same kind of outfits.
Dammit! How are we supposed to get
the Dragon Balls away from those guys!?
H- hey, look at this.
That group just now is heading
toward another Dragon Ball.
What's going on?
Do they have radar, too?
What's the location?
About 14 kilometers
in that direction.
That's where we sensed that Ki
Kuririn-san said could be Namekians!
I'm going to go over there
and see what's going on.
I'm going with you!
J- just a minute, now!
Are you planning on
leaving me here all by myself!?
It's a lot safer staying here
than moving around carelessly.
W- when you put it
that way, you're right.
Okay then, I'll put up a house with my
Capsules inside this cave and wait for you.
Okay, please do.
Come back soon, okay?
Remember, Gohan, keep your Ki
as suppressed as you can, but hurry.
You can do that, right?
Yes.
All right!
They're gone. I wonder
if they'll really be okay.
Oh, that's right!
I need to contact Earth!
Oh, okay, okay, okay...
Hello? Oh, Bulma... Yeah,
I was just heading to the hospital...
What?
Doctor, can't I have
your permission to train yet?
Are you still goin' on about that!?
I told you, bed rest is the best
thing for you right now.
If I don't start training soon,
my body is going to go soft.
How are you doing, Goku?
Old Timer!
Oh, Doctor, hello there.
Uh, is Chichi around, too?
Does me bein' here make
things inconvenient for you?
Oh, no, no, no,
I wouldn't say that...
I'm goin' to go do some laundry.
Ah, thank goodness.
As it happens, I just received
a message from Bulma and the others.
Not again!
Oh, my, no, what a naughty hand!
Sorry 'bout that.
So, are Gohan and them okay?
Ah, they did indeed arrive
on Planet Namek safely. However,
Gohan and the others weren't the only
ones who went to Planet Namek.
That Saiyan, Vegeta,
has gone there, too.
Vegeta!? He's there!?
That's not all.
In addition to Vegeta,
there are dozens of his buddies
there on Planet Namek.
Those guys wrecked the
spaceship they went there in,
so they can't get back to Earth.
W- what!?
What's more, at least one of them has a Ki
that's even greater than Vegeta's.
That can't be... Someone with a Ki
even greater than Vegeta?
Hey, you still alive?
What's this? After I went to all
the trouble of comin' here,
ya don't look to happy to see me.
The senzu beans're finally ready.
There's just a few of 'em, though.
But Karin-sama said
to take all seven of 'em.
Wow, all right! That's what you call
good timing! Hurry and let me have one!
N- now look, you, you can't go
giving strange foods to patients!
Here ya go.
I've been waiting for this moment!
Here it is, here it is. Kaio-sama
sent this new gi to me for just this day.
All right! I'm off to Planet Namek!
Oh, thanks. I'm taking
the rest of the senzu with me.
H- how are you planning
to get to Planet Namek?
When Bulma's daddy came
to visit me here earlier,
I asked him to make me
a spaceship, just in case.
A spaceship? You mean
like Kami-sama's?
That one was made from stuff
that ain't found on Earth,
so even Bulma's daddy
said he couldn't do that.
Well, then-?
When I thought hard about it,
I realized there were still two
Saiyan spaceships here on Earth.
The spaceship that my
brother came here in,
and the spaceship that I myself
came to Earth in as a kid.
T- that's right!
I had Bulma's daddy go looking for them,
and while my brother's was blown up,
mine was from long ago,
so it was still all right.
I'm having him repair and rebuild it.
Kinto Un!!
Okay, I'll be back later.
Um...
I'm off to Bulma's house!
Ah! Goku-sa!
Hey! Where are you goin'!?
Goku-sa!!
So, where's he going?
Hmm, well, as it turns out...
With things's bad as you're saying
they are, what's that guy so happy for?
I guess it has to be his Saiyan blood.
Of course, he wants to save everyone,
but more than anything, he seems thrilled
to be able to fight someone so strong.
That guy sure ain't normal, all right.
I can't take being around him.
Idiot. It's obvious he's got
zero chance of winning.
l can't believe it. How could there be
anyone even more incredible than Vegeta?
Gohan, your Ki is a little too strong.
Suppress it a little more.
Right.
Huh?
Goku-chan!
Ah, Bulma's mommy.
Oh, my, are you all better now?
As fit as you see me.
By the way, is the reconstruction
on the spaceship that I asked for finished?
Well, I'm not sure. It looked like
he was still working on something.
He ain't done yet?
That's a problem...
It's in the inner yard.
Let's go there.
You know, I never thought that little
Goku-chan would grow up to be so handsome.
Say, let's date sometime, okay, okay?
I- I have to beat that Saiyan
before I can do that...
You're so busy, aren't you?
Oh, right, I discovered this terribly
delicious cake shop not long ago,
and it's all thanks to you, Goku-chan.
If the earth had been lost,
I wouldn't have been able to eat
any of it. Thank goodness for that.
I guess so.
Dear, Goku-chan is here!
I- is this...
...my spaceship?
It's huge!
Oh, Goku, you're better already?
Yeah, thanks to a senzu.
This is mine, right?
Is it true it ain't finished yet?
Yeah, there's still a little bit
left on it. Well, come on in and see.
Okay, I'll go get us
something to drink.
Thanks.
This is incredible! I'm surprised
that teeny spaceship has become this.
Nothing to it.
Everything is as you ordered.
I can train just fine like this.
I took great pains. It was
hard to find your spaceship.
It was broken into
little pieces, you know.
Still, lucky for us,
the important parts were left intact,
but I had to rebuild most of it.
My spaceship was in pieces!?
That's strange. I wonder if
I busted it when I was a kid.
You know, this Saiyan science
is absolutely amazing.
Huh? Um, where is the artificial
gravity device thing?
Oh, this is it over here.
Wow, this thing, huh?
Let's see, this is the switch.
This is the controller.
As you ordered, it can generate
at most 100 Gs worth of gravity,
but even for you,
isn't that a bit reckless?
At 100 Gs, after all, if you weigh
60 kilos, that will become 6000 kilos.
That's six tons. Ordinarily,
that would kill you.
That's okay. If I don't train
someplace like that,
I won't be able to beat that Saiyan.
So, can't this thing fly yet?
It can fly anywhere you want to.
Even to the ends of the universe.
Huh? Then...
Uh, the bathroom, kitchen
and bedroom are down that ladder...
Say, then what still ain't done yet?
I can't quite settle on the placement
for the stereo speakers.
As long as you're listening to it,
you want it to sound good, don't you?
T- that's all!? When you say it ain't
finished, is that all you mean!?
" Is that all?"
When you consider reverberations
and everything, it's quite difficult.
I- I don't care where the stereo is placed!
I'm in a hurry here! I'll leave right now!
What are you in such a rush for?
We got a message from Bulma,
and anyhow, I just have to hurry!
Tell me how to make
this thing fly, quickly!
All right. Now, you're sure about
the placement of the stereo?
Uh-huh!
The data has all been input. All you have
to do is give the switch a little boi-oing,
and six days later, you will
arrive on Planet Namek.
Six days? I can get there
in just six days? That's awesome!
Is it true that Goku is here!?
Yes. He's looking at the spaceship
in the inner yard right now.
Huh?
Let's see... after that
comes this button, right?
Ho, for as hurriedly
as I put that together...
...it actually flew.
Huh? Where's Goku?
He left in a hurry.
I wonder if he's really
okay with the stereo...
Close... we're close. Cut your Ki
completely. Let's walk our way in.
Right.
They're on the other
side of that bluff.
What an incredible Ki!
This is bad! We've come up
right in front of them!
Let's move around
to the other side.
Right.
Those houses are just like
the spaceship that we came here in.
What are they doing?
Those other guys aside,
those three- especially the one in
the middle, riding in that round vehicle-
each have a terrifyingly strong Ki.
I can tell.
Look at what the two guys on
either side have in their hands!
They're Dragon Balls!
H- huge Dragon Balls...
Is something the matter, Dodoria-san?
No, there was just a slight power
reading coming from that cliff.
It is gone now, though. It must
have been a small animal or insect.
Y- yikes, yikes!
They very nearly spotted us!
Freeza-sama, we have
only found five of them.
The remaining others appear
to be out at the moment.
Get out here, now,
unless you want to die!
He looks just like Piccolo-san!
T- they're Namekians!
Wow, this certainly is fast.
Outer space sure is dark, huh? Or maybe
it's just nighttime out here right now.
Well, never mind. I've got
to start training right away.
I'm glad it's only going to
take six days to get there,
but I've got to surpass
that Vegeta guy before then, too.
Let's see, as I remember,
Kaio-sama said that his world
had 10-times gravity, didn't he?
For the time being, I guess I should
get used to around 20 times.
It's working, all right!
At last, Goku had
blasted off into space.
However, the Dragon Balls were falling
into Freeza's hands, one after the next.
ls Goku's power
about to be unleashed?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org