Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Oni?
Something's coming oni.
Watch out oni! Stop oni!
I thought he had fallen off
the Serpentine Road earlier oni.
Be that as it may, it looks like
he's a lot faster this time oni-
Aaa oni!!
Uncle Piccolo is awesome!
Well, with this many of us members here,
I'm not at all afraid of those Saiyans.
I can't wait to see what kind of
training Kami-sama puts us through.
Thanks to my eating that fruit,
I've already come this far in a flash.
What's that?
I wonder if this is
Kaio-sama's residence.
What is this!? What is this!?
Welcome to our lobby, honored guest!
Snake Princess-sama, we have a visitor.
What? A visitor?
My!
Such a handsome gentleman!
He's just my type!
The Snake Princess-sama approaches!
Then Kaio-sama, you're...
...a woman? You're cute, huh?
Cute, you say?
Such a gallant gentleman! For some reason,
my heart is all a-flutter!
The Snake Princess-sama
hasn't been this worked up
since Great King Yama-sama, has she?
Yes! He was quite handsome too!
It's been nearly five
hundred years, I'll bet.
F- five hundred years!?
Well, no matter. Never mind that,
Kaio-sama, teach me some martial arts.
M- martial arts?
How about instead,
we dance the tango?
This is so romantic! Surely we
were destined to come together.
The tango is a lot like the
dance we did at my wedding.
So this is Kaio-sama's
martial arts technique.
I get it! This is a technique to
get your opponent off their guard,
then clobber them!
--Ee-yow!
--Kaio-sama is a lot weaker than I thought...
What are you doing!?
She is not Kaio-sama!
This is the Snake Princess-sama,
who shone in the glory of victory
at the Other World Beauty Contest!
What? You ain't Kaio-sama?
I'm leaving.
G- goodness, no!
Please wait!
I'm in a hurry!
A- at least have dinner before you go.
D- dinner? Come to think of it...
...I ain't eaten anything since that piece
of fruit. I guess I'll eat before I go.
I'm so happy! Okay, okay, you guys,
quickly prepare something for dinner!
--Right!
You guys understand, right? We'll do
whatever it takes to keep that man here!
After all, he's the kind of nice man
we haven't had for five hundred years.
I won't have him get away from us!
Snake Princess-sama, if I mix this
sleeping potion in with the cooking,
it will bring on an
irresistible urge to sleep,
he'll doze off,
and won't leave here!
Well, it's not a very elegant method,
but what choice do we have?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
We have foie gras,
made from the bird of paradise,
sauté of bear's paw,
from Needle Mountain,
baked crocodile, taken from the
River Sanzu, and mussels au gratin.
Let's dig in!
Yes, yes, be my guest!
Help yourself to as much as you like.
All right, I'm eating!
I- if you like, help yourself
to my serving as well.
Really? Thanks!
Okay, then... I'll take it...
I'm full, I'm full!
Well then, I guess I should go.
Please, wait!
Are you not sleepy?
I ain't got time to sleep. I've got
to go meet Kaio-sama and everything.
You're sure you put
the sleeping stuff in, right?
Yes, plenty of it.
Thanks for dinner.
Okay then, I'm going.
You guys!
Please, wait. We have a bath warmed up.
How about if you took a bath before going?
Kaio-sama dislikes dirty people.
Yeah, maybe I am a little sweaty.
Maybe I should freshen up before I go.
--Yes, yes!
This feels great.
How is the water?
Fine. It's a little bit hot,
but it's okay.
This originally comes from
the steam baths of hell.
He should be warmed
clear through to the bone!
Okay.
Huh? Suddenly it's become night.
Goku-sama, there are so many stars.
To think that I should be together with you
on such a wonderful evening, Goku-sama,
it makes the Snake Princess so happy...
Say there, Goku-sama?
Goku-sama?
Oh, my...
T- this is terrible!
He's been boiled alive!
98... 99... 100!
Oh, that's refreshing!
How embarrassing! But still,
what a manly figure he has.
Wow, that was revitalizing!
Okay then, I'll be going.
Ah, wait!
Hey you guys, stop him!
--Just a moment!
--What is it? I'm in a hurry!
I have to hurry and see Kaio-sama,
and learn martial arts from him!
In that case, then we have
just the thing! How about this?
A thrilling, spine-tingling
game of Russian Roulette!
You can help train your mind
to overcome fear with this!
Russian Roulette?
How does it train your mind?
First, you take one bullet
and place it into the pistol.
Then you spin it round and round.
The chances of the bullet
being shot are one in six.
When it does,
that's the end of the story.
It's a game brimming with thrills,
in exchange for one's life!
That ended all too easily, huh?
I ain't doing anything that dangerous.
Thank you for waiting!
It is now showtime!
Yes, yes, please leave after
you've watched this show!
Is this martial arts too?
Yes! It is a new martial art.
Snake Princess-sama,
this time I made sure to use
all the sleeping potion we had left.
Make it good.
Here, have some specially prepared juice.
Wow, thanks.
Yummy!
For this guy to have eaten and drank
that much sleeping potion and still be alive-
what is he, a monster?
We did it! He should be asleep
for three days and nights like this!
He's pretty tough, huh?
Yes. He is no ordinary person.
But you know, he has such
a lovely face when he's asleep.
He really is my type.
Chichi... Gohan...
He's having some kind of dream.
Bring the dream-viewing mirror.
Right.
This will reflect whatever
dream he is having.
Chichi... Gohan...
--Father!
--Goku-sa!
What's this?
A woman and a boy?
Ah, apparently they
are his wife and child.
He's not single!? He still
looks delicious, though!
Are you going to eat this one too?
I wonder if there will be
any for us this time.
After all, the only one to get out of here
safely has been Great King Yama.
Good, Gohan!
Once you've finished doin' those drills,
your studyin' is done for today.
Mm-hmm. I want to hurry up
and go out and play.
W- who are you!?
I'm scared! Father!
Goku-sa!
Gohan!
Chichi!
Oh, it was a dream, was it?
Did I fall asleep?
He's awake already, isn't he?
Yeah...
That's right! I was on
my way to see Kaio-sama!
Please, don't go!
Sorry, but I'm going. Everyone on
earth is waiting for me to come back.
You're going, no matter what?
Yeah, no matter what.
Why, you-!
I am the Serpentine Road Goddess,
who has lived on the Serpentine Road
for a thousand and five hundred years!
How dare you bring disgrace upon me!
Now listen to me! You will
never return home from here!
What is this?
If you cannot realize my charms,
then you can just dissolve away!
This is bad! I've got to
get out of here quick!
Dammit...
That was close!
Why, you-!
You're not getting away!
Damn! In that case...
Ka... me...
No, I won't. She did feed me
all that food, after all.
Hey, let me pass!
I have to hurry and go see Kaio-sama!
No way! If you want to live,
you'll have to defeat me!
Damn... I know!
Wait up!
See you! Thanks for the meal!
And the bath, too!
This is so degrading!
The journey to Kaio-sama is still far.
The Saiyans' assault is drawing near.
Hurry, Goku! Run the length
of the Serpentine Road!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org