Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"Such Regret... ! Vegeta, Pride of
the Saiyans, Dies"
Damn...
Piccolo-san!
All right, they're very close. My
apologies, I'm coming now!
Something might just become of this!
How dull. You've utterly lost the
will to fight back.
It's a little soon, but maybe I
should finish you off.
So then, the identity of that huge Ki
was Piccolo after all.
S- Son!
Nice. You were brought back here
with the Dragonballs, huh?
Father!
Are you all right now?
Yeah. Thanks to you guys, I've
recovered from all that damage.
You've stuck it out well, Gohan!
Leave it up to me now.
What!?
Leave it up to you? What, are you planning
on taking that freak on by yourself?
Yep.
Father!
Are you really Goku? There's something
different about the way your
Ki has felt up until now.
S- Son!
Is that Son? He's got an unbelievable
strength of Ki.
There's no comparison to
when he was on Earth.
So you're Freeza?
You're much more of a runt
than I'd imagined.
So there's still another one of you scum left?
Vegeta has promised to fight with
me. Don't you interfere!
You... It's like I've seen you before...
K- Kakarrot, it's you...
K- Kakarrot? But that name is Saiyan.
It's him!
Freeza! Get out here!
I won't let you get away with this!
He looks just like that last Saiyan who
opposed me when I destroyed planet Vegeta.
I won't let a single one of you Saiyans live.
Don't you see, you would do well
just to tremble before me.
Maybe so.
H- He's not the same Kakarrot as before...
He's at last climbed over the
wall of his limitations...
W- Which means...
Are you ready, then?
Yeah.
W- What was that? Did Goku
just do something?
Unreal!
Not even I could see that clearly.
He's exceeded Freeza's speed!
Oh, no! Get out of the way, Goku!
It can't be! He deflected every one of
them, and with just one hand!
Freeza, you'd better fight like you mean it!
H- He's the very thing you fear most...
A Super Saiyan!
That's right! The strongest warrior
in the universe, a Super Saiyan!
Freeza, you're finished now!
Serves you right!
Vegeta!
You knew, Vegeta, that I hate such
petty jokes, didn't you?
Vegeta!
Hey! Vegeta was in a state where
he couldn't even move!
There was no reason to finish
him off on purpose!
The Super Saiyan is nothing more
than a frivolous legend.
He wouldn't stop going on about it.
I hate it when people get tedious.
- K- Kakarrot...
- Vegeta!
Are you... still reciting that soft crap?
Are you not a Super Saiyan!?
Wait!
You foolish scum! Get cold-hearted!
If you had only discarded your leniency,
you would surely already be...
...a Super Saiyan!
I just don't see how I could act as
cold-hearted as you do.
And as for this Super Saiyan business,
I don't know what you mean.
A- A Super Saiyan is...
How wonderful! Look at it, Zarbon-san,
Dodoria-san! Behold such beautiful fireworks!
L- Listen well, Kakarrot...
And here I've pierced his heart.
What nerve. Are you going to keep talking?
Your... our planet of birth, Planet Vegeta...
was not destroyed... in a collision with a
giant meteor...
Don't say any more! You're just
hastening your death!
Freeza did it... !
This after we Saiyans... served as his
hands and feet... working exactly as
he ordered... !
Everyone besides us was killed... !
Your father... and my father,
the king, as well... !
Freeza... was afraid that as the Saiyans
gathered strength...
a Super Saiyan would be born among us...
Just listen to you.
Vegeta!
l- I beg you... ! Freeza... defeat Freeza... !
Please... by your Saiyan hand...
Vegeta...
Has he finally croaked? Well, shall we
reconvene this Show of Terror, then?
For you to cry...
For you to beg of me, must have been
awfully difficult, I bet.
I understand. It wasn't that your fellow
Saiyans had been killed that was
rough on you-
Having to do as he told you must have
been worse than anything you could stand.
I hated you so much...
...but you had your Saiyan pride.
And now I too will share in some of
that pride of yours.
I am a Saiyan raised on Earth!
For all the Saiyans who were killed by you...
...as well as for all the Namekians here...
I am going to beat you!
Such drivel.
Son Goku opens his eyes to his Saiyan pride.
Just how great is his terrible anger?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org