Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Don't you die, Goku.
Father...
That guy's intense.
It's no use. This is all over.
It's not like I'm
desertin' ya, though.
There's just nothin' I can do.
Don't go holdin' it
against me, 'kay?
Suffer good and long,
and then die!
It's close!
We're almost there!
Even though it's the evening, because of
that strange light, it's as bright as this.
W- what the hell is that thing?
K- Kuririn-san, o- over there!
Get down, Gohan!
Get down, and hide!
W- what is that?
Hurry up, you stupid twit!
Ah, it's those guys.
lt can't be... He's turned
into a Great Ape!
Feels like most of your bones
just broke, huh? Does it hurt?
Goku is getting
done in! This is bad!
This way!
Right!
Hey!
Yajirobe!
Hey, who d'ya think that monster is?
It's the Saiyan, I tell ya, the Saiyan!
I know.
There's no way you can stand up
to that monster, you know! Give it up!
I know that, too. But if we cut off
his tail, he'll return to normal.
His tail?
Listen up.
Gohan and Yajirobe, you guys circle around
in front of him, and get his attention.
I'll find an opportunity
to cut off his tail from the back!
Hurry! Goku is going to die!
R- right.
Y- ya gotta be kiddin' me.
Get his attention, did'ja say?
You guys don't even know!
Even after he's back to normal,
he's still gonna have unbelievable strength!
Father, don't die!
Goku's Ki is almost completely gone!
Dammit, he's moments from death!
Eh, do whatever you wanna.
There's something out there.
Where is it?
Over here!
L- let my father go!
This is a surprise.
If it isn't Kakarrot's kid.
I get it. So you've come here just to
see your father meet his end, have you?
You've got good timing.
He was just about to die.
I was right about to finish him off.
Kienzan!!
Damn it all...
Watch very closely. I'm going to
crush him until there's nothing left.
Kuririn-san, hurry!
Unfortunately, it appears he has
already lost consciousness.
I- i- it can't be!
Did you think I wouldn't notice
that there was another one of you?
You guys seem to share some worthless
attachment for each other, after all.
There's no way this kid would just
come strolling back by himself,
so I was just waiting
to see what would happen.
Apparently, you know about
our tails. Too bad for you.
Just you wait. Once I've taken care
of Kakarrot, it will be your turn next.
D- damn! What kind
of beast is this?
Even after turning into a monster,
he still has his presence of mind
and his guard is flawless.
l'm sorry, Goku. I don't
want to just let you die,
but this guy's Ki is so incredible,
l can't even get close to him.
You guys were mistaken
to have challenged me to battle!
Dammit! If we don't do something...
Stop...
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
So, you want to die
ahead of your father, do you?
T- this is bad!
What's the matter?
Too scared to move?
Dammit! I didn't know
there was yet another one!
My tail!
H- he did it!
I got nothin' to do with this...
I- I got nothin' to do
with this from here on...
I- it's gone!
His tail is gone!
You did it, Yajirobe!
He returned to his original form!
lt's not my problem... Whatever
happens now, it's not my problem...
W- why, you!
You want to die so badly
that you've made me angry!?
W- what's going on?
Why did that monster-?
In that case, as you wish,
I will kill you, you miserable scum!
There, ya see?
Gohan! Get out of there!
I'll start with you.
What's the matter? Wasn't a Super
Saiyan supposed to be strong?
Show me your true power.
Maybe the order
has been changed.
There, you see?
Don't say I didn't warn ya.
Come on, get up! Amuse me
a little while longer.
Hey, what's wrong?
Is that the best you can do?
I guess the son of scum...
...is scum, as well.
You may be scum, but it looks
like your blood is red, at least.
How awful!
How can he be
so cruel to a child!?
She's strangely tranquil, huh?
I'm sure she must have
run out of tears.
She hasn't fainted,
has she? Hey!
Hey!
Ee-yow!
--Yow! Yow! Yow!
--Fight...
Fight.
Fight! Fight, Gohan! Fight!
Avenge your daddy's death!
Get up, Gohan! Fight, Gohan! Fight!
How about I at least let you die
next to your father? I'll be kind.
G- Gohan...
Oh? Kakarrot, you're a tough one.
You're still conscious, are you?
Gohan, can you hear me?
Gohan, your daddy's whole body
is a mess. I can't move anymore.
Fight in my place. His power
should have dropped considerably.
I- I can't, Father!
He's too strong! I can't beat him!
All right, I'll do it this way-
I'll follow my order, and kill Kakarrot first.
Next will be Kakarrot's kid.
After that, I'll finish off
that bald bastard from earlier.
Finally, I'll kill the bastard
who cut off my precious tail!
He remembered me, huh?
You don't have to beat him...
Just keep him bottled up...
Your power should be even more
incredible than his... even more...
While you're doing that,
I'll have Kuririn finish him off...
I can't! I can't even
move anymore!
You stupid jackass! Do you want
everyone else's deaths to be in vain?
What did Piccolo teach you?
I'm counting on you, Gohan...
For left-behind scum, you're sure
giving me a lot of trouble!
G- Gohan!
What's the matter!? Eh!?
S- stop... that...
Die!
Stop... that!
What's the matter?
Die! Die!
Stop that!!
What!?
I'm going...
...to defeat you!
You are going to defeat me?
What the!?
Kuririn!
Kuririn, please!
Come here!
D- dammit...
Don't you mess around
with Vegeta-sama!
G- Goku, it's hopeless.
He's just too terrible.
Why didn't you tell Gohan to run away?
I'm going to give this
to you now, Kuririn...
The Genki Dama that I gathered
from all over the earth...
Eh? What did you say?
What are you going to give me?
A- a Genki Dama... Ki that I've
collected from everything on earth...
About half of it got away, but I think
it will still defeat him, the way he is now...
W- what?
Kuririn... take my hand...
I don't understand this at all.
Hurry! Gohan is going to die!
I just have to take your hand?
Please...
Like this?
Your bones are broken, aren't they?
That's okay... Don't let go...
I'm giving it to you now,
so take it...
W- w- what is this?
I- it's awesome... This is
a tremendous amount of Ki!
Turn your palm upward, and focus it...
You can make it into a ball...
You dirty brat!!
Hang in there...
Gohan ain't able to control
this kind of Ki...
I- it came out!
Is this-?
A Genki Dama...
You did it!
You're a pesky brat!
Kuririn... hit him with it...
I can't make another Genki Dama...
M- make sure you hit him! Please!
U- understood.
I'll try.
Will the Genki Dama that has been entrusted
to Kuririn be able to put a stop to Vegeta?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org