Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Do you want to die!?
Yow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
Wait!
Don't forget that your
opponent wants to kill you!
I know, Piccolo-san...
Nyah-nyah!
Is that all the jumping
power you've got?
You're even softer than your father.
Well now, shall I finally
put you out of your misery?
Die, Kakarrot!!
S- stop picking on...
... my father!!
That little brat!
Wake up... Kakarrot...
What are you doing over there?
Wake up...
Wake up... Kakarrot...
You little brat!
What the hell has gotten into you!?
Damn!
Why, you-!
You dirty brat!
What's the matter?
Nowhere left to go!
H- his tail!
That's it, all right...
It was half a year ago
that I pulled it out.
And now it has grown back.
Which means... it can't be!
How can this be?
You little brat!
Die!!
Wha-?
What!?
A- at this rate, I'm done for!
Begone!
What!?
What's up with that moon!?
Cheers!
My, my, we've finally
gotten them together.
Now we'll be able to
bring Goku back to life.
We can take a breather now, too.
Now all we have to do is wait
for those infernal Saiyans.
You say that, but originally,
when Goku was a baby,
he was a Saiyan too,
who was sent here from Planet Vegeta
in one of those round vehicles, right?
N- no he wasn't! That might
be the way he was born...
...but Son-kun is an exemplary Earthling.
Right, Turtle Hermit-san?
Er, of course he was.
What's the matter?
The moon is out.
Oh, you're right.
It's been a while, huh?
Something about that moon...
Don't get too carried away,
you dirty brat!
T- that's Saiyan blood
you've got, all right.
The power l've got right now won't
do any good against the Saiyans.
Let go of me!
Dammit!
Damn...
Dammit! At this rate, the earth is
going to be destroyed by that brat!
W- what's that?
Wake up... Kakarrot...
So that's it.
The thing that's behind that moon...
...is the pod that Son Goku
came here in as a kid.
It's all over now!
Sorry about that.
I'm going to make sure that I draw out
those dormant abilities of yours.
Geez, you sure are a lot of trouble.
A tail!
Hooray! I'm there!
Huh?
There ain't anything here.
You've got to be kidding me.
What's that?
He's there! That's where Kaio-sama is!
This is it, all right.
There's his house.
What!? What!?
What's wrong with the ground?
Dammit!
Incredible... It's like I'm being
sucked in by some outrageous power!
I- it's no use! It feels like my body
is as heavy as lead! Dammit!
I've finally... reached... here...
and I'm going... to meet
Kaio-sama... no matter what!
A little farther...
a little farther...
But before that,
let's find me something to eat.
K- Kaio-sama?
Are you Kaio-sama?
Despite how he looks,
l'm sure he must be incredible.
G- good day. I'm Son Goku.
I ask that you train me.
Kaio-sama, before we do,
can I ask you for an apple?
Wow, Kaio-sama, impressive!
You climbed up there easily!
Kaio-sama, sorry, but pick me
another one. I'll catch it this time.
All right, whenever you're ready!
I caught it! I caught it!
Kaio-sama, teach me martial arts,
okay- I mean, please?
Is that training?
You're saying I should
move like that, right?
This is definitely hard...
K- Kaio-sama, what's the matter
with the ground here?
What are you doing?
ls this curious man the real Kaio-sama?
When does Goku's training begin?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org