Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Wow, this truly is amazing.
The universe really is a big place.
To think that there's a genius
even greater than myself out there...
This is no time to be admiring it, Dad.
Check it out as fast as possible, okay?
Okay, okay.
So anyway, this is an incredible spaceship.
It took us to Jupiter, just like that!
Really, it was amazing!
Huh? Sweet olives?
What's wrong with your nose?
No! Jupiter! Jupiter!
Anyhow, once we finish up here,
we're taking off, so get everyone together!
I'm counting on you!
Nah, it's nothin'.
Here.
I've had enough.
No you haven't! You've got to eat,
and recover from your injuries, quick.
Okay.
We've done it, Goku!
Cheer up! Word is, we've found a spaceship!
We can go to Planet Namek!
Piccolo and Tenshinhan and the others
will be coming back to life for sure!
Is that right?
Good work.
I splurged, and bought this many! See?
G- Gohan-chan?
Where did he go!?
What's wrong?
Gohan-chan isn't here.
Huh? He was there reading
his book just a little while ago.
He shouldn't even be able
to walk properly yet...
What if he breaks a bone!?
She's making too much of it.
35...
36...
37...
38...
That was close, that was close...
Gohan-chan!
Where could Gohan-chan have gone?
His legs haven't healed,
so he couldn't be up walkin'...
All righty...
That should be okay.
Gohan-chan!
What are you doin'
in a place like this!?
Mother... It was such a nice day,
I thought I would read my book outside.
Don't be so rash!
Come on, I'll carry you
back to the room.
I- I'm completely okay now...
That carelessness of yours
is dangerous. Come on, get on.
Good grief, you're so reckless.
Who are you takin' after?
What that all means is,
the spaceship is absolutely okay!
In that spaceship, you'll be able
to get to Planet Namek in just one month!
All that's left is to remodel
the interior a little.
I'd say you can
leave in five days.
That's right.
To Planet Namek in Kami-sama's
spaceship, huh? Amazing!
That glimmer of light
looks like it's becoming reality.
And so, Popo-san, it's all up to you
to go to Planet Namek for us.
Mister Popo not going.
Mister Popo can't go. Be away from
Kami-sama's palace two months. Can't.
Oh, no! But you're the only one
who knows how to speak Namekian!
You also seem pretty tough. Popo-san,
you have to be the one who goes!
No worry.
Teach you Namekian.
Well, Bulma-san, you'll have to go.
If anything were to happen, you're the only one
familiar with the mechanics, Bulma-san.
Fine, then. It doesn't
sound all that dangerous.
I'll have to build in
a shower room, too...
...and a more comfortable
bed, and a stereo...
But there's no way I'm going by myself,
okay? Someone come with me!
I'm tellin' ya right now,
there ain't no way I'm goin'.
Nobody was expecting you to.
Ahem...
Two months round trip, huh? All right,
I guess I've got no choice but to go with you.
That will just add
unnecessary danger!
I knew it.
Son-kun is in this state and all...
Kuririn, you'll come with me, right?
M- me? That's okay and all,
but for two months? I wanted to train...
You never know when that
Saiyan will be coming again.
Nice for you.
I wanted to go, too.
I wanted to see what kind of Shen Long
would appear on Planet Namek.
Well, Goku, you stay here and rest up,
and come up with a strategy
against the Saiyan, or something.
Yeah, right. We'll be
counting on the both of you.
U- um...
What's the matter?
Have to go potty?
P- please take me, too!
G- Gohan-chan! W- what kind
of silly joke is that?
It's not a joke!
I- I really want to go...
D- don't be absurd! It'll take two more
months, on top of everythin' else!
I'm sorry. I want to go,
no matter what.
I want to be the one who brings
Piccolo-san back to life myself.
So that's it.
Well said, Gohan.
What kind of nonsense
are you two talkin'!?
There's no reason for Gohan-chan
to be doin' any of this!
What if anythin' were to happen!?
For cryin' out loud,
he hasn't even healed enough!
We'd better stand back.
As far as my body goes, I'm fine.
W- what are you doin'!?
S- stop that, Gohan-chan!
I beg you, please take me.
I won't stand for this!
I absolutely won't stand for this!
It's two months! On top of the year
of anxiety I've already been through!
What about cram school?
What about your lessons!?
You've already fallen
way behind the other children!
Piccolo's got nothin'
to do with anythin'!
You are a little child,
and you should act like a child!
Shut up!!
Gohan-chan... you've
turned into a delinquent!
M- Mother... right now... right now really
isn't the time to be talking about that.
We all fought desperately
to save everyone on earth,
and we have to bring
those who died back to life,
to fight against
the Saiyan once again!
I can... I can fight, too!
I have to... I have to do something!
Understand, Mother.
I'm sorry.
That kid says some pretty
awesome things once in a while.
He's got you beat, Chichi.
Now let Gohan go off
into space willingly.
Gohan, nice going.
You really have grown stronger.
It's okay, I tell you.
He'll be completely fine.
Let us take care of him.
There won't be anything dangerous
this time around, after all.
Can you learn Namekian in five days?
Right, we'll have to input it all
into a translator device,
so... let's see,
we'll need ten days.
All right, let's meet up
ten days from now at Kame House!
Right!
" Good day" is " Pikonatto."
" Pikonatto," huh?
All right, you're fine.
Yow!!
You don't need to bother...
Oh, no! If you say that,
girls aren't goin' to like you.
Time for your medicine already.
Oh, water, water...
Hit me.
All right!
Don't hold back!
Hit me as hard as you can!
Right.
Good. If you can hit that hard,
you'll be fine, Gohan.
You'll do a great job
of standing in for me.
And so, in the blink of an eye,
ten days went by,
and the day of launch had come.
Whoo! Can we really get
to Planet Namek in this thing?
Well, don't you look sharp, Kuririn?
You're not, by any chance,
making light of outer space, are you?
I even cut my hair, because it would be
in the way inside my space suit!
Well? Isn't Gohan-kun here yet?
He'll be coming really soon,
from the hospital.
He hadn't been discharged yet?
No. Chichi-san insisted that he
remain up until the last minute.
Good grief, she's so overprotective.
Say, Bulma-san...
Do you think we should take umbrellas?
Planet Namek won't necessarily
have nice weather.
Suit yourself.
Oh, looks like they're here.
Sorry we're a little late.
So this is the spaceship, huh?
It's somethin' else!
Okay, Gohan-chan, make sure
you're careful as you go.
What's the matter?
Come on out.
Make sure you brush
your teeth after meals.
Is that really you, Gohan?
What happened to your hair?
F- Father laughed at me, too.
Whatever else you might say, this is
the first time man is goin' to outer space.
We don't want to be ill-mannered.
Uh, what is all that?
This is his change
of underwear and study gear...
this is two months' worth
of his medicine and vitamins...
his dryer...
his brush... his bowl
and chopsticks... also-
T- that's enough.
Well, shall we get going right away, then?
For some reason, I'm feeling discouraged.
We're depending on you. Make sure
you find the Dragon Balls for us.
Right!
" Piccolo"
Grandpa, Mother, Turtle Hermit-san,
Turtle-san, we're off. Take care.
" Piccolo"
Make sure to eat all your meals!
Send me a letter every day!
Bye!
This is a little exciting, huh?
Say, Bulma-san,
where should I put my bag?
You can stick it wherever you need to,
can't you!? Hurry up and sit down!
She's in a bad mood
for some reason.
Five seconds to launch!
Destination: Planet Namek!
J- just a minute!
4...
3...
2...
1...
W-w-we still haven't
f-fastened our b-b-belts!
It's too late to stop now, you know!
T- that truly is some tremendous speed.
They're out of sight already.
Gohan-chan!
Be sure to rinse, too!
You can move about freely now.
Once we're out of the atmosphere,
everything calms down.
Eh? Already?
I wanted to see Earth.
Huh? What are you doing, Bulma-san?
How nosy!
I'm changing my clothes!
You're changing? You mean, into pajamas?
You're going to bed already?
Whoops, come to think of it,
I forgot to bring pajamas myself.
What about you, Gohan?
I made sure I brought some.
I know it's none of my business,
but can't you do anything
about that Shichigosan outfit?
This is just for the first part.
I actually have some clothes that I made
without Mother finding out about it.
Well?
You really do look up
to Piccolo, don't you?
Yes. About the same as I do Father.
Huh? T- those are unusual pajamas, huh?
They look hard to sleep in.
Of course they're not pajamas!
When I saw you guys,
I felt like an idiot for working so hard
getting ready to go into space.
Hey, did we do something wrong?
Search me.
Good luck, Gohan.
The trio had departed for Planet Namek,
carrying the hopes of Goku and the others...
...with no way of knowing
the incredible terror that awaited them.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org