Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Gohan! Don't take your
eyes off of theirs!
R- right!
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Right!
Gohan, don't lose your nerve!
R- right!
This time, shall we
take the fight to them?
Kuririn!
Tenshinhan!
Chaozu, you're here, too?
Mm-hmm!
Weren't there only
supposed to be two Saiyans?
Well, a lot has happened.
It looks like there are more of them.
However many there are,
it's all the same.
Is that him? Goku's son?
Yeah. He appears to have been
trained quite a bit by Piccolo.
He's got a fine look to him.
What shrimps...
Saibaimen, make them all suffer!
Just a minute!
Kuririn, sorry I'm late.
Yamucha-san!
I guess we're all here, except for Goku.
Yeah!
1... 2... 3... 4... 5... 6, huh?
Interesting. The exact number
of Saibaimen that we have here.
Yes, it is.
How about you all take turns
fighting each one of our soldiers?
It will be a game.
A game!? Ridiculous!
Stop beating around the bush
and let's settle this right here and now!
Now, now, where's the harm? It works out
better for our side to do it this way.
Goku hasn't arrived yet, after all.
Very well.
I'll lead off.
Now, come and get it!
He's going to be bowled over once he
realizes how strong the Saibaimen are!
So, which one of you is going to face me?
You go first. Hammer him with
all you've got. Understood?
T- Ten-san, good luck!
We're going to start reporting
from above the scene now...
Whoa! Those are the Saiyans!
The Saiyans!
Noisy mosquitoes!
Okay, Saibaiman!
Don't hold back! Crush him!
These Saiyans appear to possess
tremendous power. Is everything all right?
You idiot! 'course
everything ain't all right!
L- like I said, my boys're fightin'
with 'em for your sakes right now!
--Who do you mean when you say " my boys" ?
--Won't you be surprised when I tell ya!
The winner of the Tenkaichi
Tournament, Son Goku.
With him're Tenshinhan,
and Piccolo, as well.
That is amazing!
So, everything'll be okay.
Prob'ly...
There's a good chance
that this'll be my last meal...
But I can't tell 'em that!
Muten Roshi-sama, are you sure
that Goku has been returned to life?
Gyumao!
He should be heading to where
Piccolo and the others are, right now.
W- well then...
W- where is my Gohan?
Muten Roshi-sama, where is my Gohan?
He's still with Piccolo and the others.
Chichi!
I- incredible!
W- what!?
You did it!
That's Tenshinhan for you!
Incredible!
I- impossible!
Saibaimen have a battle power of 1200.
They're on par with Raditz,
as far as power goes!
His battle power
must be higher than that.
B- but...
It's simple arithmetic.
That wasn't in our data...
Nappa, it looks like these guys
are going to be somewhat entertaining.
Ten-san! He's getting up!
V- Vegeta! How could you do that?
W- what is this strange
uneasiness l'm feeling?
l've got a bad feeling about this.
Piccolo, hang in there somehow
until I get back! l'm counting on you!
W- why?
Anything more would be a
waste of time. He couldn't win.
That Saibaiman took him
too lightly when he attacked.
I told him to go at it
with everything he's got.
H- how could he do that!?
T- that Saiyan blew that monster
to bits in the blink of an eye!
What destructive force!
We'll be okay from here.
This special lens is working out great!
There's so much energy colliding
in the area, we can't get very close.
This is almost as if the end of the world
were approaching, it's such a spectacle.
Now, who's going to be next?
You guys, go all-out
from the start this time!
A- all right... I'll face them.
Wait, Kuiririn.
Yamucha-san...
Let me do this. I want to show them
that we've had enough of their games.
Yamucha-san, l can do that-
You've already been brought back
to life once by the Dragon Balls.
Supposing that the unthinkable happens,
you couldn't come back to life again.
Let me handle this. I'm going to take care
of the other five all at the same time.
Y- Yamucha-san...
What a beautiful friendship you must have.
All right, you take him on.
All right, come on!
Don't you take us so lightly!
He's getting cocky.
Give us a look...
...at how truly terrifying
you Saibaimen are!
T- these are the Saiyans!
These are the Saiyans that have
plunged us into depths of terror!
Oh, that face!
It's one of the regulars
from the Tenkaichi Tournament!
Yamucha!
Yamucha-sama's face is looking
even tougher now, isn't it?
It's not just his face. His abilities
are a lot greater now, too.
Bulma, you're taken
with him again, aren't you?
D- don't be silly!
Once they defeat the Saiyans, you could
get married, couldn't you, Bulma-san?
Y- you don't mean-
I mean, marriage!
Oh, that's the face of Piccolo Daimao!
It's Gohan!
G- Gohan-chan!
He's lookin' a lot tougher, huh?
Gohan-chan...
Look at how you've become...
G- Gohan-chan is in the same place
as those revoltin' monsters?
C- Chichi!
W- why isn't Goku there?
T- they vanished!
You fool! They're moving at high speed!
Try feeling out the movement of their Ki.
T- the movement of their Ki?
Everyone except for you can see them.
You all can see them?
All right, then!
Use your whole body as your eyes.
My whole body as my eyes?
Do you see them?
I see them!
You're not getting away!
You did it!
I- incredible!
He did it!
Yamucha-sama!
Yamucha did it!
Not again!
Looks like these monsters
aren't as strong as you think they are.
W- what did you say?
Keep your head, Nappa.
I'll take care of the
other four by myself, too.
It appears that this time, you're the ones
who took the Saibaimen too lightly.
What?
Oh, crap!
N- no!
Yamucha!
Yes. That will do.
W- what a fiend!
He blew himself up!
H- how awful!
H- he's dead...
W- what's wrong with Yamucha?
What happened, Oolong?
I- I'm not sure. I couldn't
hear what he said.
Yamucha-sama! Yamucha-sama!
Yamucha-sama!
Bulma...
No!!
Y- Yamucha-san must have had
a bad feeling about this.
T- that's why he went
in my place. Damn it all!
Damn it all! What do I tell
Pu-erh and Bulma-san!?
What a pathetic Saibaiman-
ending in a draw!
What did he think he was doing,
against scum like that!?
Hey, clean that filth up.
He's polluting up the place.
You dirty bastard!
Get back, everyone!
Yamucha-san,
I'll avenge you, no matter what!
Let me show you
the results of my training!
Having watched Yamucha die before
his eyes, Kuririn's fury has erupted!
What were the results of his training?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org