It was a silent night
Eclipse was beginnin'
Kasaneau setsuna o
Kitto eien to shinjikomu
In darkness...
It's darker than black
Meikyuu no sora
Hikari o kou
If bite your soul
Shoudou ga mushibande yuku
Can I... Can I... Can I... Who am I...?
Risei o kakikesu libido
(Where is my heart?)
Kurayami ni
Ochikitta
(Where is my heart?)
Minikui sugata ni natte
Hito no namida kareta nara
Kimi wa boku o dou omou no ka?
Kotae o oshiete
Makka na chi ga
(Bloody bonds)
Kizuna o nurashiai
Yowasa o wakeatte
(Bloody bonds)
Futari wa ikite yuku no ka?
Kizu o nameatte
Sei o teigi shiatte
Ai o musabotte
Offline
A complete transformation?
But he didn't drink any blood.
I have to get Tsukasa from-
He dodged me?!
Hey!
Didn't you just tell me that if you transformed,
it was my job to keep Tsukasa safe?
Give her to me, now! I'm taking her to the hospital!
Are you listening to me, Anzai?!
Anzai... it's you.
Huh?
I thought... I was...
shot in the stomach...
The bullet... it's stuck in here.
I had this right where the bullet hit me!
It was Zero Sev... the sniper. She gave it to me.
I'll have to thank-!
He regained his sanity while still transformed.
If he went through the proper training,
he might learn to really control himself.
Permission to shoot?
Granted.
Take care of it, Zero Six.
I know that face... Makimura?
I wish all devil-human couples could be like you two.
Did she say something?
Our work here is done.
Let's get out of here, Nine.
Are you okay?
I told you, I'm not hurt that badly.
Not that.
That was your first time shooting a human.
Wasn't that hard?
It wasn't, really.
Not much different from sniping devils.
Oh. In that case...
Because I'm shooting from a distance.
Does Tsukasa always administer
your sedatives for you?
This is only the second time.
But it's a good idea for me to be able to do it.
I called the police.
Told them there were people with guns
on the roofs of two hotels.
But I didn't say a word about Ushio.
Is that good?
I can't figure out what we should do.
I'll have to ask Sawazaki.
Aye-aye, sir.
Tsukasa.
Uh, yes?
I want to talk to you.
Talk?
Hey, let me play with you!
Huh? A foreigner?
Your Japanese is so good!
There's this doctor, a friend of Yanagi's.
He told me that to control the devil inside me,
I have to get to know myself.
That it's important to figure out
what triggers my transformation,
and exactly how far it makes me transform.
But to be honest, I'd never thought about it that way.
I didn't want to hurt you, so I always thought
it would be better to keep my distance.
Pretty much every time I transform,
it has something to do with you.
So if I want to learn more about why I transform,
I'm going to have to drag you into it with me.
It would mean putting you in more danger.
I didn't ever want to do that, but...
I realized I never actually talked to you about it.
Back at the hotel, it was just like
when you saved me at the college.
You knew I was bleeding, but you still ran to help me.
And this time, I'd been shot.
I could have been bleeding.
I was so happy you came for me.
I really wanted to see you.
If I had lost it and bitten you,
would you still be able to say that?
It wouldn't end there.
Devils drink blood, and much worse.
I'm sure Lee would have stopped you
before that happened.
Isn't that why you brought him with you?
Kind of like insurance, just in case.
Don't worry.
One or two bites aren't going to kill me.
But getting bit hurts.
Was she always this reliable?
Physical pain doesn't bother me that much.
It's much harder not being with you.
Oh, of course.
It was never about her reliability.
She's sincere.
But, I guess I'm being selfish.
I'm sorry. I know this is hard on you, too.
She never lies.
You don't think my face is disgusting?
Why?
D-did somebody say it was?
Don't let them bother you!
They're just being cruel!
It was me.
The one who told me I was disgusting.
Everyone thinks so.
You're just weird.
I think it will be dangerous for us to be together.
But I don't want to leave you alone, either.
You might run off and get yourself hurt.
That doctor told me.
There are ways to train yourself
to control your bloodlust.
But to do it, you'll need her help.
I'm still a little concerned about what it might mean
to control the devil inside me, but...
Let's be together.
Yeah.
Bye-bye!
Thank you!
Uh, oh yeah. Um...
Actually, never mind!
What? Come on, now I'm curious.
I know, but...
Just spit it out!
Does... does this mean...
we're a couple?
Wow. It's true.
Y-you're laughing?
"Does this mean we're a couple?"
We really haven't talked about any
of the important stuff, have we?
Do you want to be?
Yes.
I do.
Okay, then. Um, I look forward to it.
Yes, me, too.
Um, do you mind if I just...
The sedative hasn't worn off yet,
so I don't think I'll transform.
Yeah.
Anzai's a bigger perv than he lets on.
You better watch yourself, Tsukasa.
Emergency Ward Entrance
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
The manager of Cross Bar...
Kiwako Oe and her employee
Wataru Akase, both dead.
And Ryunosuke Katagiri is in hiding?
But he's virtually immobilized for now.
Two people died because of him.
That should be warning enough.
C Squad, Ushio, private line. Status report.
Zero Seven and Zero Nine appear to have
escaped the Mino Hotel.
The workers who went up to inspect
the water tank had their uniforms stolen,
and were left tied up on the roof.
And the hostage?
Well, a devil showed up and took her away.
Zero Six says it was Anzai from F Squad.
Him...
What do we do?
We got a tip earlier from what
sounded like a young man.
He said there were snipers on top of the Mino Hotel,
and the Grand Hotel across the street.
The blood spatter on the roof will eventually
tell them that Makimura was involved.
But there was nothing in the tip
about you being a spy.
Why not?
I couldn't say.
But Anzai's just a low-rank officer.
It may be that he couldn't make the call on his own.
We'll keep an eye on F Squad for the time being.
Understood.
Can you find out who the hostage was?
I'll look into it.
And, this is just a hunch...
but I think Anzai and the hostage are lovers.
Well, well.
So the boy has gotten old enough to
fall in love with a human, just like his father.
Aside from the hair color,
he and his father are identical.
Although, if he gets to be any more like him...
it would be tragic.
The half-devil son of a mass murderer...
My interest in you is piqued again, Yuuki Anzai.
After I move to the bar,
we'll be able to see each other every day.
Yeah, I guess so.
This place is a mess.
They'll have people in to fix it next month.
Next month?
Bring all of your valuables.
This place is just asking people to come rob it.
You can take that, too.
We won't be seeing this apartment again for a while.
When everything calms down,
I hope we can relax under the kotatsu again.
Yeah.
Someone fishy's out there.
He's not with the police. It's an amateur stakeout.
Could be a reporter or a trouble-seeker,
trying to get a look at Taira.
A lot of people saw her during the Ikebukuro Incident.
Tsukasa Taira?
Some people have leaked her name and school, too.
Damn...
Changing the subject...
There are rumors going around about
a new group that's trying to wipe out all devils.
What in the...
The name is CCC.
Chosen Civil Community.
So they think they're chosen, eh?
Sounds sketchy.
After the Ikebukuro Incident,
it's only to be expected.
Groups like this were bound to pop up. But...
It's a little too soon for a group to be fully formed yet.
Exactly.
Um...
Oh, I see the happy couple's here!
Ready for some bloodlust training?
The Anzai Couple will be in Guest Room A.
Yanagi and I will be standing by
in Room B next door.
I brought a few restraining devices.
They were all made with devils in mind.
So, what are we supposed to do, exactly?
You're going to make out.
And we'll actually have you transform.
Wait! I thought this training was to help me control it!
Yes, to control it, we need to learn
the timing of your transformation.
And the point of the training is to be able to
control the transformation after the fact.
Control doesn't mean "stop,"
it means gaining mastery over it.
If you want to stop the bloodlust,
all I can tell you is to stop dating women.
Don't stress so much.
This is why we have these devices.
Knock yourselves out.
And hey, we'll be watching you live
from next door in Room B.
Yanagi, can you hear me?
What?!
Loud and clear.
Why?
I thought we only needed a doctor
to watch if we were doing it!
Calm down, it's only to make communication
easier between Rooms A and B.
We'll have it off most of the time.
Besides, depending on how things go,
you might end up wanting to.
Don't be stupid.
Anyway, Yanagi and I will be monitoring
your temperature from Room B.
If you transform and your temperature rises
above the control value...
we will force the audio channel open
and address you from the other room.
We will then ask, "Are you hurt?"
You must both answer this question.
If we feel it necessary,
we will also turn on the video feed.
Th-they really are keeping this offline, right?
If he's not, then that doctor has some
serious problems he needs to take care of.
Oh! Maybe this is it.
The microphone and the camera are both X-ed out.
Oh, it should be okay th-
Anzai?
Don't push yourself too hard.
Want to take a break?
No, I'm okay.
Why don't you put these on?
Uh... okay.
Nail protectors...
They protect your nails when they've grown,
and measure the added length.
Are these handcuffs? They're heavy.
Maybe I should take them off.
I feel kind of weird about them.
No, I like it. I feel like it's safer this way.
Really?
I could hide them.
Like this.
That's even worse!
Ow, ow, ow!
I'm sorry. I just hit you where you got shot.
Oh, actually...
It's already healed up.
See?
What?
Nothing. Just, um...
Does it hurt or anything?
Not anymore.
The skin feels kind of tight, though.
Oh, sorry! I didn't even think. I just reached out...
It's okay, you can touch it.
You smell good.
Oh! Sorry!
Sorry. That was a weird yelp.
Wanna touch...?
His pulse went up.
And his temp went up one degree centigrade.
S-sorry. Did you not like that?
No, I don't mind. It's okay. Keep going.
It's moving.
What's the control value?
34 degrees centigrade,
the average transformation temperature.
Four degrees to go.
You can take my bra off.
Three degrees.
R-relax...
Touch me... lower...
Two.
One.
Your temperature is above the control value.
I'm going to ask you a question.
Are you hurt?
N...no.
Maybe he didn't hear him?
If he doesn't answer soon...
the video...
Anzai, are you hurt?
No.
I'm turning the video feed on, just in case.
You have one minute.
Understood.
I'm sorry...
for not stopping sooner.
What?
So, did he hear the question?
When you've settled down, I'll start asking questions.
Take a breather.
I'm gonna go get some fresh air.
Okay.
That little yelp when I touched Anzai's nipple...
it was so cute.
I want to hear it again.
When I pushed her down and we were
in that position and I pressed against her...
I definitely heard it.
A small sound.
She was wet.
She was really turned on.
I want to hold her.
I want to touch her. I want to be in her.
I want to move.
I want to lick her.
I want to be in her.
I want to drink...
I want... to drink?
It may be a good idea to assign a new leader
to Public Security Division 5's F Squad.
He has a habit of allowing his subordinates
to disobey orders when told to stand by.
F Squad?
You mean Sawazaki?
Did something happen?
We had trouble with him before,
with him and a devil inspector.
The skies are clear. The weather report was wrong.
I haven't been to Tokyo since
my high school class trip, Chief Anzai!
Calm down. We're not here for fun.
And I want you to call me by my
maiden name while we're here.
Until we get back to Obihiro, it's "Chief Sako."
Exterminate the devil pests!
The Redeyes' Rights Protection Committee.
R2PC for short.
It's a civil rights committee that works to
preserve human rights for devils.
And I happen to be on that committee.
The main reason I'm in Tokyo to begin with
is to attend this conference.
Why did you bring us?
For me, it makes sense, but Tsukasa, too?
Is there some reason?
I figured you must be tired from training,
and thought I'd give you a reward.
My signature can get up to two of my guests
free dinner at the hotel restaurant.
How is ONLO doing these days?
Fine. It's peaceful.
Everyone's doing well.
I hear more of your high school kids
are looking to be police officers.
And how are things at the lab, might I ask?
I thought you promised not to pry.
I suppose I did.
Anyway, you might run into
a handsome stranger later.
The fellow who gave me a ride here.
What are you talking about?
The view here is amazing!
We are on the 46th floor.
The restaurant's one floor down.
Looks like it opens at six, so you want to go now?
Oh. Let me stop by the restroom.
Go ahead.
We're a couple.
We made it official, but what does it even really mean?
If we keep up with the training...
will it come more naturally?
Yes?
Oh, nothing.
I'm sorry. You looked like someone I know.
Please excuse me.
It's alright.
Ecological Research
Department Director
Midori Sako
You're not going to the conference?
Oh, I'm not on the committee.
I'm just a friend's chauffeur tonight.
Thanks for waiting.
Oh! Excuse me.
Well, goodbye. Please excuse us.
You be good to her, okay?
Uh... I will.
Someone you know?
No, I've never seen her before.
She kind of reminds me of you, a little.
I might run into a handsome stranger, huh?
That old bastard.
Yuuki has grown into a handsome young man.
I wish you could have seen him...
Tamaki.
Allow me to be frank.
At this point in time,
we should hold off on passing the law
allowing devil-human sex with a doctor present.
ONLO is working to develop restraining devices
to use during intercourse,
but there are issues that need to be resolved first,
such as the safety of these devices
and availability to the general public.
Passing the new law without
addressing these issues
would be like setting a trap.
Now that the Ikebukuro Incident has made
the devils' existence public knowledge,
Susumu Sofue
Minister
Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare
Kaname Shirase
Parliamentary Secretary
Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare
I can't help but think that the government
might be using this new law
to capture devils and
eliminate them from our society.
Sotto tokete yuku you ni
Motto ai shiaetara
Nani o tsutaerareta no
Ai o tsumugenai meguriawase
Dare ka yurushite
Kegareta sugata ga boku de aru koto o
Aa doushite
Fureru yubi ga furueteiru
It's story of fight together
Dakishimetai yo
Kizu tsukezu ni mamoritai yo
Anata dake o
It's story of desire forever
Aragai tsuzukeru
Wakiagaru shoudou ni
"Aa, mata boku wa..."
Deep red dawn
Sotto futari tokete yuku you ni...
Obihiro National Laboratory
Bionomic Research Facility
It was so sudden, I couldn't just come out
and say, "Hi, I'm your mother."
But, oh, how he's grown.
He even has a human girlfriend.
Yeah, I'm a little worried, too.
But I also had a feeling that they would be okay...
When I saw both of their faces.
I had to tell you so badly,
I came back as fast as I could.
But there weren't any direct flights.
I wish I could hug you.
Me? Or Yuuki?
Both of you.
I agree. I hope...
I hope the day comes that you can...
Tamaki.
Next Time
DEVILS' LINE,
Line 9,
"Command."
Command