I'll get you something, too.
A present.
Yay!
We didn't have our hot pot.
Still want to?
Sure, but when?
Any time will be fine.
Any time? What about work?
I've been suspended.
I'm unemployed for two months.
What? Because you hit my professor?
I-I'm sorry. I'm really just so sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Because it's my fault.
Stop talking.
It's not a problem. Stop worrying.
Okay...
It was a silent night
Eclipse was beginnin'
The overlapping moments
We might believe them to be eternity
In darkness...
It's darker than black
The labyrinthine sky
Begs for light
If I bite your soul
The impulse eats away at me
Can I... Can I... Can I... Who am I...?
Libido erases my reason
(Where is my heart?)
Into darkness
I have fallen
(Where is my heart?)
Taking a hideous form
If my human tears have dried
What will you think of me?
Give me an answer
Our crimson blood
(Bloody bonds)
Wets our bond
We share our weakness
(Bloody bonds)
Will we two live on?
Licking each other's wounds
Defining each other's life
Thirsting for love
Paradox
I wonder if she's there yet.
Oh! Tsukasa!
Over here!
I haven't seen you since winter break started!
You don't give me any attention anymore.
I assume this means you have a man?
What? For real?
Oh, but... W-we're not exactly dating...
Yeah, but from the look on your face,
I'm guessing it's going pretty well!
So spill! What happened to you?
C-come on.
You're overreacting.
I am not! Last I heard, men totally freaked you out.
So what's he like?
Is he cute? How'd you meet?
Er... um...
He's not very friendly,
and he often gets angry with me.
But he's really very nice,
and he's willing to admit when he's wrong.
Oh, and he can jump really high!
Wait, what? Is he in track and field or something?
Um, no, but... something like that?
And... I met him on the way home one night...
He's been coming over after work.
I'll make dinner and we'll eat together.
What?! You let him in your house
and feed him dinner?
Are you sure that's a good idea?
Is he a decent guy? Can you trust him?
Yes. I think I can trust him.
W-well, if you're that sure, then I guess...
I'm disgusting.
I house this filthy devil inside me, and I...
I act like I'm some knight in shining armor.
It's Yanagi. How have things been?
Come see me sometime after New Year's.
It's almost time for your physical.
Oh, and Sakaki's hosting his usual
New Year's party at the bar.
I got a wife and kids, so I won't be there,
but all the singles should be.
Check it out if you feel like it.
I got carried away. I bought too much stuff.
I'm feeling kind of out of it.
Is it because I didn't get any sleep last night?
I couldn't.
Hot pot with Anzai on New Year's Eve?
J-just thinking about it makes me blush!
Oh!
O-ow...
I-I'm sorry! Are you alright?
Uh, yes. I'm fine.
I-I really am so sorry.
Huh?
Is he...?
Here you are!
Th-thank you very much.
Alright, Miss, I'm in a hurry, so...!
A friend of yours?
Yipe!
You... you startled me.
Oh, you went to the store already?
Yeah.
Are you feeling okay?
What?
I'm fine! Why?
Oh, it's just, your face looks kind of red...
Don't worry, it's not a cold.
You're sure?
I'm sure.
Oh, it's snowing!
I hope we get a lot of it.
You don't want too much snow.
Then you have to shovel it.
Is it that bad?
Hey, I can carry that!
I got it.
Oh, but I guess it doesn't snow that much in Tokyo.
Authorities are still on the lookout
for a man who disappeared
Restaurant Murder, Man Goes Missing
after a stabbing at a restaurant earlier today.
You're from Hokkaido?
According to the manager who found the body...
Well, yeah.
Around Obihiro.
Wow, I'm jealous.
Oh no, didn't you want to go home for New Year's?
Didn't you?
I don't care.
I never go home.
D-did I ask something I shouldn't have?
Stab wounds were found in
multiple places on the victim's body,
Could be the work of a devil.
Stab wounds were found in
multiple places on the victim's body,
Could be the work of a devil.
and it is believed that loss of blood
was the direct cause of death.
Vampires tend to stab their victims after a kill,
to hide any signs that they drank the blood.
I think I'd suspect the missing man.
Right, because if he's missing,
that means he ran away.
We can't say for sure, though.
If the fugitive really is a devil,
he may be around here by now.
Around here?
But that restaurant is pretty far away.
Devils have excellent physical abilities.
And they run fast.
That reminds me, did you know that guy at the store?
He was suspicious.
I-I didn't know him.
But he seemed nice.
You are way too trusting!
But he picked up my vegetables.
Picking up vegetables makes you a good person?
Oh, but maybe he did look kind of like a vampire.
That makes him even more dangerous!
No, I mean he had dark circles under his eyes.
I don't think he had drunk any blood.
How...? You really know your stuff.
But you didn't know the man.
N-no.
Is he worried about me?
I can't stop myself.
M-meow.
I can't believe I have to work on New Year's Eve.
Well, when the person of interest is a devil...
Of course, we're still waiting for the autopsy results.
Hey! Are you folks detectives?
One of my employees, Katagiri, he's a vampire!
He's the guy that did it!
Get out there and arrest him!
And you're Mr. Okino, the manager, right?
We don't know for sure who did it yet.
What's to know?
She had no blood in her body, right?
It had to be a vampire! What else could it be?
Now, sir, just calm down.
Excuse me.
Why is it that I smell blood
coming from your entire body?
Y-you're making stuff up!
What do you know?!
My sense of smell is a little better than average.
Humans only reek this badly of blood
when they've been drenched in someone else's.
Y-you're a devil?
Hello? What is it? I'm busy.
Sawazaki, is there a wanted devil on the loose?
Huh? Yeah, the suspect in the restaurant stabbing.
But it looks like he was framed.
He's innocent?
According to the autopsy, definitely.
The killer made it look like a devil did it,
by causing massive blood loss.
I haven't identified him yet,
but there's a devil nearby
who seems to be running from-
Hey! Don't feed him!
Name and age?
I'm Oryo.
Your real name. In full.
Ryunosuke Katagiri, age 36.
You get that?
Yeah, that's our guy.
We'll send a car to get him. Where are you?
Those circles under his eyes...
Is your boyfriend a devil, too?
H-he's not my boy-!
That's your objection? And he's not?!
But you're spending New Year's Eve together!
I have a question for you.
If you were framed, you shouldn't need to run.
So why did you come all the way out here?
Give me an honest answer,
and you can have some food.
Devils run faster than humans. And we're stronger.
If we get in a little fight, we might end up
beating the other guy half to death.
Once I hit a man and he started bleeding.
Then I felt the urge.
I lost my mind.
I hated that man, but I sucked his blood.
So I made up my mind.
I'll never hurt a human again,
and if I feel like I might, I get out of there.
The murder victim was a nice girl.
She was the only one there
who treated me like a human being.
I refuse to become a devil.
Thanks for the hot pot. It was delicious.
That's the girlfriend? She's just a baby.
Let's go, Jill.
Well, she beat me in chest-size.
Yuuki!
Come see me sometime.
I'll be waiting!
Huh?
What was that about?
Nothing. Come on, let's go.
The hell I'd go to her place.
That woman looked like a Hollywood movie star.
Wha...?
Well, she was really pretty.
You think so? I think she's average.
What? Wh-why are you crying?
I'm sorry. It's nothing.
Is it what she said? About going to see her?
That was just... you know, one-sided.
These stairs are killing me!
She was just saying that.
You bought too much to drink.
Some of that's for you, you know.
I don't drink wine!
You okay?
What's gotten into you?!
I'm sorry.
I just... feel so pathetic.
Pathetic about what?
Um... I was jealous of that beautiful woman.
And... and I didn't even know your first name, Anzai.
Huh?
What's happening?
I've dreamed of this. More than once.
I really am pathetic.
Always doing things like this in my dreams.
But I know I'm nowhere near good enough for him.
H-hey!
Anzai...
Your face is redder than before.
Hey, can you walk?
I'm the one who's pathetic.
I could tell she wasn't feeling well,
but I ignored it, and now look at her.
2013 Is Almost Here!
The Countdown Begins!
I'm here looking at the holiday lights
at Sapporo Odori Park.
Hokkaido.
The place is packed with visitors
waiting for the big countdown.
I'd like to go there someday.
The place is packed with visitors
waiting for the big countdown.
Are you sure?
It's cold.
I'll take you.
Yeah...
What am I doing?
I need to get myself a sedative.
Get ready for the countdown.
Ten. Nine. Eight. Seven.
What am I saying? "I'll take you"?
Five. Four.
Three. Two. One!
She's a human. I'm a devil.
Another one?
Shot through the head with a 7.62mm bullet.
Died instantly.
This is the fifth one now.
Jill, take a look?
I already did!
You saw the blood and didn't transform.
Which means this one isn't human, either?
Excuse me. Can't you be
gentlemanly enough to ask if I'm okay...
Aww. Poor girl.
Last night's victim makes five
in this series of shootings.
All with a single shot to the head.
And the victims are all devils.
Devils?
But not one of them was in
a transformed state when they died.
They looked just like normal humans.
So the killer knew they were devils?
Assuming that's true,
then how did the shooter know
the victims were devils?
That information is exclusive to city halls,
insurance companies, hospitals, and the police.
There are some devil dating sites, but...
What's wrong?
You got a date or something, Yuuki?
How far have you gone with her, anyway?
Touch her boobs yet?
Do you have to broadcast your stupid questions?
Come on, I really want to know.
How does one go about dating a human woman?
The sight of blood arouses you,
and when you're aroused,
you want to see more blood.
You can't even feel her up without being very careful.
Don't talk like that! And quit it with the hands!
You know it's driving you crazy.
I'd be happy to help you... let off some steam.
Excuse me.
Do you know why I asked Anzai here,
even though he's suspended?
If there's a list of devils going around,
then either of you could be the next target.
Awww. Are you worried about us?
No. I'm saying I don't have time to babysit you.
So watch yourselves.
You're so mean.
They are like children, aren't they?
Hey, guys.
Yanagi.
I thought I might find my patient here.
I'll take my physical another time.
I didn't forget, I promise.
I told you to see me after New Year's.
And I bet you're running low on sedatives, too.
I have one left.
One? You shouldn't be going through them that fast!
So when are you coming, Anzai?!
I want a specific date! Today?
Today's not good. Tomorrow.
Tomorrow, then! Ten in the morning!
His gangster roots are showing.
A list of devils...
So what is the devil population, anyway?
What was it? 0.01%? Sawazaki?
That's about the percentage here in Japan.
Roughly a thousand in Tokyo.
Somewhere between
near-threatened and endangered.
And now that sex between humans and devils is legal,
I'm guessing we'll be seeing even fewer purebloods.
Oh!
You could let Yanagi watch,
then you can screw your girlfriend!
Get your mind out of the gutter!
Quit fighting!
I still haven't gotten her that Christmas present.
I almost forgot.
You can see your girlfriend if you want,
but hold off on the jumping telephone poles
for a while. You'll attract attention.
I know! I'm walking, okay? On the ground.
I know how you like jumping.
Whatever, I'm hanging up.
Cheese-stuffed cabbage rolls.
Pretty good idea, if I do say so myself.
Should be tasty.
I think he should be getting home soon.
Wait, "getting home"? Why would I say it that way?
And you're sure you can trust this guy?
I told you, yes!
Well, I'm worried about you!
You had virtually no interest in men before now.
And you haven't known him that long, right?
R-right.
You can't be too careful, okay?
If anything happens, talk to me. Got it?
It's like she's my mom.
But she's right.
We haven't known each other that long.
I only met him two months ago.
I'm not even his girlfriend.
And I feel like I hardly know him.
I wonder why he keeps coming to my apartment.
Who could it be? A delivery?
Anzai always comes in through the balcony, so...
Uh... whaa...?
Nice to see you, too!
B-but why are you at my front door?
I do that sometimes, okay?
Oh! The rice is done.
We're having cabbage rolls today.
I tweaked the recipe, and I think it'll be good.
How are you feeling?
H-how am I...?
Good! I'm all better!
Your fever's gone? But your hand is hot.
No, yours is just too cold.
You're 80 degrees, right?
Are all devils that cold?
Did you go out today?
What? No, just to the store.
But something seems... different about you.
Oh, I... I did put on some makeup.
I really like you.
Huh?
I missed.
The next one gets your head, monster.
Go to Hell!
Anzai! Anzai!
Are you hurt?
No. But you, Anzai-
Don't cry.
I'm going to be fine.
Get your head down.
Where'd it come from?
How long were they after me?
Never mind that... why were they after me?
Because I'm a devil?
Hey!
Kill.
Are you... okay?
Kill!
I really like you.
There!
No...
Anzai, wait!
I know it's late,
but Merry Christmas.
Did I lose him?
Don't touch me, you monster!
What are you after, murderer?
Your kind are the murderers!
You pretend to care just long enough
to get your chance to drink our blood!
My mother died because of you!
If you devils never existed, she'd still be alive!
That's why I kill you!
To make sure you never kill again!
Dammit!
I... I hate you all.
Like softly melting away
If we could have loved each other more like that
What could I have told you?
A chance encounter that cannot amount to love
Someone forgive me
Because this filthy form is who I am
Oh, why?
Are these fingers trembling as they touch you?
It's a story of fighting together
I want to hold you
I want to protect you without hurting you
You and only you
It's a story of desiring forever
I will keep fighting
Against the urges surging up inside me
"Oh, again, I..."
Deep red dawn
Like we're softly melting away...
You're weaker than I thought.
You a civilian?
Next Time
DEVILS' LINE:
Line 4,
"Monster."
Monster