Who was it?
Who shot him?
Stop Kikuhara...
Stop...
It was a silent night
Eclipse was beginnin'
Kasaneau setsuna o
Kitto eien to shinjikomu
In darkness...
It's darker than black
Meikyuu no sora
Hikari o kou
If bite your soul
Shoudou ga mushibande yuku
Can I... Can I... Can I... Who am I...?
Risei o kakikesu libido
(Where is my heart?)
Kurayami ni
Ochikitta
(Where is my heart?)
Minikui sugata ni natte
Hito no namida kareta nara
Kimi wa boku o dou omou no ka?
Kotae o oshiete
Makka na chi ga
(Bloody bonds)
Kizuna o nurashiai
Yowasa o wakeatte
(Bloody bonds)
Futari wa ikite yuku no ka?
Kizu o nameatte
Sei o teigi shiatte
Ai o musabotte
DEVILS' LINE
Stop Kikuhara...
You can't shoot me.
Can you get to the roof?
I'll have to do it in one jump!
People are gonna see us, so they might shoot.
Hang on tight!
Something's coming from the north!
Up on the roof!
You idiot! What are you doing...
Sorry!
I'm fine.
Don't try to resist.
Throw down your weapons and surrender!
Can you hear me?
What are you doing? Hurry and throw down...
Taira and Lee are on the roof?
What? What are they doing there?
She wouldn't...!
Don't move! I'll shoot!
To the roof!
Stay off the roof.
You'll get in the way.
Tsukasa? Why...
Stay away.
Too... dangerous.
Stay... away...
Anzai!
Can you hear me? Anzai!
A sedative?
Lee!
How many cc's of blood will it take to heal him?
For just the wound and blood loss, 200cc.
But right now, he's gonna need 400cc.
Four hundred?
If he used that sedative before he got shot,
he'll have a hard time transforming.
It'll take twice as much blood as normal.
But in the event that a devil
ignores the deployment ban,
if they transform and engage in violence,
cause injury, or drink blood,
they will be immediately relieved of duty,
regardless of their reasons.
They will thenceforth be placed
under strict surveillance
and forbidden to make contact with humans
for the foreseeable future.
Thank you.
400cc is too much for someone your size, Taira.
I'll give him blood, too.
Who are you talking to?
Drop your weapon right now!
You keep the riot police busy.
I'm going to close Anzai's wound.
The truth is... I want to let you drink my blood, too.
I want to do anything I can to help you.
Don't worry.
I promise... I'll never give you my blood.
I'm sorry.
It's not sharp enough.
Don't push yourself. You might-
Bite down, Anzai!
Wake up! Bite my arm!
Anzai!
Taira, they broke through! Hurry!
Tsukasa?
Anzai-
Push your arm down...
or he'll bite it off!
Don't move! All of you stay where you-
Hold on! We're almost done!
There's a devil on the roof.
Anzai. Don't worry about me!
I'm going to be fine.
So no dying, okay?
The wound is starting to close up.
Hey, you over there! A little help?
Look in his pouch and find a tranq.
Inject him when I give the signal.
What?
I'm trying to save the lives of everybody here!
Please!
Ogata?
Be alert! If anything happens, shoot all of us!
There's two different kinds! Which do I use?
Uh, the thicker one!
It's closed!
Tranq him!
Is there an ambulance here?
Uh, I think one should be getting here soon.
Don't kill him, okay?
He won't give you any more trouble.
Wait, where are you-
Hey!
What's that?
I'm carrying an injured person!
Don't shoot, okay?
She was bitten by a devil and lost a lot of blood.
Take care of her.
Uh, yes, sir!
Are you alright? Can you hear me?
Get the stretcher!
Armed Officers Instigate Devil Hunting Incident
Tsukasa?
Freeze!
Down on your knees, slowly!
Don't try to resist!
His eyes are red!
Be careful!
What are you going to do with me?
Arrest you for everyone's safety!
I think you're pointing your guns at the wrong guy.
We need a stretcher on the roof.
We have one devil, male. He's been tranquilized.
He has...
...no external injuries.
I'm here in a quiet residential neighborhood
where there seems to be an incident involving devils.
We don't have any details yet,
but they've called in the riot police,
Kill the devils!
and I understand they've found multiple bodies.
Exterminate the pests!
I'm calling on the F Squad private channel.
Section 11 wants to hear from your leader, Ishimaru.
That voice!
It's Makimura.
It's possible that central government offices,
starting with the Ministry of
Health, Labor, and Welfare,
were involved with the formation of the CCC.
You need to redirect the focus of your investigation.
One more thing.
There are signs that Kikuhara was attempting to
trade out members before this incident.
The old members may be
pushed out of the organization.
They are vital witnesses in this case.
Do not let them get killed.
Can't get down?
Jump.
I'll catch you.
I'm looking for a mass murderer named Tamaki Anzai.
He killed a lot of people.
He's your...
your genitor.
Geni...tor?
He was sentenced to death,
but for some reason,
he was secretly released from jail,
and brought here instead.
I don't like it here. Let's go back.
In a sense...
these are a type of the darkness
that lurks inside all human beings.
Everyone here is a devil.
Just like you and me.
This monster killed 15 people...
a devil in the truest sense of the word.
Tamaki Anzai.
Your father.
Devil...
Father...
Murderer...
Hey, none of that! You have to lie down.
I'm your attending physician, Feng.
How are you feeling?
The hospital?
That's right. Shirase Hospital Basement 2.
The special wing for treating devils.
Your wounds have closed up, but you lost
a lot of blood, so you still need to...
Th-they didn't bring her with me?
A woman with short hair...
You mean Tsukasa Taira?
She's here. They admitted her to the third floor.
Don't worry; her injuries weren't fatal.
Really?
Well...
Her left arm was broken, with lacerations and
deep bite marks, but it's been treated.
She lost consciousness,
but she's in stable condition now.
I understand she forced you to bite her own arm.
I... Tsukasa...
I was finally...
starting to control myself.
I thought... there was a light at the end of the tunnel...
Just remember this.
There was no time to wait for medical help.
If she hadn't closed up that wound then and there...
If she hadn't been there for you,
you would be dead. Period.
She made a call.
And it was the right one.
Yesterday, someone attacked Naoya Ushio.
But he escaped with no serious injuries.
And this morning in the
detention center, Kohei Nakamura,
also known as Zero Four,
stole a gun from a guard.
He was killed in the ensuing gunfight.
I understand Kikuhara visited him yesterday.
Kikuhara?
At the very least, we need to immobilize Kikuhara.
I'll put a guard on him.
But if Makimura is right, and there are
multiple government agencies pulling the strings,
then restraining Kikuhara won't stop the murders.
Don't worry about the rest.
As of today, F Squad is dissolved.
Would you please reconsider Anzai's punishment?
Officer Anzai saved my life and Ishimaru's.
We did take that into account.
I'm guessing F Squad is done?
That's a good guess.
I could tell from the look on Sawazaki's face.
What? I'm impressed.
Sawazaki's face has always looks
exactly the same to me.
I've known him a lot longer.
Anyway, we've all been suspended for 20 days.
And Ishimaru and I are taking pay cuts.
F Squad will be dissolved,
and the remaining squads
will divide its jurisdiction.
I'm going back to Public Security General Affairs.
You, Asami, will be returning to Division 1.
And Sawazaki will be
transferred to Division 5, Section 1.
Tied to a desk...
Miss Lloyd will be transferred to Y Squad.
And Dr. Yanagi will go back
to the hospital we got him from.
I'll miss you all, but this is goodbye.
Anzai!
Miwako?
Tsukasa! I'm so glad you're okay!
Ms. Tsukasa Taira
The man who saved you...
he was a devil, wasn't he?
What?
I saw it on TV.
He had long hair...
Oh, that's Lee.
Everyone's afraid of devils,
and they have a really bad reputation.
But I guess they're not all bad.
Miwako.
I kind of think I'm starting to get it.
That there are devils who can be trusted.
I don't think I'm the only one...
lots of people are getting it.
They've decided on our punishments.
Anzai will most likely be allowed to resign.
After that...
he'll be placed under strict surveillance,
and prohibited from seeing
his human victim for the foreseeable future.
After the Ikebukuro Incident and this one,
public opinion is leaning in a harsher direction.
Protests Intensify After Introduction
of Red-Eye Protection Bill
The Red-eye Protection Bill was submitted to the Diet,
Vampires Really Do Exist!! Segregate Now!
but all it will do is place more restrictions on devils.
Segregate Now!
In the current political climate, the police had
no choice but to deal with it the way they did.
But...
if I had my way, I want you
and Anzai to be together.
A human-devil couple like you two
would be a symbol of hope for
those of us who want to coexist.
I see. So F Squad is...
I asked them to come up with a way
to lighten your punishment, but...
No, it's okay.
If something like this were to happen again...
I think I would...
I'd kill Tsukasa.
Devils just don't...
deserve to live with humans.
I always knew... devils were just...
I'm not going to comment on
your relationship with Taira.
And I don't have an answer to
whether or not we can coexist.
But...
No matter what happens...
I want us all to be able to live our lives together.
Isn't that what you want?
It is what I want!
But...
Are you going to talk to Taira?
Starting tomorrow afternoon,
you and Anzai will be banned from making
any contact with each other whatsoever.
If there's anything you want to tell him,
you have until then to see him.
Talk to her? What would I say?
I still...
Anzai, have you had any more flashbacks
since we last talked?
Yeah, I was a kid.
I met Kikuhara at ONLO.
He took me to the basement...
and showed me my father...
Tamaki Anzai.
He said he was a devil and a mass-murderer.
Your father, Tamaki Anzai...
had a human girlfriend before he met your mother.
But she was killed by a bunch of humans.
Tamaki took revenge on the men who killed her.
But after he drank the blood of
his victims, he lost control.
He killed 10 more innocent people,
passersby and the like.
He'd lost his love, murdered 15 people...
By the time they brought him to ONLO,
he was a living corpse,
ruled by his addiction to blood.
Your mother knew that's the kind of man he was.
I don't know what she ever saw in him.
She told me she can't explain it herself.
But from the first time they met...
...he was always on my mind.
And by the time I saw him again, I had fallen in love.
You may be a devil, but that's not all you are.
If you fixate on just one part of yourself,
your thoughts skew too far in one direction.
Be brave and face the woman you love.
Did you hear about my punishment?
Yeah.
I'm glad you called me out here.
There's something I really had to say to you.
I'm glad you're alive.
Thank you for saving me.
I...
I was so close to finding the key to
confronting the devil inside me.
If I'd had a little more time...
I might have... found it.
I might have found hope... found a future.
I'm sorry!
Oh, no!
If you hadn't given me your blood, I would have died!
That wasn't what I meant.
I wouldn't have made it this far without you.
If I lost you now...
I feel like everything I've gained
will slip through my fingers.
I'm scared.
Don't worry.
You'll be alright.
I always hated the devil inside me.
I always hated myself.
That's why, when you said you liked me...
Your smile was so blindingly bright,
I couldn't quite accept it.
Would you let me hear it, just one more time?
How you feel about me?
I love you, Anzai.
I love you, too.
Look me in the eye and say it again.
I love you.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
I'll wait for you.
We have to move forward.
If Anzai is moving forward...
I'll move forward, too.
Sotto tokete yuku you ni
Motto ai shiaetara
Nani o tsutaerareta no
Ai o tsumugenai meguriawase
Dare ka yurushite
Kegareta sugata ga boku de aru koto o
Aa doushite
Fureru yubi ga furueteiru
It's story of fight together
Dakishimetai yo
Kizu tsukezu ni mamoritai yo
Anata dake o
It's story of desire forever
Aragai tsuzukeru
Wakiagaru shoudou ni
"Aa, mata boku wa..."
Deep red dawn
Sotto futari tokete yuku you ni...
I like your hair.
Very cool.
You're...
more beautiful.
The Potential for Human and Red-Eye Coexistence
Tsukasa Taira