It was a silent night
Eclipse was beginnin'
The overlapping moments
We might believe them to be eternity
In darkness...
It's darker than black
The labyrinthine sky
Begs for light
If I bite your soul
The impulse eats away at me
Can I... Can I... Can I... Who am I...?
Libido erases my reason
(Where is my heart?)
Into darkness
I have fallen
(Where is my heart?)
Taking a hideous form
If my human tears have dried
What will you think of me?
Give me an answer
Our crimson blood
(Bloody bonds)
Wets our bond
We share our weakness
(Bloody bonds)
Will we two live on?
Licking each other's wounds
Defining each other's life
Thirsting for love
Dark Side
That makes three victims now.
Just how long will this string of
"vampiric killings" go on?
I never realized.
As I went on living my normal life,
in the places I never stopped to notice...
What's wrong?
Oh... nothing.
He was always there in the crowd.
Always there, watching.
What? I don't believe it!
You need to break up with him fast!
Right, Tsukasa? What do you think?
Huh?
Forget about that.
Don't you have a boyfriend yet, Tsukasa?
Me? I don't think I need one.
Come on, you can't be like that forever.
I could introduce you to someone.
What about Professor Ochiai?
You're his favorite student, Tsukasa.
I'm not his favorite.
And I'm pretty sure he's married.
Hey, cut her some slack. Tsukasa is "pure," okay?
She's not like you lot.
What makes her so different?
Tsukasa is actually responsible.
You make it sound like we're
a bunch of shallow airheads!
And believe it or not, Tsukasa has...
Tsukasa. Can I sit next to you?
And would you mind showing me your notes?
Sure, no problem.
What? Borrowing Tsukasa's notes again?
Her's are the most helpful,
she knows how to organize them.
That's for sure.
Let me see them, too!
Hey, Tsukasa.
I'm having a hard time getting this one.
Um, well, you have to...
There's Professor Ochiai!
Alright, take your seats.
And quit stealing Taira's notes.
So where were you heading next, Miwako?
Well, there are a few companies I'd like to apply for.
Oh yeah, we have to find jobs.
No, you're such a great student,
you could go for a PhD! You know?
I'm not so sure. I don't think I want more school.
Huh?
I do like doing research and learning new things,
and I like college, too, but...
It's okay. You don't have to rush.
Yes, you do.
You don't have to get a boyfriend,
but if you don't get serious about your future
pretty soon, you could be in big trouble.
It's true.
Ogikubo
As the days go on, I usually just go with the flow.
I can't see the future,
so my only option is to do my best
with what's in front of me.
How do you figure out what it is
you really want to do in life?
Vampire Murder
Victim Discovered
Body Drained of Blood
There it is.
That feeling I've been getting.
Like someone is watching me.
The target is on Hakusan Dori.
He left Kasuga Station and
is headed for Tokyo University!
The victim has what appear to be
bite marks on her neck,
and all the blood has been drained from her body.
Police! Freeze!
You won't get away from us! Don't even try!
Attention all on-duty officers within the jurisdiction.
The suspect in question has been identified
as a Level 3 special case.
We're giving this to Public Security Division 5.
I repeat.
This is a special case for Public Security Division 5.
Public Security Division 5
I want a name for this suspect.
What's his escape route?
Hey, have you heard about the Vampire Murders?
I've heard of them. But they're just an urban legend.
There's no such thing as vampires.
Is something wrong?
No, I'm fine.
You sure?
And hey, I can hear your show
through your headphones.
Oh, you can? Sorry.
What are you watching?
A special on the Vampire Murders.
You and your occult obsession.
But look!
They found fang marks on the victims' necks and-
That's the kind of stuff you only
read about in the tabloids.
You never hear about it on the real news.
Must have imagined it.
F Squad has gone on ahead
and blocked the target's escape route.
Sawazaki, F Squad, I copy.
I'm with one striker, and one doctor.
On our way to apprehend the target.
Initiating information control.
Issuing gag order to all police officers.
Requesting backup from the MPD Aviation Unit's EC135.
Division 5 detectives and riot police
now in position on target's escape route.
Freeze!
This is Sawazaki.
He's headed your way, just like we planned.
It's up to you, Jill.
Did you think we'd let you get away?
This game of tag ends here.
Think he's a first offender?
Hard to say.
Once they get a taste of blood, they never forget it.
They lose themselves to the mental high
and the sexual rush.
Human blood is just like a narcotic to them.
And they get ten times higher
than any human on drugs.
I can't even imagine it.
An entire race, born with an addiction to human blood.
Vampires.
I know you're suffering.
Let me put you out of your misery.
Is he the one behind the serial vampire murders?
No. Those were done by...
Hey, Tsukasa, what do you think?
What's really behind the Vampire Murders?
Come on, she doesn't need to see that stuff!
Aww, look at you, Akimura.
Why are you looking at me like that?
The next station is Korakuen.
Tsukasa's place is pretty far from the station.
The doors on the right side will open.
Make sure she gets there safely!
I will. Get off my back.
It was so pretty!
Yeah, it was.
What do you wanna do now?
You really don't have to worry about it, Tsukasa.
Huh?
What I said to you the other day.
I always knew you didn't think of me that way. It's okay.
I'm not trying to make you feel bad.
I know that, okay!
Whoa. If looks could kill.
What?!
But anyway, it does help to know that
you don't have a boyfriend, Tsukasa.
I just feel like, if you did have one...
I might not be able to recover.
What are you talking about?
I'm serious.
What?
For now...
I'm okay as friends.
But someday,
if you ever start to...
Never mind.
Akimura?
Let's take a different way.
I don't feel safe here.
Okay.
We should be far enough away by now.
It's definitely him.
That's the guy I saw on the train.
I don't believe it.
He followed me?
Sorry.
Let's go.
Hey there, vampire.
What? A man's blood doesn't do it for you?
Don't...
Who are you?
What are you...
I'm not going to drink her blood.
Leave us alone.
Akimura...?
Look what you did. You scared her.
I don't know who you are,
but there's nothing to worry about.
I've never directed my bloodlust at her.
Of course not. You found an outlet.
You turned your bloodlust on the three other
random women you murdered.
That wasn't me.
I'm told your semen was found
at each of those scenes.
It wasn't mine!
Don't talk about that in front of a lady!
Your DNA was a match.
I wouldn't be following you without the evidence.
Get away from here.
Tsukasa!
You keep your hands off of her!
So you can act like a hero in front of your girl, eh?
Devil, human. Either way, you're piece of trash.
You're better off letting me arrest you now.
Once a vampire has raped and murdered a victim,
they can never shake the thirst for that pleasure.
They're guaranteed to kill again.
Sooner or later, you would have done
the same thing to her, too.
I would never hurt her.
I've been taking medicine to help me.
I even gave myself a sedative earlier.
I was going to take this secret to my grave.
I know human lives are all equal.
But they're not equally important to everyone.
I just can't protect everyone, okay?
I agree, it's not right.
Why should I have to kill other women
just to keep Tsukasa safe?
Or should I have killed Tsukasa
to stop myself from killing the others?
Or should I have died myself?
Tsukasa.
I'm so sorry. I should have realized.
Can you walk?
Ow!
Not on that leg, you can't.
This is Anzai from F Squad.
I've apprehended Target A.
Currently at Hongo 4.
This is Sawazaki.
Hidaka will be there to back you up in three minutes.
I tranqed him.
And sorry, something came up. Take him in for me.
What?!
You could at least wait three minutes for someone to-
Don't you have to go?
I'll be...
Fine? No, you won't.
This way?
Hey. 301, right?
Thank you for everything, Anzai.
You need to forget my name.
And what happened today.
Don't cry.
I will cry!
Akimura and I were really good friends
for a really long time!
I least, I thought we were.
I just...
I didn't know anything about him.
The thing about vampires is...
Biologically, they're extremely similar to humans.
If they don't ever transform,
even most other vampires
can't pick them out in a crowd.
So if he was trying his damnedest to hide it,
then you can't blame yourself
for not knowing he was one.
But vampires are fighting a constant battle
against the fear that they'll lose control
the instant they see human blood.
I think he really meant it when he said he loves you.
But devils and humans were
never meant to be together.
Devils?
Yeah. That's what we call vampires.
Your mouth.
It's bleeding.
Now you notice?
Yeah, I cut my lip when you shoved me!
And I'm getting a little sick of your violent-
Like softly melting away
If we could have loved each other more like that
What could I have told you?
A chance encounter that cannot amount to love
Someone forgive me
Because this filthy form is who I am
Oh, why?
Are these fingers trembling as they touch you?
It's a story of fighting together
I want to hold you
I want to protect you without hurting you
You and only you
It's a story of desiring forever
I will keep fighting
Against the urges surging up inside me
"Oh, again, I..."
Deep red dawn
Like we're softly melting away...
Next Time
DEVILS' LINE:
Line 2,
"Safe House."
Safe House