Upsy-daisy.
Weather Report
The weather report?
Yeah, actually, I'm really into
this weather girl right now.
Yuriko Hyuga
Good evening, everyone.
I'm here at the fountain plaza.
See? That's her.
Yeah, she definitely looks like your type.
Well, as long as you like watching her.
And tomorrow, we'll finally
be getting some more snow.
We're not going to see a real rise in temperature,
which means it's going to be a cold day.
So everyone, I hope you'll all
stay warm, and good night.
It's a slasher!
But this is a live broadcast!
Hey! What's that?
That's insane. What in the...
It was a silent night
Eclipse was beginnin'
The overlapping moments
We might believe them to be eternity
In darkness...
It's darker than black
The labyrinthine sky
Begs for light
If I bite your soul
The impulse eats away at me
Can I... Can I... Can I... Who am I...?
Libido erases my reason
(Where is my heart?)
Into darkness
I have fallen
(Where is my heart?)
Taking a hideous form
If my human tears have dried
What will you think of me?
Give me an answer
Our crimson blood
(Bloody bonds)
Wets our bond
We share our weakness
(Bloody bonds)
Will we two live on?
Licking each other's wounds
Defining each other's life
Thirsting for love
Plan B
Anzai?
Yanagi, sedative.
Uh, right.
What are you wearing?
I gave it to him.
It's a high-performance gas mask.
It blocks out odors and colors.
Calling all Public Security Division 5 personnel!
Level 5 Vampire Incident in progress!
Dispatch human officers to the fountain plaza
in Ikebukuro West Gate Park immediately.
The victim is bleeding profusely.
It took place during the live weather broadcast,
there were several onlookers!
It's possible that devils have witnessed
the event and have transformed.
Don't push, stupid!
Wait!
Why?
What is she doing there?
Don't push, stupid!
Wait, I'm taking a picture!
You need to sit down.
I'm gonna go stop that devil in the knit cap.
If he keeps drinking her blood, she'll die.
They've probably stopped the cameras,
so I'll be back in about three...
Make that one minute.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
I can't believe a slasher would attack
during a live TV broadcast.
And there happened to be a devil
right there watching.
"Happened to be"?
They did that broadcast every day.
Is it possible that the attacker knew
there was a devil on the crew?
Maybe the slasher wasn't trying to kill the woman.
Maybe he wanted the devil to see human blood.
Monster...
Devils throughout the Kanto Region are
transforming after witnessing the attack on TV.
The situation is getting out of hand.
Did anybody call the police?
Or an ambulance?
I'm gonna tie him up, so somebody-
You're really something.
Taking down a monster like that.
You don't have to help him.
You better kill him, just in case.
I mean, look at that monster.
Stop filming. This isn't a show,
and I'm not killing him.
Why not?
Whatever, just kill him already.
Do it!
What is wrong with him?
Can you run?
Run. Get away from here.
Hurry!
What's that?
Where... can I run?
Hey, I think the monster's going after her!
Maybe we'll be safe if we just get away from her!
Who's that?
Another monster?
Anzai.
Thank you.
Sawazaki, this is Anzai.
I have Tsukasa Taira.
Can you come pick her up?
Sorry, not right now.
Give me a status-
Take these. They're sedatives.
If you ever get attacked when
you're alone again, you can inject the guy.
I-I can't do that!
I don't know how to give someone an injection!
It doesn't matter how!
Just take the needle and stab-
I-I'm sorry!
That devil back there scratched me...
It's okay.
I'm wearing a gas mask.
I can't make out the color or the smell.
Don't think of it as blood!
No. Don't go.
I'll hide the scratch!
If you need me to, I'll find somewhere
to wash the blood off right now!
So please!
Please.
Don't disappear again.
I need one of those sedatives.
If you inject me in ten seconds...
I'll stay.
Y-you might feel a prick.
All done.
How do you feel?
Are you okay?
"Might feel a prick"?
S-sorry. Did it hurt?
No, I...
It was just...
kind of funny.
It's working.
I don't think I'll be able to move much
for about ten minutes.
So we'll have to wait here for a while.
I-I'm sorry!
I just couldn't help it...
Again.
Will you... do that again?
Will you do that again?
Um...
This is Makimura, B Squad!
A unit has fired his gun at a devil!
We believe that the devil was
among the audience and had transformed.
The officer is in shock.
He likely did not know about devils.
What...?
Apparently a cop shot a devil.
I'm with the police! Everyone, please calm down!
Put the gun down!
Y-yes...
If you see anyone who looks unusual,
do not get involved.
Report to us immediately!
Tsukasa?
When I can move again, I'll take you and we'll go.
I don't know if it's safe here.
Okay.
What?
Nothing.
Oh, but... Lee is still down there.
He might be looking for me.
Are you and he... close?
No!
I was looking for you, Anzai.
I went to that alley,
and I happened to run into him.
He said he dropped his cross
and he was looking for it.
I told him I was looking for you,
and he said he would help me find you.
A cross?
This is what was on his necklace.
A long, black cross.
It's the symbol of ONLO, the orphanage I grew up in.
It's near Obihiro.
They take in devil orphans and raise them there.
I didn't know.
Don't worry about it.
It's better not to talk about this stuff.
It doesn't bother me that much, anyway.
I still don't know very much about you, Anzai.
So, I'm happy to learn that.
Oh! But you don't have to tell me
anything you don't want voo...
"Want voo"?
It's been a long time since you hit me like that.
He laughed again.
It's so cute.
I wish he would laugh more.
If he had a cross like this one...
then there's a strong possibility
we're from the same place.
But there weren't any foreigners
like him in my age group.
And the other kids were all devils;
I was the only one who was half.
Are half-devils that unusual?
Well, yeah.
Having only one devil parent is...
Would that... even be possible?
Devils can't have sex with humans.
So there's no way to conceive...
a half-devil child.
Are you okay?
How can you stand being around me?
It's just like the other day!
I attacked you.
I could have killed you!
And I might not be a half!
I might just be a devil!
How can you?!
Because!
I...
like you.
Um! That is, I mean, well...
I don't think it really matters...
if you're half or full-devil...
or if you're just human.
It doesn't change the fact that you are Anzai.
I'm more worried about whether or not
I'm a good match for you.
What?
What the hell is going on?
The TV was saying something about vampires!
This is bad.
The sedative hasn't worn off yet.
My knees... are giving out...
Hey, grab the handrail.
Huh?
Or you'll fall.
You sure do fall a lot.
You...
Who are you?
Hey, are you sure you have devil blood in you?
Your physical abilities are pretty weak.
That's just because I gave him
a sedative a little while ago.
What's the deal with your eye?
You don't know that, either?
Are you really a half?
We're wrapping things up
over by Ikebukuro West Gate.
Human personnel from each squad
will now go help contain the devil transformations
happening throughout the region.
Be informed that the investigation will be
assigned to human personnel only.
Devil personnel, please stand by.
I have a lot of questions for you.
I guess I have answers.
Sawazaki!
Kikuhura.
Is everyone in F Squad alright?
We're all fine. And you?
No one's been injured.
Personally, I was held up in traffic.
Oh, this is a civilian we found on the scene.
My guy's over there.
Anzai, say hello. You haven't met, have you?
I'm Anzai.
I'm Kikuhara, A Squad. A pleasure.
Something about him scares me.
Um...
Have I met you somewhere before?
Before?
Oh, maybe at the new staff ceremony.
Chief Kikuhara.
About our next deployment...
Right.
Well, Sawazaki, I'll see you at the meeting.
Are you okay?
Is there something about Kikuhara?
No, it's nothing.
His hand...
was unusually warm.
I'm so glad you're both alright.
I have a fire going, so hurry on upstairs.
Oh?
Sorry, we have two extra people.
This is Tsukasa Taira.
Oh, your girlfriend!
What? Um, uh...
I'm Sakaki, the owner here.
Tsukasa Taira.
I'm Hans Lee.
A friend of Anzai and Tsukasa's.
He's a witness in the sniper case and this new one.
Let him stay here until I get back.
And Ms. Taira, I'll want to get
your version of what happened, too.
Uh, yes, sir.
I do have guest rooms available,
and the lounge is rather large.
Please, make yourselves comfortable.
Thank you.
In fact, I own the whole building.
I rent out everything from the third floor up.
I don't have any vacant rooms at the moment,
but Yuuki is one of my tenants,
so you could stay in his...
No.
It's a mess right now.
Oh yeah. I have to tell him
it's possible to get used to blood.
Would that make life a little easier for you?
Could we spend more time together?
What's wrong?
Um...
I was thinking about blood tolerance.
Oh, right.
Yeah, you probably should tell him.
Could help him live longer, too.
Huh? Live longer?
You didn't know?
A devil's average lifespan is only 39 years.
What?
Wow, you really brought everybody.
I'm going back to the scene.
Keep an eye on them.
You're gonna be busy.
They'll want to set up an investigation committee.
Yeah, well.
I don't think I'll be back until after midnight.
I'll stay in touch.
It is unclear whether they are
related to the Ikebukuro incident,
I heard on the radio.
It is unclear whether they are
related to the Ikebukuro incident,
I knew they'd leave us devils
out of the decision-making eventually.
but similar phenomena are occurring all over Japan.
Police are scrambling to handle the outbreak.
This was the only line of work
where devils got any decent treatment.
Police are scrambling to handle the outbreak.
This was the only line of work
where devils got any decent treatment.
It won't be long before we're out of places to go.
You don't know they're going to cut you all off.
Don't I? They always thought devils
were tough to deal with.
We're high maintenance.
Freaking out every time we see a little bit of bl-
Uhh!
This is where you belong.
Do I have to keep spelling it out for you?
You, too, Anzai.
I won't let anything happen to you.
So just sit tight.
Sawazaki.
Sorry I almost attacked you.
It wasn't your fault.
Yanagi, I want to ask you something. Got a minute?
Hm?
If Anzai isn't half-devil, if he's a full devil...
can he develop a blood tolerance like Lee?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I'll help. You're making food, right?
Thank you.
Oh, me, too.
Me, three.
What are we making?
When I say "midnight snack," you think...
Ramen?
Oh, I'm Tsukasa Taira.
Officer Juliana Lloyd.
I'm a full devil.
My parents are American and Russian.
So you're a half.
Nationality-wise.
Here's an apron for each of you.
What?
You're just so pretty, like a Hollywood actress.
Why would you say that?
It's not flattering, it's embarrassing!
Uh, um...
I just always admired beautiful,
sophisticated women... so, um...
Please, let's stop this, Zero Seven!
What good will it do to chase me?
It's already over!
I know you were against Plan B!
But it was our leader's decision!
Are you saying you bear no responsibility?
When did I ever say that?
By sacrificing a few humans,
we call attention to the existence of devils!
It's the vital first step in
eliminating them from our society!
Stay away from me! Drop your gun!
I'm not carrying a gun.
You trust humans too much!
The truth is... I have another mission.
If you tried to interfere with Plan B...
Mura...
I'm sorry. As long as you're around,
you'll only get in our way.
Sex between a devil and a human?
I'm sure there are ways.
Tie up the devil, gag them.
It's certainly not impossible.
What about artificial insemination?
That would be even harder,
the way things are now.
Don't let it bother you, Anzai.
However they were conceived,
the child didn't do anything wrong.
I-I'm sorry.
I'm taking a count for ramen flavors.
I'll have miso.
Shoyu.
Um, Anzai, I...
I'm gonna head back.
You two stay here and make out
as long as you want.
Huh?!
Later.
Lee told me...
devils usually only live 39 years.
What's that mean?
Well, you know that devils are always
going without blood, right?
He told me that lowers their life expectancy.
Stop it. I've never seen any data
on devil life expectancy.
The government never released any of those numbers.
That night, when you got hurt,
you drank blood and it healed you.
Can you really trust-
Lee drinks a little blood every day
to get used to it,
so he can drink blood to heal
when he needs to!
That's why his wounds heal, and he's so strong.
And he can live longer!
Anzai, please...
drink my blood.
I'll give you some every day.
Like softly melting away
If we could have loved each other more like that
What could I have told you?
A chance encounter that cannot amount to love
Someone forgive me
Because this filthy form is who I am
Oh, why?
Are these fingers trembling as they touch you?
It's a story of fighting together
I want to hold you
I want to protect you without hurting you
You and only you
It's a story of desiring forever
I will keep fighting
Against the urges surging up inside me
"Oh, again, I..."
Deep red dawn
Like we're softly melting away...
Zero Two?
I know that last job was hard on you, Fifteen.
Oh, no! I'd do anything...
for the team and for you, Zero Two!
I'm sorry, Murakami.
Ren Murakami, unemployed.
Had been stalking weather reporter Yuriko Hyuga,
attacked her out of resentment for
her failure to reciprocate his feelings.
But was struck by a guilty conscience
during his escape,
stabbed himself, and jumped off a building.
That is the entirety of Plan B.
No... please...
A few sacrifices...
will save society.
Why did you need to kill Murakami?
Don't kill humans, Kikuhara.
We should only have to kill devils!
So. Before you die, tell me.
Do I...
look human to you?
Next Time
DEVILS' LINE:
Line 6,
"Dogmatic."
Dogmatic