I really like you.
Huh?
No...
Anzai!
Hey! Anzai, what's wrong?
Come in!
Let's go, Yanagi.
Jill, you wait here.
What?! Why?
Your kind are the murderers!
My mother died because of you!
If you devils never existed, she'd still be alive!
Dammit!
You're weaker than I thought.
You a civilian?
Whoa! I think she blew your lung out.
If you don't do something, you're gonna die.
You've lost a lot of blood, and you gotta fix that lung.
I guess I can give you this.
Since we're repairing organs,
you'll need, what, like 200cc?
Nothing works better than human blood, after all.
Don't...!
I...
I don't want...
that stuff!
Where am I?
It looks familiar.
Hey! You! Are you a friend of his?
Not really. I'm just a passing life-saver.
Shared my human blood with him, that's all.
Human blood? You are a devil!
Oh, don't get any funny ideas.
I bought this blood. From its owner, even.
You expect me to take a devil at his word?
That man... that devil...!
He tricked my mother into thinking he loved her!
Then he drank the blood from her dead body,
as he raped her!
You know, I think you're looking at this
all the wrong way.
What I'm getting is that your mom's
boyfriend was a slimeball,
and he also happened to be a devil, that's all.
It takes more than one factor
in someone's life to drive them to crime.
The environment they grow up in,
what attracts their interest, who's around them.
All of these factors join together in
a complex pattern to create that foundation.
In other words,
treating someone like a potential criminal
just because they're a devil is way too simplistic.
Are you scared? They're devils. Just like you.
I... I'm not... I'm only half...
I'm not like these...
Not another word, devil!
If he weren't a devil, he would never
have done those terrible things!
Blood! Blood!
I want blood! Blood!
I'm not...
like them!
People do terrible things, too, you know.
It was a silent night
Eclipse was beginnin'
Kasaneau setsuna o
Kitto eien to shinjikomu
In darkness...
It's darker than black
Meikyuu no sora
Hikari o kou
If bite your soul
Shoudou ga mushibande yuku
Can I... Can I... Can I... Who am I...?
Risei o kakikesu libido
(Where is my heart?)
Kurayami ni
Ochikitta
(Where is my heart?)
Minikui sugata ni natte
Hito no namida kareta nara
Kimi wa boku o dou omou no ka?
Kotae o oshiete
Makka na chi ga
(Bloody bonds)
Kizuna o nurashiai
Yowasa o wakeatte
(Bloody bonds)
Futari wa ikite yuku no ka?
Kizu o nameatte
Sei o teigi shiatte
Ai o musabotte
Monster
Then Anzai ran off by himself?
Uh, yes, sir.
Must be chasing the sniper.
Oh, Anzai... All because I was bleeding.
He was crying.
What do I do? It's my fault.
I have to do something.
Hm? What just happened?
He wouldn't!
Sawazaki, come on!
We need to find Anzai, and fast!
No, wait!
I'm going with you!
So you're saying Anzai didn't lick your wound, correct?
No, he didn't!
He resisted.
I see. Then there's still hope.
Maybe if Anzai sees me,
he'll come back to his senses?
Hey, what's that sound?
You know he wears that ring, right?
I'm using it to monitor him, keep track of his
temperature, in case of an emergency.
And this sound is the alarm that goes off
when he gets above 102 degrees.
He's normally only 80 degrees. That's a big jump!
There's only one thing that
could have this effect on a devil.
He must have ingested
a large quantity of human blood!
If his temp keeps going up like this,
the fever will affect his brain and internal organs,
and lead to permanent damage.
Worst case scenario, he might die.
Die? Anzai?
Oh, no...
We have to find him and
stop him before that happens.
I've never seen this happen before, either.
Now, now, just calm down.
No good, eh?
His wounds are healed, but now
the blood's totally gone to his head.
Go to Hell, monster!
This is only a theory,
but it's possible that the sniper is identifying
vampires by their body temperatures.
With thermography, you could tell at a glance.
And you're absolutely certain
Anzai's had some blood?
I didn't believe it at first, either.
But it is possible that resisting the urge to drink
Taira's blood has amplified his bloodlust.
So it is my fault.
If he did drink blood, we'll have to
bring out the tranquilizers.
Tranquilizers? Not sedatives?
A sedative is a medicine,
but a tranquilizer is a weapon.
Only police are allowed to use them,
on devil suspects who have lost control.
"Suspect"?
We have no choice. We have to help
whoever he got that blood from.
Lots of devils go after young women, so...
Huh? What was that...
That pain I felt?
Are you alright, Zero Seven?
Fifteen!
Monster...
Run!
Okay, we're almost there! It's coming up!
The next corner!
Don't drink her blood, Anzai!
Anzai...
Hey! Cut it out!
Calling for backup!
I'm fighting the wanted sniper and
someone we assume to be an accomplice!
Suspect is armed with what appears to be a rifle!
Look, over there!
Jill?!
What happened to you?
Hey, I told you to wait at the-
Don't give me that crap!
You want me to sit around and wait
while my coworker gets himself killed?
Sorry for eavesdropping, but I heard it all.
Only a devil can fight off another devil.
If you don't use me now,
then why even have devils on the team?
Snap out of it, Yuuki!
So much for back up. She can't even get near him.
Is she the one that shot Anzai?
But it doesn't look like he drank her blood...
Then whose blood did he drink?
I gave him some human blood to drink.
He was dying, shot right through the chest.
And now I don't have any blood left for me.
Just one red eye?
Who are you? And what's with your eye?
Hans Lee. Half-devil, half-human.
Half? Then he's just like Anzai.
Anzai? The guy with black hair?
He wouldn't happen to be from Hokkaido, would he?
What? How did you know?
Wow. To think I'd run into another
hybrid in the outside world.
Jill!
Not even a devil can stop him?
The difference between a devil on human blood
and one who's not is like night and day.
Hey!
I was just trying to heal him.
I didn't think it would turn into this.
Even I couldn't have seen this coming.
Well, what's done is done.
I guess that's what happens when you
drink blood without building up a tolerance.
Oh, no.
If we don't do something, Anzai will...
No... don't...
Stop...
Anzai!
Oh. That's what it was.
I felt inadequate.
What are you doing?
You could've died.
Get back!
Dammit!
Is that him?
We're on the scene!
We've found one of the suspects
described in the witness report!
Wait, he's not...
I don't think I really wanna hang out with the police.
Zero Seven's snipe attempt failed.
We're moving to Plan B.
It's been two weeks.
Anzai stopped coming to see me.
Miwako Toda
Tsukasa Taira
Yoohoo, how you doing?!
And how's it going with your crush?
Of course he's not calling me.
I never gave him my phone number or email address.
I know it's late,
but Merry Christmas.
Will he never come back?
Why won't he come back?
This is the last place I saw him.
It's the only place I can think of
where I might see him.
You!
We met the other day!
Oh, hi there. Fancy meeting you here.
So hey, did you see a cross?
I think I dropped it somewhere
around here the other day.
So? What are you doing here?
He hasn't come to see me since then,
and I have no way to contact him.
Hmm. Well, it makes sense, really.
What?
I mean, you jumped in front of a rampaging devil.
Try putting yourself in his shoes!
It's not uncommon for a devil to lose it
and kill their significant other.
Then they either kill themselves in despair
or fall down dark paths.
Happens all the time.
That's a good point.
I've only been thinking of myself.
I don't know anything about Anzai.
Or about devils.
I really don't know anything.
But if I keep talking to him,
maybe I can learn some things.
So, um...
Can I see your left eye?
Why only the one eye?
That's a geeky reaction.
This eye doesn't scare you?
The guy I like is a devil.
The guy you like? You mean Anzai?
I'm right! Are you dating him?
N-n-no! We're not exactly...
I really like you.
If I tell him I like him, too...
maybe we could start dating.
Wait, so, he's just waiting for you
to get back to him?
When are you gonna tell him?
Oh right, you have no way to contact him.
I think you're right.
I think he is bothered by
what happened two weeks ago.
That was the most devil-like I'd ever seen him...
And he almost attacked me.
Come on, Anzai.
How long are you going to hole up in there?
Your suspension ends tomorrow.
We're meeting at the bar downstairs at 6pm.
Don't be late.
If you're that worried about it, you can wear this.
It's a gift. I'll leave it here.
A gift?
He's afraid he's going to lose it and hurt someone.
So that's a tool to help ease that anxiety.
Anzai. Who are you?
Are you a devil?
No. You're a cop.
Come to think of it, doesn't it bother you?
Doesn't what bother me?
He almost killed you.
That would scare most people.
But it was Anzai.
You like him that much?
Then what if he trained to get a tolerance for blood?
Tolerance?
See, I drink a little bit of human blood every day.
You drink blood?
But is it really okay for you to do that?
I said just a little at a time,
to get my body used to it.
That way, it's easier for me to resist
the urge to feed on others.
So I can see or even taste blood
and still maintain my sanity.
It heals wounds, too.
Oh!
So the other day, when Anzai survived
that gunshot wound, it was because...
But whose blood is it?
I ask a bunch of people to share a little with me.
That way it's not too hard on
any one person, you know?
I never would have thought of that.
Want me to help you find this Anzai?
Huh?
There aren't a whole lot of half-devils out there,
and I'd like to talk to him.
And then, maybe I can initiate him
into the art of blood tolerance.
Yeah.
She's smiling and crying?
I've never seen a tearful smile before.
Anzai, there's a way to build up
a tolerance for blood.
Would that make things a little easier for you?
Could we be together again?
I have to tell him.
I will tell him!
This time, I'll be the one...
to tell him I like him.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm here at the fountain plaza.
We had just a little bit of sun today.
And tomorrow, we'll finally be getting
some more snow.
Now let's take a look at the national forecast.
I'll find you.
I will see you again.
Wait for me, Anzai.
We're not going to see a real rise in temperature,
which means it's going to be a cold day.
So everyone, I hope you'll all stay warm,
and good night.
It's a slasher!
But this is a live broadcast!
Hey! What's that?
Sotto tokete yuku you ni
Motto ai shiaetara
Nani o tsutaerareta no
Ai o tsumugenai meguriawase
Dare ka yurushite
Kegareta sugata ga boku de aru koto o
Aa doushite
Fureru yubi ga furueteiru
It's story of fight together
Dakishimetai yo
Kizu tsukezu ni mamoritai yo
Anata dake o
It's story of desire forever
Aragai tsuzukeru
Wakiagaru shoudou ni
"Aa, mata boku wa..."
Deep red dawn
Sotto futari tokete yuku you ni...
Next Time
DEVILS' LINE:
Line 5,
"Plan B."
Plan B