Wha...!
It was a silent night
Eclipse was beginnin'
Kasaneau setsuna o
Kitto eien to shinjikomu
In darkness...
It's darker than black
Meikyuu no sora
Hikari o kou
If bite your soul
Shoudou ga mushibande yuku
Can I... Can I... Can I... Who am I...?
Risei o kakikesu libido
(Where is my heart?)
Kurayami ni
Ochikitta
(Where is my heart?)
Minikui sugata ni natte
Hito no namida kareta nara
Kimi wa boku o dou omou no ka?
Kotae o oshiete
Makka na chi ga
(Bloody bonds)
Kizuna o nurashiai
Yowasa o wakeatte
(Bloody bonds)
Futari wa ikite yuku no ka?
Kizu o nameatte
Sei o teigi shiatte
Ai o musabotte
Safe House
Let's see...
How about Taira?
Tsukasa.
Tsukasa!
You alive, Taira?
You can stay in your seat,
but would you read paragraph three?
Page 136 of the text.
I... I'm sorry.
Medieval communes in the European Middle Ages
had sworn allegiances of mutual defense...
It's been one month since Akimura disappeared.
They're saying he's studying abroad in Canada.
His arrest wasn't on the news.
Is that because he was a vampire?
I haven't seen Anzai once since the incident.
What if...
What if I imagined the whole thing?
Huh?
Um! There's a syringe sticking out of your leg!
Shut up! I did it on purpose!
I can't believe I'm using a sedative on myself.
Do my eyes look normal now?
Uh, yeah...
Huh? He looks so much better now.
The dark circles are gone.
So, um...
Sorry about that. With the tongue.
You don't have to remind me there was tongue!
I said sorry! Don't hit me! Stop it!
Anyway...
Are you a vampire, too?
I'm sorry. I...
What? Oh, no, it's fine.
Well, I have genes from both,
so I guess I'm a half vampire.
Half...?
So I was under the impression
my bloodlust was weaker.
But apparently not.
All of Akimura's self-control, and I almost wasted it.
Anyway, cheer up, alright?
Huh?
There are plenty of fish in the sea.
Wait!
Since then, I haven't seen Anzai once.
Is it because he kissed me?
Is that why I can't stop thinking about him?
But...
that's not how real love is supposed to work, is it?
Akimura?
I hope you're okay, Akimura.
Come to think of it,
have I ever really fallen in love with anyone before?
Honestly, that was basically my first kiss.
I wonder where you are now, Anzai.
Hey! Don't scare me like that!
Huh?
A-Anzai?
Wh-why are you on my balcony?
I came via telephone pole.
It was the closest entrance.
Telephone pole?!
How are you?
Huh?
You're worried about Akimura, aren't you?
You always stop for a minute when you
get to the place we arrested him.
I can put in a request for you if you want to visit him.
And depending on the trial,
sometimes they get off with just a life sentence.
Uh... yeah.
I'm a terrible person.
I was so busy thinking about Anzai,
I forgot about Akimura.
I'm the worst.
Have you gotten skinnier?
You know guys prefer a girl with
a little meat on her bones.
Ow! Don't punch me! Not the fist!
Well look at you.
You're doing much better than I thought.
He... he smiled.
Sawazaki here. We have a Level 1 Special Case!
Our suspect is Yuuko Tamaru, age 21. Female.
Hereafter the investigation will
refer to her as Target T.
We believe she is currently
hiding out in the Mikusa Building.
This is Anzai. I copy.
I'm close. I'll be right there!
Mikusa Building
Calm down.
I want to settle this peacefully.
Yuuko Tamaru, right?
The police?
Public Security Division 5, for devil-related crimes.
We can make special allowances in cases like yours.
You have no priors.
If you claim it was an accident,
they might not press charges.
Charges?
I don't care what they do to me.
Then why are you running, Yuuko?
Yuuki...
What?
Do you have someone...
Someone you'd do anything to protect?
If you don't, you wouldn't understand how I feel.
He meant the world to me.
He was helping me make dinner.
He slipped and cut his finger. Then he said...
"Lick it off?"
The next thing I knew, I had stabbed him...
and I had been desperately drinking his blood!
I was...
I was always so careful!
So careful not to hurt him.
I should have known it wouldn't work.
A devil marrying a human...
Living under the same roof.
Damn right it didn't work.
He stuck out his bloody finger
and asked you to lick it.
What part of that is "being careful"?
What?
I don't care if he was your husband.
If you see blood, you're gonna lose it.
So I guess you didn't really teach your husband
how scary devils can be.
You said you'd do anything to protect him,
but you were just afraid he'd stop liking you.
You can't leave out the important stuff.
December 3, 23:35.
Target T was arrested on charges of
assault by F Squad.
Present on the scene: Senior Officer Sawazaki
and Officer Anzai.
I knew it!
You followed me, didn't you?
And hello? You didn't even lock the door?
A woman alone, in the middle of the night!
Uh, yes. You're right, I'm sorry.
But you left this here, so...
I'm sorry.
I'm surprised he's actually apologizing.
But from now on,
you don't have to bring me my stuff.
Understand?
Uh, yes.
Um... that woman...
An old friend.
We made snowmen together when we were kids.
It's cold.
Don't you ever get hurt in front of me again.
It's not easy to arrange for
non-family members to visit a devil.
But they might make an exception if the visitor
could help the devil reform himself.
If you want to see him, then...
Are you okay?
I mean, um... if you want...
A kotatsu.
Do you have one?
I only have the things I need to get by.
I think everyone needs one.
Do you get cold easily?
No, but my temperature's usually about 80 degrees.
Th-that's low!
Hey, Anzai. Where are you now?
How many times have I told you
to stop running off on your-
Sorry. I have to go.
And you make sure to lock your door.
Um, wait!
What? Do it with somebody watching? Not a chance.
Welcome back.
Hey, Anzai.
Right, here are your sedatives.
Oh, thanks. This'll help.
Where's Sawazaki? Not here yet?
He'll be here soon.
He said he's gonna be lecturing you all night.
Something about you running off on your own again?
He's right!
You've been such a stranger lately, Yuuki.
When you have this wonderful older woman taking
pity on you and inviting you over for some company.
Leave me alone.
Water, please.
Wait. Are you two dating?
Oh, please. Of course we are.
What? Really?
"Of course we are" not.
What's wrong with you guys?
Don't believe her.
So? What were you talking about?
Hm? Oh.
Just about a ridiculous new clause
they added to the guidelines.
Devil Conduct Guidelines Article 1:
Sexual intercourse between a human
and a vampire will now be legal,
as long as there is consent from
both parties and a doctor is present.
But is that really a good idea?
That "Tamaru" couple, they were a human and a devil.
They even signed a prenup promising not to
have sex, and look how that turned out.
What kind of hot pot should I make?
Huh? Hot pot?
In your apartment?
It's cold out on the balcony.
And I was hoping we could talk more.
No, wait. That's no reason to...
I can't just go in your room. That would be...
If... if it can...
wait until after my squad meeting tomorrow...
Okay, I'll stop by the store on my way
home from class and buy ingredients.
Is there anything you-
Hey...
What are you so happy about?
What? N-nothing!
You know, if you wait until my meeting's over,
we can meet up and I can carry the bags.
So, what school do you go to again?
Let's see, Professor Ochiai's office is...
Oh, here it is.
The lights are on-
Whoa!
Taira.
You startled me.
What are you doing here at this hour?
I-I came to return the book I borrowed.
What? So YOU had it.
S-sorry. I kept forgetting to return it.
Oh, no, that's okay.
What? Is it snowing outside?
I see. You must be cold, then.
Why don't you stay and warm up?
N-no, I...
I can at least make you some tea.
Devils and humans should
live apart from each other, huh?
Where did that come from?
Not from me. It's Anzai's creed.
Apparently Target T, Yuuko Tamaru, lived at
the orphanage with him when they were kids.
What?
I guess he's had a lot to think about
after we arrested that serial killer.
He's been checking on the girl who was
the motive behind the murders ever since.
Here. Careful, it's hot.
Th-thank you very much.
So, ummm... Right.
Where did I put it?
Maybe I'm just being neurotic.
Something about him scared me.
Oh, but...
I don't think I was scared the other day when he...
But wait... he was a total stranger, kissing me!
Normally, that would be much worse.
Something is wrong with me.
Your timing was perfect.
I got another good book.
I was thinking I'd lend it to you next time I saw you.
Oh, no...
I just had one of your books for over six months.
I couldn't borrow another one.
Hey, as long as it leads to a good thesis, I don't care.
You can keep this one another six months if you want.
Take it.
Oh, well, if you really don't mind.
I did not expect to be out this late.
Is this a good place to wait?
That guy's hot.
Think he's waiting for somebody?
Shh! He'll hear you!
Well, I'm just asking!
What am I doing?
N-no!
What are you doing?
It's so like you, not to swing it
straight at me, Taira.
But I really liked that mug.
I'm sorry...
I'm kidding.
Show me your hand.
You didn't have to do that.
If you didn't want me to,
you could have just said so.
J-just said so...?
But even if I don't, that doesn't mean you can just...
Really? I thought silence was consent.
But, Professor... You're married.
You have children...
What's your point?
You know, in the end, whether or not someone
turns into a monster is entirely up to them.
No!
What the hell?
Who are...
S-stop! That's enough!
You'll kill him!
Professor Ochiai?
What was that sound? Are you okay?
Call the police.
You can just tell them a vampire got in.
And tell them about the sexual assault
when they get here.
Hey, do you have a spare key?
Wait. Stay here.
Don't touch me!
Wh-what happened here?
Professor Ochiai! Are you okay? What's wrong?
Call an ambulance!
How in the world did this happen?
Ah! Wait! Professor!
I'm gonna be disciplined for this.
This is her blood.
I have to wash it off!
It's been two weeks.
Professor Ochiai was given a disciplinary dismissal.
NOTICE
Professor of Humanities
Keiji Ochiai
The above professor has been found in
serious breach of school policy.
He has been dismissed accordingly.
Keio University Dean
My hand has healed up, too.
See you later!
But since that night...
I've been seeing Professor Ochiai in my dreams.
Cold!
I wonder what he's doing now.
Wha... you're awake?!
Anzai.
Oh, um. That's to thank you for everything.
You made this?
Huh? Yes.
That's pretty good.
Sorry. Are you afraid of men?
I'm not scared. Not of you.
Why aren't you scared of me?
Because...
Oh! Your jacket is pretty warm.
And when I wear it, I feel like I won't...
have so many bad dreams...
You're having nightmares?
I'll get you something, too.
A present.
Sotto tokete yuku you ni
Motto ai shiaetara
Nani o tsutaerareta no
Ai o tsumugenai meguriawase
Dare ka yurushite
Kegareta sugata ga boku de aru koto o
Aa doushite
Fureru yubi ga furueteiru
It's story of fight together
Dakishimetai yo
Kizu tsukezu ni mamoritai yo
Anata dake o
It's story of desire forever
Aragai tsuzukeru
Wakiagaru shoudou ni
"Aa, mata boku wa..."
Deep red dawn
Sotto futari tokete yuku you ni...
Next Time
Devils' Line:
Line 3,
"Paradox."
Paradox