Howwonderful itwould be,
to be like Hakim...
...to be able to speak my mind,
and put my thoughts into action.
Sometimes, I'm jealous of him.
Episode 5
The Dinner Party
Come now, you have to stay still.
Try not to move.
It's harder than I expected.
It can't be helped. These things take time...
Was I asleep...?
I had a dream just now.
A dream, ma'am?
To have dreamt of him...
How many years has it been?
My mistress married when she was 18.
She Iost her husband when
she was 20, becoming a widow.
She has no children.
After working as a governess
for 30 years, she retired,
and has Iived here ever since.
Thank you. It has gotten a bit cold.
My mistress rarely talks about her past.
That's all I really know of it.
Emma.
Mr. and Mrs. Knox will be
joining me for dinner tonight.
Eh?
How is it, do we have enough?
I think we'll be all right.
It all depends on the menu, though.
I see... I can't believe
I invited them, and then forgot...
Honestly. It's fortunate that I remembered.
Let's see, there's the coke...
Oh yes, and candles need to be brought out.
Do we still have some?
Ah, right away, ma'am.
It's all right, I'll set the table.
You just concentrate on dinner.
Do the best you can, dear.
Yes, ma'am.
How is dinner coming along?
The bread is nearly ready.
Well done.
It seems a shame to open this,
but I guess it's all right.
The candles are ready.
The table is set.
We have plenty of coke.
Emma! Can you come here, please?
Yes, ma'am!
What is it, ma'am?
The rain soaked through,
and the wallpaper has...
These walls are old...
By the way, what about your work, mate?
It's not a problem.
No one at work even knows that I'm here.
What?!
You two all right? Your faces are pale...
Excuse me...
Could you hurry, please?
My guests will be here soon.
It's not my fault that it rained!
There we go!
Thank you for your help.
Unfortunately, that stain is permanent.
The paper'll have to be changed.
I see. You'll take care of it then, won't you?
You know, this house
really has seen better days.
Just like its owner.
It can't be helped.
We're so old, the both of us.
I'll have to check my schedule.
Next time I'm free, I'll stop by.
As I understand it, you're
always free during the day.
Looks like your guests are here.
I'll use the back door.
Al, wait a moment.
Emma, bring something to drink.
This way.
Eh, the kitchen is fine with me.
Old Kelly isn't very good with people.
It must be hard on you, too.
The mistress has always been good to me.
Say...
Did she say that the
Knoxes were coming tonight?
Yes.
Don't you have anything else?
This stuff's too good for them.
What?
Nothing... It's just that my
mistress said the same thing.
Ah!
Um...
Yes?
Have you known
the mistress for a long time?
Yeah. Her late husband Doug
and I were good friends.
That's why Kelly occasionally
asks me to help out.
You knew the master?
We lived near each other.
When we were young, we used to
pinch apples together in Covent Garden.
Hasn't Kelly ever told you about her past?
Yes... But only that her husband died.
Oh?
Were you friends with my mistress too?
Eh?
Oh, no, I mean... I just wondered where
the mistress and her husband had met...
Nowhere, it was an arranged marriage.
I think they married after meeting three times.
Oh, really?
It's a common thing.
Kelly is a stern woman.
But even so, when it
came to her husband, she-
Are you talking about me?
Well then, guess it's time to go!
Wait a moment!
You're in luck. It seems
the Knoxes aren't coming.
What?
Emma, it would be a shame to
let your hard work go to waste...
...so let's enjoy this meal together, all three of us.
Eh?
What's wrong, William?
You're certainly off form today.
You've done nothing but miss.
Hm? Yeah...
On the other hand, your
lndian friend can't do anything wrong.
So it would seem.
It's as though he doesn't
have a care in the world.
I wouldn't say that.
Bravo!
To Emma!
Wha-?
To Mr. and Mrs. Knox!
Al, you're not as strong with
alcohol as you used to be.
I've always been weak where
ladies and fine wine are concerned!
Would you like another roll?
This bread is really delicious.
I'll have two or three rolls if I can.
I'm fine, thank you.
It certainly was delicious, though.
You wouldn't think it to look at her now,
but Kelly was once a beauty.
You should be silent when you eat.
Even though it was an arranged marriage,
Doug fell in love with Kelly at first sight.
I could tell she was stubborn,
so I tried to warn him...
I can hear you, you know.
She was tart with me,
but always so kind to Doug.
But of course. He was my husband.
They were... a handsome couple.
Well then, guess I'll fetch some more wine.
I'll go...
Nah, I'm fine.
I'm just fine.
He'll be all right. No need to worry.
Yes, ma'am.
He may be old, but a
bottle of wine won't hurt him.
He's a good man, Mr. Al.
I worry that he is still on his own.
You were 15 when you came here.
I had left the Jones' employ as a governess,
and had just retired to this house...
It's been five years since then...
Time move so quickly.
By the way, Emma... What are your
thoughts on Young Master William?
Will you turn him down too?
I've never met anyone like him.
Although he's of the gentry,
he doesn't seem to notice that I'm a maid...
It's true... that young man
can be rather careless.
He doesn't ask me simple "yes or no"
questions like others do...
...he always seems happy just to talk.
Do you like him?
I see...
What has William been up to recently?
What do you mean, sir?
He appears to be wasting a great deal
of time goofing off with Hakim.
Yes, sir.
Master William spends much of his
time at the residence of Mrs. Stownar.
Mrs. Stownar? You mean his
former governess, Kelly Stownar?
Yes, sir. Master William is
a thoughtful young man.
He seems concerned about his aging governess.
I don't believe there's any cause for concern.
I wonder where he is.
He's been gone a long time.
I'll go see, ma'am.
Please tell him that I've retired to bed.
I'm very tired tonight...
Yes, ma'am.
What the... Was I asleep?
The mistress has retired to bed,
and asked me to say goodnight to you.
Oh.. In that case, I'll retire too.
Ma'am?!
Ma'am!
Are you all right?
Yes... I'm fine...
It doesn't seem broken.
All right, here we go...
Hold on to me.
I turned back to get a book I was
reading, but I lost my footing...
...and then I slipped.
Such a bother. Thanks to you,
I'm completely sober now!
Emma, can you check the staircase later?
I seem to have lost my old-
I think I managed to gather most of it...
The string must have broken, then.
It can't be helped. Just leave it as it is.
Yes, ma'am.
Al, I'm sorry, but might l
ask you to do one more job?
Yeah, sure.
Honestly, you really aren't
very good with people, are you?
Here we go...
Slowly now...
There we go.
Good, good.
Ma'am!
Here, this is for you...
I tried my hand at fixing it.
Is this as it was?
It's as good as new!
But how...?
I used this photograph as a guide.
It's such a lovely necklace.
Was it a present from your husband?
Yes...
Emma.
Yes, ma'am?
Come here.
I'd like you to have this.
Ma'am?
It doesn't suit me anymore.
But...
I'm sure Doug would be happy for you to have it.
I've finished the wallpaper.
Then, could you take a look
at the gutters out back next?
It seems as though the rain is leaking in.
Please.
Emma, could you make a pot of tea please?
Yes, ma'am.
You took a photograph?
Isn't Kelly a beauty?
Of course that's what you'd say.
Well, it's a nice keepsake.
Yeah. I plan on having one taken every year.
You have to stay still for so long.
My shoulders felt stiff.
Oh dear, we've run out of sugar.
Say Al, can you run and buy some for us?
Why me? Ask Doug.
But Doug's my husband.
I can't ask him to run errands.
Right. Because I'm the husband.
Come now, hurry up!
Yeah, sure.
Honesly... She's so bad with people...
Next Episode:
The Visit