Hey, that lndian prince who's visiting...
...he's kind of cute, isn't he?
You think so? I wasn't that impressed...
I think he's a bit odd.
What? But serious men are so tiresome!
Eccentric guys are so much fun,
and much more interesting!
That man really is...
Wonderful...
What?!
Episode 4
Mudie's
Hey, William!
First an elephant, and now an automobile...?
This is such an amusing toy!
It can move around without a horse.
An automobile is for outside use.
But this is inside.
I see...
Anyway Hakim, weren't you
supposed to go home after a week?
I've changed my mind.
What?
There are many things I find
interesting here in England.
All right then, let's go!
Go where?
An automobile is for outside use, right?
Let's make a day of it,
and go sightseeing together!
H-Hey, hold on!
Not again...!
Emma?
Please go and borrow this book for me.
Yes, ma'am.
What was his business here, I wonder?
Hm?
The lndian prince.
O-Oh, well...
With the way he was dressed,
the neighbors will gossip.
I'm sorry...
There's no need for you to apologize.
Hey, Hakim! This is against the law, someone's
supposed to walk ahead of us with a red flag!
Oh, this is bad.
Didn't you check it before you left?
Is it broken?
No, but there's no fuel in the tank.
Fu-fuel...
What's "fuel"?
If you can wait here,
I'll send someone on with a message.
It's a bit far to send someone home...
Well then, how about a carriage?
I don't have any money with me...
Ah...
William.
What is that? People are going in.
Oh, that's Mudie's. It's a book lender.
Mudie's?
It looks interesting.
What? H-Hey, Hakim!
Hey wait, what about the automobile?
Sorry! I'll come back for it.
Oh, look!
Here, this book!
This is such a lovely story.
It's about a woman born into a poor family...
...and her affair with a nobleman.
It's a love that crosses social boundaries!
My, how romantic!
I think I'll borrow it next time!
Yes! I certainly reccomend it.
I look forward to it!
H-Hey, Hakim!
Don't just wander off like that!
William, look at this.
It's filled with pictures of women.
Hakim! What on Earth are you looking at?
Oh, I see. So it's one of those books.
Where did you find such a book?
It was right there.
Let's see... Two books then, miss?
This one will be on my card.
Then, please go to counter E.
Here you are, your member card.
Sign here, please.
Yes...
Nothing at all remarkable. How boring.
Just because your women go around
half-naked most of the time...
How about this woman?
Well, I think this one's a bit better.
Which one?
She's nice.
Isn't she?
Hakim...?
Hey, Haki-
Eh?! Oh, um... Emma! That is...
Why are you...
Wait, asking "why" is silly.
You're here to borrow a book, of course.
But, to meet you here!
Were you about to go home?
Yes...
Well, I'll take you home, then!
Oh, wait, the automobile isn't working.
Erm, ah...
Um... I have to be going now...
Huh? Emma?
Hm?
That's Kelly's maid...
What?
She's running...
She's so young!
Run, run, o young one!
In a life so short and fragile as a dream...
...don't be afraid, take hold of time and run!
Is that Goethe?
It's me.
What is it?
Nothing...
Hakim... Are you hiding something from me?
That's right.
Grace invited me to a game of tennis.
Huh?
So much free time on her hands...
She's always looking for something to do.
That's all my sisters ever think about.
A leisurely life makes for beautiful ladies.
What?
And they give us pleasure in return.
Have you ever honestly loved anyone?!
Is there a way to falsely love someone?
I pity the woman who falls in love with you!
Why are you so angry?
Shut up!
Honestly, brother Arthur!
Playing so seriously against a child...
You're being immature!
A match is a match.
You make that "child" excuse
whenever it suits you.
Fine, I quit.
I'll play a match with you, if you'd like.
Ah, Prince Hakim!
Please, let's play!
Isn't Hakim wonderful?
He truly is wonderful!
More than wondeful, he's a prince!
How lovely, to be a prince.
But being married to a prince
would be difficult.
That's true. It would be difficult!
But he's a prince that has elephants!
What? He has elephants?
That's right!
Phew, I'm saved.
How wonderful!
Come to think of it...
Arthur, I heard that you've
become a school prefect.
How wonderful! A prefect?
I heard it from Grace!
Is that so?
Well, yeah.
Hey, what's a prefect?
You sure like being in charge, don't you?
Well it's fine for you,
you're inheriting the house.
But when it comes to my future...
...I don't have the luxury to relax.
Hey... what's a prefect?
Vivian! You're better than
Charlotte Cooper at Wimbledon!
Really, Prince Hakim?
He's quite a character...
Hey, Arthur?
What is it, Colin?
Ah, here she is.
Indeed, here she is.
We were waiting for you.
Good day, Eleanor.
Hello.
Grace, what a lovely dress!
It really is lovely!
Thank you.
Grace, please sit here.
Yes, please do!
Sister, you're such a gossip.
Eh? What are you talking about?
You told everyone about my becoming a prefect.
Arthur, what's a prefect?
Well, why not?
Arthur, you mustn't be mean to our dear Grace.
Yes, don't be mean!
Arthur...!
Wh-Why are you crying, Colin?
What's a pre-prefect?
It means a student representative.
A senior student, who's chosen to
monitor and advise the younger students.
There's no need to cry...
Arthur, you were being mean
to Colin, weren't you?
You were rather mean.
Of course he was being mean.
Hello.
Hello. Nice weather we're having.
Uh, um... If you don't mind...
...could you teach me how to play tennis?
Well, I'm not really
good enough to teach people...
But I've never played before!
Huh?
I... don't know the first thing about it...
Well then, If I can be of help.
Really?!
Of course. Shall we?
Let's rest a while, Vivian!
Okay, Prince Hakim!
Hey!
Oh, I'm so thirsty!
Hey, Vivi!
Say, would you look at that...
Those two look very happy!
They make a nice couple!
I'm a bit jealous.
One, two, three! One, two, three!
Just like that. You're doing great!
When you hit the ball, bring your wrist back.
One, two, three! One, two, three!
It seems he's no fool after all.
Eh?
If all goes well between those two,
we could have a title in the family.
Arthur...
It's more than the Jones family
could have hoped for.
Stop it, Arthur!
One, two, three! One, two, three!
William.
Hakim...?
And then, Annie...
William had said that he
couldn't play tennis well.
But you know, that prince from lndia?
Prince Hakim?
That's right!
He beat Prince Hakim!
He was so modest.
William is very quiet,
but he can be forceful too.
What time do you think it is?
I can't sleep.
Of course you can't sleep,
with all this commotion.
I held this party because I couldn't sleep.
Smoke?
No, thanks.
I was thinking...
Eh?
There's something I want to tell you.
W-What is it?
William...
I confessed to Emma.
Co-confessed...
In other words, I proposed to her.
I see...
But she turned me down.
What?
Is that so...
No, not that I'm happy...
I'm sorry...
It's all right.
I know how you feel.
You do?
You're easy to read.
Then why?!
You love her, but you haven't done
anything about it yet, have you?
Then why?!
You love her, but you haven't done
anything about it yet, have you?
If you've exchanged promises, that's different.
Why don't you tell her?
Why...? I've only just met her.
Besides, I don't know how Emma feels...
And what about how you feel?
If you hesitate, I'll take her from you.
What are you saying? She turned you down.
That's not really much of a problem.
What...?
Hakim...
It will be a wonderful day for both of them.
What?
Call it women's intuition.
Emma!
Mr. Jones?
Um...
Yes?
Nothing...
Well... shall we go back?
Yes...
Um, Hakim told me.
Eh?
Hakim does things without thinking...
But, he's not a bad guy.
I've known him since public school...
I have already given
Prince Hakim my answer.
Huh? No...
What am I saying?
This isn't about Hakim...
Sometimes, I'm jealous of Hakim.
I think about how wonderful would it be,
if I could speak my mind,
and put my thoughts into action.
Yes... I do as well.
Huh? You feel that way too, Emma?
Yes.
But, I could never be like Hakim.
Be who you are...
I like you just the way you are, Mr. Jones.
Emma...
That's right!
Are you hungry?
Let's get something to eat!
U-Um...!
I've been tense all day.
I haven't eaten a thing!
Welcome home, Young Master.
Teresa!
Y-Young Master!
Glad you're doing well!
Young Master William!
For Heaven's sake!
Next Episode:
The Dinner Party