Iread your letter.
You're really going, then?
That day... I figured that William
boy must have met up with you.
He didn't.
Perhaps I said too much and scared him off.
It might sound conceited of me to say so,
but I don't think that's the case.
Well... sometimes, trying to be considerate
can make a person hesitate...
But, he should at least see you off!
Episode 12
Lilies of the Valley
I see. So you're going to retire
from being a governess?
Yes. I'm getting on in years.
I need to take things easier.
Who's this girl?
Oh, she's a girl who was living on the streets.
She here came looking for work,
so I use her for simple jobs.
She looks intelligent.
Which reminds me, I've been wanting a maid.
Come now Kelly, you can't be serious.
She's not the type you can train to be a maid.
She's perfect. I've always wondered how much
can be accomplished through education.
What?
I'll teach you everything from scratch.
Will you come with me?
Yes, ma'am.
That's it, then.
It's fine with you, I trust?
Honestly...
Don't blame me if you regret it.
Thank you for everything...
...ma'am.
Red sky at night.
Shepherd's delight.
Red sky in the morning.
Shepherd's warning.
Vivi?
It's not my fault.
It takes a lot for father to raise
his hand against someone.
But it was bound to happen sooner or later.
Don't worry, Colin.
Like they say, if it rains
before 7, it'll be fine by 1 1.
Brother Will will be fine soon, too.
So there's no need to fret.
Is William ready to go?
Well, sir... he appears to be in his room, but...
Master...
William, open the door!
William!
Oh, you've finally decided to come out.
Only because I wanted to get away.
When she really needed someone
by her side... I couldn't be there for her.
Did l... ever really know her?
I was only thinking of myself. I didn't
consider what would make Emma happy.
Well... I wanted to consider her feelings.
But Emma was suffering so badly.
Even if I decided to marry Emma,
she would have to take on the Jones name.
She'd be bound by the strict traditions of
polite society, exposed to the curiosity of others...
Sacrificing so much, would Emma
ever really be happy marrying me, I wonder?
Am I even a worthy partner for Emma?
When I think of it... I become
too afraid to face her.
Go ahead and call me spineless.
You are undoubtedly spineless.
Also miserable, and pathetic.
You're not prepared to lose Emma,
yet you keep acting all melodramatic.
Hey.
You're overdoing it a bit, aren't you?
You asked me to say it.
You love Emma...
...and Emma loves you.
What else do you want?
Why are you so confused?
I don't understand you at all.
More importantly, if you don't hurry and
stop Emma, you'll never see her again.
What do you mean?
Emma said she was going
back to her childhood home.
What?
Why didn't you say that sooner?
Because I didn't really want to tell you.
Please summon the coachman.
What?
But...
What's wrong? Quickly now, hurry up!
Eleanor...
I was told to ask you out for a ride,
but there must have been some mistake...
I'm very sorry.
It's all right.
Eleanor, you have to know. I...
I'll wait for you.
What...?
It doesn't have to be today, or tomorrow.
I really don't mind...
So please, invite me out again...
...because, I'm waiting for you.
Please prepare the carriage.
Yes, sir. Where to?
To Marylebone. Hurry up!
The upper level's full!
Aw!
Don't be stubborn about it. Come back down.
Okay.
How very naughty! Behave yourself!
Emma! Emma!
I can see it!
That's Kings Cross station, right?
Yes, it is.
Here now! Don't run!
Can't you go any faster?!
That would be dangerous,
we're in the middle of the city.
I don't care! Go faster!
Y-Yes, sir.
One third class ticket, please.
Oh, I'm afraid third class is full.
What?
We still have second class tickets.
Second... class?
If you'd have come just a bit earlier
you might have gotten into third class.
It's only a difference of 5 or 6 shillings.
One first class round-trip ticket to York.
What'll it be?
Well, that will have to do.
Round-trip?
No... one way.
Oranges, oranges!
They're two for a penny!
Extra! Extra!
This is the engine of the Midland Railways...
...and this is the Great Northern. This one here.
Really?
It's really, really fast.
It can hit 50 miles an hour!
Hey now! You're not supposed to doodle there!
'Scuse me! Make way, please!
Luggage coming through!
Oh, it seems we've got the wrong number.
We still have time to change it,
so please hurry back to the ticket window.
Oh!
I'm so sorry. I mistook you for someone else.
It's all right.
Madam!
It's really crowded over there too!
Eh? You mistook her for me?
Whatever shall I do with you, Madam?
I wonder if you will notice this letter...
That we must part this way... it is my one regret.
However, my heart now feels
strangely peaceful and calm.
Even though our love crossed classes
and was never meant to be,
that our hearts have touched in this way...
...has meant everything to me.
The memories we shared
will stay with me, always.
No matter how far away I am,
I will always pray for your happiness.
Um, please buy a flower.
How much is it?
One penny.
I'll have one, then.
Thank you.
May the grace of God go with you.
Oranges, oranges! Sweet, delicious oranges!
The train is about to depart.
Please hurry to your seats!
Emma!
Mr. Jones...
Emma...
Emma, l...
Thank you.
What?
Thank you so much.
Emma...
Emma!
Sir?
Please buy a flower.
Thank you, sir!
May the grace of God go with you.
That's beautiful...
It's a lily of the valley, isn't it?
Yes... though I'm not sure why I bought it.
Oh, don't worry about that!
Flowers are great to have anywhere.
In the "language of flowers," that lily is
wonderful, too. Do you know what it means?
No...
It means that "happiness will return."