Prince Hakim!
Miss Vivian!
Miss Vivian, that's dangerous!
Come down, miss!
Miss Vivian!
Why did you let her climb up?
But, there was no time to stop her!
What are you doing?
Taking a nap.
On the roof?
It's too cramped inside that house.
What?
But our house is so big...
Episode 10
Missing One Another
Say, Prince Hakim...
Will you play tennis with me again?
Emma.
Huh?
Emma?
Emma... as in, the girl that
brother Will was talking about?
Ah, Prince Hakim?
Where's William?
I believe he will return soon.
There's someone here to see him.
Please let her through.
Yes, sir.
Who are you, then?
You have some business here?
N-no...
Pardon me, but are you
here to see Master William?
Yes.
If you would, please come in.
But...
It's fine.
I've been asked to tell you to wait inside.
Come with me, please.
Please wait here.
But l... I shouldn't...
Please.
That's her?
I'm sure of it. He said her name's Emma.
What's this?
It's brother's maid.
Why was she shown to the guest room?
She's pretty.
For a maid.
You think so? I think she's rather plain.
She's even wearing glasses!
It's a shame about Mrs. Stownar.
What?
If I had known about it,
I would've attended the funeral.
Um... What funeral?
Didn't you know? Mrs. Stownar... she died.
She's dead?
He didn't know, did he...
That's dangerous!
I'm sorry.
Take me to Marylebone.
What?
And hurry!
Yes, sir.
Brother Arthur, don't push!
He changed clothes...
H-Hey! Why are we running away?
Because.
I hate that guy. I never know what he's thinking!
Huh?
Where's Colin?
Prince Hakim.
I'll be leaving now.
Didn't you have something to tell William?
I just... wanted to say goodbye.
But... it's fine.
What do you mean?
I'm going back to the village where I was born.
Where you were born?
It's a small town by the sea.
Though, it might not be there anymore.
I don't understand.
My mistress has died.
I can no longer stay at her home.
Is your village far away?
Yes.
When will you come back?
I won't be coming back.
It's strange...
You love William and William loves you, right?
So why would you run to some
far-off place on your own?
I'm sorry... I'm so sorry, Colin!
It's not as though we forgot about you...
But we did forget about him.
Arthur!
He was wearing musk cologne.
I wonder what Prince Hakim
could possibly have to say to her?
It looks like brother Will still hasn't
given up, in spite of what father said.
He doesn't understand anything.
It's none of our affair.
I'm sure our brother knows what he's doing.
She must be a fortune hunter.
I agree. This whole maid business is too strange!
Don't say such ridiculous things!
It must be true! She's seducing our brother!
Wha... Vivi! Where did you learn such a word?
He's so naive.
He certainly is. To fall into her trap like that!
I'm going to give her a piece of my mind!
V-Vivi!
Come back here, Vivi!
That's right. She planned it all along!
How dare she come to the house!
She is utterly shameless!
Brother Will...
...is such a simpleton!
Hey, you! I don't know what your intentions are,
but you should just give up and go home!
Brother Will's stupidity is one thing,
but you don't have any common sense either!
A servant is a servant. A master is a master.
How do you not understand something so simple-
Vivi!
Sister, what are you doing? Let me go!
Who was that?
That was William's sister.
His sister...?
It seems we have an unexpected guest.
Yes, sir.
She's an acquaintance of Master William's.
Prince Hakim is entertaining her at the moment.
I see...
I know, I know. Let me go now! Let go!
You really are hopeless.
Why? You don't approve of her either!
You shouldn't shout like that.
You never know who's listening!
What's more, we've only just
been accepted by the gentry.
If rumor gets out that
our brother is courting a maid,
we'll be the laughing stock of polite society.
That's enough!
None of you seem to realize the situation we're in!
Ah... why am I being scolded
when she's the one at fault?
Thank you for the food.
I don't feel well... May I leave the table, please?
Is that so? Then rest a bit, dear.
I will.
I'm sorry.
Has she seen a doctor?
There's no need.
It would seem our daughter is lovesick.
It will be wonderful if the match with
the Jones family goes through, won't it?
Don't make so much noise!
Forgive me, sir.
It's true, isn't it...
I kept thinking that we lived in the same place.
You both live in the same England.
No, we don't.
Coming here, I understand.
I realize that the worlds we live in...
are completely different.
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
William will be back soon.
No, I must go.
Now that I think about it,
it's good that we didn't meet today.
It isn't good.
Now that I think about it,
it's good that we didn't meet today.
It isn't good.
It isn't good at all.
I gave you up because William loves you.
Don't just leave. Don't decide this by yourself.
I've already made up my mind.
Emma...
I didn't know. I'm... so sorry...
It must have been so lonely...
Mr. Jones...
You should be ashamed.
I've done nothing to be ashamed of.
It's you who should be ashamed, father.
Could you leave us now?
I'll make certain you are well paid.
Father!
Excuse me.
Emma!
Stop right there!
How could you say such a thing?
Emma!
Brandy, sir?
Oh, thank you.
What's wrong?
Well, come on in.
Next Episode:
The Past