It's been too long.
Episode 3
The Confession
Mr. William...
Uh, Mr. William?
Here's this month's stock list.
Oh, right.
Also, regarding the goods that
have yet to arrive by sea...
Should we inquire about them
once more, just in case?
Yep. I'll leave that to you.
Excuse me, sir!
Uh...
There is a visitor at the door...!
A visitor?
What in the world is this?
Ha-
Hakim!
Long time no see, William.
Are you surprised to see me?
I can't believe you rode here on an elephant...
But at any rate, why the surprise visit?
My grandmother's been
giving me a hard time at home.
Sometimes you just feel like
taking a trip by yourself.
"By yourself," eh?
You always came to visit me.
I thought I'd return the favor
and come to visit you instead.
Brother...
Ah, let me introduce you.
This is my friend from lndia, Hakim.
A pleasure to meet you.
I'm William's sister, Grace.
He's told me about you.
Thank you for always looking after him.
Huh? I'm the one who was
always looking after him...
He's so exotic and handsome!
I can't believe he's a friend of brother Will's!
Are you serious?
Even so...
...I never expected to see
a sight like this here!
If you like the elephants, I'll give you one.
Choose whichever one you want.
Thanks, but no thanks.
Besides, can those creatures be trusted?
If something that large
was to go on a rampage...
Ah, no need to worry about that.
Elephants are really quite calm and docile.
It's rare for them to attack a human.
They're very clever, sacred creatures.
If that's true...
...then perhaps you'd be able to
explain what's happening outside?
Don't worry about him.
He's just a bit cranky.
Anyway, I plan to stay for a week.
What?
And since I'd like to keep things quiet,
please don't tell anyone else that I'm here.
What?
Oh my!
"A member of the lndian royal family,
the son of Atawari, Hakim Atawari..."
"...is staying with the Jones family in secret."
Well, if it's in the newspaper,
it's not much of a secret.
India, you say?
The Jones family is involved in trade.
It's something to do with their work, no doubt.
India...
So then, did he come on an elephant?
That's unlikely!
Master William.
Is that you, Stevens? What is it?
Mister Hakim would like to
see you in his room, sir.
Hakim, I'm coming in.
Wha...?
Hakim... this is...
Impressive, isn't it? I can redecorate
your room this way too if you like.
No thanks... I'll pass.
You really do need to relax more.
Anyway, what did you want me for?
Ah, yes.
Since I've come all this way to England,
I thought some sightseeing would be nice.
Very well. I'll prepare a carriage for you.
That won't be necessary.
What's that?
I haven't drank enough yet to be hallucinating.
Has London zoo started up sightseeing trips?
Large animals like elephants should
use the tube tunnels, don't you think?
We're so conspicuous...!
Impressive, huh? Even lndians
don't often see this kind of thing.
Well, it certainly is remarkable, but...
But I can't get used to the swaying...
I'm happy you approve.
All right then, as a special favor,
I'll show you how fast this one can go.
How fast?
Speed up!
Hey now, what are you...?
W-Wait a minute!
If we go faster, the swaying...
...will just get worse...
Isn't it wonderful? This is my fastest elephant.
I understand that... can we please just...
Mr. Jones?
Ha-Hakim! Please, stop!
Wow, neat!
Are you all right?
You'll feel a bit better if you throw up...
How disgraceful, for a grown man
to feel ill from a simple ride.
People were never meant to ride such things.
To think...
...that an elephant... would move that much...
...I had no idea-
You're sweating badly.
Does that feel a bit better?
Yes, much better.
Honestly, you gave me such a scare!
You always drop in on people so unexpectedly!
Forgive me.
Well, I'll let you off the hook for today.
Yes, ma'am...
Pleased... to meet you.
Hakim...?
Oh! I'm sorry. This is Hakim.
He's visiting from lndia.
Emma.
Yes?
Everything's fine now.
You may return to work.
Yes, ma'am.
Emma...
It's not so bad when you get used to it.
And I was able to meet Emma.
What is is, Hakim? You've been very quiet.
Are you feeling ill?
Huh? Has someone gone out?
Yes, sir. Your guest left a few minutes ago.
Hakim did?
Emma.
Mr. Hakim?
I'll give you a ride home.
Eh? No, I'm fine...!
U-um...
There's no need to refuse.
That Hakim...
Why is Emma...?
Follow that carriage!
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
Oh that's right, lndian food
uses many spices, doesn't it?
That's right.
But, isn't adding all those
spices bad for your health?
Turmeric, cloves,
cardamom, coriander, cumin,
ajwain, fennel...
There are many spices,
but they're all good for your health.
Hakim!
What is it?
Uh, no... Never mind...
The Wilbur and Hopkins Company...
...here to see me?
They have come to deliver the item you ordered.
Thank you very much for your order.
Here is the completed item.
I see... Hm?
I trust the name is correct?
The name?
Wha- What?
Eh?
Ah, b-but...
The order form says that I should
deliver this to the Jones residence.
May I see that?
Of course.
Please come in.
Are you alone today, sir?
Yes.
The mistress will be home soon.
Please have a seat, sir.
I hope you find the taste agreeable, sir.
Actually, I came here to see you.
Emma, are you and William lovers?
What?
No, nothing like that...
I'm glad. It would have
been awkward if you were.
William is one of my most precious friends.
I don't want to betray his friendship.
I know that it's sudden,
and that we've only just met.
Forgive me, I don't mean to
cause you trouble... That is...
You see,
I love you.
Although I don't know you very well,
I love the way you stand.
I love the way you move,
and the way you speak so gently.
Your dulcet voice is beautiful as well...
But I love your face most of all.
My... face?
Don't you like your own face?
I apologize if I upset you, but...
Emma... if you don't mind,
I'd like to take care of you.
That's what I wanted to tell you...
At any rate, I just wanted to see you again.
William.
You've had that gloomy look on your face
all night. Did something happen?
No, not really.
By the way, I saw the newspaper.
Seems like there's a lot going on at your place.
Isn't your famous guest with you today?
Oh, no... I'll introduce you next time.
Then again...
...I suppose if a member of the
royalty has come all this way to England,
he must be out searching for a wife!
I guess there's no use for this now.
Next Episode:
Mudie's