I'm sorry... I just couldn't be alone.
That's all right.
Thank you.
So, what do you intend to do now?
I'm thinking of going back
to the village where I was born.
I see.
But, what about the Jones boy?
That doesn't matter now.
Kelly was worried about you
and that boy until the very end.
She asked me to look after you.
It was rare for that old lady
to ask something of me so humbly...
The mistress was worried?
As you can see, I don't really
have the means to employ a maid.
Nor do I know anyone who can,
on such short notice...
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
If only Kelly were still alive...
Oh, I'm sorry!
If I keep that up, the old lady
won't be able to rest in peace.
It was my decision.
If I keep that up, the old lady
won't be able to rest in peace.
It was my decision.
I believe it's for the best.
I see...
Episode 11
The Past
And then, Master William, without
a care for who saw him, held her like this!
Unbelievable!
And what's more, the girl was a maid!
Who would have ever guessed?
She's really a maid?
So that's why he and
Master Richard got into a fight!
Eh? A fight?
That's right!
To think they fought over a maid!
You can't be serious!
Just think, if he were to marry her,
we'd have to call that maid "ma'am", eh?
Well I certainly wouldn't.
Well, she might be a maid now, but what if
she's a noble lady who's fallen on hard times?
I truly doubt that.
But it's an utter disgrace that Master
William should fall for a mere maid!
So you say, but are you sure you're not
planning to find a rich husband for yourself?
If I were 20 years younger!
Exactly!
You may object, but my feelings won't change.
If I cannot marry Emma,
then I shall never marry!
Do you not realize how insular polite society is?
Although fortune, land and position count,
the most important thing of all is...
...respectability.
You must be worthy of people's respect.
If not, you will be rejected.
The world is unforgiving.
I don't believe that marrying Emma
would warrant me losing respect!
It may take some time, but I believe
that people will understand in the end.
I've told you before...
Don't go thinking you can
graft a reed to an elm tree.
Elms grow in the hills, reeds by the water.
That's just the natural way of things.
If you try to bend the rules,
the reeds could wither and die.
If that's the case...
If that's the case, then l
shall have to live by the water!
That really happened at the Jones' house?
Well, that ends Miss Eleanor's
chances for marriage.
Indeed! It's as if the whole
Campbell family's been snubbed...
You're right.
And here I thought the Jones' wanted a title.
Hurry!
What?
Don't pay any attention to them.
It's bound to be an unfounded rumor!
Just between us gentlemen,
I'm rather tired of all these parties.
Already looking forward to the Epsom Derby?
Oh yes, I can't wait!
You prefer horses to ladies? Shame on you!
Excuse me for a moment.
Mrs. Campbell...
Mr. Jones.
A pleasure to see you.
Is Miss Eleanor with you today?
She's at a difficult age.
She seemed quite happy yesterday,
but today she's out of sorts again.
I haven't kept a close enough eye on William.
His recent behavior has been most inappropriate.
Many people behave inappropriately
in their youth, it can't really be helped.
Even so, some behavior is simply unacceptable.
I intend to hand out much
stronger discipline in the future.
The poor dear, don't be too hard on him.
Please ask him to invite Eleanor out sometime.
I certainly will. I'll inform William as such.
Young Master!
Young Master, please don't!
Someone, please stop the Young Master!
Mr. Stevens, stop him!
You must stop the Young Master, now!
Why didn't you stop him? The Master
didn't want him to leave the house!
The Young Master is not permitted to leave.
Yes, but...
So, Stevens understands
the workings of love as well.
That was not my intention...
I wish Master William to lead
the life he wants as well.
But, not with a maid! Even if he does love her,
it's obvious that life will always be hard for them.
I'm certain the Master is only thinking
of the Young Master's happiness.
Do you have some business here?
Ah! Um, do you know where Emma...?
Could you possibly be...?
Eh?
Please buy a flower, sir.
Um, sorry!
It's not exactly a place to bring nobility...
You'll have to forgive the mess.
Pardon my intrusion...
Step aside.
This whole place is falling to pieces.
I was going to have lunch with Emma.
I wonder where she's gone off to?
Anyway, have a seat.
If we wait here, she should be back soon.
Thank you.
It's started raining?
Um...
About this village of Emma's...
I don't know much about it either.
From what Kelly told me, she was
born in a little village by the sea.
The place was dirt poor.
She had no father, and her mother
died when she was very young,
so Emma was brought up in her uncle's home.
Emma!
Don't just stand there staring at nothing.
Bring the bucket here, quickly!
Is that all? Not much there, is there?
You've been off playing around!
That's all you're good at, weaseling out of work.
I wasn't playing.
Children shouldn't answer their elders back!
Before you came here,
we were so much better off.
Honestly. Your Uncle's soft, that's what it is.
So what if you're his sister's daughter?
That man's always been nothing but trouble.
You, take these into town and sell them.
And don't come back until you've sold them all!
Got it?
For pity's sake. Such a sullen child!
No...
No! No!!
No!
Let me out! Someone, help!
No! Let me out!
Please someone, let me out!
No!!
She was held prisoner in that carriage for days,
and then it seems she was brought to London.
Come here!
How about this one? She's a
country girl, but she has a nice face!
She's rather small.
And very thin. She'll take time to groom.
Think about it, she's a bargain!
If you're lucky, she'll be the
belle of the establishment.
How about 40?
I want someone I can use
immediately. 20 at the most.
Don't joke with me!
Nothing less than 37.
I'd be making a loss on that deal.
Oh!
That girl's runnin' away!
Imbecile! You took your eyes off her!
Come back here!
Damn it, where'd she go?
Please.
I'm afraid there's not much I can do.
Please. I'll work for it.
Even a scrap of bread will do.
I haven't eaten for days.
I'm sorry. Ask somewhere else, all right?
If you do something wrong,
I'll be the one who pays for it.
Sorry, can't help you.
No, no! We've got enough staff!
Please.
There's no end to girls like you! Go away!
If I can be of help, I'll do anything.
Please!
Where's the tea for upstairs?
Who's the girl?
She has no money, poor thing.
We'll be in trouble if the mistress finds out!
She won't find out! And she certainly
won't miss one piece of bread.
Thank you, very much.
Take your time, or you might choke.
This is how you make them.
You buy the flowers from Covent Garden.
The sweeter ones sell best.
If you do well, you can buy bread every night.
Please buy some flowers.
Would you like a flower?
Thank you very much, sir!
Please buy some flowers!
Would you like a flower?
Would you like one?
Going home?
Yes.
Emma should be home soon, I think.
Thank you very much, for all you've told me.
No need for thanks. Just felt like talking.
Next Episode:
Lilies of the Valley