Good morning, sir.
Do you know what the most important
trick to living in this country is, Stevens?
I'm sorry, sir. I do not...
It's knowing one's place.
Appropriate behavoir...
That's how order and dignity are maintained.
Episode 6
The Visit
Eggs.
Right away!
Emma, help me up.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry to make more work for you.
Not at all.
I suppose I should ask Al
to make me a walking stick.
Um, it really isn't any trouble for me...
I see.
It's perfectly fine.
I'd do anything for you, ma'am.
Stevens, my cigars.
Yes, sir.
Hey brother, borrow "The Death of
King Arthur" for me next time, okay?
I want to see Beardsley's drawings!
They're not appropriate for you to see.
Beardsley?
Apparently, he always wears black clothes.
They say he looks like the grim reaper.
The grim reaper just loves crybabies!
Stop that!
Maybe he'll come visit you tonight, Colin!
That's enough.
All right...
It's okay, there's no such
thing as the grim reaper!
The minute father leaves the room,
the place turns into a zoo.
Eh?
So you're out here again.
This is the most pleasant spot.
I see.
I envy you.
You want to rest in this girl's lap?
No!
Well, what is it then?
Because you can act as you please.
You can too, if you wish.
Balance, common sense,
principles and self-control.
Will those virtues make you happy?
I wonder if Beardsley would
dismiss those virtues so easily.
So as heir to the Jones estate,
employing nearly a hundred servants,
you can't just do as you please.
And yet... the world can change, if you want it to.
Young Master.
Yes?
You're not making any headway on your work.
Hmm... Nice weather, isn't it?
It's cloudy today.
It might rain this afternoon.
Master.
We must decide the new
footman's wages. What shall we do?
I'll leave that up to you.
Yes, sir.
Is William here?
I believe he has gone out, sir.
To where?
I'm sorry, sir. I did not ask.
Honestly. I wonder if he plans
to attend the ball tonight?
I'll stop by again soon.
He's blatantly using our store
as a rendezvous point now.
It certainly is cloudy today.
Yes.
And it was so nice this morning...
It made me want to go out somewhere.
That's true.
Shall we go somewhere?
If the weather's fine.
Do you not want to?
I do want to...
That's good.
Rain...
Here.
I'm fine. I'll hurry home.
Are you sure?
Goodbye.
I'll send you a letter, sometime...
Yes... Sometime...
It appears he's not coming.
Mr. Jones.
Oh, Mrs. Campbell.
That conspicuous young man
is a friend ofWilliam's?
Yes. William should take a leaf out of
his book when it comes to social skills.
Excuse me... but where is William?
He's an unpredictable boy...
Please invite him out for a drive
when the weather clears.
I'll relay the message to him.
Yes, of course!
Go and get yourself something to drink.
Eleanor speaks of nothing but
your son William these days.
I apologize, he's a boorish child.
Not at all! I'd be delighted ifWilliam
would take my daughter's hand in marriage.
It would be an honor.
By the way, have you heard?
I probably haven't, I'm afraid.
The ladies are much more up-to-date
than myself when it comes to gossip.
It's about Mrs. Stownar...
She's apparently had an accident.
What? To Mrs. Stownar's?
That's right. I informed her by post
that we'd visit this afternoon.
A visit... today?
Honestly, William. Why didn't
you tell me about the accident?
Well, l... didn't hear about it directly.
Directly or indirectly, if your mentor
is sick, you should call upon her.
Yes, sir...
Get ready then!
Y-yes, sir...
Good day!
Oh! Welcome, miss.
Do you have any asparagus?
I do. It just arrived yesterday.
Miss Emma!
Hello.
I'm going to boarding school soon!
Going soon!
Boarding school?
You're not going!
A state school, miss. Some strange new
changes have been made to the school system.
I'm losing my helper to the education board.
Besides, no one wants to marry
an educated woman!
It's fine!
We're in the era of learning.
If a girl can recite a piece of poetry,
she might even attract a man of noble birth.
Hah! Don't go giving her any stupid ideas!
Having an education doesn't ensure your future.
Here you go.
Study hard, okay?
I will!
Please come again!
Again!
Good day!
A letter, miss.
Thank you.
Yes?
Welcome home.
A letter, ma'am.
Well now.
What a splendid envelope.
Oh, this is a rare honor.
Here, ma'am.
Thank you.
I went to the market today.
It seems the price of vegetables
has gone down recently.
Is that so...
I've been making puddings
for dinner so often lately...
...so I bought some asparagus today.
Emma.
Mr. Jones and his son are calling in to see me.
There was no need for you to come...
I've been meaning to call
upon her anyway. It's fine.
It'll be enough if I just visit by myself...
William!
You need to learn a bit more about manners.
You never even visited your
governess until I told you to do so.
I am grateful for that advice at least.
It appears they have arrived.
Mr. Jones.
We've been waiting for you, sir. Right this way.
It's been too long!
I didn't expect you come all this way.
Forgive me for not standing up.
Not at all, Mrs. Stownar.
Please have a seat.
William.
Er... yes.
It's been a long time, Mr. Jones.
You haven't changed.
You look surprisingly well.
I merely twisted my leg. It's nothing serious.
William said nothing about it.
I apologize for not visiting sooner.
Please, think nothing of it.
I'm afraid my son has no manners.
He must have been so troublesome.
Oh, not at all. He was a fine student.
He just suffered from a
slight lack of concentration.
I'm certainly glad to hear that, but William
can be complacent. It's a flaw in his character.
I keep cautioning him about it,
but unfortunately he lacks
a sense of self-awareness.
You can't blame him. He's of a certain age.
I think it's about time for William to take...
Emma.
The scones.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
I think it's about time for William to
take charge of the family business.
Although I am very healthy at present,
I may meet with an accident
like yours at any time.
Father!
That is true.
I tried to be careful...
So when I consider what could happen,
it makes me very uneasy.
I think William will mature
if he takes on some responsibility.
I'm also arranging a match for him.
There's a certain lady who would like William
to take her daughter's hand in marriage.
Wait a minute! What are you talking about?
This is the first I've heard of it!
Of course. These matters have to be
discussed by the parents first.
Who are you talking about?
Mrs. Campbell's daughter.
What?
This isn't 50 years ago.
Just because the parents have
made up their minds about marriage,
it doesn't mean the children
must comply with their wishes.
Is there someone you have your heart set upon?
Wha-?
Well? Is there?
Well, you see...
I assume she is a lady worthy
of joining the Jones family.
Emma!
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Your personal feelings are important, of course.
But you must marry someone
from the same country.
She's not a foreigner, father.
England is one nation, but there
are two countries within it.
In other words, the aristocracy
and the commoners.
Although these two countries share
the same language, they are divided.
Mr. Jones!
Forgive me... This is not a subject
we should be discussing here.
We'd best be on our way.
William!
Next Episode:
Crystal Palace