Good morning!
Morning!
I'm sorry! Are you all right!?
I didn't realize anyone was there!
Uh... I'm fine...
Oh! Your hat!
What's wrong, Emma?
It's been a long time, ma'am.
It really has been a long time.
You've grown tall.
But it's strange...
Your face looked a bit better back then.
Oh, well, that's...
Episode 1
The Gift
Such bad timing! That's just like you.
I told you, didn't I Emma?
That I used to be a governess.
Yes.
Well this is the Young Master
I cared for, William Jones.
Y-Young Master...?
Have you stopped wetting the bed?
Of... Of course I have. A long time ago.
Looking back, I realize that the Jones family...
...had but a modest presence among the gentry.
Is your father well?
Yes.
Very well...
Ah, thank you...
I told you to come and see me,
but you never did...
Now, after all this time, you finally come.
You never cease to amaze me...
Have you never seen a maid before?
What...?
Of course...
I'll get it.
It's probably Mr. Graham.
You seem tense, sir.
What?
The truth is... that woman
always makes me feel uneasy...
I could tell.
She used to be even more
frightening, you know...
If I forgot my homework,
she'd make me sit
facing the wall for an hour...
Hm?
This is... me!
This brings back memories!
This is me, you know!
Yes, I can tell.
Huh? You knew?
The mistress talks about you sometimes...
I recognized you the moment we met.
Well, that's a bit embarrassing.
If I remember correctly,
this was taken on my 13th birthday...
I'm surprised she displays it here...
The Mistress doesn't have
any children of her own.
Don't you think she must
consider you as a son?
You think so? She was
always so angry with me...
That's just how she is.
I hope you learn to like her.
Yes.
Emma?
Yes?
There seems to have been a mistake.
Mr. Graham is apparently waiting
at the station. I will go and fetch him.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm afraid that I cannot
spare you any more time today.
What...?
Even retired people have busy schedules.
Next time, inform me by letter
when you will arrive.
After all, you must remember your manners.
Young man!
Yes...
Please visit me again soon.
I will.
You must tell me everything.
Oh...!
It appears he forgot these.
He's as careless as ever.
If I hurry...
It's fine. He can collect them next time.
I see.
Would you go deliver them?
Yes.
This is for your mistress...
...and there's one more.
It's from me. I'll await your reply
when next we meet.
The post?
Welcome home, ma'am.
Could you make some tea?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes!
Young Master, your father is calling for you.
Can we stop this "Young Master" business?
What are you saying?
You are the Young Master, after all.
My father talks for hours.
Can you tell him no?
Certainly not, Young Master.
What is that?
Don't you know? It's an airplane.
You're surprisingly light on your feet.
Young Master!
Can't sleep?
I just have to write this...
You seem to turn everyone down...
I didn't think you'd put your skills of
reading and writing to use in this way.
Ah well...
Do as you wish. As long as
you can work tomorrow.
Yes, ma'am...
That Kelly woman. She's a slave driver.
She never thinks about what other
responsibilities we might have.
Responsibilities, Al?
You're always either playing cards or drinking.
He surely is.
But then again, we're just the same as you, Al!
Let's go down to the Ruth and Bear again today!
A toast, to the God of beer!
Welcome!
'Come!
Potatoes, please.
Of course.
It's Miss Emma!
It's Miss!
Hello there.
Good day to you!
Mr. Jones, what can I do for you today?
Nothing.
Ah!
We've kept something for a
special customer such as yourself.
What do you think of this doll?
It's chinoiserie. They're currently all the rage.
Is that so...
Oh!
Well, how do you feel about this invention?
This is called a "tea-making clock".
It's a combination alarm clock
and teapot, quite a rare item...
Ah!
Mr. Jones?
Please deliver that to my house!
Miss Emma!
Thank you for yesterday.
Mr. Jones...
Hello...
I'm sorry. I didn't notice it was you.
Yesterday, your gloves...
Yes. In fact, I was just
thinking of visiting the house.
Mr. Jones...?
Um...
Would you do me the honor...
...of taking a walk with me?
Please sir, buy some flowers.
Flowers...
This park wouldn't be so crowded
if it weren't for The Season.
On top of that, Sydenham's Crystal Palace
was built here for the World Trade Festival...
I'm sorry, I'm talking too much.
That's all right... I don't mind.
That large elm tree back there was
apparently going to be chopped down, but...
Oh, a squirrel.
What?
Look, up there!
Could it be that earlier, you also couldn't...?
Yes, my eyesight is somewhat...
Of course!
May I buy you a new pair of
spectacles as a present?
What?
That's right, of course!
Please let me buy them for you.
But really, I couldn't...
But look!
Birds are flying...
Flowers are blooming...
Children are falling over!
Really, it's no problem at all!
Rain...
I'm sorry. They only had one left.
Are you sure you don't want a carriage?
But you just rented that umbrella...
And to be honest,
I rather like walking in the rain.
To be honest, so do I.
Well then, I'll say goodbye here.
Your gloves...
It's all right, I'll come back again.
The poor flowers have wilted...
Send my regards to the mistress.
And please do think about the spectacles.
That he should send wilted flowers!
He really is careless.
But, I cut their stems...
By taking in a little air and water,
they seem to have regained their freshness.
Very well.
I'm sure the flowers weren't for me anyhow.
He sends his regards to you.
Is that so...
You've broken another cup?
I'm sorry...
Sometimes you leave dust on the banisters.
You must be more careful.
Yes...
Oh dear, I wonder who that dog belongs to?
Well?
How are they?
They might feel strange
until you're used to them.
Yes, ma'am.
The birds...
How beautiful!
I didn't know...
how beautiful this view was!
What? You don't need them?
That's correct.
But...
I'll be fine.
I'll be fine, just as I am.
Forgive me... You were looking forward to it.
It's fine, really.
I know, isn't there anything else
you want instead?
What?
Whatever you want.
Can't you think of anything?
Anything?
Yes, anything!
Well, I suppose...
Lace...
I would love to have even
a single lace handkerchief...
A handkerchief? A handkerchief!
Very well, I'll buy you 100, maybe 200!
What?
No please, wait!
Lace... It's been a dream of mine for years.
Lace?
Thank you so much, Mr. Jones.
Not at all...
Young Master!
You've bought even more useless objects?
Why do you spend so much time
every day in that store?
No reason...
Next Episode:
Two Worlds