We ask thee, Father, to forgive us
our sins and grant us eternal life.
When we leave this world, may we
go peacefully into the arms of our Lord.
We offer this prayer to our savior,
the Lord Jesus Christ. Amen.
As her soul departs from this world,
may she find eternal peace in the next.
Amen.
Episode 9
Alone
Honestly. You've been dragging
your feet, and now you're running late.
You know that the dinner tonight is important!
It's fine, I'll do it myself.
So you say, but If you had gotten ready
earlier, I wouldn't have to be nagging you-
Young Master!
Will that girl be at the dinner party as well?
You mean Miss Campbell?
Oh, I see. You're her escort, aren't you?
Duty is duty. I'll just have to put up with it.
If I want my father to accept Emma,
I can't show any sign of weakness.
Let me try. I can do it.
Eh?
So, Emma is a weakness?
That's not what I meant. Stop nitpicking!
And stop being so familar,
you should call her "Miss Emma"...
Even if both families encourage the match,
it's up to the couple themselves in the end.
And therein lies the problem.
Eh?
You can't guess the feelings of a woman in love.
Miss Eleanor, I can't pull any tighter.
I'm... fine...
It might be fashionable to have a tiny
waist, but this is very bad for your health.
Still, just a little more...
Please, Annie.
Brace yourself, miss.
There's a trick to opening the window.
You have to push and lift at the same time.
That's it.
This will be your room.
It's small and old, but it will have to do.
The front door was open. That's dangerous.
Have you finished?
Not yet...
The kitchen will take a little longer.
I've asked my mates to help out. They'll
get rid of anything you don't need next week.
Thank you. You've done so much.
You haven't told him?
What?
The Jones boy.
The funeral may be over, but you
should still tell him, you know.
I'll stop by again.
All right.
Your clothes...
You realize you don't have to wear
a maid uniform anymore, right?
It's just force of habit...
Well, you were here a long time.
If you need anything, just let me know.
I will.
Emma, could I have some tea?
Yes, ma'am.
Miss Campbell! Mr. William Jones!
Lord Melville, thank you for your invitation.
Welcome.
Please, enjoy yourself.
Thank you very much.
You have a beautiful home.
Please make yourselves at home.
Eleanor, you're more beautiful
every time I see you.
The same to you dear aunt,
you're as beautiful as ever.
My, even your words have
the grace of a true lady.
Um... I hope you don't mind escorting me.
Eh?
Mr. Jones suggested that I come,
and I couldn't help but comply...
Perhaps it was impudent of me.
Oh, of course not...
Not at all. I'm grateful, in fact.
I'm pleased.
Well then, shall we go?
You've seemed a little out of sorts recently...
Who, me?
Is anything wrong?
No... nothing at all.
Ladies and gentlemen, I am delighted
that you've gathered here tonight.
I hope you will enjoy yourselves.
Well then, to your health.
This is sea turtle soup.
Even cooked, a sea turtle still ends up
swimming in water, doesn't it?
What?
It's delicious...
It truly is.
Lobster and sole cooked in an orange sauce.
It's amazing.
Everything tastes so good...
This is puree of ptarmigan.
I must remember to talk.
I'm forgetting my manners.
Don't worry. I'm forgetting them too.
Number 43 and 44 have gone up!
Is the garnish finished?
Yes, Cook.
Add the final touches, please!
All right, move on to the sauce then, please.
Where's the roast duck?
Ready, Cook.
What do you think?
Perfect. I did well.
All right, take it up.
You're fired if you drop it.
Yes, Cook.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hurry up with the trimmings!
Even if you can't handle wine to begin with,
you get used to it the more you drink.
Is that so...?
The first time I drank, I made a terrible mistake.
I was with people who loved to drink, so l
couldn't refuse when they offered me more.
Port wine, Hock, Claret, Sherry,
there was even Madeira, I think....
So, what happened?
When the ladies retired to the next room,
I trod on the hem of the lady next to me.
Oh my!
I have yet to make a single mistake, you know.
Very impressive!
My mother was worried
before I left the house tonight.
Really?
She told me not to disgrace the
traditions of our family...
Mother is always talking about it,
tradition this, tradition that.
Tradition is...
Of course, tradition is important.
After all, it's something that has been
handed down through many generations.
But, I despise the idea of upholding
tradition simply for the sake of it.
That's just being stubborn.
Oh, I don't mean to criticize your mother.
I'm just speaking of the topic in general.
You're here again?
Do you want something to eat?
I'll be leaving here, you know.
From now on, you'll have to
search for another house.
Do you understand?
Are you all right?
That wasn't much at all, I'm fine.
Phew!
All right, it's ready. This is the final dish.
Well?
Have the guests said anything?
Everyone seems very satisfied.
Even the mistress was praising you!
Of course she was.
There you go, being modest again.
Come now, we're not finished yet!
We still have to clean up.
If you start daydreaming
and break a valuable plate,
you'll be packing your bags
come tomorrow morning!
Yes, Cook!
Are you really all right?
I am... fine...
I must say, it's delightful to dine
with a young couple like yourselves.
Sir?
"Young love is clearer than crystal,
more vibrant than gardens in June."
How wonderful indeed.
That's not... not really the case here, sir.
It is not the case.
I invited the young lady to dinner.
Oh!
Of course, I would be happy
if love were to blossom.
Well then, "One sees the elegance of
the rose in the bud." Or something like that.
It appears the salon is ready,
so the ladies can now retire.
I'm sure the gentlemen
wish to smoke their cigars.
Please take your time, gentlemen.
Shall we be going?
Y-yes...
Thank you.
I'm so full. I wish I could take my corset off...
I know!
Ah, um... is William always at home?
Yes, I believe so.
I wonder if he likes round games.
Perhaps I should ask him next time.
I'm not sure.
But my brother is so unpredictable.
He doesn't make for very good company.
That's not true! I really enjoy talking with him!
I wonder... ifWilliam already
has someone that he likes?
Oh dear! Just listen to me babble...
This biscuit tastes good.
Miss Eleanor, are you all right?
Miss Eleanor...!
I told you I'm fine, didn't l?
No, that's not...
William!
I apologize for my father's rudeness earlier.
Oh, no, l...
I didn't mind at all.
Actually, there's something
I have to tell you, Eleanor.
Truthfully, I don't know
whether I should tell you...
In fact, it may make you uncomfortable.
However, to be silent any longer
would be dishonest to my...
I'm sorry.
I'm not feeling very well.
Oh...!
Maybe I had too much wine,
I'm still not used to it.
So I must excuse myself for tonight.
Oh, then I'll escort you home.
Annie, call the carriage, please.
Yes, miss.
But...
I'll go home alone, tonight.
It's terrible that after all this work,
we never get to eat the food.
We do get to eat it.
I don't mean the leftovers!
It can't be helped. They're the
aristocrats, and we're the cooks.
And the gap between us is
wider than the London Bridge.
I wouldn't say that.
We may be cooks, but when the flavors we create
move the hearts of the nobles, in that moment...
...we become equals.
Isn't that so?
Why did you say that? "lf love would blossom."
I only spoke of my personal wish.
It's the same thing! You talk
as if it's already been decided.
Well, it has.
No matter how much you oppose me,
my feelings won't change.
This is not some childish whim!
You told me to consider my responsibilities
to the Jones family, and I have.
I've had enough of this talk.
What's wrong with you?
Do you want something to eat?
Next Episode:
Missing One Another