Episode 8
The Pocket Watch
Good morning.
The latch on the back gate is creaky.
Want me to oil it later?
Please do. The mistress would also
like you to shorten her stick by an inch.
Again?
Has Kelly's temperature dropped?
Yes. She's recovered from her cold.
However, she's had no
appetite the last few days...
Well, I suppose it does take
the elderly a while to recuperate.
"Sugar, a pound of tea, a pint of vinegar,
and a quart of milk should always be stocked."
"Red lentils, broad beans, and shallots..."
"...are cheapest at the
green grocers in Covent Garden."
Um...
You're going to be a wonderful wife.
I was asked to give you this.
Thank you, as always.
Not at all.
You made breakfast?
Won't you try to eat a little?
I'm not really that hungry.
But, you should at least try a mouthful...
Well, maybe just the soup...
Did you receive another letter
from Young Master Jones?
It's easy to tell.
What beautiful weather!
It's a shame I can't take a walk in
Hyde Park on such a wonderful day.
Once your leg mends,
you can go whenever you wish.
That's true...
Where is Al?
The latch on the gate is broken,
so he's gone to buy a new one.
I see...
It's stopped again...
It stops so often these days.
For years, I would wind
it 1 5 times every morning.
I have to wind it more these days,
since I haven't been using it.
Um...
Shall I take it in to be mended, ma'am?
Yes...
Please do.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh? Your mistress has hurt her leg?
Yes...
Even when my father fell into the Thames
years ago, he lived through it, hardy as ever.
But when he hurt his leg,
it wasn't long before he died.
You'll have to leave this with me.
Yes...
They would often come here together,
when her husband was alive...
All right. My regards to your mistress.
I hope she gets well soon.
Yes...
I will keep trying to convince my father
until he understands how serious we are.
PIease, I want you to trust me and wait for me...
Master William?
Can you inform me when my father returns?
I'll be downstairs.
Understood, sir.
Where's lndia?
Who knows?
So, Prince Hakim, you think lndian
women are the most beautiful, right?
Vivi!
No. I used to think they were...
...until I came to London,
and noticed the error of my ways.
I've come around.
Prince Hakim...
English women are all so very beautiful.
Why, Prince Hakim...
Eh?
I'm honored. But I'm afraid I'm already spoken for.
Such a shame.
Sister gets all the attention!
Will...
Yes?
Where's lndia?
Where?
Let's have a look.
By the way, brother...
You've been sending a lot of letters recently!
Letters? To whom?
Isn't it obvious? To Eleanor!
Eleanor?
Those are letters for work.
But if they aren't for Eleanor, then who?
I told you, they're for business.
Emma...
Hakim...
Emma?
Who's that? What kind of person is she?
What kind of person...?
Come now, have I met her?
No.
Is she a Duchess? A Countess?
Knowing you, she's a Baronet's daughter.
You're wrong.
She's a maid.
A maid...?
A maid...
Well, she may be a maid now...
You're lying!
Why would I lie?
You're serious?
I'm serious.
What are you thinking?
Unbelievable! I didn't think even you
could have so little common sense.
I am absolutely against her!
You're being inappropriate.
Even a child would know that!
Enough, you two!
Stop this.
Anywhere...
Love can be found anywhere.
That's not the point!
You always think with
your heart instead of your brain.
You have no grasp of the situation!
You're hardly one to speak!
Haven't you thought about
our family's reputation?
Vivi! Stay out of this.
I've got things to say!
Brother! We haven't finished talking yet!
We'll continue after I've spoken to father.
You're going to tell father?
No. Absolutely not.
I knew what your position would be.
But I'm telling you this, regardless.
No.
She isn't like other maids.
Her character isn't the problem.
Well, then...
A wife has many important duties.
She must organize dinners, balls and tea parties.
She has to converse appropriately,
display the correct manners.
She must be educated,
and speak the Queen's English.
Can a mere maid accomplish all this?
You told me once yourself, father.
A gentleman is bred, not born.
Through its nature and training,
a horse can become a champion.
However, a cat cannot become a horse.
Some things can't be changed.
If you insist on going through with this,
then you'll be banishing yourself from your class.
You have brothers and sisters, Stevens, and
over 1 00 servants that you're responsible for.
There's also the history that your
predecessors in the family have created.
Have you not considered these things?
Are you prepared to shun your
responsibilities to satisfy your own desires?
Is that the kind of man you are?
Don't think that you can
graft a reed to an elm tree.
Elms grow on hills, reeds live by the water.
This is the natural order of things.
Freedom and disorder should
not be confused. Don't forget that!
You might feel better if I wipe you down.
I thought I'd gotten better...
It seems I overdid it.
Your stick has been adjusted.
You seem sad.
And you seemed so happy up until recently...
Young people do have their ups and downs.
Mr. Jones... wrote me to say
that he would talk to his father.
I see...
He says that he will make his father understand...
But... I know that's impossible.
The more realistically I think about it...
...the more I realize that the divide
between our classes... is too wide.
Don't fret. You'll be just fine.
Master William...
I wonder what's wrong?
Are you really going to sleep there?
Yes. It's more convenient.
I'll turn the light out.
I really am getting old...
Just talking to myself.
Good night, ma'am.
Good night, Emma.
Do you have an appetite?
Not really...
You should really try and eat a little bit
of what you fancy. Don't skip meals entirely.
How is the mistress?
Well, nothing to be done about her age...
Please, take care of her.
Thank you.
I'm sorry...
Not at all.
How about a bit of fruit?
I really don't have an appetite.
Is Al here?
Yes.
Can you tell him to come and see me?
He comes here every day, but he never
bothers to climb the stairs to see me.
Yes, ma'am.
Um... The mistress would like to speak with you.
Mr. Al?
Huh?
Is something wrong?
No... I was just thinking of planting some roses.
Roses?
Yes. I could order the bushes
from a friend of mine.
He owes me a few favors.
That... would be lovely...
We could have afternoon tea
when the flowers are in bloom.
What did you want to talk to me about?
I have a favor to ask.
I don't know if I can be of help, but I'm all ears.
It's about Emma.
A gentry and a maid.
There's no way they could be happy.
You shouldn't give her false hope.
That's true... everything is so complicated...
But, Emma is in love with him.
Our Emma...
She's never felt this way before.
She may never feel this way again...
I sympathize with Mr. Jones,
but I want to help them.
What can I do?
Look after her...
Look after Emma for me.
The pocket watch has been mended,
so I was asked to deliver it here.
Thank you.
Is it the right one?
Indeed it is.
Good day!
I'll get the doctor!
What...?
Ma'am...
Ma'am...?
Your pocket watch has been fixed...
Ma'am!
Next Episode:
Alone