You're Miss Emma, right?
This is for you.
I was told to deliver this letter
to you by the back door.
You must marry someone from the same country.
England is one nation, but there
are two countries within it.
In other words, the aristocracy
and the commoners.
Episode 7
Crystal Palace
What's with that face? If I was
that upset, I'd do something about it.
Forget it.
You came!
Thank you for inviting us.
My father sends his regards.
This is all rather embarrassing...
Not at all, it's very lovely.
It captures your characteristics well.
The artist has a fine touch.
Do I really look like that...?
Your father told me that
I should invite you for a drive.
Does that displease you?
Of course not. I'd be delighted.
Really?
Yes.
Eleanor, your portrait is delightful!
Indeed!
It's so elegant!
But, the artist didn't quite capture your mouth.
Pardon me.
I'm going to commission a
different painter for my portrait.
Pardon me.
I'm going to commission a
different painter for my portrait.
Alice, don't be rude!
Oh! All I meant was that
you're prettier than your portrait.
Right, Miss Eleanor?
Do you want to say something?
Not really...
"Be clearer in your actions. You're
giving her the wrong impression."
That's what you're thinking, isn't it?
I'm aware of the situation. I'm not just
going along with my father's wishes.
I haven't said a word.
What is it?
You look like you have
something you want to say.
I can tell these things.
Um... may I take a half-day
holiday next week, ma'am?
Next week, eh?
But, I know that half a day would
inconvenience you... Not to mention...
It's fine.
It's fine. Take the whole day off, if you need to.
You have somewhere you want to go, don't you?
You've been such a help to me
recently. You deserve a break.
Yes, ma'am...
You'll find a dark red muslin dress
on the second shelf of the cupboard.
Wear that when you go out.
It was mine when I was younger, so the
style's old, but I think the size should be right.
It will suit you.
You should wear nice clothes
when you meet a young man.
Especially a young man that you like.
I can tell these things.
This is the Crystal Palace?
In 1 851, the first Great Exhibition
was held here in London, in Hyde Park.
This modern beauty, made from glass and iron,
was built as pavilion for the event.
A year after the Great Exhibition,
it was rebuilt here in Sydenham.
Works of art from all around the world,
even all sorts of tropical animals and plants...
...have been gathered together here,
to create a paradise on Earth.
You know so much!
I studied overnight.
This is the symbol of the Crystal Palace.
It's often used as a meeting place.
It's 27 feet tall, and was made from
8,960 pounds of crystal glass.
At the time of the opening ceremony...
It's beautiful.
Let's see...
The Byzantine Corner is that way,
and over here is Romanesque.
Which way shall we go?
I wouldn't really know... Either way is fine.
Well then, let's start with the closest.
Amazing!
This area represents Rome.
Is it real?
It would appear so.
Here's a model of the temple.
Maybe it's this pillar?
It's a part of the entrance.
It's so thin when you look at it like this.
There's more over there!
This is the Egyptian Corner.
I wonder how they moved
such large statues here?
These sphinxes are for guarding tombs.
Is it all right to bring a tomb's guardian here?
I didn't think of that.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry...
Strange, isn't it? That they would spend
a fortune making such childish things...
The building of the Crystal Palace was
opposed by both Parliament and the public.
The plan was nearly quashed several times,
but the perseverance and strong will
of Prince Albert allowed it to be built.
When I look at this shining monument,
it gives me the courage to overcome anything.
I must sound very naive.
Not at all.
Are you cold? Let's have
something hot to drink inside.
All right.
Café... café...
Over there, perhaps?
Mr. Jones!
Emma!
Thank heavens. I thought I'd lost you.
Yes...
But, why did you come to this spot?
Because you said that the fountain
was used as a meeting place.
I thought that you might come back here...
Me too! I had a feeling that you'd be here!
It's like we've traveled around the world!
A stroll around the world, eh?
All in a single day.
There's still more to see.
There's a library, and a moving picture gallery.
On Saturdays, there are
performances in the concert hall.
The northern water tower
has an observation platform...
It makes me dizzy just hearing about it.
In summer, they hold fireworks displays.
Fireworks?
Shall we come see it sometime?
It's amazing! There are fireworks
that look like the Niagara Falls...
The exhibition will be closing in 1 5 minutes.
The exhibition is closing!
Please make your way to the exit.
We are closing!
And finally they found me, looking
at the models, completely nonchalant.
So then, you weren't really lost.
I didn't consider myself lost, either.
I couldn't understand why he was so angry!
But then, I realized that my
mother was nowhere to be found.
What...?
So my father dragged me and my sister around
by the hand, searching for our lost mother.
"It's like I have three children,"
he kept complaining.
It all seems so long ago now...
It's rather quiet, isn't it?
Is it that late already?
The sun is setting... Shall we go?
Yes.
Huh?
I don't believe it!
It won't open?
It's locked!
No good. This one's closed as well.
Hey! Is anyone there?!
P-Please, wait!
But...
I'm sorry. It's turned out to be a terrible day.
Not at all.
Being here like this gives me such a
strange feeling. I've never been so happy...
...but, I'm also afraid.
This happiness, it can't last.
That's the feeling I have.
Why do you... feel that way?
Because so much has happened.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have...
It's all right.
It's the first time I've ever heard
you talk about yourself in this way.
Come in.
Do you know where Master William is?
Why?
Mr. Jones is searching for him.
I thought you might know where he is.
Your name is Stevens, is it not?
Isn't that Master William's?
I'm sorry, but please tell Mr. Jones
that his son has already retired to bed.
Just pretend that you mistook me for him.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Come now, don't say such boorish things.
The full moon is so bright.
It is indeed.
The insects are buzzing...
But the birds are asleep.
Aren't you sleepy?
I normally go to bed much later than this.
It must be hard.
I'm used to it.
Um...
Yes?
Nothing...
Mr. Jones?
Yes?
Oh... it's nothing.
Are you tired?
No... I saw so many things that I'd never
seen before, I think my eyes must be in shock.
What? What are you two doing here...?
Hey... The door's open.
It's a fine morning.
I'm sorry to have fallen asleep.
Not at all.
Stevens, please close the curtains...
Sir?
I've only just gotten to sleep.
Did you not sleep last night?
No...
Where's William?
He is sleeping, sir.
Sleeping? At this time of day?
He told me not to wake him, sir.
Honestly, what on Earth is that boy thinking?
I do apologize.
And after you went to all this
trouble to come and see him.
Not at all. He must very be tired.
So that's how it is, Eleanor.
We'll ask him out another time.
But... the weather has finally turned nice...
It isn't something to be fussing about.
If you'd like, Miss Campbell...
William doesn't have a partner for the next ball.
Would you be gracious enough to accept?
Would that be all right?
William would be happy to see you.
Yes, of course!
I'm glad to hear that!
I will inform William as well.
Good morning.
I slept soundly last night.
What time did you return?
Ma'am...
Ah, what a wonderful smell!
It's nearly ready.
Thank you.
Next Episode:
The Pocket Watch