It's about that time.
Indeed.
Look, here he is now.
Welcome!
Emma!
Oh!
Uh... Here, I'll take this.
Don't worry about the change.
He doesn't need to buy anything...
Episode 2
Two Worlds
Thank you.
Not at all. I was coming here anyway...
Oh, I have to return your gloves.
I'll get them for you.
I-I'm sorry...
I'll collect the gloves another time.
But...
I'd like you to keep them.
In other words...
They'll be my excuse.
You don't need an excuse...
The Mistress would be
pleased to see you anytime.
What? No, that's not what I meant...
However,
if you wish to come again...
Your father is very angry.
He wants to know why you're
off gallivanting around instead of working.
I leave it in your capable hands, Teresa.
Flattery won't help you. I can't
make excuses for you every day!
Well, it's not as if I want to
carry on my father's work.
You shouldn't say things like that.
Oh! Looks like someone's here.
You're avoiding the subject again!
No, it's the truth.
Will-
Brother Will!
We're home, brother.
Welcome home, Vivi, Grace.
Oh, Arthur's here too?
You sound so pleased to see me.
We ran into him at the station.
Welcome home, sir.
Thank you, Stevens.
How was Lyme Regis?
I much prefer London.
Oh, but the country's better in some respects.
But in the country, there are no
shops or theatres. It was so boring.
Will...
Brother Will, I heard that Harrods has
been refurbished. Take me there!
Some other time.
Some other time? And when would that be?
As I said, some other time.
Some other time never seems to come.
Welcome home, Colin.
Come in!
Excuse me, sir.
Your father wishes to see you.
It would seem you've turned down
every invitation you've received.
Moreover, you've left it to
Stevens to pen your regrets.
I apologize, sir.
You're not the one who needs to apologize.
I'm sorry.
There were just so many.
We may not have a title, but do you know
why our merchant family receives invitations?
Because of our money?
That is one reason. But we mustn't forget
character, intelligence and manners.
Those are the qualities valued by polite society.
The upper class is dependent upon
polite society. That is part of our work too.
Yes, but I-
You will go to the ball this evening.
I told them you would be there.
Yes, sir.
Lady Elliott...
...and Miss Elliott.
It's no use standing there like that, you know.
Robert!
You should dance with someone at least once.
I know I should.
But to be perfectly honest, it's a bother.
Why did you come, then?
William?
It's been such a long time, Mrs. Campbell!
It has indeed, William. I was worried
because I hadn't seen you lately.
I must apologize.
Is your father well?
Yes, I'm pleased to say he still
has a lot to say for himself.
I knew I should have worn my lace gloves...
What's this? You're still going on about that?
This is my daughter.
Eleanor, introduce yourself.
Good evening. My name is Eleanor Campbell...
My name is William Jones. Delighted to meet you.
Tonight is her first ball.
Oh, is that so?
She doesn't like her dress, doesn't like her hair...
She's been complaining all night.
Mother!
If you don't mind, would you
dance one waltz with her?
But of course.
Would you do me the honor
of a dance, Miss Campbell?
Yes.
You're quite good.
I never would have thought
this was your first dance.
Really?
Yes, you're a natural.
They certainly do make a handsome couple.
I'll hold this for you!
For you!
Thank you.
Hey now. Don't be a nuisance to Miss Emma!
Honestly, I don't know whether
you're helping or hindering...
Some potatoes, and...
I recommend the green beans today!
Today!
Well then, some green beans please.
Thank you!
You!
You have two wonderful assistants.
Look, brother Will! Does it suit me?
Yes. It's nice.
You didn't even look.
Are you sure we should be here with you?
Hm?
Didn't you have something else
that you wanted to do?
Not at all. The three of us haven't
spent time together for ages.
It's the least I could do.
Sister, it's Eleanor!
Eleanor, it's been such a long time!
Grace!
How fortuitous that we should meet like this.
Not really. All fashionable ladies shop
at the same stores, you know.
Good afternoon.
Huh? Brother Will, do you know Eleanor?
We met at the ball the other night.
Yes.
Oh, what a nice umbrella!
What are you...?!
I think they like each other!
Vivi!
Do you come here often?
No, I just wanted a parasol.
A parasol?
That's an umbrella.
Oh...!
I try to coordinate my parasol with my dress
each day, so I'm always in need of a new one.
Is that so?
Yes. For example,
as you can see, some are
decorated with lace or ribbons.
And some of the handles are made from
ivory or are intricately sculptured.
I see...
I admit they are rather lovely.
Would a lady be happy
to receive a present like this?
Yes... she would.
Hm...
Oh... b-but...!
I'd like to give this to a lady.
Could you wrap it?
Of course, sir.
Oh! Brother Will's going to
buy a present for Eleanor?
I didn't mean to imply that...
What are you talking about?
Oh, l...
I didn't mean to imply
that I wanted you to...
I'm sorry, for giving you
the wrong impression.
That was careless.
But...! Well then, who are you
going to give that parasol to, brother?
That's none of your business.
Vivi, stop it!
Yes, Grace.
Miss Eleanor, are you sure you
didn't want to buy a parasol?
I'm not interested in a parasol.
Hey, I heard this rumor...
...that Master William has a lady friend.
What?
That Master William should
fall in love at first sight... I'm jealous!
But really, Master Arthur is more my type.
What?
His moodiness just drives me wild!
Girls!
Stop chattering and get on with your work!
Yes, ma'am.
We are working hard!
She's the housekeeper,
she just wants to be bossy!
Hello.
Mr. Jones...
I came for my gloves.
My gloves-
I know.
Right.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Emma baked that scone, you know.
It tastes good! Very, very good!
Our Young Master is so
accustomed to a lavish lifestyle...
...that he finds the homely taste refreshing.
I didn't mean it like that...!
Emma?
We've run out of sugar, have we not?
Please go and buy some.
But ma'am, I haven't finished cleaning...
Never mind that.
Yes, ma'am.
Um, I'll go with her!
When The Season begins, there
seem to be more people in London.
Actually, my brothers and sisters have
just returned from a health resort.
I had to go shopping with
my sisters. But you know what?
I found a parasol that
I thought would suit you.
I'd be very happy if you use it.
I'm honored, but...
...I couldn't accept such a lavish present.
It's nothing, really. Please don't worry about it.
That may be so for you,
but to me it's quite extravagant.
It's not something I could easily
afford, even if I worked hard.
Have I upset you?
Oh, no! I don't mean to be rude.
But, the lace handkerchief I received...
...is more than enough.
I don't wish for anything else...
I apologize. I've acted poorly.
Your smile then, when you
accepted the lace handkerchief...
...I just wanted to see it again.
That's all.
Mr. Jones...
I won't buy any more presents.
However...
Can't we spend some time
together occasionally, like this?
Yes!
I'm back, ma'am.
Emma, a pot of tea, please.
Yes, ma'am.
What is it, Young Master?
Over here, Teresa.
All right, sit down.
You can take that off now.
This is a gift of thanks,
for always putting up with me.
This is for me?
Open it!
What is this? Such a fussy umbrella!
I'm not a girl anymore, you know!
Really?
I think it suits you.
You do...?
Well, since it's a gift,
I must accept it, I suppose.
Well then, thank you very much.
That parasol...!
Eh? Doesn't that woman
work for the Jones family?
Next Episode:
The Confession