Water.
Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Long ago, the four nations lived together in harmony.
Then, everything changed when the Fire Nation attacked.
Only the Avatar, master of all four elements, could stop them.
But when the world needed him most, he vanished.
A hundred years passed, and my brother and I discovered the new Avatar...
...an airbender named Aang.
And although his airbending skills are great.
He has a lot to learn before he's ready to save anyone.
But I believe Aang can save the world.
Those clouds look so soft, don't they?
Like you could just jump down
and you'd land in a big, soft cottony heap.
Maybe you should give it a try.
You're hilarious.
I'll try it!
Yehhhh!
Turns out clouds are made of water!
Hey, what is that?
It's like a scar.
Listen, it's so quiet. There's no life anywhere.
Aang, are you okay?
Fire Nation! Those evil savages make me sick! They have no respect for...
Shh!
What? I'm not allowed to be angry?
Why would anyone do this?
How could I let this happen?
Aang, you didn't let this happen.
It has nothing to do with you.
Yes it does. It's the Avatar's job to protect nature.
But, I don't know how to do my job.
That's why we're going
to the North Pole to find you a teacher.
Yeh, a waterbending teacher,...
...but there's no one
who can teach me how to be the Avatar.
Monk Gyatso said that Avatar Roku would help me.
The Avatar before you?
He died over a hundred years ago,
how are you supposed to talk to him?
I don't know.
Uncle! It's time to leave!
Where are you? Uncle Iroh!
Over here.
Uncle?
We need to move on, we're closing in
on the Avatar's trail and I don't want to lose him!
You look tired, Prince Zuko.
Why don't you join me in these hot springs
and soak away your troubles.
My troubles cannot be soaked away.
It's time to go!
You should take your teacher's advice
and relax a little.
The temperature's just right.
I heated it myself.
Enough! We need to leave now!
Get out of the water!
Very well.
On second thought,
why don't you take another few minutes,...
...but be back at the ship in half an hour
or I'm leaving without you.
Hey Aang, are you ready to be cheered up?
No.
Hey, how was that cheering me up?
Cheered me up.
Ow! Yeh, I probably deserved that.
These acorns are everywhere, Aang.
That means the forest will grow back.
Every one of these will be a tall oak tree someday,...
...and all the birds and animals
that lived here will come back.
Thanks, Katara.
Hey, who are you?
When I saw the flying bison,
I thought it was impossible,...
...but those markings... are you the Avatar child?
My village desperately needs your help.
This young person is the Avatar.
So the rumors of your return are true.
It is the greatest honor of a lifetime to be in your presence.
Nice to meet you too.
So... is there something I can help you with?
I'm not sure...
Our village is in crisis, he's our only hope.
For the last few days at sunset a spirit monster
comes and attacks our village.
He is Hei-Bai, the black and white spirit.
Why is it attacking you?
We do not know, but each of the last three nights
he has abducted one of our own.
We are especially fearful
because the winter solstice draws near.
What happens then?
As the solstice approaches,
the natural world and the spirit world...
...grow closer and closer
until the line between them is blurred completely.
Hei-Bai is already causing devastation and destruction.
Once the solstice is here there is no telling what will happen.
So, what do you want me to do exactly?
Who better to resolve a crisis
between our world and the spirit world...
...than the Avatar himself?
You are the great bridge between man and spirits.
Right... that's me.
Hey, great bridge guy',
can I talk to you over here for a second?
Aang, you seem a little unsure about all this.
Yeh, that might be because
I don't know anything at all about the spirit world.
It's not like there's someone to teach me this stuff!
So, can you help these people?
I have to try, don't I?
Maybe whatever I have to do will just... come to me.
I think you can do it, Aang.
Yehhh, we're all gonna get eaten by a spirit monster.
Who's there?
A meadow vole! I should have known.
You startled me, little one.
Ehh, seems I've dozed off and missed my nephew's deadline,...
...but it was a very sweet nap.
He's a Fire Nation soldier.
He's no ordinary soldier.
This is the Fire Lord's brother, the Dragon of the West,...
...the once great General Iroh,
but now, he's our prisoner.
Hello? Spirit, can you hear me?
This is the Avatar speaking.
I'm... here to try to help stuff.
This isn't right.
We can't sit here and cower
while Aang waits for some monster to show up.
If anyone can save us, he can.
He still shouldn't have to face this alone.
The sun has set. Where are you, Hei-Bai?
Well, spirit, uh, I hereby ask you
to please leave this village in peace!
Okay. Well, I guess that's settled then.
You must be the Hei-Bai spirit. My name is...
My name is Aang! I'm the Avatar
and I would like to help! Hey, wait up!
The Avatar's methods are... unusual.
It doesn't seem too interested in
what he's saying. Maybe we should go help him?
No, only the Avatar stands a chance against the Hei-Bai.
Aang will figure out the right thing to do, Sokka.
Please, would you stop destroying things and listen?
I'm just trying to do my job as spirit bridge.
Excuse me, would you please turn around?
I command you to turn around now!
That's it! He needs help!
Sokka wait!
It's not safe!
Hei-Bai! Over here!
Sokka, go back!
We'll fight him together, Aang.
I don't wanna fight him unless I... huh!
Sokka!
Uncle! Uncle, where are you?
Sir, maybe he thought you left without him?
Something's not right here. That pile of rocks...
It looks like there's been a landslide, Sir.
Land doesn't slide uphill.
Those rocks didn't move naturally.
My uncle's been captured by earthbenders!
Aang, over here!
Help!
Hang on, Sokka!
Sokka!
I failed.
Where are you taking me?
We're taking you to face justice.
Right. But where, specifically?
A place you're quite familiar with, actually.
You once laid siege to it for 600 days,
but it would not yield to you.
Ah! The great city of Ba Sing Se.
It was greater than you were, apparently.
I acknowledged my defeat at Ba Sing Se!
After 600 days away from home,
my men were tired and I was tired,...
...and I'm still tired.
I'm sure they'll be back.
I know.
You should get some rest.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Your brother is in good hands.
I would be shocked if the Avatar returned without him.
Katara, Katara I lost him.
The sun is rising. Perhaps he will return soon.
What? No, I'm right here!
I'm in the spirit world!
Yup, that's Uncle Iroh.
I'll figure this out, Katara, I promise.
Like they said, I'm the bridge between the worlds, right?
All I have to do is... figure out
what I have to do. But once I do that, no problem!
Appa! Hey buddy, I'm right here.
But, I guess you can't see me either.
It's ok, Appa. Dont' worry.
I'm sure they're on their way back.
I bet they even found you a bunch of moon peaches for a treat.
What am I supposed to do?
Avatar Roku, how can I talk to you?
Sokka?
That's definitely not Sokka!
What? I can't airbend in the spirit world!
You don't know where Sokka is, do you?
You're Avatar Roku's animal guide!
Like Appa is to me.
I need to save my friend and I don't know how.
Is there some way for me to talk to Roku?
I'll be back Katara. Take me to Roku!
What's the problem?
Nothing. Actually, there is a bit of a problem.
My old joints are feeling sore
and achy and these shackles are too loose.
Too loose?
That's right. The cuffs are loose
and they jangle around and bump my wrists.
It would help me if you would tighten them
so they wouldn't shake around so much.
Very well. Corporal,
tighten the prisoner's hand cuffs.
Hey, what are you doing!?
I don't understand. This is just a statue of Roku.
Is that what Roku wants to talk to me about?
A comet? When can I talk to him?
It's a calendar,
and the light will reach Roku on the solstice!
So, that's when I'll be able to speak to Roku?
But I can't wait that long.
I need to save Sokka now.
He is too dangerous, Captain.
We can't just carry him to the capital.
We have to do something now.
I agree. He must be dealt
with immediately and severely.
It's no use, Appa. I don't see them anywhere.
Our best hope is to go back to the village and wait.
The Avatar!
You're back!
Where's Sokka?
I'm not sure.
These dangerous hands must be crushed.
Excellent form, Prince Zuko.
You taught me well.
Surrender yourselves, it's five against two.
You're clearly outnumbered.
Uh, that's true, but you are clearly outmatched!
Now would you please put on some clothes!
Aang, what are you doing? Run!
You're the spirit of this forest. Now I understand.
You're upset and angry
because your home was burned down.
When I saw the forest
had burned I was sad and upset.
But my friend gave me hope
that the forest would grow back.
Sokka!
What happened?
You were trapped in the Spirit world
for 24 hours. How are you feeling?
Like I seriously need to use the bathroom!
Thank you, Avatar.
If there only were a way to repay you for what you've done.
You could give us some supplies and some money.
Sokka!
What? We need stuff.
It would be an honor to help you prepare for your journey.
I'm so proud of you, Aang.
You figured out what to do all on your own.
Actually, I did have a little help.
And there's something else.
What is it?
I need to talk to Roku and I think
I've found a way to contact his spirit.
That's great!
Creepy, but great.
There's a temple on a crescent shaped island,...
...and if I go there on the solstice
I'll be able to speak with him.
But, the solstice is tomorrow.
Yeh, and there's one more problem.
The island is in the Fire Nation.