Water.
Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Long ago, the four nations lived together in harmony.
Then, everything changed when the Fire Nation attacked.
Only the Avatar, master of all four elements, could stop them.
But when the world needed him most, he vanished.
A hundred years passed, and my brother and I discovered the new Avatar...
...an airbender named Aang.
And although his airbending skills are great.
He has a lot to learn before he's ready to save anyone.
But I believe Aang can save the world.
I'm not one to complain, but can't Appa fly any higher?
I have an idea, why don't we all get on your back and you can fly us to the North Pole?
I'd love to! Climb on everyone, Sokka's ready for takeoff!
Look, we're all just a little tired and cranky...
...because we've been flying for two days straight.
And for what? We can't even find the Northern Water Tribe.
There's nothing up here.
They're waterbenders! We found the Water Tribe!
He's heading north. The Northern Water Tribe.
The Avatar needs to master waterbending. He's looking for a teacher.
Then what are we waiting for? Let's go get him!
Patience, Captain Li. This isn't some little Earth village we can just march into.
The Water Tribe is a great nation.
There's a reason they've survived a hundred years of war.
The frozen tundra is treacherous. The landscape itself is an icy fortress.
We'll need a massive invasion force.
There it is!
The Northern Water Tribe...
We're finally here...
I can't believe how many waterbenders live up here!
We'll find a master to teach us, no problem!
This place is beautiful.
Yeh, she is.
Winter, spring, summer and fall. Winter, spring, summer and fall.
Four seasons, four loves. Four seasons, four loves.
Tonight, we celebrate the arrival of our brother and sister from the Southern Tribe,...
...and they have brought with them someone very special,...
...someone whom many of us believed disappeared from the world until now.
The Avatar!
We also celebrate my daughter's 16th birthday.
Princess Yue is now of marrying age.
Thank you, father.
May the great Ocean and Moon Spirits watch over us during these troubled times.
Now, Master Pakku and his students will perform!
Hi, there. Sokka, Southern Water Tribe.
Very nice to meet you.
So... uh... you're a Princess, huh?!
You know, back in my tribe, I'm kinda like a Prince myself!
Ha! Prince of what?
A lot of things! Uh, do you mind? I'm trying to have a conversation here!
My apologies, Prince Sokka.
So it looks like I'm gonna be in town for awhile.
I'm thinking maybe we could... do an activity together?
Do an "activity"?
Very smooth.
Master Pakku, meet your newest student, the Avatar.
Just because you're destined to save the world, don't expect any special treatment.
My friend and I can't wait to start training with you...
...after we relax for a couple days.
If you want to relax, then I suggest visiting a tropical island.
If not, I'll see you both at sunrise. Good night.
For the last time, I'm not playing the sumki horn.
No, it's about our plans. There's a bit of a problem.
I'm taking your crew.
What!?
I've recruited them for a little expedition to the North Pole.
Uncle, is that true?
I'm afraid so. He's taking everyone. Even the cook!
Sorry you won't be there to watch me capture the Avatar.
But I can't have you getting in my way again.
I didn't know you were skilled with broadswords, Prince Zuko.
I'm not. They're antiques. Just decorative.
Have you heard of the Blue Spirit, General Iroh?
Just rumors. I don't think he is real.
He's real all right. He's a criminal, an enemy of the Fire Nation.
But I have a feeling that justice will catch up with him soon.
General Iroh, the offer to join my mission still stands if you change your mind.
I've waited for this day my whole life!
I finally get to learn from a real waterbending master!
Good morning, Master Pakku!
No, please, march right in, I'm not concentrating or anything.
Uhh... this is my friend, Katara, the one I told you about?
I'm sorry. I think there's been a misunderstanding.
You didn't tell me your friend was a girl.
In our tribe, it is forbidden for women to learn waterbending.
What do you mean you won't teach me?
I didn't travel across the entire world so you could tell me "no"!
No.
But there must be other female waterbenders in your tribe!
Here the women learn from Yugoda to use their waterbending to heal.
I'm sure she would be happy to take you as her student despite your bad attitude.
I don't want to heal, I want to fight!
I can see that. But our tribe has customs, rules.
Well your rules stink!
Yeh! They're not fair. If you won't teach Katara, then...
Then what?
Then I won't learn from you!
Well have fun teaching yourself. I'm sure you'll do a great job.
Wait! Aang didn't mean that.
You can't risk your training for me.
You have to learn from Master Pakku. Even if he is a big jerk.
Why don't we get started then?
Princess Yue! Good morning!
Hey, how about that picnic last night?
Boy, your Dad sure knows how to throw a party.
I'm happy you enjoyed yourself.
Well, it wasn't as much fun after you left.
So, I'm still hoping we can see more of each other.
Do an "activity", you mean?
Yes! At... a place! For... some time!
I'd love to! I'll meet you on that bridge tonight.
Great! I'll see you... aahh!
Sorry!
That's okay, it was worth it. See you tonight.
I'm very impressed.
You all seem highly qualified for the mission I have in mind.
That's some tasty gold!
What do you need us to do?
I believe you're acquainted with Prince Zuko?
Um, hi. Are you Yugoda?
Are you here for the healing lesson?
I guess I am.
Welcome! Welcome!
You're moving the water around, but you're not feeling the push and pull.
I'm trying!
Maybe that move is too advanced for you. Why don't you try an easier one?
Thanks for the lesson.
So, who's the lucky boy?
Huh?
Your betrothal necklace. You're getting married, right?
Ah, no, I don't think I'm ready for that yet.
My grandmother gave my mother this necklace,...
...and my mother passed it down to me.
I recognize this carving! I don't know why I didn't realize sooner!
You're the spitting image of Kana!
Wait, how do you know my Gran Gran's name?
When I was about your age I was friends with Kana.
She was born here, in the Northern Tribe.
She never told me.
Your grandmother had an arranged marriage with a young waterbender.
He carved that necklace for her.
If Gran Gran was engaged, why did she leave?
I don't know. That's always been a mystery to me. She left without saying goodbye.
Good luck!
The crew wanted me to wish you safe travels.
Good riddance to those traitors.
It's a lovely night for a walk. Why don't you join me?
It would clear your head.
Or, just stay in your room and sit in the dark.
Whatever makes you happy.
Careful with the blasting jelly!
Uncle? Uncle, is that you?
Zuko!
Zuko...
Hi, Princess Yue. I made you something. I carved it myself.
It's a bear.
Actually, it's suppose to be a fish, see it has a fin.
Oh. I'm sorry! I made a mistake. I shouldn't have asked you to come here!
How's warrior training going?
That bad?
No, it's Princess Yue. I don't get it.
One minute she wants to go out with me and the next she's telling me to get lost!
So how's waterbending training?
Master Poophead won't teach her because she's a girl.
Why don't you just teach her, Aang?
Why didn't I think of that?
At night, you can teach me whatever moves you learned from Master Pakku.
That way you have someone to practice with and I get to learn waterbending.
Everyone's happy!
I'm not happy.
But you're never happy. Come on, Aang!
Master Pakku said this move is all about sinking and floating.
I got it!
That was amazing!
That wasn't me.
I... I was just showing Katara a few moves.
You have disrespected me, my teachings, and my entire culture.
I'm sorry, I...
You are no longer welcome as my student.
What do you want me to do? Force Master Pakku to take Aang back as his student?
Yes... please!
I suspect he might change his mind if you swallow your pride and apologize to him.
Fine.
I'm waiting, little girl.
No! No way am I apologizing to a sour old man like you!
Uh, Katara...
I'll be outside... if you're man enough to fight me!
I'm sure she didn't mean that.
Yeh, I think she did.
I'm devastated to hear about Prince Zuko. Just devastated.
The Fire Lord will not be pleased when he learns who was responsible.
You know who... was behind the attack?
Yes... pirates! We had a run in with them awhile back.
They wanted revenge.
So, have you reconsidered my offer?
Yes, I accept. It will be an honor to serve as your general. To the Fire Nation!
To victory!
Are you crazy, Katara? You're not gonna win this fight!
I know! I don't care!
You don't have to do this for me. I can find another teacher.
I'm not doing it for you! Someone needs to slap some sense into that guy!
So, you decided to show up?
Aren't you gonna fight?
Go back to the healing huts with the other women where you belong.
Fine. You want to learn to fight so bad, study closely!
Don't worry, I'm not going to hurt you!
You can't knock me down!
Go Katara!
Well, I'm impressed. You are an excellent waterbender.
But you still won't teach me, will you?
No.
This fight is over.
Come back here! I'm not finished yet!
Yes, you are.
This is my necklace!
No it's not, it's mine! Give it back!
I made this sixty years ago... for the love of my life. For Kana.
My Gran Gran was supposed to marry you?
Our plan is working perfectly. Zhao doesn't suspect a thing.
You didn't have to do this.
No nephew of mine is going to stow away on a ship without some backup!
Thank you, Uncle.
Someone's coming!
Stay hidden until we get to the North Pole and the Avatar will be yours! Good luck!
I carved this necklace for your grandmother when we got engaged.
I thought we would have a long, happy life together. I loved her.
But she didn't love you, did she? It was an arranged marriage.
Gran Gran wouldn't let your tribe's stupid customs run her life.
That's why she left. It must have taken a lot of courage.
Go get her.
What do you want from me?
Nothing. I just want you to know, I think you're beautiful...
...and, I never thought a girl like you would even notice a guy like me.
You don't understand.
No, no, see, that's the thing. I think I do understand now.
You're a princess, and I... I'm just a southern peasant.
No, Sokka...
It's okay. You don't have to say anything. I'll see ya around, okay?
Okay, now I'm really confused! Happy... but confused!
I do like you! A lot. But, we can't be together... and not for the reason you think.
It's because... I'm engaged.
I'm sorry!
Not bad! Not bad! Heheh!
Keep practicing and maybe you'll get it by the time you're my age!
Hey Katara!
What do you think you're doing? It's past sunrise. You're late.
Good to see ya here.
You too.
My fleet is ready. Set a course for the Northern Water Tribe.