Subtitles by DramaFever
[Ten Miles Of Peach Blossoms]
[Episode 55]
Crown Prince!
Crown Prince, I had
a hard time finding you!
Didn't you wake up in Xiwu Palace?
I don't know.
I woke up on Kunlun Mountain.
How did you know that I've returned?
I checked the Book of Destiny.
I realized that your mortal self
was so lovesick
that you died young from illness.
It's good that you've returned.
Trouble is brewing in the Grand Hall.
Please come with me immediately!
What happened?
High God Bai Qian of Qing Qiu
barged into Xiwu Palace
and vanished after digging out
Lady Su Jin's eyes.
Qing Qiu's Little Princess rushed in
and had an argument with Lady Su Jin.
One said that Qing Qiu bullied her
and the other claimed that
Lady Su Jin framed High God Bai Qian.
It's a mess.
Qian Qian took away Su Jin's eyes?
Yes.
Qian Qian...
Your Highness, you can't leave.
Lord Dong Hua said that
only you could resolve this issue.
All right, I need you to bring
three people here.
My Uncle Sang Ji, Lian Song,
and Yuan Zhen
who just finished his trial
in the Mortal Realm.
Yes.
There's one more.
It's a figurine called Su Su who served
my mother in the Mortal Realm.
Su Su?
I'll get it done right away.
Crown Prince.
I wonder why you asked
to see me so urgently?
Today, I'll uphold justice for Yuan Zhen
and redress his case.
Forget it.
Yuan Zhen has already
returned from his trial.
High God Bai Qian had also
kept him safe in the Mortal Realm.
As for the case...
We don't need it redressed.
I know that Father punished Yuan Zhen
because even after I was demoted to
Water King of the North Sea
I still doted on Shao Xing greatly.
He was just too angry and
wanted to teach me a lesson.
In fact, as his son,
I hurt him so deeply.
There's not much to say now
that my son had to pay for my sin.
Ye Hua, I'm grateful for your kindness.
Uncle Sang Ji, have you considered that
if we don't get this case
straightened out today
Yuan Zhen or even your other children
will still continue to suffer from it?
What will you do then?
This is...
Brother Sang Ji, Ye Hua is right.
We should always set things straight.
Otherwise... It's unfair
to Yuan Zhen.
Sure!
Once we get to the Grand Hall
I'll do whatever you have me do.
Just tell the truth, all right?
Yes.
Crown Prince, is this the right person?
Yes, it's her.
Let's go in.
Qing Qiu's Bai Qian threatened me
to seek punishment from
Heavenly Lord to guard the...
Guard the Bell of East Emperor that
imprisons Qing Cang by Ruoshui Riverbank
and never return to the heavens, right?
Yes!
Don't stand on ceremony.
Crown Prince, you've returned?
I happened to make it back today.
I've heard that there was
a problem in the Grand Hall
so I came to take a look.
You should be present.
This is after all an issue of your harem,
but I ended up having to handle it.
It has put me in a tight spot.
Yes.
Ye Hua!
Ye Hua, you must uphold justice for me!
Ye Hua...
Don't worry. I'm here to uphold justice.
Your Highness.
Who are you?
It's me, Your Highness.
I don't know you.
Don't address me!
Your Highness.
Who is she?
I don't know her!
Send her away!
Don't let her come near me!
Make her leave!
This is...
She's a figurine?
Heavenly Lord.
Ye Hua, what is this about?
When I'm going through
my trial in the Mortal Realm
Su Jin made this figurine to seduce me.
According to the celestial law
how would Father punish her?
It's the crime of seducing
an apparent heir
of the celestial tribe with witchcraft.
She is to be stripped of
her celestial status
banished to tiryagyoni-gati
to be reborn as animal.
Mark that down.
Yes.
No!
I didn't make this figurine!
I didn't make it... It wasn't me...
Why would Water King of
the North Sea have the time
to bring your eldest son
to the Grand Hall today?
I'm here for Yuan Zhen's
wrongly accused crime.
Wrongly accused?
You mean that I've misjudged his case?
Yuan Zhen, tell them
what happened that day.
Yes.
Yuan Zhen greets Heavenly Lord
Lord Dong Hua, and my uncles.
Don't bother with the formalities.
Just tell the truth.
Since I'm here today,
I'll uphold justice for you.
Yes.
I never molested Lady Su Jin.
That day on Heavenly Lord's birthday
I came here with Father
for the birthday celebration.
Father went to meet Heavenly Lord
so he had me wait outside the hall.
Lady Su Jin approached me.
She said that Heavenly Lord
is actually at Xiwu Palace.
She even smiled and said
that she could take me there.
Then Lady Su Jin knocked me out
with her magical powers.
She even fed me wine
and tore off my clothes.
When I woke up
Lady Su Jin was already crying
and accusing me of molesting her.
It was a huge mess then so
I just sat there dazed
until she brought out
the white linen to hang herself.
That was when Heavenly Lord walked in.
That was it.
I've finished my story.
You told it well.
It's very clear.
Su Jin, what do you have
to say to that?
He's lying!
He was drunk and barged into
my slumber hall to lay his hands on me.
He lied!
Yuan Zhen, how many times had you
been to the Celestial Palace?
That was my first visit.
Su Jin, you think that someone who came
to the Nine Heavens for the first time
would be able to locate Xiwu Palace
and then find your slumber hall
among the many other slumber halls
in Xiwu Palace to molest you?
I... He...
If you can't come up with
any reasons, don't speak.
Consort Le Xu, how should she be punished
for framing the grandson
of Heavenly Lord?
She is to be stripped of
her celestial status
banished to tiryagyoni-gati
to be reborn as an animal.
- Star Lord.
- Present.
- Note that down.
- Yes.
We haven't even tried her
for High God Bai Qian's case.
And she already guilty
of so many crimes?
No! Lord Dong Hua!
Lord Dong Hua, you've wronged me!
You've conspired with Qing Qiu's
Bai Feng Jiu to frame me!
You set me up!
- You set me up!
- How atrocious!
Heavenly Lord!
You have to uphold justice for me
They are all villains!
You mustn't believe in them!
They conspired to frame me!
They framed me, Heavenly Lord!
You mean to say that I'm also
a villain who plays up to those in power?
As my side consort, what is your crime
for slandering your husband?
That is a severe crime.
That's more severe
than the two former crimes.
Su Jin, you'd better think it through.
No, I...
Ye Hua...
Ye Hua!
You can't be so cruel to me!
You can't!
Have you forgotten?
I grew up with you.
I was...
I was just too flustered.
I panicked.
Ye Hua, you can't slander me
like they did!
You can't!
I'm the Crown Prince of
the Celestial Tribe.
I'd never side with anyone.
Even if I were to side with anyone
shouldn't it be my side consort?
No!
You never take my side!
Never! Not once!
You've always pushed me away
no matter how well I treat you...
It doesn't matter how well I treat you!
Do we still need to go on with this?
Judging by High God Bai Qian's character
and this woman's tainted criminal record
if we were to go on with this hearing
I'm afraid that Qing Qiu will bear
a grudge against us
for believing in such a woman
and accusing the Queen of Qing Qiu.
Indeed. This hearing need not continue.
Su Jin...
You've disappointed me.
I am utterly disappointed.
I think that Lord Dong Hua is right.
Fortunately, all who are present
in the Grand Hall today
are our own family members so
this has yet to cause a bigger impact.
As the foster father of Su Jin
I'm  ashamed to have
raised such a woman.
Father, please make a decree
to punish Su Jin immediately
so as to prevent further trouble.
I concur. I'm speechless.
I concur.
Uncles!
Uncles, you can't do this to me!
You can't treat me so!
Uncles, look! I'm a princess
of the Nine Heavens!
Uncles...
Have you forgotten about my parents?
They sacrificed themselves
to save you!
Have you forgotten about that?
Look at you!
How could you face your loyal parents?
Su Jin, considering that you're the
offspring of a faithful clan
I won't punish you for seducing
Ye Hua with a bewitched figurine.
However, for the crimes concerning
Yuan Zhen and High God Bai Qian
you have to be punished.
Today, you should
volunteer to guard Ruoshui.
Take her away!
No, Heavenly Lord!
I don't want to go there!
- I won't go there! I won't!
- Your Highness...
Heavenly Lord!
- Ye Hua!
- Your Highness...
- I won't leave!
Ye Hua.
Your wedding with High God Bai Qian
shouldn't be postponed any longer.
I'll arrange to meet the Fox King
and decide on a date
to marry her into the Nine Heavens soon.
I accept the decree.
Congratulations, Crown Prince!
Ye Hua.
What is it, Mother?
I never would have thought
that Bai Qian of Qing Qiu
could be that mortal, Su Su
from 300 years ago.
Although it is for the friendship
between Qing Qiu
and the Celestial Tribe
that you have to marry her
I still feel that you've suffered
many grievances.
What do you have in mind
about the wedding date?
The second of September.
What?
Qian Qian said that the second of
September is a good day for everything.
She wishes to hold our wedding
on that day.
Mother, rest assured.
Despite everything that happened
she's still the one
I have been waiting for.
I don't want anyone else but her.
All right.
I'll make the arrangements.
What is it?
Is there some other matter?
I have a question for you.
Ask away.
If...
I said if.
If you didn't remove your name
from the Rock of Three Incarnations
would you have fallen for me?
You haven't answered me yet!
I told you to ask the question,
but I didn't say that I'll answer you.
Why are you following me around?
If you don't answer me
I'll keep following you around.
By all means, do so.
Is Your Lordship still going to Ruoshui?
Head back to my study first.
Yes.
From this day forth
Qing Qiu is closed to all.
I will see no one.
Yes, Auntie.
That's not right.
What about Little Princess?
It's best not to disturb Auntie.
Anyway, with that temperament of hers
Little Princess can get by anywhere.
Crown Prince, our Auntie drank
a lot of wine and fallen asleep.
She's given orders that
none is allowed into her Fox Den.
Pass a message to her.
Tell her that I'll wait out here
until she's willing to see me.
Yes.
My Lord, I've already built
the ritual platform
in front of the Grand Hall.
Good, very good.
Fortunately, you managed to
finish it within seven days.
It's also fortunate that
my father still hasn't broken out
of the Bell of East Emperor.
It's been 70,000 years.
Hundred thousands of our warriors
died in the battle of Ruoshui Riverbank.
Whose fault was that?
The Celestial Tribe!
We offered our best food,
the most beautiful ladies
and our largest, most luminous pearls!
Think about it! Think long and hard!
When the Old Ghost Lord was in reign
did we ever had to suffer so?
- Exactly!
- That never happened!
- Am I right?
- Yes...
Yes! Exactly!
Look up at the sky!
Such strange sightings are the signs that
our true Ghost Lord is about to return!
Our Old Ghost Lord will eventually
return with his crimson hellfire
to defeat the Celestial Tribe
and conquer all realms!
Ghost Lord, abdicate the throne!
My Lord, there are many rebels
gathered outside Grand Ziming Palace.
What should we do?
What you need to do next is to
safeguard Grand Ziming Palace
for the next seven days.
I need to use these seven days
to disperse the crimson clouds
and restore peace to the Ghost Realm.
Father, since you used
your children as your power vessels
You should have known
that such a day would come.
Only our blood could summon your spirit.
Please return to Grand Ziming Palace.
The place you once
held as the Ghost Lord.
Put an end to all this
with your son, Li Jing.
Be it my mother's life
or that of Li Yuan
we should both put an end
to this once and for all.
Li Jing!
Treacherous son!
How dare you use your blood
to summon my spirit!
What are you going to do?
I never should have spared
such a treacherous son 70,000 years ago!
Why have all of you come to Ruoshui?
How could I help you?
This is the fairy, Su Jin.
She volunteered to the Heavenly Lord
and gave up her celestial status
to train near Ruoshuo as well
as guard the Bell of East Emperor.
Heavenly Lord consented to it
in appreciation of her kindness
and ordered us to bring her here.
Fairy Su Jin is too kind.
I'll take my leave now.
Let's go.
Isn't that Lady Su Jin?
Yes.
Su Jin is punished for
some wrongdoing and her eyes are hurt.
Heavenly Lord had her use the eyes of
the North Sea's legendary fish
so that she could at least get around.
Has the Crown Prince returned?
He has returned
but he's now in Qing Qiu.
Qing Qiu?
His Highness just returned from
the Mortal Realm
so he must have gone to Qing Qiu
to discuss the wedding
with High God Bai Qian.
All right, you may head back now.
Yes.
Ye Hua...
I love you.
I want to be with you forever.
Back then, I didn't know
what I truly felt for you.
Don't take what I said then to heart.
Now that we share a mutual affection
the engagement can't be canceled.
Auntie, His Highness has been waiting
outside the Fox Den for seven days.
He insists on seeing you.
I acted upon your orders
so I don't dare to let anyone in.
Not even the Crown Prince.
However, it's been seven days
and His Highness doesn't seem
to be leaving anytime soon.
I can't make any decision
so I came in to ask you what I should do.
Ye Hua...
300 years ago, did you only marry me
because Su Ji betrayed you?
Have you ever truly loved me?
If you do love me
how deeply do you love me?
If I weren't tricked into jumping
off the Zhuxian Terrace
would you have willingly married Su Jin?
Are you now so deeply devoted to me
because of that guilt from 300 years ago?
What if he admitted to all that?
What if he said that were all true?
Auntie, will you see him or not?
I won't see him.
Tell him never to come to Qing Qiu again.
I'll go to the Heavenly Lord tomorrow
to break off the engagement.
Yes.
Crown Prince.
My Auntie said...
She still refuses to see me?
Not exactly.
She's just too drunk,
so she didn't pay much attention to me.
Your Highness has been here
for seven days already.
Why don't you head back?
I'll inform you when she's sober.
I'm not going anywhere.
Let me get you an umbrella first.
- It might rain soon...
- Don't bother.
I'll take my leave now.
Mi Gu.
What is it, Your Highness?
Pass on a message for me.
Please do tell.
Before I went for my trial
in the Mortal Realm
your Auntie told me that
should my mortal self
get into any relationships
she would snatch me back
to lock up in her Fox Den.
If the maid I brought home to
serve my mortal mother
counts as a relationship
could you ask her if what she said
to me still counts?
I'll pass on your message to her.
Auntie.
His Highness asked me
to pass on a message to you.
You said that if he gets into any
relationships as a mortal
you would lock him up in Qing Qiu.
If the maid he brought home
to serve his mother
is considered as a relationship,
do your words still count?
No!
No matter what excuses he has,
it doesn't count!
Make him leave!
I don't ever want to see him again!
Auntie, calm down. Appease your anger.
Get out! Leave now!
Your Highness suffers from
new injuries and old ailment.
There's not enough cultivation
to protect your body.
You can't stay out in the rain.
Take the umbrella away.
Your Highness...
Take it away!
Your Crown Prince stood there
like that for seven days?
Exactly, High God.
Please try to talk Auntie around.
Only the both of you know that
His Highness almost died
from losing am arm and
using up his cultivation
to make the elixir for High God Mo Yuan.
If it weren't for High God Zhe Yan
he would have died.
If this goes on
he might really die young.
Knock wood!
What nonsense is that?
Don't jinx my brother-in-law.
High God, does that mean
you could persuade Auntie?
No, I can't.
Why not?
Jia Yun, you're not married yet?
Not yet.
The argument between a married couple
is strictly between them.
No other advice from anyone
would have helped.
It would only make it worse.
Exactly.
We can't help much.
Not even his own son.
Let's just wait and see.
Wait and see?
Wait till Qian Qian
figures her heart out.
Do you think it's that easy to
marry the Queen of Qing Qiu?
Among us four brothers
we only have one baby sister.
She happens to be very stubborn.
She's also a high god.
She suffered so much then
and even had her eyes dug out.
She will surely be upset for a few days.
Don't worry.
She'll get over it in a few days.
What if she never gets over it?
That's not possible.
We know how she is with Ye Hua.
High Gods, please rest soon.
I'll take my leave now.
How is the Bell of East Emperor?
Your Lordship.
It's been raining heavily
at Ruoshui Riverbank for ten days.
What could be the problem?
Would you like to ask the Crown Prince?
Since he's kept an eye
on Ruoshui all this time
he might already know about
some bad news?
Where is Ye Hua?
He's... in Qing Qiu.
That's right.
He should be in Qing Qiu.
Doesn't absence make
the heart grow fonder?
Yes.
Forget it.
I can only set my mind at ease
if I see for myself.
- Star Lord.
- Present.
Whatever happens
you must keep the Little Princess safe.
Yes.
Father, stop struggling.
Come back to the desolate Ghost Realm
and vacant Grand Ziming Palace
that the battle made bleak
70,000 years ago.
Treacherous son!
Do you want me to kill you?
- Lord Dong Hua.
- How was it last night?
The strong currents raged on
and dark clouds swept in.
Such a sight disturbed me greatly.
Now that I've lost my powers
I can't investigate into the bell.
Judging by this phenomena
it's highly likely that
Qing Cang's spirit has consolidated
and is about to break out of the bell.
If we're to look inside the bell
we'll need to use soul-tracking magic.
I'm not capable of such magic either.
Head over to
Ten-mile Peach Tree Woods now
and invite High God Zhe Yan.
Yes.
Your Lordship, I can use
the soul-tracking magic.
You?
Auntie and Zhe Yan taught me
when we were in the woods.
I know how to conduct it.
Besides, you lost your powers
because of me in the Mortal Realm...
I should handle this matter.
Don't hesitate.
Just let me do it.
Lord Dong Hua, there's no spirit in it!
What?
It might be that I'm not
skilled enough.
Let me try it again.
Treacherous son!
How dare you imprison my spirit!
Father, how have you been?
Don't forget.
Only your spirit is here so
you can't touch me.
My biggest mistake was
letting you off 70,000 years ago!
You're wrong!
Your biggest mistake was raising me.
You wanted to use me
to boost your powers, right?
You raised children to serve
as your power vessels.
What father can be more cruel than you?
You exhausted all resources and
thousands of our soldiers in one night!
You deserve to be killed!
You used your children to
store your powers. How cruel.
You deserve to be killed!
You know that crimson hellfire
would destroy all realms
and yet you didn't hesitate
to drag everyone down with you!
You deserve to be killed!
Treacherous son!
Have you forgotten
that I've raised you?
Have you forgotten that
my blood runs in your veins?
You want to kill your father?
How monstrous!
You've used up all your blood
to summon my spirit.
How much longer could you live?
Good!
Then the both of us will die here today.
Double Crescent Halberd?
You didn't think of that?
My spirit might not be able to hurt you,
but this Double Crescent Halberd will.
Li Jing, I'll take your life!
Subtitles by DramaFever