Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 25]
Impudence! How dare you try to trespass
into the Crown Prince's chambers?
Let me see His Highness!
My lady is about to give birth!
Quickly summon someone
to help my lady deliver!
The Crown Prince issued strict orders
that nobody is to enter.
Sisters, my lady cannot afford to wait!
Please allow me inside!
- Third Prince.
Nai Nai, what has happened?
Third Prince, my lady is
about to give birth!
What did you say?
Quick, get up.
Take me there.
What about His Highness?
Don't worry about him. Get going!
Yes.
- Quick!
- Your Highness.
Medicine King, quick! You must ensure
the safety of both mother and child!
Yes. Greetings, Your Highness.
Forget about those formalities!
Remember, you must ensure
the safety of both mother and child.
Yes.
A woman in childbirth mustn't
be subjected to the wind.
Quick, pull down the curtains.
- Yes..
- Quickly!
- Third Prince, please step back.
- Your Highness, you will be all right.
Your Highness, Medicine King is here.
You must stay safe and sound,
Your Highness.
Ye Hua.
Your Highness, trust me.
The Crown Prince will surely come.
Ye Hua! Ye Hua...
Is it a boy or a girl?
Your Highness, it...
Speak quickly!
Your Highness, this baby
really is a sick child.
Your Highness, spare my life.
Spare my life!
It was you! You harmed my son!
Xuan Nu, you just gave birth.
Why are you out of bed?
Get back in and rest.
Your Majesty, it was this shaman.
I don't know what
antiabortifacient medicine he gave me.
It not only caused me
to go into premature labor
but... but also caused our child
to be unconscious when born!
What did you say?
Your Majesty, I'm wrongly accused!
Your Majesty, signs of
the baby's condition
appeared half a year ago
from Ghost Queen's womb.
Ghost Queen forced me to use black magic
to aid in the delivery of her baby.
This is not my fault, Your Majesty!
You dare accuse me?
You were clearly the one who
cruelly plotted against my son's life!
Guards! Drag him out.
Behead him at once!
- Yes!
Your Majesty, I've been wronged!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! I've been wronged!
Your Majesty, this is unjust!
Go!
Ghost Queen, may you die
a terrible death!
Your Majesty, I've served
three generations of Ghost Lords!
I am loyal and devoted!
I've been wrongly accused, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, you should not
be treating me this way!
Your Majesty!
My son.
I will definitely save you.
Your Majesty!
In ancient times, there were some
who sinned too deeply
and would thus meet with
the wrath of heaven.
For example, there was someone
by the name of Jie Yu.
Because she had sinned too greatly
she had three successive pregnancies
that resulted in sick children.
- Really?
- Of course it's true.
My mother told me this when I was young.
That's why retribution
follows unfailingly.
After you follow me, you must not do
anymore bad things, all right?
I shall do as you command.
Si Yin, you're actually attempting
to break my seal?
That is impossible.
Unless I die.
Or if you die.
Your Highness.
Third Uncle, is Su Su all right?
I don't know the situation inside,
but Medicine King is here.
Don't be too worried.
It's born. It's finally born.
Congratulations, Your Highness,
on the birth of your son.
Congratulations on giving birth
to a son, Your Highness.
He looks very much like you.
Feel him.
I won't be staying in the Nine Heavens.
You are a young prince.
They won't give you trouble.
Nai Nai.
Your Highness.
Is he hungry?
Heavenly Lord had a nanny sent over.
I will bring him out to be fed.
Go on. I'm tired. I'll be sleeping.
Rest soon, Your Highness.
What?
She actually gave birth to a prince?
Yes, Your Highness.
The mortal sure has a lucky life to give
birth to a prince on her first pregnancy.
Now she will be able to
rely on her precious son.
In the future, they are certain to be
obstacles for Your Highness.
Why?
Why would she have such a good life?
She is merely a mortal.
She married the one I couldn't marry.
Her first child...
is a prince!
Xin Nu, tell me why!
Why would she have such a lucky life?
I am a princess of the Celestial Tribe,
a child of a meritorious subject!
How am I inferior to her?
In what way am I incomparable to her?
Your Highness, please don't be like this.
I know you are heartbroken,
but do not panic.
Hasn't Heavenly Lord already bestowed you
in marriage to the Crown Prince?
Once you are married into Xiwu Palace
would you still need to fear that you
won't have a child with the Crown Prince?
No matter what, Crown Prince is a man.
You will be his side consort
in the future.
As time passes
the Crown Prince will surely understand
your deep affections for him.
I can't accept this.
I don't deserve this.
I grew up with Ye Hua.
He has always been
the only one in my heart!
Why?
Why was she allowed to claim him first?
Last night, you maids took advantage of
the fact that His Highness wasn't present
and denied entry to one from Xiwu Palace
nearly causing Her Highness, Su Su,
and the young prince to be in danger.
His Highness is merciful,
and won't sentence you to death
but punishment is inevitable.
Go accept your punishment today
and experience the hardships of
the mortal realm for a hundred years.
Yes. Thank you, Your Highness,
for sparing my life.
I believe it must have
a very beautiful color.
It is a plain color you like.
However, when the time comes, the
wedding outfit can't remain with you.
Wedding outfit?
Didn't I say before
that I would marry you?
Your Highness.
Crown Prince.
I'll be going now.
Your Highness, were these all
bestowed by the Crown Prince?
As expected, it is true.
Your Highness,
everybody in Xiwu Palace is saying
the Crown Prince will be
marrying you soon.
Your Highness, are you not delighted?
His Highness marrying me now
is merely out of pity for me.
Your Highness, don't think such nonsense.
I am jesting.
Help me put away these clothes.
Nai Nai, walk with me to Zhuxian Terrace.
Your Highness, how come you have been
going to Zhuxian Terrace so often lately?
It is... an inauspicious place.
I want to smell the fragrance
of flowers along the way.
No need to hold on to me.
I can't rely on you all the time.
Were we taking this same path yesterday?
Yes, Your Highness.
This is the shortest path from
Xiwu Palace to Zhuxian Terrace.
The fragrance of the flowers here
is most comforting.
From now on, I'll walk here by myself.
You can just follow behind me.
Taking care of the young prince
is tiring enough for you.
I can come out for a walk
by myself once in a while.
All right, Your Highness.
Crown Prince has lifted the restrictions
on the Hall of Beautiful Youth.
Your Highness has also given birth
to Crown Prince's first son.
Your Highness can now go wherever
you wish in the Celestial Palace.
Is that so?
Nai Nai.
What orders do you have, Your Highness?
Has Ye Hua chosen a name
for the young prince yet?
No.
I've asked His Highness.
He said the young prince
is to be named by Your Highness.
I want to call him A-Li.
Is this a good name?
It does sound nice
but which "Li"
is Your Highness speaking of?
The "li" of separation.
That's... That doesn't seem
very propitious.
Didn't you say I am in favor now?
I want to call him A-Li.
Is that not allowed?
I have made an indiscreet remark.
Nai Nai, ever since I lost my eyes
my mood has constantly been unstable.
If I cause you discomfort,
do not take it to heart.
I know most clearly
the suffering you have endured.
Why would I blame Your Highness?
Good.
Follow me. I want to walk to
Zhuxian Terrace by myself.
Yes.
Zhe Yan?
He isn't... here to talk me back, is he?
Thank you.
You are too polite.
Have you come to ask about
the sealing of Qing Cang?
Bai Qian of Qing Qiu sealed Qing Cang.
You are so close with Qing Qiu.
Why have you ignored what is
close at hand and come instead to me?
Would it be possible for...
this lady to step out?
I have been impolite.
Which palace is she from
for her to not step out even when
Dijun discuss matters with someone?
Could she be...
She is Ye Hua's cousin.
She comes here often.
She is a junior. I can't
bring myself to say anything.
Please continue.
Actually, there isn't much to say.
There are hidden circumstances
regarding this incident
but I cannot speak of them
in detail to you yet.
I came today to try my luck
and see if I can find here from you
something that I do not know.
Since you are unwilling to reveal
the truth's entirety
then I shall not force you.
I just had a speculation that
Bai Qian is the Si Yin of
Kunlun Mountain of the past.
The rest should be
about the same as what you know.
I truly did not expect that
you would have guessed so.
It was Feng Jiu who said it.
Feng Jiu?
If you hadn't mentioned her,
it really had slipped my mind.
Feng Jiu, that little girl, has left
Qing Qiu for quite some time now.
It's said she came to
repay your kindness.
That is correct.
She has indeed been here.
Has she finished repaying her debt?
I do not need her to repay any such debt.
Are you saying... she has caused
complications for you?
It has been a little inconvenient.
In his eyes...
I am but an inconvenience.
Don't come any closer!
I... I am Bai Feng Jiu of Qing Qiu!
No!
Thank you for the tea, Dijun.
I take my leave now.
You are too polite.
Your Highness, there are steps here.
Be careful.
Miss, you...
The uncovered half of this lady's face
looks extremely similar to Bai Qian.
And this faintly discernible
peach blossom scent is highly familiar.
High God Zhe Yan.
Crown Prince.
Has Su Su offended you?
Su Su? Her name is Su Su?
Yes. She belongs with Xiwu Palace.
So she belongs with you, Crown Prince.
Just now, I had nearly
taken her for an old friend.
She is just a mortal. She has never been
to Ten Mile Peach Tree Woods.
I'm afraid you are mistaken.
Ten Mile Peach Tree Woods?
Miss, do you know of
So in the future
I won't be able to see
this Ten Mile Peach Tree Woods again.
In the future, I will plant
a grove for you.
Then I want ten miles as well.
I don't know of it.
The name just sounds unique.
You can visit when you have the chance.
Visit?
I hope there will be a chance.
Be careful.
Ye Hua.
I just wanted to go out
for a walk by myself.
The scent of the flowers
along the path smells very nice.
Su Su, you don't have to explain to me.
From now on, you are the Crown Princess
in the Nine Heavens.
Nobody will dare to question
your whereabouts again.
Ye Hua, don't worry.
I won't be going anywhere in the future.
I won't cause trouble for you again.
Are you thirsty?
I'll pour a cup of tea for you.
Su Su.
We'll be getting married in ten days.
Married?
- You...
- Ye Hua.
I can't see anything.
There must be many protocols
during the wedding.
I will probably be made fun of.
You won't be.
You have me.
That's good.
- Eldest Prince.
You may go.
Yes.
Your Highness.
- Father.
- It's as you can see.
Ye Hua will announce to the four seas
that he is marrying the mortal.
He has also fought against the decree
to allow Su Jin into Xiwu Palace.
I have been incapable of
disciplining my child.
Please punish me, Father.
After he received the Crown Prince's seal
he first replaced
the maids of Xiwu Palace
then he selected his own soldiers
to guard Xiwu Palace
and now he is taking a side consort.
He has made meticulous arrangements.
Even I cannot do anything about it.
What would you be able to do?
Father.
Ye Hua just received
the Crown Prince's seal.
He is the heir apparent chosen by heaven.
Even I have to salute him
as a heir apparent.
I cannot do anything to him now.
Let him be.
I simply do not believe he will focus on
this woman his whole life.
It's just that Qing Qiu...
Bai Qian of Qing Qiu is
the number one beauty of the world.
When she marries into
the Celestial Palace
she will certainly sway Ye Hua's heart.
I can only hope so.
You know I most dislike women crying.
If I ask you a question, you will answer.
No need for unnecessary talk.
I...
I locked the fox in Evil Sealing Pagoda.
Don't come any closer!
Why does Dijun's power look so strange?
It is crimson in color?
How dare a mere Pagoda Guardian
act so atrociously in front of me?
My tails!
Oh no!
Why is she bleeding so much?
I'm afraid she can't be helped.
Fool, you have it wrong.
The blood on Her Highness is from Dijun.
Dijun has suffered severe injuries?
Who in this world
is capable of injuring Dijun?
A few days ago, Dijun spent
a great amount of his powers
to save the Little Princess.
Today, he killed the Pagoda Guardian
of the Evil Sealing Pagoda.
These injuries were caused by
the Pagoda Guardian.
Pagoda Guardian?
That is the monster king
that Heavenly Father left behind
that terrifies the Nine Heavens.
All right, enough.
Treat Dijun's injuries first.
Yes.
I didn't die?
What is this place?
This is Dijun's chambers.
Chambers?
This is my first time in here.
Where is Dijun?
He is resting.
Is he heavily injured?
Have I caused him trouble again?
No, he really is resting.
Dijun said you have caused
too much damage.
You should return to Qing Qiu.
As for repaying his kindness,
he never expected it.
Little Princess, don't cry.
When you cry, I don't know what to do.
Dijun...
Is he throwing me out?
Your Highness has been
at Taichen Palace for a while now.
Do you still not know
Dijun's temperament by now?
He is an immortal made out of a rock.
He possesses no emotions or desires.
Don't waste your efforts any longer.
Bid farewell to Dijun for me.
I have asked the Little Princess to leave
the Nine Heavens as you wished.
Your Highness!
Didn't you set out to repay a kindness?
How come you're in this state?
Where is Aunt? I want to
discuss some things with her.
Aunt is not in Qing Qiu.
How come Aunt left Qing Qiu?
Has something happened?
Let's head back first.
I'll tell you all about it.
I remember now.
Did Aunt tell you anything?
Ever since Aunt's battle with Qing Cang,
she hasn't been seen.
What?
How come nobody told me
while I was in heaven?
Don't panic, Your Highness.
Fox King and Zhe Yan have said that
according to the stars, Aunt is fine.
We just don't know where she has gone.
You know Aunt's personality as well.
Perhaps she is just wandering around.
That is true.
Aunt and the Crown Prince
have an engagement.
For fear of alarming Celestial Tribe
and to avoid making this disappearance
known in every household around the world
Zhe Yan has told us
not to speak of this to others.
So has nobody taught Shao Xing a lesson
for stealing Aunt's marriage?
Who has the time to be concerned
about the snake?
No.
I have to stand up for Aunt.
Dijun stopped me when I wanted to teach
her a lesson in the Celestial Palace.
There's nobody to stop me today.
Your Highness.
How can you be so extreme?
You were so distracted when you returned.
How come you are out for revenge now?
I just want something to do
to temporarily forget about Dijun.
Just let me go, all right?
What... What's wrong, Your Highness?
Why do you look like you're about to cry?
Why would I cry?
I am going to teach a servant
a lesson for Aunt's sake.
Why would I cry?
Your Highness already
confronted Shao Xing once
back in the Celestial Palace.
Seeing as you are from Qing Qiu,
I made a concession.
Why have you come today
to stir up trouble again?
For someone like her
who betrayed her savior
how is one scolding enough?
You!
Do not go too far!
My lord, calm down.
You have already yielded to her once
in the Celestial Palace.
Are you going to allow her
to humiliate you again?
These all are what I deserve
to go through.
Your Highness has come at a good time.
I wanted to take this fan to Qing Qiu
to humbly apologize to Aunt.
Apologize? You aren't lying to me?
I was Aunt's maid.
I did something to betray her.
Of course I have to beg for forgiveness.
Since Your Highness has come today,
I will make the trip with you
and settle this matter.
You want to return to
the Fox Den with me?
That's correct. We'll go right now.
Wait. Aunt is not at Qing Qiu right now.
Nobody in the world knows.
I can't let this snake go.
I only came to scold her to vent. I
must not ruin things because of this.
You don't need to go to apologize.
Aunt said she does not want to see you.
- But--
- No but.
Although Aunt doesn't want to see you
the Cloud Clearing Fan
still belongs to her.
You still need to return it to her.
Please take it, Your Highness.
I don't dare keep it for myself.
Although you betrayed Aunt
and I shouldn't forgive you
ever since you left, you indeed have not
told outsiders about Qing Qiu's matters.
You also returned the Cloud Clearing Fan
to me of your own accord.
You have just narrowly gained
my forgiveness.
Qing Qiu's matters?
Is Your Highness referring to
the one in Yanhua Cave?
Yes.
Please rest assured, Your Highness.
I will not breathe a word of it
in my entire life.
I hope you will remember your own words.
Should I go against my word,
I shall be struck by lightning.
That puts me at ease then.
I will take this Cloud Clearing Fan.
However, I cannot say whether
Aunt will forgive you.
I understand.
Mi Gu! Mi Gu!
Your Highness.
Bai Feng Jiu!
Father.
Kneel!
Father, I know I was wrong.
I should not have gone to
the Celestial Palace to repay my debt.
Subtitles by DramaFever