Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 58]
My dear!
- My dear!
- Let go of me!
I never want to see you again!
My dear, don't leave! My dear!
Fourth Brother, I know what
you're going to say.
I think that the Heavenly Lord
punished her too harshly.
It might be because of Ye Hua...
Anyway, whatever she owed me,
she has paid the price for it.
She now has nothing to do with me.
Fourth Brother.
You've brought me here
especially to look at her?
Since you say so, it is so.
We've been walking for quite some time.
I'm tired. Let's go and have some tea.
A pot of tea, please!
Sure!
Sir and Madam...
Si Yin?
Yan Zhi?
We haven't seen each other
in 70,000 years.
Stay and chat.
I'll go and take a look around.
You're right.
We haven't talked since that battle
at Ruoshui Riverbank.
Thank you for being willing
to speak to me.
Si Yin.
When I met you, you were Si Yin.
So... can I just call you that?
Sure.
Si Yin, when I saw you just now
it made me remember those days
when we were young.
You and I were still messing around
in Grand Ziming Palace.
My Brother Li Jing
was still alive then...
Mother, this auntie is so pretty.
You're also pretty.
Mother!
Mother, do you not want A-Li anymore?
How could I not want A-Li?
I've been thinking of my dear
Little Riceball for the past three years.
Why didn't Mother visit me
in the Celestial Palace?
I've been asleep
for the past three years.
I didn't wake up.
I didn't wake up from my dreams
until yesterday.
I'd wanted to take a stroll in
the Mortal Realm
and then visit you
in the Celestial Palace.
Who knew that you'd sneak out here?
When I went past here above the clouds
I noticed an auspicious aura
of a  high god around here.
I wanted to take a look
to see which high god it was.
Then I saw Mother down here.
A-Li!
A-Li greets Uncle Zhen.
You're so polite
Imperial Great-grandson!
- Tian Shu greets both high gods!
- Jia Yun greets both high gods!
Where are you taking little A-Li?
You can't tell me?
What is there not to tell?
Mother, I'm going to visit
Father at the Sea of Innocence.
Will you come with me?
The Sea of Innocence?
- Greetings to Heavenly Lord.
- Zhi Yue greets Heavenly Lord.
Get up.
- Thank you, Heavenly Lord!
Several years ago,
I wronged you unjustly.
You ended up enduring
a heavenly trial for 60 years.
Yuan Zhen, tell me.
How would you like me
to make it up to you?
Heavenly Lord, I don't regard
those 60 years as suffering.
Therefore, I wouldn't ask
for any compensation.
You're a dummy!
How presumptuous.
It's all right.
I always reward and
punish just as fairly.
Go ahead and tell me.
I... I'd like to visit High God Bai Qian.
It's just that she's ranked so high up
that I don't dare to request
a visit at Qing Qiu.
Why are you dumb?
You had to say what shouldn't be said.
You can't mention the name
Bai Qian in here.
Don't you know that?
It's been three years
since Ye Hua passed away.
There's nothing that can't be said.
Yuan Zhen.
Tell me.
Why do you wish to visit
High God Bai Qian in Qing Qiu?
She was my mentor
when I was in the Mortal Realm.
Once a mentor, always a mentor.
I wish to greet her and thank her
for looking after me in the Mortal Realm.
I believe High God Bai Qian
would be very touched by your words.
However, we should discuss
this matter some other time.
The Crown Prince sacrificed his spirit to
the Bell of East Emperor at a young age.
Didn't I already remind you?
Didn't I tell you
that in the Nine Heavens
you're not to mention the deceased
Crown Prince, or his fiancee?
I don't understand.
Why can't we talk about them?
Tell me what you know about them first.
Don't keep touching me.
You might be the Crown Prince's cousin
but it's still inappropriate for
men and women to touch.
Goodness...
- By the way, on you...
- What are you doing?
Do you have any treasures on you?
What do you want with it?
I owe a deity friend some money,
so I have to pay her back.
I don't believe you.
You're always fooling me.
Not once have you told the truth.
You're always carrying this
Cloud Clearing Fan around.
You treat it like some treasure.
I'm going to steal it away
just to spite you!
Mother, who was that lady?
That lady the Queen of Qing Qiu.
High God Bai Qian.
I see.
It's going to rain soon.
We should tidy up and head home.
Good girl.
Mother misses Father again?
I miss your father at all times.
I remember that your father went alone
to slay the four mythical beasts
left behind by the Heavenly Father,
and sank Yingzhou of the Eastern Sea.
He was so valiant that
none was a match for him.
Father was once the son
of the Heavenly Father.
He's definitely invincible.
Now that I think about it,
I've been really fortunate.
The Heavenly Father had two sons.
One is my mentor and
the other, my husband.
Since then, I no longer have eyes
for any other men.
Seventeenth, you're really not
ashamed to brag about yourself.
I've really been very lonely
for the past three years.
Finally, someone has come
to visit me today.
Let's go.
That is the Crown Prince's
basalt crystal coffin.
I know.
His parents took him away from
Qing Qiu in this basalt crystal coffin.
Father, I've been unfilial.
It took me three years to visit you
in the Sea of Innocence.
I've been locked away in Xiwu Palace to
study every day for the past three years.
Grandmother kept an eye on me
and wouldn't let me leave...
Father... I miss you...
Now that you're sleeping in here,
you finally have some rest.
You don't have endless reports to read,
or conquests to make at any time...
Here.
Ye Hua...
A-Li.
Mother, I have to return
to the Celestial Palace now.
I'll surely visit you in Qing Qiu
next month on your birthday.
A-Li, if there are too many books
to study, just leave some out.
I just want you to be happy.
I don't expect you to become
the next Heavenly Lord.
A-Li is the first born of
the Nine Heaven's Crown Prince Ye Hua.
I mustn't slack on my studies.
Although I'm nowhere
as smart as Father was
I must be just as diligent in studies
as Father once was.
You really are Ye Hua's son.
You don't take after me at all.
Fourth Brother.
I watched a play the other day
and felt like watching a few more.
Why don't you head back to
the Peach Tree Woods first?
I'll watch some more plays.
All right.
You'd better not watch so many that
you lose track of time.
Heavenly Lord.
Since this morning
the basalt crystal coffin that
encased the Crown Prince
is suddenly swarmed over by
celestial blessings.
No one can get close to it.
I rushed over to report it to you.
Ye Hua's spirit was already vanquished.
Why would it be protected by
such powerful celestial blessings?
Perhaps...
Ye Hua isn't dead.
Ye Hua...
Ye Hua has returned?
The junior family members are
to be dismissed now.
Not a word about this is to be said.
- Yes!
Could High Immortal Zi Lan
invite High God Mo Yuan over
to take a look personally
in the Sea of Innocence?
I'll head back to Kunlun Mountain
to invite Master over.
Ye Hua...
If it weren't for this basalt crystal
coffin and the Sea of Innocence
Seventeenth might have to
wait a few more years for you.
Mo Yuan...
High God Mo Yuan...
Seek out Seventeenth.
She's been waiting three years for you.
The cenotaph she made for you is
in Ten-mile Peach Tree Woods.
Thank you...
Brother.
- Great!
- Well done!
Upstairs, please.
You really are here!
You came especially to look for me?
Yes! It's rare to find a friend
who likes to watch plays like I do.
Why is the play still so tragic?
Life never turns out the way you want.
This play isn't that tragic,
comparatively.
But whenever I watch this play,
I can't help but think
of my highly talented cousin
who died young!
You had a cousin?
Yes, my cousin was very handsome.
All the women of Heaven and Earth
couldn't walk away after seeing him.
All they could think about
was marrying him.
Sadly, his life was cut short.
He died young on the battlefield,
and left behind bereft parents
as well as a young son
who cries all day in sorrow.
How sad.
The worst is always when the children
pass away before their parents do.
It's sad for your cousin,
but even more so for his parents.
The son he left behind
is the most pitiful one.
Three years ago, our entire tribe thought
all that was left was my cousin's corpse
and his spirit had been vanquished.
They made him a basalt crystal coffin
and sunk him into a sea.
I went to visit him then,
and it all seemed normal.
Who knew that yesterday
in that sea where his coffin lay
the waters were greatly disturbed.
They said that the disturbance
was caused by
the celestial blessings
around the coffin.
Isn't that strange?
My cousin's spirit was long vanquished.
How could his body still be protected
by such powerful celestial blessings?
Anyway, my parents said that
perhaps my cousin isn't dead.
- Great!
- Well done!
What's the matter with you?
Continue with your story.
If he isn't dead, that poor little
A-Li wouldn't have to cry all day.
Is that sea the Sea of Innocence?
Your cousin...
Is he the Crown Prince
of the Celestial Tribe, Ye Hua?
You... How did you know?
Have I given away a secret?
You mustn't tell anyone!
If my parents learn of this,
I won't have the money to watch plays.
- Well done!
- Great!
I finally managed to steal the
Cloud Clearing Fan to pay for that pearl!
Wasn't that High God Bai Qian?
I thought I was seeing things.
- High God!
- Where is His Highness? Where is he?
His Highness?
Isn't he already buried
in the Sea of Innocence?
Master!
Where is Ye Hua?
I knew that you'd come here.
Fret not.
I'm here to talk
to you about this matter.
Heavenly Father used half of his powers
to create the celestial fetus
into a golden lotus.
Since then, those powers have
been hidden in his spirit.
Three years ago, Ye Hua slayed
the four beasts of Yingzhou
and attained the other half
of Heavenly Father's powers from them.
I believe that Ye Hua must have
used all of Heavenly Father's powers
to curb the destructive energy
from the Bell of East Emperor.
His own spirit was wounded from
the collision of those two powers
so it triggered his body to
sink into a cycle of slumber.
Ye Hua?
He would have slept for decades.
However, the basalt crystal coffin
is a great artifact.
The Sea of Innocence might
be a burial place for the Celestial Tribe
but it's also a sacred place
for recuperation.
That was why Ye Hua could
wake up in just three years.
Qian Qian...
Come here.
Ye Hua!
Don't cry.
Look at me.
Am I not standing
before you safe and sound?
What brings you here?
I've brought her here to
greet her savior.
Quickly!
Bow to High Immortal Zi Lan
for saving your life.
High Immortal, thank you
for saving my life.
Get up quickly!
She... Isn't the child a boy?
I kept hearing Xuan Nu call
the child her son.
I thought...
No, the child is a girl.
Perhaps, Xuan Nu wanted a son too badly
to inherit Brother Li Jing's throne
as the Ghost Lord
so she called her a son.
Xuan Nu lived her entire life
fooling herself and others.
You...
Have you been in
Kunlun Mountain all these years?
Yes, I've been here all this time.
I never left.
I heard that your mentor returned.
Did he ever blame you for
making an elixir for the Ghost Tribe?
No.
Did your seniors ever pick on you
for helping me with the elixir?
Not once.
Then I can set my mind at ease.
Farewell.
Hold on!
This is, after all, Kunlun Mountain.
Don't ever come here again.
Don't come looking for me either.
All right.
Farewell.
Master has returned?
Zi Lan just rushed back here to say
that the Crown Prince is waking up?
He is already awake.
That's wonderful!
Seventeenth can finally be married!
Play it well.
Your father already told me that you have
to finish seven rounds of chess with me
before you can go looking for him.
How could I possibly defeat
High God Zhe Yan?
It's all right. I'll let you win.
Your father surely places...
his wife before his son.
Let's not play chess anymore...
How about this?
I'll tell you stories about
your mother when she was little
or the tales of your parents'
love-hate relationship?
When did my parents ever have
a love-hate relationship?
There's only sweet love.
All right...
In all Four Seas and the Eight Far Lands
your parents are the most deeply in love.
I'll tell you about stories about
your mother when she was little then?
Zhen.
Where should we start?
Let's start from that year when she went
traveling across the four seas with me
at 20,000 years old and
created havoc in the realms?
That's a long enough story to tell
until Riceball's baby brother is born.
When your mother was little,
she was very naughty.
She got into trouble every day,
and often took things from others.
She would take things from others
and forget to return them.
Your mother...
Ye Hua.
For the past three years,
I often saw you in my dreams.
Gradually, I couldn't make out
the dream from reality.
In my dreams, you often spoke to me
and played chess with me.
I told my Fourth Brother that
it's best when I dream of you.
Whenever I fell asleep, I could see you.
That was why for the past three years,
I was often very sleepy.
I'd sleep from dawn until dusk
and then get a sip of water
before sleeping all the way
until the next afternoon.
Now... This is not a dream.
Ye Hua...
Tell me.
This isn't a dream, is it?
It isn't.
Qian Qian.
In the previous life, we first met
in Mount Junji of the Far East.
You mistook me for a small black snake.
You kept me as a pet and
even fed me raw meat.
Then I approached you in the name
of repaying your kindness
but you had me marry you.
Later, we just went ahead
and held a wedding ritual.
We became husband and wife.
That was the first time,
I ever felt truly happy.
Not long afterwards
you were forced into the Celestial Palace
and eventually jumped off
the Zhuxian Terrace.
If it hadn't been for A-Li
I really didn't know
how I could have survived.
Fortunately 300 years later...
I met you again.
I remember seeing you
in the Crystal Palace.
I watched you as
you preached to Uncle Sang Ji's wife.
You had a fan in your right hand and
strummed the table with your left
like you always did.
The way you preached at her
and that scar on your wrist
from the crimson hellfire...
I was certain that...
Whether you're Su Su or Qian Qian,
you are just you.
See?
I remember it so clearly.
Would I be able to do so in your dreams?
That's why this isn't a dream.
This isn't a dream.
What you just said
was what we went through.
How can you remember it so clearly?
I still remember what I first
said to you in the Crystal Palace.
I can't remember it very clearly.
Ye Hua failed to recognize that
you were actually High God
Bai Qian of Qing Qiu!
Subtitles by DramaFever