Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 11]
Your Highness.
- Is Fifth Sister here?
- Aunt?
Didn't she say she was going to
Ten-mile Peach Tree Woods?
You didn't see her?
She was there last night
but I haven't seen her
since I woke at daybreak.
Has she returned?
She has not.
However, Zhe Yan is here.
- Zhe Yan?
- Yes.
He is back from the Celestial Palace?
Yes, I am back.
What brings you by Bai Qian's Fox Den?
Why are you here?
I just returned from
the Celestial Palace.
That's right.
I've been focused on where
Fifth Sister might be
and I've forgotten you went to
Celestial Palace to cancel the marriage.
Come.
Let me tell you about
her marriage arrangement.
Has it been canceled?
The marriage to
second prince Sang Ji is canceled
but the marriage arrangement with
the Celestial Tribe is still in place.
What do you mean?
Let me tell you all about it.
Dijun?
Did it ring?
Why are you here?
I followed my aunt here.
Aunt?
Bai Qian of Qing Qiu,
who never appears in public?
Yes, my aunt is Bai Qian.
I remember last night...
I'm not sure if
it was last night anymore.
Before I fell asleep, I saw my aunt
leaving Ten-mile Peach Tree Woods
so I followed her all the way here.
Could it be... your aunt is
somehow tied to Kunlun Mountain?
No, I've never heard her mention it.
Did your aunt leave you this?
Yes, my aunt left it.
Do you know what is written in this?
My aunt said a magic technique
is recorded there.
That's correct.
The technique to seal a spirit within the
Bell of the East Emperor is written here.
The Bell of the East Emperor?
Isn't that the magical weapon
that can destroy heaven and earth?
That is correct.
Isn't that the artifact that
caused Mo Yuan's soul to be scattered
70,000 years ago at Ruoshui Riverbank?
That is correct.
Mo Yuan used this very technique
to seal away Qing Cang.
It seems your aunt does indeed
have many ties to Kunlun Mountain.
How is that possible? My aunt has never
left Qing Qiu since she was born.
Is that true?
It is true.
You are my savior.
I wouldn't dare lie to you.
Where are you going?
The color of your outfit is strange,
but it looks quite nice.
Where did you buy it?
Qing... Qing Qiu.
A-Yin.
I like you.
Since you've tacitly consented,
why must you act so shy?
When did I tacitly consent?
Li Jing.
If you wake up,
I'll give you my promise.
Once you promise me,
you can't go back on your word.
In this lifetime, I, Li Jing
will only be with A-Yin.
If I break this oath
I shall have no posterity
and live a life of loneliness.
Back then, you said
you would be with me
regardless of what happens.
Now you say you were foolish.
Very well.
I'll let you two be.
How long are you going to
keep following me?
I... I said I was going to
repay your kindness.
Did I want you to?
Zhe Yan says a debt must be repaid.
If I don't repay it here
then I'll have to repay it elsewhere.
So, I've thought about it carefully
and I think I should be proactive
about repaying this debt.
This way, I'd able to
choose how I repay you.
Then...
how do you plan on repaying me?
I... I haven't decided yet.
Ever since Mo Yuan left,
Kunlun Mountain hasn't been this lively.
Dong Hua Dijun.
What are you doing at Kunlun Mountain?
I was just passing by
and came in to take a look.
The place is now deserted and no longer
as magnificent as it was back then.
Apologies for intruding.
A-Yin.
It has been 70,000 years.
Where have you gone?
Dijun.
I came upon this just now
and finally understand.
The Bell of the East Emperor's seal
is not permanent.
This must be reported immediately
to Heavenly Lord to make a plan.
When will the seal be lifted?
It happens today.
Today?
The sealing spell lifts
after 70,000 years.
70,000 years? Then...
A lady appeared at
Ruoshui Riverbank today.
She must have known the sealing spell
was about to be lifted
and was there to seal Qing Cang.
70,000 years.
Not even you knew
the sealing spell would be lifted.
Who else in this world
could predict this?
It was not a prediction. Instead...
This lady already knew of this fact,
but did not tell anybody.
I'm afraid she had already planned
to fight Qing Cang alone
and not involve anybody else.
The more I hear from you
the more I admire this lady.
Dijun, who might this lady be?
It is most likely...
This young princess's aunt.
My aunt?
I have yet to ask. This is...
I am Bai Feng Jiu of Qing Qiu.
Granddaughter of the Fox King.
- Princess Feng Jiu.
- That is me.
Then your aunt is Bai Qian of Qing Qiu?
That's right, my aunt is Bai Qian.
Then isn't she the Crown Prince's
Crown Princess Consort?
What Crown Princess Consort?
Isn't my aunt marrying the second prince?
Why has it turned into
the crown prince?
It is a long story.
- Then make it a long story short.
- All right.
Then we'll have to start from
that little snake from your aunt's den.
Little snake? Do you mean Shao Xing?
Yes, Shao Xing.
Shao Xing--
Why do you guess that
it is Bai Qian of Qing Qiu?
The scroll you're holding
is what Bai Qian left for
the princess last night.
The Bell of the East Emperor's
sealing method is written in detail.
Don't you find it
too much of a coincidence?
It is too much of a coincidence.
However, I have one question.
It's said Bai Qian has never stepped foot
outside of Qing Qiu after she was born.
How did she come to know about
Mo Yuan's special sealing technique?
That is also what puzzles me.
Moreover, this kind of special technique
is passed down from master to disciple.
Mo Yuan never accepted
a female disciple.
Your Highness.
Do you know something we don't?
My aunt has no relation
to Kunlun Mountain.
Then that's strange.
I'm afraid this question
will only be answered
when Mo Yuan comes back from the dead.
Or...
When Ye Hua marries Bai Qian,
you can ask her yourself.
You must be joking, Dijun.
Miss Bai Qian of Qing Qiu
has such a high rank.
I do not dare speak carelessly.
Star Lord, you've piqued my interest
in hearing a story.
You'll have to explain everything.
After that, you have to help me
repay Dijun's kindness.
Repay his kindness?
That's correct.
Quick, tell me.
Why is my aunt marrying the crown prince?
And you were talking about my aunt
sealing the Bell of the East Emperor.
Everything is so confusing.
Can you explain everything to me?
Let's go.
Let's talk while we go.
Where do you want to start?
Start from the snake then.
All right.
I was only gone for a few days.
That snake made my aunt into
the world's laughingstock?
No, even if Zhe Yan
and Grandfather can tolerate it
I cannot!
So what if you cannot?
Your aunt doesn't even care.
She can tolerate it
because she is magnanimous.
I cannot tolerate it.
Why don't you take me to
the Celestial Palace?
What? I have to teach
that snake a lesson.
Then wouldn't I be committing
the crime of aiding and abetting?
You ruined your life's prospects
for this woman.
Do you harbor any resentment?
I dare not.
You can take this snake with you,
but you are not to give her any title.
That is the most I can tolerate.
I accept your command.
Shao Xing, stop right there.
My aunt has treated you well.
Yet you dare steal her future husband,
causing her to be ridiculed by the world?
Princess.
Do you still acknowledge me
as the princess?
It is all my fault.
Please do not be angry, Your Highness.
Be mindful of your health.
You were always good at
pretending to be delicate.
Impudence! Where did
this feral girl come from?
You dare behave atrociously
in the Celestial Palace?
You dare stand in my way? You--
You are that heartless man.
The Celestial Palace's
second prince, Sang Ji.
No, you've been demoted.
You are no longer the second prince.
You are Water King of the North Sea.
Your rank is lower than mine. What right
do you have to stand in my way?
Shut up!
Water King of the North Sea.
Please calm down,
Princess, please calm down as well.
Since the Heavenly Lord
has made his ruling
then you two should try to
maintain some harmony.
Out of respect for Star Lord Si Ming,
I'll let you off this time.
I am a princess of Qing Qiu.
I don't need your pardon.
You were unfaithful to Qing Qiu first.
- You can't even take a lecture from me?
- You--
Feng Jiu.
Dijun.
How... How come you're here?
If I didn't come
was I to let you have a confrontation
with Water King of the North Sea?
I am just standing up for my aunt.
This is the young princess of Qing Qiu.
She has been spoiled by the Fox King.
Please do not take it
to heart, Water King.
I don't dare.
This lady...
Have you always been serving
by the side of Bai Qian of Qing Qiu?
Yes.
Then...
Have you ever heard of Si Yin?
Oh no, is Dijun investigating
Mo Yuan's whereabouts?
Then will Shao Xing...
I do not know.
At least she has some conscience left.
Do you know who I am?
I do not.
I am Dong Hua Dijun.
If you lie to me,
nobody would be able to save you.
Dijun, you're a bully!
I...
truly have never heard of Si Yin.
Hold it together.
Dijun, do not pressure her.
She stays in Qing Qiu all year round.
How could she possibly know Si Yin of
Kunlun Mountain from 70,000 years ago?
That is true.
- Dijun.
Taichen Palace?
Outrageous! You dare
trespass into Taichen Palace?
So there is still a place in this world
that I, Bai Feng Jiu, cannot enter.
How unexpected that
there would still be a human
who would dare come to
Mount Junji of the Far East.
The Jade Purity Fan of Kunlun?
70,000 years ago... 70,000 years ago...
I will bury you all with the dead!
Impossible.
That was clearly a mortal in that hut.
And it was a woman.
But why would she have
the Jade Purity Fan of Kunlun?
Scarlet Flame Golden Lion.
Who are you?
Crown Prince of
the Celestial Tribe, Ye Hua.
Why is there red lightning
on this mountain?
Run!
Quick, run!
There's a monster!
Run!
I have been hiding from
the Celestial Tribe for 70,000 years.
Why must you be so ruthless?
As a man sows,
so shall he reap.
Mother!
Mother, where are you?
My child!
It is a dragon!
- It's a dragon god!
- A dragon god!
A dragon god!
Dragon god!
Thank you!
The Golden Lion's crimson hellfire
sure is powerful.
I actually cannot even return
to my human form.
I'll have to rest here for a few days.
You're awake.
Here.
There's a cat at my house.
I hope you two can get along.
Does it taste good?
How come you're here?
Little black snake, come with me.
What is this place?
That person?
In my dream,
that person was a man.
How come it is a woman now?
You're awake.
Do you know?
You're the most attractive snake
of the ones I've met.
Look, there are even horns on your head.
They feel so smooth. How nice.
Do I look like a snake?
When I saw you in the cave
I thought you were
hibernating for the winter.
Then I remembered it's only
the ninth month of the year.
It's not time for snakes to
go into hibernation yet.
So I figured you might have been injured
and brought you back
to nurse you.
The Golden Lion might be powerful,
but he can't hurt me.
Do you know what this place is?
Other than birds and beasts,
why aren't there any other humans?
This is Mount Junji of the Far East.
The Golden Lion has forcibly occupied
the mountain for over 10 years
so naturally, nobody would
dare hunt here.
Let me tell you. I only have this hut.
You look like you don't have
a home to return to either.
Why don't you stay
and I'll take care of you?
I only need three days to be able
to resume my human form
and return to the Celestial Palace.
Why would I need you to take care of me?
No, I shouldn't discuss this with you.
Since I brought you back,
you should stay to accompany me.
But if you want to leave,
I won't stop you.
However, you must not have
any other owner, all right?
Owner?
All right.
I couldn't catch any animals.
I only have some fruit.
Have these to eat.
This fan...
Could it be
the Jade Purity Fan of Kunlun?
How would a mortal have
Kunlun Mountain's artifact?
Your Highness.
Why is His Highness
resting so early today?
Is he feeling unwell?
Princess, His Highness
received Heavenly Lord's orders
and has gone to the mortal realm
to subdue the Golden Lion.
Golden Lion?
Isn't that Qing Cang's mount?
Yes, it is that Golden Lion.
It fled to the mortal realm due to
unforeseen events in the Ghost Realm.
Then when will His Highness be back?
I've made soup for him.
I'm afraid it will cool.
A day in heaven is a year on earth.
His trip there and back
will at most be the time it takes
for an incense stick to burn.
Then please bring this soup inside for me
so His Highness can drink it
when he returns.
Yes.
They don't attend court
and yet the separate clans
expect me to commend their loyalty?
Please calm down, Father.
Kunlun Mountain has already disbanded.
I believe peaceful relations
are most necessary.
We can only try to
placate the clan leaders.
Eldest Brother is correct.
The Mermaid Clan is in the south.
The north is not at peace either.
We must not raise
internal strife at this time.
I understand. You two
need not be so worried.
Where is Ye Hua?
Your Majesty.
Crown Prince has gone to the mortal realm
to subdue the Golden Lion.
Since Ye Hua is not here,
why don't you two speak first
about what plans you have
to make the clan leaders believe
my sincere intentions for harmony?
Su Jin, you may leave.
Your Majesty.
Do you believe that
I am siding with outsiders?
Your Majesty brought me into the
Celestial Palace when I was a child. I...
You are a woman.
There is no use for you to stay here.
You may go.
Yes.
I have a way to pacify
the separate clans.
You have a way? What is it?
Grant me the title of side consort.
Confer the title of side consort to you?
If you confer
the title of side consort to me
you would not be strengthening
the power of any one clan
and it would also show
the whole world
that Your Majesty values
each and every clan.
I am already old.
I have long since
lost interest in the harem.
I will be holding you back.
I only wish to do something
for Your Majesty.
I wish to do something useful for
the world, just as my father did.
It is precisely because your father
made sacrifices for the Celestial Tribe
that I have even more reason
to not allow you to do so.
The south poses trouble
from the Mermaid Clan
while the north is in such unrest.
The Celestial Tribe is
in need of manpower.
Do not hesitate
any longer, Your Majesty.
I am willing to do this.
I have absolutely no complaints.
You do not understand, child.
This is an important life decision.
You must not act rashly.
If...
If Your Majesty feels you owe me a debt
could you allow me this?
In the future, no matter
what wish I may have
Your Majesty will grant it to me.
Why didn't I notice
you were injured when I took you in?
When I took in those birds,
I also used this herbal medicine on them
and they were healed within 10 days.
Bear with it for a while.
I'll be done soon.
This is the yellowseed herb
found only in the far east.
It can remove rotting flesh.
It must be used with the juice of berries
with a regenerative effect to be useful.
By using this by itself,
aside from making my injuries worse
there is no other benefit.
All done. Aren't I good to you?
Snakes like to eat raw meat, right?
Snakes do like to eat raw meat.
But I do not.
Eat it. You'll get hungry.
Meat must be cooked before it's eaten.
If you starve, I'll be sad.
Presumptuous!
You still won't eat?
Are you not eating because
you want me to give you another kiss?
No... No need. I'll eat.
The snakes here are so smart.
They even know to pick out
the food they like to eat.
It's a good thing that
I brought you back that day.
You're much smarter than
those birds and cats.
Why don't you come with me
to the market for some things?
I've already been here for three days.
I should be leaving now.
Although you've made
my injuries a bit worse
it was out of good intentions.
Thank you for your
three days of hospitality.
Farewell then.
Let's go then.
Can't you see it'll rain soon?
It's about to rain!
I have to find a place to hide.
I heard Crown Prince is in this area
to subdue the Golden Lion.
It would have been great
to have heard the news earlier.
I've been at the Celestial Palace
for dozens of millennia
but I never had the chance
to speak to him.
Are you about to cast rain?
Crown... Crown Prince.
No need to cast rain today.
Yes.
The dark clouds are clearing already?
You're sleeping again?
If you're not eating, you're sleeping.
You truly are a snake.
- Your Highness.
Su Jin.
Heavenly Lord.
I have already killed the Golden Lion.
I have come to report back.
Good. You subdued him so easily.
You have indeed
lived up to my expectations.
However, I was careless and was injured.
I am not worthy of your confidence in me.
- Is it serious?
- No, it is just a light injury.
The wound has just not been handled well
and will need a new dressing.
Crimson hellfire is
no ordinary monster power.
Do not treat this lightly.
Yes.
- Come, put some effort into it.
- Slowly, slowly. Be careful.
- Clear this up. Let me help you.
- Put it here. Here, give me that.
Here, hold this.
Watch out for your foot.
- Put this over there.
- All right.
There's still some more wood over there.
Pick it all up.
Sir, what happened here?
Yesterday, there was a monster
that looked much like a lion.
Its whole body was red.
It spewed flames everywhere.
Look, it burned everything here.
The heavens must have been
looking after us.
A black dragon suddenly appeared
and cast rain, putting out all the fires.
It even killed the monster
with a single thunderbolt.
Did the monster look like a lion?
That is what is being said.
The Golden Lion?
Sir, do you know where
the monster's corpse is?
You are such a strange lady.
You want to see the monster's corpse?
I don't know, I don't know.
Back then, Li Yuan disappeared with
Father's mount, the Golden Lion.
If it really is the Golden Lion
I'll be able to find a clue
to Li Yuan's whereabouts.
I sold some fruit and got some money.
Let's go to the teahouse
for tea and opera later.
Let's go.
Come, take a look at this talisman.
If yesterday's events happen again
this will give you
the black dragon's protection
and leave you unharmed.
- I'll have one!
- Come, come.
- I want one!
- Plenty for all.
Can this talisman really ward off evil?
Of course. Do you want a talisman, Miss?
I'm not afraid of monsters.
For a lady, you have such courage.
You're not afraid of monsters?
- It was beaten to the ground.
- Good, good!
Before you knew it, the hero had
turned around and rode astride the tiger
and delivered a few cuffs and kicks.
- Good, good!
- Miss.
Why did you follow me?
I'm not buying a talisman.
I only want to ask you about
the origins of this fan.
I picked it up.
How about selling it to me?
It's not for sale.
This fan is the first item I found.
I'm keeping it as a memento.
It is of no use to you.
Why must you insist on keeping it?
I said I'm not selling it.
- Miss, look.
- You!
Miss, why did you steal my fan
while I was making talismans?
Who stole your fan? Give it back--
You!
I was selling talismans outside just now.
You came to join the crowd
and stole my fan while I was unawares.
I found this fan.
- You--
- Everybody, look!
Come, come.
Miss, since you are so stubborn
why don't we have
someone else bear witness
and see who this fan really belongs to?
The fan originally belongs to me.
Why should I need someone else
to make the judgment?
If this fan really does belong to you
then do you know
what is drawn on this fan
and who had inscribed the words on it?
Yes, that is reasonable.
I did not take a close look at it before.
Of course you don't know.
Even if you did know, you wouldn't know
the history of this fan.
This was passed down from my ancestors.
It has been passed down
for several generations to me.
The painting on here depicts
the immortals' Kunlun Mountain.
This fan is an immortal's artifact,
the Jade Purity Fan of Kunlun.
Is it that impressive?
Jade Purity Fan of Kunlun?
Subtitles by DramaFever