Subtitles by DramaFever
[Ten Miles of Peach Blossoms]
[Episode 6]
Qing Cang is so ridiculous.
He hasn't even won the war yet
and he's already started to celebrate.
- Master.
These two are my disciples,
Si Yin and Ling Yu.
Greet the Heavenly Lord's three princes
and Yao Guang.
Kunlun Mountain's 17th disciple, Si Yin
Kunlun Mountain's 9th disciple, Ling Yu
greet Yao Guang and the three Highnesses.
Let's end here for tonight.
Master, why have the people of
Celestial Palace come as well?
Master, did the Celestial Palace
receive bad news?
Even the Heavenly Lord's
three princes have come.
No.
The three princes have never
been in a war before.
They have come for the experience.
I also happen to need someone with
tremendous magic power to lead the army.
This time, I have arranged
seven formations.
Each formation has seven variations,
for a total of 49 variations.
Although the princes
have seen the formations
they have never practiced them
in actual combat.
Ling Yu.
Lead 10,000 soldiers
as vanguard tomorrow.
That will put me more at ease.
Yes, Master.
What about me, Master?
You will follow me to lead
the main force.
Yes.
Although the formations are ingenious,
Qing Cang is not one to be taken lightly.
Do not underestimate him.
Yes, Master.
I will not let you down.
Master.
Are you worried about tomorrow's battle?
When I think that this place will soon be
littered with corpses tomorrow
I feel it is a shame for
Ruoshui Riverbank's beautiful scenery.
This war can at least bring
700,000 years of peace to the world.
Would it be any better to
think of it this way?
Seventeenth.
You once asked me about the method
to seal the Bell of the East Emperor.
- Do you still remember?
- I remember.
I will pass on the spell to you tonight.
Really? Thank you, Master.
I have 17 disciples.
You are the one with the most talent
and able to perform this spell.
If it were not so
I really do not wish to impart
such a dangerous spell to you.
Thank you for your praise, Master.
Could Master have
seen through my disguise
and know I am the Fox King's daughter?
What is the matter?
It's nothing, Master.
You can begin.
Charge!
Break into the Celestial formation!
Those who behead a general
will be conferred a rank of a nobility!
Attack!
The formation has been broken!
Impossible! How could the formation
be so quickly broken?
Li Jing, don't go!
I cannot watch A-Yin die.
Li Jing, you clearly know--
You clearly know
they will undoubtedly lose.
Why must you still go?
Is it really as Li Yuan says?
The one you like is Si Yin?
Ninth!
Seventeenth!
Seventeenth, don't come any closer!
Ninth!
Ninth.
Ninth! Ninth!
Seventeenth.
Leave quickly.
Ninth!
Ninth, hold on!
Ninth! Ninth!
Wake up, Ninth!
I'll get you out of here.
Master will definitely
be able to save you.
Ninth.
Ninth!
Si Yin.
You should worry about whether
you yourself can escape.
Li Jing!
You dare side with the enemy?
The formation was broken by my men.
Naturally, I should be the one
to take the credit.
What's the matter?
Do I not even have the right
to keep one person alive?
All right.
You are correct.
Your Xuan Nu has indeed earned merit.
She helped you steal
the tactical formation strategy
and gained you an advantage.
But now, you dare to
openly defend the enemy!
I also have the right to
execute you on the spot!
What did he just say?
A-Yin, I will explain this to you later.
Li Jing.
You had Xuan Nu steal
our Kunlun Mountain
tactical formation strategy?
A-Yin, I...
God Mo Yuan.
Master! Master!
Master, hurry and save Ninth.
Send word to Die Feng.
Have him come
and take Ling Yu's body
back to Kunlun Mountain.
Master!
Not even you can save Ninth?
Ninth! Ninth!
I'm sorry, Seventeenth.
This time, there is nothing
I can do either.
It's all my fault.
Master, it's all my fault.
If I had noticed earlier,
Ninth wouldn't have died.
This isn't your fault.
The formation was broken.
Master, the formation was broken
because of Xuan Nu.
She stole the formation strategy.
What did you say?
Xuan Nu stole
the tactical formation strategy
and gave it to Qing Cang.
Mo Yuan, once this formation
has been arranged
there is no leeway for change.
So we...
We...
not only will suffer a crushing defeat
but 200,000 Celestial soldiers will also
lose their lives at Ruoshui Riverbank.
Report!
Report, after Ghost Tribe
broke our formation
they formed a strange formation
and had my troops enveloped.
- Report!
My left flank has been breached
with disastrous casualties!
Report, my right wing and rearguard have
been breached with grievous casualties!
Thank you for your assistance.
You are of the Fox Clan?
I am Bai Zhen.
You are the fourth son of the Fox King?
Yes.
You aren't a high-ranking officer
in this war.
You need not stay here.
Please take my disciple
out of the tent as well.
All right.
I won't intrude then.
Si Yin.
Fourth Brother.
I am the cause of Ninth's death.
If I hadn't met Li Jing
and didn't let Xuan Nu stay with me
then Ninth wouldn't have died.
Fifth Sister, going by what you say
I am the one who sent Xuan Nu
to Kunlun Mountain to find you.
Then won't we both
have to pay with our lives?
Eldest Sister-in-law even
sent a letter a few days ago
saying she was quite satisfied with
Xuan Nu's marriage
and told me to thank you.
If not for Eldest Sister-in-law, I would
have already slashed her to pieces.
Since she has chosen the Ghost Tribe
then she is no longer
affiliated with Qing Qiu.
If you ever see her again,
you can kill her with one stroke.
You need not think twice.
It is what she deserves.
Mo Yuan, I request to fight.
- Mo Yuan, I also request to fight.
Princes, you need not rush to fight.
If there's a need to lead troops,
Kunlun Mountain has 16 disciples.
Since we have come,
we are not here just for show.
We're willing to live or die
with all the soldiers.
We are willing to live or die
Right now, I need 100,000 men
to throw away their lives.
Throw away their lives?
That is correct. Throw away their lives.
The soldiers outside are all
descendants of the Celestial Tribe.
Although they're not as respected
as the royal family
they are all precious lives.
Please reconsider.
The present situation is urgent.
We must take a risky move.
Only then can we
turn defeat into victory.
If this plan succeeds,
the rest can live.
If we do not make this move
I'm afraid the world
will have a new ruler.
I will personally lead the troops and
create an opening in their formation.
However, I need a brave and skilled
military officer
to lead these 100,000 soldiers
towards the southeast corner
to break the enemy's encirclement.
If it can lure 100,000 soldiers
of the Ghost Tribe in pursuit
it can gain us
one last hope at surviving.
Mo Yuan, I am a part of
the Celestial Tribe.
This time, I happen to have brought
100,000 soldiers.
My entire clan is willing to
clear a path for you!
Are you of the Su Jin Clan?
That is correct, Su Jin Clan.
Very well.
Mo Yuan.
In terms of bravery and skill in warfare
in this tent, aside from you,
there is no other but me.
If you send an unknown officer
to lead the troops
I'm afraid Qing Cang
will not fall for it.
I am willing to personally lead
the army of 100,000
and offer one more to the count for you.
This path is doomed to have no return.
For the people
I am willing to accept the order.
Fourth Brother.
If we lose this war
then won't we be
letting down Ninth Disciple?
If Ninth Disciple's parents were to know
he already died at Ruoshui Riverbank
how upset would they be?
All people eventually die.
It is only sooner or later.
Live with a clear conscience
then even in death,
there will be no loss of dignity.
His death was worthwhile.
I had originally wanted to
watch the war from afar
but who knew nothing would
happen as expected.
Fourth Brother, do you know of
the Bell of the East Emperor?
Yes. I've also seen it when I was young.
However, its whereabouts are unknown now.
It is in Qing Cang's possession.
Is that true?
This is another serious matter then.
In an hour, we will carry out the plan.
Remember, after you have
broken through the encirclement
thin out the enemy's frontline
as much as possible.
Understood.
Farewell for now.
On the day I return
I will have another contest with you.
No matter the outcome
after our duel
let us wipe the slate clean.
What do you say?
Very well.
Everyone, I will be going first.
- Farewell.
Of the seven formations I laid out
one general has perished,
and one general will lead a diversion.
I still need two other generals to lead.
We have already split our troops.
If we request for more troops
from Heavenly Lord
I'm afraid they won't get here in time.
Master, I request to lead.
You have never led an army, Seventeenth.
I have followed you for 20,000 years.
I have long since committed
the formation to heart.
Please believe me.
I am also willing to lead.
You?
In this canopy, in terms of magic power
aside from you, I'm afraid
I am the only other choice.
Very well.
The two of you will lead the troops.
Si Yin will lead
Yao Guang's left flank forces.
Bai Zhen will lead Ling Yu's vanguard.
- Yes.
In a bit, according to
my agreement with Yao Guang
I'll lead the main force to break through
the enemy's southeast corner
and allow Yao Guang to escape
from the encirclement.
At this time
Yang Cuo, Sang Ji, and Lian Song
will pretend to give up and retreat.
Mo Yuan, Qing Cang has already
changed his formation
and diverted at least 100,000 soldiers
in pursuit of Yao Guang.
Good.
Seize Qing Cang's head
as an offering to Celestial soldiers
who heroically sacrificed their lives!
Seize Qing Cang's head
as an offering to Celestial soldiers
who heroically sacrificed their lives!
Seize Qing Cang's head
as an offering to Celestial soldiers
who heroically sacrificed their lives!
Qing Cang.
If you allow yourself to be captured
your troops behind you
might have a chance to live.
But if you do not surrender
then you shall pay with your life
for the Celestial soldiers
who died in this war.
As long as I am lord of the Ghost Tribe
I will never surrender.
It is time for a change in this world.
With all these gods to accompany me
I deem this war worthwhile.
Mo Yuan, do you recognize this?
The Bell of the East Emperor?
This Bell of the East Emperor
was created by you.
Today, you will die by it!
Si Yin!
Catch him!
Si Yin.
Qing Cang.
Since I was the one who created
the Bell of the East Emperor
then I know how to control it!
Master!
Seventeenth, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Wait for me.
Master.
Master!
- Master!
- Seventeenth!
Master!
Master.
- Master!
Master!
Master.
- Master!
Master!
Immortals, this is the Ghost Tribe's
document of surrender.
My father has been sealed in
the Bell of the East Emperor.
The Ghost Tribe no longer wants to
stand against the Celestial Tribe.
Please accept this document of surrender
and allow my 30,000 defeated troops
a chance to live.
What is the use of
a document of surrender?
I'll have you all buried with the dead!
Seventeenth!
- Seventeenth, stop!
- Seventeenth!
This concerns all the people
in the world! Do not be rash!
The Ghost Tribe has millions of people.
You'll never kill us all!
I'll annihilate the entire Ghost Tribe
even if I have to
devote my whole life to it!
Si Yin, casualties are unavoidable
when it comes to war.
Moreover, my father
has already been sealed.
Please do not implicate any others!
Let go of me!
- Si Yin!
- Seventeenth!
Let's go back to Kunlun Mountain.
What did you say?
Mo Yuan used his spirit as a sacrifice
to the Bell of the East Emperor
and his soul has been scattered.
All right.
I understand.
Wait.
What orders do you have, Dijun?
Regardless, Qing Cang has
already been sealed.
Go quickly to Grand Ziming Palace.
Go sooner rather than later.
Yes.
Here, have some fruit.
Go away!
I was beaten half to death for you.
I also went to Kunlun Mountain
to steal the formation strategy for you.
Now that we have lost,
it is just your father's destiny.
Why must you still treat me so?
What does winning or losing
have to do with me?
And what do the things you've done
How do they not?
Now that the Ghost Tribe has lost
and Mo Yuan has consequently died
I have become a sinner
of Kunlun Mountain.
From now on,
on heaven or on earth
I can only rely on you, Your Highness.
Do you know, Xuan Nu?
You've relied on the wrong person.
I have no power or influence
in the Ghost Tribe
and I've always been
antagonistic to Li Yuan.
Now that Father is dead
Li Yuan will succeed the throne.
Very soon, I will be dead.
You rely on me?
Then who am I to rely on?
Second Prince.
What is it?
Someone from Celestial Tribe has come.
- Send him in.
- Yes.
I am Star Lord Si Ming.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Hasn't my brother already handed over
the document of surrender?
What are you people from Celestial Tribe
coming to see me for?
I am here to help Your Highness
take the position of Ghost Lord.
The position of Ghost Lord?
I have absolutely no interest.
You can leave.
Your Highness, supposing that
Eldest Prince succeeds the throne
you will probably not live past tomorrow.
Besides, he and you have animosity
over the death of your mother.
You have yet to take revenge.
How could you possibly be resigned?
How could Master...
Master...
Master!
Master.
Zhe Yan, when will Master wake up?
Subtitles by DramaFever