Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 31]
I've finally gotten rid of
that father and son.
I'll find a place to sleep on
the north bank tonight.
I'll deliver the wine to
Fourth Brother's manor tomorrow.
- A-Li has gone to sleep?
- He's sleeping.
He always falls asleep come nightfall.
All these years, you've taken on
the role of his father and his mother.
It truly is not an easy task.
I have yet to thank you
for saving my life.
I wasn't expecting you to thank me.
Why?
Although I saved you 300 years ago,
I did not wake you up.
At the time, you were completely
disheartened and had no will to live.
Since you did not want to live,
why are you thanking me now?
But it seems you have found
something to live for now.
Come, try my peach blossom wine.
Tell me. What have you come for today?
Bai Qian of Qing Qiu.
When I accepted the engagement between
you two 300 years at the grand hall
you did not seem interested.
Yet, you are now.
I have three questions.
What are they? Tell me.
Let's see if I can help you
clear things up.
Why is Bai Qian so averse
to bright lights?
Were her eyes injured before?
It is an ailment she was born with.
Is it true that in her battle
with Qing Cang 300 years ago
she was injured and
was unconscious for many years?
Of course it is true.
The whole world knows it.
What's the matter?
You don't believe it?
Look at how old I am. I'm an old phoenix.
Why would I lie to a junior?
It's true, it's true.
It doesn't seem as if Zhe Yan is lying.
Could it be...
No, it can't be.
Even if everything else is a coincidence,
that scar is real.
Nobody is able to remove
the scars left by crimson hellfire.
And what is the third question?
Has she once forgotten something?
How did you know?
She truly has?
That's an exaggeration. It's not amnesia.
It's just that in the few years
she was asleep
there were many events that happened
that she is unaware of.
Why would you think
she had lost her memory?
I am overthinking things.
Does this fellow know something?
Could he be the one
Bai Qian wanted to forget?
By the way, Ye Hua,
I also have a question for you.
Please ask.
From the first time I saw you
you have always been dressed
in black from head to toe.
Even to this day.
I just find it most strange.
Why would such a young man as you
like to wear such a dark, gloomy color?
This color indeed is not too pleasing,
but it is very practical.
Should I be sliced by a sword one day
and my clothes become soaked with blood
nobody would be able to tell.
One would merely think
I'd fallen into a lake.
If nobody can tell
then my adversary will not
feel satisfaction from wounding me
and my loved ones will not worry either.
You are similar to Mo Yuan.
Sometimes, even I speculate
whether you are actually Mo Yuan.
No, I am not Mo Yuan.
Here.
My lord, you're awake?
What time is it?
You've only slept for an hour.
Do all the men of Ghost Realm
hold their liquor as well as you do?
I don't know about other people.
But my tolerance has grown
over these last 70,000 years.
My lord, don't look so heartbroken.
Since fate has brought us together,
then we should act like lovers.
Your eyes see me.
Your heart should see me too.
These woods aren't as nice as Zhe Yan's
but it's good for shielding me
from the elements.
I'll sleep under these shrubs tonight.
A-Yin, where have you been
all these years?
So it is Ghost Lord Li Jing.
A-Yin, don't speak to me like that.
I have long ago
broken all ties with you.
I don't deserve to be called A-Yin.
Please call me by my proper name.
A-Yin.
You've been avoiding me for 70,000 years.
Are you going to keep hiding from me?
I have been searching for you
all these years.
I was wrong. It was all my fault, A-Yin.
I searched the entire Kunlun Mountain
and all corners of the Celestial Realm.
I know you blame me.
You said Grand Ziming Palace was
your sworn enemy. Do you know I--
I'm sorry to have troubled you,
Ghost Lord.
The things I said back then were
only in the heat of the moment.
The Celestial Tribe and Ghost Tribe
get along well now.
I did not live so long
without learning anything.
I do understand some principles.
Naturally, I will not
make trouble out of nothing
and come to your
Grand Ziming Palace to cause trouble.
What do you mean by that?
You won't even bother
to blame me anymore?
There is no love,
so naturally there is no blame.
From now on, we should
both mind our own business.
No, A-Yin.
You must not say that
without listening to me first.
I betrayed you back then.
Just because you were
part of the Celestial Tribe, I...
All these years,
they've told me you already...
I didn't believe it.
A-Yin.
I was thinking of you all these years.
I've also been searching for you
all these years.
I don't believe that I do not exist
even a little bit in your heart.
Who says I am part of
the Celestial Tribe?
Open your eyes and take a clear look.
I am Bai Qian of Qing Qiu.
You are Bai Qian of Qing Qiu?
Then... Back then, you...
Back then, only for the purpose of
studying at Kunlun Mountain
did I hide my identity as part of
the Nine-tailed Fox Clan.
Since you have mentioned the past to me
let's talk about it.
Back then, you abandoned me
and chose Xuan Nu.
She was carried by four qilin beasts
and officially wed
with nine days of celebration.
Is that not the truth?
Don't mention her.
Did you not feel sad back then?
Why didn't you tell me
you were of the Fox Clan?
Generally speaking, I was sad
for a period of time.
Now I can't even remember it.
Since Ghost Lord adores Xuan Nu
then you must adore
her character and temperament
and not her face that is similar to mine.
I no longer hold any resentment for you.
There is nothing worth mentioning.
A-Yin.
I know you blame me.
You blame me for not giving the soul jade
to you back in Grand Ziming Palace.
But I regret it, A-Yin.
I later went to
Kunlun Mountain seeking you
but they said you had already...
You had already left with Mo Yuan's body.
High Immortal!
You don't look much different.
You still look like a child.
Ghost Lord.
What happened 70,000 years ago
was a big mess.
There is no need for you to
keep thinking about it every day.
You have a beautiful lady here.
Do not keep thinking of the past.
Farewell.
A-Yin! A-Yin!
A-Yin!
A-Yin.
If you leave like this,
how am I to find you?
How am I to find you again?
My lord!
My lord.
Was that female immortal
once your lover as well?
Go away.
My lord, I heard
your conversation very clearly.
She is merely a lover from the past.
If it's over, it's over.
You like female immortals.
Well, I am a female immortal.
Female immortal?
Don't tell me you want to follow me
back to Grand Ziming Palace.
Are you aware of this?
The lives of immortals who live in the
Ghost Realm for too long are shortened.
Did you also know this?
The children born from immortals
in the Grand Ziming Palace...
are either sick or dead.
My lord.
My lord!
Do you truly want to enter
the Celestial Palace?
It is my life's wish.
Please grant me my wish, my lord.
If you insist, I will have Tian Shu
lead you into the palace.
When you have come to your senses,
you can leave on your own.
Thank you, Your Highness!
Father, walk faster!
Father, is this where Mother lived
for hundreds of thousands of years?
That's right.
I can't believe Mother is
so many years older than you, Father.
Father must be quite regretful
that you did not get to be with Mother
when you were a child.
Your Highness!
Your Highness.
Aunt is not in the Fox Den.
I know she is not back yet.
Then does Your Highness know
where Aunt has gone?
She fled from the North Sea.
Fled?
Did Aunt displease someone?
That shouldn't be.
She's survived hundreds of millennia
to become a high goddess.
There isn't anybody
she should be afraid of in this world.
What did she flee for?
There are some matters I must attend to.
I'll be leaving A-Li here for now.
Imperial great-grandson?
You mustn't.
How can I look after
the imperial great-grandson by myself?
I'm really easy to look after.
Just give me a cup of tea and two books.
Just bring me whatever
my mother usually likes to read.
Your Highness, don't jest.
I came to the Fox Den
when I was around your age.
I've never left Qing Qiu.
How would I know what your mother likes?
High Goddess Bai Qian is my mother.
I'll read what she likes to read.
When I burned Su Su's belongings...
the fire would burn
in the green color that she likes.
If it...
Green? It's green!
How come you still haven't given up?
Why is the lamp...
I thought you had no more
of Su Su's possessions?
It wasn't easy to bring the flame back!
Why did you put it out?
- I no longer need it.
- No longer need it?
I have already found her.
What do you mean by that?
Could it be that the mortal didn't die
when she jumped off Zhuxian Terrace?
Impossible. Unless it wasn't her
who jumped off.
Neither.
You're an enigma! Tell me quickly!
You're truly killing me with suspense!
It turns out the reason
the Soul-gathering Lamp
was lit for 300 years
but did not create a wisp of a shadow...
is because Su Su's soul
was not destroyed.
She merely forgot about me.
Her soul was not destroyed?
How is it possible for a mortal
to survive a jump off Zhuxian Terrace?
Unless she is an immortal.
Are you saying she is an immortal?
That's right.
Where is she from?
Has she never been to Celestial Palace?
She is Qing Qiu's queen,
High Goddess Bai Qian.
What did you say?
Do not tell this to anyone yet.
There are still two things
I have yet to figure out.
Why did she not have any celestial aura
and was left in the Far East?
Why has she now forgotten about me?
Wait, I need some time.
I need to think about this.
Where are you going?
I'm going to see Dong Hua Dijun.
He knows best what happened 300 years ago
when Qing Cang broke out of the Bell.
I'm going to Taichen Palace.
Please help me put away
the Soul-gathering Lamp.
Su Su is Bai Qian.
Bai Qian is Su Su.
Then didn't you go through
that torment for nothing back then?
If it was her, you could have
just married her
with the whole world congratulating you.
Is Your Highness here to see Dijun?
Yes. Is Dijun already in
the mortal realm to experience trials?
Yes, he's already left.
You have always been by Dijun's side.
Do you know what happened 300 years ago
when Qing Cang broke out of the Bell?
Hasn't the matter been resolved?
Aunt Bai Qian of Qing Qiu
sealed away Qing Cang.
She was injured and
was asleep for many years.
Is there nothing else?
I am not sure about anything else.
All right, I understand.
Yun Sheng.
Aunt, you haven't come by in many years.
You've come at the wrong time.
Bi Fang has run away from home.
Fourth Uncle left yesterday
in search of him.
If you do not mind, allow me
to provide you my hospitality.
What a hobby he has.
He's always chasing after a bird.
I'm already used to it.
Aunt, let's hurry inside.
Wait.
You seem to be acting strangely.
Could it be that Second Brother is here?
Aunt, that's a really good guess.
Second Uncle came early in the morning.
He's been in a foul mood.
Didn't you see I was sitting outside?
I don't dare go inside.
I should get going.
Fifth Sister, come in.
Second Brother.
Let's go.
Oh, yes! Aunt, you just arrived.
You must not have had breakfast yet.
I... I'll go prepare breakfast for you.
Where is Xiao Jiu?
A few days ago, she was still
cooking in my Fox Den.
She has already done
many shameful things for Dong Hua's sake.
When she returned to
my manor 300 years ago
I had to hang her up and spank her twice
for her to become well-behaved.
If she is at your residence,
then keep a good eye on her.
Rest assured, Second Brother. I'll surely
keep her confined in Qing Qiu's Fox Den.
She won't be outside being a disgrace.
- The life debt to Dong Hua Dijun...
- Don't worry, Second Brother.
Qing Qiu will take on the debt
that Xiao Jiu owes to Dong Hua Dijun.
As her aunt, I'll repay it in her stead.
I absolutely won't allow Xiao Jiu
to form any new ideas for
that notion she's finally rid of.
This Dong Hua Dijun is an immortal
that sprung out of a crack in a rock.
One must not love him
or hold him in their heart.
He's not one to feel affection.
Good.
Why did you suddenly came
to the Far North?
The Water King's son
happened to turn one month old.
He sent an invitation to Qing Qiu.
Mother and Father are traveling.
I had nothing much to do,
so I came for a visit.
The Eastern Sea is in the east.
If you were returning to Qing Qiu,
you should be traveling in the east.
Oh, I forgot to mention...
Fourth Brother had me bring
two jars of wine from Zhe Yan's.
I came to deliver them along the way.
What trouble.
I'm going to take them to
the kitchen now.
Aunt, do you not need breakfast anymore?
I'm leaving.
These contain the peach blossom wine
Fourth Brother wanted.
By the way, Aunt, I heard just now that
you attended the Eastern Sea banquet.
I did.
It's said the Crown Prince
was there as well. Did you see him?
I did.
Back when the Crown Prince came to
the Far North to pacify the rebellion
I had the good fortune to deliver
a map of the Far North to His Highness.
I will never in my life forget
the Crown Prince's grace.
You were merely
a young child 300 years ago.
How could you remember so clearly?
To be honest, I love hearing others
speak of the Crown Prince.
Aunt, did you know that in
all the battles of the past 30,000 years
wherever the Crown Prince made
a stand, he mowed down all resistance?
Should you marry
the Crown Prince in the future
you must not forget to bring me with you.
I'm leaving now.
Take care to attend to the one inside.
Your Highness! Your Highness, slow down!
Your Highness!
Mother!
Mother, you lied.
You said yesterday that you were going to
return to the Celestial Palace with us.
I deserve to be punished.
You ordered me to defend Qing Qiu.
But I really could not stop
the Crown Prince from coming.
Please punish me as you will.
Lord Ye Hua is here too?
Father said you do not want
to return with us.
He's afraid you cannot adapt
to living in the Celestial Palace.
That isn't a problem.
Father and I will just
move here to live with you.
As long as Mother is present,
I can live anywhere.
You’re going to move here
to live with me?
Your father is coming as well?
Aunt, do not fret.
There is precedent.
Precedent?
It's said when Heavenly Lord
was still a crown prince
the former Heavenly Lord arranged for
his cousin to be his crown princess.
Heavenly Lord was displeased.
The former Heavenly Lord issued a decree
to have him confined in
his aunt's residence.
Who knew that after a month,
affection would grow.
They returned to the Celestial Palace
and it became a wonderful story.
Wonderful story?
Yes. It is in Lord Ye Hua's right
to stay here in Qing Qiu.
Nobody could rebuke him for it.
I actually think he came
to give me a hard time.
Did you anger Lord Ye Hua
at the Eastern Sea?
I broke up his relationship with
the princess of the Eastern Sea.
Then...
Lord Ye Hua is not present at
the moment. You can hide for a while.
He isn't here?
He left after leaving
the young prince with me.
Mother, I am a little hungry.
Did you save any food here?
No.
Where's Xiao Jiu?
With her here,
isn't there someone to cook?
After you left, she left as well to go
to the mortal realm to repay a debt.
She's left to repay a debt again?
Could it be Dong Hua Dijun?
Forget it.
Let's take A-Li to
the Mushroom Market for food.
Come.
Honored Lady! Honored Lady!
Your Ladyship, His Majesty is coming.
Your Majesty, this is Honored Lady Chen
who nearly died after falling into water.
She is almost fully recovered by now.
- Honored Lady Chen?
- Yes.
Your Majesty has not
called upon her much.
She is quite pitiful to have
suffered through an illness.
- It'll be her tonight.
- Yes.
Make preparations, Your Ladyship.
You'll be attending to
His Majesty tonight.
Attending to His Majesty?
Congratulations, Your Ladyship.
Did... Did he just say I will be
attending to His Majesty tonight?
Yes, Your Ladyship.
His Majesty will finally lie with you.
When I was an immortal, repaying
his kindness was always on my mind
but I did not know how
I was going to do so.
Now I have to lie with him right after
I've come to the mortal realm.
I'm truly startled.
I was trembling with fear that night,
waiting for the eunuch to pick me up.
I'd never imagined the day would come...
Greetings to Virtuous Consort
and Worthy Consort.
I heard that after you
started recovering from an illness
a plumed cockscomb flower
appeared on your forehead.
I've invited
Spiritual Master of Jade Purity
to make a judgment on this flower.
Master, you say this flower
on my forehead is a demonic flower?
That's right. It is clearly
a demonic flower!
Guards, confine
Honored Lady Chen in her room.
She is not to step foot out
of Handan Quarters without my permission.
It is a demonic flower?
Then let the matter rest.
Is Your Majesty not going to issue
an order to send her out of the palace?
I do not believe what
some Spiritual Master says.
I only find it troublesome.
I just won't call upon her from now on.
Step out.
Yes.
She's been let off lightly.
That lying, deceitful Spiritual Master.
He says the flower on my forehead
as an immortal is a demonic flower?
How ludicrous.
I've already been locked in
for seven days.
Don't tell me I won't be able to
see Dijun in my entire lifetime.
Why don't I enter Dijun's dream and
ask him what his wish is in this life?
This way, I'll get an idea
of how to repay him.
Dijun, I am sorry for this.
I came this time because I wholeheartedly
want to repay your kindness.
I hope you will tell me
what it is you truly want.
I will spare no effort
to fulfill your wish.
Do you have any wishes in this lifetime?
Who is speaking?
I am an immortal of the Nine Heavens.
I was passing by and
saw you were in a dream.
I'd like to ask why you are
wearing such an expression.
Is there a wish you cannot fulfill
or an infatuation you cannot attain?
A wish?
I do not want riches,
honor, or the world.
I merely seek to have the heart of one.
Can you give that to me, Immortal?
It is such a simple wish.
Could it be that even an immortal
cannot grant it?
Is... what you said true?
You truly want a sincere heart,
wholeheartedly devoted to you?
I am a ruler.
Naturally, I will not lie.
All right, I give you my promise.
Isn't Dijun...
an immortal made out of rock?
Why would he have worldly desires?
She has already done
many shameful things for Dong Hua's sake.
When she returned to
my manor 300 years ago
I had to hang her up and spank her twice
for her to become well-behaved.
If she is at your residence,
then keep a good eye on her.
A day in heaven is
a day in the mortal realm.
Xiao Jiu will be back
in two months at most.
Second Brother probably will not notice.
Xiao Jiu, Xiao Jiu... Hurry back soon.
Otherwise, even I won't be able
to save you this time.
Aunt.
Aunt, you're back.
How come Princess Feng Jiu isn't here?
It used to be the Little Princess
who picked fruits for Aunt.
She'll be back soon.
Aunt!
My mother is so young and beautiful.
Why do you have to make her sound so old?
When did you pick up a young child, Aunt?
Just yesterday.
So it is Aunt's young prince.
There are many fun and tasty things
in the Mushroom Market.
Would Your Highness like any?
Mother, I want this one.
Take it.
Aunt.
There's been an excellent harvest.
Why do you still look so miserable?
It's because it's a big harvest
that I'm unhappy.
I'll have to sell at low prices now.
There was a small harvest last year.
You all earned a lot.
The fruit looks pretty good.
You learned to pick fruit from
Xiao Jiu herself. You pick.
Then let's have half a basket from here.
Lord Ye Hua, you’re back.
Good timing. We're eating loquats for
lunch today. Would you like to join us?
A-Li is growing right now.
This is all you're feeding him?
Do you like to eat these?
Yes.
Where can we find meat and produce?
- Do you still want the loquats?
- Yes!
Look.
- He's so handsome!
- Yes.
Look, the young child calls
our queen Mother.
Yes, and he calls the man Father.
Aunt! Aunt, you're back!
These two fish are
a present for you, Aunt.
Take them home and stew them
to nourish your body.
Thank you.
She's been looking after
a child by herself.
She should indeed have some nourishment.
Go cook.
Aunt, you clearly know...
you clearly know I can't cook.
There's a first time for everything.
You could even survive
a trial of lightning bolts.
I believe in you.
Mother, I'm hungry.
Aunt, please spare me.
I am a tree spirit.
I am deathly afraid of fire.
I know, but I'm not telling you
to burn yourself like firewood.
A-Li is hungry now.
I...
I truly do not understand you.
Qing Qiu is clearly a land of immortals
but you manage it like the mortal realm.
Men till the fields and women knit.
There's no trace of magic anywhere.
If everything is done with magic,
then life would not be interesting.
They would be bored as well.
I'm thinking of creating
a battlefield for them sometime
so they can have some fun
fighting each other
so they don't get too bored.
That actually sounds quite interesting.
When the time comes, I'll lend you a few
Celestial generals to liven things up.
Subtitles by DramaFever