Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 52]
It's a promise then.
You can't marry anyone else.
I'll come and visit you
when I have the time.
When you're all grown up, I'll marry you.
Ye Hua, you loved to read
when you were a child.
Who would have expected you to be
the same as your mortal self?
Little man.
You're talking to me?
Who are you?
Do you not know me?
Your Highness, the Crown Prince
took the amnesia potion.
It's normal that he doesn't know you.
Don't be upset.
It isn't that.
I know that he doesn't remember me.
It's just that seeing him at this age
reminds me of the time
we spent together
in the Celestial Palace.
Back then, that mortal,
Su Su, didn't exist.
Nor was there Qing Qiu's Bai Qian.
I was the only one in the Nine Heavens
who could keep him company.
Indeed.
I've served Your Highness since then.
I remember that Prince Yang Cuo
made you the Crown Prince's playmate.
Back then, Your Highness was
still very playful.
You often teased the Crown Prince
until he frowned.
It was so cute.
Indeed.
Ye Hua has always been
very pretty since he was a child.
He didn't like to talk much,
nor was he lively.
I had to tease him for a long time
to get a reply from him.
I've been by his side since he was born.
He's my only kin.
I treat him wholeheartedly and
valued him more than my own life.
What are those other women
compared to me?
Young Master, you must be
tired from your studies.
Why don't you continue tomorrow?
Master.
Father.
You're studying hard again?
What good deeds have I done to get
such a self-motivated child?
Our Liu Family relies on you
to make our family proud.
Come here.
This is your older cousin, Su Jin.
She will be staying
in our manor for a few days.
Take her as your playmate.
Hey! Aren't you going to greet me?
Are you a mute?
There are books in the back.
You can go and read them.
Don't disturb me.
Why have you come home so late today?
You just started in the Imperial College
and there's so much homework?
Look at you. You're drenched.
What will you do if you get sick?
Seriously, Sixteenth.
He said that
he's been guarding Kunlun Mountain
but he didn't even
clean the wine cellar....
These men are all so lazy.
Who knew that the lazy Seventeenth
had changed after 70,000 years?
Master, you're here?
Look! Is this place tidied up well?
It's very clean.
Master, do you remember?
Back then, I made such a big fuss
over the break up with Li Jing.
Master was forced to leave
your meditation early.
It was right here that you drank with me.
Did you already know that
I was a girl then?
Since the moment you stepped
into the Grand Hall of Kunlun Mountain
I knew that you were Fox King
Bai Zhi's youngest daughter.
Why did you still take me
as your disciple?
Isn't it a rule in Kunlun Mountain
not to take female disciples?
Why do you think I took you in?
It was definitely because of
Zhe Yan, right?
Master is such an easygoing person.
You must have been scared of being
pestered by that old phoenix.
Master probably didn't know then
that taking me in as your female disciple
would be even more troublesome.
You even had to take
my godly ascension trial.
Speaking of which,
all I did then was cry.
I haven't even thanked Master properly.
Zhe Yan told me that
you pierced your heart
to feed me your blood
for 70,000 years.
Is that true?
Master is my benefactor.
If I have to sacrifice
my life for you, I will.
I think that it was totally worthwhile
to offer blood from my heart
to keep Master intact.
If I hadn't sacrificed my spirit to
seal the Bell of the East Emperor...
would you still be here
in Kunlun Mountain today?
Definitely.
I wanted to stay in
Kunlun Mountain forever.
Stay in Kunlun Mountain forever?
I don't mind if Master makes
fun of me about it
but when I broke up with Li Jing
I was too upset and I thought
that I'd just stay
in Kunlun Mountain forever.
I could keep Master company
and stay forever carefree
while learning Taoism. How nice.
As a woman, you have to
get married sooner or later.
Even if you wanted to stay,
your parents wouldn't have agreed.
Ye Hua wasn't around then
and I hadn't thought of being
with anyone forever.
Indeed...
Ye Hua wasn't around then.
Seventeenth.
Do you know why I worked unceasingly
for 70,000 years to repair my spirit?
I do.
Zhe Yan said that you would never
disappoint those you care about.
Back at Ruoshui Riverbank
Master told all the disciples of
Kunlun Mountain that you'd return.
We knew that you would.
You worked so hard for us.
I've never disappointed
those I cared about...
That's true.
I did it for the one I cared about.
I know that Master cares about all of us.
I remember when Master rescued me
from Grand Ziming Palace.
It was because you cared.
How nice.
Master has finally returned.
Yes, I've returned.
Seventeenth.
An honored guest has asked for you.
Come quickly!
An honored guest?
Master, do join us.
Master, come with us.
Look, how cute is he?
He does look quite lovely.
Where is the honored guest?
- Master!
Mother!
What brings you here?
Come here to greet my mentor,
High God Mo Yuan.
A-Li greets High God Mo Yuan.
Get up.
Thank you, High God.
I'm here on Father's behalf to
greet High God with Lord Dong Hua.
It's just that Lord Dong Hua has
lost his powers temporarily
so A-Li had to come here alone.
Your father is...
Crown Prince of the Nine Heavens, Ye Hua.
He's... he's that future husband of mine.
A-Li, your father is
my mentor's twin brother.
He's the son of the Heavenly Father.
His spirit sunk into a deep sleep
after a huge battle.
He turned into a golden lotus
and rested in this lotus pond.
Then due to a series of coincidences
he was born as Crown Prince Ye Hua.
Father is the younger brother
of Mother's mentor?
How should I address High God Mo Yuan?
Uncle? Or Grand Master?
Mother, this difference in hierarchy
seems to be quite huge.
Why don't we wait until
we can ask your father about it?
Who would have thought?
You're not married yet
and your child is already so grown up.
Seventeenth, you've really impressed me.
Exactly.
Seventeenth got ahead of us.
She's definitely the first
among us to have a child.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
Look at Senior.
He's still all alone by himself.
Don't you feel bad?
Master is also still single, isn't he?
Why would you single me out?
Don't frighten my Riceball.
Go and play now.
How adorable! Come here!
How cute. Look at his tiny face.
It's snowing.
Aren't you going to take a look?
Little nerd, I have a secret to tell you.
My parents told me that your father has
asked to have me marry you.
Ridiculous! I'll go and break
this engagement off right away!
No! I want to marry you!
You've been holding on
to this all the time.
Who gave it to you?
- Give it back to me!
- I won't!
- Give it back!
- Give it back to me!
- No!
Give it back to me!
I won't!
Give it back!
Young Master, what's wrong?
Give it back to me!
Ye Hua, come back here!
Young Mistress Su Jin, are you crazy?
Who is Ye Hua?
How dare you speak to
Young Master like this?
Even Master and Mistress have
to give in to Young Master's temper.
Why would you dare to touch his beads?
Whatever you do, you can't touch those.
They mean the world to Young Master.
Who gave them to him? Tell me!
I... I don't know.
I only know that
they're related to Qing Qiu.
Qing Qiu?
Do you know where it is?
Young Master has been searching
through ancient records for that place
but to no avail.
If you really know about it
tell him quickly.
He will be so happy.
I know about it. I definitely do.
Really?
Go and tell him now.
Young Master will be
very grateful to you.
No! I won't tell him!
I'll never tell him what Qing Qiu is!
Your Highness, does it hurt?
Get some rest, Your Highness.
You've been carving that
for two days now.
If you keep using your eyes
you might go blind.
No...
If I don't finish it soon,
it might be too late.
Xin Nu, look.
Do you think this wooden
figurine resembles that mortal, Su Su?
Your Highness...
I'm asking you.
Does it resemble her?
It's...
It's about two thirds similar now.
It has to be at least three quarters
similar to fool the Crown Prince.
Little Princess, since you returned
to the den
you haven't eaten or slept at all.
All you do is cry.
Are you trying to worry me sick?
What are you worried about?
Even my aunt doesn't care
about me anymore.
Little Princess,
Mi Gu watched you grow up.
You always have a say in
who you like and who you don't.
So what if you take
the throne as the Queen?
What does that have to do
with your affection for Lord Dong Hua?
You don't understand!
If I become the Queen,
I have to stay in Qing Qiu.
Who said that?
Am I not right?
Auntie can't be the Queen once
she marries Crown Prince Ye Hua.
She has to marry into the Nine Heavens.
Of course not.
Are you muddleheaded?
You're the muddleheaded one,
my Little Princess.
Why would Auntie
have to marry into the Nine Heavens?
Because Crown Prince Ye Hua
is the future Heavenly Lord.
He's the master of the world.
Hence, Auntie has to leave Qing Qiu to
marry into the Nine Heavens.
Because Auntie will be
the Heavenly Empress.
Exactly.
But who is Lord Dong Hua?
He was once the
God of Heaven and Earth.
But he's retired now.
He can go anywhere he wants,
or stay in the Heavens.
Who could hold him back?
Am I right?
That's true.
See?
Why would it matter if you become
the Queen of Qing Qiu?
It doesn't change anything.
I'd say that it would be better if
you were the Queen of Qing Qiu.
As the Queen of Qing Qiu
you'd have a lot more chances to
discuss matters in the Nine Heavens.
You just need to stand on one side
and Lord Dong Hua on the other.
You get to look at each other every day.
As time goes by, won't that
kindle some affection?
That's true.
In my opinion, you and Lord Dong Hua
just need some more time.
How long have you known him?
Didn't Lord Dong Hua fall in love
with you in the Mortal Realm?
If you get to spend more time together
how could Lord Ding Hua not fall for you?
Exactly!
Hurry up, Mi Gu! Waste no time!
Bring me the books of rites
for Qing Qiu's Queen.
I'm going to read them now.
That's my Little Princess.
Wait here. I'll get them from
the cellar for you.
Little Princess, you've been
reading all night.
Shouldn't you get some rest?
Auntie will marry the Crown Prince soon.
I can't waste any time.
The sooner I finish reading them,
the sooner I can take the throne.
The sooner I can attend
court sessions in the Nine Heavens.
This is it?
These are just a portion of the books.
The rest are the ancient teachings
of Qing Qiu.
Finish reading these first.
The others were all thrown
into the cellar by Auntie.
They are a bit damp.
I'll go and dry them off.
Star Lord.
I heard that Little Princess is soon
to become the Queen of Qing Qiu
so I've come to present
a small gift to you.
What gift is it?
I was going through some
ancient records of the Celestial Tribe
and I discovered something interesting
so I hurried over here to
hand it to Little Princess.
More ancient records?
This ancient record isn't
just any ancient record.
It's the record of Lord Dong Hua when
he was still the God of Heaven and Earth.
Some events recorded in here
might be of some help to you.
It's about Dong Hua?
[Removed his name from
the Rock of Three Incarnations.]
Are the records all true?
Definitely.
No wonder...
It's no wonder that even my aunt
persuaded me to give him up.
Are you using this record
to try to convince me too?
I think that Little Princess is entitled
to know the truth.
His Lordship isn't really
so cruel to you.
It's just that before you were born,
he had already made that decision.
It isn't that His Lordship hasn't
taken a liking to you.
His Lordship didn't take that
heavenly trial in the Mortal Realm
to experience the six
sufferings of the mortals
but to fulfill your wish
for a romance with him.
In the Celestial Palace, Lord Dong Hua is
tied down by his destiny.
He can't be with you.
However, in the Mortal Realm
he could defy destiny
in the name of taking on
a heavenly trial.
It might have only been a few years,
but His Lordship was true to you.
This is the truth that
I wish for you to know.
Lord Dong Hua...
He went to the Mortal Realm for me?
Exactly.
Therefore, before the Crown Prince went
to the Mortal Realm
for his heavenly trial
he'd already sent you to guard
Ruoshui and the Ghost Realm?
Indeed.
Mo Yuan has just returned and trouble is
already stirring in the Ghost Realm.
Is something going to happen soon?
Lord Dong Hua...
I don't wish to see you again.
Lord Dong Hua!
What's the matter?
You used a third of
your power on that leap.
It's too much for me.
The Star Lord was telling the truth?
You've lost your powers since
you returned from the Mortal Realm?
Exactly.
Why didn't you tell me?
What is so shocking about that?
How can I not be shocked?
You were so powerful.
What will you do if you encounter
danger without your powers?
What danger will I encounter
in the Celestial Palace?
I've lost my powers temporarily
for returning to the Celestial Realm
before the end
of my scheduled 60-year trial.
Not even I can defy
the will of Heaven, you see?
But I'll be all right in a year or two.
I've cleared things up with you
so you can go home now.
Lord Dong Hua...
You purposely avoided me
because our names aren't
on the Rock of Three Incarnations?
How do you know about
the Rock of Three Incarnations?
Did Zhe Yan or Mo Yuan tell you about it?
Or was it your father?
But he promised me that
he wouldn't breathe a word of it to you.
Neither.
The Star Lord brought me
the Celestial Tribe's ancient records.
They said that you gave up
the heavenly throne.
Is that true?
You ruined your own destined
marriage recorded on the rock?
Is there no way to fix it?
I don't believe that.
It doesn't matter if you don't.
The Rock of Three Incarnations
records all destined marriages.
My name won't be on it.
It isn't just you, no one
will be in a relationship with me.
I don't believe that...
Stop fooling around!
I don't believe that your name can't be
on the Rock of Three Incarnations.
Every tail of a nine-tailed fox can
turn into a magical artifact by will.
I'm going to carve your name
into the Rock of Three Incarnations.
There were ceaseless battles
in the realms then.
As the God of Heaven and Earth
Lord Dong Hua defined
the law of the immortals
as well as life and death
in all six realms.
In order to make himself invulnerable
he removed his own name from
the Rock of Three Incarnations.
The Rock of Three Incarnations
determines all marriages.
Anyone whose name isn't on it,
won't be in any relationships.
No matter how long Lord Dong Hua lives,
he will always be single.
It isn't that he is deprived
of all emotion.
It's just his name isn't on the rock.
Whatever relationships he encountered
he regarded them
as ill-fated romance.
Little Princess, do you understand
what an ill-fated romance is?
It's just like what you both
went through in the Mortal Realm.
The relationship between you
and Lord Dong Hua will never end well.
Lord Dong Hua...
Where is your name?
Where is it?
Bai Feng Jiu...
That's impossible...
That's impossible…
How can that be right?
It can't be!
How can it be...
Lord Dong Hua is the one I love!
Little Princess.
Heed my advice.
If you remain so stubborn and continue
to defy the will of Heaven...
it won't do you much good.
It won't do Lord Dong Hua
any good either.
Those years you shared
in the Mortal Realm
were but a few days in Heaven.
Yet that was enough to make
Lord Dong Hua lose his powers.
Although it's only temporary
and His Lordship will recover
in a year or two...
this serves as a warning to him.
If you insist on staying by his side
who knows how the two
of you will be punished?
Little Princess, it's not too late
to set things right.
Why?
[Bai Qian and Ye Hua]
[Bai Feng Jiu and Lord Wen Chang]
Why is it gone?
How did that happen?
Why?
How could it be? Dong Hua, tell me!
How can it be?
It can't be...
What happened to Little Princess?
Take her to Qing Qiu right away.
The pain of losing a tail
is unbearable for a nine-tailed fox.
You violated the regulations.
Ancient records of the Celestial Tribe
aren't allowed outside the Nine Heavens.
As the Star Lord,
you violated the regulations knowingly.
Go to Lord Pu Hua for
your punishment.
I willingly accept the punishment.
Mi Gu!
What is it now?
- She cut off her own tail.
- What?
The loss of a nine-tailed fox's tail
is like digging one's heart out!
Is it really that bad?
All right now, give her to me.
I'll take her to the Peach Tree Woods.
Don't follow me.
High God! High God Zhe Yan!
Fourth Uncle!
I'm so forgetful.
They have all gone to Kunlun Mountain.
Auntie!
You are...
Isn't this Seventeenth's niece?
Yes, this is our Little Princess.
I'm the minor deity, Mi Gu, who serves
in Auntie's Fox Den.
Our Little Princess... she broke her tail
and her fever won't go down.
She's still unconscious.
I couldn't find High God Zhe Yan,
so I came for Auntie in Kunlun Mountain.
Here.
Come with me.
Why aren't they here yet?
Don't worry. I've sent someone
to search for them.
She's awake.
Little Princess, are you awake?
Does it hurt badly?
Seventeenth!
Mu Gu!
- High God!
- What happened?
Wasn't she fine when
she returned from Kunlun Mountain?
It's because of Lord Dong Hua.
When is it not because of him
that Little Princess is wounded?
What does that mean?
When the Star Lord carried her back
to the Fox Den
he said that she had cut off her tail.
Fourth Brother, look at that child!
She really doesn't care about her life.
Think of a way to ease the pain quickly!
The pain of a broken tail could
easily kill her!
I already eased the pain.
Don't say another word.
Leave the room now.
What is Lord Dong Hua doing here?
Fifth Sister, speak politely
to Lord Dong Hua.
After all, this isn't his fault.
You know about the
Rock of Three Incarnations?
So?
Lord Dong Hua, you knew that
you couldn't have any relationships.
You should have rejected Xiao Jiu sooner.
The Nine-tailed Fox Clan is
one stubborn clan.
Once we decide on someone,
we never change our minds.
You meddled with her and
made her fall in love with you
but then you told her that
you can't be with her.
What play is this you're acting?
I'm sorry.
What good is an apology now?
Can you bear the pain of
her broken tail for her?
Seventeenth.
Lord Dong Hua has his reasons.
All right, I won't say another word.
All right, she's awake now.
She's just still a bit dazed.
You can take a look at her.
Auntie...
Who do you think I see?
Lord Dong Hua, whom you care for deeply.
Subtitles by DramaFever