Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 26]
What are you two doing?
Crown Prince has issued an order.
There will be a wedding in a few days.
Aside from the palace's people,
nobody else is to enter.
Impudence!
How dare you block my lady's way?
Consort Su Jin has long been bestowed
in marriage by Heavenly Lord.
She will be moving into Xiwu Palace
in less than half a month.
Are you two not afraid
of the consequences?
We are freshly returned
from the battlefield.
We have been used to
mindlessly drifting around the world.
We really do not know
the rules in the Nine Heavens.
If we have offended you two ladies,
please understand.
Not lady, but consort. Consort Su Jin.
It is of no matter. No wonder
the two of you look so new.
After I move into Xiwu Palace,
we'll all be familiar with each other.
- Farewell, Your Highness.
Be careful.
Thank you.
No, there was a wonderful
peach blossom scent around the lady.
It is the scent of my peach tree woods.
She must be tied to Bai Qian in some way.
I must make another trip
to the Celestial Palace.
Bi Fang!
A-Li.
Mother is leaving now.
Your Highness, Nai Nai has taken
the young prince to Consort Le Xu.
I understand.
Where is Your Highness going?
It is stifling inside.
I want to go out for a walk.
Would you like us to come with you?
No need. I am familiar with these paths.
I can go by myself.
Your Highness, do you really
not need us to come with you?
This lady hasn't held
the young prince even once.
She must not like to
interact with others.
She seems quite pitiful. I wonder
what disease she caught to end up blind.
- Your Highness.
Is Your Highness going to
the lotus pond again?
I, Ye Hua, ask all the gods
of the world to bear witness
in front of the Lakes of the Far East.
From this day forth,
I will be married to Su Su.
I will love her with all my heart
for all eternity
and never part from her
regardless of fortune or calamity.
Congratulations, Sir,
you are going to be a father.
Congratulations to you as well.
You are going to be a mother.
Are you really going to marry that woman?
Have you thought about it?
You used the events of the night
A-Li was born as justification
to replace all the maids
that Heavenly Lord granted you
and stationed many of your own soldiers
to guard Xiwu Palace.
It has already been wearing
on your father's nerves.
Your Highness, Your Highness!
The young prince won't stop crying.
He won't stop no matter what I do.
How can this be?
Wasn't he doing fine just now?
Why is he suddenly acting like this?
Is he hungry?
He was fed before we came over.
The young prince is normally
very obedient.
I don't know what is wrong today.
Be good.
Su Su, Su Su!
Su Su, where are you?
Ye Hua.
Su Su.
I am leaving now.
Don't look for me.
I will be fine on my own.
Take good care of A-Li for me.
I once dreamed I could hold his hand
and go with him to view the moon,
the stars, and the sea of clouds.
However, it seems I won't be able
to do any of that now.
Don't tell him his mother
is just an ordinary person.
The immortals of Heaven
don't seem to really like him.
Su Su, tell me where you are.
I'll come to you.
I am at Zhuxian Terrace.
Su Jin told me
if I jump off, I will be able to return
to where I should return to.
Ye Hua.
Let me go.
I will also let you go.
From now on, we won't
owe each other anything.
I will definitely marry you.
- From now on...
- No.
- I will be your eyes.
- Don't, Ye Hua.
Ye Hua!
Since we have made an oath
in front of the Lakes of the Far East
we are to be husband and wife
for all eternity.
You must not do me wrong
I have always held a clear distinction
between love and hate.
I can tolerate no wrong.
If you betray me...
What would you do?
If you betray me, those oaths
will become null and void.
I will leave you, never to see you again.
Si Yin.
There is such substantial activity
coming from Qing Cang all of a sudden.
It must be related to
the one who sealed him.
Dijun.
You already lost half of your powers
from saving Little Princess.
- I'm worried you--
- You are right to worry.
I need to go into seclusion
to recuperate.
While I am away...
write something for me
in the Book of Destiny.
Book of Destiny?
I control the fates of mortals.
I am powerless to do anything
about the fates of immortals.
After I come out of seclusion,
I will be going to the mortal realm.
What will you be doing there?
The Hong Luan Star will not
be ascendant in my destiny.
When I go to the mortal realm
you can write of a marriage
in your Book of Destiny.
She kept me company for so long
in the Celestial Palace.
Nevertheless, I should fulfill
her wish to stay with me.
If Heavenly Lord asks,
how should I reply?
Just say...
I am going to experience
the bitterness of life.
Father, you must not.
Celestials need the divine fungal grass
to purify their cultivation.
Otherwise, both you and Ye Hua
will lose control of your powers
and fall into a demonic state!
There is no time to worry about that now.
You must not,
even if there is no time!
Father is Heavenly Lord,
while Ye Hua is your successor.
If you both fall into a demonic state,
what will become of the Celestial Tribe?
Wait for us to get divine fungal grass
from the Eastern Sea.
Father, do not be impatient!
No, there is no time.
Sorry, Father.
Third Brother, what are you doing?
What do you think I am doing?
You know how much Father loves Ye Hua.
He will even risk his life for him!
Why would he fear turning demonic?
Don't delay anymore, Eldest Brother!
Come with me to get divine fungal grass.
Sister-in-law, you'll stay here.
Before we return, aside from
Medicine King, nobody is to come in.
All right.
Let's go!
Ye Hua.
Why must you treat me like this?
I have never sought to
have you only for myself.
Am I not even allowed to
merely stay by your side?
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Go quickly to Zichen Hall!
What's the matter?
His Highness... His Highness
jumped off Zhuxian Terrace!
It's unknown whether he's still alive!
What? What did you say?
Hurry! Go quickly, Your Highness.
Perhaps... you may still get to
see His Highness one last time.
Your Highness!
High God.
What has happened?
My lord has suffered critical injuries.
Heavenly Lord is waiting for
divine fungal grass in Zichen Hall
to transfer his own cultivation
to save my lord's life.
Critical injuries? Wasn't he
perfectly fine this morning?
- High God.
Quick, Medicine King, follow me.
Wait.
High God, what orders do you have?
Why don't you bring me inside?
Perhaps my medical expertise
may be of help.
Yes!
In this world, the one with the most
medical expertise must be you, High God.
Jia Yun, why don't you bring
the two of us inside?
All right, please follow me.
Your Highness may not enter.
Why am I not allowed inside?
Eldest Prince and Third Prince ordered me
not to allow entry to anyone
but Medicine King before they return.
But High God Zhe Yan...
Why was he allowed inside?
High God Zhe Yan's medical expertise
is known throughout the four seas.
By defying orders, I am risking my head
to allow High God Zhe Yan inside
to save the Crown Prince.
Your Highness cannot provide any help
for the Crown Prince's injuries.
Please do not make my task difficult.
Then tell me.
Ye Hua...
He is still alive.
Consort Le Xu.
High God Zhe Yan.
Your Highness, my medical skills are
incomparable to Zhe Yan's.
He was outside the hall by chance.
Why don't you allow him to take a look?
All right.
You may take a look at Ye Hua.
I will not be in your way.
Heavenly Lord is...
No need to explain.
I do not see anything.
I have long since sequestered myself
from the three realms
and am no longer confined to convention.
May I request that you all step out?
All right.
Your Highness, when High God Zhe Yan
retired from the three realms
he may have sealed his magical artifact
under Kunlun Mountain
but he still has his medical expertise.
Nobody else in this world
can compare to him.
Let us wait patiently.
I do not know what relationship
you have to Mo Yuan
for even your spirit
to be so similar to his.
If you are him,
then you had better live on.
Kunlun Mountain has already
waited for you for 70,000 years.
If you are not him,
then since you have a face just like his
then you should be like him
and persevere for
all the people of the world.
Ye Hua.
My good grandson.
High God Zhe Yan?
Was it my two unworthy sons who went to
the Peach Tree Woods to ask you to come?
How I came is not important.
Heavenly Lord, Ye Hua is in
no critical danger now.
However, whether he will wake up
will depend on his luck.
What?
What you mean is...
He will continue sleeping like this?
It is highly likely.
Well? Have you retrieved
the divine fungal grass?
Those four beasts possess half of
Heavenly Father's life cultivation.
Even Third Brother and I together
are unable to defeat them.
It's all right. It's all right.
Zhe Yan has been inside for
a whole night already.
There is surely hope for Ye Hua.
High God Zhe Yan is inside?
Yes, he has been inside the whole night.
- Father.
Thank you for your help, Zhe Yan.
It was only by chance.
I have told your father already.
The Crown Prince's life has been saved
but whether he can wake up
will depend on his luck.
You mean to say...
it's possible Ye Hua may not wake up?
It will depend on his will to live.
Summon anyone he cares about and
have them accompany him day and night.
This will be helpful in waking him.
That mortal is the only one
he constantly longs for.
That mortal has already lost her soul
at Zhuxian Terrace.
Mortal? Is it the lady who is blind?
Everyone, I have already done all I can.
- Farewell.
- Zhe Yan.
You have done a favor for
the Celestial Tribe by helping us today.
I will surely repay the favor one day.
I am already one unconcerned with
temporal affairs, and have no desires.
Naturally, I do not need any repayment.
I merely have been brought to
the Crown Prince by fate.
Bai Qian?
Fortunately, you are not in
any critical danger.
You only have some minor wounds.
Is there wine?
There is wine.
But first, you have to tell me
what happened.
Ever since you sealed away Qing Cang
your parents and brothers have been
searching for you like madmen.
Even I have not had
a good night's sleep for a while.
Your eyes, and the injuries all over
your body... What exactly happened?
What's the matter?
Did you do something shameful and are
afraid I'll tell your Fourth Brother?
I may have sealed away Qing Cang
but I did not gain any advantage.
He sealed my memories and powers
and left me on Mount Junji.
I underwent a trial.
Zhe Yan.
I remember you have a medicine.
When taken, one can forget the things
one does not wish to remember.
Am I right?
These past few years must have been
very depressing for you.
Whether to remember or to forget
is your own choice.
However, I must warn you in advance.
There is no way to undo the effects
of this medicine of mine.
Once you use it
the past events will truly be
of no more concern to you.
My mother often said
I am lucky in life.
I was born as an immortal.
I was already an immortal
without needing to cultivate.
But there is nothing
so convenient in this world.
Without experiencing a heavenly trial,
how can one ascend to high god?
In the years that flew by
I merely experienced a heavenly trial.
Since this trial has already passed
there are some things
that need not be remembered.
Ye Hua.
Open your eyes and
take a look, won't you?
This is your child.
He has just lost his mother.
If he loses his father as well,
how pitiful would he be?
Open your eyes, won't you?
How come things are suddenly like this?
He was subjected to
lightningbolts every day.
For the Crown Prince's seal
he endured 36 sacred blazes
and 9 holy lightning bolts.
This jump of his
was clearly to seek death.
If we had allowed him
to marry that mortal
at most, there would just be
one more side consort in Xiwu Palace.
It would not have been
as bad as losing his life.
That's enough.
It is my fault.
Father, I have been unfilial.
I raised a disappointing son.
In the end, he is still
the Celestial Tribe's Crown Prince
whom everyone believes in.
Ye Hua, you took this step
because I forced you to.
I thought after I forced her to her death
you would only be
in low spirits for a few days
but thereafter, you would still be
the Celestial Tribe's heir apparent
revered by the four seas.
However, I never expected...
you would actually place
such great importance on that woman.
Ye Hua...
Is he really not going to wake up?
I was incapable of curing him.
Perhaps there is still a chance.
What chance?
The Celestial Tribe has a sacred object
called the Soul-gathering Lamp.
It was created by Heavenly Father
during the time of the Great Flood.
The lamp can gather together
the parts of an immortal's spirit.
The Soul-gathering Lamp?
It is a sacred item of
the Celestial Tribe?
How come I have never heard of it?
This sacred object belongs to
the Su Jin Clan.
Su Jin?
I remember. I remember that lamp.
My mother did indeed say
this lamp can gather
an immortal's spirit!
Is this true?
Where is it now?
It was kept in my mother's possession
ever since I was young.
Later, when my entire clan perished
and was buried in the Sea of Innocence
I put it away for my mother
with the items buried with the dead.
It is in the Sea of Innocence!
Sea of Innocence?
It is where the Celestial Tribe
preserves the bodies of immortals.
Since it was buried with the dead
then it must be in
your mother's crystal coffin.
It's been 70,000 years
since she has passed away.
If we are to open her coffin now,
I'm afraid...
Heavenly Lord need not worry.
Since the lamp can save
the Celestial Tribe's heir apparent
the buried surely would not mind
being disturbed for the lamp's retrieval.
I'll send Tian Shu to take you
to retrieve the lamp.
Being disturbed by her own daughter
is better than by a stranger.
Yes, I'll go right now.
Mother, thank you
for giving me yet another chance.
This time, I definitely won't waste it.
I definitely won't.
Your Highness, have you gotten the lamp?
In my hands is the Soul-gathering Lamp.
Follow me quickly back to
the Celestial Palace.
Yes.
I have retrieved
my mother's burial possession
the Soul-gathering Lamp.
I hope Your Majesty will remember
everything I have done in the past
and remember what you once promised me.
Su Jin, you were once my side consort
and are also a descendant
of a meritorious subject.
Should you wish to marry again
I will grant you another
fine marriage arrangement.
Why must you be so attached to Ye Hua?
Please grant me my wish, Your Majesty.
All right, I promise you.
You brought us this lamp today.
If it really can save Ye Hua
I will definitely have you
married into Xiwu Palace.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Subtitles by DramaFever