Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 19]
Ye Hua!
You plotted to kill my son.
Today, I will have you
die by my Soul Slayer!
Attack!
Why do I feel so flustered tonight?
Ye Hua?
Is he asleep?
Ye Hua!
Your Highness!
Ye Hua? Ye Hua, wake up! Ye Hua!
- Ye Hua, hold on! Hold on!
- Ye Hua?
- Ye Hua, wake up! Wake up!
What's wrong, Ye Hua?
Ye Hua!
Ye Hua, wait for me!
Ye Hua! Ye Hua!
Ye Hua!
Who are you?
Where is Ye Hua?
Why would you know the crown prince?
Speak!
I don't know any crown prince.
I just want to find Ye Hua.
Where is Ye Hua?
Impudence.
Who are you to speak
the crown prince's given name?
Please calm your anger, Father.
Please calm down, Heavenly Lord.
Stop right there.
I did not tell you to rise.
You dare to rise?
Do you know what this place is?
This is the Celestial Palace.
Celestial Palace?
Who are you?
How dare you act atrociously
in the Celestial Palace?
Nobody can save you.
Even if it is Ye Hua, he wouldn't
have the courage to save you.
- Guards.
- Present.
Throw this mortal into
the Evil Sealing Pagoda.
- Yes.
- No, no!
- Go.
Please save me. Please save me!
You... You are Ye Hua's woman?
Ye Hua and I bowed to heaven and earth.
I am carrying his child in my womb.
Can you bring me to see him?
Bring me to him, please?
What did you say?
Stand up.
Come with me.
Kneel.
Your Highness.
She really is carrying
Ye Hua's child in her womb.
Are you certain?
Could there be a mistake?
Your Highness, you know very well
in the Celestial Palace,
aside from Medicine King
I am the only one who can
read a pulse most accurately.
Father.
She really is carrying Ye Hua's child.
It is still not known whether
Ye Hua is dead or alive.
Please save his only child.
Le Xu.
She and Ye Hua
have violated heaven's law.
You want me to spare her.
Wouldn't that be telling me
to bend the law?
She truly is carrying Ye Hua's child.
Or, why don't you punish her
after she gives birth to the child?
Or, I am willing to carry
the punishment in her place.
Father.
I did not teach my son well.
I am willing to suffer
the punishment for this mortal.
Please save Ye Hua's child.
Take this mortal to
the unoccupied Zhaohua Palace
and place a strict watch on her.
Thank you, Father.
Ye Hua! Ye Hua!
Ye Hua!
Let me out!
I want to be with Ye Hua!
I want to be with him!
Let me out!
Ye Hua! Don't die!
Ye Hua.
Ye Hua!
Medicine King, come quick.
Crown Prince is waking.
His Highness has survived this trial.
Medicine King, step out first.
I have to speak with Crown Prince.
- This...
- Go out.
Yes.
Third Uncle.
What went wrong?
What about Su Su?
Ye Hua, listen to me.
Three days ago, after you were
slashed by the Mermaid Clan's Soul Slayer
your wife in the mortal realm
dashed through your barrier.
What did you say?
Why?
She rushed through your barrier
and was found by Father.
Heavenly Lord... Heavenly Lord.
Ye Hua!
- Let go of me!
- Ye Hua!
- Let go.
- Listen to me!
If you want to save her,
then you better stay alive.
If you lose your life,
death will come to her shortly after!
She is still alive?
She is alive, she is still alive.
She is carrying your child.
You don't have to worry about her safety.
The Mermaid Clan has been
entirely annihilated.
Stay here a few days to recuperate
and then we'll return to
the Celestial Palace.
No.
We must not hurry back.
Don't you want to see her sooner?
From the moment
Heavenly Lord found out...
it was no longer possible to be with her.
Now the only way to save her life
is to make Heavenly Lord think
that she holds no importance to me.
What did you say?
On the first day of the war, he was
slashed by Mermaid Clan's Soul Slayer
and was nearly killed.
Third Prince was afraid news of this
would affect the war
so he had the news suppressed.
How is Crown Prince now?
According to Medicine King's diagnosis,
Crown Prince has barely saved his spirit.
Good.
You have been following by
Crown Prince's side.
How could you let him take such a risk
and nearly lose his life?
When the army returns
you will go to Lord Pu Hua
for punishment.
Yes.
Wait.
Your Majesty.
Lord of Numinous Treasure'
assembly invitations have been sent out.
Everyone will be coming to
the Celestial Palace.
I can only go to Chang Sea
a few days later.
Have Third Prince take good care of him.
Yes.
Your Highness.
I must see His Majesty.
I'm afraid even if the sky falls down,
His Majesty won't be coming here.
Your Highness,
Celestial Tribe's Crown Prince
nearly lost his life to
the Mermaid Clan at Chang Sea.
Regardless, Mermaid Clan is
a part of the Ghost Tribe.
If Celestial Tribe seeks blame
Ghost Tribe will be
in deadly danger again.
Back when Qing Cang was sealed away,
Ghost Tribe was not in deadly danger.
We won't be now either.
Impudence! How dare you speak
Ghost Lord's given name directly?
You are the impudent one.
Could it be that even after
70,000 years has passed
you still only have regard
for Qing Cang and not His Majesty?
Ghost Lord?
Who is the true master
of Grand Ziming Palace?
Please forgive us, Your Highness.
I can't be bothered with you.
Your Highness, this is an invitation
sent from the Celestial Palace.
Invitation?
Lord of Numinous Treasures of
the Realm of Supreme Purity
is holding an assembly.
This is the invitation for His Majesty.
You could have just sent someone.
You didn't have to come to
the mortal realm yourself.
Ever since the Mermaid Clan
was annihilated
the palace has been in turmoil.
The old subjects are afraid
the Celestial Tribe will think
the Mermaid Clan is
a part of the Ghost Tribe
and direct their anger at us.
They can't find you,
so they pester me all day long.
I had no choice
but to use the invitation to come ask you
when you will be returning
to the Ghost Realm.
I will go directly to
the Celestial Palace.
You are going to the assembly?
To discuss scriptures and Daoism?
When have I ever known
how to speak about scriptures?
And how would I know
how to discuss Daoism?
I am only going to offer a humble apology
and make amends to the Celestial Tribe.
No matter what reason you had
taking my military seal
was a huge offense.
Seeing as you and I are husband and wife
I will not punish you.
Return to the palace
to reflect on the past.
Your Majesty!
You cannot treat me in this way.
I am... carrying your child in my womb.
What did you say?
That night... I conceived your child.
How is that possible?
Why not?
Don't you want a child?
Your Majesty will be a father.
Aren't you happy?
I have been hoping for this day
for 70,000 years.
Never mind.
I'll return to the palace with you.
Medicine King, quick!
This...
- What happened?
- Quick, save him.
Your Highness.
Get out!
You are but my father's consort.
How dare you trespass into
the heir apparent's chambers?
Get out right now!
Please let me out. I want to see Ye Hua.
Tell me. Is Ye Hua still alive?
Is he still--
Ye Hua.
Don't die.
Ye Hua. I'm begging you, Ye Hua.
Say something, please.
Ye Hua?
Ye Hua, say something.
Ye Hua! Ye Hua!
Ye Hua!
What? Crown Prince kept
a woman in the mortal realm?
This matter must not be made known.
But he already has
an engagement with my aunt.
Why did he have to seek other women?
Your Highness, even
the mortal realm's emperor
has a harem of countless women
let alone the next Heavenly Lord.
Even if Crown Prince
doesn't seek them himself
he will still have many consorts later
to continue bearing a line of heirs
for the Celestial Tribe.
Nonsense. A line of heirs?
Qing Qiu has always been
one man and one wife.
Our line hasn't ended.
No, I have to find out.
It's locked?
Are you still alive?
I am Bai Feng Jiu of Qing Qiu.
Are you the woman that
Ye Hua had in the mortal realm?
You said Ye Hua?
Of course.
He is the Crown Prince.
Who doesn't know of him
in the Nine Heavens?
Is he still alive?
I don't know.
Did something happen to him?
Not even you know?
Ye Hua.
Wait, wait.
I still have things to ask you.
Don't cry yet.
Wait, wait!
Heavenly Lord won't allow us
to speak to the mortal
and won't allow us
to speak of this matter.
While Crown Prince is not around,
could he be thinking of--
You can't speak of it.
Have you forgotten the incident of
the Water King of North Sea?
Clearly, I should be feeling furious
on Aunt's behalf.
Why do I still feel a little sad?
This mortal is actually quite pitiful.
I'm not eating. I'm not eating!
I want to see Ye Hua.
Your Majesty, are you really
going to the Celestial Palace?
The Mermaid Clan was
a part of the Ghost Tribe.
Although they separated
from us for 70,000 years
they had severely injured
the Crown Prince this time.
It is difficult for me to escape blame.
I can make use of
Lord of Numinous Treasure's assembly
to go to the Celestial Palace
to apologize
to prevent the Ghost Tribe
from being further implicated.
I understand.
Your Majesty is doing so
for the sake of the Ghost Tribe.
But, these three days were the happiest
I've been in these 70,000 years.
I can't bear for you to leave.
Take good care of your health.
Shaman, how come she is feeling so unwell
so early in the pregnancy?
Ghost Queen is an immortal.
The child in her womb is of Ghost Tribe.
There will be times when
their essences conflict.
I think with more bed rest
she will naturally feel better
as the months go by.
That's good.
I'll have the Shaman stay
to keep you company.
No.
You haven't been to the Celestial Palace
ever since you took the throne.
Since you are going to an assembly
then as Ghost Queen,
I must stay by your side.
You are carrying
a child of the Ghost Tribe.
It already disagrees with
your immortal essence.
If you go to the Celestial Palace,
won't you feel even more unwell?
It does not bother me.
When women in the mortal realm
are pregnant
there will be times when
they feel unwell.
I am the Ghost Queen.
How would I be so delicate?
All right.
In the 49 days of the assembly,
Ghost Lord shall stay here.
If you have any requests,
please let me know.
Thank you.
I shall take my leave.
May I ask.
Do you know
where the winter lotus sent from
the Ghost Realm 70,000 years ago
is being kept now?
Winter lotus? It is in the lotus pond
next to the Zhaohua Palace.
- Can you take me there?
- Yes.
I'll be back soon.
I just feel a bit...
a bit unwell,
so I won't be going with you.
Stay here with her.
Didn't you say you would
surely save this child for me?
Why does my stomach constantly hurt?
Perhaps it is because
you have been living in the Ghost Realm
for too long as an immortal
and your body has many injuries,
so it isn't fit...
to conceive a child.
Not fit?
Then what am I carrying now?
Your Highness, I...
I... I can no longer feel
the young prince's heartbeat.
What did you say?
Your Highness, please calm down.
I am speaking the truth.
The young prince no longer
has any signs of being alive.
I think Your Highness should
return to the Ghost Realm.
I will give you a medicine,
and have the young prince...
Your Highness,
now that it has come to this
your own health is more important.
No.
I must save this child!
Didn't you see?
In these 70,000 years, His Majesty has
never treated me with such patience.
I must keep this child.
I must!
You are not allowed to tell anybody.
Do you hear me?
Otherwise, I will take your life.
Your entire clan's life!
I will definitely keep my mouth shut.
Where is that peach blossom fragrance
coming from? It is so familiar.
Ghost Lord?
Lord of Numinous Treasures.
It has been many millennia
since I last saw you.
Seeing your back just now,
I wasn't certain it was you.
Yes, it's been 70,000 years.
I remember the first time I met you
was at Kunlun Mountain.
Just now, I heard the palace maids say
you had just arrived.
How come you would be in the mood
to admire this lotus?
I came to see the winter lotus.
I'm afraid it had been in
the Ghost Realm for too long
and is not used to
the Celestial Realm's lotus pond.
I did not expect you to be
such an attentive person.
You would be so concerned about a lotus.
- Fire! Help put out the fire!
- Help! Fire!
- Someone! Help!
- Zhaohua Palace!
Quickly find someone to put out the fire.
There's still someone inside.
How come there is a fire?
It is my mount
who has caused this trouble.
Please forgive me, Lord.
You need not blame yourself too much.
- Is this lady hurt?
- I am not certain.
I'm taking her back to
Realm of Supreme Purity
and have my shaman take a look.
A-Yin.
Her? How come she is here?
No, it's impossible.
Your Majesty, it must be
a Celestial transformed. It must be.
They know Your Majesty
had a relationship to Si Yin
and must have transformed someone
into Si Yin's image to deceive you.
Shaman!
- Your Majesty.
- Quick, treat her injuries.
She was hurt by crimson hellfire. Quick!
Yes.
How is she?
She may be an immortal
but being injured by crimson hellfire
can be very troublesome.
Do you think she needs...
Your Majesty.
This is just a mortal.
What? Mortal?
Mortal?
Yes, Your Majesty.
She is not an immortal.
She is just a mortal woman.
Are you certain?
There is no sign of immortal essence.
She is indeed a mortal.
I was confused.
I actually failed to tell the difference
between immortal and mortal.
- Treat her injuries.
- Yes.
Rather than say her face
looks like Si Yin
I'd say she looks more like Bai Qian.
Fortunately, she is neither.
Come in.
Your Majesty, I have done wrong.
Do you know this is not
Ghost Realm's Grand Ziming Palace?
This is the Nine Heavens.
Why did you use crimson hellfire
in the Celestial Palace?
I passed by that abandoned palace
and felt that fragrance was so familiar,
so I followed the scent
and saw this woman locked in the chambers
and she was crying.
So...
So I wanted to help her out.
But the lock on the door
was millennium cold iron
and my powers could not break it.
So you used fire to burn it off?
Didn't Your Majesty say crimson hellfire
can exterminate all living things?
That is correct.
It can exterminate all living things.
That is why you are unable to
control the intensity of the fire.
You wanted to burn the lock
so naturally, the chamber
would burn as well.
Forget it.
I just hope Heavenly Lord
will not pursue this incident.
Where is Ye Hua?
What is this place?
Do you feel better?
Who are you?
I am Ghost Lord Li Jing.
Just now, it was my mount
who accidentally set the fire.
I am truly sorry.
So it was a fire set by you.
I thought they wanted to take my life.
They?
How old are you?
70,300 years old.
70,300 years old?
Sister, the peach blossom scent on you
smells so nice.
Why would a mortal be living in
the Celestial Palace?
I was seized by them.
Have you seen Ye Hua?
Where is he?
How is he?
Ye Hua?
Who are you to the Crown Prince?
I am Crown Prince Ye Hua's mother,
Consort Le Xu.
Greetings, Consort Le Xu.
No need to stand on ceremony, Ghost Lord.
I heard you saved someone of mine.
I came to express my thanks
and take my person back.
This lady belongs to your palace?
That is correct.
This lady violated some of heaven's law.
I had her locked in Zhaohua Palace
to reflect on her mistakes.
I did not expect a fire to break out
and for her to be saved by you.
Go and take her away.
Yes.
I take my leave now.
Farewell, Your Highness.
Your Majesty, that lady is with child.
- I'm afraid...
- With child?
Your Majesty, the Celestial Tribe has
always taken their laws seriously.
For them to keep a mortal in custody,
and one that is pregnant
this matter must not be simple.
I came on this trip to
the Celestial Palace to apologize.
As for other people,
there is nothing I can do.
Subtitles by DramaFever