Subtitles by DramaFever
[Ten Miles Of Peach Blossoms]
[Episode 56]
You didn't think of that?
My spirit might not be able to hurt you,
but this Double Crescent Halberd will!
Li Jing, I'll take your life!
What a good son.
I couldn't have left the
Bell of East Emperor so soon.
I owe you.
Once your life is given to me...
I'd add 100,000 years of cultivation.
This is the day I avenge myself!
Everyone has betrayed me!
Even you betrayed me!
The day my spirit returns to my body
is the day I break out of the bell
and torch the Eight Far Lands
with my crimson hellfire
to destroy Heaven and Earth!
It's the crimson hellfire!
The Ghost Lord has returned!
- The Ghost Lord has returned!
- The Ghost Lord has returned...
Jiu'er!
Your Lordship, what happened
to the Little Princess?
Quickly! Go to Kunlun Mountain
to see Mo Yuan!
- Yes!
- No, there's no time to lose!
Go to Qing Qiu!
Qing Qiu is the closest.
Bai Qian also knows how to
seal Qing Cang.
Yes.
Tian Shu, obey my command!
Present!
Auntie...
The Crown Prince is still
outside the Fox Den.
He hasn't moved an inch.
If you mention him again...
I'll turn you back into
your original form!
Why has the weather
suddenly changed, Mi Gu?
Auntie...
I don't know.
Is he still outside my den?
Yes, Auntie.
He's still out there
braving the sun and rain.
Lord Dong Hua...
If we both die here, not even
the heavens could tear us apart.
As long as I'm here, you won't die.
I'll use my spirit to pin him down.
But without my powers, I could only hold
him off for a while.
You have to go to your aunt
and fourth uncle immediately.
No, I won't leave.
Do not disobey!
I am not!
I told you that I would live
and die with you!
No one can!
I've used my life to protect all lives
and sacrificed my marriage.
If I insist on my relationship with you
it would surely cause ceaseless wars
within the four seas.
All shall be in misery.
Neither of us will meet a peaceful end.
Bai Feng Jiu, you're not
some common woman.
You're the future Queen of Qing Qiu!
Don't be absurd!
I'm not!
Dong Hua, if you live and so will I.
If you die, so will I.
If you could fend off Qing Cang
I'd never hold you back.
At most, I'd just kill myself if you die.
However, you're no match for him now.
You don't even have one tenth
of his powers.
I can't let you seek your own doom.
You can't go to him!
Step aside!
Not unless you kill me!
Today, I'll have all living beings
buried with me.
None of you can get away!
Jiu'er!
Jiu'er... Jiu'er!
Auntie, take a look at him.
Just one glance will do.
I can't take that step forward.
Star Lord of Destiny seeks
audience with Auntie!
There's trouble in Ruoshui Riverbank!
What did you say?
There was a weird sighting at the bell.
Lord Dong Hua said
only Auntie could seal Qing Cang.
Qing Cang broke the seal?
When I left, he was still sealed.
But it's just a matter of time now.
Mi Gu, send a message to Fourth Brother.
Get him to assist me in Ruoshui.
- Yes.
- Qian Qian...
Protect Lord Dong Hua!
Earth Deity!
Not even High God Mo Yuan
could defeat him.
We're just minor deities.
How can we tackle him?
I'm the Earth Deity of this area.
Even if I am no match for him
I still have to give it a try!
I'll risk my life to stand up to him!
- Qing Cang!
- Earth Deity!
I've been guarding you for 70,000 years!
Don't you dare dream of leaving
this place to harm anyone!
Earth Deity!
- Auntie...
- Step aside!
Si Yin, is that you?
Exactly! Qing Cang, it's me.
Who knew that I've only sealed you
for about 300 years
and you've broken out again?
I've been waiting for you and Mo Yuan!
It was you and your mentor
who had me trapped for 70,000 years.
I'll avenge myself today
and take both your lives!
How arrogant!
What magical artifact is this?
Let go of me!
You can't defeat Qing Cang
with your cultivation.
Leave him to me.
You've transferred all your cultivation
to my mentor so you can't defeat him!
Take good care of her.
Ye Hua!
Untie me!
He's seeking his own doom!
Don't panic, High God.
This magical artifact is really weird.
I can't undo it!
Get me Lord Dong Hua!
Lord Dong Hua has lost all his powers
so he's even worse than me.
Lord Dong Hua?
Little Princess?
Qing Cang, if you want to pick a fight
come out here!
Mo Yuan?
You've finally shown up.
Who are you?
You're not Mo Yuan!
I am the Crown Prince of
the Celestial Tribe, Ye Hua!
What?
Qing Cang broke free again?
Our Ghost Lord has returned!
Kill them all and the world will be ours!
Don't you dare act so arrogantly,
Ghost Tribe!
Fourth Brother!
- Ghost Lord!
- Ye Hua!
Young man, I lost to you today
but it's not a fair fight!
If I weren't still affected by
the severe injuries from 70,000 years ago
and damages to my spirit
by my treacherous son
I would never have been
defeated by you!
Ye Hua!
You were still defeated in the end.
Ye Hua lost so much of his cultivation,
but he still defeated Qing Cang?
- Ghost Lord!
- Ghost Lord...
Ye Hua!
Qing Cang, what have you done?
All I did was to make use
of the past 70,000 years
to connect my life to
the Bell of East Emperor.
Once I'm dead...
The Bell of East Emperor
will release the crimson hellfire.
it will have all of you killed
and buried with me!
Ye Hua!
- Ye Hua!
- Qian Qian!
- Qian Qian, you can't!
- Get back here, Ye Hua!
Ye Hua!
Get back here!
- Ye Hua!
- You can't go!
- Qian Qian!
Get back here, Ye Hua!
Ye Hua!
Ye Hua...
Don't cry.
I'm all right.
This injury isn't serious.
Ye Hua! Ye Hua...
Ye Hua...
Are you trying to swallow
your blood again?
You're still young.
It's all right to look weak.
Ye Hua...
Tell me the truth...
Are you going to die soon? Ye Hua...
Mo Yuan has returned.
Stay with him.
He... He'll take good care of you.
He would be better than me.
I'm not worried.
- No...
- Qian Qian...
Qian Qian...
All along, I...
I've loved only you.
Don't... Don't forget me.
Don't...
Don't... Don't forget me...
No... Ye Hua!
You can't die!
Hang in there, just hang in there!
I'll take you to my mentor.
He will be able to save you, Ye Hua...
Ye Hua...
Don't die!
I'm begging you!
You can't die.
You can't die...
If you die, I'll go to Zhe Yan
for that potion.
I'll forget you!
I'll live just fine all by myself!
I don't want to remember who you are.
Do you hear me?
That's good.
You...
Ye Hua...
Ye Hua!
No...
Ye Hua, open your eyes! Ye Hua!
Ye Hua!
Heavenly Lord!
Qing Cang triggered
the Bell of East Emperor
to cast crimson hellfire upon the realms.
The Crown Prince...
He used his spirit as
an offering to the bell.
What?
You said that the Crown Prince...
How could that happen?
Didn't Lord Dong Hua said that the seal
would only be broken every 70,000 years?
The Crown Prince seemed to
have known in advance.
Before he went to the Mortal Realm
for his heavenly trial
he had Tian Shu guard the bell.
Little did we know that
after he's left the Mortal Realm...
Le Xu! Le Xu!
Master, did you hear that bell chime?
It sounds so depressing
and comes from Ruoshui River.
That is the Bell of East Emperor...
Master!
Could it be that Qing Cang
is going to break free?
Master... you can't go!
- Send me there instead!
- It's all over now.
Someone has offered his spirit
to the Bell of East Emperor.
So what if the Bell of
East Emperor is triggered?
So what if the deities of all realms
are vanquished in flames?
At least, we'd still be together.
How could you leave me?
Ye Hua...
How could you leave me all on my own?
Qian Qian is very stubborn.
If this goes on, she might die.
What should we do?
I don't know.
First it was her mentor
and now her future husband.
Qian Qian is destined to
go through the loss of her loved ones.
Exactly.
She was going to marry Ye Hua.
What should she do now?
High God.
We're acting on the orders
of Heavenly Lord
to collect the Crown Prince's body.
Please let me know what we should do.
You should all head back.
I think she will sit here
holding on to your Crown Prince
for all eternity on Ruoshui Riverbank.
Auntie...
Auntie, please don't be
so hard on yourself?
The dead can't be revived, Auntie!
You still have me and your brothers.
You still have
the entire Qing Qiu, Auntie!
Auntie!
Auntie, don't behave like this.
You're scaring me.
Auntie!
How is she?
Your disciple is too emotional.
She can't be consoled.
Seventeenth.
Master, you're here?
You must have a way
to save Ye Hua, right?
You overcame the trial of
the Bell of East Emperor.
You must be able to save him.
Seventeen...
Get Ye Hua a coffin
so he can rest in peace.
Master, you can't make such a joke...
I can wait.
70,000 years or even hundreds of
thousands of years. I can wait for him.
Master...
He already breathed his last breath.
When you offered your spirit
to seal the bell
they also said that you were vanquished.
But I still managed to
wait until you returned.
Ye Hua will also return.
He will surely return...
Even if you are to wait for him...
You should let him rest comfortably.
You can't just keep sitting here.
Master, you're right.
Earlier... I promised Ye Hua...
I'd take him back to Qing Qiu
and lock him up in my Fox Den.
Then he could only look at me.
I'll take him back to Qing Qiu now.
Head back there first.
- What is going on?
- Auntie!
- What should we do now?
- Exactly.
This is...
Lord Dong Hua...
Go on.
- What now?
- How should we report back?
- Exactly...
What should we do now?
What are we to do?
Honorable deities, this is the home
to generations of Qing Qiu's rulers.
Auntie now rules one of Qing Qiu's
Five Far Lands as the Queen.
Although there aren't as many regulations
in Qiu Qing as in the Celestial Palace
the Queen's home is still
not to be entered freely.
This is...
What should we do?
What are we to do now?
We do know that Auntie is
the Queen of Qing Qiu
and that she is engaged
to the Crown Prince.
However...
The Crown Prince isn't just any immortal.
He is also the apparent heir
of the Nine Heavens!
Now that the Heavenly Lord has sent us
to bring him back, and yet Auntie...
Little Deity, this really
puts us in a dilemma!
- Exactly.
- Exactly!
Please try to talk Auntie around and
hand over His Highness's body to us.
When Auntie went in, she already said
that no one is to enter.
Please leave now.
This is...
Indeed...
We can't report back!
It seems that Auntie wouldn't
give His Highness to us.
It's already been ten days.
I think that we'd better
report back to the Celestial Palace.
This...
Auntie, A-Li is still in
the Celestial Palace.
Should we bring him back to Qing Qiu?
Do you not see that
I'm looking after Ye Hua?
I don't know how to talk you out of this.
High God.
Auntie has been behaving
like this all day and night.
What if she wears herself out?
I'll write you a prescription.
Make the decoction and
trick her into taking it
so that she could get some sleep first.
I'll get it done right away.
Su Jin.
As the guardian maid of the bell
you've failed in your duty to
alert the Celestial Palace in time.
Ye Hua had no choice but
to take on Qing Cang alone.
And he sacrificed his spirit
to seal the Bell of East Emperor!
Do you know what you have done?
I... I saw so many high gods there.
I didn't want to cause them any trouble.
My cultivation isn't of much use anyway.
For the sake of the Celestial Tribe
your clan still went ahead
without any hesitation
even if they knew that
they were to be sacrificed.
But you...
You're nothing like your parents.
I'm totally disappointed in you.
Heavenly Lord, I beg you to
spare me this once!
Please spare me this once, Heavenly Lord!
Guards!
Greetings to Heavenly Lord...
According to the celestial law,
banish Su Jin from the Nine Heavens!
She's never to be given
a celestial status for all eternity!
Take her away!
Yes...
High God Bai Qian is
of a prestigious status.
The deities I sent over
dare not offend her.
I wonder if Lord Dong Hua is willing
to deign yourself to visit Qing Qiu
and assist my two sons
in bringing Ye Hua back?
I was also at the battle of Ruoshui.
Back then...
Forget it.
Since Heavenly Lord said so
I'll accompany both princes there.
I'm going with you.
Lord Dong Hua is already
coming with us so you won't have to.
I'm going to take a look at that
Su Su or Bai Qian...
I'll see what we have to do
to make her return my son.
My poor son...
Is it ready?
I wonder if Zhe Yan's drug would work
and put Auntie to sleep all day.
I'm worried that should this continue
they might send celestial guards
to snatch the Crown Prince back.
Who knows?
Who broke my celestial shield?
Feng Jiu greets Lord Dong Hua,
Prince Yang Cuo
Prince Lian Song, and Consort Le Xu.
Could you inform her that
we're here to retrieve Ye Hua?
Yes, please wait here, Lord Dong Hua.
I'll inform Auntie right away.
Le Xu!
High God Bai Qian, I've come to you
with an unfavorable request.
Although I know of
your utter devotion to Ye Hua
the Heavenly Lord and his parents
haven't seen him since he passed away.
The Heavenly Lord favors
his eldest grandson greatly.
Upon hearing the bad news
he has been devastated.
It's been more than ten days.
And the old lord has yet to see
the corpse of his grandson.
It's hardly justifiable.
So...
You're all here to take Ye Hua away?
Indeed.
Ye Hua's parents have already
prepared a basalt crystal coffin.
They intend to take him back
to the Celestial Tribe's
sacred Sea of the Innocence
to be given offerings.
You can't take him away.
He promised to have me
take him to Qing Qiu.
Since I learned that
you were that mortal, Su Su
I've been so worried.
This still happened in the end.
What sins had Ye Hua committed
to have died twice for you?
When you were Su Su
he devoted his heart and soul to you.
He would even give up
being the Crown Prince.
As for your conflict with Su Jin
the Heavenly Lord made you
compensate her with your eyes
and three months of lightning torment
after you gave birth to A-Li.
You only gave her your eyes,
but Ye Hua took the torment for you.
When you jumped off the Zhuxian Terrace
Ye Hua jumped in after you.
But that was your trial for
godly ascension into high god.
What has that got to do with Ye Hua?
Ever since he met you,
he hasn't had one peaceful day.
He did so much for you
but what have you ever done for him?
You never did.
Yet you dare held on to him so defiantly!
Now that he's dead
you'd even hold on to his body!
I only have one question for you.
Bai Qian, who are you to do so?
That's enough.
My son slayed Qing Cang
and sacrificed his spirit
to the Bell of East Emperor to stop it
from engulfing the Nine Heavens.
He sacrificed himself for all lives
in Heaven and Earth.
The Heavenly Lord has made
his merits known to all.
Le Xu's opinion is
but that of a woman.
High God, please don't take it to heart.
However, it's indeed inappropriate
to keep my son's body with you.
Although my son is engaged to you
the wedding was never held.
It's somehow unjustifiable for you
to keep my son's body.
My son was the Crown Prince
of the Celestial Tribe.
We have regulations in the
Celestial Palace that can't be broken.
Please allow us to take him back
to be buried in the Sea of Innocence
on the 36th day.
High God, please grant us this wish.
Subtitles by DramaFever