Subtitles by DramaFever
[Ten Miles of Peach Blossoms]
[Episode 3]
You may all go.
- Yes.
You've woken up?
Do you know how long
you've been sleeping?
Ten whole days, and over an hour.
I slept for ten days?
That's right.
Leave us.
You drank all the wine in the palace.
Luckily, I was with you
and fed you the anti-hangover medicine
that only Grand Ziming Palace has.
Otherwise, the consequences would
have been too horrible to contemplate.
In the ten days I've been asleep,
how has Ninth Disciple been?
He...
flung himself into a pillar three times
slit his wrists twice
and I think he's also thrown himself
into the lake twice.
I heard he's recently
started to refuse to eat.
What did you say?
What is so bad about my father?
He is the Ghost Lord
who dominates the world.
Why does he not appeal
to your fellow disciple?
Of course.
Taking someone as a father
is no trivial matter.
Can you take me to see Ninth Disciple?
What's the rush? Let me finish.
The adoption ceremony is set for
the third day of next month.
Whether or not your Ninth Disciple agrees
the invitations have
already been sent out.
Adoption?
That means before the ceremony,
nobody can see him.
- Not even you?
- Of course I can.
But you can't.
Li Jing.
Preposterous!
You dare to touch Father's people?
Why not?
Even if you were
to die somewhere one day
I wouldn't care.
But you cannot have this person.
He is but an immortal.
He is nothing but bait.
If you want to coerce Mo Yuan,
Ling Yu is enough.
Leave this one for me.
If it weren't because Father
took pity on your mother
he would already have driven you
out of the palace.
Now you're having a good time
fooling around.
Fooling around?
I say he is clearly a female disciple
that Mo Yuan is hiding in Kunlun Mountain
disguised as a man.
Brother, you do not need
to criticize me so.
The more I fool around,
the more delighted you are.
Isn't that so?
Very well.
Go and have fun.
When we break off our alliance
with the Celestial Tribe...
I'll see what you will do then.
Beautiful woman.
You are a woman, aren't you?
I have actually already seen through
your male disguise enchantment.
Tell me. Are you a woman?
Could he really have
seen through my magic?
You... Don't you speak such nonsense.
Tell the truth.
You can really see?
The people at Kunlun Mountain
didn't see through it.
All right, so it's clear now.
You really are a woman.
The truth was so easily
shaken out of you.
Why are you disguised as a man
here at Grand Ziming Palace?
Are you afraid my father
will force you into his harem?
Do not worry.
My father is using you two
to lure Mo Yuan here.
However, your fellow disciple
is quite stubborn.
He wasn't as comfortable as you,
asleep for ten days.
I heard he has recently
taken up the idea of killing himself.
Is what you're saying the truth?
The invitations have
already been sent out.
It is all to humiliate Kunlun Mountain.
If Mo Yuan comes and rescues you two,
things would still be manageable.
If even Mo Yuan cannot save you two...
I'm afraid you and your fellow disciple
will have your skin torn off
and tendons pulled out
to taunt the Celestial Tribe.
There is nobody in this world
who can defeat my master.
You have such confidence?
My master is the God of War.
All right, all right.
Your master is most formidable.
However, in my opinion
it's best not to wage war.
After all, when both tribes
break into war
the world will be plunged into
misery and suffering.
How about this?
Wait quietly for a few days.
I have already made arrangements.
You'll be sent out of the palace
on the third of next month. How is that?
You're helping me escape?
You don't trust me?
Why are you helping me?
I find I get along well with you.
Even if you don't take me as a friend,
I will take you as a friend.
All right, regardless of how
Celestial Tribe and Ghost Tribe end up
since fate brought us together,
we will be friends.
Sit down.
Write down what you want to say
to your fellow disciple.
I will bring it to him tonight
so he can be reassured.
All right.
By the way, there is something
I want to ask you.
My sister, Yan Zhi,
has taken a liking to you.
Why don't I send her away with you?
You can help me take care of her
for the rest of her life. How is that?
I... I can't, I can't!
I am also a woman.
Don't make such a joke.
Then tell me how to explain to her
that you are also a woman.
Don't tell her.
All right. Since you are a woman,
I won't lead my sister amiss either.
Write.
I am the second prince of Ghost Realm.
This is a letter from
your fellow disciple.
Si Yin?
Read it quickly so I can take it away.
Your Highness, how come you suddenly
took a liking to viewing the lotuses?
You come to the lotus pond
several times a day.
Isn't it nice to relax once in a while?
Your Highness!
Li Jing?
Has it been arranged?
By sending out invitations far and wide
and humiliating Kunlun Mountain
Father is firmly resolved to rebel.
If we let Si Yin go free,
it will be difficult to see him again.
As princess of Ghost Realm, I cannot
be with someone from Celestial Tribe.
Much less have the right to say
what my heart wants.
You are right.
It is impossible for
those of Celestial Tribe
to be with those of Grand Ziming Palace.
Master, Master! Come save us quickly!
No, no, you can't come.
If you come, you will
fall for Ghost Lord's plot.
You are in Ghost Realm?
You had too much to drink again?
A-Yin, I'll tell you a secret.
Do you want to hear it?
How much did you drink?
It seems you really do think of me
as a friend. Go ahead.
A-Yin.
I like you.
You're taking off my clothes again?
Since you've tacitly consented,
why must you act so shyly?
When did I tacitly consent?
You like me?
You're drunk and acting crazy.
[Invitation]
Qing Cang actually dared to
openly dishonor Kunlun Mountain.
With Mo Yuan's temper,
he would never tolerate it.
It seems Qing Cang is certain to rebel.
Investigate the situation at
Grand Ziming Palace in secret
especially Qing Cang's
princes and princess.
Yes.
This is intolerable!
He dared to kidnap
Kunlun Mountain's disciples
and send out invitations
to humiliate Master!
That's right!
The Ghost Realm has gone too far!
Second Disciple.
With Master in seclusion and
Senior off searching in the mortal realm
only you are in a position
to make decisions.
Just say the word, and all of us will
storm into Ghost Realm with you
to rescue Ninth Disciple
and Seventeenth Disciple.
- Yes!
We must not act so rashly.
- Master.
All rise.
- Yes.
Master, Ninth and Seventeenth
have been captured by Qing Cang.
The Ghost Lord even spread invitations
forcing Ninth Disciple
to become his godson
mocking Kunlun Mountain in such a manner.
I heard just now.
We were just discussing plans to go to
Grand Ziming Palace on a rescue mission.
I alone am enough.
After all, the Ghost Tribe has yet to
declare war on the Celestial Tribe.
It is inappropriate to involve
so many people.
Quickly summon Die Feng back.
When I return, seal off
the mountain immediately.
Nobody else is allowed to come or go
from Kunlun Mountain.
- Yes.
You...
How come I slept in your bed?
You had too much to drink last night.
You came over here
in the middle of the night
and said you like me.
What did you say?
I... I'm telling you
it was not intentional.
I really do think of you as a friend.
Those from Ghost Tribe cannot
be with those of Celestial Tribe.
Yes, it was not intentional on your part.
You...
What is the meaning of this?
Your demeanor is clearly saying
I took advantage of you.
You nearly tore off
my clothes last night.
That's a lie!
You've nearly torn off
my clothes twice now.
You're saying I'm lying?
I...
I really took them off?
Immortal.
Your Highness.
Have you seen my Second Brother?
Second Prince?
He was drunk last night.
He slept in my room for the night.
And then?
And then...
And then he left.
The past few days, Li Jing and I have
made arrangements to send you two away.
Thank you, Your Highness.
There's no need to thank me.
We of Ghost Tribe have always
done things for our own purposes.
I...
Never mind. Take your time
enjoying the view.
It's a shame
I am also a woman.
What can I do to not let down
your heartfelt affections?
What is wrong with me?
Have I really fallen for her?
Master.
Master!
I knew you would come to rescue us!
Are you all right?
We will take revenge on another day.
Let's save Ninth Disciple first.
Master.
- Master.
- Ninth!
- I have been unfilial.
I have caused trouble for you.
You are my disciple.
There is no need to say such words.
Let's go quickly.
Who dares trespass into
Grand Ziming Palace?
Attack!
Master, let's go!
Report to Father immediately.
- Yes.
Mo Yuan.
I truly cannot believe
you would violate the treaty between
our two tribes for your two disciples
and slaughter my men at
Grand Ziming Palace.
Qing Cang, how can you call yourself
the lord of Ghost Realm?
This is nothing but an ambush.
You went so far as to use
such despicable means
as kidnapping my disciples.
If what you want is a duel,
then let's fight.
That's exactly what I want.
Li Jing!
Run! He has the Bell of East Emperor!
Master.
The heavenly trial!
Let's go.
Scum!
Kill me.
Do you think I won't kill you?
Of course I know you want to kill me.
And naturally, I also know why
you won't kill me.
Treacherous spawn.
Don't you forget who gave you
the utmost glory and splendor!
Guards!
Lock up this treacherous spawn.
Without my permission,
nobody is to let him out!
- Yes.
- Master!
- Seal the mountain.
- Yes.
Zi Lan, here.
Everybody else come with me!
- Yes!
Master.
Master!
Master! Let me out, Master!
Master, let me out!
Master!
I should be the one suffering
these lightning bolts! Master!
Let me out!
Master!
Master! Master!
This is my heavenly trial, Master!
Master.
Master! Master!
- Master!
- Seventeenth, you're awake?
Master!
Master has gone into seclusion.
- Master.
- Come.
Master has gone into seclusion?
Here.
Master endured three lightning bolts
for you yesterday.
Seventeenth, you should study and develop
your skills properly from now on.
It wouldn't be right to have Master face
another trial for you
for your next ascension.
Lightning bolts...
How is Master right now?
Before Master went to
Ghost Realm to save you two
he'd already ordered us
to seal the mountain.
I had thought something had happened.
It seems Master was already prepared
to endure lightning bolts for you
but afraid Ghost Tribe
would seek revenge
and we'd be no match for them
with him in seclusion.
Seventeenth! Seventeenth!
Where are you going?
Master, are you heavily injured?
Master, I have been unfilial.
I have caused you harm.
I've learned from you for 20,000 years
but I can't even predict
the day of my heavenly trial.
Master, come out soon!
I'll stew myself in a soup for you.
Master.
His injuries are severe.
If you keep crying like this
his spiritual balance will be
thrown into disorder.
What a dumb fox.
Greetings, Princess.
Have you seen Second Prince?
Second Prince has been imprisoned.
Why?
Because of the two Celestials.
Second Prince.
Second Brother, why don't you
hide out in the mortal realm for now?
Come back when Father's anger
has dissipated.
All right.
I will wander about at leisure.
You do not need to worry about me.
As for you, make sure not to
admit that you freed me.
Second Brother, don't worry.
Even if Father found out,
he wouldn't do anything to me.
Oh, yes.
If you see Si Yin,
send him my regards.
Second Prince, are we going to
the Yijing Gardens that we frequent?
No.
We are going to Kunlun Mountain.
Kunlun Mountain?
That is Celestial Tribe's sacred land!
Seventeenth.
I have never seen you so diligent
in the past 20,000 years.
Now that the heavenly trial is past,
you know to work on self-cultivation.
You came at the right time, Senior.
I have something to ask you.
Look here.
"When the East Emperor is
brought forth, all shall perish"
"and destruction will
devour the world."
Is it saying the Bell of East Emperor
is a top magical artifact
and one of the finest weapons?
It was created by Master and is one of
the godly weapons of the Celestial Realm?
Seventeenth, if you were
so diligent before
you wouldn't have needed Master
to suffer the trial for you.
Run! He has the Bell of East Emperor!
Senior, there is a guest here for Si Yin.
I am Bai Zhen, fourth son of
Fox King of Qing Qiu.
Fourth Brother!
Fourth Brother.
This is wonderful!
I had been with Zhe Yan and the others
ever since I was young
so I have gotten used to
calling him Fourth Brother.
Fourth Brother, this is
Mo Yuan's senior disciple
Water King of West Sea's
second son, Die Feng.
The environment at Kunlun Mountain
is indeed very nice.
No wonder Zhe Yan wanted to
send you here to learn.
Look at how our little Si Yin has grown.
He looks like an elegant and
outstanding high immortal now.
Why are you crying?
It's all my fault.
I had Master suffer
the heavenly trial for me.
No wonder your aura feels different.
You have actually ascended.
Your master really does
treat you very well.
Not many can withstand a heavenly trial.
You are family. I'll let you two talk.
I'll have the kitchen cook more today.
No need to go to that trouble.
I am just passing by and paying a visit
to Si Yin who has gone through a trial.
I won't be staying long.
All the more reason for me to
take my leave. Enjoy your time.
Fourth Brother, come.
You just got here and you already need
to leave. Why are you in such a hurry?
It has to do with the Ghost Realm.
Qing Cang?
Yes, it is because of Qing Cang.
Speaking of which, why didn't you
stay at Kunlun Mountain?
What did you go to Ghost Realm for?
I heard Second Sister-in-law
was about to give birth.
I wanted to take a look.
You, honestly.
You sure are the Fox King's
youngest daughter.
Just a quick trip out and
you've caused great chaos.
Because of Mo Yuan and Qing Cang's duel
at Grand Ziming Palace
Heavenly Lord has been very concerned
and has summoned Zhe Yan
to discuss how to subdue Ghost Realm.
I came along to visit you here.
Are they going to subdue Ghost Realm?
Is Qing Cang really
raising an armed rebellion?
It is just a matter of time.
You are Mo Yuan's most junior disciple.
You probably won't be in any position
to step onto the battlefield.
Once my master, always my mentor.
If Master is really going to
lead an army to war
I definitely will not run from it.
On the day Heavenly Father's spirit
returned to chaos
I had the weapon, Fuxi Zither,
sealed under Kunlun Mountain.
Even if I have the mind to
lend my assistance in this war
I'm afraid I would be
powerless to kill the enemy.
I understand.
Go to Kunlun Mountain.
Yes.
On the day Qing Cang is defeated
I will send someone to deliver
the peach blossom wine I brew myself
to congratulate you.
Thank you, Zhe Yan.
Farewell.
Most of the ancient gods
have withered away.
Only a few able ones are left
who now shun the world.
Yet, they cannot be used.
If you want to handle a moment of danger,
Mo Yuan is sufficiently capable.
However, if you want to preserve
the continued peace of the world
why don't you instead choose
a new and obedient Ghost Lord
and choose the right time
to replace Qing Cang?
Do you have a choice in mind, Dijun?
Heavenly Lord.
Ghost Realm's eldest prince, Li Yuan,
views Celestial Tribe with animosity.
Second prince, Li Jing,
has not amounted to anything
losing himself in women all day.
The rumor is that in order to
strengthen his own power
the eldest prince has been bullying
the second prince.
There is discord between father and son,
and fighting among henchmen.
That is the current situation
in Grand Ziming Palace.
Father, what Dijun just said was right.
If we choose the right moment
and help Li Jing into power
as Ghost Lord
it is indeed a way
to ensure long-lasting peace.
Yes.
The less accomplished he is,
the easier to control.
Fifth Sister, I'll be leaving now.
Fourth Brother, what is
the name of my little niece?
Feng Jiu, Bai Feng Jiu.
Feng Jiu?
Like the flight of a phoenix
for nine days.
It sounds like a magnificent name.
Your interpretation is quite nice.
I just wonder if such a name
will negatively affect her marriage.
Has Mother divined her future?
She was just born. Why are you
worried about her marriage?
Our Bai family should be
most worried about you.
Quickly finish your studies and
return home so we can find you a husband
so Mother won't nag at me
all the time to find a wife.
You go get married first.
You always use me to misdirect them.
All right, I really have to go now.
Fifth Sister, remember this.
As a disciple of Kunlun Mountain
if you want to follow Mo Yuan into battle
we would be in no position to oppose.
Mother and Father
absolutely wouldn't stop you.
It would be your obligation
as a disciple.
However, you need to remember
you also have four older brothers.
No matter what happens,
don't try to face it by yourself.
I know.
A-Yin, I have come.
I've heard the divine energy
at Kunlun Mountain
is most incompatible with our physiques.
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid your life essence
will be harmed by the divine energy.
Is it that powerful?
I would like to see for myself.
Your Highness!
You have followed me
since you were a child.
Have you ever seen me
so serious about anyone else?
I just want to see her.
Wait for me at the foot of the mountain.
Don't follow me.
Who trespasses on Kunlun Mountain?
Thank you for your assistance.
I am looking for A-Yin.
Seventeenth?
Who are you?
A-Yin calls me Brother.
Brother?
All right, you wouldn't dare lie
at Kunlun Mountain anyway.
Follow me.
Wait.
What are you doing?
When on Celestial Tribe's sacred land
it would be inappropriate
to be so unkempt.
That would be disrespectful
to God Mo Yuan.
That sounds appropriate.
Follow me.
Second Prince?
A-Yin!
Thank you for helping me escape
from Grand Ziming Palace that day.
Did your father give you
a hard time for that?
How come your face is injured?
I am fine.
A-Yin, I understand now.
I came to see you
so we can be with each other.
What did you say?
I am willing to give up
my status and identity.
I only ask to be able to be by your side.
I...
But...
But I am a disciple of Kunlun Mountain.
I saw you seemed to get along well
with your wives in Qin Hall.
You aren't lacking in women.
I knew it.
I knew I would frighten you.
But listen to me.
Ever since you left Grand Ziming Palace
from the day Father had me
imprisoned in the dungeons
I thought of you day and night.
I know my heart will not
have another from now on.
Subtitles by DramaFever