Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 32]
Qing Qiu is clearly a land of immortals,
but you've made it like the mortal realm.
Men till the fields and women knit.
There's no trace of magic anywhere.
If everything is done with magic,
then life would not be interesting.
Everyone would get bored.
I'm even thinking of creating
a battlefield for them sometime
so they can have some fun
fighting each other
so they don't get too bored.
That actually sounds quite interesting.
When the time comes, I'll lend you a few
Celestial generals to liven things up.
I'm hurt!
I told you I can't cook, Aunt.
Looks like we'll just have to
forget about this meal.
We'll be fine even if we don't eat.
What about Riceball then?
Mi Gu, hurry to the mortal realm
and drag Feng Jiu back here.
Say that something big
has happened at Qing Qiu.
But I can't find her, Aunt.
Then post a notice at
the entrance of the Fox Den
and say that we need a cook right now.
All right, I'll go right away.
That's settled then.
You can at least make a fire
and burn some firewood.
Add some more wood.
Your first wife must have had
amazing culinary skill
to have taught you to cook so well.
Wait.
His wife has already died.
Wouldn't mentioning her
be reopening an old wound of his?
She was like you.
She could only tend the fire
and burn wood while I cooked.
I don't know how she survived
on Mount Junji before she met me.
Why aren't you speaking?
I'm afraid you're sad.
I don't know what to say.
Su Su.
See? You're terribly heartbroken.
You've even called me by the wrong name.
Have you been to the Far East?
Far East?
I used to go to the Far East
with Sixteenth Disciple to play around.
Has the Crown Prince found some clues
and guessed that I am Si Yin?
Is that why he's using Little Riceball
as an excuse to stay at the Fox Den?
Does he want to recover Master's body?
Why are you looking at me like that?
You look guilty.
N... No, I'm not.
You're almost done cooking.
Although I don't know how it tastes yet,
you do look quite like a cook.
Forget about it for now.
I don't believe that
he can figure out something that's been
concealed for 70,000 years.
If you keep feeding me,
I'll turn into a ball.
How nice would that be?
I wouldn't need to carry you
as I leap across clouds
back to the Celestial Palace.
I'll just need to roll you up and
roll you back to your Qingyun Hall.
Father is mean!
Now you have someone to run to.
It's all right.
Qian Qian, here.
You need more nourishment.
A-Li, here.
Uncle Mi Gu, you need
more nourishment.
Qian Qian, clear out a study for me
to handle official documents.
You need to handle official affairs?
I'm going to stay here for a few days.
Mi Gu.
Go tidy up Fourth Brother's old room.
All right, I'll get to it right now.
Mi Gu, come here.
Aunt.
Are they going to sleep?
They're asleep now. The young prince
falls asleep come nightfall.
The Crown Prince takes good care of him.
He does everything himself.
When are they leaving?
He didn't say.
Didn't you say His Highness
is here to settle a debt?
- I'm afraid...
- Afraid of what?
I've heard
the Nine Heavens has been searching for
Mo Yuan's whereabouts for 70,000 years.
His Highness must not be trusted, Aunt.
You're normally not very clever
but you're thinking
the same thing I am today.
I'll be going now.
Qian Qian.
Ye Hua? You're not sleeping yet?
A-Li has gone to sleep, so I've come
to find you for a game of chess.
Chess?
You're in the mood to play?
Over these years, other than the days
I have been guarding the Chang Sea
I have not stopped searching
for Seventeenth.
Yet, I have not found any clues.
I'm afraid the lookout is grim.
I am the senior disciple,
but I have failed in my duty.
I couldn't even look after
a junior disciple.
I feel guilty towards Master.
Do not say that, Senior.
Not being able to look after Seventeenth
and losing him
is the fault of all of us disciples.
Never mind. It is rare for us to meet.
Let's not speak of
these upsetting matters.
By the way, Sixteenth, are you going
back to the mortal realm for experience?
I'll be honest with you, Senior.
In these 70,000 years,
I said I was gaining experience
but I have been searching for
Seventeenth's whereabouts.
I intended to continue my search
but I changed my mind after
encountering the Ghost Lord yesterday.
Kunlun Mountain was worshiped
by all immortals in the past.
Yet, it has now fallen to the extent
that not a soul is in sight.
Since I have not been able to
find Seventeenth even in 70,000 years
then why don't I return
to Kunlun Mountain
and look after Kunlun Mountain
in Master's stead?
Do you still remember the words
Master said before he left?
I am the same as Seventeenth.
We both believe in what Master said.
Since he has told us to wait for him,
then he will surely return!
Every day that Seventeenth is not found,
I will continue searching for him.
Then I shall return
to Kunlun Mountain first
and patiently await your good news.
Who are you looking for?
Aunt, this is Crown Prince's
civil officer, Star Lord Jia Yun.
This is the Crown Prince's
military officer, Star Lord Tian Shu.
Aunt.
Aunt, His Highness gave orders yesterday
that official reports are
to be sent here from now on.
Sent here?
Rest assured, Aunt.
I'll only be here once a day
in the morning
to collect the ones
finished from yesterday
and deliver the ones
awaiting instruction.
And you...
Rest assured, Aunt.
I am here to protect
the Crown Prince and the young prince.
I absolutely will not disturb
you and His Highness.
I will make my greeting and
then disappear from your sight.
Without His Highness's permission,
you absolutely will not see me.
They're from the Ghost Realm?
Why would they be after me?
Does the Ghost Realm still wish to
wage war against the Celestial Tribe?
You say His Highness had
Jia Yun and the others
send all official reports to Qing Qiu?
Yes, Your Highness.
Jia Yun had returned just now
and announced it to those in
His Highness's slumber hall.
His Highness only met Bai Qian once
at the Eastern Sea.
How come he has now
gone to live with her?
Nine-tailed white foxes are said
to have a naturally seductive appearance
and are skilled at using
enchanting spells.
I am guessing...
I'm afraid she has done
something unbearable to His Highness
and enchanted His Highness!
What does it matter if she has
a naturally seductive appearance?
Wasn't Second Prince
still stolen from her by a snake?
I had to do so many things
suffered the pain of replacing my eyes,
and offered the Soul-gathering Lamp
to finally be able to enter Xiwu Palace.
But just because she was born
a princess of Qing Qiu
she could so gratuitously take
the position of his main wife.
This world is truly unfair.
Yes, Your Highness.
We must quickly think of a way
we can teach her a lesson.
No.
She is a queen of Qing Qiu.
She is someone who is addressed
as Aunt by the four seas.
She is also the Crown Princess
selected by Heavenly Lord himself.
I will not gain any benefit
by entering into a conflict with her.
It can't be that
Your Highness will tolerate this?
No.
This is not a matter of tolerance.
I was able to come this far
enter Xiwu Palace even while
Ye Hua was unwilling
and make the four seas believe I am
the only favored consort of Xiwu Palace.
It was not done by swallowing my anger
and confronting adversity...
but by relying on...
this.
Your Highness is right.
Because Second Prince called off
the engagement to her once
Heavenly Lord absolutely will not allow
Ye Hua to do anything.
I had thought Ye Hua would
continue to miss the dead Su Su
and wouldn't marry Bai Qian so easily.
But who would've known that
after a visit to the Eastern Sea
he would be ensnared by her?
Xin Nu.
To dispose of this obstacle
the best method is to make her cancel
the engagement of her own accord.
Cancel it of her own accord?
That's right.
She does not have any feelings for Ye Hua
and is herself a queen of Qing Qiu.
If by being with Ye Hua,
she feels restricted
uncomfortable, and finds nothing happens
according to her will
then in a fit of anger
perhaps she really might
cancel the engagement.
Even if she does not
she certainly wouldn't be
pleasant to Ye Hua.
Good idea!
That's right!
Your Highness's idea is best.
Go to Qing Qiu now.
Pass on a message to the high goddess
according to my intentions
and let her see that
the Celestial Tribe has rules.
She may have an engagement with
His Highness but they're not married yet.
Being together all day and
lying with each other is inappropriate.
Weaken her authority first.
Yes.
I shall go now.
Aunt, did you not sleep well yesterday?
The Crown Prince insisted that
I play chess with him last night.
I was too sleepy, so I laid my head
down on the table.
In the end, I slept like that
for the night.
I'm going to catch up on sleep.
I'm leaving him to you.
All right.
Raise your head.
Let me see your face.
Your Highness.
I heard you saved
the imperial great-grandson.
Your Highness, when I was previously
passing by Mount Junji
I saw a monster taking advantage of
the imperial great-grandson
so I stepped in and saved him.
I escorted him to the hut
that His Highness often stays in.
The young prince
is the Crown Prince's first son.
He is also the Crown Prince's only son
and greatly favored.
You are very lucky.
Tell me. How should I thank you for
this kindness in His Highness's stead?
I don't dare.
I only wish to be able to stay in
His Highness's palace as a normal maid.
I will be content just to
serve His Highness for many millennia.
You are a princess of the Eastern Sea.
With that identity
even if you were to marry into
Xiwu Palace, nobody would say a word.
Wouldn't it be too humbling
for you to be a maid?
Don't you agree, Princess Miao Qing?
Stand up.
With your identity, and the fact that
you saved the young prince
it would not be difficult for you
to be made a consort.
In these 70,000 years
I've been the only one
to serve His Highness in Xiwu Palace.
It is quite lonely.
Sister, if you truly have the intention
then I can help you into
a marriage with His Highness.
It would be nice to have more company.
Thank you, Your Highness.
There is no need for thanks.
I understand your infatuation.
It is just like how I am to His Highness.
I sympathize with you,
for we are the same.
I heard that High Goddess Bai Qian
of Qing Qiu also attended
the Eastern Sea's banquet
for the Water King's one-month-old son.
Did you see the legendary high goddess?
High Goddess Bai Qian?
What is the matter?
Is it something you cannot speak about?
No, it's just that while at
the Eastern Sea
I had mistaken High Goddess Bai Qian
for Your Highness.
That sounds quite interesting.
Tell me about it.
Hold it.
Is your Aunt in the cave?
Are you looking for our Aunt?
That's right. I work for
Consort Su Jin of Xiwu Palace.
I want to see your Aunt.
My Aunt and your lord play chess at night
and take walks during the day.
She's tired now, and is resting.
If anything is the matter, just tell me.
My lady isn't someone
who has a low tolerance.
Moreover, she is
a future imperial consort.
Her Highness sent me
with good intentions.
High Goddess Bai Qian and Crown Prince
have yet to be wed in ceremony.
They are together all day,
and lie with each other.
On the whole,
it is unacceptable behavior.
Even Heavenly Lord did not
act in this way in the past.
Moreover, Princess Miao Qian has just
been invited up to the Celestial Palace.
The Crown Prince should not neglect her.
Our Qing Qiu doesn't have as many
involved rules as the Celestial Tribe.
A mere low immortal
is here causing a fuss?
Are you bullying Qing Qiu
because we have no guards?
- Exactly!
- That's right!
You're clearly looking for an excuse
to give us a hard time!
Leaving aside that your lord has
a mistress, he even has a son.
Our Aunt doesn't disapprove of you all,
yet you all disapprove of her?
You all... You uncivilized peasants!
How dare you disparage the
Celestial Tribe for having many rules?
Scram! Leave Qing Qiu immediately!
- Leave!
- Scram!
- Get out of Qing Qiu!
- Leave!
- Get out of here!
- Leave Qing Qiu!
You can't do this!
- Get out!
What are you all doing?
Leave!
Mi Gu.
What were they clamoring about?
Aunt, Consort Su Jin from
the Celestial Palace sent someone
to urge the Crown Prince
to return to the palace.
I hadn't even said much to her yet
and she was already driven away
by the people of Qing Qiu.
Su Jin? Ye Hua's side consort?
Yes, Aunt.
How come those people were so fierce?
She said some unpleasant things.
She said you and the Crown Prince
had not been wed in ceremony yet
but are together all day
and lie with each other
and it is unacceptable behavior.
She said even Heavenly Lord
did not act this way in the past.
When the crowd heard that, they were
so furious that they drove her away.
I understand.
That is a nice painting.
Your side consort sent someone just now
to ask for you to return to the palace.
She said some things
that were only somewhat truthful.
I considered it for a bit,
and think her words are reasonable.
What was it?
She said you and I have not yet
been wed in ceremony
but are together all day
and lie with each other.
Although what she said is not the truth
I think it's indeed inappropriate for you
to be staying here in my Fox Den all day.
What do you think?
I wanted to live here,
so I came to live here.
All in all, you are my wife.
How is it any of other people's business?
If I had married at a proper age
my grandchildren would've been
as old as you by now.
Qian Qian, you've repeatedly reminded me
you are dozens of millennia
older than I am.
Is there something you want to say?
It is just an offhand comment.
That palace maid said
you brought Princess Miao Qing
into the Celestial Palace.
Yes.
Qian Qian, sit down.
You should lie down.
Choose a comfortable position.
Raise your hand and face me.
Have a smile on your face.
Very good.
Is he making a painting for me?
How come this Crown Prince has
such variable moods?
One moment, he has a cool expression,
and in the next, he has a pleasant smile.
Miao Qing was insistent on not marrying
the second prince of the West Sea.
She had saved A-Li's life.
I allowed her to go to
the Celestial Palace to be a maid.
When she has thought things through,
she will eventually leave on her own.
Actually, the second prince of
the West Sea is not that unbearable.
You know him?
He's testing me again.
I don't know him.
I've just heard Fourth Brother
mention him before.
And isn't the second prince
a disciple of Mo Yuan?
In all likelihood, he wouldn't be
that hedonistic.
I'm guessing it was just an excuse.
Qian Qian, is there anything else
you want to tell me?
There is one more thing.
Go ahead.
My... my arm is turning numb.
C... Can I change positions?
As you wish.
Your Highness.
Bai Qian of Qing Qiu is not
one to be trifled with.
All of Qing Qiu
is full of uncivilized peasants.
They dared disparage the Celestial Tribe
for having a copious amount of rules
and said that in Qing Qiu, they just need
to have affection for each other
and decorum is of no concern.
What?
They really said that?
Did Bai Qian say that?
That is what makes me furious.
I didn't even get to see Bai Qian.
That Bai Qian put on airs
as a high goddess
and had a mere tree spirit send me away.
She did not care that I was sent by you.
No matter what,
I was once an imperial consort.
I was bestowed to the Crown Prince
by the Heavenly Lord himself.
And I was the first to be
officially wed into Xiwu Palace.
She would actually dare
to belittle me so?
She was not just belittling you.
Those savages in Qing Qiu also said...
They said Your Highness
is the Crown Prince's mistress
and that we are lucky that
their Aunt doesn't disapprove of us
so how dare we go to lecture her.
Atrocious!
It is too atrocious.
- They practically--
- Don't say anymore!
Your Highness, what is the matter?
I said not to say anymore!
Your Highness, don't be angry.
Let me think about
how to make His Highness come back
from that fox's side.
Your Highness, today is
Heavenly Lord's birthday feast.
You must not get too angry.
It's all right.
I just couldn't control
my resentment for the moment.
It's all right.
You said today is
Heavenly Lord's birthday feast?
Yes, Your Highness. Have you forgotten?
I have been thinking about
that Qing Qiu fox the past few days.
I actually forgot about this.
Have you prepared the gift
I told you to arrange?
Yes, Your Highness.
Are there any special guests this time?
It is the same as last year.
If I am to say there's anyone special
it would be the Water King of North Sea
and his eldest son, Yuan Zhen.
- Yuan Zhen?
- Yes.
I heard Yuan Zhen wrote many words
of congratulations for the Heavenly Lord.
The Heavenly Lord was very pleased
and even allowed Water King
of North Sea to bring his eldest son.
I am guessing
the divide between the Water King
of North Sea and the Heavenly Lord
may be able to be bridged with this son.
Quickly, go make preparations.
This must be carried through.
Your Highness!
Are you truly going to do that?
- I'm afraid...
- No need to be afraid.
Nothing will happen.
I heard you've been at the Fox Den
since you were young.
You were here before Qian Qian
was 10,000 years old.
Yes. Counting the years,
it has indeed been that long.
Since Qian Qian is a high goddess
then it's reasonable to say she had to
experience two heavenly trials.
Once to ascend to high immortal,
and another to ascend to high goddess.
Yes... yes...
Since you watched her grow up
then you must know what she
went through for these two trials.
Let me think... let me think...
I'm old, so my brain
doesn't remember things too quickly.
Aunt ascended to high immortal
while she was at Kunlun Mountain.
Could it be the Crown Prince
is in search of Mo Yuan?
I must be careful.
When our Aunt ascended to high immortal,
she happened to be at the Fox Den.
The Fox King himself
shielded her from the trial.
As for ascending to high god
Crown Prince, you know as well
that she had the battle with Qing Cang.
The battle with Qing Cang?
That's correct.
She battled with Qing Cang.
That's how she lost her memory
and became a mortal.
Ye Hua, Ye Hua...
She is your Su Su.
Why must you seek confirmation
over and over again?
Whether or not she has forgotten,
it is enough that she is back.
Your Highness?
Did you think of something?
You look so delighted.
It's nothing.
I'm going to take your Aunt
to the mortal realm.
Mortal realm?
The Crown Prince is
so hard to understand.
He's gloomy one moment,
and bright the next.
The rain sure is delightful today.
I finally don't have to
go on a stroll with him.
Lord Ye Hua.
Look. I wonder which Water King
is casting rain today.
I don't want you to get drenched.
Why don't we stay inside
the Fox Den for the day?
Father says he's taking us to play
in the mortal realm today.
Fortunately, it's not raining
You two are going to the mortal realm?
You should find
an earth deity to guide you.
I stay in the Fox Den every day.
I'm not familiar with the mortal realm.
Mother, I'd like you to come.
Wait for me to get changed, all right?
Godfather, I want this one!
All right.
Which one would you like, young master?
Here, this one.
Wait. Your pearl could buy
the entire street.
Be careful. Don't drop it.
- Here you go.
- All right.
- All kinds of nuts! Healthy and tasty!
- Thank you, Godfather.
Come try them! All sorts of nuts!
Young master, I have
all sorts of nuts available.
Godfather, I want this one.
- Fill up a bag for me.
- All right.
How come you're in the mood
to visit the mortal realm today?
Jia Yun brought a large pile
of reports yesterday.
Judging from his expression,
they weren't trivial documents.
Today is A-Li's birthday.
How insincere of you.
Why didn't you tell me earlier about
such an important matter as
A-Li's birthday?
He calls me Mother.
I don't even have a gift prepared.
It's so disheartening.
What gift are you going to give him?
A luminous pearl?
How did you know?
Hasn't it been your habit all these years
to gift luminous pearls?
Small pearls for young immortals,
and large pearls for old immortals.
Although a luminous pearl
would be most precious
A-Li is young and
wouldn't know its value.
It would just be a waste
to give it to him.
Don't you know? I have one
that is half as tall as a person.
It is like the moon.
If placed in A-Li's Qingyun Hall,
it would still be a pleasure to look at.
It is the world's one of a kind--
Watch out!
So you're over here! What were you doing?
Thank you, young master.
You're welcome.
I was so scared.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Qian Qian.
After being missing for a few years,
how come you're now in this state?
I have never left Qing Qiu
in these 70,000 years
and hadn't been injured.
Could it have been a dream
that I just remembered?
What's the matter?
Misters, all the dishes are served.
Here you go.
This young master is quite adorable.
He may be cute as a child, but who knows
how he will look when he is grown up.
Enjoy.
Mother, do you not like me now?
Good looks on a man are not useful.
A pair of strong fists is more useful
than a handsome face.
Besides, daughters resemble their
fathers and sons resemble their mothers.
In my opinion, A-Li won't look anywhere
near bad when he is grown up.
Mother is beautiful.
Naturally, I won't be anywhere
ugly enough to bring Mother shame.
Yes, no matter how you look
when you grow up
you will still be the apple of my eye.
I'll be most protective of you.
You know that, right?
You are so good to me.
Misters, this liquor was just warmed up.
It is perfect for drinking right now.
Have a taste.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
You like to eat this. Have more.
You hate eating this, but it's healthy.
You are so skinny.
Even if it doesn't pain you to see
yourself like this, it pains me.
Qian Qian, if you can't bear to listen
to these endearing words
what will you do from now on?
My lord, Aunt.
Deities from all around the world
have arrived for
Heavenly Lord's birthday feast.
Second Prince Die Feng of West Sea
arrived at Celestial Palace
and came to Zichen Hall soon after
saying he has urgent matters
to discuss in person.
I dared not delay,
and came in search of Your Highness.
Keep A-Li company. I have to
return to the Celestial Palace.
I'll come back to
look for you two tonight.
All right.
Take care, Mister. Please come again!
All right!
Mister, how come it's just
the two of you?
Where is the other mister
who was with you?
Is there any place worth visiting nearby?
Place worth visiting? Yes!
Head south that way.
There is a teahouse.
This teahouse may charge high prices
but there is some wonderful
storytelling there.
- Storytelling?
- Yes.
Let's go to the teahouse then.
- All right.
- Thank you.
[Yunji Teahouse]
Let's continue the story from last time.
Good, good...
- It's said the python was 10 zhang long.
- Right here, please.
Its scales and spots
shone fluorescent bright.
A rush of astonishing courage
filled Zhang Fei.
Searching for prey left and right,
the python instilled panic in all.
Splendid...
Sure death awaited nine of ten men
caught in its mouth.
Thus, the three men
glanced at each other...
In the time it takes your father
to drink a cup of tea in heaven
night will already be upon us
in the mortal realm.
Let's sit here and wait for him.
Crown Prince.
I still have urgent business
in the mortal realm.
I'll have to leave when
this candle goes out.
Then I'll keep it short.
Immortals who have left
the Eastern Sea banquet in recent days
have encountered groups of attackers
of unknown identity who aimed to kill.
Such an occurrence happened?
Were any captured alive?
None were left alive.
They were all killed by demonic magic.
My Sixteenth Disciple means to say
they were puppets
created by demonic magic.
So, it is highly likely their master
comes from the Ghost Realm.
The Ghost Realm?
Subtitles by DramaFever