Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 49]
Auntie, are you really going
to marry the Crown Prince?
I have to marry him sooner or later.
There's no harm in choosing "earlier."
Surely not.
I'm just surprised by
your fiery passion with Ye Hua.
You can marry whenever you want.
I wouldn't dare voice an opinion.
The marriage between Qing Qiu and
the Celestial Tribe is very important.
We can't be the only willing party.
The wedding was brought up
by Ye Hua's mother first
so I came home to discuss about it.
Consort Le Xu mentioned it?
- But...
- Second Brother!
Look at you.
They are already engaged anyway.
It's just holding the wedding now.
Why do you have that many worries?
What about Mo Yuan?
Master?
Once a mentor, a father for life.
I do have to inform my mentor about it.
However, this marriage was
decided by the Heavenly Lord and Father.
Master wouldn't object to it.
Moreover, he probably still
doesn't know that I'm a girl.
Naive... You're too naive.
Do you think that High God Mo Yuan
couldn't see through Zhe Yan's magic?
They are brothers!
I've always thought it was Mo Yuan
you had on your mind.
Second Brother, you mustn't make
such a joke.
My mentor saved me from
my heavenly trial.
He also mentored and educated me.
He's as close to me as Father is.
Even if I had to sacrifice my life
for Master one day
I wouldn't hesitate at all.
However, Ye Hua is the only
man on my mind.
That is absolutely true.
All right.
Since you clearly know
what it is you seek
I won't hold you back.
It's just that you've been
engaged for a long time.
Why are you suddenly in a rush
to get the wedding done?
It's because Ye Hua went to
Yingzhou for me
and used up his cultivation
to make the elixir.
He saved my mentor.
He doesn't have much cultivation left.
I'm worried that should he
take the throne of Heavenly Lord
he might not be able to withstand
the karma of 81 sacred blazes
and 9 holy lightning bolts.
What has his inheriting the throne
got to do with your wedding?
Since the ancient times
both the Heavenly Lord and Empress have
endured such fires of karma together.
If I could marry him soon
I could take on
the fires of karma with him.
You're not his wife yet,
and you're already so thoughtful of him?
Fifth Sister is from Qing Qiu.
She's so faithful. So faithful.
All right. I'll write a letter tomorrow.
I'll have it sent to Mother and Father.
Thank you, Second Brother.
I'll get going.
Sure.
Where are you going?
This is your Qing Qiu Fox Den.
Riceball is still young.
Ye Hua is constantly busy with work.
I have to head back to look after him.
What about your second
and fourth brothers?
You don't care about us?
Ignore him.
Get going.
Yes, Second Brother. I'll leave now.
Look at her.
What a good step-mother she is.
It's a pity that there's a side consort
bestowed by the Heavenly Lord
in Ye Hua's harem.
Fifth Sister and Ye Hua can't just be
a loving couple with intruders.
By the way, I forgot about a matter.
What is it?
I'm about to marry into
the Celestial Palace.
I took one of the thrones of
the Five Far Lands
so it must be passed on to another.
I can't be a heavenly princess consort
and a queen at the same time.
Although it seems correct in theory
our parents only had five children.
Five Far Lands of Qing Qiu, five rulers.
No one should take two thrones.
I mean...
Among the five of us
only you have a daughter, Feng Jiu.
Why don't I... pass it on to her?
Me?
Good! Great idea.
However, Second Brother is the emperor
of Qing Qiu's Five Far Lands.
If Feng Jiu takes your throne
isn't the seniority a bit messed up?
Head back first.
I'll discuss this matter with
our parents and Bai Xuan first
before we make a decision.
All right, I'll get going now.
I...
Auntie, why have you asked to talk to me?
Did your father hit you again?
He didn't beat me up that severely.
What exactly is it?
I don't really know the details.
It's just that Third Prince's girlfriend
has asked me to pass on a message.
She asked that you visit her
in the Nine Heavens.
Lady Cheng Yu?
Exactly.
Lady Cheng Yu always
acts very cautiously.
If it weren't an important matter
she wouldn't have asked
Auntie to approach me for her.
I don't know the details.
However, judging from her expression
it seems to be a serious matter.
I won't stay to chat.
I'm in a rush to head back
for dinner with Riceball.
If you're going to sneak
into the Nine Heavens
get Bai Zhen to help you.
Feng Jiu sees Auntie off.
You've been smiling all day.
Is there some joyous occasion?
Exactly.
There are actually two joyous occasions.
First, our little Feng Jiu is going
to become the Queen of Qing Qiu.
Isn't Qian Qian the Queen of Qing Qiu?
That's the second joyous occasion.
My Fifth Sister is getting married.
She's really fallen in love this time.
She even approached Bai Yi to
have him bring it up to our parents.
She's also set a date.
It's the second day of September.
Mo Yuan...
Aren't you going to say anything?
You're not surprised?
Even a man like my brother
Bai Yi was shocked.
What is so surprising and shocking?
Indeed. Ye Hua's father is already
making a list of betrothal gifts.
I also have much to prepare.
Su Jin.
Not only are you the side consort
of Xiwu Palace
but also the only concubine in its harem.
You have to help with the preparations.
Assign the servants to
start preparing for the wedding.
We haven't had such a grand
joyous occasion for a long time.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
I'll surely do my best to make
all the arrangements for Your Highness.
High God Bai Qian will marry
into the palace glamorously.
I wonder when the wedding will be held?
We have yet to set a date.
The date isn't set?
Didn't Ye Hua sink Yingzhou
of the Eastern Sea?
He slayed the four mythical beasts
left behind by Heavenly Father.
He's now punished to withstand
heavenly trial in the Mortal Realm.
The soonest he could return
is two months.
We'll set the date when he returns.
I understand.
High God.
Is His Highness in there?
His Highness didn't know
when High God would return
so he's instructed me to wait here
for your return to take you to him.
He's made it so mysterious?
High God, this way, please.
High God, is there a problem?
I'm fine.
I've been to this lotus pond before.
Why is it so foggy here tonight?
His Highness has especially
arranged it to be so.
High God, this way, please.
Greetings to Auntie!
Qian Qian, come here.
Come here.
Qian Qian.
These are all the deities of
the Celestial Tribe.
Bai Qian greets everyone.
What a perfect match.
How lovely.
A match made in heaven.
What a beautiful couple!
Why did you welcome me in
with the Crown Prince's formality?
You're the Crown Princess Consort
of the Nine Heavens.
It should be done so.
Who knew that
you could sometimes be so...
What?
So likable.
Just likable?
A-Li greets Father and Mother.
- Come here.
- That's so adorable!
Why has Mother sneaked in here again?
I thought that I wouldn't be
able to see you for some time.
I've gone to visit a few of
your uncles in Qing Qiu.
I've asked them to make arrangements
so that I can marry your father soon.
Really? That's wonderful!
Look!
He's such a good boy.
How lovely!
He's so adorable.
Ye Hua.
I visited my brothers back in Qing Qiu.
My second brother has already
agreed to speak to my parents.
If it all goes well, we can get married
on the second of September.
Qian Qian, I'm afraid that we won't
be able to make it then.
Why?
I have to withstand
a heavenly trial in the Mortal Realm.
Why would you have to do so
for no reason?
It has to do with those four mythical
beasts of Yingzhou.
Although I've rendered a great merit
in destroying the divine fungal grass
it's a great sin to have killed
those four beasts.
After all, they did possess half of
Heavenly Father's powers.
There's still much to make up for it
after rendering the merit.
I have to be punished.
Hence, the heavenly trial
in the Mortal Realm.
It's actually because of
those four mythical beasts?
I already didn't like them when
they wounded my father.
It seems that they are really
my nemesis in life.
How long will you be gone?
It's 60 years in the Mortal Realm
until my mortal self dies.
That's just two months apart from you
in the heavens.
Two months?
You'll head down into the Mortal Realm
at the beginning of August
so if the trial takes two months
we'll postpone the wedding to October?
In October, there's the Indian Summer.
It's also a good date.
Although it's only two months for me
it will be a lifetime for you
in the Mortal Realm.
Have you read the destiny
that Star Lord wrote you?
He wouldn't write you a two-timing
or three-timing relationship?
Star Lord won't get to write
my story this time.
Heavenly Lord gave orders to
leave my destiny blank.
Whatever relationships I might have
are entirely up to me.
It's left blank?
It means that no one will know
what you will experience?
Exactly.
I have a few reminders for you.
Do tell.
Even if you will forget your identity
as the Crown Prince of the Nine Heavens
when you descend into the Mortal Realm
and that you still have a legal consort
in Xiwu Palace to marry
you're not allowed to marry
anyone else as a mortal.
I'm not worried about anything else.
I'm just concerned that
you might get involved
with some women in the mortal realm.
You should know that I draw
a clear line between love and hate.
I can't stand any betrayal.
If I really got involved in
such a mortal relationship
what would you do?
Should that really happen
I'd snatch you back to Qing Qiu
and lock you up in my Fox Den.
You would only look at me every day.
You'd have to look at me when you eat.
You'd have to look at me when you read.
You'd have to look at me when you draw.
If that is so, I'd rather that
you snatch me away right now.
Then... it's a deal?
When you get back
from your heavenly trial
come and look for me in Qing Qiu.
By then, we don't have to worry
about those wedding rituals.
We'll just go with Qing Qiu's customs.
I'll lock you in my Fox Den.
Sure.
Qian Qian.
Let's go to bed?
You're going to the Heavenly Palace?
When we were in the Heavenly Palace
Lady Cheng Yu was very kind to me.
She suddenly had Auntie pass on
a message to me urgently.
It must be a matter of great importance.
I can't just make up some excuse.
You have a point.
She has taken good care of you.
Now that she has asked to see you
you shouldn't make any excuses not to go.
However...
Your father has forbidden you
to leave Qing Qiu.
But Fourth Uncle, you could.
Just take me along with you.
As long as I stay on you
I can get past the celestial shield that
my father put up at the valley.
It's fine that I take you with me.
However, you have to understand that
we can't keep this a secret.
If you escape, your father will
surely go after you.
Give it some thought.
If you make such an effort to escape
you must have gone
to the Celestial Palace.
By then, your father wouldn't even
have to search for you.
He would go straight to Lord Dong Hua.
I'm not going to visit him this time.
Whatever. I'll act accordingly
after my father finds out.
I have to get away first.
Fourth Uncle, please?
- Fourth Uncle...
- All right!
Little lass.
I'll grant you your wish this time.
Thank you, Fourth Uncle.
Where are you going, Fourth Uncle?
You're not staying for lunch?
I'm thinking about visiting that
Die Yong in the West Sea
to see how High God
Mo Yuan's spirit is faring.
Qian Qian has been looking after
her future husband
in the Celestial Palace these days.
How could she care about the West Sea?
I'll tell Little Princess
not to make you lunch.
Feng Jiu is still asleep.
Don't wake her up.
She hasn't been in a good mood lately.
Just let her sleep in.
Wake her up at lunchtime.
Sure.
Fourth Uncle is so thoughtful today.
Fourth Uncle, be gentle!
You threw me to the ground.
You're still yammering?
If you don't hurry up,
your father will catch you.
I'll get going now.
Thank you, Fourth Uncle!
Since I've made an excuse
to leave the den
it's troublesome to head back now.
That lass got me in this fix.
I don't even have a place
to go for lunch.
Forget it.
I'd better go to Zhe Yan.
What brings both high gods over?
Your 17th junior has to look after
the Crown Prince in the Celestial Palace.
She can't come here.
Zhen and I decided to take a look.
How has your brother been?
He was suddenly unwell last night.
It went on all night, so I thought
that his situation might deteriorate.
However, he said that he felt
energetic the next day.
It was as if his lingering
illness was gone.
He even ate quite a lot.
Really?
Yes.
It seems that there will be
some good news soon.
High God, you mean...
Your mentor will return very soon.
Is that right?
Forgive my manners.
It's all right.
Quickly. Take me to your brother.
After you.
It's indeed as I thought.
Your mentor's spirit isn't here anymore.
I think that he must have
returned to his own body.
Then... What should I do?
Don't panic.
Hurry back to Kunlun Mountain now.
Gather up all the disciples.
Have them prepare to welcome
Mo Yuan back home.
Zhen and I will rush back
to Qing Qiu's Yanhua Cave.
We'll check to see if your mentor
Mo Yuan's spirit has really returned.
Yes, I'll head back to
Kunlun Mountain right away.
He doesn't seem like the first disciple
of Kunlun Mountain.
He's more like a reckless teen.
It's not just him.
Even I'm so thrilled that
I don't know what to do next.
Quickly. Let's rush back
to Qing Qiu now.
Go on.
I'll head down to the Mortal Realm
after visiting the Heavenly Lord.
Why won't you let me
see you off to the Mortal Realm?
It's just two months.
If the others learn that High God
Bai Qian of Qing Qiu
went personally to see me off
aren't you worried about being teased?
The Celestial Tribe's regulations
are so bothersome.
By the way, I have something for you.
Take this with you.
Soul jade?
Do you know why Li Jing
handed this over to Mu Gu?
It's probably because I saved him
and his sister in Yingzhou.
Since you saved them
it's fine for you to keep it.
Do you not find it strange that
I accept it so quickly?
You're worried that Li Jing would
use that as an excuse to meet me?
I'll get going now.
Go on.
- Second Senior!
The bell is chiming again.
It's Master!
- It's Master!
- Master has returned!
- This is great!
Master has returned!
Master...
- Indeed...
- We've been waiting for so long.
You're right.
That's Kunlun Mountain.
Lord Dong Hua, could you
recognize this bell?
It is as Heavenly Lord thinks.
The bell is chiming in Kunlun Mountain.
Mo Yuan has returned.
Fifth Sister!
Your long-awaited wish
can probably be fulfilled today.
Fourth Brother.
Have you also heard the bell chime?
It isn't just the bell.
Your fourth brother and I just
rushed back from the West Sea.
Die Yong had a tough night yesterday
so I investigated with
my soul-tracking magic.
I found out that Mo Yuan's spirit isn't
residing in Die Yong's body anymore.
That's why I rushed back here
to check on Yanhua Cave.
Mo Yuan has been asleep for so long.
He's finally picked
a good day to wake up.
Master...
Master is going to wake up?
Crown Prince.
According to the regulations
before I take you to the Mortal Realm
you'll have to drink the amnesia potion
from the River of Oblivion.
Then... it's a deal?
You'll come to look for me
in Qing Qiu when you return.
We won't abide by the wedding rituals.
We'll just go along with
Qing Qiu's customs.
I'll lock you back in my Fox Den.
Qian Qian...
Await my return.
What are you doing?
I want to put on my male disguise.
After all, my mentor used to
see me as Si Yin in the past.
He probably wouldn't recognize me.
With Mo Yuan's cultivation,
he long knew that you're a girl.
He didn't expose your identity
because of your parents.
Did you really think you fooled
him for 20,000 years?
Fourth Brother said that to me as well.
But I still think that Master is used
to seeing me as Si Yin.
Stop fooling yourself.
Go ahead.
Don't be scared.
Go and take a look at your mentor.
It's been 70,000 years.
Between the Four Seas and the Six Realms
I've looked at the lakes of
Qing Qiu 779 times.
70,000 years...
That is as long as half of my lifetime.
I've used half of my lifetime
to do just one thing.
I've been waiting for Master to wake up.
From this day forth
you're the God of War
Mo Yuan's 17th disciple.
Deity Si Yin.
Master, don't leave.
Master! I should be the one
to take that heavenly trial!
Master!
Seventeenth.
Come and let me take a look at you.
Let's see if you've made
any progress over all these years.
Master...
You're indeed my little Seventeenth.
You've finally returned.
Yes.
I have returned.
My little Seventeenth looks lovely
in this form as well.
Master...
You haven't changed at all.
Is that so?
Mo Yuan.
After 70,000 years, you finally woke up.
70,000 years...
Yes.
It isn't that long,
but it isn't short either.
Qian Qian has hidden out here
in Qing Qiu for 70,000 years as well.
She safeguarded your body
to await your return.
It's too damp and cold in here.
Let's leave this cave.
You must have had a hard time
in the past 70,000 years?
My spirit was split into fragments
so it took me quite a lot of time
to put them back together.
Mo Yuan...
You're finally awake.
Do you think the Bell of East Emperor
could trap me without your spirit?
I just need a bit more time...
It won't take me too long.
We will soon meet again.
Master.
Zhe Yan.
During the past 70,000 years
when I was asleep
did anyone who looked identical
to me appear?
There is one such man.
Your little disciple even
knows him quite well.
Little Seventeenth, you know him?
What is it?
Only when it comes to Mo Yuan
would you show some fear.
Don't be shy. Tell him.
The man you just mentioned...
He's my fiance.
The Crown Prince of the Celestial Tribe.
Your fiance?
What is his name?
When was he born?
His name is Ye Hua.
He was born about 70,000 years ago
when I brought your body
out of Kunlun Mountain.
Little Seventeenth.
My twin brother
is snatched away by you just like that.
Why haven't I heard that
you have a twin brother?
It's no wonder that you're surprised.
I only learned of it when
Heavenly Father passed away.
A golden lotus?
Heavenly Father...
I have to tell you  a story first.
That year, the Four Pillars of
Heaven and Earth collapsed.
In order to hold up and repair those
four pillars that supported the heavens
your mother nearly had a miscarriage.
When she went into labor
she was supposed to
give birth to twin sons
but she only managed to
keep the eldest alive.
The younger twin was lost.
You're that eldest twin.
I had a younger brother?
I felt guilty toward your brother.
So I used up half of all my powers
to create a celestial fetus.
I turned that celestial fetus
into a golden lotus.
Now that I'll soon go into
the realm of nothingness
I'm entrusting your brother's
celestial fetus to you.
You must nurse him in
Kunlun Mountain's lotus pond.
Hopefully he shall one day
be born into this world.
The both of you are bonded by blood.
That might give him a better chance
of reviving him some day.
Keep him safe.
Mo Yuan.
This is... my only wish.
Yes.
When I sacrificed my spirit
to the Bell of East Emperor
he was finally awakened.
I only know that after
Heavenly Father passed away
you've dedicated yourself
to looking after that lotus.
I've never once suspected
where it came from.
It's no wonder.
That golden lotus withered
when your soul and spirit vanished.
Soon afterwards, Consort Le Xu gave birth
to Crown Prince Ye Hua.
No wonder when that lad was born
72 rainbow birds flew around
the pillar for 81 days
and the misty clouds in the twilight
appeared for three years.
He's actually High God
Mo Yuan's twin brother.
Indeed.
Only the twin brother of Mo Yuan
and the son of Heavenly Father
could be blessed with
such a celebratory sight.
The records in the Nine Heavens
stated clearly that
Heavenly Father only had one son
High God Mo Yuan.
It seems that these historical records
are not to be trusted.
Instead of reading those records,
I might as well read Star Lord's stories.
Everyone said that
Ye Hua resembles Master.
I almost mistook him for Master
as well when I first met him.
Yet no one could have known
they were related in such a way.
Seventeenth.
I'd like to meet my twin brother.
How is he doing?
Master.
You just woke up.
You'll still need to
meditate for some time
to be restored to your original state.
Ye Hua is now in the Mortal Realm.
I can't locate him either.
Why don't we wait till
you're well recuperated
and I'll bring him here to you?
That's good.
I'll meditate in Kunlun Mountain
to await his return.
Are all your seniors doing well?
70,000 years ago after you passed away
your disciples searched for us
for several thousand years.
Then their families came
and took them home one by one.
They went to fulfill their dutiful roles.
Kunlun Mountain is no longer
what it used to be.
Moreover...
I don't wish Master to see
what Kunlun Mountain has become now.
It doesn't matter.
We'll set out toward Kunlun Mountain now.
Yes, Master.
What did you say?
Lord Dong Hua will meet
his destined calamity?
Feng Jiu, look on the bright side.
Irregardless of their capability
or ranks, all deities in the heavens
will have to meet
their destined calamity.
All have to enter
the realm of nothingness.
Look at how long Lord Dong Hua
has already been around.
It's time...
It's time that he meets
his destined calamity.
I don't believe it...
I don't believe it.
I'm going to ask him.
Lord Dong Hua!
Where are you, Lord Dong Hua?
Lord Dong Hua...
Why are you crying?
If Your Lordship lives, Feng Jiu lives.
If you die, I'd never survive alone.
Feng Jiu.
Don't behave so.
I won't obey you.
Qing Qiu's princess comes up to
the Nine Heavens
and hugs me for no reason.
Aren't you embarrassed?
We have been married for years
in the Mortal Realm. Why would I mind?
That was to overcome the calamity.
How can you regard that with another?
Are you still brooding over what
happened between me and Yuan Zhen?
Star Lord made me do that.
I never had an affair with Yuan Zhen.
I know.
Anyway, I won't leave you before
you meet your destined calamity.
Who told you that I'll meet
my destined calamity?
Are you not?
Subtitles by DramaFever