Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 24]
As far as he is concerned
your eyesight didn't hold
much significance to begin with.
Su Jin?
It is me.
Su Su, how is your injury?
Does it still hurt?
I trusted you.
Why did you harm me in this way?
Leaving aside
that you hurt your own eyes
you have also caused me to lose my eyes.
What good does this do for you?
It is true you don't have your eyes.
But now, I can already see.
I came today to tell you
your eyes are quite handy.
You're using... my eyes?
Did Ye Hua not tell you?
He took out your eyes to give to me.
When Medicine King changed my eyes for me
Ye Hua stayed by my side
the whole day and night.
How could you understand
what is between me and him?
You can continue to stay in
the Hall of Beautiful Youth.
You just have to remember...
This is Ye Hua's future consort,
Su Jin's charity to you.
This was originally between
the two of them.
I was just a passerby...
who was dazedly drawn in,
and became an obstacle for them.
This is preposterous!
Guard this hall well.
She may not have a proper title,
but she's still the Crown Prince's woman.
Should there be any mishap,
you will have to answer to me.
- Yes, Consort Su Jin.
Your Highness, are you all right?
The things this mortal keeps
are all just wild at heart.
Beat that evil creature to death.
Yes.
Consort Su Jin.
Didn't you already leave for
the lower realm's Deity Mountain?
Your Highness, Consort Le Xu
just graciously permitted me
to be demoted back
to the lower realm's Deity Mountain
after the imperial child
reaches one year of age.
Is this little fox a pet kept in
your Hall of Beautiful Youth?
Your Highness, this little fox indeed
comes often to Hall of Beautiful Youth
but it is not my lady's.
I clearly saw it coming out of
the Hall of Beautiful Youth.
You would dare tell a lie
over an evil creature?
Your Highness,
this little fox really isn't--
Impudence!
Dijun.
A little fox of mine has gone missing.
Has Your Highness seen it?
Little fox?
It's the one your servant is carrying.
Tell me. Who hurt it?
Dijun.
It bit my lady's wrist.
Her Highness only flung it aside
out of defense.
It was so disobedient?
How could it be?
It must have been unintentional.
So was it intentional or unintentional?
Unintentional.
It must have been unintentional.
I may have been in its way. It has
an unstable temper and was vexed.
It isn't a big injury.
Since it is your fox,
I will return it to you.
Since you say it injured you,
I mustn't discriminate in its favor.
Why don't you tell me
what happened just now?
It...
Isn't this where
the Crown Prince's mortal wife resides?
I heard a tiny incident happened
a few days ago
that caused a lot of unpleasantness.
Come inside with me
to ask the mortal woman...
why this little fox suffered
such a provocation
as to dare bite someone.
You must be jesting, Dijun.
This small bite is not worthy of you
personally inquiring about it.
It bit me, I also injured it.
This matter has been balanced out.
Balanced out?
I see that it is hurt
more severely than you are.
How is it balanced?
Dijun, please calm your anger.
I have done wrong.
What did you say?
I was in a bad mood because I visited
the mortal in
the Hall of Beautiful Youth.
And this little fox
happened to be playing here
yet, it was harmed by me for no reason.
Harmed for no reason?
Dijun, please calm your anger.
I was boiling with fury,
and hurt Taichen Palace's fox.
I am willing to kneel here
for two hours in apology.
That is very well.
You grew up here in the Nine Heavens.
You must have heard I am
accustomed to leading troops in the past
so I am both protective of my own,
and impervious to reason.
You had best stay away from
the people and fox of my palace.
Yes.
- Your Highness, get up.
- Do not help me up.
Otherwise, if someone tells Dijun,
there would be more trouble.
Regardless, Your Highness is
an imperial consort.
Why would you have to
humble yourself in such a way?
What do you know?
Dijun might never involve himself
in the affairs of the Celestial Palace
but if he says the word,
nobody would dare disobey him.
Just now, he was obviously angry.
Even if Heavenly Lord were here,
he wouldn't help me.
He may even sentence me
to kneel here for the whole day.
Xin Nu.
It was not easy for me
to reach this point.
I will endure whatever grievances I can.
As long as I can get into Xiwu Palace,
nothing else is a concern for me.
Your Highness.
It would be nice if the Crown Prince
knew of your devotion to him.
He will know sooner or later.
This is a report submitted by
the water kings of the four seas
the various clan leaders,
and the vassals of every sea altogether.
The Far North war has won
many people's hearts for Ye Hua.
They are all requesting
to allow the Crown Prince
to officially accept the seal.
Congratulations, Brother and Father.
Once Ye Hua receives
the Crown Prince seal
the two of you will have someone to
share the burdens of official matters.
He has not betrayed my expectations.
In this world, there are trials in life.
Whether you are an immortal or a human,
you have your own trials.
You can't help her.
She can't help you either.
- Heavenly Lord.
Dijun.
Something good seems to
have happened to you.
I have received numerous reports
in the past few days.
They are all asking for the Crown Prince
to complete his investiture.
Is that so?
Congratulations are in order,
Heavenly Lord.
The Crown Prince has not disappointed you
and has won the hearts of
all those around the world.
Yes, I am also very pleased.
Haven't you been sending official affairs
to Zichen Hall starting from
20,000 years ago?
After the Crown Prince receives
his seal, you can be like me
free of all matters and no longer
concerned with palace affairs.
You are right.
In the past dozen years
I have deeply felt myself to be
less capable than I wish to be.
Start preparations for
Ye Hua's investiture early next month.
Thank you, Heavenly Lord.
Rise.
Ye Hua.
I have to congratulate you.
Thank you, Third Uncle.
Ye Hua.
Father has always had
high expectations of you.
After your investiture, you must be
prudent with your words and actions
and carry on
Father's principles as a ruler.
I shall sincerely obey
Father's instruction.
Nai Nai, the lotuses are so fragrant.
If Your Highness likes it, I will
come with you every day to enjoy them.
Your Highness,
Heavenly Lord has recently ordered
that Your Highness is not to step out
of the Hall of Beautiful Youth.
Your Highness has slept
for a long while again.
Nai Nai.
What day is it?
How come I am always so drowsy?
It must be because you are pregnant,
so you are exceptionally sleepy.
Your Highness, the Crown Prince
has come to visit you.
Ye Hua has come?
Are the stars bright tonight?
Su Su, have you forgotten there is
no day and night in the Celestial Palace?
I will soon be officially conferred
the title of Crown Prince.
We will be able to marry very soon.
Once you are Crown Princess
we will no longer have to
consider other people's opinions
and we can begin living the life we want.
I know you are very busy.
Go attend to your affairs.
I'm a bit sleepy. I'm going to sleep.
I heard from Medicine King that
you have been feeling lethargic lately.
Yes.
Go to sleep then.
I will be receiving
the Crown Prince's seal in a few days.
I will be struck with 36 sacred blazes
and 9 holy lightning bolts.
If Su Su hears the thunder,
don't tell her the truth.
I'm afraid she will worry.
Yes.
Not eating is counter-productive.
I will order someone to extend your life.
I guarantee you won't die.
If I had known this day would come,
I wouldn't have--
Wouldn't have what?
Wouldn't have let me off?
Or, when you killed my mother,
would you have killed me too?
That's correct.
The mistake I regret the most in my life
is not tearing you to pieces
70,000 years ago!
Let me tell you.
Don't think that Father
loves you so very much.
You are just a worm he kept.
What do you mean?
You, Yan Zhi, and I
are his children,
the Ghost Realm's princes and princess
as well as his lifesavers.
Regardless of whichever of
the three of us dies
his powers increase.
The three of us are just vessels of kin
used for cultivation of his powers.
When my mother gave birth to me,
she discovered this secret.
That was why she was banished
to the Cold Palace.
That is how you had
the chance to kill her.
Trust me.
If you rescue Father,
we are the first ones he will kill.
Then his powers will greatly increase
and he will seek revenge
from the Celestial Tribe.
Impossible.
Father absolutely would not
do that to me!
What is impossible in
Grand Ziming Palace?
That is why as long as I am alive,
I will surely keep you alive.
From this day forth
you will be locked here day and night
never to see the sky again.
I will take your life!
- Ghost Lord.
Li Jing.
It's so late. You're not sleeping yet?
I want to leave the Ghost Realm
to go to the mortal realm.
Yan Zhi.
I only have you, my sister.
I can pardon all your past betrayals.
I only want you to stay
in Grand Ziming Palace
and be the princess.
Don't think about saving Li Yuan,
or Father.
Li Yuan, you, and I all grew up
together in Grand Ziming Palace.
Both sides of this feud are my family.
If you ask me to pay no heed,
I cannot do it.
However, I don't want
to betray you a second time.
So please let me go.
Let me leave this place.
Go.
Remember.
No matter where you go...
you must stay safe and sound.
All of you, listen up.
Follow the princess.
From now on, you are her men.
Ensuring her safety
is your only mission in life.
- Yes.
Your Majesty, wine can be unhealthy.
Don't drink so much.
My child.
You are the only family I have left.
Your Majesty.
Aside from our child, you also have me.
A-Yin.
- A-Yin.
- A-Yin?
Why do you only have A-Yin
in your heart?
Si Yin, do not appear again.
Otherwise, I will pull out your tendons
and tear off your skin.
- Water King of North Sea.
- Water King of Eastern Sea.
Water King of West Sea.
Water King of North Sea.
Ghost Lord.
It seems all the rulers around
the world have gathered here today.
Yes, yes.
The Celestial Tribe Crown Prince
being awarded his seal is a major event.
Of course they would attend.
Ghost Lord.
I heard Your Highness was
bestowed marriage to the Crown Prince.
Ghost Lord, you sure are well-informed.
I have to deliver these clothes to
Consort Le Xu, so I won't stay to talk.
Your Highness.
What is it?
Is there something else?
I just want to ask
is the lady that was at the
Hall of Beautiful Youth doing well now?
Are you asking about Sister Su Su?
Yes.
She...
She was the one who made
Her Highness's eyes blind.
Ghost Lord, I'm afraid you are
asking the wrong person.
Shut up. Who allowed you to
speak in front of Ghost Lord?
Your Highness's eyes?
It is a long story.
I believe it was
unintentional on her part.
She's currently waiting for labor
at the Hall of Beautiful Youth.
She will be giving birth very soon.
It was my fiery qilin
who caused her injury.
I have had a guilty conscience.
Since I came to the Celestial Palace,
I thought I'd ask after her.
Do not take it to heart, Your Highness.
Look at how decorous Consort Su Jin is.
Yes, yes. No wonder Heavenly Lord
bestowed her to the Crown Prince.
Only a woman like this
is worthy of assisting
our Celestial Tribe's heir apparent.
Fiery qilin.
Go search around.
See if she is still in
the Hall of Beautiful Youth.
Yes.
Your Highness,
why did you sneak out again?
Medicine King said you have been
in weak health lately.
You must be careful not to catch a cold.
I just wanted to bask in the sun.
The sunlight feels warm on the back of
my hand. It feels particularly nice.
It is as if I can see the light again.
Your Highness.
Go.
With these regalia bestowed upon
imperial grandson Ye Hua
he is conferred the title of
Imperial Crown Prince
to preside over the East Palace
and to place
the unity of the four seas
and the hearts of those
around the world above all else.
To preside over the East Palace
and to place
the unity of the four seas
and the hearts of those
around the world above all else.
- Congratulations, Crown Prince.
Your Highness!
Your Highness,
Crown Prince's investiture is today.
I heard the maids of Xiwu Palace say
Heavenly Lord had already issued a decree
that after the investiture,
Consort Su Jin is to be...
bestowed to Crown Prince.
It was to happen sooner or later.
But Consort Su Jin and Your Highness
have an outstanding grudge.
I'm afraid if she enters Xiwu Palace,
she will make your life difficult.
It won't be difficult.
I don't have much to do with
Xiwu Palace anyway.
Your Highness, if Crown Prince
heard that, he would be displeased.
Don't say it in the future.
Nai Nai, why do I hear thunder?
That is... in celebration for
the Crown Prince.
Your Highness, what is the matter?
I might be going into labor.
I'll find the Crown Prince.
- I'll find the Crown Prince!
- Don't go, Nai Nai.
Don't go. Don't go...
What should I do?
It is three months early,
and there is such severe bleeding.
Your Highness, you mustn't force labor.
If my child cannot be saved,
then don't think of living!
Your Highness, please spare me.
The imperial family is
the root of the Ghost Realm.
If His Majesty learns I used taboo magic
to extend the life of the prince
inside Your Highness's womb
and kept it from His Majesty
I would surely lose my life.
This magic was banned
because it is overly dangerous
and defies the natural order.
Now that Your Highness is
in premature labor
it is sufficiently clear that
you must not defy nature!
Do not save this child. Let it go!
Deliver this baby for me.
No matter what method you use,
you must deliver it from my womb!
He lives, you live.
He dies, you die!
Your Highness!
Congratulations to Crown Prince
on officially receiving the seal.
- Rise.
- Thank you, Your Highness.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
- Your Majesty.
What has you two in such a panic?
You speak first. Has something happened
in the Ghost Realm?
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
Ghost Queen is in labor.
Is that true?
Last night, Ghost Queen ordered me
to come to Celestial Palace
to ask Your Majesty to return.
Let's go!
- Your Majesty.
What has happened?
Ghost Queen suddenly went into
premature labor. It's highly dangerous.
Shaman has given orders that
nobody is to enter.
All right.
I will wait here.
Congratulations on receiving
the seal today, Your Highness.
I think Your Highness
can return tomorrow.
No need.
Nobody is to defy Heavenly Lord's orders.
Very well. Please step up to
the punishment platform, Your Highness.
Subtitles by DramaFever