Subtitles by DramaFever
[Ten Miles of Peach Blossoms]
[Episode 36]
But you don't have to be scared.
Only Xin Nu and I know about this.
We'll think of a way so that you can
become the crown prince's woman.
We'll use a wedding
to cover this matter up.
Are you really going to do that?
Of course. I like you.
Naturally, I'll help you. Don't worry.
Okay.
In any case, it is over.
You may leave.
Thank you for saving my son.
I will repay you one day.
You don't have to.
This was entirely because of
my past relationship with Shao Xing.
It has nothing to do with you.
If you were to come to me
I'm afraid you wouldn't have been
able to make it to the fox den.
You may leave.
Farewell.
Your Majesty, you can't leave me.
I won't leave you.
If you leave...
I'm embarrassing myself again.
Your Majesty, the empress and other
concubines have been waiting a long time.
I should--
If I tell you to stay, you should stay.
How about I bestow you
the title Pure Consort?
Huh?
Your Majesty,
that isn't proper etiquette.
Is it rare for things in my harem
to not follow proper etiquette?
What is your name?
Xiao Jiu.
Then I'll call you Jiu'er
from now on, okay?
Okay.
The sun has set.
That girl should be normal.
Come here.
Master, do you want to eat dinner?
Take me to Handan Quarters.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Master, I have something
to discuss with you.
Can you go over there with me?
Master, look at this.
Master, look. Isn't it cute?
- A sealed-soul bell?
- Yes.
My previous master gave this to me.
It's always just sitting there.
There was not much use for it.
So I put it on Xiao Guai Guai.
It's a pity that the one in your
hands already has an owner.
If you keep it, it will cause trouble
if its owner looks for it.
That's why I wanted to
discuss it with you.
You're very capable.
Can you help me to keep Xiao Guai Guai?
I am a mortal.
I have a limited life here.
But when I return to the immortal world
I'll give Xiao Guai Guai
back to its owner.
No, High God! No!
Master, see? Xiao Guai Guai is really
excited that I'm taking care of it.
Since you call me master,
I should help you.
Fine. I'll talk to its master for you.
It shouldn't be hard
to let it stay here.
Really?
Master, you're agreeing to help me!
I'm not dreaming, right?
What are you two doing?
It's a new moon tonight and it's windy.
You two should come down
so that you don't scare others to death.
Live deities! I'm actually
seeing live deities!
This is my first time
seeing live deities.
Are you two coming here so late at night
because my father is a wise and kind
ruler who is about to go to heaven?
I'm afraid I'll have to disappoint you.
I'm here to see my wife.
Here... Here to see me?
In any case, I should leave you now.
See your wife?
You do not have to worry.
I erased his memory.
Luckily, because of your skills
Yuan Zhen's fate
was transferred perfectly.
But Dijun's fate was slightly changed.
I ask that you lead the way.
I need to find Feng Jiu
to ask for her help.
You're asking her to lead the way?
You'd be looking all night and you still
wouldn't be able to find Feng Jiu.
You should ask an earth deity.
Star Lord.
Take us to Handan Quarters.
Yes.
Wait.
My magic powers are sealed.
Can you use your magic to
send my disciple to his palace?
Qian Qian, you treat
my cousin quite well.
He's my only disciple.
Then he can't address me as cousin.
He'll have to address me
as master's husband.
Why are you taking advantage of this?
You still harbor hurt feelings because
he took liberties with your consort?
If you hadn't brought it up
I would've forgotten why he was
punished to the mortal realm.
For taking liberties with a consort
who's not really a consort
he was punished to the
mortal realm for 60 years.
Then how should he be punished for
holding my wife's hands before my eyes?
Let's go.
You said you came here to see your wife.
Why are you in such a hurry to
see Feng Jiu?
Si Ming came to fix
Dong Hua Dijun's fate.
I just came along to come see you.
To see me?
Today, His Highness called me
out of the Feast of Peaches
just so he could see how you had others
push Dijun into the water.
When Dijun finds out in the future,
I'm afraid he'll kick me down here.
When that time comes
the crown prince will plea
on your behalf.
Little Princess Feng Jiu and
Dijun's fate have come together.
This is the reason why
I've come to ask for your help.
What does this have to do with Feng Jiu?
Please come with me.
Then you will understand.
This way.
Your Highness, High Goddess, Star Lord.
This is Handan Quarters.
I will take my leave now.
Okay. Go on.
Since His Highness has already
broken the seal on your powers
let's secretly head inside.
Yu Dang, guests are here. Pour some tea.
Little brat, turn around.
Aunt.
I've embarrassed myself today.
It's okay since you're using
Honored Lady Chen's mortal body.
You're not embarrassing Qing Qiu.
I won't tell your father.
But I messed up Dijun's fate.
His time and his life as well.
Why is His Highness here too?
Does my father know?
Star Lord Si Ming and I hurried over
here because we saw that you messed up.
Besides the people here,
no one else knows.
Don't worry.
Aunt, what do I do?
When Dijun was in a coma today,
he kept holding on to my hand.
When he woke up,
his eyes kept starring at me.
They were filled with such emotion
that tears were about to come out.
Did you see wrong?
Maybe it's because he was
in the water for too long
that it looked like tears.
But he said that he would
promote my rank.
You saved his life.
He should do that.
Little Princess, you mean Dijun
has already fallen for you?
Si Ming! What rotten fate
have you created.
Since Dijun has already fallen for you
then I can only ask that you go
along with this act with him.
What act?
Originally, he was to fall for
the woman who fell into the water.
But now, you'll have to play that part.
You're not going to help me think
of a way to get out of this?
Instead, you want me to
stay to continue this act?
Some friend you are.
Little Princess, you're the one
who messed up his fate.
I don't care. In any case, I don't want
to go to Taichen Palace anymore.
Actually, it's not Xiao Jiu's fault.
Maybe things turned out like this
because I altered Yuan Zhen's fate.
Since Little Princess is involved in this
if Dijun's fate goes
through a huge change
it'll be hard for her to avoid disaster.
The method I mentioned
just now is the only way.
It'll continue Dijun's love fate and
help Little Princess avoid disaster.
Looks like there's no other way.
Then...
Then how do I continue this fate for him?
That's easy.
You just have to first give Dijun
a sweet taste of something.
Once you have a hold on his heart
and he becomes devoted to you
take out his heart and
trample it again and again.
You want me to trample on his heart?
When the time comes,
I'll give you the script.
It'll teach you how to
trample on his heart.
Aunt.
Your Highness.
How can I repay for
his kindness this way?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
I've broken your Two Lives Curse.
You can slowly repay his kindness.
Your Majesty.
You're not asleep yet?
I can't fall asleep.
I can't fall asleep either.
I just wanted to come see you.
If you were asleep
I would just stay here to look at
the place where you sleep.
It's very late at night.
You should come in.
I still have some things to take care of.
You should go back to Qing Qiu tomorrow.
I'll come see you in a few days.
Please don't be offended.
We snuck out of the Feast of Peaches,
so we have to hurry back.
I will take my leave.
Jiu'er, you're still not going to sleep?
I had such a scare today,
maybe that's why I can't fall asleep.
Then I'll play go with you.
I don't really know how to play.
No matter what you do,
I'll just give you your way.
First you have to first give Dijun
a taste of something sweet.
Once you have a hold on his heart
and he becomes devoted to you
take out his heart and
trample on it again and again.
A taste of something sweet?
Back when I was in the Celestial Palace,
I couldn't get any part of his heart.
Now... what do I do now?
Jiu'er.
Huh?
When did you enter the palace?
When I was 17 years old.
When I was in my resting quarters,
I was trying to recall how we first met
but I couldn't remember anything.
Even though you're already
an honored lady
and you have already slept with me
I can't remember the night
when you first became my wife.
Do you hate me for it?
I wouldn't dare.
You have many things to deal with.
What is Your Majesty looking at?
I heard from the empress that
I doted on you back then
because you were excellent at go.
What?
After falling into the water,
you forgot how to play go?
Maybe Her Highness was mistaken.
My expertise is in cooking, not games.
Oh?
Then when I wake up tomorrow, will I be
able to eat a meal that you've cooked?
Your Majesty, you're really
going to spend the night here?
Is something inappropriate about that?
No.
Do you blame me for giving you
the cold shoulder back then?
You have many things to deal with.
How could I dare to--
Is that all you know how to say?
What should I do?
The people of Qing Qiu have
always been simple and honest
and only come together
through mutual consent
if Father finds out that Dijun and I...
I'll give you a wedding ceremony.
I'll marry you again in a ceremony
according to commoner traditions.
Your Majesty, to do this
without conforming to palace rules...
If Her Highness finds out,
I'm afraid she'll blame me.
No one in this palace will ever dare
to make things hard for you again.
Crown Prince. Third Prince...
The message you gave Bai Feng Jiu
was full of mistakes.
Are you hiding something from me?
Since you've seen through me,
I'll just tell you.
Dong Hua Dijun went to the
mortal realm to repay her debt of love.
Debt of love?
When Bai Feng Jiu was at Taichen Palace,
she was deeply in love.
But Dijun and Bai Feng Jiu
aren't fated to be.
So Dijun went to the mortal
realm to give her a mortal love.
But this fate will only
last a mortal's lifetime.
Nothing will come out of it.
So this time, you fulfilled
Qian Qian's wish to help Yuan Zhen
and the wish of making Dong Hua Dijun
and Bai Feng Jiu fated to be.
Fortunately Bai Qian came up with this.
Otherwise, I'd have to think of
another way to make the
mortal Dijun fall for Bai Feng Jiu.
Your Highness.
I have results for what
you had me investigate.
Tell me.
Those ambushed immortals
don't have much in common except...
they're all of high immortal rank.
High immortal rank?
Aunt, you're back.
Mi Gu, without me sending
you on errands these days
you've been living quite freely.
Aunt, you came back yesterday
and took care of something big.
Why are you saying it
like you just came back?
I was still in the mortal realm
yesterday. When did I come back?
That's not right. You came back...
I think you told me to stay at Fox Den
and not go anywhere else.
Who put an enchanting spell on you?
Enchanting spell?
There's no enchanting spell.
What happened?
Aunt, you're finally back!
Something horrible happened.
Xuan Nu took on your appearance
and took away Mo Yuan's body
and Imperial great-grandson!
Fan, I'm afraid you'll get a taste
of blood again today.
Aunt!
Why am I so inept?
How could I let her go alone?
What should I do?
Crown Prince. Yes, Crown Prince!
Celestial high immortals
keep getting killed.
It must be because of that sick child
born to the ghost queen.
What?
It's a sinister kind of magic.
In the ancient times,
there was a woman named Jie Yu.
Because her murder aura was too strong
all the children she birthed were ill.
So she came up with an idea.
She murdered high immortals
and turned their bodies into an elixir
for her sick children to take.
Her children were able to recover.
How could such vicious magic exist?
To be able to control so many puppets
and to have the audacity
to kill high immortals...
I don't think it's Ghost Lord Li Jing.
Rather, it must be
the Ghost Queen Xuan Nu
who betrayed Kunlun Mountain and
the Celestial Tribe 70,000 years ago.
If it's Xuan Nu's doing, Li Jing must be
somewhat responsible as well.
I'll go and report this
to Father right now.
Third Uncle, wait.
This is a huge matter between two tribes.
We can't come to a conclusion
solely from my speculation.
Wait until I go to Grand Ziming Palace
to investigate.
Okay. Then let's go together
after the Feast of Peaches.
This entrance to the palace was
heavily guarded 70,000 years ago.
But today, no one is here to guard it?
Xuan Nu, are you inviting me in?
Your Highness, Qing Qiu's
Mi Gu would like to see you.
Bring him in.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, please help Aunt.
She went to Grand Ziming Palace
all alone.
What did you say?
The Ghost Queen stole High God Mo Yuan's
body and Imperial Great-Grandson.
Aunt's eyes were red with
fury and went over there.
Your Highness...
Who is that tree spirit?
How dare he intrude
during the Feast of Peaches?
What unacceptable behavior.
See? Because of that woman
His Highness doesn't respect
Celestial customs.
If you really marry into
Xiwu Palace in the future
you must not be that way.
Yes.
Jade Purity Fan of Kunlun!
Go back to the palace!
Qian Qian, I trust you've been well
since we last met 70,000 years ago.
I heard His Majesty say that Si Yin
is a woman from the fox tribe
so I guessed it was you.
When I first saw Si Yin
at Kunlun Mountain, I was stunned
that someone else in this world
resembles Qian Qian more than I do.
You say you resemble me?
Did you forget what
you used to look like?
It just so happens that Zhe Yan of the
Ten Miles of Peach Woods
has had a lot of free time lately.
Why don't we invite him over
to help you remember?
No matter what you say,
I will take your life today.
Then no one would look the same as me.
Yesterday, I took Mo Yuan's
body and your son.
I knew you'd come find me.
I've been waiting here
for you the whole time.
You've been preserving
Mo Yuan's body quite well.
I'm really happy about it.
My son will get
High God Mo Yuan's vitality.
Because of your contributions,
I'll have them kill you quickly.
That depends on whether
you have the ability to do so.
Her eyes aren't good.
Is she afraid of the light?
What a blessing.
Seeing you covered in wounds
really makes my heart ache for you.
Who will you call upon to save you now?
Since things have come to this,
I'll tell you this.
Back then, I used your face to get
His Majesty to sleep with me.
So what if you can take on my appearance?
You're just deceiving yourself.
I've loved His Majesty for thousands of
years, yet he can't forget about you.
Today, I'll take your life.
Then, I'll be the only one
in the world with this face.
Naturally, His Majesty
will protect me forever.
Let me tell you something, Xuan Nu.
As a high goddess,
even if I close my eyes
I'll still be able to wipe out
these useless people by your side.
Kill her for me.
Qian Qian.
If you came an hour earlier,
I wouldn't have been injured like this.
I'm sorry for coming late.
Tell me who injured you.
I've already killed everyone
who injured me.
That woman is the only one left.
Do you want to take care of it yourself
or do you want me to help you?
She humiliated my master
and hurt my loved ones.
I will finish her myself.
- A-Yin?
- Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I'm Xuan Nu.
Why do you look just like A-Yin?
Exactly the same, right?
Your Majesty, if we just
kill that wench Bai Qian
then I'll be the only one
in this world with this face.
If you like it,
you can stare at me all day.
I'll also keep protecting you.
You... What's going on?
That woman took my master and your son.
He's also your son.
Son?
Your Majesty, our son will
get better soon.
Really.
Look. Look at Mo Yuan.
We'll turn him into an elixir.
You Majesty, you were jealous of
Mo Yuan in the past, right?
You don't have to be jealous any more.
Our son will have
Mo Yuan's vitality soon.
Shut your mouth.
Am I wrong?
You didn't give the soul jade
to Bai Qian back then
because you were
jealous of Mo Yuan, right?
Your Majesty, you don't know yet, do you?
She is Si Yin.
Xuan Nu, let me tell you something.
My master's body is extremely precious.
It's received blood from
my heart for 70,000 years.
I'm afraid your son won't
be able to handle that.
Blood from your heart?
You mean...
Li Jing, let's not talk about
your past for the time being.
I want to ask you how you plan
on taking care of today's matters.
Do you want to do it
privately or publicly?
What happens if it's private?
What happens if it's public?
If privately, then pull the limbs of
and skin your ghost queen
who doesn't know her place,
to alleviate my anger.
If publicly, the Celestial soldiers
haven't fought a battle in a long time.
They have a lot of free time.
We can use this opportunity to see
whose army has been training better
after all these years.
Your Majesty, are you really going
to punish me that harshly?
No, right?
Your Majesty, did you forget?
Did you forget all the
things I've done for you?
Without me, would you be ghost lord?
He wouldn't dare to deploy troops!
He wouldn't dare.
Don't think I don't know that you
wouldn't dare to deploy troops.
You don't have that power!
You're just the Celestial Crown Prince.
Heavenly Lord wouldn't agree to deploy
the troops for the sake of one woman.
I'm not deploying troops
for the sake of one woman.
High God Mo Yuan is a highly-respected
God of the Celestial Tribe.
High Goddess Bai Qian
is the future Heavenly Empress.
And A-Li will succeed
my position in the future.
Right now, these three people
have suffered extraordinary
humiliation at Grand Ziming Palace.
Do you think the Celestial soldiers
will just let this slide?
Xuan Nu was always a little crazy.
Otherwise, she wouldn't have
made such a grave mistake.
Your Majesty.
I ask that Your Highness show mercy.
Qian Qian.
Do you think we should show mercy?
Celestial Crown Prince, so much for
you treating that wench Bai Qian so well.
You don't know, do you?
She and her master...
Qian Qian said her face
looks like yours...
But I don't see any similarities at all.
I didn't mind giving you
my appearance back then.
But now that I see you
using this appearance
it really makes me unhappy.
What are you going to do?
What are you trying to do?
I've always had this appearance.
Don't even think about
taking away my beauty!
I wouldn't be scared of you even
if you brought Zhe Yan here.
Why would I bring Zhe Yan here?
I was just joking with you back then.
Did you really think Zhe Yan
is the only one in the world
who can use magic to change appearances?
I'm not talented but I had nothing to do
these past 70,000 years
so I became proficient
at this kind of magic.
If you're really going to be skinned
and have your limbs pulled
you shouldn't have this appearance
while going through that.
What are you going to do? No! No!
No!
Go take a good look at your face.
I told you
if you use Zhe Yan's
magic to do evil deeds
it'll come back to bite you.
Qian Qian, can you take care of yourself?
If you can't, just sleep for a bit.
Li Jing.
You do as you see fit.
Why did this happen?
This is what I look like!
I don't want to see this face!
I don't want to!
Subtitles by DramaFever