Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 23]
Ye Hua.
Ye Hua?
Are you asleep?
No.
Is Nai Nai in your room?
Nai Nai is already in bed.
I heard from Nai Nai that...
The battle in Far North is dire.
Are you all right?
I'm doing very well.
We...
We haven't seen each other
for half a year.
Ye Hua.
Listen.
The baby... has been moving around
a lot these days.
Sometimes, I can feel
his hands and feet.
I don't want him to be born too soon.
I'm worried that you won't
get to see him be born.
Ye Hua, I'd like to know...
That day...
At the Lakes of the Far East...
The oath that we made...
Does that still count?
I want to wait until our child is born
to tell him the story of his parents.
Then he will know what
his father has on his mind.
It does count.
I know now.
Take care.
I await your return.
Little chap.
Your father will soon
return to the palace.
You have to grow slowly.
Then he can see you when you're born.
That would be the best.
My prince, great victory!
Keep talking.
Ghost Lord Li Jing made use
of the freezing weather
and transported much ice upstream.
Then he used his powers to melt the ice.
Then he borrowed the Celestial Tribe's
powers of rain and thunder
to create rainfall
for three days and nights.
It caused great flooding
across the lands of the Far North.
Our enemies were defeated
without a fight.
This is...
That is to say...
Not only did it take out all the rebels
but also the creatures
of the Ghost Realm are...
Indeed.
He is indeed Qing Cang's son.
The Ghost Realm isn't the territory
of the Celestial Tribe.
We deployed our army to assist the
Ghost Tribe in pacifying their rebels.
However, I find it hard
to accept such a method!
Split the army into five troops.
Send one to the flooded areas
and save as many as possible.
As for the other four, set out
as agreed with the Ghost Lord
to seal off the four routes
of the Far North.
Intercept and defeat the enemy.
- Yes!
Li Yuan!
Tens of thousands of years went by.
Who knew that we would meet again
in combat after all these years?
Li Jing.
You're so ruthless.
You've disregarded the lives of thousands
of creatures in the Ghost Realm.
You collaborated with the Celestial Tribe
to wipe them out!
You're wrong!
You're the one who harmed them.
If you hadn't asked them to support you
they wouldn't have died so tragically.
Yan Zhi.
Since Father was sealed
how have I treated you?
Brother Li Jing...
Why have you chosen to assist that man?
Brother Li Jing.
I... I don't wish to go
against either of you.
I don't want either of you dead.
All these years, I've stayed by Li Yuan's
side so that he wouldn't hurt you.
- Take them down!
- Yes!
Li Jing! If you want to kill me
do so yourself!
How dare you send
such lowly subordinates?
I don't want you dead.
My brother.
Fine!
I'll take you to Father then!
Brother Li Yuan! You promised!
You said that you wouldn't
attack Brother Li Jing!
Get lost!
Brother Li Yuan!
Golden Lion!
My princess...
You have lived up to
my expectations after all.
All of you have worked hard.
Great blessings to the Heavenly Lord!
You're blessed by the Heavenly Father!
Consort!
Consort.
The Crown Prince has returned
to the palace in victory.
He's discussing matters with
the Heavenly Lord now.
Deliver this card to
the Hall of Beautiful Youth now.
Tell the lady that she's been invited
to Lotus Pond to admire flowers
and most female family members
of the Celestial Palace will attend.
Should any guards outside
the Hall of Beautiful Youth keep you out
tell them that the Heavenly Lord
has lifted the house arrest.
Yes, Consort.
This is an invitation from
Consort Su Jin.
She's invited female family members of
the Celestial Palace to admire flowers.
The Heavenly Lord has agreed to let the
Hall of Beautiful Youth's lady attend.
This is...
If you don't believe me, you may check.
Please enter, Fairy.
My lady, walk more slowly.
I'm getting bigger now.
It wears me out just to take a few steps.
You are due soon.
You could have turned
the invitation down.
Why would you insist on
coming to Lotus Pond?
All female family members in
the Celestial Palace are attending.
I'm Ye Hua's wife.
How could I not attend?
Lady Su Su is the only female family
member in Xiwu Palace.
You and the Crown Prince
were married in the Far East.
They have to acknowledge that.
Lady Su Su is the Crown Prince's wife.
Su Su.
How unfortunate.
I heard that Ye Hua has just
returned to the palace.
The Heavenly Lord has just
canceled the gathering.
Everyone has gone to welcome Ye Hua.
Ye Hua has already returned?
Exactly.
I'm waiting right here
to bring you over to him.
Great. Please take me to him now.
Let's go.
- Consort.
Let go of me!
Have you forgotten who you are?
A celestial maid from the Lower Realm
has the lowest rank.
How dare you speak
before Consort Su Jin?
Lady Su Su is pregnant.
She can't go to a place with
a malicious aura like Zhuxian Terrace.
Lady Su Su!
My Lady!
What is going on?
Let's go.
But...
Why would Father suddenly
give Su Jin to you?
How is this a gift?
He's deliberately forcing you
to have her!
This can't be that simple.
Congratulations, Your Highness!
Not only did you defeat the rebels
but you also won yourself a beauty!
Your Highness should treat the heir
of a loyal tribe kindly.
Your Highness, I...
Your Highness!
Consort Su Jin has had
an argument with Lady Su Su.
No, that isn't true!
Your Highness!
Do you know that the Heavenly Lord is
hosting a conferring ceremony for Ye Hua?
He's going to make me Ye Hua's concubine.
Ye Hua and I share mutual affections.
The Nine Heavens were never meant
for a woman like you.
After you give birth to the child,
jump off Zhuxian Terrace.
Head back to where you should.
Does Ye Hua want me to leave?
I am his wife.
I should stay by his side.
You really think so?
Ye Hua!
Ye Hua...
Don't blame Su Su.
I believe that she didn't
mean to push me.
It's just that she's heard about
the Heavenly Lord's decision
to give me to you.
She became too agitated.
Ye Hua...
I didn't push her.
- I didn't push her.
- Ye Hua...
- Believe me.
- Crown Prince!
- Ye Hua, believe me!
I didn't push her, Ye Hua!
I really didn't push her!
- Believe me!
- That's enough!
I only believe what I saw.
I didn't push her!
Ye Hua...
Ye Hua!
I didn't push her.
Take her back
to the Hall of Beautiful Youth.
She's not to go anywhere
without my permission.
Lady Su Su.
I didn't push her...
Ye Hua.
Do you know how happy I was
when I heard
the Heavenly Lord's decision
to give me to you?
I've already sent for the Medicine King.
Don't say another word.
Su Jin!
Uncle.
What exactly happened?
When I got there, I witnessed Su Jin
feign a conflict with Su Su.
She pretended to be pushed
by Su Su and jumped down to frame her.
Su Jin jumped?
If I had know, I'd have held
the generals off.
If accused of pushing
the Heavenly Lord's concubine
off Zhuxian Terrace,
that woman will be killed!
What do you intend to do?
What else can I do, Uncle Lian Song?
If I speak up for Su Su
the Heavenly Lord will be more inclined
to sentence her to death!
But you...
- Heavenly Lord.
- Father.
- Medicine King.
- Yes.
What happened?
Why are the consort's eyes hurt?
Heavenly Lord.
Heavenly Lord, Her Highness
was going to treat the female members
of the Celestial Palace to a banquet.
However, the Crown Prince returned
so she canceled the banquet.
Who knew...
Who knew that mortal from
the Hall of Beautiful Youth
would take her to Zhuxian Terrace?
I don't know what she said to the consort
but she suddenly pushed
Her Highness over the edge.
Fortunately, the Crown Prince
arrived in time.
Her Highness managed
to survive the accident.
What?
That woman dared to harm the consort?
How outrageous!
Consort Su Jin is the heir
of a loyal tribe.
All of her tribesmen sacrificed
for the Celestial Tribe.
Even us, the commanders of the sub-tribes
and even the Heavenly Lord treats her
kindly with great care.
That mere mortal!
How dare she push the consort
off Zhuxian Terrace?
Heavenly Lord!
Crown Prince!
That mortal must not be spared.
She must be pushed off Zhuxian Terrace.
Only when her soul disintegrates
can it make up for Su Jin's eyes!
Exactly!
That mortal must not be spared!
Heavenly Lord.
That mortal is carrying
the Crown Prince's child.
She must have found out that
Su Jin has been given to Ye Hua
and pushed her by accident?
By accident?
Do you call this an accident?
Look at her!
Take a good look at her!
The consort's eyes are ruined!
Uncles...
Don't...
Don't be angry at that mortal.
After all, she is already pregnant
with the Crown Prince's child.
She didn't mean to do this to me.
You don't have to say a word.
I'll uphold justice for you.
Heavenly Lord!
Ye Hua.
Su Jin is the heir of a loyal tribe.
The Celestial Tribe
should treat her kindly.
However, she has now been
severely injured by Su Su.
If this matter isn't handled well,
my officials might be disheartened.
How do you think Su Su
should be punished to appease everyone
and to uphold justice for Su Jin?
Nai Nai...
You must testify for me.
I didn't push her.
She set me up for all of this.
Lady Su Su...
When I got to Zhuxian Terrace
Consort Su Jin was already
in the Crown Prince's arms.
Do you also think that I pushed her?
No, I'd never think that you did that!
Lady Su Su...
You witnessed it last time.
Even if I testify for you,
no one will believe me.
You're right.
Even if you could testify for me...
no one would believe you.
Even Ye Hua doesn't believe me.
Why would the others?
Ye Hua and Su Jin
are childhood sweethearts.
He loves her so deeply.
He surely won't believe me.
Lady Su Su, what are you talking about?
You mustn't say such nonsense.
Su Jin is the Heavenly Lord's concubine.
She won't be. Not for long.
What did you say?
She's been given to Ye Hua
as his side consort.
What?
I didn't push her.
Ye Hua won't just believe
her side of the story.
There were so many others around.
So many people witnessed it.
Someone must have seen
that I didn't push her.
It wasn't me.
It shouldn't...
Lady Su Su!
What's wrong?
Is anyone out there?
Lady Su Su!
What's wrong?
Heavenly Lord is right.
I didn't see very clearly either.
I only heard from the consort
that Su Su didn't do it intentionally.
Although it wasn't intentional...
the consort's eyes were still injured.
As a mortal, she pushed
a celestial consort off Zhuxian Terrace.
Su Su's action is not to be condoned.
I wonder if it would appease everyone
to hand over Su Su's eyes
and be struck
by lightning for three years?
The Crown Prince's
suggestion sounds good.
The Celestial Consort did say that
the mortal pushed her by accident.
We shouldn't be too harsh on her.
Yes.
Indeed. Three years of
lightning torment is harsh enough.
The Crown Prince's suggestion is just.
The Crown Prince is wise!
All right.
That is just fine.
Heavenly Lord.
Su Su once saved my life.
You've taught me that one who doesn't
repay the kindness one receives
isn't a truly righteous man.
Su Su was only brought to
the Celestial Palace because of me.
Now that such an accident has occurred
I should bear the consequences.
Moreover, she is now carrying my child.
Hence...
I ask for your permission to take
the three years of lightning torment
in her stead.
You wish to take on three years
of lightning torment for her?
Exactly.
This is to repay her kindness.
It's also for the sake of my child.
All right.
I will agree to it.
Thank you, Heavenly Lord.
I will have her eyes taken out today.
The Medicine King will have
those eyes implanted into Su Jin.
Head over to Jade Manor.
Be prepared to take on
the lightning torment.
Lord Pu Hua is righteous and just.
He won't be lenient just
because you're the Crown Prince.
Bear this in mind.
Three years...
Not even one day less.
I understand.
I still have one last favor
to ask of the Heavenly Lord.
Please allow me to remove
Su Su eyes personally.
What?
You want to do it?
Since you insist on doing it...
I will allow it.
I'll abide by your decree.
Is my mistress all right?
She is fine.
Fortunately, the little prince is fine.
Lady Su Su is also doing well.
That's good.
Ye Hua.
- Greetings, Crown Prince.
- Ye Hua.
Believe me.
Step out.
Yes.
Ye Hua, you do believe me, don't you?
You know that I didn't push her.
I would never push her.
You believe me.
That's why you've come to see me.
Am I right?
I believe you.
You didn't push her.
She jumped down by herself.
However, Su Jin's eyes were burned
and she's now blind.
The only way to spare you from death...
Is to take your eyes out
to replace hers.
Only then will the Heavenly Lord
be appeased.
Why?
Why would you say such words?
Don't you believe me, Ye Hua?
Why?
Don't come near me!
Su Su...
This is all my fault.
I didn't push her!
It's my fault.
I can't protect you...
Su Su...
I didn't...
I will marry you.
From now on, I will be your eyes.
Ye Hua, don't do this.
Ye Hua, don't do this to me...
Don't...
Don't do this, Ye Hua...
[The Hall of Beautiful Youth]
Don't...
My eyes...
My eyes!
Lady Su Su!
The Medicine King said that
you mustn't get too agitated!
As long... As long as you
recuperate for some time
you will get better.
I will get better?
Will I get better?
Tell me.
What can I do to get better?
My eyes are gone...
How will I get better?
I've lost my eyes...
Crown Prince!
Crown Prince.
I am here to receive
the lightning torment.
Sure.
Three years in total.
49 lightning strikes each day.
Not one fewer.
The lightning won't harm you.
However, every strike of lightning
upon your body
will hurt as if your soul
is being torn apart.
Many deities passed out
from such pain right here.
Your Highness.
Would you like the others to leave?
That's not necessary.
All right.
Crown Prince.
Please get on the platform.
My apologies.
It wasn't me! She jumped off!
It had nothing to do with me!
Why don't you believe me?
I didn't do it!
Why am I the one
to pay the price for it?
Step out.
Yes.
Uncle Lian Song.
Do you think that I'm qualified
to be given
the Crown Prince's Seal after
the battle in the Far North?
You have contributed to
defeating the Mermaid Clan
and pacifying the rebels
in the Far North.
Your reputation is widely known
in all realms and lands.
It's about time the Heavenly Lord
gives the seal to you.
However, you're now wounded.
If given the Crown Prince's Seal
you must be tested with 36 bursts
of sacred blaze
and 9 holy lightning strikes.
I'm worried that you might not survive.
Do I appear to be that weak to you?
Since I was appointed the apparent heir
how am I to have all realms obey me
if I can't even survive
36 bursts of sacred blaze
and 9 holy lightning strikes?
I'll be honest with you.
You were severely wounded
in the Chang Sea.
This test will be tough for you.
It matters not.
Why are you so anxious?
Can't you wait for a while?
I had thought that by staying away from
the Hall of Beautiful Youth
and pretending not to care
about her when others are around
that I would be able to keep her alive.
Hence, I didn't dare to marry her.
I just wanted her
to give birth to our child
and then send her back
to the Mortal Realm safely.
However, I came to my senses today.
I was wrong to think that.
I was so terribly wrong.
No matter what I do...
the Heavenly Lord will have her killed.
You're right.
The Heavenly Lord got scared after
what my second brother did.
He doesn't dare take any risk.
After all, you're the Crown Prince.
You matter even more to
the Celestial Tribe than Sang Ji.
Therefore...
Once I'm given the Crown Prince's Seal
I will officially become
the apparent heir.
By then, I won't have to worry
about anyone else.
I can then marry Su Su as my consort.
You're going to marry her
in the Celestial Palace?
Exactly.
I will announce it to
all six realms and lands.
She is to be my side consort!
I'm begging you, Your Highness!
I don't want to leave
the Hall of Beautiful Youth!
I don't want to leave!
The Heavenly Lord
has had all celestial maids
who witnessed this accident
removed from the Celestial Palace.
It was done to cover up
such a shameful scandal
so it will not be an embarrassment
to the Celestial Tribe.
My mistress is due any moment now.
And now she has lost her eyes!
No one else in the Nine Heavens
can look after her.
Please allow me to stay in
the Hall of Beautiful Youth!
Let me stay until my mistress
delivers her baby.
I'm begging you, Your Highness!
Who would have known
that there was such a loyal servant
in the Hall of Beautiful Youth?
Listen up.
Once you get to Deity Mountain
in the Lower Realm
you have to bury this accident
deep in your heart.
Not a word is to be said.
Have you all kept that in mind?
We understand.
Why are so many celestial maids
being dismissed?
Has something serious happened?
A serious matter? Indeed.
It's said that the Crown Prince's mortal,
Su Su, had a conflict with Su Jin.
She pushed Su Jin off Zhuxian Terrace.
The Crown Prince later removed
Su Su's eyes to replace Su Jin's.
Why would the Crown Prince
do that to Su Su?
The Heavenly Lord intends
to cover up this accident.
Therefore, he's sent all maids and guards
who witnessed the accident
to the Lower Realm.
The ones you saw
should be the last batch.
Why would he cover this up?
I'm not sure about the details.
However, Dong Hua did say that
the Hall of Beautiful Youth
is now the most scandalous place
in the Nine Heavens.
Nothing could escape the eyes
of old Lord Dong Hua.
Little Princess, where are you going?
This is bad.
Could she be going to
the Hall of Beautiful Youth?
Who is it?
It's me. Don't you recognize me anymore?
Little fox?
You've been so cautious here
in the Celestial Palace.
You were nice to everyone
for the sake of that Crown Prince.
How could you possibly push
Su Jin off Zhuxian Terrace?
Have you come to visit me
because you know that I've lost my eyes?
Do you know that in the Nine Heavens
he was once my one and only?
I keep thinking that
after I give birth to our child
we can go and watch the billows
of the Ten-mile Sea of Clouds together.
Watch as rays of sunlight
come shining through.
However, I've now lost my eyes.
What can I still see?
Little fox?
Your eyesight means nothing to him.
Su Jin?
Subtitles by DramaFever