Subtitles by DramaFever
[Ten Miles of Peach Blossoms]
[Episode 35]
Qian Qian, I haven't seen you in days.
I missed you terribly.
Have you missed me?
I came to tell you some important news.
Do you know who reincarnated into
Yuan Zhen's father in this lifetime?
Could it be your grandfather?
It isn't my grandfather,
but that is close.
Then...
Lord Shaoyang of Dong Hua Zi Manor.
Dong Hua Dijun?
Could Xiao Jiu have--
I'm going to close the window.
Are you sleeping on
the inside or the outside of the bed?
I'll... sleep on the floor.
Qian Qian, if you sleep on the floor
or the bed tonight
the end result will be the same.
If you had any magic power
you could fight me
then we'd both end up wounded.
But haven't I already
sealed away your powers?
Or perhaps, are you only
putting on a show of reluctance?
Lord Ye Hua, you must be joking.
I'm just afraid the bed is too small.
I don't want to be a bad host.
I'm used to sleeping on the outside.
Are there really roc birds
in the mortal realm?
The roc bird was borrowed from Buddha.
My second uncle and Si Ming
had grudges.
Si Ming has put a lot of energy
and effort into this.
I didn't expect Star Lord Si Ming
would be so vengeful.
He planned such an elaborate scenario.
If I ruin his plans,
won't he bear a grudge against me?
Qian Qian, don't you worry.
He still owes me a big favor.
Do you want me to
hold you while you sleep?
As I expected.
I know you move around in your sleep,
so that's why I said I'd hold you.
The bed is too small.
Yes, it is indeed.
Qian Qian.
Do you know the immortal Si Yin?
I've... heard of him but never met him.
Didn't he retire and go into seclusion
with High God Mo Yuan?
I thought you would know more.
I don't know any more.
Ghost Lord Li Jing
made a painting of Si Yin
and has been searching for
Si Yin's whereabouts in private.
The painting landed in my possession.
I took a quick look.
And noticed it looked like
you dressed as a man.
It must be a coincidence.
It's getting late. Go to sleep.
Third Prince, are you also
going to the Feast of Peaches?
Excuse me, excuse me.
I don't know why
I've been doing that all day.
It seems someone is talking about you
behind your back again, Si Ming.
How can that be?
Such an easygoing, idle deity like me
wouldn't be the subject of any gossip.
Where is the Crown Prince?
I had seen he was here just now.
He's thinking about
a certain high goddess.
He snuck off to the mortal realm
while everyone is making a toast.
He'll be back in
a half a cup of tea's time.
Qian Qian, come bind my hair for me.
Are you talking to me?
Mi Gu said that you are
quite good at combing hair.
I have an audience with
the Heavenly Lord today.
It wouldn't be good to look disheveled.
All done.
In the past, you...
It's nothing.
Qian Qian.
Carry this string of beads.
You are no different from a mortal now.
It is unlikely that
you will encounter any danger
but it is still good to take precautions.
I'll return to the Celestial Palace now.
Oh, last night, I was so busy
that I forgot to tell you
on the first of the sixth month,
hold Yuan Zhen back
and then send someone to
push Dong Hua Dijun into the water.
This way, you can protect Yuan Zhen
and you won't be
hindering Dong Hua Dijun
from experiencing the
hardships of life.
This way, everyone will be satisfied.
All right.
What serious matters
was he busy with last night?
I nearly forgot about Xiao Jiu.
Master.
I was just about to go looking for you.
- Follow me.
- Yes.
Master, what is on your neck over there?
It seems to be...
You noticed such a tiny red scar?
Someone once told me
you are so kind that you wouldn't
even step on an ant on the road.
It seems that is true.
Do you know that to not step
on an ant on the road
not only requires kindness,
but also attentiveness?
Kindness and attentiveness are the same.
Yes.
In this case, I shall test
your attention to detail.
Please proceed, Master.
I know you were living in the Daoist
temple before you were 16 years old.
You only entered the imperial palace
after turning 16 years old.
So, I won't pose any difficulties.
I will only ask you two questions.
One is regarding the Daoist temple,
and the other is regarding the palace.
In the Daoist temple you were living in
there was a nun
who wore white robes.
There was a fly whisk she often used.
What was the fly whisk made out of?
Fly whisk?
You don't need to answer yet.
I'll ask you another question.
In the imperial palace
you are living in now
there is a woman who has a birthmark
of a plumed cockscomb on her forehead.
Where does this woman reside, what is
her position, and what is her name?
Master, I am not well-informed.
While I lived in the temple, I had never
seen the white-robed nun you mentioned.
As for this woman who has
a plumed cockscomb on her forehead
I do know of her.
She is the Honored Lady Chen
who lives in Handan Quarters.
As for Honored Lady Chen's name...
I truly do not know.
Xiao Jiu followed Dong Hua here.
It's already rare for you
to have this level of attentiveness.
However, you must be even more meticulous
as you study Daoism.
You may go for today.
Go and take note of the manner
in which you study.
Yes.
Yuan Zhen, you are actually
meticulous enough.
Any more investigation
and you'd be a nosy man.
Miss.
What orders do you have,
Daoist Master?
Take me to Honored Lady Chen's
Handan Quarters.
Yes, please follow me.
Daoist Master, this is Handan Quarters.
Xiao Jiu, Aunt is here to see you.
Aunt, Aunt!
Aunt, I'm begging you,
don't take me away!
I love him, Aunt! I can't lose him.
I'm begging you, Aunt!
I'm begging you!
I'll do anything to repay you
in the next life!
Please let me be with him!
Aunt, I'm begging you.
With this crazy behavior
could she have used
the Two Lives Curse on herself?
Please, I'm begging you.
I'll repay you any way I can.
Someone come!
Help Honored Lady Chen inside.
- Yes.
Why did Xiao Jiu use
the Two Lives Curse for no reason?
Aunt, please don't take me away.
I want to be with His Majesty
for all lifetimes.
Aunt! Aunt!
Wait, why did Aunt come here?
If Aunt knows I used the Two Lives Curse,
wouldn't she drag me back to Qing Qiu?
Then how will I repay my debt?
My queen, aren't they respected members
of the Celestial Tribe?
Why would they be in our palace?
Because I am going to use
their bodies to save my child.
Your Highness, it was already
a capital offense to use puppets
to kill high immortals
of the Celestial Tribe.
If His Majesty were to
know of today's events
wouldn't you be adding to your crimes?
Your Highness, quickly return them!
Shut your mouth. Who are you to
tell me what to do, you lowly servant?
- Your Highness, do not be angry!
- Guards.
Take this lowly servant
to the water dungeon.
- Yes.
And summon the generals in.
- Your Highness, I won't do it again!
Your Highness, I won't do it again!
Your Highness!
I really like this body.
- Greetings, Your Highness.
- Greetings, Your Highness...
Come have a look.
- High God Mo Yuan?
Your Highness, hasn't he been missing
for over 70,000 years?
I will explain this to you in a few days.
I summoned you here to tell you
to prepare the elixir chamber.
I am going to use the furnace.
And use Mo Yuan's body to make
an elixir for my son's recovery.
- That's...
- Elixir?
That's correct.
In a few days, my son will possess
the vitality of
the Celestial Tribe's God of War.
Don't you all find it amusing?
Aunt, unfilial daughter Feng Jiu
has come to beg for forgiveness.
You've really used the Two Lives Curse?
You are wise, Aunt.
Sit down and talk.
Since you've come to repay a debt
why did you use
the Two Lives Curse on yourself?
A while ago, I entered Dijun's dream
to ask him if he has
any unfulfilled wishes
or any unattainable infatuation.
What did the stone-faced Dijun say?
Don't tell me he said
he doesn't want any riches
or to conquer the world,
but only to win someone's heart?
You are wise, Aunt.
Dong Hua Dijun is
so unambitious in this lifetime.
It must be because he experienced
the fickleness of human relationships
in his early years in the mortal realm
and thus, wishes for a woman
who would never leave him.
So, you inserted yourself?
I didn't throw myself in.
It was just that Star Lord Si Ming said
Dijun didn't encounter a woman he loves.
But on the first of the sixth month,
he will encounter a woman he adores
yet the one the woman loves
is Crown Prince Yuan Zhen.
Yuan Zhen?
So, I wanted to offer him
my heartfelt affections.
When Dijun encounters the one he loves
I would leave with my work
having been done here.
I had thought this was a great plan
but after borrowing
Honored Lady Chen's body
I couldn't say any affectionate words
when I saw Dijun.
Dying embers are not easily rekindled.
Don't brood over it.
That's why I could only use
the Two Lives Curse on myself.
During the day, I am able to
adore Dijun very much.
When the sun sets,
I can be free of such a task.
Were you taken advantage of by Dijun?
Dong Hua Dijun only visited
Handan Quarters once
but he left after some time.
Look at you.
Everyday, you make yourself
love him so desperately.
Why are you doing this?
I just think loving someone is an act
that requires dedication.
It is pretending not to be in love
when others are looking
but being in love
when others aren't looking.
Never mind. You should just go.
You can continue offering
your heart to him.
When you were in Qing Qiu, you lived
such a free and unrestrained life.
Look, now you're feeding fish in this
place, all for Dong Hua Dijun.
What can you say?
It seems Zizhu Quarters
is a place for immortals.
You came back?
There's something I forgot to tell you.
The day after you left for
the Eastern Sea banquet
Heavenly Lord's grandson, Ye Hua,
came to see me in the Peach Tree Woods
and asked me things about you
from 300 years ago.
I told him that after
your battle with Qing Cang
you slept for a long time
before waking up.
He left and didn't ask anything else.
Bai Qian, your engagement with Ye Hua
won't fall through again, will it?
Probably not.
That's good.
Zhen Zhen really misses your cooking.
When will you have time to come
to the Peach Tree Woods?
But I'm still repaying a debt
in the mortal realm.
Repaying a debt?
The Two Lives Curse
is working well on you.
Aunt, he's threatening me.
He's threatening you
only because he wants you back
to cook for Fourth Brother.
That's true.
By the way, Aunt,
why did you come today?
- For Yuan Zhen.
- Yuan Zhen?
Yuan Zhen is the Crown Prince's cousin.
He was sent to the mortal realm
because he did some things.
I won't speak at length here.
Didn't you just say?
On the first of the sixth month,
a beauty will fall into the water.
Yuan Zhen will save the beauty.
And the beauty will
fall in love with him.
Dong Hua Dijun will also
fall in love with the beauty.
Yes.
So, I am going to is pull Yuan Zhen out
of Dong Hua Dijun's trial of love.
Have you thought of a plan yet, Aunt?
I have.
On the day the beauty falls into
the water, I will hold Yuan Zhen back
and then find someone to
push Dong Hua Dijun into the water.
Dijun will naturally go
and save the woman.
When the two fall for each other,
Yuan Zhen will no longer be involved.
Xiao Jiu, are you willing to be the one
who pushes Dong Hua Dijun into the water?
I am restricted by the Two Lives Curse.
I am not myself during the day.
We will be lucky,
if I don't ruin your plan.
I'm afraid I won't be able to do it.
Never mind. That is true.
If I can't find anyone,
then I'll have to do it myself.
So you're here.
I went to the mortal realm
to look for you.
Let's go. I've been waiting a long time.
Come to the West Sea with me.
- Let's go.
- The West Sea?
Yes. I was just at the West Sea.
I had happened upon the second prince
of the West Sea in the mortal realm.
Mo Yuan's disciple,
Bai Qian's Senior Disciple?
That's him.
I came across him in a restaurant in the
mortal realm and we had a meal together.
Someone just happened to come
to report from the Crystal Palace.
I watched as worry spread across
his face as he listened
and he wouldn't stop drinking.
So, I asked him about it.
It turns out the matter
he is worried about
is something you can help with.
Me?
Yes, you, High God Zhe Yan.
Come on.
Thank you for coming to examine my son.
I do not know whether
I can treat him yet.
Why not let me take a look first?
Yes. This way, please.
It's said that on
a certain day 600 years ago
the West Sea's eldest prince's
weakened body
steadily began to deteriorate.
The healers of the West Sea
examined him
but could not find the cause
and were at their wit's end.
They watched as the eldest prince
coughed up blood.
They had no choice but to
send a request
to the Medicine King in heaven
to solve this conundrum.
However, Medicine King
could not figure out why he was ill.
In the end, he could only
prescribe two medicines
so that Die Yong would stop
coughing up blood.
Before Medicine King departed
he said the eldest prince's illness
did not seem to be a bodily sickness.
In that case, he could not
do anything as Medicine King.
Seeing as there was nothing left to try
they sought medical treatment
from all around the world.
But in the end, nobody has
managed to cure him.
How could this be?
High God, you have
such a grave expression.
Is my son...
Do not worry, Water King.
Eldest Prince's life is not in jeopardy.
Then do you have a way to heal my son?
Let me think about this some more.
Why do you have such an odd expression?
The eldest prince's illness
is quite strange.
Give me a few days.
I'll tell you after I find the truth.
It is rare to see you so cautious.
Yuan Zhen.
I miss you very much.
- Aunt.
- Follow me.
Sit down.
I will stand.
I have found a way to
help Yuan Zhen through his trial.
- Allow me offer my heartfelt thanks.
- No need. Sit down.
Everything is in order to
divert Yuan Zhen's trial
except for the one in the crucial role of
pushing someone down.
Pushing someone?
Simply put, on the first of
the sixth month, when the beauty appears
someone needs to push
the emperor into the water.
All right, I'll do it.
When the time comes,
you will use an invisibility spell.
When the beauty appears
walk quietly to the emperor's side
and push him into the water.
However, this will cause
your powers to turn against you.
It is rather dangerous for you to do it.
It should be done by someone strong.
Since this deed must be done,
then I'll have my lord do it.
That would be good.
After all, he is Yuan Zhen's father.
It would be most appropriate
for him to do this misdeed.
I will find my lord now
and tell him to see you.
All right. You must be quick.
There isn't much time until the first of
the sixth month in the mortal realm.
Do not worry, Aunt.
Now the preparations are complete.
High God, you took me in
70,000 years ago.
Now 70,000 years later,
you are going to save my son.
You are certainly our savior.
Your Highness, the altar will be ready
before the sun sets.
Good.
Then I shall wait another few hours.
What?
Bai Qian wants me to push
Dong Hua Dijun into the water?
Yes.
You agreed?
Aunt said this is
the only way to save Yuan Zhen.
Why?
Time is tight. I didn't have
time to ask many questions.
But since this is what Aunt says, then
this must be the only way that will work!
Could it be...
She wants to use this chance
to take revenge on us?
Revenge?
You might not know this.
Those who use their powers
to change fate in the mortal realm
will be punished.
Bai Qian could have chosen anyone.
She had to choose me?
Isn't she using this to take revenge
on me for canceling my engagement to her?
My lord, you cannot say that of my Aunt.
She agreed to go to
the mortal realm to help me
out of regard to our relationship
as mistress and servant
disregarding any former enmity.
Moreover, she has always been
the Aunt I respect the most.
She would never use this chance
to turn on us!
All right, all right.
Do not be mad.
I am being narrow-minded.
Do not get excited.
I will go to the mortal realm now.
- High Goddess.
- Sit.
I must apologize for what happened.
No matter what, it was wrong of me
to break off our engagement so suddenly.
No need to mention the past. Sit.
Has anyone ever told you
you look very much like
High God Mo Yuan's 17th disciple, Si Yin?
I had met him once. You two--
Water King, since you have come
for Yuan Zhen
then there's no need to
speak of anything else.
- Let's talk about tomorrow.
- Yes.
To be honest
the one you are to push into the water
is Dong Hua Dijun.
I was going to have your wife do this,
but she is with child.
It would not be very good.
Thank you for taking
such thorough consideration.
No need to be polite.
I'll begin talking about
what you are to do tomorrow.
All right.
When the time comes tomorrow,
you will use an invisibility spell...
Crown Prince, you really cannot stop
worrying about the high goddess.
That is Dong Hua Dijun after all.
Do not worry, Your Highness.
Dijun is not one who is petty.
When the time comes,
the roc bird will appear.
I must hurry and summon Yuan Zhen.
Go call the crown prince to me.
Yes.
Crown Prince, the Daoist Master
requests to see you.
Master?
Master, have you called me here
at this time for an urgent matter?
It is good you have come.
For some reason, a ray of light
just flashed through my mind
and I suddenly understand
all the principles I normally
couldn't comprehend.
Would you like to know why?
Of course I would like to know.
Great.
Go wait for me at your hall.
I will follow soon after.
Could it be that song and dance
are more important than my teachings?
No, no. I am wrong.
I will leave right away.
Look there. That looks like a roc bird.
I can't believe such a big roc bird
exists in this world.
It looks so ferocious
and is flying so quickly.
Such a big roc has been mentioned
in the scriptures.
Could it be appearing now as an omen?
Your Majesty, this is clearly
an auspicious omen.
An omen of fortune?
You say this is an auspicious omen
just on the basis of one bird?
Your Majesty, it's dangerous!
Shut your mouth.
Your Majesty, watch out!
Your Majesty!
Help!
Your Majesty, don't go near the water!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty!
- Help!
Guards! Go save her!
- Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Guards!
Your Majesty! His Majesty cannot swim!
Guards, come quick!
- Your Majesty!
- Guards! Quick!
- Come quick!
Quickly, quickly!
Someone save His Majesty!
- Your Majesty is in the water!
- Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Even with all my preparation
I did not foresee that Dong Hua had
reincarnated into someone who can't swim.
Who will save the beauty now?
- Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
- Quickly! Quickly!
Your Highness must not use your powers.
- Someone come!
- Quickly!
How are you? Are you all right?
Why would someone push me into the water?
Perhaps it is because
the Crown Prince trusts you so much
attracting the envy of others
and someone made use of the chaos
to teach you a lesson.
Ye Hua, you used your powers.
It is against heaven's law.
As long as you are safe,
it doesn't matter what happens to me.
Since you saved me, what will happen
to Dong Hua and Feng Jiu?
High Goddess, they are all right.
This was the original trial
for them to endure.
In a few months, the Little Princess
will get what she wants.
That is good.
In that case, you two should
return to the Celestial Palace.
It isn't good for a Crown Prince
to stay in the mortal realm for too long.
My task isn't finished yet. I have to go.
- Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty, wake up!
- Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty, I'm begging you.
Your Majesty, I'm begging you.
Wake up, Your Majesty!
I cannot live on without you,
Your Majesty!
Were you the one who saved me?
Don't speak. The physician
will be here soon.
Hold on a while longer.
You will be all right, Your Majesty.
Quickly! Save His Majesty!
- Quickly!
- Your Majesty!
What?
You pushed High Goddess Bai Qian
into the river yourself?
Is she in any danger now?
I did not expect the Crown Prince
to be nearby.
He used his powers to save her.
This princess is so easy to deceive.
I had told her to go to the mortal realm
to teach Bai Qian a lesson.
Who knew that she would even dare to
plot to take a high goddess's life?
If she succeeded,
that would have been fine.
But she has failed.
If the Crown Prince were to investigate
this matter
it could be a lot of trouble.
You are so senseless.
How could you do such a thing
to the Aunt of Qing Qiu?
I understand the jealousy
you have for her.
However, His Highness will be
ruling over the four seas.
It will be inevitable for there to be
many women in his palace.
How can you enter Xiwu Palace
if you are so prone to jealousy?
Sister, didn't you tell me to--
You misunderstood me.
But don't be afraid.
Only Xin Nu and I will know.
Let's think of a way so that you will
become the Crown Prince's woman.
And use a happy occasion
to bury this incident.
Are you speaking the truth, Sister?
Of course.
I genuinely like you,
so naturally, I will help you.
Don't worry.
Subtitles by DramaFever