1
00:01:34,532 --> 00:01:37,330
So, where are you right now?
I see.

2
00:01:39,204 --> 00:01:41,263
I have to go. My master is calling.

3
00:01:52,584 --> 00:01:54,552
Excuse me.

4
00:01:58,089 --> 00:02:00,182
You wanted to see me sir?

5
00:02:01,593 --> 00:02:03,322
Who...

6
00:02:07,332 --> 00:02:10,392
Who is that woman?

7
00:02:13,238 --> 00:02:15,536
The woman on the monitor.

8
00:02:19,110 --> 00:02:20,737
I believe...

9
00:02:21,713 --> 00:02:27,276
...that is the wife of President
Toyama and a world famous dancer...

10
00:02:28,786 --> 00:02:33,382
...Shizuko Toyama.

11
00:03:51,970 --> 00:03:56,930
FLOWER AND SNAKE

12
00:04:23,801 --> 00:04:26,827
That dream again...

13
00:07:14,505 --> 00:07:22,674
It's time to announce the winners
of the 1993 National Dance Contest.

14
00:07:26,017 --> 00:07:28,144
And the winners are...

15
00:07:30,021 --> 00:07:37,985
...number 141, the group of
Kenji Mochida and Shizuko Kisaragi.

16
00:07:38,596 --> 00:07:49,268
Trophy to be presented by our guest
judge, President Takayoshi Toyama.

17
00:07:49,607 --> 00:07:52,201
Working too hard, huh?

18
00:07:54,512 --> 00:07:55,410
Yes?

19
00:08:02,153 --> 00:08:05,316
- You were groaning again.
- I'm sorry.

20
00:08:11,496 --> 00:08:15,592
This schedule is very hectic,
just like a celebrity's.

21
00:08:16,400 --> 00:08:21,201
I see there's no choice for tonight
due to the dinner show...

22
00:08:21,839 --> 00:08:26,003
...but is it really necessary
for tomorrow's TV show?

23
00:08:26,244 --> 00:08:27,973
I'm sorry.

24
00:08:28,312 --> 00:08:31,713
But my former manager arranged for it.

25
00:08:35,319 --> 00:08:38,379
Your job requires you to be in
top-notch physical condition.

26
00:08:38,489 --> 00:08:40,980
Don't get crushed
down by popularity.

27
00:08:41,158 --> 00:08:43,649
- The driver is here now.
- Ah, ok.

28
00:08:48,065 --> 00:08:54,368
Well, I'm very proud to have a
world famous tango dancer as a wife.

29
00:08:54,505 --> 00:08:56,769
I'll be more careful.

30
00:08:58,943 --> 00:09:03,107
Can your manager be someone
outside the industry?

31
00:09:03,214 --> 00:09:04,340
Yes.

32
00:09:04,615 --> 00:09:09,917
I believe there is this macho ex-cop.
Isn't that right Eguchi?

33
00:09:10,021 --> 00:09:12,114
Yes, good morning.

34
00:09:12,256 --> 00:09:13,450
Good morning.

35
00:09:13,624 --> 00:09:17,424
- At the investigation agency we use...
- The Yamazaki investigation agency.

36
00:09:17,528 --> 00:09:19,792
- Any good ones?
- Let's see...

37
00:09:19,931 --> 00:09:24,095
A bodyguard for me?

38
00:09:32,176 --> 00:09:33,905
To ward off stalkers.

39
00:09:34,045 --> 00:09:40,450
What if some maniac with a
fixation tries to kidnap you?

40
00:09:40,685 --> 00:09:44,451
Even Eguchi over here is
a huge fan of yours.

41
00:09:44,689 --> 00:09:47,351
- Isn't that right, Eguchi?
- Yes!

42
00:09:48,693 --> 00:09:50,991
You see what I mean?

43
00:09:56,267 --> 00:09:57,894
Have a nice day.

44
00:10:20,658 --> 00:10:21,852
Come in.

45
00:10:24,795 --> 00:10:27,389
Minister Tomimoto is here.

46
00:10:30,668 --> 00:10:32,465
Thank you for coming.

47
00:10:32,570 --> 00:10:35,198
I don't have much time today.

48
00:10:35,339 --> 00:10:39,605
You have someone
you would Like to introduce?

49
00:10:39,777 --> 00:10:42,575
- Hey!
- Sir, please come in.

50
00:10:43,481 --> 00:10:48,748
Let me introduce Mikizo Morita.
President of Morita Corporation.

51
00:10:48,886 --> 00:10:51,980
This is President Toyama.

52
00:10:53,524 --> 00:10:56,652
Pleased to meet you.

53
00:10:58,329 --> 00:10:59,557
Same here.

54
00:11:04,168 --> 00:11:06,193
I'm here.

55
00:11:45,176 --> 00:11:48,407
Tashiro, you mean Mr. Ippei Tashiro?

56
00:11:48,546 --> 00:11:50,878
Impressive building!

57
00:11:51,015 --> 00:11:55,645
Intelligent structure
on such a prime site!

58
00:11:55,820 --> 00:12:01,725
100 billion yen asset indeed.
Well done for a man of such youth.

59
00:12:03,527 --> 00:12:09,329
I have heard a great deal about
Mr. Tashiro from my father. How is he?

60
00:12:10,101 --> 00:12:13,730
This was sent for Mr. Tashiro.

61
00:12:16,273 --> 00:12:18,639
- Come in.
- Excuse me.

62
00:12:18,809 --> 00:12:21,334
Ah. It's here, it's here!

63
00:12:27,418 --> 00:12:28,749
Good job.

64
00:12:31,422 --> 00:12:37,486
PLEASE INVESTIGATE.
MORITA

65
00:12:38,429 --> 00:12:46,029
YAKUZA?

66
00:13:06,490 --> 00:13:09,288
And your support for the project?

67
00:13:09,426 --> 00:13:11,155
I'm glad to be part of it.

68
00:13:11,328 --> 00:13:17,062
How much did you pay for
the site? 50... 80 billion?

69
00:13:17,268 --> 00:13:21,364
- Who is it?
- It's Kazuo Kawada.

70
00:13:23,374 --> 00:13:25,001
Kawada?

71
00:13:26,143 --> 00:13:33,049
For the great financial loss
Kawada is to blame. He must resign.

72
00:13:34,251 --> 00:13:36,310
All in favor?

73
00:13:36,754 --> 00:13:41,589
Please give me one more chance.
I have a wife and daughter to support!

74
00:13:41,725 --> 00:13:43,056
Agreed!

75
00:13:44,228 --> 00:13:50,463
I'd have never guessed
this company to be so huge.

76
00:13:50,634 --> 00:13:54,400
I'll contact you later.

77
00:14:06,083 --> 00:14:11,578
What the hell?
That bastard's as guilty as I am!

78
00:14:11,956 --> 00:14:16,825
- Revenge, for firing him.
- What revenge?

79
00:14:17,061 --> 00:14:25,400
He's unemployed, his wife left,
and he started gambling.

80
00:14:25,769 --> 00:14:30,433
He's also in heavy debt.

81
00:14:30,708 --> 00:14:34,508
Our boss hates people Like you.

82
00:14:34,645 --> 00:14:40,242
He says the war wasn't
fought for idiots Like you.

83
00:14:41,619 --> 00:14:46,147
Let's cut the crap! Name your price!

84
00:14:57,034 --> 00:14:59,093
Are you OK?

85
00:15:01,071 --> 00:15:02,504
Drive!

86
00:15:02,640 --> 00:15:04,039
All right.

87
00:15:04,942 --> 00:15:06,170
Asshole!

88
00:15:18,355 --> 00:15:20,186
Are you OK?

89
00:15:28,098 --> 00:15:34,503
Look what they've done to you.
Mrs. Toyama, right?

90
00:15:35,072 --> 00:15:36,004
Yes.

91
00:15:36,373 --> 00:15:41,743
I'm Kyoko Nojima, your
new manager and bodyguard.

92
00:15:41,845 --> 00:15:44,006
Sure you're not hurt?

93
00:15:44,148 --> 00:15:48,585
Bodyguard?
I thought you'd be a macho guy.

94
00:15:48,719 --> 00:15:49,913
I'm macho!

95
00:16:37,368 --> 00:16:39,336
What the hell do you mean?

96
00:16:39,503 --> 00:16:43,599
We seek several billion yen
in timely contributions.

97
00:16:43,807 --> 00:16:46,901
There must be another way!

98
00:16:47,077 --> 00:16:49,910
Give us your wife...

99
00:16:50,147 --> 00:16:53,583
...the world famous dancer.

100
00:16:53,784 --> 00:16:58,312
Why her? If she dances for him...

101
00:16:58,856 --> 00:17:03,020
Is that worth that much?

102
00:17:05,929 --> 00:17:08,796
What do you intend on doing to her?

103
00:17:08,932 --> 00:17:11,025
- Hey!
- Stand back!

104
00:17:15,606 --> 00:17:21,340
Unfortunately, she's not worth it.

105
00:17:22,513 --> 00:17:29,885
She may look hot and sexy, but
in fact, she's an ice queen.

106
00:17:30,487 --> 00:17:32,216
I know...

107
00:17:32,823 --> 00:17:38,352
From failed ballerina to dance champion.
Beautiful and talented.

108
00:17:38,562 --> 00:17:43,261
Pure as snow, then, she married you.

109
00:17:43,434 --> 00:17:48,167
And now a world-class tango dancer
thanks to you.

110
00:17:48,338 --> 00:17:50,397
Like a virgin.

111
00:17:52,409 --> 00:17:54,809
What a windfall!

112
00:17:55,712 --> 00:18:01,048
By the way, this is my idea,
not Mr. Tashiro's.

113
00:18:01,251 --> 00:18:07,281
He just likes beautiful things.

114
00:18:08,058 --> 00:18:13,394
He himself is one of a kind.

115
00:18:17,201 --> 00:18:19,260
So what?

116
00:18:20,571 --> 00:18:26,203
Give him the rare beauty
of your wife and...

117
00:18:26,777 --> 00:18:29,644
...you're off the hook.

118
00:18:29,913 --> 00:18:33,781
And what about the minister?
Why pick on me?

119
00:18:33,917 --> 00:18:38,581
He's of no use to us anymore.
His days are over.

120
00:18:38,755 --> 00:18:44,250
You are one lucky guy to
have such an attractive wife!

121
00:18:47,564 --> 00:18:49,964
Who the hell are you people?

122
00:18:50,067 --> 00:18:55,095
Boss, I know who they are!
Let's call the cops!

123
00:18:55,239 --> 00:18:56,672
It's all right.

124
00:18:57,741 --> 00:18:59,333
You asshole!

125
00:19:02,346 --> 00:19:03,574
Boss!

126
00:19:05,282 --> 00:19:06,874
- The cops!
- No!

127
00:19:07,184 --> 00:19:08,708
- That won't be necessary.
- Hey!

128
00:19:10,020 --> 00:19:12,853
This is not a game!

129
00:19:14,258 --> 00:19:16,556
This is my job.

130
00:19:17,728 --> 00:19:19,355
If I fail...

131
00:19:20,831 --> 00:19:23,959
...I must pay with my life.

132
00:19:25,068 --> 00:19:27,502
You got that kiddo?

133
00:19:33,310 --> 00:19:38,077
Or would you rather
I put this on the web?

134
00:19:38,982 --> 00:19:40,381
Wait!

135
00:19:41,485 --> 00:19:43,817
What do you want me to do?

136
00:19:49,259 --> 00:19:50,248
Come in.

137
00:19:51,361 --> 00:19:53,852
Mr. Yamazaki is here.

138
00:19:57,734 --> 00:20:00,430
Find anything useful?

139
00:20:00,537 --> 00:20:04,997
- Thank you for using Kyoko...
- Enough. Get to the point!

140
00:20:05,409 --> 00:20:08,469
About Ippei Tashiro...

141
00:20:10,647 --> 00:20:12,239
Is he alive?

142
00:20:12,382 --> 00:20:17,410
He made a fortune in
the war in Manchuria...

143
00:20:17,688 --> 00:20:22,318
...and at over 95 is still in good health.

144
00:20:24,361 --> 00:20:25,794
95?

145
00:20:25,963 --> 00:20:31,196
Yes. Though confined to a wheelchair...

146
00:20:31,435 --> 00:20:36,737
...he still has great influence over
politicians and the underworld.

147
00:20:37,040 --> 00:20:41,204
Didn't know he's that old.

148
00:20:41,712 --> 00:20:45,512
- Unbelievable...
- And as for Morita...

149
00:20:45,649 --> 00:20:49,949
Enough! It's very late.
We'll talk tomorrow.

150
00:20:50,387 --> 00:20:53,413
As you wish. Good night.

151
00:20:57,461 --> 00:20:59,486
Good night.

152
00:20:59,630 --> 00:21:01,257
95?

153
00:21:02,232 --> 00:21:04,393
Is that it?

154
00:21:10,374 --> 00:21:13,605
He just wants to see her naked?

155
00:21:18,382 --> 00:21:21,977
She'll give him a heart attack.

156
00:21:22,286 --> 00:21:28,156
I can be off the hook
and save a lot of money.

157
00:21:29,660 --> 00:21:31,287
Perfect!

158
00:21:36,900 --> 00:21:40,427
Her future is at stake too.

159
00:21:40,570 --> 00:21:44,097
I need her help!

160
00:21:45,776 --> 00:21:50,076
She must! She’ll understand.

161
00:21:50,447 --> 00:21:59,116
It's our happiness that's at stake.

162
00:22:27,150 --> 00:22:30,779
I have to see an acupuncturist.

163
00:22:30,954 --> 00:22:34,549
See you on Monday.

164
00:22:39,563 --> 00:22:41,428
I'm so tired.

165
00:22:41,698 --> 00:22:44,496
You've been working too hard.

166
00:22:49,673 --> 00:22:51,368
Please...

167
00:22:52,008 --> 00:22:54,499
...lay on your back.

168
00:24:09,019 --> 00:24:10,486
You're back...

169
00:24:11,688 --> 00:24:15,419
Sorry, must've fallen asleep...

170
00:24:19,796 --> 00:24:22,094
What's the matter?

171
00:24:22,699 --> 00:24:23,791
What?

172
00:24:24,768 --> 00:24:26,099
Nothing.

173
00:24:29,005 --> 00:24:30,472
Dinner?

174
00:24:30,607 --> 00:24:32,905
Or shower first?

175
00:24:34,744 --> 00:24:36,211
Shizuko.

176
00:24:37,581 --> 00:24:38,570
Yes?

177
00:24:39,249 --> 00:24:42,685
You wanna have some wine?

178
00:24:42,986 --> 00:24:44,248
Wine?

179
00:24:53,396 --> 00:24:57,594
A masked ball? That's fantastic!

180
00:24:58,969 --> 00:25:00,266
I'll go!

181
00:25:00,704 --> 00:25:04,105
It's tomorrow night.
Don't you have work then?

182
00:25:04,241 --> 00:25:09,338
I can cancel. The new manager is great.

183
00:25:09,713 --> 00:25:12,944
She's quite macho too.

184
00:25:13,250 --> 00:25:14,774
Thanks.

185
00:25:15,986 --> 00:25:17,419
I'm glad.

186
00:25:30,700 --> 00:25:33,396
Where's the party at?

187
00:25:34,070 --> 00:25:37,665
I must practice my waltz.

188
00:25:39,242 --> 00:25:42,769
Where's that Dead of Winter CD...

189
00:25:42,913 --> 00:25:45,814
Practice? You?

190
00:25:46,249 --> 00:25:48,717
Who's the host?

191
00:25:49,185 --> 00:25:51,085
Well...

192
00:25:52,389 --> 00:25:59,761
...Mr. Tashiro, a man with great power
over the political world.

193
00:25:59,896 --> 00:26:02,421
A fixer?

194
00:26:02,933 --> 00:26:04,560
Exactly.

195
00:26:05,168 --> 00:26:08,137
My father knew him.

196
00:26:17,447 --> 00:26:20,610
Hey, Let’s dance!

197
00:26:22,018 --> 00:26:22,882
Now?

198
00:26:24,487 --> 00:26:26,318
It's been a while...

199
00:26:26,423 --> 00:26:28,823
Ten years.

200
00:26:30,026 --> 00:26:31,084
Really?

201
00:26:32,395 --> 00:26:34,420
Since the wedding?

202
00:26:40,437 --> 00:26:43,372
May I have this dance?

203
00:26:47,277 --> 00:26:49,472
With pleasure.

204
00:27:04,561 --> 00:27:08,998
He has a huge mansion
up in the mountains...

205
00:27:09,499 --> 00:27:16,632
...and throws parties for
politicians and celebrities.

206
00:27:18,108 --> 00:27:22,067
Airways invites me, but I'm usually busy.

207
00:27:23,046 --> 00:27:27,676
This time though, I must go.

208
00:27:30,020 --> 00:27:35,287
He's an old man and
quite a fan of yours.

209
00:28:15,365 --> 00:28:16,662
You all right?

210
00:28:16,766 --> 00:28:18,256
Sorry.

211
00:30:48,218 --> 00:30:50,015
It hurts.

212
00:30:57,660 --> 00:30:59,093
Sorry.

213
00:31:44,007 --> 00:31:46,134
It's not you...

214
00:31:47,143 --> 00:31:49,338
It's my fault.

215
00:31:50,780 --> 00:31:52,509
Forgive me.

216
00:31:54,617 --> 00:32:01,079
Maybe with another man,
you'd feel it too.

217
00:32:01,658 --> 00:32:03,319
Nonsense...

218
00:32:03,860 --> 00:32:06,829
I don't want another man.

219
00:32:21,411 --> 00:32:23,379
I'm pitiful.

220
00:32:32,422 --> 00:32:37,382
Honey, I've made a decision.

221
00:32:38,161 --> 00:32:44,122
I'll work Less and spend
more time caring for you.

222
00:32:45,802 --> 00:32:48,896
This should help you...

223
00:32:50,039 --> 00:32:56,444
...recover your energy.

224
00:33:01,617 --> 00:33:02,948
But...

225
00:33:04,420 --> 00:33:07,821
- What about your dancing?
- I won't give it up.

226
00:33:07,957 --> 00:33:11,893
Just work Less.

227
00:33:12,962 --> 00:33:14,486
OK?

228
00:33:18,668 --> 00:33:20,636
What's wrong?

229
00:33:24,273 --> 00:33:27,470
Let's skip the party.

230
00:33:28,077 --> 00:33:29,305
What?

231
00:33:30,780 --> 00:33:35,308
It's such Late notice
to get ready for and...

232
00:33:35,818 --> 00:33:40,448
I'll be fine. Don't worry.

233
00:33:40,590 --> 00:33:42,785
Let's cancel it.

234
00:33:42,959 --> 00:33:44,256
Why?

235
00:33:45,395 --> 00:33:47,590
What's wrong?

236
00:33:47,730 --> 00:33:49,357
Nothing.

237
00:33:50,433 --> 00:33:51,923
It's just...

238
00:33:54,737 --> 00:33:56,204
I'll get it.

239
00:34:01,677 --> 00:34:02,666
Yes?

240
00:34:03,012 --> 00:34:04,980
You still awake?

241
00:34:05,782 --> 00:34:11,652
The minister's dead.
He hung himself.

242
00:34:11,788 --> 00:34:12,914
What?

243
00:34:16,092 --> 00:34:18,026
When is the news?

244
00:34:18,161 --> 00:34:22,723
He just killed himself.
So watch the news at noon.

245
00:34:41,217 --> 00:34:44,675
Did you bug my house?

246
00:34:44,854 --> 00:34:48,984
We’ll be expecting you shortly...

247
00:34:55,765 --> 00:34:57,562
What's wrong?

248
00:34:58,134 --> 00:35:00,102
A friend of yours?

249
00:35:01,404 --> 00:35:02,530
No...

250
00:35:06,075 --> 00:35:09,704
Perhaps we should go tonight.

251
00:35:10,246 --> 00:35:11,338
What?

252
00:35:48,384 --> 00:35:50,477
How mysterious.

253
00:35:50,586 --> 00:35:51,553
Yeah.

254
00:35:51,687 --> 00:35:58,490
Our guest of honor, the world famous
tango dancer, Shizuko Toyama.

255
00:36:10,606 --> 00:36:12,005
Thanks.

256
00:36:12,508 --> 00:36:15,136
May I have this dance?

257
00:36:16,445 --> 00:36:18,276
With pleasure.

258
00:37:12,602 --> 00:37:15,162
- What's wrong?
- Let's Leave.

259
00:37:15,938 --> 00:37:17,235
Sorry.

260
00:37:20,209 --> 00:37:21,574
You!

261
00:37:22,144 --> 00:37:23,634
Mr. Kawada?

262
00:37:27,817 --> 00:37:32,982
Give me one more chance!
I have a family to support...

263
00:37:33,122 --> 00:37:36,285
One more chance...

264
00:37:38,361 --> 00:37:39,988
Just kidding.

265
00:37:41,230 --> 00:37:43,858
Madam, may I cut in?

266
00:37:45,034 --> 00:37:46,865
Wait a minute!

267
00:37:48,537 --> 00:37:53,338
Where are you taking me?
Let me go!

268
00:37:57,079 --> 00:38:02,415
Please! I'll pay.

269
00:38:03,319 --> 00:38:06,811
It's too Late now!

270
00:38:08,924 --> 00:38:09,822
No!

271
00:38:12,628 --> 00:38:13,788
Shizuko!

272
00:38:14,230 --> 00:38:16,562
Shizuko! Don't go!

273
00:38:16,699 --> 00:38:17,893
Help!

274
00:38:24,173 --> 00:38:28,200
Mr. Morita, let me do it.

275
00:38:29,545 --> 00:38:31,843
I deserve it.

276
00:38:31,981 --> 00:38:35,314
It doesn't matter who it is.

277
00:38:35,484 --> 00:38:36,781
Stars...

278
00:38:37,186 --> 00:38:43,614
...what the Coliseum needs
is stars or it's the end!

279
00:38:44,827 --> 00:38:49,958
Now I can finally repay
my debts to Mr. Tashiro.

280
00:38:50,266 --> 00:38:52,791
What debts?

281
00:38:53,536 --> 00:38:55,504
- Hey Kawada.
- Yes?

282
00:38:56,339 --> 00:39:03,541
Don't you know that Mr. Tashiro
raised the boss Like his son...

283
00:39:03,679 --> 00:39:06,648
That's enough!

284
00:39:07,149 --> 00:39:08,514
Sorry.

285
00:41:15,311 --> 00:41:23,446
Ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome, distinguished guests...

286
00:41:23,619 --> 00:41:34,496
...tonight's main attraction, the
high-class, world-famous dancer...

287
00:41:35,664 --> 00:41:39,395
...Madam Shizuko!

288
00:41:41,136 --> 00:41:44,105
What is all this?

289
00:41:44,640 --> 00:41:48,007
You all know her...

290
00:41:48,811 --> 00:41:52,577
...but is this really her?

291
00:41:52,781 --> 00:41:57,309
Show us, madam, take off your clothes!

292
00:41:57,453 --> 00:41:58,818
What?

293
00:41:59,054 --> 00:42:03,650
Take off your dress!

294
00:42:03,859 --> 00:42:05,451
Take it off?

295
00:42:05,895 --> 00:42:10,355
Madam Shizuko! Do as you're told...

296
00:42:11,500 --> 00:42:14,128
...or the driver dies.

297
00:42:16,472 --> 00:42:18,497
Mr. Eguchi!

298
00:42:20,543 --> 00:42:22,033
Madam...

299
00:42:23,779 --> 00:42:25,804
Madam Shizuko!

300
00:42:28,217 --> 00:42:33,314
Take off your dress or the driver dies.

301
00:42:37,359 --> 00:42:42,092
You give us no choice!

302
00:42:44,099 --> 00:42:49,162
We’ll kill him Like this woman!

303
00:42:51,073 --> 00:42:53,166
I see.

304
00:42:54,410 --> 00:42:56,207
As you wish...

305
00:42:56,779 --> 00:43:00,840
...he shall die! Music, maestro!

306
00:43:01,350 --> 00:43:02,544
No!

307
00:43:05,087 --> 00:43:08,215
I'll take it off.

308
00:43:10,392 --> 00:43:11,950
Splendid.

309
00:43:15,297 --> 00:43:19,859
Then, please, take it off!

310
00:43:48,197 --> 00:43:51,598
Is this all, madam?

311
00:43:51,900 --> 00:43:54,630
Take everything off!

312
00:43:56,939 --> 00:44:00,705
A high-class Lady indeed!

313
00:44:02,611 --> 00:44:06,377
Too bad for the driver.

314
00:44:06,849 --> 00:44:08,316
Farewell!

315
00:44:08,450 --> 00:44:09,940
Stop it!

316
00:44:11,854 --> 00:44:13,651
I'll do it.

317
00:44:42,685 --> 00:44:44,744
Stand up!

318
00:44:47,289 --> 00:44:50,986
Don't cover yourself!

319
00:44:53,429 --> 00:44:56,057
The audience awaits!

320
00:45:02,938 --> 00:45:04,838
Show them...

321
00:45:05,474 --> 00:45:06,634
...your...

322
00:45:07,076 --> 00:45:08,805
...everything!

323
00:45:17,352 --> 00:45:19,843
Do as he says!

324
00:45:21,924 --> 00:45:23,789
Show it all!

325
00:45:23,926 --> 00:45:28,693
What are you doing?

326
00:45:28,864 --> 00:45:33,358
Ask your husband. He's being
manipulated by these guys.

327
00:45:33,736 --> 00:45:38,139
Do as he says and it will be over.

328
00:45:42,144 --> 00:45:43,304
You!

329
00:45:43,579 --> 00:45:45,410
Mr. Kawada!

330
00:45:45,748 --> 00:45:51,482
Hey, bitch! Shut your yelping!

331
00:45:52,821 --> 00:45:54,880
Do it now!

332
00:45:57,926 --> 00:46:00,417
Lady, my ass!

333
00:46:17,159 --> 00:46:18,626
Hold her!

334
00:46:27,335 --> 00:46:28,233
Can't!

335
00:46:29,304 --> 00:46:31,568
Can't get it up.

336
00:46:33,308 --> 00:46:35,276
Do it, come on!

337
00:46:35,377 --> 00:46:39,040
I can't get it up!

338
00:46:58,733 --> 00:47:01,793
I can't get it up!

339
00:47:07,075 --> 00:47:08,702
I can't...

340
00:47:19,487 --> 00:47:22,456
What was that all about?

341
00:47:47,016 --> 00:47:50,213
I apologize for this.

342
00:47:51,520 --> 00:47:53,715
No, no...

343
00:47:54,624 --> 00:47:56,148
...it's OK.

344
00:47:56,292 --> 00:47:57,486
What?

345
00:48:06,269 --> 00:48:08,203
My, oh, my!

346
00:48:08,871 --> 00:48:13,069
The loyal servant burning for revenge...

347
00:48:13,609 --> 00:48:16,134
...and the noble Lady...

348
00:48:16,345 --> 00:48:20,782
Alas, the rape failed!

349
00:48:21,284 --> 00:48:24,981
What a sorrowful tango!

350
00:48:31,093 --> 00:48:32,993
Enough!

351
00:48:37,967 --> 00:48:39,867
Release me!

352
00:48:42,405 --> 00:48:43,599
Now!

353
00:48:44,106 --> 00:48:47,075
Return to your seats please!

354
00:48:47,209 --> 00:48:48,801
Release me!

355
00:48:49,445 --> 00:48:50,810
Release me!

356
00:48:56,018 --> 00:48:57,610
Release me!

357
00:49:04,927 --> 00:49:07,418
Take the chains off!

358
00:49:08,898 --> 00:49:10,365
Release me!

359
00:49:18,908 --> 00:49:20,205
It's me.

360
00:49:50,373 --> 00:49:51,533
It hurts.

361
00:49:59,682 --> 00:50:01,343
Bastards!

362
00:50:03,552 --> 00:50:05,383
Help me.

363
00:50:11,927 --> 00:50:13,724
I rule!

364
00:50:24,373 --> 00:50:27,342
Don't fuck with Yakuza!

365
00:50:27,877 --> 00:50:32,280
It's all a show to see him killed.

366
00:50:33,582 --> 00:50:36,210
Don't resist them.

367
00:50:36,419 --> 00:50:38,114
Got it?

368
00:50:39,221 --> 00:50:42,122
Do as they say...

369
00:50:42,625 --> 00:50:46,755
...or you'll never Leave this hell.

370
00:50:58,107 --> 00:50:59,768
What's this?

371
00:51:00,876 --> 00:51:04,744
Is this a nightmare?

372
00:52:13,816 --> 00:52:15,477
Shizuko...

373
00:52:26,328 --> 00:52:27,795
Shizuko!

374
00:52:28,531 --> 00:52:29,930
Shizuko!

375
00:52:33,669 --> 00:52:35,034
Shizuko!

376
00:52:47,550 --> 00:52:48,812
Shizuko?

377
00:52:52,087 --> 00:52:57,753
Yes, we were supposed to meet
at 1:00, but she's not here yet.

378
00:52:57,927 --> 00:52:59,588
She's not there!

379
00:52:59,828 --> 00:53:05,733
But it's a live broadcast!
Did something happen Last night?

380
00:53:05,868 --> 00:53:07,836
Mind your own business!

381
00:53:10,172 --> 00:53:12,037
What now?

382
00:53:23,552 --> 00:53:26,544
Watch where you're going.

383
00:53:29,091 --> 00:53:31,252
The Missus needs you.

384
00:53:31,393 --> 00:53:33,190
What the hell...

385
00:53:57,052 --> 00:53:58,849
It's no good...

386
00:53:59,188 --> 00:54:01,816
They're not stupid.

387
00:54:29,485 --> 00:54:32,249
What have I done?

388
00:54:35,924 --> 00:54:37,721
Shizuko!

389
00:54:45,534 --> 00:54:47,297
Damn it!

390
00:55:43,792 --> 00:55:45,282
Mrs. Toyama!

391
00:55:55,070 --> 00:55:57,868
Oh, she's awakened!

392
00:55:58,607 --> 00:55:59,972
Next up...

393
00:56:00,809 --> 00:56:07,009
Sold to the mafia by her beloved
husband in return for his debts...

394
00:56:07,416 --> 00:56:14,413
...the president's wife
is gonna be learning...

395
00:56:15,023 --> 00:56:21,485
...the painful way of
becoming a porn star!

396
00:56:22,197 --> 00:56:23,824
Madam!

397
00:56:25,134 --> 00:56:28,433
But the chaste Lady...

398
00:56:29,304 --> 00:56:31,101
...is in fact...

399
00:56:32,508 --> 00:56:37,878
...a frigid bitch and won't cooperate.

400
00:56:38,147 --> 00:56:46,521
So the audience is bored.
If she continues Like this...

401
00:56:47,356 --> 00:56:52,055
...we'll have to kill her.

402
00:56:53,262 --> 00:56:58,996
Her Life is in your hands, Kyoko!

403
00:57:19,922 --> 00:57:22,516
Now you see it going in...

404
00:57:22,691 --> 00:57:24,852
What could it be?

405
00:58:02,164 --> 00:58:03,961
Now it's done.

406
00:58:05,667 --> 00:58:08,636
What are you doing, you freaks?

407
00:58:09,938 --> 00:58:12,338
What the hell is this?

408
00:58:13,308 --> 00:58:15,503
A secret show...

409
00:58:18,046 --> 00:58:21,482
...for a select audience.

410
00:58:26,722 --> 00:58:30,988
You heard of a clown.
Some of our guests here...

411
00:58:31,960 --> 00:58:39,799
...they get their kicks from dead bodies.

412
00:58:41,336 --> 00:58:47,366
If she's useless alive,
they'd Love to watch her die.

413
00:58:48,644 --> 00:58:50,168
Hey!

414
00:58:53,782 --> 00:58:55,113
Look!

415
00:58:55,284 --> 00:58:58,685
Poor little Kyoko!

416
00:58:59,454 --> 00:59:02,912
Such a cute fighter!

417
00:59:03,258 --> 00:59:07,695
So strong and tough!

418
00:59:10,198 --> 00:59:19,971
Misses, if you don't cooperate,
poor Kyoko will suffer.

419
00:59:21,777 --> 00:59:27,579
Can you withstand the master of pain?

420
00:59:29,217 --> 00:59:33,176
Behold, trainer Origin!

421
00:59:41,997 --> 00:59:44,124
Who the fuck?

422
00:59:44,266 --> 00:59:47,030
Don't touch me!

423
00:59:52,641 --> 00:59:56,042
Poor girl.

424
00:59:57,412 --> 01:00:01,041
Poor Little Kyoko!

425
01:00:02,017 --> 01:00:05,509
What unbearable pain!

426
01:00:06,254 --> 01:00:09,883
Do as they say, or she'll die!

427
01:00:11,259 --> 01:00:19,598
Poor naked madam!
Hasn't relieved herself for 12 hours.

428
01:00:20,936 --> 01:00:24,736
She can't do it if we watch. Why?

429
01:00:25,607 --> 01:00:34,777
Coz she's a real Lady.

430
01:00:36,018 --> 01:00:37,383
Right?

431
01:00:38,453 --> 01:00:46,952
A moment ago though,
we gave her a diuretic.

432
01:00:52,801 --> 01:00:58,637
Pee or poor Kyoko will suffer.

433
01:01:01,810 --> 01:01:04,301
Don't Listen to him!

434
01:01:04,513 --> 01:01:05,639
Don't!

435
01:01:05,914 --> 01:01:08,212
Be strong!

436
01:01:08,450 --> 01:01:19,349
"Don't! Be strong! Like me!
Don't Listen to him!"

437
01:01:23,832 --> 01:01:26,357
So you still won't?

438
01:01:27,369 --> 01:01:30,429
Well, I have no choice.

439
01:01:30,706 --> 01:01:34,802
Her clothes shall be stripped off!

440
01:01:58,967 --> 01:02:01,629
Well done, Shizuko!

441
01:02:01,837 --> 01:02:05,102
Shall we go on?

442
01:02:05,273 --> 01:02:08,242
You're the stars now!

443
01:02:08,410 --> 01:02:16,875
Madam Shizuko sold out by
her husband and her bodyguard.

444
01:02:17,853 --> 01:02:21,949
A tragic Lesbian show!

445
01:02:22,858 --> 01:02:25,554
Why would he...

446
01:02:27,295 --> 01:02:30,423
Why would he do such a thing?

447
01:02:30,632 --> 01:02:32,497
That's right.

448
01:02:36,104 --> 01:02:40,370
He sold her for several billion.

449
01:02:40,509 --> 01:02:42,067
No!

450
01:02:42,277 --> 01:02:43,938
Yes, he did.

451
01:02:44,146 --> 01:02:50,051
He's a coward!
A weak businessman turned alcoholic.

452
01:02:50,886 --> 01:02:52,615
No!

453
01:02:52,954 --> 01:02:54,785
Right.

454
01:02:55,690 --> 01:02:57,715
He's useless.

455
01:02:58,360 --> 01:03:02,888
Left all the work to us and drank.

456
01:03:03,165 --> 01:03:08,125
Jealousy made him an alcoholic.

457
01:03:08,637 --> 01:03:10,730
Useless fool!

458
01:03:10,872 --> 01:03:12,897
Liar, Liar!

459
01:03:15,076 --> 01:03:22,141
Enter Kyoko!

460
01:03:23,218 --> 01:03:24,378
What the...

461
01:03:24,586 --> 01:03:27,214
You son of a bitch!

462
01:03:29,457 --> 01:03:31,152
Stop it!

463
01:04:11,166 --> 01:04:14,567
No!

464
01:04:28,850 --> 01:04:30,078
So...

465
01:04:31,419 --> 01:04:35,856
...what'll be her fate?

466
01:04:44,878 --> 01:04:48,336
She’ll go mad soon.

467
01:04:50,350 --> 01:04:53,319
You're all she has.

468
01:04:54,021 --> 01:04:56,819
Will you save her?

469
01:05:18,412 --> 01:05:19,674
Really?

470
01:05:22,916 --> 01:05:25,077
Are you sure?

471
01:05:27,888 --> 01:05:29,685
All right!

472
01:05:31,725 --> 01:05:35,684
Let the show begin!

473
01:05:42,436 --> 01:05:44,666
No!

474
01:06:24,520 --> 01:06:25,953
Now...

475
01:06:27,123 --> 01:06:29,853
Let yourself go!

476
01:06:31,193 --> 01:06:34,959
Let your inhibition go free!

477
01:06:35,131 --> 01:06:37,463
Release yourself!

478
01:06:37,666 --> 01:06:41,932
Golden rain will fall.

479
01:06:50,546 --> 01:06:52,741
In and out...

480
01:06:54,216 --> 01:06:56,844
...front and back.

481
01:06:58,621 --> 01:07:06,551
What will happen when
the water starts flowing...

482
01:07:53,242 --> 01:07:54,732
Kyoko...

483
01:07:57,146 --> 01:07:59,137
Mrs. Toyama...

484
01:08:12,261 --> 01:08:15,458
They're watching us.

485
01:08:15,698 --> 01:08:18,861
Fake it if you must!

486
01:08:19,268 --> 01:08:24,205
Otherwise they'll kill you. Understand?

487
01:08:24,740 --> 01:08:29,200
Listen to me! Pretend you enjoy it...

488
01:08:29,712 --> 01:08:34,479
...and we might get a chance to escape.

489
01:08:34,650 --> 01:08:37,551
Sorry for this.

490
01:08:37,920 --> 01:08:39,888
It's good.

491
01:08:42,024 --> 01:08:46,427
You wanna get screwed, do you?

492
01:08:46,695 --> 01:08:49,823
Want me to screw you?

493
01:08:58,941 --> 01:09:00,408
Bitch!

494
01:09:09,919 --> 01:09:15,880
I won't hurt you.
Just pretend to enjoy it.

495
01:09:16,358 --> 01:09:17,950
Please.

496
01:09:36,645 --> 01:09:38,875
I'm all confused.

497
01:09:39,081 --> 01:09:42,881
I Love you so much.

498
01:09:43,519 --> 01:09:47,853
I airways watch you, even on TV.

499
01:09:48,090 --> 01:09:52,754
And now, to be able to do this...

500
01:09:53,329 --> 01:09:55,160
...it's wonderful!

501
01:09:55,397 --> 01:10:06,433
If they kill us here in the mountains,
no one will ever find us.

502
01:10:17,086 --> 01:10:21,045
He sold you for several billion...

503
01:10:21,290 --> 01:10:24,589
...bought himself out...

504
01:10:27,529 --> 01:10:29,656
I'll be over.

505
01:10:48,417 --> 01:10:49,850
Get out!

506
01:10:53,722 --> 01:10:55,690
Both of you!

507
01:11:09,672 --> 01:11:10,900
Run!

508
01:11:24,953 --> 01:11:26,352
This way!

509
01:11:35,964 --> 01:11:37,693
This place...

510
01:11:50,612 --> 01:11:53,046
Is this the way?

511
01:11:55,284 --> 01:11:58,253
I think so. That door...

512
01:11:59,054 --> 01:12:02,546
- Wait, there's something's wrong!
- What is it?

513
01:12:02,691 --> 01:12:05,023
- It's just Like before...
- Before?

514
01:12:06,562 --> 01:12:07,893
It's a trap!

515
01:12:11,567 --> 01:12:12,829
Kyoko!

516
01:12:14,002 --> 01:12:15,333
Are you OK?

517
01:12:16,505 --> 01:12:19,372
Bastards!

518
01:12:20,175 --> 01:12:24,839
Welcome back to the Rape & Snuff
show...

519
01:12:25,381 --> 01:12:28,316
...Ladies and gentlemen!

520
01:12:29,184 --> 01:12:35,145
For your enjoyment this
angelic face and tough body!

521
01:12:35,457 --> 01:12:39,188
- Let's go! Go! Go!
- Stay away!

522
01:12:39,328 --> 01:12:41,125
No!

523
01:12:45,834 --> 01:12:49,429
Don't kill her! Please!

524
01:12:55,511 --> 01:12:56,671
Don't!

525
01:13:01,049 --> 01:13:02,846
Please!

526
01:13:03,285 --> 01:13:07,415
I'll do anything.

527
01:13:07,723 --> 01:13:10,385
Don't kill her!

528
01:13:19,902 --> 01:13:21,130
It's me.

529
01:13:27,943 --> 01:13:29,740
Promise?

530
01:13:30,546 --> 01:13:34,949
If you Lie, I'll stick needles in you.

531
01:13:50,466 --> 01:13:53,765
Please, forgive me!

532
01:13:54,169 --> 01:13:55,864
Madam!

533
01:13:56,104 --> 01:13:58,766
I'm really sorry!

534
01:17:15,267 --> 01:17:16,962
So beautiful.

535
01:17:29,881 --> 01:17:31,712
What's wrong?

536
01:18:02,187 --> 01:18:04,018
Here, here.

537
01:18:17,569 --> 01:18:21,005
There, there.

538
01:18:36,354 --> 01:18:39,084
There, see that?

539
01:18:42,194 --> 01:18:44,492
There, there.

540
01:18:49,968 --> 01:18:50,992
There.

541
01:18:55,106 --> 01:18:59,042
Don't be shy.

542
01:19:05,517 --> 01:19:10,284
Let me see.

543
01:19:20,332 --> 01:19:23,927
Were you a naughty girl?

544
01:19:24,069 --> 01:19:24,865
Yes!

545
01:19:25,003 --> 01:19:27,403
Were you? Speak up!

546
01:19:27,505 --> 01:19:28,494
Yes!

547
01:19:28,640 --> 01:19:30,733
Were you?

548
01:19:31,509 --> 01:19:35,843
Then I have to punish you more!

549
01:20:32,948 --> 01:20:41,287
Ladies and gentlemen, I hope
you enjoyed our whore show!

550
01:20:42,091 --> 01:20:47,461
It's time for the grand finale!

551
01:21:14,726 --> 01:21:17,194
She's faking?

552
01:21:17,629 --> 01:21:22,657
No way! Onigen's a professional.

553
01:21:23,201 --> 01:21:24,998
She came!

554
01:21:25,137 --> 01:21:27,264
Gave me a hard-on, too!

555
01:21:27,472 --> 01:21:31,568
No, Mr. Tashiro knows...

556
01:21:32,077 --> 01:21:36,537
...she still hasn't shown her real face.

557
01:21:36,748 --> 01:21:38,477
Real face?

558
01:21:38,617 --> 01:21:42,883
This Location isn't safe anymore.

559
01:21:43,055 --> 01:21:46,024
Someone might speak.

560
01:21:48,693 --> 01:21:53,153
We must use our Last resort.

561
01:21:54,132 --> 01:21:55,258
The Last?

562
01:21:58,070 --> 01:22:01,665
Here's one billion yen.

563
01:22:04,142 --> 01:22:06,736
It's all I have Left.

564
01:22:11,049 --> 01:22:13,017
Let her go...

565
01:22:19,591 --> 01:22:21,491
I mean it!

566
01:22:21,726 --> 01:22:25,662
Let her go, or I'll go to the police.

567
01:22:28,533 --> 01:22:29,966
The truth is...

568
01:22:30,669 --> 01:22:31,727
What?

569
01:22:32,070 --> 01:22:39,977
She's having so much fun that she
may not want to come back to you.

570
01:22:40,112 --> 01:22:41,909
What do you mean?

571
01:22:42,881 --> 01:22:46,681
She knows how you sold her out.

572
01:22:47,986 --> 01:22:49,783
And so...

573
01:22:51,356 --> 01:22:54,154
I'm giving you all my money!

574
01:22:57,162 --> 01:23:02,498
How about you go and
convince her to return.

575
01:23:31,196 --> 01:23:33,858
So this is the Coliseum...

576
01:23:34,666 --> 01:23:42,300
Annual membership is 50 million
and a million per show.

577
01:23:43,008 --> 01:23:46,102
There are currently 100 members.

578
01:23:46,244 --> 01:23:51,477
Strictly intellectuals,
stars, and celebrities.

579
01:23:51,917 --> 01:23:56,183
It's their fantasyland.

580
01:23:57,355 --> 01:24:00,950
And the show is superb!

581
01:24:02,294 --> 01:24:05,627
I hope you enjoy it.

582
01:24:08,166 --> 01:24:09,326
Please!

583
01:24:38,730 --> 01:24:41,221
What the hell?

584
01:24:41,399 --> 01:24:44,527
What do you think you're doing!

585
01:24:51,776 --> 01:24:53,266
Shizuko...

586
01:24:56,214 --> 01:24:57,738
Do me.

587
01:24:59,084 --> 01:25:02,247
Just do me.

588
01:25:06,224 --> 01:25:07,851
Shizuko...

589
01:25:25,577 --> 01:25:28,808
Forgive me!

590
01:25:31,416 --> 01:25:35,182
I bought you back with everything I had.

591
01:25:36,988 --> 01:25:43,484
Let's start over. Just the two of us.

592
01:25:49,567 --> 01:25:50,864
Do me...

593
01:27:02,507 --> 01:27:04,907
Beautiful.

594
01:27:07,512 --> 01:27:09,139
Master...

595
01:27:18,690 --> 01:27:21,523
So beautiful.

596
01:28:23,021 --> 01:28:24,921
Let's go home.

597
01:28:28,560 --> 01:28:29,925
Hey you!

598
01:28:31,496 --> 01:28:33,020
Let go of me!

599
01:28:33,131 --> 01:28:34,325
Shizuko!

600
01:28:34,466 --> 01:28:37,026
Let her go! Shizuko!

601
01:28:41,539 --> 01:28:48,035
So it has to be with the one he Loves.

602
01:28:49,948 --> 01:28:52,041
I want her back!

603
01:28:53,017 --> 01:28:54,541
I Love her.

604
01:28:55,787 --> 01:28:57,414
I Love her.

605
01:29:02,427 --> 01:29:05,225
The show's not over.

606
01:29:07,532 --> 01:29:10,126
You’ll have to wait a Little Longer.

607
01:29:10,301 --> 01:29:13,998
It's magnificent!

608
01:29:14,873 --> 01:29:18,775
Long Live the Coliseum!

609
01:29:19,110 --> 01:29:21,010
Forever!

610
01:29:46,437 --> 01:29:47,699
No!

611
01:29:49,607 --> 01:29:51,234
What's wrong?

612
01:29:51,743 --> 01:29:53,643
Leave!

613
01:29:55,914 --> 01:29:57,381
As you wish.

614
01:30:06,524 --> 01:30:08,958
Just in case.

615
01:30:33,518 --> 01:30:35,281
I'm good.

616
01:32:51,122 --> 01:32:52,953
Beautiful.

617
01:33:45,176 --> 01:33:47,167
Beautiful...

618
01:33:48,279 --> 01:33:50,179
Beautiful.

619
01:33:57,155 --> 01:33:59,020
Are you...

620
01:34:06,464 --> 01:34:08,261
Beautiful.

621
01:34:15,306 --> 01:34:20,039
Will you dance with me?

622
01:37:49,653 --> 01:37:51,086
Master!

623
01:37:59,296 --> 01:38:00,490
Master!

624
01:38:02,900 --> 01:38:04,094
Master!

625
01:38:07,804 --> 01:38:08,793
Master!

626
01:38:10,073 --> 01:38:11,267
Master!

627
01:38:11,842 --> 01:38:14,174
Master! Master!

628
01:38:21,018 --> 01:38:23,248
You bitch!

629
01:38:37,100 --> 01:38:38,397
Master!

630
01:38:40,070 --> 01:38:41,332
Master!

631
01:38:45,042 --> 01:38:46,304
Master!

632
01:38:55,285 --> 01:38:56,980
You whore!

633
01:38:58,789 --> 01:39:00,689
Bring him back!

634
01:39:07,965 --> 01:39:09,865
Bring him back!

635
01:39:14,805 --> 01:39:16,466
Bring him back!

636
01:39:17,908 --> 01:39:19,535
Bring him back!

637
01:39:20,410 --> 01:39:21,536
Bring him back!

638
01:39:40,864 --> 01:39:43,059
Shoot me!

639
01:39:44,801 --> 01:39:47,668
Shoot me, bitch!

640
01:39:49,272 --> 01:39:50,569
Shoot me!

641
01:40:07,591 --> 01:40:09,115
Shoot me!

642
01:40:40,891 --> 01:40:44,725
Kyoko, I'm coming to get you.

643
01:41:03,513 --> 01:41:05,481
What is this place?

644
01:43:12,142 --> 01:43:13,473
No!

645
01:43:14,211 --> 01:43:16,338
Where am I?

646
01:43:24,287 --> 01:43:25,686
Where?

647
01:43:38,435 --> 01:43:39,993
Shizuko.

648
01:44:04,828 --> 01:44:06,955
Let's go home Shizuko.

649
01:44:08,632 --> 01:44:10,623
You had a nightmare.

650
01:44:12,769 --> 01:44:14,862
Is it really you?

651
01:44:15,405 --> 01:44:18,704
Was it all just a dream...

652
01:44:20,577 --> 01:44:22,238
Just a dream?

653
01:44:22,445 --> 01:44:25,642
It's the same dream.

654
01:44:28,551 --> 01:44:32,112
Let's go home, just the two of us.

655
01:44:45,902 --> 01:44:48,166
When did it...

656
01:44:49,339 --> 01:44:51,204
...start?

657
01:44:52,108 --> 01:44:55,441
When indeed?

658
01:44:57,247 --> 01:44:59,408
The night before...

659
01:45:00,750 --> 01:45:02,911
...the masked ball?

660
01:45:03,086 --> 01:45:04,110
No...

661
01:45:08,658 --> 01:45:12,719
The day we met?

662
01:45:14,431 --> 01:45:15,728
Madam...

663
01:45:17,133 --> 01:45:19,727
...may I have this dance?

664
01:45:21,671 --> 01:45:23,502
With pleasure.

665
01:45:25,008 --> 01:45:27,977
We must finish the dance.

666
01:46:48,858 --> 01:46:52,055
No!

667
01:46:53,897 --> 01:46:57,333
Shizuko, I Love you.

668
01:51:39,882 --> 01:51:46,947
Welcome to the show!

