Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
There are men who sniff around the mystery
that surrounds myself and my friend.
Little by little, their search brings
them closer to our secret.
Hear me, young man and young lady.
Hear me, noble souls acting in unison.
Be on your guard,
...and know that there are some things in
this world that one is better off not knowing.
Count!
You miserable brat!
Die!
Act 14:
Lost Souls
You sons of...
Count! Are you
all right?!
You needn't worry
about me.
But...
Why is this
happening to me?!
Hasn't my record
always been perfect?!
You should know that!
Right?
I've always been above reproach,
with no blemish on my record!
Albert!
This is all your fault! It's all because
you brought that accursed Count to Paris!
What lies did you fill his head with?!
Tell me!
Mark my words! Don't get cocky!
You'll be next!
Disaster will come calling
at your house, too!
Give it a rest!
Hey, let go of me!
Do you have any idea who I am?!
Let go! Get your hands off me!
Count!
You should
go home now.
Let us meet again
some other time.
Are you really okay?
This ain't good...
Hey, Ali!
Do your thing.
Your abilities are as
impressive as ever...
Albert! This is all
your fault!
You'll be next! Disaster will come
calling at your house, too!
Yoo-hoo!
You've been in there for ages.
Did something happen?
No, I'm fine.
What is it?
Maximilien is here
to see you.
Maximilien!
Monsieur Albert.
You're looking well!
It's good to
see you again.
Why the sudden
return to Paris?
I've come here to fetch
Monsieur Noirtier.
I thought that he should be
at Valentine's side.
I guess you're right.
I came here expecting to have another
quarrel with Monsieur Villefort,
...but I heard the news of his arrest
the instant I arrived in Paris.
It came as quite a shock to hear
what had become of him.
Yeah...
I wanted to come pay you a visit
and express my gratitude.
Thank you for all you
have done for us.
Still as upright and formal
as ever, huh?
It was because you were
there for me...
...that I was able to save those
who are dearest to me.
If nothing else, please don't
forget that one thing.
Maximilien...
I am glad that
I met you.
Take good care
of Valentine.
I will.
See you around,
Maximilien.
Thanks to you, my stocks have hit the
trading limit for several days in a row.
These various tidbits of information
find their way to me, that's all.
I don't really ask
for them.
Oh, how I envy you...
It's a waste of one's life to tie one's happiness
to the fluctuations of numbers.
More importantly, though...
"Dramatic Arrest of Crown Prosecutor
Villefort in Public Spectacle."
This is most shocking,
isn't it?
Yes, it is...
One never can tell what will
happen next in life.
By the way, Baron, what's this I hear about you
and the Crown Prosecutor being old friends?
Not at all, not at all! We're just acquaintances,
we're not what you'd call friends.
Oh, is that true? You, General Morcerf, and
the Crown Prosecutor here are old friends,
...and you've used each other's influence
to expand your own power bases.
I've heard stories along those lines,
so I was curious.
T-That must be a rumor spread
by jealous people, no doubt.
Well, if you say so.
Still, people can be brought low
by the most unexpected things.
I suggest that you exercise the utmost caution
in the company you choose to keep, Baron.
Baron?
Yes?
I'm quite serious about
your daughter.
I'd like to receive your blessing
as soon as possible.
What a mess...
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
My name is Beauchamp.
Y-You're a reporter?
Yeah.
Then this is
your lucky day!
You're gonna have a scoop that's gonna
be splashed across the front page!
What do you want
in return?
How much will your company
pay for a big scoop?
I'm really busy, so if
you'll excuse me...
W-Wait! I'm talkin' about a huge scandal
involving General Morcerf!
This is gonna knock
even YOUR socks off.
Hey, sorry to bother you.
Why did you need to
see me so suddenly?
Well, we're doing a special feature on
General Morcerf's presidential bid.
I figured I should use my personal connections,
so I was hoping to ask you a few questions.
Sure, if it's something
I can answer.
Thanks.
By the way, why do you think your father
has managed to achieve such success?
I'd like to hear your frank opinion
as one of the people closest to him.
Well, let me think...
I guess it would be
his sincerity.
My father loves and worries about the country in
the same way that he loves my mother deeply.
Have you heard about how
my father became a hero...
...by defending Janina's citadel
to the bitter end?
After he returned to Paris, he used that as
a springboard and shot up through the ranks,
...even making it to the rank of general
in spite of his young age.
And now he's making a bid
for the presidency, huh?
Yes. My father's enthusiasm for
politics is the real deal.
I see...
I'm rooting for
your father, too.
It's times like these when a man makes a lot
of enemies. You should watch your back, too.
Did something happen?
Nah, it's nothing serious.
But when you deal in gossip like you do in my
line of work, you get all kinds of crazy tips.
Tales of bribery, kickbacks, illicit affairs...
You get sick of it.
That's hilarious! My father isn't
involved with any of that stuff.
Frankly, I'm more worried that he might be
a little too straight-laced to be a politician.
You don't say...
I'd be relieved if he ever
did something like that.
"He's a lot more shrewd
than I gave him credit for."
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Sorry to worry you over nothing.
The fact of the matter is, a fishy guy
paid me a visit today.
He was this creepy, sleazy old man.
What did he say his name was?
"Caderousse," or something
like that.
What did he...
What did that man say
about my father?
Oh, some stupid story.
Something about how the stories of your
father's exploits at Janina are all a lie.
I told him he was full of crap
and chased him away.
Oh...
Open flames are strictly prohibited
in this building.
Please extinguish your
lighter immediately.
Smoking is prohibited
in this room.
Please smoke only in
designated areas.
I guess I'd better
look into this...
Step right up! Pay our establishment
a visit tonight, my good gentlemen!
The dead man has
come back to us!
Edmond would never forget what we did,
not in a million years.
Something about how the stories of your
father's exploits at Janina are all a lie.
Disaster will come calling
at your house, too!
No, that's not possible. It couldn't be.
Thank you for agreeing to speak with us.
First of all,
Marquis Cavalcanti,
...there has been an announcement that you are
making a huge investment in the Danglars Bank.
What was it that made you decide
on that particular bank?
I leave all investment matters
to my advisory analysts.
I abide by their decisions and follow
their advice. That is the only reason.
There are also rumors that you have been
seeing Baron Danglars' daughter.
Oh, are there?
I realize that it is a personal question,
but if you would care to make a comment...
All right, just a
brief one, then.
The fact is, Eugenie de Danglars and I
were formally engaged this morning.
My goodness!
It's like a fairy tale!
Is that true?
Congratulations on your engagement!
This is big news, everyone!
He has to be lying...
Idiot. If I'd known you were here,
I would've been able to play even better.
I would've been playing
for you.
Yes. Naturally, she's overjoyed
about this, too.
Step right up!
Watch it!
Eugenie...
Please, I have to speak with Eugenie.
Let me see her.
Mademoiselle has said that she
doesn't wish to speak with you.
I want to see her in person and
ask her how she feels about this.
Please, I'm begging you!
I am sorry, Monsieur.
Please! At least tell her
that I'm here!
Eugenie!
Was someone at the door
just now?
No, Mademoiselle.
Just a deliveryman.
Oh.
What are all these
flowers for?
What's the meaning
of this?!
How could you arrange an engagement
for me without asking me about it?!
I told you that your happiness
is my main concern, didn't I?
But I'M the one who's going
to have to marry him!
You're still young.
It's too soon for you to make
important decisions on your own.
Do you really mean what
you're saying, Father?
Of course I do.
I wish you'd stop
doing this!
Where are you going? I invited
Marquis Cavalcanti to dinner tonight.
Don't be late!
If you're looking for Albert,
he's out right now.
Out where?
Beats me.
Oh.
Albert...
Ow! I didn't throw mine
that hard!
You bastard!
Jerk!
Now you're gonna
get it!
It's all over between
me and Eugenie.
I hear that she got engaged
to Cavalcanti.
Yeah...
This isn't what Eugenie wants.
There's something behind it.
Come on, you know Eugenie would never
voluntarily get engaged to a guy like that.
I'm not so sure...
I don't know anymore.
I can't tell what's true,
and what's a lie.
I just don't know anymore.
Albert...
Franz... I'm still me,
aren't I?
Whatever happens,
I'll still be...
Please, Franz, tell me!
I won't change, right?!
No matter what happens,
I'm still gonna be me, right?!
"Death is certain, its hour uncertain," huh?
Talk about a sinister expression...
Albert.
As far as I'm concerned,
I think I'd rather know the truth.
Even if learning the truth
changed who I am.
Franz...
I'm thinking of leaving
Paris for a while.
You're going back
to Luna or something?
That's a good idea! At a time
like this, a trip is the best thing to...
I'm sorry, but I can't
take you with me.
Why the hell not?!
What's the big idea?!
I'm sorry.
You, too, huh?
Now I get it.
We've all grown up.
We're supposed to keep secrets
from each other.
You and I should call
it quits, too, Franz.
I mean, a secret hideout?
What are we, kids?
Albert...
Wait for me, Albert.
Trust me, I'll get to the truth.
Albert!
Count?
You weren't hurt!
Yes, I am right
as rain.
Is something the matter?
You're out without an umbrella.
Oh, I thought that getting soaked for a change
wouldn't be such a bad thing.
So I see.
That reminds me, I'm on my way
to go off into space again.
What do you say?
Would you care to join me?
Um... Today isn't
a good time.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
Oh, there is no need to apologize. I hope that
you will accept my offer some other time, then.
I cannot bring myself to leave you here;
not with that look on your face.
Come, let us go together.
Welcome home.
We waited for you,
but dinner has ended.
I was out looking
for Albert.
I see that there is still room in
your heart for no one but him.
Monsieur Albert has gone off
into deep space.
Apparently, he is going to spend time
with the Count at his summer retreat.
Oh... He is?
Oh, that's right. There's been a steady
stream of flowers to congratulate you.
This one is from me.
Why? Why do these things
keep happening to me?
Why do you suppose
that is?
Count, I'm afraid...
What's the truth?
What is a lie?
That is something that you
must decide for yourself.
Do you have the resolve to overcome
your limitations and press ever onward?
If you possess a powerful will that bends
to no one, I can say this with certainty:
You will be
all right.
Count...
The first public speech by presidential race
forerunner General Fernand de Morcerf...
...is about to begin in the
National Assembly building.
Numerous public figures have also
rushed here to show their support,
...and the crowd inside the hall
is already at a fever pitch!
General Morcerf,
it's time.
Please take your place
on the stage, sir.
I only made it this far because
I had you at my side.
I'm so proud of you.
Get the car ready!
I'm going to the National Assembly!
Away from the worlds of men,
I find myself alone with the Count.
But there is no escaping
from the truth.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo act 15:
..."The End of Happiness,
The Beginning of Truth."
Act 15:
The End of Happiness, The Beginning of Truth
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!