Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
At Luna's Carnival, I encountered
an immature soul.
My friend said to me, "This shall be
the prelude to my vengeance."
But this soul was too young
and beautiful.
It is that alone which
gives me cause for fear.
Act 2:
Until the Sun Rises Over the Moon
Are you going to come?
That's enough
fun and games, boy.
I heard you met him
the other day.
Are you bored?
Not at all. It's a wonderful party,
don't you think?
Where is your friend?
Oh, you mean Albert?
He's probably out trying to pick up girls, and
getting turned down by every one of them.
But this is terrible!
This is Luna!
Strolling around alone at
night is tantamount to suicide!
Surely you're exaggerating...
It's no laughing matter.
You'll get kidnapped by Luigi Vampa!
Luigi Vampa?
He's an up-and-coming
bandit!
They say that he drags his victims
into the catacombs,
...tortures them,
and finally kills them!
How horrible!
Surely the police won't
stand by and do nothing.
You don't know?
The police on Luna arrange
their patrols to avoid the bandits.
My very own cousin was robbed blind,
had his arms and legs broken,
...and was left stark naked
in the plaza!
All because he spoke
to the bandit's mistress!
I'm sure he's fine. I bet that he's back
at your hotel at this very moment.
Would you care
to dance?
I simply despise when
a party ends.
First one guest leaves, then two.
Especially at this hour.
You won't abandon me,
will you?
Take him away.
You can't! It's mean!
Today is my birthday!
I'm sorry, Franz.
I have to go.
No, no, no!
Your father is leaving to see to
some very important business.
Fine, see if I care! I hope
you never come back!
Father...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I keep you waiting long?
I... think I should go.
Are you Baron
Franz d'Epinay?
Hey, you're that...
I'm sick of
your whining!
As for me, I killed
ten people!
This is for you.
"My Lord Baron
Franz d'Epinay."
"I, Luigi Vampa, have taken custody of
your friend, the Viscount Albert Morcerf."
"Hand over the sum of 50 million ducats
to my messenger immediately."
"If the messenger should
not return by sunrise,
"...although it pains me to do so,
think of your friend's life as forfeit."
Where is Albert?!
He's a valuable hostage, so we're
taking real good care of him.
If the money is handed over, he'll be sent
home without so much as a scratch.
You should have died!
Is this how you people do things?
Even I have a certain
lifestyle to maintain.
50 million
is absurd!
I'm sure that a Parisian aristocrat won't be
hard pressed to come up with such a sum.
Dawn comes fast
on Luna.
If you value your
friend's life,
...I suggest that you make arrangements
for the money as soon as possible.
I want to make an immediate withdrawal
from the Bank of Paris!
I'm terribly sorry,
sir,
...but our connection to Europe is currently
offline due to solar winds.
Isn't there anything
you can do?!
How much does
sir require?
Albert... Damn!
Say, son, it's awfully sad to see a young fella like
yourself all alone on the last night of Carnival.
If you want, I know
a fine girl who...
Please, just be quiet
and drive.
It was at my father's funeral
that I first met Albert...
Don't cry.
I'm not crying...
I'll play with you,
so cheer up.
Leave me alone!
Get lost!
Hey...
Ever since that day, Albert
and I have been inseparable.
Damn! What am I
going to do?
It's almost sunrise!
Have you raised
the money yet?
Give me more time!
Once it's morning, I'll have the
money transferred from Paris!
I'm sorry, Luigi is a stickler
for punctuality.
If you don't have the money ready by sunrise,
your friend is a goner.
Stop messing
with me!
I suggest that
you hurry.
I'm sure that you don't want to see your
friend die a horrible death, My Lord Baron.
You bastard!
Violence is unseemly,
My Lord Baron.
Damn it!
Yeah, that's better. A gentleman has
to worry about little things like discretion.
There is no more fascinating spectacle
than a man's death.
Yes, it almost feels as if one has
become God, does it not?
His Excellency,
the Baron d'Epinay.
I'm sorry to disturb you
at such an hour...
Is something the matter?
You do not seem entirely well.
Count! I have a favor
to ask of you!
What's the big idea?!
There is your
50 million ducats.
Now, you will take us
to the hostage.
To the Colosseum!
Have the two of you been
friends for a long time?
Yes, we've been best friends
since we were children.
Ah, so you are
childhood friends.
Constant friendship...
It is a wonderful thing,
is it not?
Who do you like?
C'mon, tell me!
At least give me
a hint!
You wouldn't understand.
Luigi.
It's almost time.
Kill him.
So, have you made
your peace?
C'mon, ma'am,
let me kill him!
No, let me!
Oh, give it a rest,
you two!
You can carve him up as much
as you want after he's dead.
Now, then. You should put up
a brave front while you still can.
I wonder what you'll sound like
when you cry?
H-Hey, guys.
Um... Visitors to
see the boss.
Who are they?
Please, Teresa, don't!
We can't kill him yet!
B-Because we won't get
the money!
And besides... There's still
a little time.
Stand aside!
If you're going to use that,
use it on me!
Squabbling among yourselves
is pathetic!
Thank you.
Stand back.
Are you trying to disgrace
the boss?
I'll be fine. Go.
So, does that mean
you've fallen for that girl?
That's so sweet...
But she's too much for you
to handle, little boy.
Or maybe... you'd rather become
one of us?
You know, I think I'll brand you...
Why, you...
Leave her alone!
I have come to meet with Signor Luigi Vampa,
whose reputation is notorious on Luna.
And who are you?
My name is... Gankutsuou.
T-The King
of the Cave?!
For one such as yourself who
dwells in the darkness,
...I expect that I am better
known by that name.
I have your money.
Now, hand over the hostage.
I'm sorry, but you missed
the deadline.
"Always be punctual,"
that's my motto.
"Punctuality is the politeness
of kings," is that it?
I'm deeply honored... by your
gracious words!
I see... Your skill
is impressive.
But you cannot kill me.
A-Are you...
Are you really...
A-Are you really him?!
I do not work for
the authorities.
If you would do me the honor
of returning my friend,
...all will be well.
You aren't injured, I take it?
I had a feeling that you
would come to rescue me.
If you wish to thank someone,
thank the good Baron d'Epinay.
He was gravely concerned
for your wellbeing.
Hey! Miss!
Are you okay?
Say, I never asked you
what your name was...
I'm Albert.
Albert de Morcerf.
I'm Peppo.
To tell you the truth, I was almost considering
throwing in my lot with the bandits.
I'm glad you're all right, Albert.
What took you
so long, Franz?
I came this close to being killed,
you know!
I was seriously...
What was that for?
Please, do not concern yourselves
over the matter.
It served as a pleasant
diversion for me.
But I have to do something
to repay you.
In that case, might I ask
one favor of you?
Anything at all!
Just name it!
I should like to take up
residence in Paris at some point.
That's wonderful!
However, a rustic aristocrat such as myself
has no connections in Paris.
As such, might I impose on you to act as
my intermediary into Parisian society?
Think nothing of it!
In that case, I shall call on you on
May 22nd, three months from this day,
...to commemorate the
events of this day.
Where in the world
did you find this?
I found it.
At the opera house.
Oh, so that is
where it was!
It shames me to say it,
but I have looked everywhere for it.
This, too, shows that there
is some bond between us.
Please accept it
with my gratitude.
Think of it as a small token
of our friendship.
Really?
It will serve to freeze the memory
of this day, this hour, in time.
A memory which belongs
to us alone.
Thank you so much!
I'll cherish it!
Carnival has ended, so what
are your plans now?
We're going to cut our trip short and
take the evening shuttle back to Paris.
Hey, wait a minute!
I've already made plans of my own!
You never learn, do you?
And what "plans" might these be?
What do you mean?
It's none of your business.
Have you arranged
a rendezvous, perhaps?
Sort of...
Love is a
wonderful thing.
However, perhaps you
have not noticed yet.
Or perhaps you knew, and
arranged the rendezvous regardless.
I do hate to be the bearer
of bad tidings, but...
A boy?
She's a boy?!
Come out and say it! You think
I'm an idiot, don't you?!
Not really.
You're always looking down on me,
laughing at me on the inside!
I'm not laughing
at you!
If I laughed at every boneheaded stunt
you pulled, I'd bust a gut!
Anyway, you were...
Thanks.
I owe you my life.
I appreciate it.
The fruits of betrayal must
be plucked from the tree...
At long last, the appointed day arrives.
He comes to Paris along with a summer storm.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo, act 3,
Act 3:
5/22, Stormy
..."5/22, Stormy".
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!