Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
My friend invited three families to his villa,
where a forbidden past lay dormant.
When that soul which had been
interred there returned to life,
...I sensed clearly that a new vengeance
was about to sprout.
Act 9:
I Dreamed A Dark Dream
Somebody!
Somebody, send for
a doctor!
What's the matter?
It's Madame Danglars!
She's collapsed!
What the hell
are you after?!
What's your game?!
Surely you jest. My only goal is to
have my guests enjoy the party.
You've gone too far! This manor was
originally owned by my father-in-law.
If you're deliberately trying to insult me,
I'll make you regret it!
Even though I was unaware of that fact,
I have indeed been most rude.
Still, this is a
most fascinating,
...not to mention
most odd, coincidence.
Which means, then, that this place is as
familiar to you as the back of your hand.
In which case, my little entertainment
was unfair from the very beginning.
This simply won't do.
Shall we start over and try it again?
What in the world happened, Albert?
I'm not really sure.
As part of the game, I was about to give
Madame Victoria the box with the prize in it,
...and the instant I did, she...
What in the world
made her faint?
H-How can this be?
Dear boy, forgive me...
It seems to be a case of anemia.
It is nothing serious.
I'll ask you again.
Who ARE you?
Exactly what do
you know?
Your life depends on
your answer.
Answer me!
I am but a poor bumpkin who has come from
the far reaches of Eastern Space.
Other than that, I have no past
which is worth speaking of.
None at all.
Victoria!
Victoria! What's happened
to her?!
You needn't worry.
She is merely feeling out of sorts.
Hey! Honey! Hey!
I expect that a few moments' rest
will have her feeling good as new.
Is that not right?
Where's Eugenie?
Let's look for her!
Eugenie!
Where are you?!
Father! Eugenie!
You there!
Do you know where Eugenie is?
She's Monsieur Danglars' daughter.
I've heard stories about you
from the Count.
All sorts of things.
So, you're Albert, son of
the Morcerf family...
Where's Eugenie?
Isn't she with you?!
She's already headed towards the inner
chambers, both she and your father.
Let me make one thing
perfectly clear to you.
In all the world, I am the only person capable
of understanding the Count's feelings.
Wha...?
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Count!
Give me your hand, sir.
My thanks, Bertuccio...
What are those markings...?
I'd ask you not to overexert yourself,
but I'd probably be wasting my breath.
Do you have it in you to follow me?
Into the darkest depths of Hell?
Of course. I'll be at your side
wherever you go, Gankutsuou.
Gankutsuou?
Mother...
I'm all right.
I'm fine now.
I'm sorry if I worried you.
Valentine!
Albert!
I'm sorry
about earlier.
I got carried away without stopping
to consider your feelings.
No, I'm the one who should apologize.
I said such rude things.
Still, I'm glad. It's nice that you two
can have a normal conversation now.
I... had misjudged him.
I'm glad we had this
chance to talk.
As am I!
Now that all the excitement's over,
I feel kinda...
Albert?
Monsieur Albert?
Hold on!
Monsieur Albert!
How are you feeling?
It feels like a weight on my chest
has been lifted.
I am glad to hear it.
I mixed this medicine especially for you.
Nothing is better for the
treatment of chest pains.
I'm sorry if I made
any trouble for you.
For some reason, I felt sick
all of a sudden...
What could be wrong
with Albert?
Ever since we were kids,
he's never had so much as a cold.
You and Albert are
childhood friends, aren't you?
Yeah.
I heard all about it from
Mademoiselle Valentine.
She said that she has always been jealous
of how close you two are.
It's just because we've known
each other for so long.
It's not just because you're
old friends, is it?
I somehow get the impression that you two
share a bond that no one else can share in.
Speaking of which, how long have
you had feelings for Valentine?
That's an awkward question
to be asked by her fiancée.
Of course, you're right.
I'm sorry.
No, I am the one who
is at fault here.
But if you love her, that should be
all that matters.
There you go, saying such
irresponsible things again...
Irresponsible, huh?
I suppose it is.
It's a strange thing.
Why can't you love Mademoiselle Valentine?
She is your fiancée, after all.
What about you? Will you stop loving her
just because you can't marry her?
As to that...
You can't, can you? You can't simply
fall out of love, can you?
Even if it's a relationship where
you can't marry the person.
Are you saying that you harbor
a hopeless love for someone, too?
Marriage isn't necessarily the only way
to make that person happy.
Don't you think?
I hadn't thought of that...
Perhaps you're right.
Valentine's found herself
a great guy.
Albert.
Sir?
I realize that this is an odd question,
but what have you eaten today?
Actually, I've been so busy today
that I haven't eaten anything at all.
But now that you mention it, I drank some
water from the table with the blue flowers.
The table with blue flowers was
the Villefort family's table.
Do you think that has
anything to do with it?
Albert, I would like you
to remain calm and listen to me.
What had been attacking
your body... was poison.
Poison?
Yes, a fearful poison that is called
"zhen-du" in Eastern Space.
You're saying that the
water was poisoned?
It would be safe
to assume so.
You managed to survive because the ice
had melted, thus diluting the poison,
...but you nevertheless
had a close call.
Who would do
such a thing?
I suspect that you were
not the target.
Right. The poison was mixed
into that water pitcher,
...so that means the target
was the Villefort family.
But why?
Feelings of hatred and jealousy
towards another...
...are emotions which silently fester and grow,
unbeknownst to the object of their affection.
The happier that person is,
the less aware he is of their feelings.
However, their attempt
ended in failure.
Which means that they
will lay another trap to...
They can't! There are people
that I want to be happy!
Albert, are you sure you
should be out of bed?
I feel fine now.
Sorry I made you worry.
Still, I think you should
take it easy.
He's right,
Monsieur Albert.
No, we have
to hurry.
I'll explain later. Anyway, we have
to get to Valentine's house.
To Mademoiselle
Valentine's house?
Yeah.
You're such a
frightening man...
And at the same time,
so very alluring...
Are we clear on this,
Boville?
Use every network at your disposal and find out
everything there is to know about that man.
Focus your investigation
on Marseilles in particular.
Understood.
"Count of Monte Cristo," my ass. Mark my
words, I'll find out who you really are.
Incidentally, what is your connection
to this man, Your Honor?
That isn't something that you need
to concern yourself about.
Yes, sir. But I suggest that
you be mindful of rats.
Yes, I know.
I'll be off, then.
Look, Grandfather.
Isn't this a beautiful rosary?
Pardon me.
I've brought you something
to drink.
Thank you, Valois.
Still, don't you think the Count
is reading too much into this?
I mean, come on, someone's trying
to kill the Villefort family?
He's not like other people.
I believe him.
Say, Franz...
Will you hear me out?
What's up? You sound
awfully serious.
The thing is, I finally
figured something out.
Well? What is it?
You might laugh at me for
saying this, Franz,
...but I really do think it's important for
the two people to love each other.
What's gotten into you?
What brought this on?
Well, I... It's just that I want Valentine
and Maximilien to be happy.
I know it's more complicated
than that for you, though.
Not at all. I want the same
thing with all my heart.
If it's humanly possible, I think two people
who love each other should be together.
You do, huh?
The love those two have is the real thing.
I want them to be happy.
No way am I gonna let
anybody poison her!
The rain has certainly
gotten stronger...
It's rather humid,
isn't it?
You must be hot, Valois.
Would you like a glass, too?
Eh? No, I couldn't possibly,
Mademoiselle.
It's all right, don't stand
on ceremony.
Valois!
Valois, what's the matter?
M-Mademoiselle...
Valois?
Valois!
W-What happened?
Grandfather...
Hurry!
Hurry, call the doctor!
Mademoiselle Valentine!
How can this be?
I can't believe it.
It's just like the Count said.
What the hell
is going on?
I'll be back.
Where are you going?
Where else?
To go see the Count.
He might be able to do
something for her.
Hey, Albert!
Albert...
I'll be at your side wherever
you go, Gankutsuou.
I'm sorry, but His Excellency is away
on a business trip at the moment.
You're kidding!
When will he be back?
That is entirely up to His Excellency.
I'm sorry I cannot be of more help.
I see that you're helpless by
yourself, same as always.
You!
I'm looking forward to seeing
how this turns out.
What's that supposed
to mean?
Do you have the courage to learn
what the future holds?
Who the hell you?
Damn it!
What am I gonna do?
Don't die, Valentine!
You child of illicit love who has
awoken from a dark dream...
...and come back to life
from the depths of death...
You beautiful child who knows nothing
of love, nor of being loved.
Thou art anathema.
Thou art anathema!
A dark cloud spreads out like
a stain to cover our lives.
And a letter arrives from an old friend
who was thought to be dead.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo act 10:
Act 10:
The Letter From Edmond
..."The Letter
From Edmond."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!