Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
When he visits
his fiancée,
...the young man saw a young
woman struggling to fight destiny.
However, none of them are yet aware of the
cruel fate that is silently bearing down on them.
Act 7:
The Secret Flower Garden
Hey!
Count!
Albert.
What happened?
She isn't feeling well.
Haidee is unaccustomed to crowds.
You needn't concern yourself.
We will meet again.
Let's go back in.
Okay?
I wonder what it was
that Haidee saw?
She looked as if she...
You saw him?
You saw that man?
I've heard that you are
engaged to be married...
Yes.
Are you happy?
I... I don't think I will be able
to restrain myself tonight.
I'm sorry.
Please excuse me.
I wonder if Haidee
is okay?
Who cares about the
Count's mistress?
She isn't like that.
He cares for her.
Like a master is kind towards
his pet dog.
Don't put the Count on the same level
as people like that!
The Count and Haidee have...
Um...
A relationship as two independent adults.
Where they both care for each other and...
Forget about other people.
What about you?
How do you feel
about Eugenie?
You're not one
to talk.
"The aristocracy doesn't marry for love,
they marry for money and honor."
Is what Maximilien said
still bothering you?
He was right. As much
as I hate to admit it.
That's how marriages work,
you know?
I'm not getting married
because I want to, either.
Baron Franz d'Epinay!
I'd like a word.
Why aren't you with
your fiancée?
How is that any of
your business?
Don't you love her?!
I like her.
I like her as just
another girl.
How can you talk
like that?!
Wait a minute, Maximilien!
Let me handle this. Okay?
If she's your fiancée,
you should love her with all your heart!
You didn't have to
say it like that.
I said what was on my mind,
that's all.
You're too irresponsible.
You're always like that.
I guess I'm no different.
I've never been in love with someone,
not like he is.
Albert, what do you think it
means to be in love with someone?
It's nothing but trouble.
I'll let you do what you can
to straighten this out.
What? Hey!
Wait!
Let's do it.
I can't go through
with it...
What are you talking about?
Just do it like we planned,
and you'll do fine!
First off,
you compliment her!
Compliment her?
On what?
On anything! Her dress!
Her makeup!
That's Crown Prosecutor Villefort.
He's Valentine's father.
Isn't he scary?
Even small-time crooks get the death penalty
when he gets his hands on them.
That's Valentine's mother.
They're not related by blood, though.
Edouard! Come here
this instant!
Edouard, her younger brother.
He and Valentine have different mothers.
I don't wanna!
Take a look. Aren't these
beautiful horses?
I hate horses!
I'm sorry, he can be such a handful.
I'm so embarrassed.
Is Valentine coming?
That girl seems to prefer
staying at home.
I hate Valentine, too!
They'll be coming soon.
It's nothing, Grandfather.
Mademoiselle, the Viscount Albert
de Morcerf is here to see you.
Hi.
About last night...
I think he has something that
he wants to say to you.
Go on.
Um...
I'm sorry, I have to prepare
my grandfather's dinner...
Hey! Wait!
I'm in...
I've fallen in love
with you!
I love you!
Geez, our plans have
gone out the window!
That's enough from you! I'll talk to
her first, so you go wait over there!
I love you!
I think she knows that!
I'm sorry if we startled you.
This wasn't what we had in mind.
He must have been
making fun of me.
No! He meant it!
What's this all about?
Why now?
Maximilien meant
what he said.
He's just a little... clumsy
at expressing himself.
I don't want to hear what he has to say. I'm already...
Franz has told me
how he feels.
He says that he only thinks of you as the
fiancée chosen for him by his parents.
But you feel the same way,
don't you?
That's why he says you should
do what you want.
He might not have a title, but Maximilien
is a fine soldier and an honest man.
And most important of all,
he's deeply in love with you.
I'm sure that he'll
make you...
Please leave.
No one... No one considers
what I want.
Valentine...
Get out.
I will now pass judgment.
The defendant is found guilty of the crimes
of larceny and insulting the aristocracy,
...and is hereby sentenced
to death.
There were extenuating
circumstances!
You'll get no sympathy
from me!
Trash like you disturb the
public order of the kingdom...
You have a visitor.
Hey. Do you miss
the outside world?
Are you getting along
with Valentine?
I've heard that you
beat her severely.
Who on earth
told you that?!
It's just a rumor.
I like to think that I'm attentive
as can be to that girl.
Just because she's the daughter of
his old wife doesn't mean that l...
Driver? Aren't we going
a little too fast?
It's not me, Madame!
The horses!
They aren't obeying me!
You are not harmed,
I trust?
Why, it's the Count
of Monte Cristo!
We have you to thank
for our lives.
It was fortunate indeed that I had on hand
one who is skilled in the handling of horses.
You look weird!
Are you an alien?
Don't be such
a rascal!
Curiosity is a sign
of intelligence.
We still don't know
your name...
This is the Count
of Monte Cristo.
He and my husband
are practically family.
I heard something about you buying
the late Prince's booth at the opera...
How embarrassing.
It is not my custom to attract
undue attention to myself,
...but there were no other
seats to be had.
This is Héloise, the wife of
Crown Prosecutor Villefort.
Then one might say that you are the
wife of Paris' guardian angel.
You're such a flatterer.
Your horses still seem
to be agitated.
Allow us to return you
to your homes.
If the good Madame Villefort is amenable,
I shall see to it personally.
Oh, my...
I've never seen her
like that before.
Madame has returned!
Maximilien! Hurry!
Barrois! Tea for our guest!
Please, that won't be
necessary, Madame.
Please, call me Héloise, Count.
Valentine! We have
a visitor!
Mademoiselle says that
she is feeling unwell.
Honestly, that girl...
Valentine!
Can't you even come out
and say hello to our guest?!
Valentine!
She is utterly miserable.
Maybe you're right.
I can tell.
Deep down, her heart
yearns for freedom.
But she is averting her eyes
from those feelings.
You might be right.
She is delicate
and fragile!
Can't you hear her soul
crying out?!
I can hear it,
all right.
It says, "No one considers
what I want."
I don't. Neither do you.
None of us do.
That girl is always making
trouble for me.
Perhaps she gets it from her late mother.
She's sickly and stays cooped up indoors.
I'm trying my best to raise her
to be more sociable, but...
"She's gonna die young."
Isn't that what you said, Mama?
Edouard! You and
your nonsense!
I feel sorry for my
own child, too.
Valentine stands to inherit the fortune
of her grandfather, Monsieur Noirtier,
...as well has that of the Marquis Saint-Meran
on her mother's side,
...but this boy will
receive nothing.
It saddens me
to hear that.
Siblings should be equally fortunate,
even if unrelated by blood.
He's got fangs
like a vampire!
Edouard!
You're making me angry!
Vampire! Vampire!
He's a blue-faced vampire!
I'm sorry, he's such
a rude boy...
Not at all, he is
a darling child.
To apologize for his behavior, shall
I show you to my secret place?
It's a modest little refuge.
I'm worried about her.
But there is nothing that
I can do for her...
What is it?
So, this greenhouse is your refuge...
It is magnificent.
You flatter me.
These flowers might be
my only friends.
Belladonna. Mandragora. Datura.
Your favorite flowers all share
a fascinating trait, Madame.
What might that be?
In each of them, their beautiful petals
conceal a deadly poison.
I had no idea...
Hey!
My love of horticulture grew
into an interest in botany.
It isn't a woman's place to be
interested in such things.
Could it be that you also have
an interest in toxicology?
Why would I be interested
in such horrible things?
Horrible? Why should
it be horrible?
Toxicology and pharmacology
are two sides of the same coin.
Also, nothing is more enticing
to human beings than poison.
Am I mistaken?
Poisons that steal a man's
life away in an instant.
Poisons that kill slowly
and leave no trace of itself.
One must wonder how
many poisonings...
...have been consigned to the darkness,
known to no one.
And one more thing.
There is a beauty to those who have
been captivated by poison's charms.
Hey! Gentlemen don't peep into
other people's windows!
This trinket is commonly referred to
as a Borgia Ring.
Come. Press on the stone
and see what happens.
It is said that Lucrezia Borgia used
these to dispatch countless people.
And among her victims
was her own husband...
That ring belongs
to you, Madame.
I'm so happy...
It is nothing, a mere
getting-acquainted gift.
Grandfather...
I want to go somewhere
far away.
To some faraway place where
no one knows who I am.
It's nothing but trouble.
Benedetto! Take a look
out the left window.
That's Viscount Albert
de Morcerf.
A party at
the Count's villa.
In the labyrinth, we cross paths
with a beautiful, horrible past.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo, Act 8:
Act 8:
A Night in Boulogne
..."A Night in Boulogne."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!