Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
At long last, the time has come for my friend
to bid farewell to things of beauty.
Sincerity. Trust.
Friendship.
All those virtues, all those wonderful things
that we possess during childhood,
...he has now cast into the darkness
of space, bidding them adieu.
Act 16:
Scandal
"Planet Janina invaded
by Empire 15 years ago."
"Space Forces
hurriedly deployed,"
"...commissioned officer makes
secret deal with Empire."
Paris has been shaken to its
foundation by this scandal...
...involving lead presidential
candidate General Morcerf.
Take me to Space Forces
Imperial Headquarters.
I'm Albert de Morcerf.
That's the son
of the general!
Were you and your family aware of what
your father had done on Janina?
Was the General trying to get at
the Pasha of Janina's fortune?
Ow! Hey, watch it!
Don't push!
What do you think of your
father's shameful acts?
Get out of my way!
The General should apologize
to the people of Paris!
Yeah, he's right!
Issue an apology!
We've heard rumors to the effect that
your parents are from Marseilles.
I don't know anything about that!
Didn't I tell you to stand aside?!
There are rumors going around that
your family isn't really of nobility.
Is it safe to assume that they
falsified their background?
Don't be rude! I've had about enough
of you people insulting my father!
Insulting?! The ones who have been insulted
all these years are us! The citizens of Paris!
You're the son of a traitor who colluded with the
enemy and sold out the Pasha out of greed!
Viscount Morcerf?!
Where's my father?!
Tell me where my father is!
You came in through the front gate?
What a foolish thing to do...
Come with me to the back entrance.
It's not safe for you here.
My father! Where is he?
Let me speak with him!
Unfortunately, he is preoccupied with
dealing with everything that has come up,
...so I believe that he might
not return here today.
Oh, I see.
In that case, give my father this message.
There is something I want to discuss with him.
And also tell my father
that I believe in him.
Understood.
Enter.
I have done everything
that I can.
However, explaining things to the
National Assembly may prove difficult.
Their discussions are already centering
around issuing subpoenas for witnesses.
Understood.
You can go.
Your son was
just here, sir.
As per your orders, I told him
that you were not here.
What did he say?
Your son said that he
believes in his father.
Albert!
Quick, get in!
Eugenie!
Where do you think you're going
at a time like this?
Why can't you do as
you're told for once?!
No! Let me go!
Let go of me!
Was I talking to myself when I ordered
you people again and again...
...not to let my daughter
out of the house?!
Call security!
Yes, Monsieur!
At once!
Something terrible has happened to my
friend's family, and you're telling me...
...to look the
other way?!
You little fool! If you went out there now,
those journalists would eat you alive!
They'll write about your relationship with Albert,
blending fact and fiction until it becomes a farce,
...and we'll be made into toys
for the public's amusement!
Can't you see that?!
I don't care about
any of that!
Listen, this matter isn't
just about you!
I won't tolerate anything that might lower
your value, whatever it might be!
Keep a close eye on her to make sure
that she doesn't leave the house!
Are you truly that worried
about Viscount Morcerf?
If you like, I will go in your place to inquire
after Monsieur Albert's well-being.
But I...
You should stay here.
I can't bear the thought of a wonderful person
like you being disgraced by heartless people.
I've been looking everywhere
for you, Albert.
We're in the middle of a huge scandal, and you
walk right into military HQ, the belly of the beast.
That was one stupid stunt,
you know that?
"A Word of Advice to General Fernand Morcerf.
By Robert Beauchamp."
I want you to take me
to Beauchamp's place.
Right now!
Hey, sorry I kept
you guys waiting.
Albert, what are you...
You bastard! All this time, you were
only pretending to be my friend!
"Watch out for scandals,"
my ass!
You were planning all along to sell out
my father to get your big scoop!
Isn't that right?!
Right?!
Listen, Albert, I'm going tell you everything
that I uncovered in my investigation.
Just the plain truth.
No lies.
So before you do anything rash,
just hear me out.
Take a look
at this.
This is a copy of a title deed that I bought
from a black-market merchant in the Empire.
"I cede ownership of Queen Vasiliki
of Janina and Princess Haidee..."
"...for the sum of
100 million Francs."
"Seller, Fernand Mondego."
What's this supposed
to prove?!
I followed the tracks of
this "Mondego" person.
But every last bit of information
on him had been erased.
It was almost as if he
had never existed.
But Mondego existed,
all right.
When he returned
to Marseilles,
...he immediately used the money he
had received to purchase orders of nobility.
And that's when he
changed his name.
Prove it!
Show me your proof!
Albert, I was also able to learn through
Ministry of the Interior records...
...that Mondego was an old friend
of Villefort's.
They were both originally
from Marseilles.
And then Villefort purged all information
regarding Mondego from all public records.
And that's how the man known as Mondego
was erased from existence,
...and the man known as Fernand de Morcerf
was born in his place.
What're you two saying?! That my father is
the same man as that monster, Mondego?!
Do you two get your kicks by ganging up on
somebody and writing about their problems?!
Come off it! Do you seriously think I decided to
have some fun by writing a made-up article?!
Do you have any idea what it did
to me to write that article?
Do you really think I'm a slimeball who
would sell out his friends for a scoop?!
All right, that's enough.
I'm a journalist.
I have a duty to get the truth out
to the people, no matter the cost.
Dammit!
Gankutsuou, the immortal man
living in the Chateau d'lf...
That mark I saw on the Count's forehead
that night in Auteuil...
...was the mark of Gankutsuou,
no doubt about it.
Then does that mean that the Count
has turned into Gankutsuou?
What's he doing
in Paris?
If you keep pushing yourself this hard,
you'll ruin your health.
Did you stay up all night
again last night?
You sure are a worrywart,
Maximilien.
Please eat. It's just country food, but it
will help you keep your strength up.
Hey, that looks great...
Thanks.
Go on, take it
to him.
No way!
I'm too embarrassed!
You were the one who said that you
wanted to meet Franz, weren't you?
Then you come in
with me, big brother.
And what are you two
up to out here?
Big brother!
Um... Uh...
Come on over.
Here! Eat this!
She said you looked like you were in
the dumps, so we made these together.
Thanks, you two.
Mark my words!
You'll be next!
Disaster will come calling
at your house, too!
This feels strange.
For there to be so many family members
in the same house, I mean.
Aren't there a great many people living
in your own house, Monsieur Franz?
A long time ago, maybe.
There were lots of servants, too.
But now, there's just a few servants
and my mother.
Oh, I didn't know.
There are a lot of different
kinds of aristocrats.
The engagement between Valentine and me
was forced on us by Monsieur Villefort...
...just because my family has been known for
generations in Paris as staunch royalists.
Unlike Albert's family, mine
doesn't have a large fortune,
...so we thought it wouldn't hurt to have
some backing once I got into diplomacy.
I'm sorry. I said all those things without knowing
the circumstances behind your engagement.
Hey, I'm not so dumb that I need
to have you worrying about me.
You'd never guess it by looking at me,
but I hit the books pretty hard.
Monsieur Noirtier
said it, too.
He said that he wanted you to make
Valentine happy in his place.
I will!
Who's this man?
My father. He passed away
three years ago.
That's a beautiful ship
that he owned.
She was called the Pharaon.
She was the star of our fleet.
She's changed hands now,
though.
Edmond Dantes?
Oh, Edmond? You know
You know him?
You know who he is?!
Yes, he worked as first mate
for Morrel and Son.
No go, huh?
With that circus out there, I'll never make it
through the front door OR the back door.
This way, this way!
Over here.
This is the one gate in the whole mansion
that isn't hooked into the security system.
How do you know
all this stuff?
Hey, Peppo!
Get a move on. The paparazzi
are coming.
I owe you one.
Goodbye, Albert.
Hey, there's somebody over there!
C'mon, let's go!
Mother!
Are you here?!
Mother, aren't you home?
Mother!
Albert...
Mother! I'm glad
you're okay.
Thank goodness you're safe.
Thank goodness...
Mother, l...
Look at how haggard you are.
I bet you haven't eaten.
Wait here. I'll have them
fix something for you.
Stop it, Mother. Stop pretending
that nothing's wrong.
I'm sick of people treating me
like some clueless kid!
I don't want to hear
any more lies.
Fernand and I aren't
true aristocrats.
We were commoners born in a small village
outside of Marseilles called Catalonia.
Mother...
Then what is Father's
real name?
Your father's real name
is Fernand Mondego.
By the time I realized what was happening,
it was already too late to turn back.
Once I said that we were aristocrats by birth,
I had no choice but to keep playing the part.
And then the truth finally struck home in the
middle of your father's campaign speech.
Why?! Why are you saying these
things, too, Mother?!
Why don't you have
any faith in Father?!
I heard the speech given by the Janinan
princess that day with my own two ears.
If I had sensed even for an instant
that her words were lies,
...I would have passed judgment over her
in Heaven's stead right then and there.
But it was true...
Albert... We each must face the consequences
of the things we have done.
We must never be allowed to
avert our eyes from the truth.
Haidee wanted this to happen
from the very beginning!
Damn it!
DAMN IT!
Every year, my father and I would go to
place flowers on Edmond Dantes' grave.
Father would always stare out at the sea,
and would never tell me much about him.
But as my father lay on his deathbed, he kept
calling out his name, tears in his eyes.
"I want to see Edmond!
I want to see Edmond!"
"Why wasn't I able
to save Edmond?!"
Maximilien, show me Morrel & Son's
crew roster.
I haven't seen many of the records
that date back to my father's time.
Edmond... Edmond...
This is him!
It's not him...
His face is completely different.
Still...
What is it about
this person?
The name Edmond was in
Monsieur Noirtier's memories.
He said he was sent to a prison in deep space
for a crime he didn't commit.
I don't believe it!
Danglars?!
He was the ship's purser?
Now I get it...
So THAT'S what this is all about...
I have to get back there, and fast.
Albert's in danger.
What in the world
is the matter?
He's alive!
Edmond Dantes
is alive!
Haidee!
Get out here,
Show yourself!
Haidee!
Long time, no see,
little boy.
Not since we met
back on Luna, right?
Luigi Vampa?
What are you doing
in the Count's home?
"What are you doing,"
he says...
This boy's still as wooly-headed
as ever, isn't he?
Go ahead and explain things
to him.
But you said that you'd
left the bandit gang, Peppo!
I've been keeping an eye on you all this
time on the Count's orders, Albert.
I've also been sending detailed reports
of your movements to the Count.
Why would the Count
do such a thing?
Come on, you must have
a vague idea by now.
About why the Count made friends with you
on Luna, and then came to Paris.
Shut your mouth!
Where's Haidee?!
Hurry up and
send out Haidee!
His servants have
left the mansion.
Their master is due to arrive
on Earth any time now.
"General Morcerf,
the Scandal of Janina"...
You're making your move,
aren't you, Count?
Albert, please stay safe.
Haidee!
Count, you have to tell me.
Where can I find hope?
Where is the truth
you spoke of?
Next time on Gankutsuou,
the Count of Monte Cristo act 17,
Act 17:
The Confession
..."The Confession."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!