Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
The youth, who had been ravaged by poison,
was restored to life through my friend's efforts.
However, my friend
said something to me.
I will not let his soul
be lost yet.
Not until the day that he himself
snuffs out that light.
Act 10:
The Letter From Edmond
Monsieur Albert.
Have you managed
to get any sleep?
If there is one thing I have
confidence in, it's my stamina.
Well, you look
like hell to me.
It looks like all the maids
have been laid off.
Yes, I heard.
I can't leave her alone
in this house.
Besides, Franz told
me something.
Marriage isn't necessarily the only way
to make the person you love happy.
And so, I've been mulling it over
as best I can.
What is the one thing that she
needs most of all right now?
Maximilien...
She may be asleep now, but I think
that Mademoiselle Valentine...
...is lonely to the
point of crying.
So I at least want to be by her side
when she wakes up.
Which is why I made up
my mind today.
I'm going to take her to my family home
in Marseilles to recuperate.
I don't want her to have to endure
any more suffering.
I had a feeling that
you would be here.
Your Honor, I came here today
to discuss...
Mark my words, boy.
I dare you to try to take my daughter
so much as one foot out of this house.
The instant you do, I'll have you
arrested as a kidnapper.
That is no threat.
But the things that are happening
in this house are...
Are none of
your business!
Get out! You too, Albert.
Begging your pardon, sir,
but someone
is trying to kill your family!
I myself was almost...
By "someone," you say?
If there is anyone close to hand
who could be described as suspicious,
...it would be that impudent
fraud of a Count!
Are we clear?! From now on,
this is strictly a family matter!
I strictly forbid you
from interfering!
The following is a report regarding my
investigation on the Count of Monte Cristo.
In the course of visiting the various
locations indicated by Your Honor,
...I discovered by accident that a certain old
priest was making a similar set of inquiries.
He has visited this area several times
during the past three months.
The priest seems to be gathering information
on an old man who died penniless here.
The old man's name
was Louis Dantes.
In order to ascertain the
priest's objectives,
...as well as to clarify the connection
between him and the Count of Monte Cristo,
...I plan to investigate the house that
Louis Dantes lived in while he was alive.
The old man's name
was Louis Dantes.
Dantes...
Dantes?!
Papa, my school play is today.
You're coming, aren't you?
Didn't your mother tell you? I'm sorry,
but some urgent business has come up.
But you promised! You said that you would
come this time, no matter what!
Papa's work keeps him
very busy, Edouard.
I don't care about that!
You're a liar, Papa!
Get him out of here. It's your job as his
mother to explain these things to him!
But Edouard has been so
excited about today.
I don't care how excited he was!
Stop bothering me!
Tell my teacher that the
yellow dwarf
isn't gonna be in the play!
Monsieur.
What?
You're still here?
Hurry up and get your bags packed.
An invitation... An invitation
to a funeral just arrived.
What's the meaning
of this?
It's all well and good that I've
inherited vast land holdings,
...but there's still so much
that I don't understand.
The first thing is to learn the law
inside and out.
That goes doubly so when you've come
into possession of a huge inheritance.
If we don't keep estate taxes and whatnot
under control, it can become a big problem.
Oh, I had no idea.
Truth be told, I'm looking for a partner who will
be able to effectively manage my assets.
Oh, a partner,
you say?
Mademoiselle Eugenie, would it be all right if
I paid you a visit in your room after I'm done?
I'm sorry, I'm in the middle
of my piano lessons.
Oh, for Heaven's sake...
Please forgive her lack of charm.
Not at all.
This is just between
you and me,
...but there's a bit of a scandal beginning
to brew around her fiancée's family.
Is something the matter?
N-No, it's nothing.
I have a letter here
for the General.
Oh. Thanks.
Edmond Dantes?
Yes?
I'm sorry,
are you working?
No, that's all right.
I was just finishing up.
There's something that I want
to talk to you about.
There is, eh?
Have a seat.
Now that the election is drawing near, there are
a lot of matters that have to be taken care of.
I can imagine.
Oh, this was addressed to you.
A funeral invitation?
The thing is, I just got back
from Villefort Manor.
I'd like to get Valentine
away from that place.
I was wondering if there was anything
that you could do to persuade her father.
She's in great danger
every minute she stays there.
If the request came from you,
Monsieur Villefort might listen to...
Why do you feel the need to poke your
nose into another family's affairs?
What do you mean, why?
My friend is...
Neither you nor your friend have any right
to throw someone else's house into turmoil!
How can you say that?! You have
no idea what's going on!
If we don't do something,
she'll...
My answer is no!
Don't get involved any further!
What are you
so angry about?!
My friend is in trouble, and you're
telling me to just abandon her?!
Forget it. It was stupid of me
to even ask.
What's the matter?
You look upset.
I got into a shouting match
with Father, that's all.
I see.
Mother, do you know someone
named Edmond Dantes?
Edmond Dantes?
Yeah. That was the name of the sender
on a letter that came for Father today.
The instant Father saw that name, he started
acting strangely for some reason.
What's the matter?
It's nothing. I haven't been
sleeping well lately, that's all.
With the election race almost here,
I bet you're tired, too.
Yes, that might
be it.
You should take it easy.
Who is he? Who's this
"Edmond Dantes" person?
That man is
long since dead...
What could be worth coming
all the way out here for?
Well, damn!
So, you were sent
one of these, too.
Who's behind this?
I don't know.
It's just a stupid prank.
Let's get out of here.
But they knew us.
Someone knows about the connection
between the three of us.
Well, well, the gang's
all here...
Who the hell
are you?
You're...
I'm your old friend Caderousse.
Now that you've made it big,
have you forgotten about me...
...along with all those
unpleasant memories?
I see you're all big, powerful men now,
not at all like you were in the old days!
You're the one who's behind this, Caderousse?
What kind of stupid stunt is this?!
I-I have one of
these invitations, too...
Who could it be?
Someone else knows
about us?
What's going on here?
You're asking me who else knows
besides the four of us here?
Only this man.
Edmond Dantes?
But he was sent to the
Chateau d'lf and...
Yes, I thought
he died there.
The dead man has
come back to us!
Edmond would never forget
what we did to him.
He would never forget what we did,
not in a million years.
Whose body is
in here, then?
Who is in this coffin?!
Open it.
No way!
I don't wanna!
Quit your whimpering
and open the thing!
Don't make me!
Go on!
Hurry up and do it!
Boville!
Hurry, this way!
Is it really okay for us
to be doing this?
There's no other way!
Mama, did you hear something
upstairs just now?
I'm not sure. Maybe your grandfather
fell out of his wheelchair again.
And with Valentine asleep, there's
no one to help him up, is there?
On the other hand, it might turn out to be
a good rehabilitation exercise for him.
Watch what you're doing!
Sorry about that.
Noirtier...
I will keep Mademoiselle Valentine safe.
Is it me, or is he saying that
he wants us to go that way?
What's this mean?
I don't believe it!
Was it really her?!
You sure were gone a long time.
Where have you been?
That's none of
your business.
Oh, my!
I'm so offended!
Gosh, and here I was gonna give you
some great news...
Tell me what?
Maximilien finally decided
to put his plan into action.
The scene of the crime, Villefort Manor.
Accomplices, two. Franz and Renaud.
They came here to get you,
but you weren't around.
What's the matter?
Commander! Commander!
This is Edouard!
Three criminals spotted!
Good work!
Apprehend them immediately!
And just what do you think you're doing
with my daughter?
What are you doing
in here, my son?
Nothing, l...
You seem to be doing a lot
of research regarding me.
What is it that you
hope to uncover?
Something about me? Or about
the Count of Monte Cristo?
Allow me to tell you
about both of them.
It will be...
...far faster this way!
Monsieur.
Monsieur!
What is it?
There seems to be some sort of
commotion in front of the manor.
What?
Those kids!
Summon my men
at once!
The lovers depart,
and new misgivings arrive.
Unexpected news leaves me
at a loss.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo act 11:
Act 11:
An Engagement Broken
..."An Engagement Broken."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!