Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
Even when wounded and made to suffer,
he is reborn and gets right back up.
Youth, what a formidable
thing it is!
However, our resolve to have our vengeance
will shatter even that.
Our grip on the reins will never loosen,
no matter what.
Act 20:
Farewell, Eugenie
Monsieur. This arrived
from Baron Danglars.
I don't believe it!
What's up?
This says that the signing ceremony for
Eugenie's wedding will be held tomorrow.
He must really be in rough
financial shape.
I can't believe he's rushing his
daughter's wedding like this.
Eugenie...
This won't stop me!
Now that's just sad.
It looks like you lost your pride the same
instant that you lost your status.
Say whatever you want about me,
but you ARE gonna let me through.
Unfortunately, the princess is in a
bit of a foul mood at the moment.
She even did this
to me.
What the hell did you
do to Eugenie?!
Isn't it obvious?
After all, we're to be man and wife!
She put up some fierce
resistance, though.
You bastard!
Relax, I didn't do anything as barbaric
as forcing myself on her.
After all, I told her,
"By marrying me,"
"...you'll not only be safeguarding
the lifestyle of your own family,"
"...but also that of the Morcerf,
no, the Mondego family."
The instant I mentioned your name,
she started behaving herself.
I owe you a debt of gratitude.
You're our sacred Cupid!
Tomorrow will go off without
a hitch, I take it?
What about
Cavalcanti's activities?
Everything is going
according to plan.
There is nothing to worry about.
Please get some rest.
Very well.
You may go.
Yes, Excellency.
Count...
Humiliation and despair.
Those will be my gifts...
...to my beloved father
and mother,
...as well as my
little sister.
Eugenie...
Mademoiselle, you look
so lovely!
Why?
Excuse me?
Why am I wearing
a dress like this?
Now, now... Today's affair will just be a
signing ceremony attended only by family.
That said, I think it would be best
for you to wear your formal gown.
Ever since I was a little girl, I
never enjoyed talking with you.
Well, I never!
Eugenie! Look at you,
you're beautiful!
It really does look wonderful on you.
Andrea will be thrilled.
I'd like to be alone
until the ceremony.
Y-Yes, of course.
Go ahead and do that.
After all, things are going
to become quite hectic soon.
Come on, now. With him in the family,
we've got nothing to worry about.
He's young, but that boy
has nerves of steel.
Your performance at the opera house
was most impressive.
For me, meeting fresh, young talent is a joy
that I would not trade for anything.
If you are interested, would you care
to come to our conservatory?
Signed, F. Damrosch,
Head Instructor of Keyboard Instruments.
Monsieur Danglars is a
slick customer, all right.
He's trying to show everyone that the Danglars
family's financial situation has stabilized...
...by inviting his stockholders and having us
cover his daughter's wedding,
Because he'll be in effective control
of Marquis Cavalcanti's fortune.
The real question is, what's
Albert going to do about it?
You think he's
gonna show up?
He'll be here. He's not a member
of the aristocracy anymore.
That means
he's free now.
Albert!
I'm so sorry...
I couldn't disobey Luigi.
He's like a father to me.
I won't ask you to forgive me.
But at least let me do something to help!
Give it up.
I've had it up to here with people
jerking me around!
Just like you want to save the girl you love,
I want to help the boy I love.
Hey, here comes
the bride!
Eugenie!
Eugenie, you have no idea how long
I've waited for this day to come.
Very well,
let us begin.
Ladies and gentlemen, we will now
carry out the signing of the vows...
...between Eugenie de Danglars
and Andrea Cavalcanti.
We will begin with
the groom-to-be.
Yes, sir.
You have no objections to sharing
all property, bonds, stocks,
...and other assets in your possession
with Eugenie, your bride-to-be?
I do not.
In that case, please place your signature
on the marriage contract.
And now, Eugenie,
the bride-to-be.
You have no objections to sharing
all property, bonds, stocks,
...and other assets in your possession
with your groom-to-be?
What's the matter, Eugenie?!
Hurry up and answer the man!
Something doesn't
seem right...
Quiet, please!
I will repeat the question.
You have no objections to sharing
all property, bonds, stocks,
...and other assets in your possession
with your groom-to-be?
I'm so sorry, she seems
to be extremely nervous.
Naturally, she has
no objections.
Danglars must really
be desperate.
Yeah.
Go on! Sign the contract,
Eugenie!
What the...?
Hey!
Maybe I forgot to pay
the power bill...
That's a good one!
Eugenie...
They say that Marie Antoinette, the wife of
Louis XVI, who ruled during the Middle Ages,
...spilled ink onto their marriage contract
during the signing ceremony,
...as if hinting at the misfortune
that would later befall her.
Hey!
This stain is saying the same thing.
I'd reconsider if I were you.
W-Who the hell are you?!
Who put you up to this?!
Nobody put me up to it.
This way.
I just don't approve
of this wedding.
Cut the crap! You don't work here!
Hold it! What do you think you're...
What's your name?!
I'm sorry, but this is too good
a scoop to pass up.
Stop that, you bastard!
Give me that!
Monsieur Danglars, I think that he's
the least of your worries right now.
What are the police
doing here?!
Andrea Cavalcanti!
You're under arrest on charges of fraud,
falsification of lineage,
...larceny, rape, as well
as six other offenses!
Let go of me, you bastards!
Let go!
Shut your mouth,
you fake aristocrat!
F-Fake aristocrat?!
Shove it, you miser!
Son of a...
I was so close!
My revenge isn't
over yet!
W-What are you talking about, Andrea?
Let go of me!
C'mon, Eugenie, let's go!
Together!
This way!
Hey, this is...
I can't believe it.
You two are sneaking in
through that hole again?
I secretly weakened it last night.
I made it big enough for adults.
I'd completely forgotten
about this.
Let's get moving.
Right.
Hey!
Your chariot awaits, Princess!
Renaud!
Bye-bye...
Reports say that Cavalcanti
has been arrested.
Bertuccio.
Excellency?
Do you dream?
Yes, just like anyone else.
I no longer have dreams.
For I no longer sleep,
you see.
In its place, I had this golden
box garden constructed.
But now, this room is the only place
in which I may remain myself.
And this single glass of water
comprises my entire fortune.
And what of you? What do you intend
to do once all of this is over?
What I dream of... is to
serve you forever.
But even if that dream
can never be,
...there is no one but Your Excellency
that I can serve.
When this is over, my wealth will
belong to you and the others.
Use it in the pursuit
of your own dreams.
Bankruptcy means nothing to me!
I still have money!
I'll run, and run,
and keep on running!
Hurry up!
I'll escape all of them!
Boarding procedures for flight 747
to New York are almost complete.
All boarding passengers, please
report to the boarding gate.
Um, I...
Um...
You go first, Eugenie.
No, you can go first, Albert.
I'm sorry about the
way I've acted.
I was always thinking
of myself.
I never gave a second thought
to your feelings.
From now on, no matter what happens,
no matter where I am,
...you'll always be in
my thoughts, Eugenie.
Albert... You'll always be
in mine, too.
Flight 747 to New York will
be departing momentarily.
Passengers intending to board, please
proceed to gate 4 immediately.
Albert...
It'll be okay, Eugenie.
Whenever things get tough,
I want you to play the piano.
The piano that I love
to hear you play.
I'll always be thinking
of you when I play.
Yeah! Show those guys in
New York how it's done!
Flight 747 to New York
will be departing momentarily.
So, Eugenie's flight
took off okay?
Yeah.
Is that from Eugenie?
Yeah. She said that she had it in the
bodice of her dress the whole time.
She did, huh?
To my dearest Albert.
Happy birthday.
By the time you read this, chances are
that I'll no longer be with you.
So instead of giving you a present,
I'd like you to hear me out.
Albert, this is important. I don't
want you to ever hate anyone.
Something occurred
to me.
Feelings of love and feelings of hate
both start out as caring about someone.
It's sad, but I think that sometimes,
when those feelings aren't returned,
...those feelings of love
change into hate.
If something like that ever happens, I want
you to think back to our childhood.
Back to a time when we could
only love openly and honestly...
...no matter how often
we got hurt.
I want you to
go on living, Albert.
Love people openly without
being scared of getting hurt.
I truly was lucky
to have known you.
Franz d'Epinay.
Forever in your heart.
I have to see him
one more time.
There's something that I have
to talk to him about.
Destiny.
And revenge.
The merciless gears
keep turning.
I once again find myself
standing before him.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo, act 21...
Act 21:
The Golden Boy's True Identity
..."The Golden Boy's True Identity."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!