Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
A rage that is only
permitted by youth.
A pure, unadulterated rage.
That is the most appropriate description for
the emotion expressed by the young soul.
How exquisite it is!
How I desire it!
More! More!
Act 18:
The Duel
C'mon, baby, why not?
Is it because you are a soldier's son that
you did not give in to fear and run away?
En garde!
Edmond... is dead.
This body retains only his
shape and appearance.
There is no longer anything
of Edmond himself left within it.
I will show you proof that Edmond,
the man you once loved, is now dead.
Edmond...
It's done!
I'm cutting it pretty close...
I wrote a message in
a birthday card for him,
...but I think we're too old for that kind of thing,
so I feel awkward giving it to him in person.
Anyway, give it to Albert
after I leave tomorrow.
Please?
I'm begging you.
He should just be a man
and give it to him himself...
I don't believe it...
It can't be!
Not so fast, Madame!
This can't be...
He's only a...
Edmond!
I'm sorry, Madame, but I
can't let you do that.
Please, let me go! I have a duty
to keep that boy safe!
Please understand,
this is a duel.
A formal duel, in which Monsieur Albert
challenged the Count.
Albert is... Albert is still a child!
Call it off!
No, Madame. Monsieur Albert
holds the rank of viscount.
In the eyes of the law, this duel
is completely legitimate.
Edmond!
Please, stop!
Your feelings...
Your pain...
Your loneliness...
I'll... I'll bear the brunt
of all of it!
Stop!
STOP!
Countess Morcerf!
Watch closely!
Watch as I prove to you that
Edmond Dantes is dead!
Please, stop...
Please!
STOP!
Oh, crap!
Why didn't you
wake me up?!
Franz!
Fran...
He wouldn't...!
This is what I've been
waiting for...
To become Gankutsuou is
to lose your humanity.
As the composition of his entire body
is being replaced with crystal,
...the temperature of his heart
drops and drops,
...until it, too,
is eventually lost.
The instant he is released from his suffering,
he will also lose his emotions.
Anger... sadness...
hatred...
He will lose
them all.
That is what he fears
above all else.
That is why his heart
is the last part of him.
If he still retains even fragments
of human emotion,
...his heart alone will
be vulnerable.
Gankutsuou, come closer...
That's right...
Come straight at me.
Franz...
Franz!
I will now prove who
the victor is...
Right here and now!
You were cursed
since birth,
...born from the union of that cowardly
traitor Fernand Mondego and Mercedes.
You, who have walked in the sunlight your
entire life, could not possibly know...
...the tale of the innocent man who
had his youth stolen away from him,
...and the old man who fell victim
to loneliness and starvation!
Fate has now come full circle, and the
curse is about to reach its fruition!
Curse your fate, and your parents,
as you die by my sword!
Don't do it!
FRANZ!
I sure hope he likes it...
Albert...
The... The doctor's gonna be here soon,
so hang in there...
Boy, you were out cold
last night...
Those pills worked pretty good,
didn't they?
Why? Why did you do it?
I'm sorry... that things
turned out this way...
But you taught me how to handle a sword,
so I put up a pretty good fight...
That's enough!
Don't... Don't try to talk.
Idiot... You think you
can boss me around?
Franz!
Albert...
I had a dream last night...
Maybe it was last year...
Or was it the year before last?
The two of us and Eugenie went
to Normandy together, remember?
No, or was it in the
south of France?
The three of us sprawled out
on the beach,
...and we celebrated
your birthday.
It was so windy that when we tried to eat
a piece of cheese, it tasted like sand...
And Eugenie's favorite hat blew away...
She was really depressed about it, remember?
Happy birthday...
Congratulations on
turning sixteen...
Franz, hang on
a little longer...
The doctor's gonna be here
any minute now, okay?
You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay, so hang on.
Say, Franz?
It's nice and warm out here,
isn't it?
Franz?
FRANZ!
Alone, I walk through the
darkness of the night...
...as I wait for the sun.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo, act 19:
Act 19:
Even if I Should Stop Being Me
..."Even if I Should Stop Being Me."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!