Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
Wishing to express his feelings,
the young man ran to the opera house,
...where his former fiancée
awaited him.
However, he is
not yet aware.
Not yet aware of his father's sordid past, which
lies concealed behind the broken engagement.
Act 13:
Haidee
That man
is a murderer!
I am surprised to see you come
all this way, Your Honor.
Is this spectacle being provided
as a sideshow to the opera?
I take it that you
recognize this?
As I recall, that is the ring
that I gave to your wife.
It had poison
hidden inside.
Goodness, what a
fascinating contraption.
It would appear that you were
trying to kill even my wife.
Surely you jest.
Why would I do such a thing?
It's obvious!
Isn't this a simple case of that barbaric custom
from Eastern Space known as the "thrill kill"?
The Count would never
do such a thing!
You're being deceived
by that man.
The Count was the one who told us
about the threat to Valentine's life!
Even a foreigner such as myself can expect
to receive a proper trial, I take it?
Of course. By law, you will
receive an impartial trial.
Hearing that sets my mind at ease.
I have a witness to offer in my defense.
What?
Someone who knows
the whole truth.
Heloise?!
I have heard many fascinating things
from Madame and your son.
Including things which touch
upon certain family affairs.
Why, you!
What would you like to do?
Will you arrest me?
What's the deal?
I thought they were
gonna arrest him.
Not to worry,
gentlemen.
It would seem that His Honor the
Crown Prosecutor made a mistake.
Way to go, Count!
It's nice to see that hanging judge
get some egg on his face!
It would be best for you
to return to your home.
But l...
You needn't worry
about me.
Don't think for an instant
that this is over!
Monsieur Villefort...
That man wants
to ruin me.
I can't believe it! You're still
saying that nonsense?
I can sense it. I can feel an evil
presence in that man's soul.
You're still worrying
about your former fiancée?
Marquis Cavalcanti.
By all means, please
call me Andrea.
I don't know what my father
said to you,
...but I don't feel the least bit
grateful to you, is that clear?
Now, now...
It's always been my dream
to play at the opera house,
...but using money to
make it come true was...
It was your own merit that won you
the right to that concert.
The reason, of course, is that your talent
has transformed me into your humble servant.
He left you there.
It would seem that he doesn't even have
the courage to try to steal you away.
It's not here, huh?
There were no records matching
the requested term...
...in any of the volumes
owned by this library.
I see.
The Royal Library prides itself on being the
greatest repository of data in the universe.
It's hard to believe that there could
be a word that isn't registered here.
It's possible that the word is on the General
Security Directorate's banned list.
What do you mean?
Regulations are in place that
prohibit general readers...
...from browsing
classified topics.
What do you MEAN, you're cutting off
my financial support?!
I've had a few
sudden expenses.
What am I supposed to do about
the presidential election?!
I'm sorry, but I'm going
to have to cut you loose.
Me... And you...
And Villefort...
I thought it was our dream to climb
hand in hand to the top of Paris!
Oh, was it?
Why pull out when we're a single step away
from making that dream a reality?!
My, um... analysts are telling me
to quit gambling on you, General.
Is this about those letters
from Edmond?
Now, now, I'm just saying that
we all need to watch our step.
If you win the election,
...feel free to give me
a call.
Excellency, we've established a comm channel
with the Seventh Eastern Space Fleet.
That was a shameful display last night,
don't you think?
What insolence!
Who are you?!
Lucien Debray, First Secretary.
I'm hurt that you don't remember me.
Ah, the spoiled rich boy
in the Ministry of the Interior.
The Count of Monte Cristo is the
talk of Paris at the moment.
You won't be able to arrest him
without good cause.
He's plotting something,
I'm sure of it.
Can you prove it?
I'm the one who decides
who is guilty or innocent.
The General Security Directorate
is stepping in.
They suspect that you're trying
to file false charges against him.
You've gone a little
too far this time.
It's probably only a matter of time
before you're suspended from duty.
They can't!
Oh, here you are.
I need your advice
on a certain matter.
It's rare for YOU to need anybody's
advice on anything.
I had no choice but to beg an elite member
of the Ministry of the Interior for help.
Your best friend
isn't with you today?
Where's Victoria?
Madame is resting
in her room.
I have no idea what to do
with your mother.
She's been acting like this ever since
she was out in the night air...
...at the party in Auteuil
and caught a cold.
So anyway, that's why I can't
offer you a suitable welcome,
...but perhaps you'd care
to join us for dinner?
I'd love to!
I have a little work to finish up, so my daughter
will keep you company until I'm done.
Why don't you play another little tune?
For Andrea this time.
I would be honored if you did!
Oh, that reminds me...
Black hole futures?!
Now, then, let's get down
to business, Michelle!
General Morcerf has called
and made an appointment.
Never mind about that! Show me the
ultra-high density materials market!
Get to it!
Understood.
Danglars has accessed
the market.
Very well.
Sell.
Understood!
Let him eat his fill. We'll make sure
that he's fattened up properly.
Wait until the time is right, and then
leak intel that there are signs...
...of an impending massive lmperial Forces
offensive in the Central Galaxy.
Still, the thought of lining that vulture's
pockets is a little distasteful.
"Gankutsuou," huh?
Are you ready
to start?
Here we go.
Welcome to the Mansion
of State Secrets.
What IS this place?
A database that's under the direct jurisdiction
of the Ministry of the Interior.
State search keyword.
Gankutsuou.
Lucien Debray, First Secretary, class S.
Access granted.
Where are we?!
Keep quiet.
Gankutsuou is the king
of the shadows.
Which means what?
Nobody's ever seen what he looks like.
His name should never be spoken.
Those who break that taboo
meet a fate worse than death.
Is that an
urban legend?
It's the truth. He appeared on the fringes
of the galaxy a thousand years ago...
...and tried to gain control
of the criminal underworld.
He's an invader?
Gankutsuou is invincible. He controls
people by manipulating their desires.
However, he was defeated
by fate.
In June of the year 4002 of
the Louis Philippe calendar,
...he was apprehended
and incarcerated.
Incarcerated where?
We can't answer that.
Where was he imprisoned?
I hereby issue
lmperial Edict 53!
Gankutsuou was imprisoned
in the Chateau d'lf.
What happened
after that?
His death was confirmed
on December 23, 5043.
Ten years ago?!
He was in prison for more
than a thousand years?!
What was that
prisoner's name?
The Man in the
Iron Mask.
What was his
full name?!
Terminate access immediately.
Why?!
We can't answer that.
I hereby issue special provision 3
of Edict 53!
His name...
His name was...
Illegal access!
Enacting article 6, clause 2 of
the Secrets Preservation Code.
T-This isn't good...
I want to know who Gankutsuou
really is!
No, I HAVE to know!
Old man Noirtier
might know.
Who, him?
A long time ago, he used to be top dog
in the Ministry of the Interior.
But he also had a lot of enemies,
and he was brought down.
You mean the assassination
of the Prince?
He was a proponent of
peace with the Empire.
Apparently, that's made it difficult for his
son, Villefort, to move up in the world.
Of course, all that work
has been for nothing now.
Father... You must be laughing at me, a man
who's lost both his status and his family.
You must think it's poetic justice
for a man who's spent his career...
...sending innocent men to prison
and presiding over merciless trials.
That this is my punishment for defying your
wishes and supporting war against the Empire...
...and for doing away with
your compatriots.
I've worked hard
to surpass you!
To surpass you, who had the power
to sway government policy!
Do you have the slightest idea
how hard that was?!
Any idea how hard it was to be your son
in a world dominated by hawks?!
"Suspended from duty," huh?
So what?!
See if I care!
I won't let it
end like this!
Just you watch! I'll come back
from this stronger than ever!
She's been like that
since we arrived.
It's as if she's regressed
to childhood.
Excellency, are you certain
that this is a wise idea?
We can still attack after seeing how
the peace negotiations at Geneva go.
We must strike
while we have the chance!
If we are to gain the upper hand at the
negotiation table, there can be no hesitation!
A victory here will give your poll numbers
a huge boost, Excellency!
His Excellency,
the Viscount Morcerf.
Welcome to our
humble home.
What may we do
for you today?
Actually, I had hoped to
meet with the Count.
The Count's illness has
rendered him bedridden.
Yes, I'd heard.
Please, let me wish him
a speedy recovery.
I ask that you allow him
to remain undisturbed.
At times like this, he will
see no one but me.
The Count has complete
faith in you, doesn't he?
Please tell him to be on his guard
against Monsieur Villefort.
He said that he'll make the Count pay
for what he did. So he has to...
You care a great deal for the Count,
don't you, Monsieur Albert?
Yes, I suppose...
I am glad that you are concerned
for his well-being.
How long have you
been with him?
It has been a long time now. A long time
since the Count deigned to purchase me.
H-He bought you?!
I was born into the royal family
of a certain frontier planet.
Our world is situated between
this kingdom and Eastern Space,
...and had prospered from
the trade between them.
However, our good fortune
was not to last for long.
War broke out between
the Empire and Earth,
...and my homeworld was engulfed
in the flames of war.
My father chose to establish
an alliance with Earth.
He did this because he had heard that the
people of Earth valued freedom highly.
And so, reinforcements
arrived from Earth.
My father told me that ten years ago
was a time of great turmoil.
He said that he himself had fought
in several wars of independence.
Those reinforcements from Earth
betrayed my father!
They started a rebellion, leveling
false charges against my father,
...claiming that he was working
in collusion with the Empire.
My father was killed
as a traitor,
...and my mother and I were stripped of our
status and sold into the hands of our enemies.
My mother died soon thereafter,
and I was left to fend for myself.
I was like a
walking corpse.
Yes, until the day
that I met the Count.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to dredge up
such painful memories.
I'm a fool, aren't I?
My girlfriend tells me the
same thing all the time.
She says I never stop to think
about other people's feelings.
Oh, I guess she's more like an old
childhood friend than a girlfriend.
She gave a piano recital at the
opera house the other day!
"It's a wonderful thing to be able
to express yourself that way."
That's what I thought to myself
when I heard her performance.
Mademoiselle Haidee, you yourself
are good at the harp, right?
Please do my family the honor
of paying us a visit sometime.
Allow me to introduce
my friends to you.
The night we arrived in Paris, the
Count said the following to me:
"Haidee, this is a land where freedom
and human rights are appreciated."
"You should do as you wish, acting
according to your own free will."
But this is the way
that I see it...
If I remain here voluntarily, I am here
because I freely choose to do so.
Our young Viscount is one
lighthearted kid.
You know? In spite of the fact that there's
a fire lit under his old man's ass.
Stop it.
"It's a wonderful thing to be able
to express yourself that way."
I'm gonna puke!
That's so damn pathetic!
You and I are
two of a kind.
I can see what you really think,
plain as day.
You're wrong.
I don't...
You hate him, don't you?!
You wanna rip him to pieces, don't you?!
Come on, let's have ourselves
some fun.
Take your hands
off her!
Count...
Leave us.
As you wish.
Monsieur Villefort?
I cast away all of the horrible feelings
within myself after I met you.
Or so I believed.
And I thought that if I could only
ease your cruel resolve...
But I... I was unable
to forget.
I could not forget how I felt
when I swore revenge that day.
Considering how I myself feel, it was wrong
of me to hope to change how you feel.
Count.
I caused you a great disservice the other day
by jumping to conclusions as I did.
As an apology for my impolite
behavior, please... Eat this!
Count!
The person I was in the past
is not the person that I am today.
Who we were in the past
is not who we are today.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo act 14:
Act 14:
Lost Souls
..."Lost Souls."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!