Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
"Death is nothing but a release,"
my friend once muttered to me.
"If death is a release, what is it
that you wish to give to them?"
My friend answered
me succinctly.
"I will give them eternal
suffering and remorse."
Count, I'm done with
running away.
I want to know
the truth.
Act 22:
Counterattack
General... Are you certain that
we are doing the right thing?
You must be afraid.
There has never been
such a thing as "the truth"!
The truth is something that you yourself create
based on your own convictions.
Even if it means setting
aside our conscience...
...and turning our weapons
on fellow soldiers, sir?
People don't look at
their conscience.
What they see is the truth that
is standing there before them!
It was the day before he... The day before Franz died.
That day, I walked all the way here
after you confessed your plans to me,
...my world turned
upside down.
I can still clearly remember how
my tears wouldn't stop flowing...
...as I looked out onto
the sun-drenched river.
Franz... Franz gave some
parting words to me.
He said to never
hate anyone.
He said that feelings of love
and feelings of hate...
...both start out as
caring about someone.
Count, please tell me! Tell me everything!
Congratulations!
A toast to Edmond's last night
of bachelorhood!
Is Edmond Dantes
in there?!
Madame.
We're here on General Morcerf's orders
to collect you.
The General will soon be entering Paris.
He will form an interim government,
...and we will see the birth of
President Morcerf before the day is out.
Take me with you. Take me to see him.
Why, that's... Fernand Mondego!
The National Assembly is hereby
under the control...
...of forces loyal to the Eastern Space Fleet!
Have you lost your mind?!
This is an act of high treason!
We don't recognize your authority!
We don't!
How dare you?!
Hold your tongues.
You traitor!
The National Assembly
is hereby dissolved!
I declare a state of
martial law in Paris!
Twenty-five years ago, I was a young man
named Edmond Dantes.
Indeed, before that day, I knew
nothing of mistrusting others.
I passed the days, praying for the
happiness of my father and fiancée.
Edmond Dantes!
You are under arrest...
...as a prime suspect in the
assassination of the Prince!
Edmond?
Edmond!
Mercedes! This is some sort
of misunderstanding!
I'll be fine!
Let go! Edmond!
Edmond!
You've been charged
with a crime.
What do you mean?
We received an
anonymous tip.
According to the written accusation,
you have in your possession...
...a letter that reveals the plot behind
the assassination of the Prince.
What in the world are you
talking about?
Before your captain died, I believe
he entrusted you with a letter.
Yes, the Captain's last request
was that...
...I deliver the letter to
the intended recipient.
Paris, Rue Coq-Heron, number 13.
Monsieur Noirtier...
The letter contained the names of the men
involved in the assassination plot.
Villefort's name was
also included within.
And I had unwittingly handed the letter over
to the very person I shouldn't have.
I see. You were simply carrying out
your duties faithfully.
Dantes. Let me take care
of this letter.
I expect that they'll be
releasing you soon.
Thank you so much, Monsieur Villefort!
How can I ever
thank you?
My fiancée must be anxiously
waiting for me to return.
By the way, have you spoken
of this letter to anyone else?
No, Monsieur. I obeyed the Captain's
last request and kept it secret.
No one else knows
of this letter.
I see...
Here in Paris, it is believed
to this day...
...that the Prince perished in an assassination
plot orchestrated by enemies of this world.
But the plot was devised
by people from Earth.
Those who had reaped enormous profits
from the war wanted it to continue.
But that's...
With the assassination, the
worst possible outcome,
prospects for peace became
a distant memory.
And just as those men wished,
the war spread,
...growing ever more intense in the name
of avenging the assassination.
A-And one unlucky man
was consigned to oblivion.
Those who had exploited me...
...became prominent figures in
the financial and legal worlds.
And the man who had climbed to
the very top of the military...
...eventually turned his eyes
to the presidency.
That is how
it happened.
Please! Call Monsieur Villefort!
What crime do they think I committed?!
I haven't done anything! I'm... I'm innocent!
What I found waiting for me when I was
imprisoned within the Chateau d'lf...
...was the very embodiment
of endless despair.
It was an automated fortress on the frontier,
built to defend against unknown enemies.
I became a component
of its control system.
In that place, that neverending Hell, I was
not even allowed the choice of death.
Please, kill me!
Please, kill me
right now!
I... I don't care about
salvation anymore.
Even if my body
should disappear,
...I'll find those who took
everything away from me,
...those who drove me
to ruin,
...and give them the cruelest, most
macabre punishment imaginable!
I won't even give them the respite of death!
What they'll get is eternal suffering!
My friend...
My friend!
My friend.
Hope... Grief...
Longing... Resignation...
Rage... Terror...
Despair... And then,
hope once again.
For thousands of years, I have waited inside
this body for the arrival of a man like you.
I... I'm...
I am with you.
And you are
with me.
To you, I give my knowledge
and power.
And to me, you give your body
and your spirit!
Albert... I am the
Wheel of Fortune.
Indeed, it is now only my unyielding,
merciless resolve which keeps me moving.
Count! Even after everything that's happened,
I don't want to let you leave!
I want you to give up on
your revenge, Count!
Only one man may give an order
to the Count of Monte Cristo,
...and that is the Count of Monte Cristo himself.
Count, are you saying that there
is no one left in your heart?
Are you saying that the Count of Monte Cristo
that I knew no longer exists?
Count!
Father...
Please, stop this... Father!
The Cabinet and National Assembly have ceded
full governing authority to the Space Forces.
Martial law has been declared!
Citizens are asked to surrender all weapons
and refrain from venturing outdoors!
I repeat, the Cabinet and
National Assembly have ceded...
...full governing authority
to the Space Forces.
Martial law
has been declared!
My money! My money!
Citizens are asked
to surrender all...
My money! My money!
Well, well, what have
we here?
So, that's what it's
come to?
Is this how the
world works?
Off with your head!
And yours!
I sentence you to death!
Baptistin!
Stand aside!
I won't let you stop me!
Take this with you.
What's this?
If anything happens, give us a shout.
Just don't turn it off.
Don't tell the Count
about this, okay?
Underground fortresses! Weapons depots!
There isn't a single one
that I don't know about.
I'm going to give them
a taste of my power!
Let's get to it!
Your next target is the Arc de Triomphe!
Spineless cowards.
Mercedes! I've been waiting for you!
Look! Paris is finally
kneeling before me!
This can't be what you wanted, Fernand.
The dreams that you told me about
were full of hope.
But there IS hope! Listen, this pain
is necessary for the good of the country!
Fernand...
You're the First Lady now, Mercedes!
There's nothing to
be afraid of now!
Edmond is alive, and he's been
right under our noses.
He's what?!
The man who was once your best friend...
The man who was once my fiancée...
...has returned to us as the
Count of Monte Cristo.
He survived... But why now?
That letter we received...
So that's what it was all about...
He's come back?
He's come back to get
his revenge on us?
Revenge? What are you
talking about?
You and Edmond were best friends.
What do you mean, revenge?
Why would Edmond want to
get revenge against you?
He and I... were
best friends?
I never once thought of that
bastard as my friend!
You must have
known that!
You're always like this!
Do you have any idea how much
that naiveté of yours hurts people?!
That's right. The man who sent that letter
that got him arrested was ME!
If I hadn't, he'd have been made the captain
of a ship on the interplanetary shipping lanes,
...and I would've spent my entire life as
a menial laborer at the Marseilles docks!
I... I had to do it.
Do you understand?! It was you!
Your naiveté cast Edmond into
the depths of misery!
I... I can't believe I said
such horrible things to you.
I'm sorry... Forgive me!
Mercedes, I love you...
Come with me.
Let's leave Paris together.
I've had it up to here with
always being the underdog!
I'm sick of living in
that bastard's shadow!
You're staying here!
You're going to stay here
by my side!
I'll never forget the time
we've spent together.
Thank you.
Goodbye, Fernand.
Mercedes...
Mercedes!
MERCEDES!
Mother!
Mother! Are you all right?! Mother!
Why? Why did this
have to happen?!
I loved her.
And I loved you more
than anything.
Father...
Not yet... I still have him to deal with.
Albert!
Albert?
This isn't over yet!
Eat this!
Albert!
You crazy kid...
Where's Mondego?
This ain't good...
Father...
As long as he's still alive,
I can't die, either!
Monte Cristo!
No, Edmond Dantes!
I'm going to take everything away from you,
just as you did to me!
I continue to plead,
as if praying.
To my father. To my mother.
And most of all, to your name.
Next time on Gankutsuou, act 23...
Act 23
Edmond Dantes
..."Edmond Dantes."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!