Move it!
We've waited and waited,
but she hasn't come back.
Fine, let her have it
her way.
All right, you bums!
We're heading home!
Back to Luna!
All I could do was
stand there and stare.
At the now masterless
number 30, Champs Elysées.
At the city blocks that had crumbled away
like sandcastles built on the beach.
At the silent blue sky
that spread out above me.
That's right. The summer storm
had come and gone.
Along with the end
of our summer.
Final Act:
At the Shore
Five Years Later
Well, well, if it isn't the
good Chief Secretary.
So, the Assistant Editor-in-Chief
came in person, huh?
What a hard worker
you are!
I was just worried about whether or not
you're carrying out your duties properly.
So, how's the peace treaty
coming along?
"Treaty Nearing Finalization At Long Last."
Something along
those lines.
Thanks to this treaty, the restoration of
diplomatic relations between our Kingdom...
...and the Empire is finally starting
to look like a real possibility.
So, this marathon of a war
is finally gonna end, huh?
Civilian interaction will
become commonplace,
...and citizens of both nations will
take each other by the hand.
We'll see the birth of a nation that's prosperous
in the truest sense of the word.
Not a nation where only
a select few prosper.
You know?
There's no telling when
the times will change.
Even so, I want to
believe in them.
I want to believe in the people
who chose THIS solution at THIS time.
And that includes you.
Me, I just go with the flow
with those times.
Well, let's leave the question of the truth
of that statement for another time, okay?
Today's the day of our long-awaited reunion
with those dear old friends of ours.
What's up?
Oh, damn!
Don't tell me you forgot
to make reservations!
Sorry! Tell my secretary that I'll be late
for the afternoon Cabinet meeting!
And tell her you're out making a reservation
so important that you can't trust her to do it?
See you tonight at the Nouveau Casino!
We'll start off with a toast!
Too bad, I came all the way down here
to show him this article...
Claire-Marie Eugenie's
Triumphant Return to Paris!
Max!
I'm home.
Julie! Julie!
Welcome home, Uncle Maximilien!
Spare me the "uncle" bit, okay?
Big brother! Thank goodness you're okay!
Did you behave yourselves and
do what Emmanuel told you to do?
Of course we did!
You bet!
That's good. I have presents waiting
for children who behaved themselves!
Yay!
That's our Uncle Max!
All right!
Big brother...
Maximilien!
Dear?
I'm home.
Valentine!
Maximilien!
I've returned, sir.
The peace that you dreamed of for so long
between Earth and the Empire...
...is finally about
to come to pass.
For that reason, I resigned from
the military as of today.
The flow of goods traveling between Earth
and the Empire will grow and grow.
So I intend to buy back my
father's ship, the Pharaon,
...and help Emmanuel and Julie
with the family business.
Maximilien...
Hey! Maximilien!
Valentine!
If we don't get moving soon,
we'll be late for the party!
You have an eye
for quality, sir!
That's an import item.
All the way from Earth.
It's a brand that's famous
in Paris.
Would it look good
on black hair?
These models from Earth certainly
are pretty, aren't they?
Ah, here we are!
I'd say that it goes perfectly with black hair,
wouldn't you?
Peppo!
Forget it.
I'll pass.
Wha...? But sir!
Forget it!
Forget it, forget it!
Trinkets like that aren't good enough
for our Princess!
It will be a whole
new you...
Thank you, Ali.
Would you care to
join me, Bertuccio?
No, ma'am. I'm on guard duty.
I would like to
show you something.
What's this?
It says that Monsieur Albert will be arriving
here on the day of the coronation ceremony.
And that he will do so as a secretarial aide
to Earth's ambassador.
Bertuccio, what would you
call this, if not fate?
Our old master must have
guided him here.
So that you would be able to fulfill your duties
to the best of your ability, Princess.
Yes...
Yes!
I also wish to keep Janina safe, so that
this peace endures for years to come.
That desire will
never change.
And we will be there
with you.
Thank you, Bertuccio.
Air France flight 1027 from Galileo
to Paris Spaceport...
...will be entering Earth
orbit momentarily.
Our estimated arrival time in Paris
will be slightly behind schedule,
...which will now be 2:13 local time.
A search is underway for the two ringleaders,
Benedetto and Gaspard Caderousse,
...who are wanted fugitives
in all systems, and...
In Paris, it's 2 o'clock, huh?
Right this way, please.
Are you done paying
your respects, then?
Yes.
Time certainly flies,
doesn't it?
How many times will I have
heard you play now? Five?
By the way, did you manage to meet your
friend this year? Your... young gentleman?
Well, then, take your time.
Thank you, Father. I appreciate it.
Hi there, Franz.
I just got back.
As I said when we spoke over the phone,
I simply wasn't able to find a buyer.
As such, we will be taking the house to pay for
the five years of accumulated back taxes.
Um..."The state hereby assumes all legal rights
to this land and all structures thereupon,"
"...and will take over management
of said land and structures."
You're sure that's
all right with you?
Yes, sir. I have
no objections.
In that case, please sign
this form.
Um... Would it be all right if I went
into the mansion one last time?
Of course. Feel free to
go in while you're here.
If you don't mind...
Franz...
I've been frantic
these past five years.
I read books like crazy,
always hunched over my desk.
And before I knew it, I'd turned 20.
I was... I was simply frantic.
I told myself that I had to live.
That I had to live in your place, in Father's
place, and in the Count's place.
Franz, I was terrified.
Of being trapped
by the past.
That I might become obsessed with the past
and end up hating someone.
I'm sorry, Franz...
I'm sorry it's been so long.
I'm sorry I haven't come back for so long.
Mademoiselle Mercedes Herrera.
It has been a long time.
How are you?
The ship has finally begun
her return voyage to Earth.
Unfortunately, the Captain
has fallen ill.
I don't think that it is anything serious, but
it looks as if our return will be delayed.
To be honest, I wish I could come home
right now and hold you in my arms.
That day we set sail,
...I could see the lights of Marseilles from the
porthole as they receded into the distance.
A day doesn't go by when I don't think back
on that warm light, the light of my loved ones.
Guided by that light, I never lose my way
or stray from my path.
That light that is shining so brightly
in our future is happiness.
So please wait for me
and don't worry.
Instead of holding you in my arms now,
I offer you these words:
Bide your time,
and hold out hope.
To my beloved Mercedes.
With all my heart,
your Edmond Dantes.
You've been here all this time...
Since long before I was born, haven't you?
I'll never forget the time I spent with you.
Or the time I spent
with my father.
with the Count.
I swear this
to you.
No matter where my life takes me,
I'll never forget that summer.
Never.