Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
On that stormy day that announced
the end of spring,
...my friend and I arrived in Paris,
where the boy awaited us.
I tremble in silence at these
emotions which leak out...
...as the hour of reunion
draws near.
This must be
your guest.
Count, if you don't mind, I'd like you to join us
for dinner after you've met my parents.
Count?
If it is not
too much trouble.
Please do. After all, we owe you
our son's life.
Welcome to our home,
my good Count of Monte Cristo.
Act 4:
A Mother's Secrets
To our new friend, the
Count of Monte Cristo.
Oh, is that so?
I'm embarrassed that you
know of the Janina campaign.
The people praise me
as a hero,
...but to a soldier, such
things mean little.
After all, nothing good ever
results from destruction.
No, these idyllic times in which we live
were built on the back of sacrifice.
Such is my opinion,
at any rate.
I expect that the far corners
of the galaxy are echoing...
...with the name of
General Morcerf by now.
You honor me
by saying so.
Oh, dear, the food wasn't
to your liking?
Not at all. Please, think
nothing of it.
I am in the habit
of eating very little.
I can't say that I don't
understand how you feel.
Having advanced in years, I find myself
weary of extravagant meals such as this.
In my case, I find lately
that I seldom sleep, either.
I'm amazed that you've managed
to stay healthy.
It is because
of these.
Are they some sort
of space rations?
In the course of wandering the
sea of stars for so long,
...my body and soul have changed
beyond recognition.
Even so, I hope that you
would at least eat something...
The thought of neither sleeping
nor eating is too sad to bear.
Too sad to bear?
Very well, then.
In that case, perhaps
I shall sample this.
Please do.
This taste brings
back memories...
Brings back memories?
I once experienced delightful cooking
such as this in the south of France.
This is the dish that you've made for as
long as I can remember, right, Mother?
Yes.
By any chance, you wouldn't happen
to be from Marseilles, would you?
No.
My wife has nothing to do
with such a barbaric province.
Isn't that right,
Mercedes?
Y-Yes...
Oh, really?
What's the matter?
One of my friends
is from there.
His name is Maximilien Morrel.
He's a really nice person.
Morrel...
Forgive me if I misspoke.
Please, do not take offense.
That's all right.
Our family traces its roots back
to a powerful Catalan family.
This soup has been a specialty of my
wife's ever since she was a young girl.
Oh, I see. So, you and the Countess
were childhood friends, then?
Yes, that's right.
Which explains why you seem so close.
I am jealous beyond words.
I had no idea that a man like you could
be jealous of anyone, Count.
Yes, of course.
If that person is a man
of your father's caliber.
Get the Count something to drink.
His glass is empty.
Please stay for as long
as time permits.
Sitting around the table like this, it almost
feels as if you are a member of the family.
What a maddening scent
this is...
Count?
It is from the
muscat grapes.
Are you fatigued?
No, please forgive me for
forcing you to eat earlier.
Not at all. I had always hoped to
experience that delicious flavor again.
It was a sublime
experience.
It was a simple
rustic dish.
But it makes me happy
to hear you say so.
Have you heard of this?
There is a saying that goes,
"Those who share bread and salt under
the same roof become eternal friends."
That is a tradition handed down
in Eastern Space, is it not?
Yes.
Which means that we are now friends.
For all eternity.
However, this is not Eastern Space.
It is Paris.
In Paris, everlasting friendship is impossible
without the act of sharing bread and salt.
Your soup truly
was delicious.
Warm, and yet evocative
of past memories.
It is something
which gives comfort.
Like a breeze blowing across
the Mediterranean Sea.
Count, are you very familiar
with Marseilles?
I could say that
I am aware of it.
But perhaps I never truly
knew it at all.
Infidelity. Adultery.
Dalliances in the dead of night.
You aristocrats are as energetic
as the rumors say.
Spare me your
crude comments!
The Count is a friend
of mine.
Honestly, you're such
a child.
If people could become friends simply
by sharing bread and salt,
...life would be simpler.
What are you
talking about?
You'll understand sooner
or later, little boy.
I am most grateful to you for allowing me
to experience a day such as today.
Not at all. I'm proud that I had the
opportunity to introduce you to my parents.
To introduce a
man I admire.
What say you?
I would like to invite you to my residence
on the Champs-Elysees in the near future.
I'd love to come!
The Count of Monte Cristo was a
mysterious man, don't you think?
Yes. There was a sternness somewhere
in him that keeps people at arm's length.
That just means that compared to the Count,
the people of Paris are dull.
My...
You might not know this, Mother, but
there's more to the world than Paris.
Out beyond the walls, there's a world
that's endlessly captivating.
I think you've changed
since your journey to Luna.
My journey is
just beginning.
Don't go to worlds too far
removed from our own.
You should exercise moderation
in your association with the Count.
Oh, please, Mother...
You sound just like Franz.
Well, even though he seems
more than a little shady,
...having the Morcerf family establish ties with
a man like him might not be a bad thing.
Not when this family is about to
throw its hat into the political arena.
Good grief, why do aristocrats
eat like this all the time?
Dinner parties, high tea,
balls...
It's probably because they
don't have anything else to do.
In other words, if you took away
the gluttony, lust, and avarice,
...there wouldn't be
anything left.
You need to watch
your mouth.
Didn't you think that their guest today
was rather elegant and handsome?
I'm not so sure.
He wasn't very refined.
Maybe, but he had a pretty good vibe going
with the mistress under the grapevine trellis.
What, really? I'd always thought that the master
was the only man in the world for the mistress.
I think that any society lady would fall for
that Count if he worked his mojo on her.
Give it a rest, already!
That was definitely the face
of a woman in love.
If you don't stop that,
I'm going to report you.
Oo, I'm so scared...
That's preposterous. Mother is the last person
in the world who would be capable of...
Mother?
Who's in that picture
she's looking at?
Do you find me
a horrible man?
No. I will stay at your side
for as long as I live.
Even if that means walking down
the path to ruin.
It is not we
who will be ruined.
I have come home,
Father.
What, you're still here?
Hey, don't touch those!
I hate to break it to you, but I've gotten
into your father's good graces,
...so I'll be staying here
for a while.
His "good graces"?
It means that your father
is a man like any other.
Give those bad jokes
a rest.
Well, setting aside your
father for the moment,
...the one that I'd be worried about
is your mother, you know?
What's that supposed
to mean?
I mean, she was staring so wistfully
at that picture of a young man...
You saw that?
It was definitely
a picture of a man.
A man who wasn't
your father.
Oh, I can understand.
If my mother was staring at a
picture of some strange man,
...l'd be depressed, too.
That's about enough!
Get out!
Yes, sir!
Eugenie? I didn't know
you were here.
Ever the late riser,
I see.
Why are you dressed
like that?
What's wrong
with it?
Skirts just don't work
on you.
I didn't come here
to see you, Albert!
Then don't have me dragged
out of bed!
I'm the one who had you
woken up, Albert.
Is something
the matter?
No, ma'am.
Eugenie is your fiancee,
isn't she?
I think it's only natural that you
should greet her when she's over.
Sure, I suppose.
Um, are you going somewhere?
Oh, we're just going out to do
a little shopping together.
Let's go, Madame!
Of course.
That reminds me. What's this I hear about the
Count of Monte Cristo inviting you over?
How did you
know that?
I heard about it
from Franz.
He said that he and Maximilien
were also invited.
They were invited, too?
What's he...
Peppo!
What are you doing?
Oh, hi, Albert!
Don't you "Oh, hi!" me!
Don't play around with Mother's jewelry!
But they're so pretty!
If my father sees you like that,
there'll be hell to pay!
Fine, fine.
I'll put them back, then.
You're dying to know
what's in there, aren't you?
It's like your mother's secret
treasure is hidden inside.
Impossible.
Oh, there's no such thing as a human being
who doesn't have secrets.
Just like you and I share
a certain secret night.
That only happened because
I was tricked by you!
If you ever want that lock opened,
come tell me anytime.
I specialize in getting
into people's drawers.
Stop being crude,
and get back to work!
Oh. Fine.
It can't be...
Why would Mother have
a picture of the Count?
This is ridiculous.
What am I so worried about?
His Excellency General Morcerf!
Ten-hut!
All high and mighty...
How do I look?
Not too strange, I hope?
It looks wonderful
on you.
What?
Thank goodness.
You're more upbeat than I expected.
Gee, thanks.
For a visit to the Count's place, that outfit isn't
quite flamboyant enough, don't you think?
Not flamboyant enough?
Albert? What in the world
are you wearing?
What's wrong
with it?
Where do I
even begin?
I'll never understand the ways
of you aristocrats.
Why are you dressed
like a pirate?!
Uh, what are you even
doing here, Beauchamp?
You don't expect me to miss my chance to
get photos of the Count's mansion, do you?
Oh, brother. And here I had hoped to go
there by myself, if at all possible.
That day when I first met you, you made me
realize that there is always hope,
...regardless of the circumstances
you might find yourself in.
I will never forget
that lesson.
Hope...
When I was flung out of the Chateau d'lf
into the black void of space,
...hope was the one thing
that I had in my possession.
You're sure
this is it?
Yep. number thirty, Champs-Elysees.
No doubt about it.
It's a lot more austere than I expected
it to be, considering the Count.
I was expecting the sort of place that would
drive a commoner into a rage if he saw it.
Welcome, messieurs.
We have been expecting you.
Early Rococo, huh?
And not Revival, either.
Isn't this amazing?
Well, it's a bit too far removed
from my world...
Please pardon the delay.
Allow me to show you to the Count.
What the...?
We're going down!
Baptistin, where are
we going?
We've stopped!
Welcome, messieurs.
The Count awaits.
That's...
Even the floor and columns are gold...
The man has expensive tastes.
Where could he have gotten
this much gold?
That's why I think there's
something fishy about him.
At this rate, I bet his bed and
pillows are gonna be solid gold, too.
I'd never be able to fall asleep
with all this glare.
Hey! Look at that!
That's...
The sea?
No, wait.
Look at that sky!
It's artificial?
I can't believe it...
This alone would make
one hell of a story.
This is so beautiful...
Wait, I know
this view!
That look suits you quite well,
Sir Pirate.
Count!
Wha...?
If you don't mind, I would like
you to have this, Sir Pirate.
I was given this blade by a
certain ship's navigator.
Perhaps it will serve to protect you,
as well as to carve a path for you.
When we meet someone,
...the selfless, considerate part of us
clashes with the selfish love of our emotions.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo, act 5,
Act 5:
Do You Love Your Fiancee?
..."Do You Love Your Fiancee?"
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!