Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
The girl sleeping in the
house of the poisoner...
...was saved thanks to the pure
souls of the young men.
However, the next misfortune then silently
creeps up and suddenly appears before us.
Indeed, just like that single letter
that was delivered to an innocent soul.
Act 12:
Encore
Excuse me?
Father, what did you
say just now?
Your engagement to Albert...
I've called it off.
All right?
What's the meaning of this?
What brought this on?
I've been hearing some unsavory rumors
about the Morcerf family.
But that doesn't mean you have to...
I can't believe this!
I don't understand you.
As I recall, you were never very enthusiastic
over the engagement from the very beginning.
You don't understand anything,
do you, Father?
Don't treat my life like it was
one of your stocks or bonds!
Here's a quick lesson
for you.
There are only two kinds of people
in this world, winners and losers.
Eugenie, I'm only thinking
of what's best for you.
Liar. You're thinking of
what's best for you!
Damn it, Mondego,
you really blew it.
Sorry, but I plan to make it
through this in one piece.
I must say, it's hard to believe you're
the Mondego I used to know.
You've done well
for yourself.
How do you know
about that?
A certain gentleman
filled me in.
Who?! Who was it?!
Oh, I can't tell you that...
But that's not important.
How much do
you want?
Gimme everything
you've got!
If you wanna keep me from talking,
stuff my mouth with gold!
It's an honor to see you
again, Mademoiselle.
Marquis Cavalcanti? Do you
have some business here?
Yes, I have a meeting
with your father.
More financial dealings?
I was hoping that I might be
of some assistance to you.
I want to take everything that causes
you sorrow and make them go away.
There's no reason for
you to do that for me.
Does a man need a reason
to be in love?
No! Let go of me!
I'll scream!
You're acquainted with the
Count of Monte Cristo, I take it?
The gossip dealing with the Morcerf family
was apparently leaked by him.
What are you
talking about?
I must say, though, I find it unlikely that
the Count's information would be incorrect.
Why are you telling
me this?
The thought of seeing sadness on the face
of the woman I love is unbearable.
Cut it out. There's no reason
for you to be in love with me.
Why would the Count of Monte
Cristo do such a thing?
I wonder what she thinks about
the engagement being called off?
Why don't you
just ask the girl?
No, this problem might be bigger
than just the two of us.
Albert...
You're serious about her,
aren't you?
I guess it's true that you don't realize how
important something is until you lose it.
Goodness, this is amazing...
This is your daughter's big night, after all.
Money is no object.
My daughter is
a lucky girl.
She never would have been able to sell out
the opera house on her own merits.
This wouldn't have happened
without your gracious support.
So, are you willing to go along with this?
Breaking it off with Albert?
You can hardly call it breaking it off.
Nothing had even started.
Maybe, but you were engaged.
This is something that both
our families decided.
Why do you seem
so hurt, then?
Who is he? Who's this Count
of Monte Cristo person?
Did the Count have something
to do with this?
He's manipulating things
behind the scenes.
It sounds like he was the source
of all those bad rumors...
...about Uncle Fernand that
my father has been hearing.
Bad rumors?
Personally, I don't care about
all that political gossip,
...but Albert hasn't been the same
ever since he met that man.
I really miss the old days,
you know?
The three of us would run around the meadow,
not even noticing when the sun went down.
When did it start?
When did we start being so awkward
around each other,
...and not even being able
to hold hands anymore?
When you were on your trip to Luna,
what happened to you?
You two haven't been the same
since that trip.
You're right, we haven't.
What does Albert think
about all this?
I haven't heard
from him.
Has he said anything
to you?
You two are
best friends, right?
Best friends, huh?
Franz, is something wrong?
I'm sorry. I don't really understand
him these days, either.
Did something happen
between you and Albert?
We got into
a fight.
Albert shouldn't associate
with the Count anymore...
Thanks for
lending an ear.
I'm sorry I couldn't be more helpful. Still...
What?
I'm relieved.
Well, whatever you might say about it,
it looks
like you really do care about Albert.
Oh, geez...
Is it that obvious?
No one can hide it when they're
pining away for someone.
Maybe the reason your piano performance
that night at Auteuil was so great...
...was because you were really
playing for Albert.
No way...
The feelings you have for someone
manifest themselves in your art.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, he wouldn't
be here...
After all,
we're still fighting...
Yeah, he wouldn't
be here...
What's keeping her?
Isn't Eugenie ready yet?!
She is still
getting ready.
Are you sure you're feeling well,
Mademoiselle?
I'm fine. This is the opera house performance
that I've always dreamed of.
It's the strangest thing.
Unlike the way it is
outside the city walls,
...the muscat grapes here always bear fruit
regardless of the season.
What is it?
Albert, you should always
listen to your feelings.
You can't lie to yourself
about how you really feel.
Have you always been true
to yourself, Mother?
This is Paris.
Perhaps it truly is a paradise
where you can find...
...whatever your heart desires
if you work hard enough.
But if you lose your courage, you'll simply
be swept along on the currents.
You're not going to
show up, Albert?
Are you looking
for someone?
Lucien!
Oh, I get it. Mother invited you,
didn't she?
Thanks to her
kind influence.
I'm dedicating my performance
tonight to lovers.
I hope you two
enjoy it.
No. For tonight, you should play for yourself
and for the person that you love.
Pianists are allowed
to do that.
That's easy for you
to say...
I suppose it is.
Albert, my boy, I'm sorry, but the hall
is already filled with invited guests.
I have an invitation.
Eugenie gave it to me.
The past is the past.
Let's pretend it never happened.
I was invited by Eugenie!
You have no right to turn me away!
Did you get that hot temper of yours
from your father?
This has nothing to do with my father!
I'm my own man!
You're going to
let me pass!
And just what are you
going to do about it?
You have no power.
You have no money.
You're nothing but
a spoiled brat!
Shut up!
Maybe so, but I still...
Damn it! Let me go!
What's this commotion? This is supposed
to be an auspicious occasion.
Oh, you were invited, too?
Yes, by Madame.
My wife seems to be feeling a little out of sorts.
Would you mind keeping her company for me?
I'm sorry, but I'm not in the mood today.
Excuse me.
Cut it out, Lucien!
I... have to get in there!
Listen!
Use your head, then!
You'll never get in through the front door.
Crap...
I don't owe you any
favors or anything,
...but I've been doing some things
that are hurting Eugenie.
Are you really sleeping
with Eugenie's mother?
It's all part
of my job.
You'll never understand your whole life,
and you don't have any need to.
Anyway, be there for her and
listen to her performance.
You love Eugenie,
don't you?
Let's go.
Albert?
Is that you?
You're a little late,
don't you think?!
I was right here the whole time.
I had a little trouble getting in.
You don't mean my father,
do you?
It's all right, I heard
you play just fine.
It was really great.
You were radiant out there.
My heart was pounding!
Idiot. If I'd known you were here,
I would've been able to play even better.
I would've been playing
for you.
Eugenie...
I'm sorry. I know I'm not
your fiancée anymore.
That doesn't matter.
I don't care.
Oh! Here.
What?
You like these,
don't you?
Well, sure, but you're supposed
to bring a bouquet of flowers.
Oh, right. I guess flowers
would've been better...
You're such a fool. You haven't
changed one bit since we were kids.
Out in the meadow,
I wanted you to pick flowers for me,
...but you would always bring
me berries instead.
They were delicious, though.
Mademoiselle Eugenie!
It won't do to keep
your audience waiting.
You!
Wait, Albert!
Listen to one more song.
I'll be playing it just for you.
It looks like you've
been shut out.
I wouldn't be so sure
about that.
Ladies and gentlemen! Let's have a warm
round of applause for Mademoiselle Eugenie!
What do you think you're doing?!
This is my performance!
Yes, one that I arranged.
That jerk!
You don't know
when to quit!
My daughter has set out on the road to
a bright future! Don't ruin it for her!
You don't have any
right to be here!
All the seats for tonight's performance
were bought out by Marquis Cavalcanti!
You've lost,
so go away!
Count...
Why, whatever is the matter?
You're not looking
well at all.
Count!
Albert?
I'm... so frustrated...
At how weak
and pathetic I am...
Count of Monte Cristo!
You are under suspicion
of criminal activity.
I will have to ask you to come with me
to the station as the prime suspect...
...in the poisoning death
of Valois!
Monsieur Villefort...
Villefort's investigation
is relentless.
Why?
When I go to visit the Count, I sit and
speak with Haidee for the first time.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo act 13:
Act 13:
Haidee
..."Haidee."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!