Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
Everything lies in ruin.
What was once believed to be solid ground
has opened up and swallowed everything.
The young soul wanders aimlessly,
betrayed by everything he had believed in.
But what he clutches at
in the end is...
Act 17:
The Confession
Someone taught me the
meaning of the word hope.
Count, that someone
was you!
Wait for me, Albert!
Mademoiselle.
A letter has arrived
for you.
Thank you.
Why aren't you
saying anything?
answering me?
My words now fall
on deaf ears.
Is... Is that what you're
trying to say?!
There is no such thing as coincidence.
I believe that is what I told you.
As I recall, it is the very
first thing I told you.
Everything that happens
does so out of necessity.
What are you trying
to say?
Tell me, if Haidee were not a living witness
to your father's true identity,
...what value would there
be in keeping her with me?
Tell me, if you were not
Mondego's son,
...why would it have been necessary
for me to meet you on Luna?
It can't be...
From the very beginning,
you were using me?
Yes. I met you under the
pretense of coincidence,
...and took advantage of this so-called
"friendship" that you have such faith in.
That is what
I am saying.
I even used props
such as that watch.
It can't be...
From the very beginning,
you were using me?
You're lying!
You're lying! You're lying!
I can't believe that everything has been
a setup since the very beginning!
I can't!
I mean, haven't you always
helped me, Count?
Haven't you always been
looking out for me?
I don't believe that all the time
we spent together was a lie!
Not one bit!
You poor, foolish boy.
You still wish to remain immersed
in those naive delusions of yours?
Is that what you
are trying to say?
Even if I deliberately brought you with me
on that pleasure cruise that day,
...knowing full well that Haidee was about to
disclose the truth at the National Assembly?
I must thank you.
You have been most useful to me
in the time we have known one another.
You have my gratitude.
From the bottom of my heart.
I challenge you!
My, how old-fashioned.
The son of a soldier must act
in accordance with tradition?
Is that it?
The time will be tomorrow morning
at five.
In the forest of Boulogne.
Weapons?
Armor and bare steel!
Very well.
Bertuccio.
You are my witness.
Did you see the whole challenge
from beginning to end?
Y-Yes, Excellency!
Albert!
I accept your challenge.
In that case, we will meet
at five tomorrow!
It will serve to freeze the memory
of this day, this hour, in time.
A memory which belongs
to us alone.
I must go see him.
Count, is there nothing I can do to stop
this duel between you and Albert?
You told me
that I am free.
That is what allowed me to live to
this day without taking my own life.
But if you... If you were
to perish,
...I would not be able
to go on living, either.
Gankutsuou...
Wait... Not yet!
It is not yet time!
Franz?
Albert!
Franz...
You've always
looked out for me,
...but I'd always plunge ahead with what
I was doing, ignoring your advice.
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry, Franz.
I'm back.
Welcome home.
Geez, wipe the snot
from your nose.
Get off my back!
You total idiot! You played
straight into his hands!
You've got to call off this duel
right now!
Cut it out!
You'll act as
my second, right?
I don't blame you
for being angry.
But this is one thing that I have
to see through, no matter what!
Listen to me,
and listen good.
The Count has been planning
to kill you all along.
Are you saying that you don't care if you end
up getting killed in the name of his revenge?!
Franz.
That bastard deceived me
and used dirty tricks to lure me in.
He used the most despicable means
imaginable to toy with me...
...and turn my life
upside-down.
And I can't... I can't let him
get away with it!
Even if the Count used to be
your mother's fiancé?
Your father was so in love
with your mother...
...that 25 years ago, he framed the Count
for a crime he didn't commit...
...and took his fiancée
away from him by force.
Edmond Dantes?
Mondego's wife is here
to see you.
Edmond!
No, Count...
You are really Edmond Dantes,
aren't you?
How I've missed you...
These past 25 years, I haven't
forgotten you for an instant.
I know that you can never
forgive what I've done.
But... But even if only once, I wish I could
speak with you as Edmond!
Edmond... is dead.
This body retains only his
shape and appearance.
There is no longer anything
of Edmond himself left within it.
That's not true.
No, that isn't possible!
If that were so, why have I had the feeling ever
since the day we met that you are Edmond?
You refuse to be disturbed
by the coldness of my hand...
You leave me
no choice, then.
I will show you proof that Edmond,
the man you once loved, is now dead.
I will await you at five tomorrow morning
in the forest of Boulogne.
It's already too late
for that, Franz.
It's too late
to do anything!
Whatever happened between the Count
and our fathers in the past,
...I don't care about
any of that anymore!
I can't take back what happened
between the Count and me.
If he hates me that much, he should
just kill me and be done with it!
Damn it!
He played games with
my feelings!
Albert! Don't do it!
Don't go!
Come back!
Albert!
Please, come back...
You're still going to go see him,
even knowing who he is?
Hi!
Franz! You're back!
Welcome home!
Is Albert here?
Uh... No, he was with me
until a while ago.
He said that he had something
to take care of.
Oh, he did?
Still, I'm glad to see you. I haven't been
able to reach you since that day.
Sorry for worrying you.
Honestly! I was worried
sick about you.
You timed your
arrival perfectly, Franz.
Franz, don't you remember?
Tomorrow is Albert's birthday!
Yeah, exactly! That's why!
That's why I came to see you!
Geez, get your
act together...
Actually, about that...
I wrote a song for Albert!
It's not finished yet,
though.
Well?
Yeah, it's nice.
It's romantic.
Not like you at all.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Don't be rude!
That settles it! Tomorrow, you, Albert and I
will have a party at our usual cafe!
But I can't...
Just say that a friend of yours is having
a recital or something, and sneak out.
It'll all work out.
Okay, I get it.
So anyway, do you think you
could do me a little favor?
As in?
I wrote a message in
a birthday card for him,
...but I think we're too old for that kind of thing,
so I feel awkward giving it to him in person.
Idiot, who cares how old you are?
You're just giving him a card.
Anyway, give it to Albert
after I leave tomorrow.
Please?
I'm begging you.
It must be a surprise.
Sure, okay.
Okay, I think I'll keep working
on that song for a while.
Don't work too hard.
See you tomorrow at 3 PM, then.
At our usual cafe.
Thanks for coming by
to visit me today.
Excellency.
What is it?
Good luck.
Let's drink to victory
with a red!
I'll have the white!
But that guy up there
is pitch-black!
To victory!
Right!
I'm gonna mop the floor with
that coward, just you watch!
The Count is no one
to fear!
The clash of steel shatters
the dawn silence.
Sword of righteous anger in hand,
I shall cut through all deception and lies!
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo act 18:
Act 18:
The Duel
..."The Duel."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!