Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
Anguish. Anxiety.
Because his soul is so
pure and innocent,
...it is all the more susceptible to
becoming troubled and tarnished.
The tarnish becomes an indelible stain,
and the stain gradually spreads.
When one is no longer
able to trust others,
...is that when one truly
becomes an adult?
Act 15:
The End of Happiness, The Beginning of Truth
It's amazing how tiny and insignificant
the world we live on is.
Yes. In the vast cosmos,
it is but a grain of sand.
And what's more, separated from Earth by
a distance of 2:5 light years as we now are,
...the light you are now seeing
is that of 25 years ago.
25 years?
Indeed. 25 years.
I'm glad that you brought me
with you.
Seen from space, all the things that I was
agonizing over seem so insignificant.
Perhaps, but hatred and malice are
amplified in the darkness of space.
Everyone's gone away...
Franz has left, and so has Albert.
I'm sorry for asking you to meet me
on such short notice, Franz.
That's all right,
I'm glad I had the chance to see you.
I'm planning on setting out
on a trip for a while.
Is Albert going
with you?
Apparently, he went off somewhere
on a trip of his own.
Even though his father's in the
middle of an election campaign.
Can you believe
that guy?
"Somewhere"?
Where do you mean?
I'm sorry,
I don't know, either.
Oh.
The one thing I can
say for sure...
...is that he's gotten himself mixed
up in something dangerous.
He still hasn't figured
that out, though.
Franz, I...
I know.
You're a victim in all this, too.
Listen, whatever happens,
don't forget who you are.
Look for the truth
on your own.
Before I made
your acquaintance,
...I traveled to the far reaches of the universe,
operating this ship by myself.
You flew a huge ship like this
by yourself?!
Yes. At the time, I was quite proud of the fact
that I was able to operate it single-handedly.
Come, take a look
at that.
What is that?
The Milky Way. I am told that in the ancient
Orient, it was called the River of Heaven.
The River of Heaven?
This is what I wished
to show to you.
It's so beautiful...
According to their legends, two lovers
lived on the opposite banks...
...separated from one another
by the River of Heaven.
They say that once a year, they cross
the river and are reunited.
That's a romantic story,
don't you think?
Long ago, I once had a friend,
a sailor who was born in Marseilles.
I heard that story
many times from him.
I bet that your friend
was in love.
This sailor of whom I speak had a beautiful
fiancée and a best friend he felt at ease around.
These three were childhood friends,
and were always looking out for each other.
Indeed, they were much like you,
Monsieur Franz, and Mademoiselle Eugenie.
However, the best friend was secretly
in love with the sailor's fiancée.
And then, the friend, who would stop
at nothing to possess the fiancée,
...framed the sailor for a crime
which he did not commit.
Unbeknownst to anyone, the poor sailor
spent more than a dozen years...
...chained up in a prison located
in the depths of space.
I can't believe it...
However, a miraculous
event occurred,
...and the sailor was set free, whereupon
he returned to Marseilles.
I'm relieved
to hear that.
However, the beautiful fiancée, rather
than waiting for the sailor's return,
...had become engaged
to his friend instead.
That's terrible...
I wonder why she didn't wait
for the sailor to come home?
Also, why did the sailor's friend steal away
his fiancée in spite of their friendship?
The sailor, now betrayed by both his best friend
and his fiancée, never returned to Earth again.
Why do you cry?
I don't know...
Until just recently, I thought that I would
never believe in anyone, just as you do.
That's what I told myself...
But for some reason,
when I see your face,
...that thought of living that way seems
like the saddest thing in the world to me.
Count, let's have faith that our friendship
will be the exception to the rule!
At the very least, you're the one person
that I can trust!
Is the watch that I gave you
still ticking away?
Albert, I shall be departing Paris
sometime in the near future.
What do you mean,
Count?
It's so sudden!
Wait, it's not because of
your illness, is it?!
No. There was a certain matter
that I had to see to in Paris,
...which is why I have kept my residence
on the Champs Elysees.
However, the task I came to accomplish
will soon be completed.
Morcerf! Morcerf!
Don't say such things!
Please, stay in Paris for good!
Or if that's not possible, please take me
with you when you go!
I don't want to
be apart from you!
Do you think that
highly of me?
I do!
The ardor of youth
eventually cools.
That's not true!
You... To me, you're...
One day...
One day, I will ask you
the same question.
I wonder if you will still feel
the same way about me then?
Excellency, there's a message
from Paris.
If you will pardon me
for a moment...
Monsieur Noirtier...
Please, you have to tell me.
Tell me what
Gankutsuou is.
What's this?
Hey, wait a minute!
"In the event of an emergency, it is possible
for a third party who knows the password..."
"...to use this pen to make contact
with its owner."
Does this mean that if I can figure out the
password, I can access your mind directly?
She's so beautiful!
Hey, isn't she...
Right. She's Monte Cristo's...
I realize I am late, but I have come to offer
my support to you, General Morcerf.
Well, well!
By all means, please
step up to the podium!
Valentine... I'm certain that your grandfather
told you a very important password.
Do you know
what it is?
Valentine, I am now surrounded
on all sides by enemies.
If anything should happen to my body,
remember this flower.
Blue rose...
My name is Haidee.
Various circumstances
brought me to Paris,
...and I have eagerly awaited the day that
I would be able to meet General Morcerf.
Goodness, you honor me.
This may sound rude, but have we met
somewhere before, by any chance?
Yes, ten years ago.
I will never forget the day.
When I was four years old,
in the land of Janina.
Janina?
You did us the honor of protecting us
as a gallant Space Forces officer.
Oh, is that it?
You were a patriot dedicated
to defending our country.
Or so I believed,
until that day.
Done!
I never expected that I would be using
this channel for this purpose...
Still, I have no further need for it
now that I have left politics behind.
Thank you, Franz.
You and your friends have kept
my granddaughter safe for me.
If there is anything in my memories that might
prove useful to you, by all means, take them.
Please take good care
of Valentine.
W-Who in the world
are you?
I am a sad woman who had the misfortune
to lose her father at Janina,
...and to be handed over to slave
traders along with her mother.
My father fell victim to the intrigues of a certain
young officer, and lost his life as a result.
Oh, my!
What's she talking about?
I-I'm curious as to what this story
has to do with these proceedings?
They have no bearing on this? Is that what
you are trying to say, General Morcerf?
Or Fernand Mondego,
should I say?
What?
What does she mean?
Who IS that woman?
"Mondego"?
Gankutsuou is...
The Chateau d'lf.
Edmond Dantes.
My name is
Haidee Tebelin,
...daughter of Ali Tebelin, former Pasha
of Janina, and his wife, Vasiliki!
I am the daughter of a father who
was brought low by your conspiracy...
...and a mother who lost
her life to despair!
Surely you can offer no justification
for what you did.
W-What's this nonsense?!
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is THIS that is a conspiracy!
A rebellion by malcontents who
are trying to disrupt my campaign!
He's right! Grab that woman
and get her out of here!
It's a conspiracy!
Don't fall for her lies, everyone!
Now, I think you
should leave.
Shut your mouth,
Fernand Mondego!
What's this?
Don't look at me like that!
Are you able to prove
what you say?
Why, that's...
Proof that will never fade for as long as I live.
Proof that was branded onto me...
...when I was turned over to
the slave traders by that man.
This brand is a record of everything
that I have endured.
Haidee... This belonged to your father.
Take it.
If you ever suspect that you are about to
be violated, use this to take your own life.
Fernand Mondego. Change your name
all you like,
...but the blood of my father that splattered
onto your forehead that day...
...will never disappear as
long as you shall live!
Ali... I... I know
I'm right.
I did the right thing.
He is my sworn enemy, the man
who stole everything from me.
So why do I feel
like this?
Ali...
The Count... I must warn him!
I mustn't let the Count suffer as I do now!
Count... Has something happened?
Why do you seem
so anxious?
I'm not sure.
I just sense the presence of
a deep, terrible darkness.
Count, what should I...
Albert, you should return to Earth.
Without delay.
You should be at your
father's side.
My father?
It's times like these when a man makes a lot
of enemies. You should watch your back, too.
Has something happened
to my father?!
Return home at once. I will lend you
my ship, the Spada.
The time has come at last
for you to learn everything.
This may be the last time
we meet.
No!
Fare thee well,
Albert my friend.
Count...
Why? I thought we were going
to trust only each other...
Count!
We're going back!
Back to that city where
vice flourishes!
Stand by for
atmospheric reentry.
Everything was
a lie.
The tiny rip becomes
an enormous tear,
...and everything I had believed in
falls in and is swallowed up by it.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo act 16:
Act 16:
Scandal
..."Scandal."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!