Albert!
This isn't over yet!
Eat this!
Albert!
Father...
I bid you welcome
to my palace!
You!
Edmond?
W-Where'd you go?!
Where are you?!
Show yourself!
Fernand Mondego!
Allow me to express my sincerest gratitude for
attacking in person, my good former General.
Vile apparition!
Those words will be the
last you ever speak!
I will give you the despair of one who
has had everything stolen from him.
Prepare to taste the
depths of my vengeance!
Act 23:
Edmond Dantes
Don't push yourself
too hard.
Where's Mother?!
We managed to pull her back from the brink.
We're keeping her doped up for now.
Baptistin! Can this ship
still fly?!
Yeah, barely.
Hurry, take us to the
Champs Elysées!
My father wants to
kill the Count!
Lifting off immediately.
Setting course for the Count's manor!
Baptistin, you've got things
covered down there, right?
You bet! Do your thing,
big guy!
Count!
Hurry! You must take
your medicine!
That will not... be necessary, Haidee.
My pact with Gankutsuou
is inviolate.
My body is no longer
my own.
No, Count! You are yourself!
You are the only person
in this world that I adore.
Your words... no longer
reach me.
My only desire is to carry out
my final revenge.
I will not allow you
to die.
Not like my father did... Never!
Damn you!
Set your mind
at ease.
I will not kill you.
I will not give you respite
so easily!
You nightmare... begone!
H-How?
How can this be?!
I will not die.
I am not even
permitted death.
S-Stay away!
Stay away from me!
Fernand... Look upon me.
Look upon the man who has sacrificed himself,
body and soul, for the sake of his revenge!
You mustn't!
You mustn't go any further!
I cannot allow you
to take this any further.
Stand aside.
I will not.
Stand aside!
I will not!
Because I... I love you.
I do not want to lose the one I love
like I did that day.
Even if I must
forfeit my life here!
You heard her, Edmond.
Her Highness says that she will
sacrifice her life for you.
Hey!
Father!
Father! Stop!
Don't do it!
Drop that sword right now, you hear?
If you don't, she's dead!
Count, please... Your medicine!
You and your "revenge"!
You and your "judgment"!
This is why you've always
been a hopeless weakling!
Highness, you got a little
too carried away.
Shall I have you pay the price for that
right here and now?
Fernand. I suggest you look
to your son.
You bastard!
Your son's life is mine
for the taking.
Bertuccio. Pull the trigger.
Have you gone crazy?!
Go ahead, I dare you
to touch that trigger!
She'll follow right
on his heels!
Stop it! Don't do it, Father!
Edmond! Give it up!
Don't try to pretend to be tough!
You're too easygoing for that!
Let go of my son!
Bertuccio, don't do this! Don't you care
what happens to her?!
The man... The man I serve is...
Father... Don't hurt
anyone but me.
Please, don't hurt her
any more...
Edmond! Please, let my son go!
He's the only thing I have left
that's precious to me.
Please, don't take him
from me!
Hate me!
Hate ME!
I'll give you my life if that's what you want!
But please, don't take his.
I'm begging you, Edmond!
Anything but my son's life!
Kill me! Kill me!
Fernand...
I'm so sorry.
Death is the ultimate end
of all things.
But in the end, it is nothing
but a release from suffering.
What I want from you
is despair.
I want your
everlasting despair.
It is time.
No! Don't!
Baptistin!
What am I doing
on the ground?
Baptistin! Why did you do that?
No! I don't want you
to die!
Quit your bawling... I'm just a little sleepy, that's all...
Count, what do you want so badly that you're
willing to hurt innocent people to get it?!
And YOU! What the hell is so important that
you'd even kill Mother and Haidee to get it?!
What's more important to you two
than people's lives?!
No matter how much you try to justify it,
murder is still murder!
Count, Father, all you two are doing
is running away!
All you're doing is deluding yourselves
by refusing to back down to each other!
You claim to understand
what my friend feels inside?
You think that you understand
my poor friend's feelings?
Well, I...
The pact is concluded.
No!
My name is Gankutsuou.
Bertuccio! Fetch me my cloak!
Count! Is this the "destiny"
you spoke of?!
Weren't you the one who told me
that destiny was something...
...that you create for yourself
with your own two hands?!
Where is your will now?
Where have you gone?
Count!
His time has run out.
You cannot save him.
Not you, a boy who does not
understand my friend's heart.
I might not understand the Count's
true feelings, but I...
Count?!
I'm... going to kill you!
I'm going to...
Count!
Damn it!
No!
Count, no!
Count!
I cannot die...
Not until he dies
at my hand...
Please, don't talk!
Where is he?
Where is Albert?!
I'm... I'm right here!
Bring me my sword, Bertuccio...
Bring me my sword of vengeance...
Put it in my hand...
I must kill him...
Count, I give you
my word.
Even if the future is shrouded in darkness,
and even if despair is raining down on me,
...I will go on living,
no matter what!
Just as you did!
I want you to remember
something for me...
My name is... Edmond Dantes.
Haidee.
I will not leave.
I will remain
with the Count.
If you wish to flee, feel free
to do so. But as for me, l...
Idiot! Do you really believe that
the Count wants you to die?!
Didn't you hear him? He said, "I want you
to remember my name."
Haidee, you have
to live!
You have to leave this place
and live!
Father, let's go!
I have always aspired
to two things.
To be nobler
than the nobility.
And to be a finer soldier
than any other.
But in the end, it was an egotistical wish
that glossed over the lies underneath.
Father!
There will be no more
running away for me, Albert.
Now, go! Hurry!
Keep her safe!
Hurry!
Run. Keep running!
Ever forward.
Edmond...
Albert!
Jump!
Excuse me.
Shout out my name.
Seek out my soul.
My name is Gankutsuou!
And I am always
with you.