Friendship is something that is
both fascinating and beautiful.
It was thanks to its power that the boy
was able to escape the bandits' clutches.
"And yet," my friend said to me, "there is
nothing so inconstant as the human heart."
Act 3:
5/22, Stormy
Hey! Albert!
Wake up!
I can't believe you
were still in bed.
I have an important visitor coming today.
I've been really busy.
You didn't have to come
if you don't want to.
Who's the visitor?
Someone who did me
a favor on Luna.
Oh, that fake Count
something-or-other.
Eugenie! That's going
too far!
Speaking of visitors, Renaud said
that he's bringing someone, too.
What?
You know, Albert, you must be
the perfect target for a con artist.
She's losing her temper...
What are you angry about?
Who says I'm angry?
I'm just enjoying our drive.
This isn't a race.
Oh, that's right. You love puttering around
at a crawl with no destination in mind.
Both behind the wheel
and in life.
My life is none
of your business!
Get out.
Sure, just watch me.
I don't want to ride with you, anyway.
What are you talking about?
We're already here.
For the life of me, I can't figure
out why you and I are engaged!
Then maybe you should ride
in Debray's car on the way...
Oh, boy...
Hey, would you
be careful?
Are you okay?
Yes.
Hey, Albert!
Come take a look!
Hey!
Geez, are women all you're good at
handling, Mr. Bigshot private secretary?
Every dull drive needs a little
stimulation, doesn't it?
Next to me is a hack
newspaper reporter,
...and in the back seat is a couple
who just got engaged!
That was amazing!
It was nothing. I was in a special
forces unit in the army.
Muscle reinforcement processing, huh?
I'd heard rumors about it...
Thank you for your
assistance.
I-I'll get it myself.
Um... What is your name,
if I might ask?
It's Valentine.
I-I'm...
Hey, Maximilien!
Sorry I'm late!
There I was, out on recon, and I
stumbled into an enemy nest.
And when I accidentally dropped my
favorite grenade, I went as pale as a ghost!
From inside the hole, I could hear the
Erindanians making threatening clicking noises.
Anyway, I don't subscribe to the theory
that they're a sentient race.
In temperament, they're
vicious and cruel.
Would you like a piece?
Thank you.
Well, I don't want to go into detail
with these ladies present,
...but just once, they ought to round up
those human rights proponents...
It's delicious!
...and send 'em in there
to have a nice chat with them!
You're a lucky man, Franz!
Once you're married, you'll be able
to eat like this every day!
Um... Where was I?
Oh, right! Just then, I thought
I was done for!
And who do you suppose
showed up then?
None other than Space Cavalry
Captain Maximilien Morrel,
...the man I owe
my life to!
You're quite a man to look after a klutz
who stumbled his way onto a battlefield.
Where do you
hail from?
My family is
from Marseilles.
That's a rough place.
And you?
Paris, of course!
Admittedly, from the old part of town.
Marseilles... What sort
of place is it?
When I was young, it was
a beautiful harbor town.
At any rate, it's not a place that
a young lady should venture into.
We haven't climbed up here
in a long time.
What a great breeze.
Those clouds look a bit
menacing, though.
Something interesting
catch your eye?
Why do you suppose there's a need
to divide the world with city walls?
The ugliness of the outside world
exists for the express purpose...
...of making the beauty of our
kingdom stand out all the more.
Maybe, but there's plenty of great
things outside the walls.
Don't you think we should
open our eyes a little more?
Oh, have you grown up a little
from going on your trip?
I suppose you're right.
So go ahead and take on all the troubles
that exist outside the walls.
That should quiet those pangs
of boredom of yours a little.
That is what we should
be looking at.
The High Court of Justice.
Danglars Bank.
And the place your father works at,
Space Forces lmperial Headquarters.
The triangle of power.
That is the true "great thing" that
we should inherit, don't you think?
To me, it feels like we're the ones
who have been sealed in.
I am now no longer alone
in my solitude.
For I am now surrounded by the Furies,
the goddesses of vengeance.
In the darkness,
I awaited the dawn.
And once dawn came, I cursed my flesh
until night fell once more.
I even prayed that I would
lose my sanity.
But those prayers
went unheeded.
I even strove for death, but the Devil's
cold, pitiless hand held me back.
Soon...
It won't be long now...
Boy, what a lousy
drive that was...
Maybe it was punishment for
skipping the Cabinet meeting...
Have the candidates for the next
President been chosen yet?
The word on the street is that
His Excellency Morcerf is the front runner.
You've heard a few things from
your father, right, Albert?
Maximilien, you should watch
your step around Beauchamp.
He's a terrible man who will use even
his friends' scandals as fodder for articles,
...and he won't think twice
about it.
That's what they call
"impartial journalism."
I read your articles
all the time.
But I do not approve
of the content.
I get that
all the time.
Where are the ladies?
They went home, saying something
about their dresses being soaked.
Renaud's antique, too.
If they'd said something, I would
have given them a lift home.
That'd be like tossing food
to a monkey.
So, the Count of
Monte Cristo, huh?
I can't say that the name
is familiar.
There's no documents on him
at the Cabinet Secretariat, either.
It's probably an alias.
Or maybe...
A pretender or
a con man, huh?
I'll thank you to stop engaging in idle gossip
about an honored guest of the Morcerf home.
Where'd you say that you ran into this
"honored guest" of yours, again?
At Luna's Carnival
this past spring.
Apparently, the honored son of the
family was abducted by bandits.
That's too funny. Were you seduced
by one of Luna's wily vixens?
Damn it...
And that's when the Count rescued me
from their clutches.
I guess you owe him
your life, then.
It's clear that he's incredibly
wealthy, as well as very kind.
And would you say that this millionaire's
money pouch was stuffed full of forged bills?
Look at this!
If he wasn't of noble birth, would he
have a watch as beautiful as this?
Con artists use trinkets like that
all the time to win people's trust.
He's no con artist!
He commands a
huge spaceship,
...he travels with aliens and a woman of
unmatched beauty from Eastern Space,
...he's free from the rule
of any government,
...and he mingles freely
with people of all classes.
In everything he does,
he breaks with tradition.
And then,
once night falls,
...he wanders the darkness in search
of the lifeblood of beautiful maidens.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he did.
The Count has a ruthless side that
doesn't care about human life at all.
Franz!
Calm down, Albert!
You know, there was a case of a sailor who
contracted a local disease on some planet,
...and went around sucking all the
blood he could find, wasn't there?
You should be careful,
too, Albert.
I hear they prefer the blood
of virgin girls and boys.
You think he's a vampire or something?
That's ridiculous.
It's a lot more plausible
than Lunar bandits.
Or kindhearted
rich people.
His Excellency, the Count
of Monte Cristo.
Show him in
at once.
I beg your pardon.
The door was open.
It's an honor to
see you again.
The honor is all mine,
Viscount Morcerf.
Please, call me Albert.
Surely you and I are on familiar
terms by now, Count.
And now, as promised, allow me
to introduce you to my friends.
You already know Franz.
This is Lucien Debray.
He is a shrewd civil servant, who already holds
a key position in the Interior Ministry...
...in spite of his
young age.
This is Beauchamp.
He's a newspaper reporter.
He can tell you anything you
might want to know about Paris.
Admittedly, it's more of a third-rate
gossip sheet than a newspaper.
Most fascinating.
Cavalry Captain Maximilien Morrel,
hero of the Eridanus campaign.
Nice to meet you.
Ah, the very paragon of a
faithful, brave soldier, I see.
You know the Captain?
Not at all.
We've heard that you've come to us
from somewhere far away.
You're trying to interview him already?
Don't be rude to our guest.
I'm just doing
my job.
On many worlds, photographs are
seen as an abominable custom.
I must ask you
to abstain.
Sorry, sorry...
In the course of visiting many
foreign lands as a sailor,
...l've become thoroughly tainted
by the customs of other worlds.
I must seem quite the savage
to the people of Paris.
What sorts of places
have you been to?
I have traveled
to many places.
To Eastern Space. To Northern Space.
Even to the core of the galaxy.
Even the lmperium?
Of course. To a sailor, there
are no such things as borders.
Could that not be considered
treason against the state?
I see no reason to swear loyalty to people
who do nothing to protect me.
Do you not agree?
I see you possess
rather bold opinions.
True enough.
I suggest that you experience being cast out
into the vast universe all alone.
I expect that you will soon understand that the
only person one can count upon is oneself.
Set the table for tea
at once.
And where do you
hail from?
I came into this world in a land
that is beyond your imagination.
A place that you'd rather
not mention?
Franz!
Don't be rude!
If we're going to be associating as friends,
shouldn't we at least know that much?
That is quite understandable.
The reason that distinguished gentlemen
such as yourselves are interested in me...
...is because of the air of mystery
surrounding me, is it not?
Were that not the case, surely a rustic
aristocrat from the frontiers of space...
...would not have been given
a seat at your table.
Well, you have us there.
But that's exactly why we want
to know more about you, Count!
You're as naive as ever, I see.
Peppo!
Is something
the matter?
Huh? Um, no.
All right, what are you
up to?
You caught me.
I quit the bandit gang.
So I came here to Paris
to look for work.
But what are you
doing here?
I followed you here, Albert.
I'm lying, I'm lying!
It's just a coincidence.
There happened to be an
opening here, that's all.
Tell me, Peppo...
So, you remembered
my name.
Are you planning to
stay here for good?
Can't I?
Well, it's,
how can I put it?
Don't worry. Let's just agree to
keep each other's secrets, okay?
Are you interested in learning
that man's real identity?
Don't worry about it too much.
He's nobody special.
What do you want to do tonight?
Hit up Le Queen?
That's okay,
I'll pass.
As will I.
What the heck
is this?
The Count of
Monte Cristo's voice...
What about it?
It isn't on the recording.
What sorts of places
have you been to?
Even the lmperium?
Some might see...
It's probably a
mechanical malfunction.
So, is this a
malfunction, too?
What a beautiful woman.
T-That's my mother.
She is rather young.
This vista is that of Marseilles,
is it not?
She likes paintings like this. I don't know
why she chose that place as the setting.
It is magnificent.
Actually, my father hates
this painting.
He was going to take it down and burn it, but
we placated him by hanging it in my room.
Edmond...
Is there something
about this painting?
No. I'm afraid that it is time
that I took my leave of you.
Don't say that! Please,
have dinner with us!
My mother and father are looking forward
to meeting you, too.
If you're interested in paintings, my mother and
father have many others in their collection.
My, what a stirring
painting this is.
This is what
my father likes.
The ones that my mother has collected
are over here.
This must be
your visitor.
My mother's past,
which I never knew.
The men
in her past.
Adults who live
in the past.
Act 4:
A Mother's Secrets
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo, act 4,
..."A Mother's Secrets".
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!