Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
Poison has taken a beautiful girl and
turned her into a sleeping beauty.
A letter from a dead man led three men
back to loathsome memories.
I can hear it, the beautiful melody entitled
"Nightmare" that my friend is playing...
Act 11:
An Engagement Broken
Papa's here. Now you guys
are gonna get it.
Please step aside,
Madame.
I think not.
I beg you!
What's the matter?
Madame?
Mama! Mama, what's wrong?
What's the matter with me?
I don't understand...
Renaud! Get the car!
Right!
Heloise?
Heloise!
Get after them!
They've taken my daughter!
Catch them!
C'mon, cut it out!
Here they come!
Damn it!
All right, watch this!
Renaud?
Albert! Block the road!
Okay, that should do it.
Ow!
You're lucky that it wasn't
anything serious.
I wish that you wouldn't
worry me so...
Cut that out!
For one thing, what you guys did is
usually referred to as "kidnapping"!
Like you're one to talk!
Once people know why we did it,
I'm sure they'll understand.
But it's gonna be Monsieur Villefort
who tries the case. Right?
Yeah.
The dead man has
come back to us!
He would never forget what we did,
not in a million years.
You can't sleep?
No. Today was a
terrible day.
Where did you go
this morning?
The funeral of
someone I know.
Don't try to hide it from me. A letter
from Edmond came this morning, right?
How did you know
about that?
Tell me what this
is all about.
It was just
a tasteless prank.
Why would anyone use that name
for a prank?
I have no idea!
Edmond was accused of treason and died
in the far reaches of space, didn't he?
Isn't that what happened?
Do you know
anything else?
Please, Fernand, tell me.
He's dead and gone.
You're hiding something
from me.
The man is dead!
I'm not hiding anything.
He died in prison!
You still can't forget what
happened 20 years ago?!
Am I right?! Have you been thinking about
that man every day for the past 20 years?!
Are you still in love
with him?!
It was only because I was told
that he was dead that l...
You only did what because
you were told he was dead?
You were told he was dead, so you gave up
on him and married me instead?
Did you?!
Stop it.
Mercedes...
Mercedes!
The crime lab determined
that the cause was a poison.
It's a botanical toxin of some sort. We're
working as fast as we can to identify it.
I see.
Your Honor, I suggest that you
exercise extreme caution.
The culprit might still
be in this house.
I've already dismissed
all the servants.
You don't need to
worry about me.
But sir...
There are two things
that you must do.
The first is to prevent news of this
from leaking out to the public.
The second is my daughter.
Find out where my daughter is without delay!
The search team arrived
in Marseilles this morning.
They will probably locate her
by the end of the day.
Notify me when you
find her.
An arrest warrant
is standing by.
No, just pinpoint
where they are.
Leave them at large
for the time being.
Yes, sir.
Franz?
What's the matter?
I wasn't expecting you
to be here, either.
Is there a reason that you
don't want to go home?
Not really.
Want to read
this letter?
Who's it from?
Maximilien?
The guy sure has
neat handwriting.
Yeah, as opposed
to you.
You're pushing it.
So I guess he made it
to Marseilles safely.
Right about now, I bet he's freaking out
over what he's done.
That's very possible.
Say...
What kind of person is Valentine's current
mother? What's Madame Heloise like?
What do you mean? She's young,
and beautiful, and intelligent.
Yeah, she is, isn't she?
That's what I thought, too.
Albert, mind if I
ask you something?
Like what?
You said that you saw Madame Villefort
and the Count in the greenhouse, right?
What about it?
Ever since you told me about it back at Auteuil,
it's been nagging at me. That means...
What're you getting at?
Why did the Count happen to pick her
to have an affair with?
I have to think he targeted her specifically
and made his move on her.
And anyway, how is it that he could
take one look at your symptoms...
...and know right away
that it was poison?
Wait a minute, are you implying that
the Count is the one behind all this?!
I can't believe that,
not for a minute!
If it weren't for the Count, I might
not be standing here today!
Listen, Albert. Even if you
looked all over Paris,
...you wouldn't find many people who just
happen to have antidotes on them.
Not even doctors would!
Were you able to save me, then?
You couldn't do a thing to help, am I right?!
The only reason I survived was
because the Count was there!
What would the Count hope to gain by
trying to poison people? Tell me!
I don't know.
But I can sense it in him.
Sense what?
A deep darkness...
Sorry I bothered you.
Albert! Take a good look at him!
Look at the real Count!
Franz.
I have faith in him.
The only one who knows
the real Count... is me!
Encyclopedia of Toxicology
So, here you are.
You've come around?
What happened to me?
My memories are a jumble...
Oh.
I can't seem to shake off
this lethargy...
That's because of the poison,
don't you think?
Poison?
There's a good amount of poison
coursing through your body.
When did you get that ring
from the Count?
What's this about?
What are you implying?
Allow me to change my line
of questioning, then.
Have you ever
seen this before?
I... have no idea
what that is.
I got it out of your jewelry box.
Does that mean that this is perfume?
I have no idea.
It isn't mine.
Are you trying
to ruin me?
What you've done can never
be set to rights.
If it gets out that my
wife is a poisoner,
...what do you think will happen
to all that I've built?!
Your plans haven't run their
course yet, have they?
Who else is there?
Valentine?
Answer me! How many more
do you plan to kill?!
Is my name on your
list, too?
That's right!
I had intended to kill you, too!
I only need my
darling Edouard!
Look at you, acting like some
high and mighty saint!
I won't stand for
these insults!
I dare you to speak to me
in that tone again!
I'll kill myself
right here!
To the mighty Crown Prosecutor, the man who
values appearances more than anything,
...there could be no greater scandal,
could there?!
You... you don't mean
to suggest that l...
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to drink it?
What kind of man are you?
Are you only capable of
killing other people?
Tomorrow morning, you will be
transferred to a hospital.
I've had a private room with barred windows
prepared for you.
The quarters won't be very spacious, but you
will spend the rest of your days there.
Along with your poisons.
Albert! Take a good look at him!
Look at the real Count!
I know the real Count
better than anyone.
Count!
Hello, Monsieur Albert.
How are you feeling?
You seem to be in rather
high spirits today, Count
So, I take it that Mademoiselle
Valentine was saved, then?
Right. She's recuperating in Marseilles now
with Maximilien watching over her.
That is wonderful news.
Yes, but we got there too late,
and Valois, their butler, died...
You were able to save the life of your
dear friend. You needn't feel sad.
And Madame Villefort has
had a mental breakdown...
Count, why do you think those horrible
things happened to the Villeforts?
It was inevitable.
There are no coincidences
in this world.
It all comes down
to karma.
What do you mean
by that?
Are you saying that the Villeforts
deserved what happened to them?
You and I met
that day on Luna.
Perhaps you feel that our meeting
was a chance encounter.
But in fate, there are
no coincidences.
Just as that setting sun does so
according to the laws of the universe,
...fate, too, is composed
of unyielding necessity.
There's no such thing as
coincidence in your life?
No. There is not.
What I have is the power
of a strong will.
Even if other people accept coincidences
and are tossed about by them, I do not.
For you see, I have forged my own destiny
through the power of my own will.
Forge your own destiny
through the power of your will...
That is why we met,
and that is why we are here now.
Count, I want
to change.
I want to be a strong man
like you.
In that case, allow me to offer you
these words of advice.
Bide your time.
And hold out hope.
Bide your time...
Albert!
Why are you sitting there with that
idiotic expression on your face?
Eugenie?
How's your mother?
It doesn't seem to be anything serious.
She's been in a bad mood ever since, though.
Oh.
But enough about that,
listen to this!
I'm going to be playing the piano at the
concert hall along with the orchestra!
At the opera house?
Yeah. My dream is finally coming true.
I just got the news!
They've recognized my talent
on the piano!
Congratulations!
Make sure you come
hear me play, okay?
You bet.
That's so amazing!
Well, I should get back
and practice some more.
Um, Eugenie.
Your playing that night
at Auteuil...
It was... How can I put it?
It was really great.
You could really tell?
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Flowers for you, Mademoiselle.
Andrea Cavalcanti?
I'm home!
What's the matter?
Look at this.
Danglars says that he wants to break
off your engagement to Eugenie.
But why?
I have to know how she really feels.
I run to the opera house.
I have to know how I really feel.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo act 12:
Act 12:
Encore
..."Encore."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!