Get your moccoletti!
How 'bout a moccoletto!
Act 1:
At Journey's End, We Meet
Franz!
Why, hello, Marquise!
When did you
arrive on Luna?
I made a loop around the inner planets.
I arrived only yesterday.
I see. You arrived just in time
to catch the end of Carnival.
And by the way...
Who is this?
Ma'am!
My traveling companion,
as well as my best friend.
Viscount Albert de Morcerf.
I am pleased to make your
acquaintance, Madame.
My... You're the son
of General Morcerf.
Well, well...
Is this your first time on Luna?
I suggest you enjoy yourself, then.
This is a city where all your desires can
be fulfilled, no matter what they may be.
Apparently, he styles
himself a count.
But I'm not so sure.
Regardless, Luna's high society has been abuzz
with rumors about him this past month.
There are some who say that he's a nouveau riche
who made his fortune on the frontier,
...or that he's an alien
from outer space,
...or even that he's a monster
in human form, or a vampire.
That might be going
a little far...
Excuse me, but what
is he called?
What is his name?
The Count of Monte Cristo.
"Death is certain,
its hour uncertain."
Are you sure you weren't dreaming or
something? Daydreaming or whatever?
Get serious. This proves
that it was real.
And?
I'm gonna use it to make his acquaintance.
To meet the Count.
Are you crazy?
It's a huge hassle.
Don't do it. You have no idea
who this guy really is.
You think so?
Sure I do!
Begging monsieur's pardon, but are you
Viscount Morcerf from room 405?
Y-Yes.
Yes, that's me.
I have a message from my master,
the Count of Monte Cristo.
Well? What do
you think?
What do I think
of what?
Why would he want to talk to two
complete strangers like us?
His note said that he wanted
to establish friendly relations...
...with fellow aristocrats who were staying
in the same hotel, didn't it?
What a coincidence...
I'm not so sure.
There you go again.
You're such a worrywart.
At least stay and have
dinner with the man.
I have some doubts about whether
this guy is even a real aristocrat.
This is Luna, remember?
He's almost certainly a con-
How do you do, messieurs. I am called
the Count of Monte Cristo.
Thank you for coming.
Come now,
this won't do.
When a man has come all the way to Luna,
he simply must try these dishes.
Are you sure? We're the only ones
who are eating.
You haven't touched anything
all through dinner.
Please, you needn't concern
yourselves about me.
Just as journeys traveled alone are dull,
daily meals eaten alone have no flavor.
For me, speaking with guests as I am now
is the greatest feast I could wish for.
Please, help yourselves.
Incidentally, what did you
think of the opera today?
Speaking for myself, I don't
normally see operas very often,
...but I couldn't help being
drawn into the story!
Oh, I see.
So, Monsieur Albert, are you saying
that you have someone...
...whom you pine away for,
just as in the play?
No, of course not!
Come on, 'fess up.
Eugenie and I were chosen
for each other by our parents.
I've never been in love like the
main character of that opera.
It's the same with everything
else in my life.
Something that I can
lose myself in.
Something that will grab my
heart and never let go.
I set out on this journey
to find that something.
Why are you trying to make it
sound so noble?
As I recall, the goal of this little quest had
more to do with what's below your waist.
Franz! Cut it out!
Oh, youth is
a wonderful thing.
Endless possibilities. Hopes.
And ardent passion.
Count, have you ever been
in love like that?
I have.
What sort of woman
was she?
Hey! Don't be rude!
To be honest, I, too, once had
feelings for a certain woman.
As well as dreams of a future
with this woman.
However...
...all of them ended as nothing
more than dreams.
In short, those dreams
were only dreams.
And in those dreams' stead
stands the man that I have become.
Bertuccio!
Coffee for our guests.
At once.
I thank you for the honor
of your company tonight.
Not at all, sir!
The honor was ours!
I would like you to join me for luncheon
on my balcony tomorrow. What say you?
Really?
We'd be honored to...
We're terribly sorry, Count.
We appreciate your kind offer,
but we couldn't possibly accept.
Luna's public executions
are the highlight of Carnival.
The festivities reach their peak
as the blood of heinous criminals...
...washes away
the crowd's sins.
One cannot speak of experiencing Luna's
Carnival without having seen this spectacle.
Is that not so,
Monsieur Albert?
Y-Yes, sir.
You're exactly right, Count!
In that case, I shall await you here
in this room again tomorrow.
Pleasant dreams
to both of you.
Hey! Albert!
Yeah?
What's the matter?
You don't look so good.
It was cold.
His hand was as cold as ice...
It was like a
corpse's hand...
Who are today's condemned?
One is a man who committed murder
out of poverty.
over a love affair.
And the third is a man who slaughtered
an entire family to steal their possessions.
All three are heinous criminals
who are beyond forgiveness.
I did it to feed my family!
I had to!
My beloved wife and child,
please forgive me!
Please, spare me...
Stop that!
Stop it at once!
My Lord Cardinal!
I didn't murder anyone!
My rival framed me!
I'm innocent!
Please, undo
these chains!
You have to
believe me!
I bet they're just saying anything
that might earn them a reprieve.
I didn't do it!
I didn't do anything!
You moron!
Shut your trap!
I'm sick of you and
your damn whining!
As for me, I killed
ten people!
Women and children,
I killed 'em all!
How's that?! Live it up,
you bastards!
C'mon! I wanna see some more
happy faces out there!
Today's card is
most entertaining.
What say you?
Why don't we have a bit of sport
with this?
A sideshow to the execution,
as it were.
I have here
a single letter.
It is a letter of pardon that
was given to me by the Cardinal.
How in the world did you
get something like that?
Unfortunately, I have but
this one letter of pardon.
To make the choice
an impartial one,
...I have written the initials of one of
the condemned men on each card.
Now, please choose
one of them.
Come now, it's nothing more
than a little game.
Just a minute, Count!
If that's the case, shouldn't we hear
what they have to say first?!
My good Monsieur Franz,
we are not judges.
Regardless of what we do,
they are going to die.
I merely suggest that we make use
of that fact in order to enjoy ourselves.
At this moment, we have in our hands the
power to offer the hand of salvation to them.
Why do you hesitate to make
use of that power to do good?
Yes, it almost feels as if one
has become God, does it not?
What are you thinking?!
You're using people's lives
as a game?! You're crazy!
Come on, let's go.
Albert!
A game?
Yes, it is a game.
Our own lives are pieces that are toyed with
as part of someone else's game.
Has it ever seemed
that way to you?
I wouldn't know.
Let's go!
Come on!
I was of the opinion that you and
I would be friends, Monsieur Albert.
This is most disappointing.
You set out on your journey
in order to find something.
To find and grab hold of a new you.
Through the exertion of your own will.
Come on, Albert,
let's go!
Albert!
I'll... I'll do it!
Don't do it!
You'll be sorry you did!
It's just a game.
Isn't it, Count?
No! No!
Albert...
No!
Albert!
A pardon has been issued
by the Cardinal!
The condemned man
who is to be pardoned is...
...Rocca Briori,
also known as Peppino!
How do ya
like that?!
Thank you!
Thanks oh so much!
Long live His Excellency
the Cardinal!
Monsieur Albert, you have
done a good deed.
Truly a good deed.
Now, the show
is beginning.
Kill him! Kill him!
You mustn't look away,
Monsieur Albert.
Not for an instant.
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Don't hold back,
Baptistin.
Please forgive me.
My vengeance...
...is now set in motion.
Hey, let's go to a cafe or something
to clear our heads.
Or how about hitting
the red-light district?
Oh, right. I forgot. Sorry about that.
You hate that sort of thing, don't you?
I guess there's always
the casino...
Please, don't talk to me
about gambling!
What's gotten into you?
You were the one who was dying
to see it in the first place.
And then you let the Count
talk you into...
I know that!
I know all that!
"I brought this on my own head, and that's
why I'm angry! I'm angry at myself!" Right?
You're always fussing
over me!
Are you my girlfriend?
Are you my mother?!
Are you?
I'm going back to the hotel
to get ready for the ball.
What about you?
You alone?
Tonight is the last night of Carnival.
You shouldn't be alone on a night like this.
I want to be alone.
Today was the worst day of my life.
Albert...
Hey, don't be
in such a rush...
Are you going to come?
A passing fling on Luna.
It was a trap set by bandits.
Moment by moment, the hour
of death approaches.
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo, act 2:,
Act 2:
Until the Sun Rises Over the Moon
Next time on Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo, act 2:,
..."Until the Sun
Rises Over the Moon".
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!