What's happened so far!
This is our sister,
Miyazawa Yukino, 10th grade!
At first glance, she's elegant and
graceful, blessed with both beauty and wit.
Although she comes from a middle-class family...
...once you saw her you'd think she was
someone with intelligence, culture, and grace.
But in reality,
she lives only to show off in front of others...
...hiding her true
identity behind a mask.
But the other day,
Sis screwed up and
her other persona was discovered!
This guy is the real model of a perfect student:
Arima Souichirou.
He gets excellent grades,
is good at every sport and is generally a
sociable guy who would never make any enemies.
And he's a thoroughbred from a famous family
of doctors dating back to the Edo Period.
But he's quite
a scoundrel himseIf!
He schemed to make Sis help him with
his work by mercilessly exploiting her weakness!
Combined with feeling love for the first time,
Sis was falling fast into big trouble.
She finally snapped after a period
of total ineffectiveness, but...
However. . .
After much fuss, they made peace.
Since they both have
reputations to protect...
...they became comrades
sharing the same secret...
...and it looks as though everything will be all right.
But, however...!
What's wrong? Does it hurt somewhere?
Why'd I remember that all of a sudden?
I'd forgotten it long ago...
I think Arima's been acting weird lately.
Oh, you're still here. Work?
Yeah.
You, too?
Yup, but I just finished.
If it's taking long, I can help out.
After all, today's a half-day.
That's okay. I'm almost finished.
I'd better get going to practice. Later, Miyazawa.
Definitely weird.
Why is he keeping me at a distance?
We were getting along great until last week...
Hey, Miyazawa.
Want to form a study group?
Our school has lots of tests, right?
If we cooperate, I think we
might both be able to do better.
I see! That's a wonderful idea.
Cooperation is such a beautiful thing!
I can just see you thinking about
getting good grades without working...
This is just like on Lifestyles
of the Rich and Famous!
That's exaggerating a bit...
Wow, it's so big! You're so rich!
Father, Mother, this is
Miyazawa from my class.
Hi, welcome.
I had no idea that Souichirou
had such a darling classmate.
Oh, surely not.
I hope you and Souichirou
will be friends from now on.
I'll cut some cake later.
Girls are so much more fun to entertain.
Souichirou, come down
for tea at 3 o'clock.
Miyazawa, too, of course.
Yes, Father.
Your skill of feigning
innocence is really amazing.
Sometimes frighteningly so.
It's the result of extremely rigorous training.
But your parents are really wonderful.
Must be nice.
My house is really small.  It just doesn't compare.
I said to forget about my house already.
I'm home!
Oh, Yuki, you brought your fr...
Good afternoon.
A guy!
What?!
*Father*
I won't stand for this!
How dare you approach my precious
princesses, you goddamn maggot!
Prepare to meet your doom!
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Arima Souichirou.
We entrust our daughter to you.
What the hell are you doing?
I guess Yukino really goes for looks.
Or like, I don't think she
acknowledges anyone below her level.
She's not that interested in
guys in the first place.
I'm sure she sees most guys
as nothing more than paper dolls.
You can say that again.
She's as cold as a demon
when it comes to stuff like that.
Anyway, I'm surprised
you allowed this, Dad.
Well, you see...
A guy like that may never
appear in Yukino's life again.
I see, a keeper, is he?
Parents are such schemers.
But I hear Aririn's family operates a big hospital.
No way! For real?
So if I tell them that
my daughter is a friend of his,
maybe they'll give me a discount.
Right! Next time, let's all go together!
But we're all perfectly healthy!
Miyazawa, don't worry,
I don't mind...
Why the hell does my family
have to be so DUMB?!
That was so embarassing.
But it was fun too.
Up until then, he laughed a lot
and was with me a lot of the time.
But this week, he became cold all of a sudden,
and barely speaks to me at all.
I wonder if it's something I did.
Arima.
Yeah, what?
Um, I was asked to give this to you.
Thanks.
This is different.
This is...rejection.
Why?
We were friends until last week!
How'd it get this way?
I became afraid.
I don't know why these things happen.
I realized then for the first
time how clueless I am.
I've always just
pretended to be nice...
...played the model student,
and never seriously made friends with anyone...
...so I have no idea what to do at a time like this.
I've never spoken from my heart.
I've never fought.
Because I never took off my
honor student mask...
...because I deceived people with it
and never looked for my true self...
. . . so now, I have nothing.
So you're depressed, Sis?
That's what you get for trying
seIf-criticism for the first time.
You don't have immunity
to your own weaknesses...
...or to the existence of a boyfriend.
You never cared until now.
Aren't you glad you found out all
this stuff since meeting Arima?
That's right. I found out that
I have many different sides to me.
But what about Arima?
Well, we're here for you any
time you have problems,
Sis.
Except when it comes to money.
That's right. I wonder what Arima does
when he has problems.
Well, unlike me he's got wonderful parents,
so maybe there's nothing to be worried about.
Thanks for the meal.
Souichirou.
Yes?
The girl you brought over a while ago...
I seem to recall her name was Miyazawa.
Yes, she was such a composed, nice girl.
That was the most enjoyable tea party
we've had in a long while.
Oh, yes.
So, Souichirou, don't mind us,
and bring her here again, alright?
Yeah...
What about Arima?
Arima acts like any
other normal high schooler sometimes.
Why doesn't he show that to
anyone, except around me?
I thought about it a lot,
and just can't figure it out.
If he's not vain like me,
why does he stay so "perfect"?
Isn't it tiring?
Is he happy?
Did I do something to
upset him after all?
But you know...
...he's probably regretting that
he told me he liked me so hastily.
I'm really like this after all...
It must've totally ruined it for him.
Could it be that...he realized that
I secretly like him...?
That's the most likely explanation!
And I bet he now finds that annoying or something!
If so, why doesn't he just tell me?
Arima...
You have something you
want to say to me, right?
Say it!
What're you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
You've been ignoring me all this time!
I hate that! Why don't you just tell me?
It's nothing.
Why're you running away?
How am I supposed to
understand if you won't tell me?
Shut up! Leave me alone!
That's my only memory of my parents.
Just that little bit.
Now, won't you come with me?
That liar. He said we were friends.
He said he liked
me the way I am.
Oh, it's no use!
No use! No use! No use! No use!
I just can't figure it out!
Wow. When you get to high school you
get homework that not even Sis can solve.
I can't understand what Arima's up to,
no matter how hard I try!
I can't make a guess.
But I know what to do!
Which means...
I've gotta do it
according to the Code of Hamurabi
An eye for an eye! A tooth for a tooth!
A slight for a slight!
That's it! That's my only choice!
This isn't some kid's fight, you know...
She's good at academics, but...
Move it!
Get your asses out of my way.
Hey, Miyazawa, could you explain
this translation here to me?
Oh, my! From now on,
would you mind asking Arima to
help with such difficult problems?
It seems he's far smarter than I!
Something's up with Miyazawa this morning.
Yeah. Arima, did you do something to her?
But I guess even she has bad days.
So she's human too...
Iron and concrete, and the sight of rain.
They stir memories from deep within me.
What's wrong? Does it hurt somewhere?
Oh, did you wet your bed?
If I answer "yes," what would they do to me?
I bet you were scared all by yourseIf.
The hand that should have slapped me,
gently patted my head.
My new mother
changed my pajamas.
My new father held me close
while I fell asleep.
Such a strange feeling...
Why am I crying so much?
Why does my chest hurt so much?
Iron and concrete,
and the sight of rain.
They stir memories from deep within me.
They give me both fear and peace,
joy and anxiety...
...along with memories of those parents.
And Miyazawa...What was I to her?
Miyazawa?
Hmph! I don't care! I'll ignore HIM this time!
Hey, Miyazawa!
Hmph!
How pathetic! Why can't I ever be brilliant?
So I'm a stupid baby who
can only deny her problems!
Here. I'm no match for you.
You're just so extreme.
W...well excuse me! Leave me alone!
Sorry, okay?
He's back to normal.
I have a past that I don't want touched.
You touched it without realizing it.
Your existence caused problems for me.
I realized it,
so I tried to run away.
Even though it's not your fault.
I first noticed during our study
meeting when we went to your place.
I thought, "It's so different
from my place.
So this is what a
normal family is like..."
See, I'm adopted.
My current father is my
real father's oldest brother,
my uncle.
I really love my current parents.
But I could never say or do anything I wanted,
Like you can in your family.
I was forced to realize that.
It seems that my real parents
were really rotten people.
Stealing and extortion were nothing new to them.
In the end, they vanished, leaving a huge debt...
...and me behind.
I'm sure they were the shame of the family.
After my parents abandoned me,
the heads of the family gathered.
I bet they thought a kid wouldn't understand.
They told me to my face:
That a kid born from such parents
would never amount to anything.
So,
I had to become a perfectly flawless person.
I HAD to.
For my own pride,
and for the parents who raised me.
I was satisfied with the way I was...
this person I created.
Until I met you, Miyazawa.
Why was it you?
At first I thought I liked you
because you were just like me.
But, the more I got to know you,
I found myself being influenced.
I really hadn't known
about that side of me.
At that point,
it occurred to me.
Could it be that what I had
believed was "me" until then...
...was merely a fake I had
created through effort alone?
Was there another "real
me somewhere inside?
I thought, "This is bad."
I never should have realized that.
You lit up one mask after another.
You were like the light to me...
Light shining through the darkness.
Just by its existence,
Light clearly reveals where darkness is.
The darkness inside my heart.
To be honest, I resented you.
So I tried to get away from you.
Why?
You found your real self, didn't you?
Then why can't you be honest?
Why do you try to hide it?
What if I'm a terrible person?!
If I inherited my parents' blood...
I'm afraid of my blood.
I can't become
a good-for-nothing!
For my father...and my mother...
You really like your
current parents, don't you.
But, Arima...
...as long as you keep
stressing yourself like this,
they'll never become your real family.
Real families and friends love you,
even if they know your faults.
I love him.
He wants to protect those whom
he loves so much that he hurts himself.
Miyazawa...
What the hell did you do that for?!
This is the real Arima.
Don't worry. You're not a good-for-nothing.
I like this Arima better.
What did you think I was gonna do?
Kiss you? Yeah, right!
Not on your life!
The real Arima wanted
to come outside...
He wanted to take off his mask and
show his face to the world.
And he found me.
What was hiding inside you discovered
what I was hiding inside me.
I think that's wonderful.
Have more confidence!
Arima's a good guy!
I've decided.
I'm going to throw away
my model student mask.
I'm going to live for
my own sake from now on.
So I can like who I am.
How about you?
I'm glad you're here.
Me, too.
And what happened to us after that?
Of course, we became great friends.
Living honestly to ourselves
has become our motto, but...
M:Arima!
A:Don't hurt me!
Pretending they didn't see
...there's what they call public image,
and nobody wants to face reality.
We both have to laugh at them.
But I've gotten strangely
self-conscious about my love,
and my heart is in turmoil.
Darn, I should've taken him up on his offer
when I had the chance.
I guess we'll have to just
stay friends for the time being...
But one day while we were talking,
Arima said out of the blue:
Oh, yeah.
There's one part I really like about myself.
You became weirder and weirder every day
but my feelings for you never changed.
I've really liked you the whole time.
What'll happen next!
Arima again tells lucky Sis
that he likes her.
But she gets so excited that she
Loses the chance to reciprocate!
Will Sis finally be
able to confess her love?!
Next time on KareKano:
Her Problem.