What's happened so far!
Our sister, the masked honor
student Miyazawa Yukino, is the
ultimate Queen of Vanity.
The one who changed her, Arima Souichirou,
is an industrious model student who tries
to bear all his sorrows by himself.
The two, being affected by each
others lives, decide to live for
their own real happiness.
We're so happy for you, Sis!
But all sorts of problems
were waiting for them.
Yeah, but they solved them one after the other.
She doesn't easily get discouraged, after all.
And at long last, it's the first
summer vacation of high school!
Sis went off to have fun with the
friends she made for the first time!
They manage the standard menu such
as tea,  karaoke, and window shopping.
It was finally Sis's debut
into the world of friends,
but as it turned out before we knew it
she was mixed up in another
family's private problems!
I'm home.
Tsubasa, could you try this on?
Definitely cute.
I'm glad I have such a good model at home.
All I have to do is come up
with clothes I want you to wear.
Say, can I have this dress?
I want to go out somewhere with it on.
You like it? Okay,
shall we go for a drive tonight?
We can go to a Chinese
restaurant in Yokohama.
Why?
Why are you talking about
remarriage all of a sudden?
I could cook and clean and do laundry.
I could do everything by myself.
Why are you bringing up
"family" all of a sudden?
Am I not enough support for you?
Morning.
Breakfast is almost ready.
Oh, let me help with that.
Let's eat!
This is really nice.
It's breakfast as usual...
...and yet having so many girls
around makes the atmosphere more festive.
You know...
Maybe I should have two
or three more children...
I.. I don't want any more siblings!
I want an older brother...
Please don't talk about
family planning during breakfast.
Besides, there's no guarantee
that they'd be all daughters.
You might get three sons.
Then I'd make a baseball team.
We have Yukino(snow),
Tsukino(moon), and Kano(flower),
so their names would have to match.
Like Riku (land), Kai (sea), and Kuu (air)?
Like Justice, Friendship, and Victory!
I want twin boys,
Kouichi-kun and Tsuyoshi-kun!
(The Kinki-Kids)
Or if they're a girl and a boy, "Love and Faith."
Flowers and Dreams!
Heaven and Earth!
The Old Man and the Sea!
Romeo and Juliet!
Beauty and the Beast!
I can't believe them...
Jack and the Beanstalk!
Fit 'n Trim!
Floor and Matt!
Abbott and Costello!
See you later!
Well, I guess I'll do some studying.
Then I'll study too.
Can I use a desk?
Here, use Tsukino's.
Ok.
I'm going home.
Yes!
I'm sorry I was so selfish.
It's not like anything would happen
by holing myself up here any longer.
But... are you sure?
Yeah.
My indulgent dad refused
to give in to me this time.
So I have to give up.
Tsubasa!
I'm home.
I'm so glad you came back.
I'm sorry,
I should have considered
your feelings more...
It's okay.
I just wanted to be a little selfish.
I'm fine now.
You can do whatever you want.
Th..Thank you.
Oh well. If my hopes can't be fulfilled,
I don't want anything to begin with.
I don't care anymore. I don't care.
You've never met her son?!
You were so gung-ho about the remarriage...
...so I'd thought you had
taken care of all that already.
You have no sense of planning.
You're a grownup so get it together!
But, but...
I wanted your understanding
first before anything else.
My son isn't one to worry about details like that.
He was rather indifferent
when I said I wanted to get remarried.
Ah...
I'm getting nervous.
I wonder if he'll like me?
Hey, calm down.
I have to show him I'm a r..reliable man,
as his f..f..father...
You don't have to worry so much...
Oops! I spilled it!
Here, wipe it with this.
I can't take you anywhere.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm her son, Kazuma.
Yes! Kazuma.
So, you play music?
You must be really serious
about it. Quite impressive.
I'm still just dabbling in it,
so I'm not that good.
Why does the guy who might become
my brother have to be
some rock dude?
I'm unlucky through to the core.
Even if I've given up already,
how am I supposed to deal with a guy like this?
Uh-ah.
Well, none of it matters anymore.
So, Kazuma-kun, which high
school do you go to?
Yes?
What was that... just now...
Uh-oh.
Maybe he fell in love with me at first sight.
Oh no! What should I do?
If they get married we'll be
living in the same house!
What should I do if he eyes me strangely?
It happens on TV all the time!
While the parents are out...
...and stuff!
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
Am I really THAT unlucky?!
Oh, dessert.
Have mine.
What?
Hey Mom, you've found a nice guy.
I wasn't going to care since it's all up to you,
but he's a really nice guy.
I think this is a good idea.
R.. really? Thank you,
that really makes me happy.
Plus, I'll get such a cute little sister!
Seventh grade, huh?
How adorable.
I'm so happy I can have such a cute little sister.
I'd heard she was a kid my age so frankly,
I didn't know what to think...
...but I guess I'd heard wrong.
This is great.
I want you to get married right away.
U.. um, Kazuma-kun...
Tsubasa's not in seventh grade.
What? Younger?
She sure has it together
well for a grade schooler.
Well, although she doesn't look it
she's really in tenth grade.
Her birthday is before yours.
She's your BIG sister.
Say what?!
Oh no!
Tsubasa snapped!
And we're at a first-class hotel too...!
That was SO rude.
I don't know if I could
remarry after that...
Damn straight!
Well well, how scary.
What are you upset about, little girl?
My, you're so cute.
Hey come on, I'll give
you some spending money,...
...so come and play with me.
No way.
Come on, just for a little bit.
Quit pestering me!
Um, I'll catch you later guys.
Kazuma?
Come on, 30,000Y?
How about 50,000Y?
Hey man...
Quit being so shameful.
You okay?
*Officer, this way!*
Where's the girl who's getting abducted?!
You can't do that sort of thing!
It's you, isn't it?!
Freeze, right there!
You better come with us!
S.. say what?!
Don't resist!
You've got it all wrong! I didn't...
That's what they all say!
We'll get the details at the station.
Hey! Wait a minute...!
Man, that was a close one.
I nearly got hauled downtown.
Thanks for saving me.
Well...
you're the one who saved me.
It must be hard being that cute.
There are lots of weirdos around lately.
I'm glad I got to see you again.
We split up on a really
bad note last time...
...and I'd been wanting to apologize.
I've always wanted siblings...
so I guess I just jumped to conclusions.
You want siblings?
Yeah.
It's not like I can just get
them by asking for them,
so I never told Mom...
I wonder why...
I've envied relationships where
you can harass and support each other.
Because we were alone.
And then, POW there's this cute
little girl right in front of my eyes.
I thought, this had to be it.
I'm really sorry.
Well, that's all. Iwanted to
apologize for myself...
...and not because of any ulterior
motive to gain favors for my mom.
I hope I'll see you again.
Later.
I want to talk some more.
Can't we talk?
Okay, want to go to my place?
It's a short train ride away.
Let's get some ice cream at the minimart.
What'll it be?
Let's see... a Hagen-Daaz.
Are you siblings? What a cute little sister!
Please come again.
"Siblings", she said.
Come on! Come on!
Yes!
Man, it's hot in here.
Gotta open the window!
Come on in!
Pretty small, isn't it. Surprised?
Uh-uh.
Aw shit! I left the miso soup out!
Oh man, it smells funky!
Hang on a sec while I do the laundry.
It's my turn today.
Oww..
I wanted to go home somewhere.
The homesickness pierces my heart.
Is that good?
How about yours?
Want a taste?
See you later!
Okay, bye-bye!
Later...
I can really relax with you around.
I wonder why? We've only just met.
Well, it's natural.
We've led the same lives up until now.
Opening the door to find nobody there.
We both experienced that loneliness.
We know that without having to say it.
Because we're the same.
I see.
Then we're already like siblings.
Yeah. Like siblings.
For the first time, I
understood what Daddy meant.
Someone who could understand is by my side.
It would be so reassuring to have
someone like that waiting for you at home.
It was a lie to say
that all I needed was Daddy.
I know that now.
I was lonely all by myself.
I was lonely... Dad.
I'm home!
Hey, something smells good!
You hardly ever have dinner
ready. What were you...?
Welcome back.
Hello.
Tsubasa-chan!
We bumped into each other in town.
So I came to visit.
O.. Oh no! You came into this filthy house?!
We hadn't even cleaned it!
Tsubasa-chan's a young
lady from Yamanote!
What's a little roach like you
doing inviting her over, you idiot!
OW!
Look at these clothes lying all over the place!
And the closet open for the world to see!
The garbage didn't get taken out...
It was your turn!
No it wasn't!
You've done nothing but
embarass me from the beginning!
Is it on purpose!? Are you doing it on purpose?!
[Kids... umm... Mothers, don't do this at home.]
I didn't do swuat, ow! Uncle, uncle!
ho ho ho ho
O..oh, pardon me. How unbecoming.
Have you been pretending
to be reserved all this time?
Well, yes but...
Oh, don't get the wrong idea!
I act like myself
in front of Toshiharu-san.
I really wanted a little girl...
...and you're so cute...
I wanted to be your mother so badly...
Have I disappointed you?
[You saying you don't want a son?!!]
No. You're just like a friend of mine.
Is it true that Tsubasa is over here?
Oh, Daddy.
Toshiharu-san.
Good evening.
See ya.
Next time let me come over to your place.
I want to see what a Yamanote house is like.
Sure. I want to introduce you to my friends too.
I think you would be
perfect for a naive...
...unworldly guy like my dad.
Take good care of him.
Does that mean...
Now then...
Let's all be happy.
The next day, the two
were happily registered.
And shortly after the four of
them began living together.
Yo, Kazuma!
We heard your old lady got remarried!
Happy Marriage!
We came to help you move.
Oh shit! Tsubasa, hide!
LOVELY!
L..L..LOVEL Y!
Quit it!
Whoa, LOVELY! Smooooch!
Hey, what the hell are you doing?!
Your face is covered in dirt!
Let me clean it off for you - smooooch!
I wonder if that's
really just brotherly love?
Can stepchildren get married?
What?
What'll happen next!
Our program, "His and Her Circumstances,"
which has gotten favorable reviews,...
...has finally come to the midpoint of the series!
So we'd like to look back on
the path we've come so far!
Next time on KareKano:
What's Happened So Far.
With our deepest gratitude!