What's happened so far!
Our sister, the masked model
student Miyazawa Yukino...
...had been the ultimate queen of vanity.
Arima, the one who changed her...
...is an industrious model student who
tries to bear all his sorrows by himself.
They were affected by each other's lives,
and after repeated fuss, established a relationship.
They decided to live solely for their
own real happiness from that point forward.
But the world isn't that simple or generous.
It forced them to become super-busy,
as though challenging their relationship...
Starting with the school event which made them
not see each other: the Athletics Festival.
In order to carry his ambition of
the Asaba Mary-Land Project...
...a guy attempted to demoralize Sis
and possibly break them up.
This delinquent, perverted hunk, is Asaba Hideaki.
Their final exam grades
were the result of yielding
to their love-power and goofing off.
Sis's one-sided feeling of estrangement
occurred because of this.
And on top of it all,
there was interference and
pressure from the teachers at school.
And so on,
the various difficulties continued
to rise to impede them.
Go for it, Miyazawa Yukino!
Don't lose heart, Arima Souichirou!
This world exists for you!
But... however!
Hey, did you hear?
About Arima and Miyazawa?
Their grades really slid at finals.
Yeah, yeah.
Aren't they going out ?
They got called into the
Student Guidance Room and got lectured.
Whoa!
What's more...I hear they rebelled
against the teachers...and their
parents got called in to school!
No way, for real?!
I wonder what happened to them?
Yeah.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm still feeling last night's all-nighter.
There was this one math
problem I just couldn't solve.
I wonder what I'm doing wrong?
I've been thinking about it ever since...
Miyazawa!
Is Home Ec. this afternoon in
sewing room #1 in the old building?
Yeah.
Whatcha looking at ?
Oh, Math?
Yeah... there's this one problem
I just can't figure out.
Wow, that even happens to you, Miyazawa?
Oh, there's something I didn't understand, either.
Can I ask you about it?
Sure, if I know how to solve it.
I'm just not
"one of the girls," am I?
I talk with everybody,
but there's none of them whom I'm really close to.
It's been a long time since I stopped
playing the model student...
...but everyone still treats me like a guest.
Well, it can't be helped.
That's how I was until now.
Others can't adjust
if you suddenly become normal.
Arima!
Math?
Which problem?
R...r...right here!
This one.
Hey!
Asama-kun!
What're you doing? Let's go have lunch.
What the hell?!
I was wondering why you weren't coming
and here you are playing with the babes?!
I'm not like you.
Disgusting!
You sex fiend!
I said I'm not like you.
You made me wait out in the
blazing sun at the entryway all this time!
So why didn't you just wait in the hall?
You meanie!  You're always so mean to me!
Sorry to stop in the middle...
I'll take my time to explain later, okay?
Oh...
Um...
Sure...Th...those three really get along well.
Yeah, they're always with each other.
It sure is different once you start going out.
Arima's always been nice,
but he was never especially friendly with the girls...
...and Asaba's never treated any one person specially...
Oh, let's go have lunch, too.
Ok, want to go to the mini-mart afterwards?
Sounds great!
Hey, have you heard about
the legend of the kendo club?
Huh, what's that?  Never heard of it.
Our kendo club's really strong ...
...so they're always going to
practice meets at other schools.  Yeah.
So all schools would cheer
for their own teams, right?
But whenever it was Arima's turn
they start cheering for our school!
*Go Hokuei!  Go Hokuei!*
That's awesome!
But I can totally see why!
A hot guy comes
before school spirit!
I hear all the girls in 1-F
went with Asaba to Disneyland!
WHAT?
How lucky!  No fair!
Arima and Asaba sure get along well.
They're so picturesque when
they stand next to each other.
They're like the valiant hunk
and the delinquent hunk.
Miyazawa's really lucky,
being friends with those two.
Naturally, when she's so perfect.
I bet I could make friends with those two.
She's pretty and kind,
and not arrogant about being smart...
And always helps us with everything so nicely.
I guess perfect people really exist.
I don't know.
Maho...
Is Miyazawa really as nice a
person as you all say she is?
Couldn't it be that you're all just being deceived?
What?
What're you talking about, Maho?!
I always thought that girl was fishy.
So perfect at anything she does.
Isn't she just a brown noser?
What?
I don't know.
But her attitude's changed lately.
Maybe she's slipping and showing her true nature.
What?
Really?
But don't you think Miyazawa's
different from before?
Kii, you think so, too?
Actually, I was
thinking the same thing!
No way!
Me, too!
What?  So everyone was thinking that way?
There are women like that, you know...
...pretending they're all virtuous...
...taking everyone in, and cunningly
getting around in the world.
People like that are good at catching guys, too.
Guys are suckers for that type.
Doesn't it look like she "chose well"
by getting both Arima and Asaba?
If...If that's true,
I can't put up with it.
Yeah.
There were lots of girls who
liked Arima and Asaba.
If this is true, we can't forgive her.
That's right !
I know lots of girls who tried
and failed to tell them they liked them.
I feel sorry for them !
We were able to suck it up
because she was so perfect...
How could she deceive us ?
If that's how it is,
I'd rather have them be
taken by somebody else!
This looks like it's going to be fun.
I'm late.
This is the right room...
Why isn't anyone here?
Something's wrong. I'll try asking the teachers.
So sewing was canceled
and became study hall?
I went to the classroom,
and I was surprised that no one was there.
I couldn't figure it out,
so I went and asked the teachers.
Huh?
Oh, I know.
Want to go back to doing that math problem?
No, we got it already.
You stopped getting it because all
you do is fool around with guys.
Oh. I see.
Did you see Miyazawa's face ?
She turned so pale, the poor thing.
She's had it so good up until now,
she should suffer a bit.
Really, she stands out too much...
...just because she's a little popular with the guys.
Her looks sure aren't anything to write home about.
You're much prettier, Maho.
You should rule the whole class again,
just like in junior high.
You were so cool, Maho!
I guess.
Miyazawa?
Hm?
What's wrong ? You look upset.
No, I just didn't get enough sleep.
Should I do the rest?
I'm fine, don't worry.
I can guess why this happened.
It's because I'm friends with Arima and Asaba...
...and stopped pretending
to be the model student...
This is what I get for
deceiving people all this time.
It's no wonder they hate me.
The karma for deceiving them
without any desire for making friends...
...and making them praise me
and getting a kick out of it...
...is all coming back to me now.
ALL RIGHT!
The time for feeling sorry is OVER !
Nothing's going to get done if I keep brooding.
There's no use crying over spilt milk.
I should at least take it with dignity.
"After all, this is the real beginning for the real me !"
I have nothing to do.
It's been several days since
they started ignoring me.
This was a sudden fall from the
glory I had previously attained.
Almost like a politician after his downfall.
But that's unavoidable.
When I exposed the fact that I wasn't elegant
or perfect without hiding it...
...a rebound like this was inevitable.
I knew it was risky.
But I didn't want to
live in pretense anymore.
I have to climb over this wall myself.
So I thought, but...
With them all ignoring me so completely,
I don't have any cards to play with...
I can't figure out where to begin fixing things.
She's so pretty!
I didn't know there was
anyone like that in our school.
I wonder why I never noticed?
Hi, Tsubasa. Did you go to the teachers' offices?
I met her.
What?  Who?
Miyazawa Yukino.
Oh, the one going out with Arima?
She didn't look so hot.
Why does Arima want someone like her?
I bet it's because she's intellectual.
Arima's not some dummy who'd
pick a girl just for her looks.
SHUT UP!
I didn't ask you to reach a conclusion!
Ooh, scary.
This certainly wasn't in my plans.
I get hospitalized right after
getting into high school...
...and when I get out,
Arima's got a girlfriend.
What about my feelings, after I've
cared for Arima all this time?
I'll crush them.
Huh?
I'll crush them!
I don't care what dirty tricks I have to use!
I'LL DESTROY THEM!
Miyazawa.
It's that pretty girl I ran into earlier.
Oh, you haven't met before. I'll introduce you.
This is Shibahime from 1-D.
We were in the same junior high.
She's been hospitalized for a long time.
She came back to school the day before yesterday.
Arima, this is the first time I've ever
seen you being this familiar with a girl.
This is Miyazawa. We're going out.
Nice to meet you. I'm Shibahime Tsubasa.
Oh, hi. I'm Miyazawa Yukino.
What are you going? Miyazawa?
I don't know.
Miyazawa suddenly slapped my hand away.
Her notebooks...
Shibahime!
Miyazawa...
Miyazawa pushed me down!
How could she?
Why would she do such a thing?
U...umm...
Oh, a cat.
Shibahime, what're you doing?!
What were you trying to do?!  Huh?!
U...umm...
Why're you doing this?!
Ow ow owwwww...
I didn't do anything!
Liar!
There's no way Miyazawa
would do something like that!
Sorry, Miyazawa.
She wouldn't normally do stuff like this...
...but it looks like her temper
got sour while she was in the hospital.
You okay ?
And you, come over here and apologize.
There's a limit to how far you can go with pranks.
Yeah yeah, I'm SO very very sorry.
Oh, don't worry about it.
But you were in the hospital
for a long time, weren't you?
Isn't it bad for you if you move around like that?
Um, kind of...
She crashed into a stone wall on her skateboard...
...got buried under the rubble...
...and wasn't found all night.
But if she can move around
this much, she's probably fine.
In junior high, everyone envied me.
Because Arima was especially friendly to me alone.
You skipped out on clean-up again, didn't you?
I know you did!
Oh, it's all right.
I'm cute, so they'll do it for me.
I swear, you're hopeless.
Don't look at somebody else like that.
Don't belong to someone like that. Don't go.
Oh, I know.
If you've been hospitalized for
so long, I bet classes are rough.
I still have some copies of the study guides...
...so if you want, I can bring you a set.
Why you little...!
Humph!
Mind your own business!
All you do is suck up to your girlfriend!
You sure have changed!
Quit lecturing me like you know everything!
Why don't you just go and curl
up in your girlfriend's lap?
Don't ever speak to me again, it's too embarassing!
Bah-bye!
What the heck's wrong with her ?
I see... she likes Arima...
And here I thought it would
be nice to see Shibahime again...
What the heck was she so upset about?
He's so dense...
Sorry, Miyazawa.
Looks like I've caused you some trouble...
But I've cared about Shibahime for a long time.
I thought, if I had a sister, she'd be like her.
I know he only thought of me like a sister.
That was just fine.
Until he fell in love with someone else.
You bit off more than you could chew.
There there.
It can't be helped.
Arima never saw Tsubasa
as a potential love interest.
So what ?
She can still monopolize Arima that way.
There's no use now.
Arima's feelings totally belong to that girl.
He won't pay attention to me any more.
Don't be such a chicken...
I can't stand it!  I hate her!
Gack!  Tsubasa!
Tsubasa, what're you doing?!
Tsubasa...
Is she a demon of revenge ?
U...Umm...
You don't even know a thing about Arima!
Tsubasa...
Shibahime totally hates me.
Ignored by all the girls in my class,
hated by Shibahime...
I'm really not doing so hot these days...
Miyazawa?
Sorry for all the trouble Shibahime's causing.
We're her friends...
Please understand her feelings.
It's really complicated for her.
Oh, sure. I don't mind.
She hasn't done anything
that bad to me... I'm okay.
What a relief to hear you say that.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Anyway, we'll try to keep her out of trouble,
so please don't be offended.
If anything happens, just let us know.
Bye bye. See ya.
Bye bye.
Lucky...that girl has friends.
Hey, how long are we going to keep doing this?
What, are you siding with Miyazawa?
Laughter, Fury, Anxiety, Love, Friendship
Rivalry, Gowth and Degeneration
Within the doors of the classroom...
...are all emotions.
What'll happen next !
Surrounded by enemies...
...Sis is ostracized by the new characters
as they appear one after the other.
But the deadlock comes to an end.
Yes, Shibahime Tsubasa goes
in for the kill!
Next time on KareKano:
Everything Starts Now.