In the second half of the 20th century,
Japan was suffering the greatest
economic recession since the War.
What with the repeated chain
reactions of bankrupcies...
...an increasing unemployment rate, atrocious
crimes committed by juveniles, and so on...
...it had become an era and a place fit...
...to be manipulated by
the image brought to mind...
...by the phrase
The End is Near.
Meanwhile, the masked honor
student Miyazawa Yukino...
...in class 1-A of the Kanazawa
Prefectural Hokuei High School...
was the ultimate Queen of Vanity.
Arima Souichirou, the one who changed her...
...was a real model student who
never made enemies...
...and tried to bear all
his misery by himself.
Although how they came about was different,
the two came to share a secret as...
...model students with
dual personalities...
...and after passing through phases as...
...partners in the Student
Assembly, good friends...
...and more than friends
but not quite lovers...
...they finally became a couple.
And they decided to live for
their own true happiness.
But the storms of life  subjected them to an...
...almost harsh series of ordeals.
Go for it, Miyazawa Yukino.
Don't lose heart, Arima Souichirou.
This world exists for you!
Whatcha doing standing there
daydreaming? You'll be late!
Hey, Tsuki!
I'm Miyazawa Kano,
currently in eighth grade.
I'm at a sensitive age!
My family has five members,
including me.
My mother, and father,
and two sisters.
Oh, and our Pero-Pero.
That makes five people and one dog.
My father's a big kid.
Very naive.
Yuki calls him our big little brother,
and I have to agree.
My mother's nice.
She only talks about simple things,
but she's warm and kind.
Even from our perspective,
they seem to be a happy couple.
My immediate older sister is Tsukino.
I have NO clue what she's thinking.
She says zany things all the time, so I
Hey! What've you been mumbling about?
Tsuki...
Hi there.
Hi
As a whole, my family keeps up a good facade.
The oldest sister is Yukino.
Put us together and we're
snow, moon, and flower,
the nice things to look at in the seasons.
I do think we sisters are all
rather good looking.
Yuki is especially pretty,
just like our mother.
Argh! I'm going home,
GOT IT?!
She's smart, and gets things done.
But she's a little...
...er... really extreme.
That's the eldest daughter, Yukino.
Ahem
I'm in eighth grade,
but I've read lots of books
and seen lots of plays.
I think I observe people rather
objectively too.
I look carefree, but I
really have it together.
That's me!
No matter what happens,
the family will be safe as
long as I stay strong.
Maybe that's a little too pompous.
What's pompous?
O-oh, um, nothing.
Gee sis, you're home early!
What's with everyone?
What are they excited about?
The lottery!
Dad said he got tickets
from someone at work.
If we win, he said we could
go somewhere for New Years!
Sheesh, why does our family always count
the chickens before they're hatched?
Well, you could say that we're
just typical middle class,
and that would be the end of it but...
Doing intense reading again?
Yeah. It's old, but it's
quite touching.
Touching is good, but try to cry
about it only when you're awake.
Your face is going to bloat.
What? Was I crying again...?
Don't just stick to sad stories
and read something fun too, ok?
Want to borrow one of mine?
I'm a kid.
A kid... but an adult.
I'm a grown-up compared to my
sisters Yuki and Tsuki.
I think I have good discretion.
Praiseworthy but audacious.
But I'm really carefree.
Bye.
Don't forget about tomorrow.
Bah-bye!
Bye.
The Culture Fair's so fun.
Everyone gets so psyched up
during the preparations.
But I can't believe how
carefree our club is.
There's nothing for the Literature
Club to get psyched up about.
I guess. They do the same thing
every year.
It might be different if we did a poetry
reading or something.
No way!
Nobody would listen to that.
I don't know. There might be
people who'd like it...
You're late, Kano!
Oh, Tsuki.
Hello.
Sis Tsuki, don't you have
to do anything?
Oh, it's fine.
My sister's sick, and I have
to take her to the doctor!
So, you're going to walk
home with me today.
Am I your excuse?
Well, my class is going to do
a maze and a bazaar...
...and I was told that it would be...
...more muddled and maze-like if we...
...do it all the day before,
helter-skelter-like.
Who told you that?
Dad.
Figures.
What is it?
I thought there was someone
watching us...
Maybe it's a stalker.
Oh, is it now?
Well, I'll have to excuse myself now.
Bye.
Bah-bye!
Take care!
It's often just your imagination
at times like this.
You know, when people take the same
path home and you get too self conscious.
If it's just our imagination
it'll be gone before we know it.
S-s-sis...
Looks like we had the
wrong misunderstanding...
How long did the silent battle go on?
It might have been only 4 or 5 minutes.
But the tension .was too much for us!
S-s-sis...
We've failed in giving our
tail the slip.
Okay. I'm okay.
It's dusk. If we make it to a main
street there'll be people there.
We should try to find a way
out of this mess...
Wait.
Here we go!
1,
2,
3!
We're sorry!
Sis, you moron!
We made a fool of ourselves!
But it looks like it was a
misunderstanding after all!
However...
This was nothing but the prelude to the
terrifying incident that was about to unfold.
See you later!
She's off early again.
It's for her play.
Yukino's an actor as she is,
so why does she need to practice?
Dear, you know how it is.
The springtime of her life, huh?
That's right!
My battle began on that day.
Seconds please!
What's wrong, Kano?
Tsuki hasn't noticed.
She's convinced that that incident
yesterday was a misunderstanding.
But I can see it.
The dark shadow, following me...
You didn't see it at all.
Morning. What's the matter?
Don't you stand behind me!
Who?
Kano's been reading too many books.
Well, I'll go on ahead.
Can't let your gloomy mood drag me down
or I'll bomb first-period English!
Is something bothering you?
Yeah, a little...
What?
Come to think of it,
I've seen her around a lot lately.
I think she's in 2-D...
Who on earth could the shadow be?
There are cases of people getting caught
up in a crime without their knowledge...
Wait, dad's lottery ticket
they must be after them...
...and they're going to kidnap me?!
No... it couldn't be.
We haven't even won yet.
However...
I'm home. Is anyone here?
Mom? Sis?
Y-yes... this is the...
Miyazawa residence...
Hello? Hello, mom? Hello
Tsuki! Welcome back...
I'm home.
Maybe it's someone who likes you, Kano.
What the heck are you thinking?
I can't believe you.
You're still talking about that?
I told you it's your imagination.
But even today...
Wow, you're so popular!
Sis!
What, you wanna rumble?
I'm going to the bathroom.
I swear! Those sisters of
mine are no help at all.
Why...
You're sure taking your time.
Tsuki...
See, I told you! That
girl from 1-D is following
Kano around because she likes her!
That happens sometimes.
Maybe it's admiration.
At the stage when they're still
not comfortable with boys...
...girls look up to female
upperclassmen or teachers.
That's so beautiful.
An episode of the good
old years, right dear?
Well, good luck Kano.
Thanks a lot!
Well, I'm too busy right now,
between love, the play, and studying.
You understand, right?
And I'm doing the maze and the bazaar.
I thought you said it's supposed be
all helter-skelter and muddled.
The helter-skelter part just started.
Kano, you're always reading
those difficult books,
so solve this one yourself.
Oh, it's wonderful to be young!
My two sisters are heartless.
My father realized it's not a guy
so he could care less.
I have no allies.
Love is something you have to
face by yourself...
Wait, why am I taking this seriously?!
Hey, isn't that the girl?
Why don't you go talk to her?
No way!
Then I will!
You'd better be careful.
Maybe that dark shadow following
me around was the girl from 2-D
Then what was that figure this morning...
Miyazawa-san!
Kano, this way!
Tsuki.
What am I doing?
But first, we have to get out of here fast.
Let's go.
Hey, what's going on anyway?
Say something, will you?!
Wait!
You OK?
I'm sorry. I can't tell you now.
But please trust me.
I trust you.
I won't have it! I WON'T HAVE IT!!
Dad...
I changed my mind.
Nobody will dare marry my little
princess, not even a girl!
What're you talking about, Dad?
We're not going to get... married or...
Get married?
I said, don't take this seriously.
Oh?
What's this?
A gentian. So pretty!
Oh! Let's see... I'm always watching you.
In short, I am at a loss.
Excuse me, What would you do if a girl
you didn't know told you she liked you?
I'd be happy.
It's all cool with me.
Sorry, I don't understand that kind of thing.
Being liked by someone is so bewildering.
There are no words to describe it.
Well, this sounds like a good opportunity
for an armchair love counselor like you.
Experience increases your understanding...
...wasn't that the basis of
learning or something?
But I honestly don't need to
experience this kind of thing.
Oh, there you are, Kano.
She had this threatening look on
her face. Is this a challenge?
That girl?
Yeah, that girl.
After school.
The school back yard.
And make sure she doesn't run away!
If she said all that, what's this for?
Isn't it just a formality?
It's a challenge after all.
Come on, come with me.
You can be my chaperone, or just a witness.
What are you talking about?
This is serious! I'm scared.
So a crisis finally befell
even you, the theorist!
What should I do, what should I do?
If she, you know, starts
crying all of a sudden, or...
How could you!
How could you dump me!
Well, that's not what I mean...
Let me die! If we can't
be together, I'd rather die!
Tsuki... you're laughing too much.
I've decided.
I'm just going to take the plunge.
You're going to plunge?
Nothing's going to happen anyway.
I'm just going to say how I feel right now.
Want me to go with you?
That's okay. I'm just going to plunge.
Don't secretly watch or anything.
Of course I won't!
Ooh, there she is waiting.
What a strange turn of events,
don't you think, Rika-chan?
When it gets this far even her cool is affected.
I gotta say it. I gotta say it.
On your mark... get set!
Do you like me or something?
What?
Like me... aren't you
the one who's after me?
I'm not after you! You're the one!
You're looking at me all the time!
I looked at you because you were there. I mean,
aren't you the one who was always following me?
At school, and on the way home, and you were
even looking up at me in front of my house!
I live in the neighborhood, so I can't help it!
I have to go that way to get home.
Why were you looking at me?
Because you were looking at me!
What about you?
Because you were looking at me...!
Too self-conscious?
Way too much.
I thought you were staring
at me all the time...
That's what I thought too.
I thought, she must've fallen for me.
Yeah, me too.
And then I started blushing myself...
And turning away if I made eye contact...
And losing sleep worrying...
And thinking that I'd have
to take responsibility.
What, they solved it?
Thank goodness. Kano, I'm sorry.
What, so both of you were
jousting the windmill?
Yeah, seems Megumi-chan was troubled too.
So her name's Megumi-chan?
Yeah, Megumi-chan the
armchair love counselor.
Birds of a feather huh?
This is great.
Well, we didn't become a couple,
but we did become friends.
Huh? Then what about that gentian?
Tsuki...
Tsukino?
Yeah. It was all her evil plot.
Evil plot huh?
Tsuki had Yurika follow me around.
Can you believe that?!
But Kano always looks so unruffled
and all-knowing and couldn't care
less no matter what happens,
so it just makes me want to
have a little fun with her.
That's true.
Sis, not you too!
So in the beginning, it was just to scare me,
but after Megumi-chan came into the picture,
they changed plans and got the gentian!
It was more fun that way!
Tsukino... maybe you're...
picking on Kano too m...
What?
Why, Why...?
Will you accept the gentian this time?
What?  Then was the gentian
last time for me too?
I just assumed that was to trick Kano...
I gave them to you.
What? But why me...?
I'd always thought Kano
had such a nice sister...
Oh, I get it. So that's it!
Otherwise, there's no way
Yurika would have helped her fool me.
Would you please be my sister?
Um... I...
Tsuki.
Kano! Help... me...
Solve this one by yourself!
Sis thoughtlessly doesn't realize that
something's wrong with Arima-kun!
But unrelated to that,
Tonami Takefumi finally realizes his feelings!
And people don't realize what's going on!
If you want to know, pls. See next Act.