It's now August,
and Arima has gone to the Interhigh.
Ah! It's a letter from Arima!
When most business can be done
over the phone these days,
letters are unusual.
What's it say, what's it say?
This is a souvenier from the
training camp in Nagano.
I'll be back on August 5th.
So concise...
But when I opened the envelope,
it smelled ever so faintly of Arima.
It gave me a painful reminder
of how much I missed him.
Oh, Arima? I saw him.
When I went to school for volleyball
practice I ran into the kendo team...
...which had just gotten back.
I was surprised.
Arima had gotten so much taller
that he looked so different, but cool.
If he gets taller with those looks, he'd be a model.
*So good looks is all that matters?*
Hey, what's the matter, Yukinon?
Maybe I should join a club too...
What's the matter all of a sudden?
Although we'd love to have you
on the volleyball team.
Well, I'm not doing anything.
Arima does sports and he's getting taller,
and there's so much going on...
But nothing changes with
me just sitting here.
Whining about relationships, are you?
I can't take any more of this
when I'm not even getting paid.
I'm leavin', so I can't understand that shit.
All right already! I'll stop talking about it!
It's not like you're doing nothing.
You do all that studying.
Yeah but, that would go without saying.
And as for studying, I finished my homework
already, so I don't have much to do.
I have more free time now that
I no longer train to show myself off.
Why don't you join?
Yu-ki-non...
Let us copy your homework!!
1000 yen per subject.
No Fair!
How could you? Are you going to bring
money into our friendship?
One good deed deserves another.
Money doesn't rule everything in the world.
I've had a change of heart about that.
My brains will bring me lots of money.
At this rate, I can be a doctor
or lawyer or anything I like.
In any case, these brains are going
to earn me an income of twenty
or thirty million yen a year.
So I'm not going to sell myself short now.
Damn! This is what's annoying
about smart people.
You've really gotten over being
Miss Goody-two-shoes.
You used to loan your notes
to people all the time,
and had everyone totally fooled.
Hey, then how about the drama club?
Huh? Drama club?
There's someone who could write the stories.
There's someone who could make the clothes.
The pretty faces.
Me?
And an acting genius.
That's not very flattering.
See, you can do it!
What are you being so amused about?
Then what are YOU going to do?
Oh, I'm on the volleyball team,
so it has nothing to do with me.
No fair!
No, no, no way!
Our school doesn't even have a
drama club in the first place.
Did you get an idea?
Hey, don't make up stuff we don't need!
Tsubaki's just teasing us!
Bye!
See ya.
Bah-bye!
Later, see ya.
Bye-bye!
We may not be able to see each
other for a while.
Okay. Good luck at the Interhigh!
It's no use.
I told myself I'd be apart from
Arima for only a little while...
Why do I become hopeless
as soon as he's gone?
Three more days...
So depressing...
Two more days...
Yuki-chan, phone call from Isawa-san.
The day before yesterday...
...you said you finished all your
homework, right?
I was hoping you could help...
...me with a couple things I'm stuck on.
Sure.
Thanks for coming over.
What's with your face?
D..Do I look weird?
You're emitting a strange aura.
I guess even someone with steel nerves
like you gets lonely without Arima.
It was like this during the
Athletics Festival too.
The moment Arima was gone
I became a wreck.
I'd been vaguely aware of it, but...
Without the vanity and pride,
I'm really a chicken.
I can't stand myself!
When Arima's doing what he has to do,
I can't stand that all I can do
is sit around moping!
Don't make such a ruckus in
someone else's house.
What's wrong with that?
Guys like that kind of girl.
But Arima has rather weird tastes...
What with Asapin and Tsubasa-chan...
*The world is money!*
I don't really know, but I don't think
he would like a passive girl like that.
I think it's all right.
It's love because it knocks your
heart off balance.
While you're acting cool and having
things under control,
it's not true love yet.
That means you value yourself...
...more than the other person.
You met someone who could even
collapse the balance of your heart.
That's why your heart gets stolen.
You're sooo mature!
You're the first person I've ever
wanted to call big sister.
Big sister!
If you're going to make fun of me
I'll stop talking.
Just kidding.
Mahorin, you must be in love now.
Are you going out with him?
I can't imagine the kind of person
you'd fall in love with.
What's he like?
A 28-year old dentist.
He's an adult,
so I'm no match for him at all.
He has composure.
He's kind and strong.
I love him, but I also admire him.
I want to become the kind...
...of person he can respect.
This is the first time I've seen that
tough punk Mahorin look so tender.
Love is such a mysterious thing.
The heart is formless and weightless.
It can't be measured in terms
of size or depth.
Although no one has seen
its true nature,
it definitely feels pain.
It only responds to a certain person.
Tomorrow...When tomorrow comes,
I can see him.
This will probably be the longest day.
Pero-Pero, let's go play.
The sisters are at practice.
Pero-Pero,
...are you trying to comfort me?
I want to see him. I want to be with him.
Every waking moment is painful
when we're apart.
Maybe I...
Maybe I actually love Arima...
...even more than I thought?
I was immature...
and so I just hadn't realized it,
but in reality...
In reality, I've always...
Yuki-chan,
can you go buy some soy sauce?
Sure. Pero-pero! You're my bodyguard.
You'd think you'd notice,
and not walk on by.
I'm home.
Before me?!
Not the tongue.
Arimaaa! Arimaaa!
Miyazawa?! A tackle?!
In any case...
Arima's gained an indefinable sexiness
since I saw him last...
You got back early.
Yeah. I was supposed to come home
on the bullet train...
...tomorrow with everyone else,
but it looked like they were going
to put me
in charge of things like organizing
the debriefing,
so I made up an excuse
and came home.
Wow. I didn't know you would
cheat like that.
Well, the way things were going.
I didn't know when I'd get to see you...
Are you on vacation for
the rest of the summer?
Can we hang out together?
Yeah. There's some practice,
but it won't take out my
whole day anymore.
What've you been doing?
You told me over the phone, but...
I did all my homework!
And I played with my friends,
and watched primetime movies,
and visited Grandpa.
That's nice.
But I was really lonely without you!
R..R..Really? Me too...
But Arima,
you've sure gotten taller
since I last saw you.
You're head's at a different
level, so I didn't notice you.
Yeah, it hurt every time
I moved my joints.
It was really tough having that happen
right before the competition.
How'd the competition go?
Oh, I won.
You WON?!
Win?! Win as in first place?!
You're the number one in kendo
in Japan?!?
Y..Yeah.
That's AWESOME!!
M..Miyazawa?!
Oh wow! That's so great!
I bet you were so cool!
I wish I could have seen it!
That's awesome!
Great job, Arima!
For a moment, it occured to
me that he was so beautiful.
But being with you is better
than anything else.
I felt an emotion I'd never felt before.
It's spreading throughout my body...
...and will have me under its control.
How could I have been so indifferent
when I was with him before?
He loves me so much...
I can't even breathe.
Is this possible?
I've fallen in love with...
...the same person a second time.
Miyazawa!
Yo!!
Have you had lunch?
No, just breakfast.
We still have some time before the movie,
so let's go grab a bite.
Freedom!
I feel so happy when
I realize I'm finally totally free!
What did it feel like to win the Interhigh?
Huh?
Oh, well, you know...
That's it? You can brag, you know.
The final match was against our
school's captain.
Wow!
Our kendo team must be really good.
He had lost the final match last year,
and I'd seen him working really hard
for the win this time.
This was only my first year, so I couldn't
help thinking that I wanted him to win.
Arima, you want me to win, don't you.
Abandon such pathetic thoughts.
I have always wanted to
go all out against you.
If you hold back even a little bit.
...I'll forcibly steal a kis...
I'll do my best!!
Don't interrupt me.
And so you beat down your senpai?
Well, if I had lost even if
I had fought seriously,
I was afraid he would take that as
an excuse and do it anyway, so...
He gets this weird look
in his eyes sometimes!
You're so popular with guys too...
I wonder if this training camp
was actually risque?
especially in the locker rooms.
That's it! Don't say anything else!
Don't even imagine it!
Arima's voice. His hair.
His expression.
The way he talks.
It's like being immersed
in pleasant music.
Uh-oh.
I shouldn't have worn a sleeveless dress.
I get paralyzed just by his gaze.
I can't imagine Arima was
immature like me.
He doesn't force his feelings
so it never dawned on me.
But there were hints of
that every so often.
Now that I think about it,
he must've been going along at my
pace because I'm such a baby.
And I express my feelings like a dog...
I have to tell him.
I love you even more than before.
My heart starts pounding
just by being with you.
Oh god that's embarassing.
No! I have a bad habit of suddenly
becoming shy about such things.
I have to express very important feelings.
I'm sure he'll be really happy.
I'm so glad I can make him happy.
But, if I said that what
would happen to us afterwards?
Want something to drink?
No thanks.
Oh, sorry.
N..Not at all!
Wow, that was great!
That final confrontation was awesome!
What should we do now?
Is there anywhere you want to go?
U..Um, no, not really...
You seem depressed today.
You periodically fall silent?
...are you not feeling well?
Oh, no!
That's not it...
Uhm... er... well...
Now, gather your courage
and tell him,
...Miyazawa Yukino! Say it, just say it!
Uh, not now... I'll tell you later!
This is bad. I'm sure he thinks
something's wrong.
It's just saying I love you.
Why am I so clumsy?
I can do everything else so well...
This is awkward.
But I will tell him.
I want to see his face light up.
Why are you avoiding me?
I'm not avoid
You're lying. You don't say anything,
or make eye contact.
Have I done something wrong?
No...
You were so happy yesterday. Why?
My feelings for Arima are
overflowing so much...
...I'm scared to even touch him.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry, I...
forgive me
IDIOT! Why can't you ever
say what's important?
I am so useless
Wimp! Coward! Liar! Showoff!
I hate myself!!
I hurt him! I hurt Arima's feelings!
I know he's afraid of being?
...rejected more than anything else...
I can't just leave it like this.
I have to apologize.
I have to get him to understand.
I'm not letting you go!
I don't care if you avoid me or hate me.
How long do you think I waited
to have you notice me?!
I'm not waiting any longer!
I'm never going to let you go!
I'm sorry I scared you.
I wasn't avoiding you.
I didn't touch you because
I was embarassed.
I didn't meet your gaze because
I didn't know what to do.
When I saw you again yesterday
after so long, I realized that
I loved you even more than before.
I love you even more than before.
My heart starts pounding just
being with you.
I'm so happy...
I finally got it out.
I was able to tell Arima.
I'm so happy Arima understood me.
We've been going out a long time,
but it feels like it's the first time
we told each other of our love.
I get nervous when I'm with you too.
R..Really?
It never looks that way...
Even with a girl like me?
Of course.
The person you love is special.
I feel like such a baby...
You must have a tough time.
What?
Oh, nothing.
It's okay. I'm happy every day
as long as you're with me.
It was so comfortable being
next to Arima...
...that we just kept watching the moon
suspended in the sky.
PREVIEW
Arima-kun came back!
Sis gets really excited.
But he was beginning to have?
...trouble coping with his reality.
And the time has finally come
to cross a certain line!
Next time on KareKano: Deepening
Well, I just hope it's not a
means of escape.