What's happened so far!
Our sister, Miyazawa Yukino...
...had a confession of love
from her classmate, Arima Souichirou.
But Miyazawa flatly
turned him down.
Right afterwards, her true nature,
that she had been desperately hiding,
was discovered,
and she became Arima's lackey.
Meanwhile, feelings of love towards him
had awakened in her for the first time.
After much fuss, they made up.
They were joined by
friendship for the time being...
...but at the very end Arima said...
My feelings for you never changed.
I've liked you the whole time.
So what'll happen
to them after that?!
Oh, look! It's Miyazawa!
She's so cute.
I wonder what she's reading.
Salinger!
That cover is Salinger.
How romantic.
That fits her to a T.
Yeah, that's the way a beauty's gotta be.
Oh, it's Arima!
He's as wonderful as always.
I wonder if he's really
going out with Miyazawa.
Oh, Arima.
Why do you show off like this?!
You said you were going
to be honest with yourself!
It's just a little!
Quit nagging.
People can't change that easily.
Ow ow owwww...
Until last week, I, Miyazawa Yukino,
and Arima Souichiro...
...had been model students.
Known all over school for
being graced with wit and beauty...
...excelling at all kinds of sports,
and for our pleasant personalities.
But that's not how we really are.
We've been "playing" model students.
Arima, to rebel against
his unfortunate beginnings...
And me, out of a swollen appetite for
praise, attention, and getting buttered up.
But we happened to find out
the truth about each other...
...and decided to stop the act.
To become more like ourselves...
But...
It takes considerable time and effort to
put into practice what you're not used to.
Geez, you're so pushy.
Well, that's fine...
...compared to the huge
problem in front of me right now.
Here you go.
Oh, the Athletics Festival.
Looks like it's gonna be a pain again.
- Oh, a typo.
- Let's see.
- Where?
- H...h...h...here!
Oh, you're right.
I was confronted with a serious,
urgent problem.
We aren't
officially going out yet.
More than friends...Less than lovers...
We stopped just short of
being an official couple...
It was like going out on the
highway with a learner's permit.
Why?
It all started when he said...
I've liked you the whole time.
Shall we head home? That's right.
What? I failed to say it.
I never get embarrassed like this!
Idiot, idiot! I'm such an idiot!
This is bad!
This isn't the time to just
Let's things take their course.
I have to do something.
"Destiny" has meaning precisely
because you shape it with your own hands.
Who cares about
"being myself" right now?!
My absolute top priority is
Telling Arima that I like him!
However...
...although I've practiced turning people down
and have successfully gone through with it...
...this is the first time I've
been the one doing the approach.
I've got absolutely no
examples and no experience.
But, nothing's going to
happen if I just sit here afraid.
All I have to do is do it.
Arima, Arima.
I'm sorry...
I was told to pick up a report
from Chemistry Room #1...
...but something came up.
Can you get it for me instead?
Sure.
This is the plan.
Lure Arima into the deserted science room,
and tell him.
Oh, Miyazawa, what's up?
Apparently a fluorescent light
broke in the 11th graders' class.
The place is a real mess with
broken glass all over.
What's wrong?
He's alone...I have a second chance already!
Oh, Miyazawa.
What was that noise?
Oh, just look at that.
Clean it up, okay?
Sorry about that.
Looks like no one's around!
Lucky! Third chance!
- Arima!
- Y...yeah?
Would First Year Class A
Officers Arima and Miyazawa...
...please report immediately
to the staff room.
Gotta tell him. Gotta tell him.
Gottatellhim gottatellhim
gottatellhim gottatellhim...
This is today's last chance!
A...Arima...
Today's lesson:
To get back a chance once
Lost requires considerable effort.
Soon...
Gotta tell him... soon...Soon...
Sis, what're you moaning about?
I swear, she's such a pain.
Although I keep doing such stupid things...
...I really like Arima.
What about him?
Let's's see...
He's smart and nice, of course...
...and he seems so gentle and neat.
And his soft, warm voice is so dreamy...
His traditional narrow eyes,
his fine hair, and his slim body...
And he says he likes me...
Whatcha' doin, Miyazawa?
We're off to the student council meeting.
Geez, Arima.
I'm blushing and stammering so much...
Why can't you figure it out?
Get a clue.
Arima hasn't tried to show
any hint of love at all since then.
I bet he's thinking that he
would annoy me if he's too persistent.
He's such a damn gentleman.
He has an excellent
poker face to begin with.
I couldn't tell what he was
thinking the first time either.
If he'd just show a little more on his
face I'd have an easier time saying it.
Show it on his face?!
That's it!
The timing's so hard because
I try to say it out of the blue.
I have to arrange
for him to be receptive.
The more Arima's flustered,
the easier it'll be for me to tell him!
I'll break that poker face!
He's alone.
This is the return match sent from heaven!
New chance!
Arima.
What're you doing?
Nothing!
I'm home...
Oh, Sis, welcome back.
Sis, listen to this!
I can't believe what Tsukino did!
Who cares?
It's over and done with.
Today, at school, right
when I was in class...
As an example, this goes like this,
and after this, goes like this...
I really got yelled at!
Quit doing weird stuff like that to me!
Well, when I saw you,
I felt like I just had to make you laugh.
It must be sisterly love.
How so?!
Sis, say something to her, would you?
You're lucky...
Jr. High is so fun...
S...Sis?!
Sis?
What's wrong?
Lots of stuff happens to high schoolers...
...stuff middle schoolers wouldn't understand.
Oh, but you wouldn't get it.
Middle schoolers are so carefree...
What's up with that holier-than-thou attitude?
Oh, the usual.
It has to do with Arima.
This is our sister
we're talking about here.
She probably dug her own grave,...
...fell into it, and ended up writhing in it.
So hopeless.
Kano, quit seeing through me!
It's times like these that
I realize how alone I am...
...that I don't have any friends
who I can share my problems with,
besides my family.
No one, besides Arima...
But nothing's going to get
done if I just mope around!
Let's's do this!
I shouldn't be blindly overconfident
about what I'm doing.
I have to think about this rationally.
Looking at my past failures...
...it looks like I should start
by radically changing my methodology.
It's possible that the cause
of the failures until now...
...is relying too much on
communication of intention...
...through first-degree encounters,
or through direct conversation.
If a direct attack doesn't work...
...then I have to try communicating
through indirect means.
...I wanted to tell you...
This isn't going to work!
This is way too embarrassing!
I don't have the talent for this kind of thing!
This is pointless.
I don't have any friends to tell him for me.
Gulp.
Sis...
...G...good luck.
I used to do everything so efficiently.
Why the sudden cowardice?
This has never happened before...
We both like each other.
And I want to tell him that.
Why isn't it working out?
Miyazawa, can we leave the rest to you?
We have to go to prep school.
Sure.
What the heck am I doing?
Darn! I'm just a breath away from enjoying a
rose-colored love-love high school life!
Where's everyone else?
They're all gone already.
All that's left is clean up.
And I hurried over too,
since practice ended early.
I'll help you.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, we're all alone...
Oh, unexpectedly lucky!
A surprise chance!
Oh, sorry. I'll pick it up.
That's okay.
What do I do?
He noticed. He saw me staring at him.
But I have to say it. I have to say it now.
Just like how I always do, and spit it out...
B...but how?
Won't he think,
Why now all of a sudden?
But you didn't answer me then...
It's been several days already...
Besides...
I don't know if he still likes me now.
Th...that's right.
He might have liked me then,
but that doesn't mean he
still likes me now, does it?
He might have gotten disillusioned.
I mean, just look at me.
I might have gotten carried
away and done something weird.
I mean, I AM weird!
I'm a showoff and a liar...
I've got personality flaws!
I'm not perfect like Arima...
He may have said he liked me,
but I don't know how he could!
I don't know a single
good thing about myself!
Miyazawa...? What's wrong?
Nothing...This is fine!
Just being friends is good enough!
Being a girlfriend isn't everything!
I'm okay with just being friends!
Because...I may lose my only friend...
Say, Miyazawa.
You haven't told me your feelings yet.
When could you give me an answer?
What?
I'm okay with just being friends!
He might have liked me then...
That doesn't mean he
still likes me now!
I'm fine with just being friends!
I don't want to lose him!
I must look really ugly right now.
I finally figured out
what's been motivating me.
I was running away.
I'm so unfair...
I ran away to keep myself from getting hurt.
I didn't have faith in Arima.
Now that I think about it,
I might not have even...
...been serious when l
tried to tell him I liked him.
Why am I like this?
I'm so ashamed...What should I do?
Now now now...don't cry like that.
Besides, it's impressive that
you at least figured it out!
By this point you've discovered the truth and
taken a hard look at reality..
The problem might as well be half solved!
Huh? I didn't get that at all.
Well, um...
Sis, you've never been hurt until now.
You've always been praised...
...and you were so good at
hiding your real feelings...
...that you became afraid
of showing your true self.
You might not feel any pain
if your fake self gets hurt.
But your real heart can feel the pain.
The person whom you're most afraid
of getting hurt by right now, is Arima.
I...I see.
But, I think you realize somewhere in your heart.
Being afraid of getting hurt
is because you care more about
yourself than about someone else.
I think being in love
might be the opposite.
Kano, you're amazing!
How do you know so much?
I get it all from manga and novels.
I've got to have courage.
If I don't overcome this hurdle,
I'm never going to make it to love.
Good morning.
...and so management should
communicate any schedule changes...
...on the day of the Athletics Festival directly
to the person in charge of each post.
If I try to say it with words,
I might screw up again.
If I'm going to get hurt...
...I want Arima to be the first one.
What'll happen next!
Sis finally became an
official couple with him!
But harsh reality brings
new trials and enemies!
When will happiness
finally come her way?!
Next time on KareKano:
His Ambition.