That feeling conveyed through holding hands:
If only we could be together for ever and ever.
But, in reality...
Excuse me, is Arima from class 1-A here?
Oh, Miyazawa. Hang on a sec.
I'm sorry, he was just here a moment ago,
but I hear he went over to Construction.
Just a sec.
I hear he got called away by
Transportation and Management.
You just missed him.
Hang on. I hear he went to
practice for the hundred meter race.
You just missed him.
Okay, I'll check.
Nope, he's not here. Maybe at the relay?
I have no idea where Arima is.
Oh, shoot!  I have to go to Records!
Oh, Miyazawa?
Arima was just here looking for you.
Miyazawa?
Practice for the Athletics Festival had begun.
And because of it...
...everyone on the staff was
totally swamped with work.
Even though we had just started
"going out" the other day...
...we spent all our time running
around between our multiple jobs.
Because we don't have
regular classes this week...
...we haven't seen each
other for two whole days.
We've only just started going out and
we'll soon be busy with the Athletics Festival.
I hope we can at
least eat lunch together.
R...really? Is it okay to eat lunch together?
O...of course!
I want to eat with you!
Oh, Arima's so cool!
We were supposed to be enjoying a
fabulous lunch together right now...
...and then continue on to
develop a refreshing love story
like in a cola commercial.
But then, this had to happen.
Both love and appetite are out the window...
I wish I could see Arima.
No, love means making time
for him even when I'm busy.
All right then! I'll do my best for him!
No! Those rows should be 4 by 10!
6 by 3 is for the VIP section!
Wrong! Totally wrong!
Sold out?!
Can we send the programs to the printers yet?
Arima? I just saw him a second ago...
Rats, he just left.
Nope, he hasn't been here.
Nope, he hasn't come over here.
I think I heard his voice a while ago.
He blew through here really fast.
Oh no! The curtain!
Senpai! Another misprint!
Pretend you didn't see it!
It's no use!
Not even Jolt is working any more!
I wanna go home...
What the hell is up with this busy-ness?
It's beyond any thought of eating lunch
with Arima at this point.
If this keeps up, I'll die.
Senpai, I handed in the list...
He's gone. Wonder where he went ?
Oh, well.
I wonder if Arima's feeling like this, too.
Good morning, Miyazawa.
You're really amazing.
You're letting your face slip.
I wanted you to know that I like you.
I fell asleep.
I had a memory dream.
That's right, until a short time
ago that's how things were.
I was still Miss Goody-Two-Shoes,
and I hated Arima.
Arima was always with me.
Yes, always with me.
I want to see him.
I want to be with him.
I didn't think about it at all then.
That I'd love Arima this much...
Days till the Athletics Festival
There you are!
Miyazawa!
Arima! Arima!
Oh, there you are!
Arima, we need you for a minute!
Don't bug me about every
fucking thing, GOD DAMMIT!
Sorry. Could I have just a small break?
Sure. Go right ahead.  No pressure.
I'm all burnt out.
Arima's having a pretty tough time, too.
This mess will be over by tomorrow.
Y...yeah !
Um, you...you been doing okay?
What?  Oh, just great! And you?
Except for that little outburst back there...
Oh, I'm fine, too.
Oh.  OK.
Uhm . . . yeah.
*Why're we being so self conscious?*
-
*I feel awkward when I haven't seen you in a while !*
Sorry !
I'm supposed to say something
smooth at a time like this...
It's ok! I can't think of anything either!
A...actually...! Not being able to see
you wasn't fun at all.
Yeah, it wasn't any fun for me, either.
The Athletics Festival sucks.
I don't want to have anything to do with the
School Festival or the field trip anymore.
We haven't been able to do
anything that couples do at all.
Nice weather.
What?
I have to get back. See ya.
More than anything else...
that freaked me out.
I hope we can always be together.
Alrighty then!
Let's do it!
The actual Athletics Festival was really great.
Arima looked really cool when he got serious.
And we finally got to eat lunch together.
Around this time of year the groups that people hang out
with get generally settled by class and club activities.
This is also the time when
the "instant couples..."
...that always form at the end of the
Athletics Festival are mass produced.
New couples began popping
up all over the place.
But this is a pair of guys...
Both of them are good-looking,
so they stand out.
Hey hey, what's that guy's name?
Oh, Asaba?
What?! Miyazawa, don't
you know who Asaba is?
He's Asaba Hideaki from class 1-F.
He and Arima are 10th
grade's two greatest heart throbs!
He's really popular, too!
He carried the trash cans for me.
He fetched a ball for me.
He really likes girls, doesn't he?
He's so cute !
Firefighters are really cool.
If he and Arima are friends,
I guess I should make friends with him, too.
I'm going out with Arima, after all...
Oh, hi...
Oh, you're Arima's girlfriend.
The guys all say you're cute...
...but it looks like you're not
such hot stuff in person.
Hey, Miyazawa. Whatcha up to?
Arima...
Hm?
Am I c...
You're very cute!
Damn you!  Asaba!
Even though I've
withdrawn from active duty...
...how dare you badmouth me,
the "Living Embodiment of Vanity."
You're dead meat !
Just you watch, Asaba!
You're about to feel my true wrath !
Ah...
You bitch! Aren't you some kind of
petite model student or something?!
Humph! It's your fault for making me mad.
Damn bitch!
Now I'm really pissed!
Stuff it!
I'll give you those words right back!
We met in the worst way possible...
...and we became arch-enemies
who fought at first sight of each other.
I wonder what's up with Miyazawa and Asaba.
They're at each other's throats.
But she's usually so sweet,
and Asaba's normally really nice to girls...
I hear you're not getting along with Asaba.
*Pout!* I don't want to
hear that name right now.
I might go into combat mode and
then there's no telling what I'd do.
What're you talking about ?
I swear ! Arima,
how come you're friends with him ?!
What's so good about him ?!
Nothing in particular.
When he talks to me, I talk back.
I don't see him as a friend or anything.
I can't figure him out.
Whatcha lookin' at ?
Movie listings. Wanna take a look ?
Sure ! The movies...
I haven't seen any lately.
Anything good playing ?
I was thinking this might be good...
Um...say, Miyazawa?
If you're not busy or anything,
do you want to go see it with me this Sunday ?
Yes ! Let's go, let's go,
Yay, a first date !
A lot's happened since I came to this school,
but I've finally made it this far!
There went my mood.
Hey, aren't WE in a good mood today.
None of your business.
You going on a date with Arima or something?
What if I am ?
Arima's got pretty weird tastes.
He could have had his pick
of better chicks if he wanted to.
What're you doing ?!
Let go !
Well, I bet Arima'll get
tired of this thing soon enough.
I guess there's nothing to worry about.
Shut up.
I'm taking Arima for myself.
W...what're you saying ?
Oh my god...
I heard there's a lot of them lately,
but you're really a...
I'M NOT !
I love women !
*My sweet,*
Cute little lambs...
I've always loved having them all around me.
I've come to hold a certain ambition.
I want more and more girls around me!
I'm going to create Asaba Mary-Land someday!
And that's where
Arima comes in.
He's the partner I've been seeking all these years.
His good looks will contribute greatly to my ambition.
All the little Marys will be
charmed by our brilliance...
...and many more Marys will come
flocking to me then ever before!
Hey, Mister High School Pervert!
What the hell're you trying
to get Arima mixed up in ?!
It doesn't matter !
I don't care as long as I'm happy!
So that's why you're dissing me,
because I'm "the girlfriend."
You finally figured it out.
Since you were a quiet little model student...
...I figured you'd run away and
cry with just a little prodding.
Seems I miscalculated.
But I guess I don't hafta go to all the
trouble of trying to break you two up.
With a girlfriend like you,
Arima'll be the one to run away.
You're really pissing me off!
What a jerk!
I never figured you to be such an ass!
How can you be so indifferent?
Aren't you ashamed?
Well, lemme ask you something then...
What about yourself?
I don't think you and me are all that different.
You played the model student and
deceived everyone else, didn't you?
If I'm a jerk, then so are you.
Why don't you stop and think about
whether you're all that well suited for Arima.
Just try to come up with
some kind of retort.
I'll even give up on Arima
if my argument is wrong.
Touche.
Miyazawa?
It's always been in the back
of my mind so I can't refute it.
What did you say to Miyazawa ?
I know you're trying to use me.
Not to be conceited,
but many people have tried to use me in the past.
But I won't permit you to hurt her.
You seem to be pretty soft on her.
Tell me, what's so good about her?
Don't you get it ?
She stays because she wants to.
I got here early. Gotta cheer up.
I can't stop being his girlfriend
just cause of what his friend said.
Here I am.
Which one are we seeing again ?
Can we still make it ?
No problem, no problem.
Sorry for making you wait !
He's not there. I've got the time and place right.
Tomorrow, at one o'clock...
I wonder if something happened.
That was great.
Thanks for the meal.
See you later.
I was really looking forward to this.
Yo. What're you doing here?
Oh, a date with Arima?
What? Looks like it's starting already.
You got stood up, didn't you.
Shut up!
I can't believe you're making
fun of me at a time like this!
*Hey, he's making that girl cry!*
So I've been stood up!
Who cares!  I chose to wait!
Just leave me alone!
Sorry, I didn't think you were actually stood up.
And I'm sorry about the stuff I said before.
Is this a trap ?
No, believe me...
I was wrong!
That's some change of heart.
Well, things happened...
I guess it means I don't
fight fights I can't win.
Hmmm?
What about the Mary-Land Project?
Oh, that's history, too.
It came to feel kind of empty...
And, I just realized...
...setting the deal with Arima aside,
I don't actually hate you.
I guess I had fun being with you.
I'm sorry! Just as I was leaving,
my mom collapsed from anemia,
and my father was out...
Apologize! You're a disgrace to
all men, making a girl wait!
Never make a girl wait, even if it
means abandoning your parents!
Die! Die as your apology to her!
It's okay!
Don't worry about it anymore!
So she says.
He did that on purpose.
He put on that performance so there wouldn't be
any hard feelings left over between us.
Still, that was dangerous.
I thought he was a jerk at first...
...but after that,
he became one of us.
Why the heck are you here?
I slept over at Arima's place last night.
You're even going
over to his house ?
Right before we went to sleep, Arima told
me all about what you did that day...
...and he was blushing all over the place.
He's so cute !
He's so innocent...
SHUT UP ! Shut up, shut up,
shut the hell up!
Anyway, I made a new friend.
What'll happen next !
Sis has made a new friend and
has finally obtained happiness.
She and Arima make up for
their failed first date !
And has the time of fate finally arrived ?!
Next time on KareKano:
"Your Voice That Changes Me."
It's so embarassing !