Hey Yukino.
We're about to leave...
Wh..What is it?
I love you.
Today we're going to visit grandpa.
But it's really only a short train ride away.
Actually...
Yukino's really taken after mom.
Sometimes it feels like
I'm seeing mom in her youth.
You knew each other
since you were kids, right?
Yeah...
We used to play together all the time...
Your father always played the
stupidest, most dangerous games.
He kept making me go along
and I had a terrible time.
Huh!
I'm feeling sick just thinking about it...
I was a bit mischievous as a kid.
Huh!
He hasn't grown up at all.
My feelings turned into love
when mom was in tenth grade.
Exactly the age Yukino is now!
So lately, when I look at Yukino...
I get this funny feeling inside...
The next stop is...
Hi Grandpa!
Oh, there you are!
I'm glad you came. Come in, come in.
Hey there. Why the hell
did you close the door?!
Shut the hell up! We don't need you!
Go home!
Mom and dad decided to get
married when they were young.
So dad got beat up by grandpa,
and they're still on bad terms to this day.
Hmph!
Oh!
Not again...
Why, the three of you have gotten even
more beautiful since I last saw you...
Just like the three dolls for the Girls' Festival.
HeeHee...
You've grown so well even under
the care of such a failure...
Such gallant effort!
It brings tears to my eyes.
The old geezer's as obnoxious as ever.
He keeps on grumbling just
because I took his daughter away.
You just don't know when to give up.
Let go of your daughter already!
You too, Dad.
You minimum-wage wimp...
Oh!
Don't bring my salary into this!!
Shut up, you brat!
You could never understand how it
feels to have married my precious
daughter off to a (bleep) like you!
I'm so tired of it. A man's worth isn't (bleep),
it's love! The love overflowing from his heart!
Love! Heh heh!
Love! Here! I'll make it into calligraphy!!
Goddammit!
Are you frustrated that you can't
do anything, my little Hero of Love?
I dare you to defeat this old geezer!
Dammit! I'll bring him down!
I'll make that old coot shut up once and for all!
Look look,
these are old pictures of me.
Wow, you look just like Sis.
Come to think of it, we really are alike.
Even I coudn't tell us apart.
See, isn't your mother cute?
And she's still cute now.
Yukino-chan really does
look exactly like Miyako.
Just make sure you don't get
taken advantage of by some jerk.
I do have someone I'm going out with.
What!?
This is him.
He seems quite pleasant.
What's with the different treatment?!
I'm going shopping for dinner, okay?
Then I'll go too.
That's right.
Go carry my daughter's things.
Just like her servant.
Would you knock it off!
Check!
This neighborhood sure has changed.
They've put up condos and everything.
It really takes you back, doesn't it?
Yeah, shall we hold hands?
Dusk...The expanse of the city lights...
The aroma of dinner,
wafting in from somewhere.
It feels lonely at this time of day.
Yet strangely, it feels pleasant.
At times like this, I remember my childhood.
My departed grandfather,
the trees I used to climb,
my friends...
I remember those distant days
I can no longer touch.
Oh, there he is!
Hey, Hiro-chan!
Yo!
Father, Age 6,
Full name: Miyazawa Hiroyuki.
Also known as the "Little Devil".
He did nothing but stupid things.
Breaking things,
fighting with elementary
schoolers and winning,
stealing a St. Bernard and riding on its back,
*He does not mean any harm*
sumo wrestling with cats, and so forth.
His nickname of "Little Devil" was
well known all over the neighborhood.
He was a being even adults feared,
saying "keep your valuables away from him."
His encounter with his wife, as well...
You girls wanna be let in our group?
Yeah yeah
Great, I got a perfect job for ya.
You get to be...HOSTAGES!
His encounter with his
wife was also rather stupid.
All right already, I'll untie you.
We gotta go pee!
What?!
Since then, he was genuinely
trying to entertain her.
He did things to the girls thinking he was amusing
them, but they didn't take it that way at all.
Ready?
Not yet!
Okay!
Oh, Hiro-chan!
Hey, did you find him?
No.
Where IS Hiro-chan?
Where'd he go?
Maybe he's over that way...
Go to find him.
Hiro-chan
Hey
Hiro-chan,
is it true you don't have a father and mother?
Yeah, that's right.
Oh!
Huh?
I don't have a mother either.
We match!
Match?
Later!
Bye!
Grandpa, I'm home!
How was your day, Hiroyuki?
I lived alone with grandpa back then.
With the small amount of
money my parents had left
and the savings grandpa had,
we were barely scraping by.
But I never felt lonely,
because it's always been the two of us ever
since I could remember, and I loved grandpa.
Now, it's about time for you to get off my lap.
My legs hurt.
Out there you're the boss of the gang,
but here at home you're such a
baby it's embarassing.
It's okay.
But at some point I stopped
clinging to grandpa's lap.
We didn't sleep together
in his futon anymore.
Because I started to think that
I can't demand the attention anymore.
Oh,
It's Hiro-chan!
He's wearing a school uniform!
He's in junior high!
Do I look cool?
You look funny!
Ha!
I'm not going to hang out with
knapsack pipsqueeks like you guys anymore.
But Hiro-chan, you're
certainly taking your time.
The girl next door leaves
much earlier every day for school.
Oh SHIT!
I left home at the same time
I always did for grade school!
Hiro-chan...
I..I..I am so damn late!
Later, you two.
Try to manage without me!
After that, he and his wife  went to different
schools and hardly ever saw each other.
Well, let's go.
Huh!
Hiro, how can you be so relaxed?
Today's the day the new students arrive!
We gotta go check out
if there are any cute girls!
We had bad luck of the draw
of girls in our class this year,
so the newbies are our last hope!
Bastards! You're so dead!!
Whatever. I'll pass.
What?
You're no fun.
You're not interested in girls at all.
You're pretty popular with the girls, too.
Aren't you gonna go out with anyone?
I don't get that stuff at all!
We will now begin the
22nd Matriculation Ceremony.
Wah!
Owww!
Uh-oh, that was a girl. Are you o...k...?
Hey, Hiro-chan!
Hey,
He was thinking of a girl as
cute for the first time.
Grandpa is thiner than before.
I'm home, grandpa.
Ah! Be careful!
Hiro-chan!
I should call you...
Senpai, good morning.
Huh?
Huh! You are so cute!
Oh no!
Oh, I like the sound of that.
Don't forget to respect your senpai.
Wet gwo oth mwe!
See ya.
Hey Miyako, is the guy you like...
Miyazawa-san in 9th grade?
What?
E..Err... I...
u..um....
Wah!
Oh, Hiro-chan.
I was surprised you got into Kawakita High.
It looked like you were always goofing off,
but I guess you had been doing your work.
Huh!
I'm a pretty smart guy.
U..um....
I wonder if you can get into my high school?
Piece of cake, with the grades I have!
Okay. Then, if there isn't
somewhere else you'd rather go,
come to my high school.
Okay. I promise!
U.um..
It's almost time for the freshmen to arrive.
What? You're not on the staff
for the Matriculation Ceremony.
You going to look for some hot little chick?
Or is there someone you like?
Are you waiting for her?
Morons.
Hi!
You're pretty early.
Hiro-chan, now that you're a senior,
you're not going to college?
Oh, we don't have any money.
What, with a big house like that?
It's only the outside that's big.
And it's just grandpa and me.
Besides,
I can finally earn money on my own.
The next stop is...
I'm home, grandpa.
How was your day, Hiroyuki?
At some point grandpa began
to clearly show his age.
There's something painful
about living with the elderly.
It was painful to watch grandpa just
getting nicer with the passing years.
At some point I really began
to want to grow up quickly.
I didn't want to be a kid
who was just protected,
but an adult who could
support grandpa by myself.
I want to let him relax
and take it easy.
I want him to eat good
food and have a good time.
I want to somehow return all the love
he's given me all these years.
When I become an adult, it'll all come true.
Maybe you should go to the hospital.
It isn't something to make that much fuss over.
I'll be fine, so you be off to school.
Okay.
Hiro-chan graduates soon!
How you've grown.
I thought you were a little kid
until just a while ago...
but now you're a fine young man.
How strange that
I never noticed until now.
Oh, Hiro-chan!
Grandpa, I fixed some food.
Grandpa?
Hiro-chan, everyone who came for
the funeral has left.
You must be worn out.
Do you want anything to eat?
No, I'm fine. Thanks for all your help.
I'll be okay by myself,
so you go on home.
But Hiro-chan, you
haven't eaten anything at all!
That isn't good for you.
Thanks,
but I'll really be okay.
Go on home.
What are you doing? What are you...
Because...! I wanted to be with you.
You idiot...
Why didn't I make it in time?
I couldn't do anything even
though I loved him so much.
I'd always been afraid that
I'd have to say goodbye
to grandpa some day.
So I wanted to have done something
to show for myself first.
It hurts...
I couldn't show anything.
I wanted to do for him in my mind...
There are only the things
And now I can't do a goddamn thing!
But Hiro-chan,
your grandfather may not
have seen things that way.
I'm sure his love for
you was bigger than that.
So much that he was fully satisfied just
by your being born into this world.
I'm sure that love goes that deep.
I wonder if I couldn't take his place.
After that...
...we waited for Miyako to
graduate from high school...
...and were then married right away.
Starting the year after,
we were blessed with lovely
girls for three years in a row.
Our life was tough, but happy.
Now I understand grandpa's feelings.
Just being born is enough.
That alone makes me happy.
Grandpa's love now flows within me,
and will be passed on to my children.
Because love is something that goes around.
They built a nice library
where your house used to be.
I had no choice.
I couldn't keep up that house by myself.
Dinnertime!
Dad, you're getting old,
so don't be stubborn and come live with us.
Yeah.
No way. It's all over when you have to get
taken care of by your kids.
I want to have my freedom.
Come on.
I'll change your diapers any time!
Shut up, you punk!
Dad!
I swear...
how long are you going
to keep being stubborn like this?
Enough already.
What do you take me for?
Dad, you spewed rice.
Oh, leave me alone.
Because love is something that goes around.
What'll happen next!
The summer vacation is both long and short.
Sis waits and waits but her
boyfriend hasn't come back yet.
She spends her days chatting
with friends and studying,
but the emptiness in her
heart does not get fullfilled.
And then, the long-awaited
Arima Souichirou returns!
But, however!
Next time on KareKano,
"Thoughts of Him"