What's happened so far!
I've been thinking, and well, I thought
maybe I could do the play after all...
I'm not doing it.
What?!
Come on baby!
Arima-kun!
It's not worth seeing.
The Dean of the class!
Power. He has power!
We're going to put on a play.
What?!
Sis is going to be in a play?!
One of my friends is a writer.
Ah?
The Week of September is almost over.
Each group has decided on what they're doing.
*Next, about printing the programs, there
will be more meetings and discussions.*
Next week...next week is going to be hell.
Everyone's going to begin preparations,
so things are going to get
nightmarishly busy again.
Now, onto the next topic.
That meeting dragged on.
Huh? They're not here.
Hey! Yukinon!
We saw you running down the hall
We're in a fix, All the classes have started
to fill up with plywood and cardboard boxes.
So there isn't a classroom we could use.
Not even the library or the science room?
No good. We went everywhere,
but they've all been taken over already.
I told you so.
It's unreasonable to start a play
What should we do?
Hey, listen when I'm talking to you!
Huh? Kawashima-sensei's beckoning to us.
What, no vacant classrooms?
Well then, use the student guidance room.
We won't be needing it for a while anyway.
Power!
Did you write down what preparations we need
to do between now and the performance?
Yeah, how's this?
Let's see?
Reading through the script,
rehearsal, dress rehearsal,
deciding on the look for the costumes,
the scene, the set and props...
Oh, we'd have to actually measure the
size of the stage in the gym before
we make the set or we'll screw up.
We'll check the lighting and sound setup then.
Deciding on the details for BGM,
sound effects, and lighting...
We can think about these while we're
reading our lines, so they can wait.
It's too bad that tomorrow's a Sunday.
Let's decide on the outline today and go
shopping for things tomorrow afternoon. Okay?
O-okay!
Yukinon really does the work
of ten people by herself.
Let's finalize the schedule first.
How much time we're going
to spend on what.
We can't afford to waste any time.
I keep telling you,
what can we do in only one we-
Have you come up with the set designs?
Yes we have!
And we can't get anywhere without
the actors knowing their lines,
so be sure to have everything
perfectly memorized by Monday.
WHAT?!
I could do it.
What, you can't even do that?
Yes I can!
So this is the stage layout?
We came up with it.
Neat! So this is what it's like.
Wow, I can just see it happening.
Oh yeah, what are we going to
do about the giant monitor?
It's key to the story...
...but it would be tough to do.
That's taken care of.
My brother works for an AV company,
and when I showed...
...him the story, he got interested
and said he'd do it.
Huh? What's wrong?
You bastard!
Ow!
What the hell do you think you're
doing?! This is your project!
Are you trying to ruin it yourself?!
You want all of us to spend the day of
the Culture Fair suspended at home?!
I told you to quit!
Huh?  When did I?
How's it going? I'd called you over because
I was going to offer some sweets.
We're finally done... It's dark already.
Okay, tomorrow at 12:30 in front of
the station.
Good work, everyone.
What's the matter, Yukinon?
The lights are still on in the stadium.
Arima might be there so...
...I'm going to take a look.
...Love-monkey.
How about you?
I'll pass.
Souichirou-kun gets really scary
if I'm around in a situation like that.
You go ahead.
Shall we go get something to
eat at a family restaurant?
Let's go!
Okay, I'll go for a little bit.
Bye Yukinon!
See you later.
Bye!
Wait, I'm coming too!
I've never seen Arima doing kendo.
What a waste.
This is exciting!
Waiting for my boyfriend, winner of the
Interhigh, to finish practice...
It's so luxurious!
That's all for today!
Oops, he saw me.
Thanks you for your help!
What's up?
The discussion for the play ran late,
so I was watching.
This was the first time
I've watched you do kendo!
You were so cool!
It was really exciting.
I should have done this sooner.
Can I come again?
Peeyew!
Ohmigod Arima,
you reek of sweaty armor!
I mean, just smelling like
sweat is one thing, but!
Get away! Don't touch me!
I can't believe you!
What is that rotten stench?!
How can you stand to wear that?!
Stay away!
There's no way I'd ever do kendo!
Ow! Who would poke their girlfriend?
...with their bamboo sword?
I came by bike today.
Then I'll ride too.
Go for it, Miyazawa!
Lift off!
Are you dragging your feet?
There's a strange sound...
No I'm not.
When?
When did you start kendo?
When I was seven.
You must really like it.
Yeah. It feels good to be moving around,
and I like the tensed atmosphere
of the stadium.
Miyazawa.
Practice is over!
Phew, am I beat!
Oh, I'm sorry, Tonami-san.
I didn't notice you there.
No, it's my fault for
standing behind you,
...Sakura-san.
I'm scared. Let's go home.
Good job guys...
Phew, I'm beat.
Hey. You still practicing?
You're really zealous.
You again.
When you get to be a starter
as a first year,
...you can't be disgraceful.
I'm busy, so leave.
I have nothing better to do, so I'll watch.
Just leave! I said, get lost!
Hey, why do you keep harassing me?
You just transferred here.
Why do you keep picking
fights with me?
Because I hate you.
I hate people like you.
No particular reason.
Hatred is just another facet of love.
Hatred is an obsession about another person.
It's the closest emotion to love.
Oh god, could it be?!
Wh-what are you talking about?
And this is a deserted gym!
Now, we have the perfect situation
for something to go wrong!
Hey, wait a sec!
Sorry, but I have no such
intentions, so go somewhere else!
I think you've got things mixed up.
I told you I hate you.
It looks like l,m doing weird things,
but that's not my intention.
You couldn't beat me in strength.
There isn't anything you can beat me in.
You moron!
You fight with your head!
You're a hundred years too young to beat me!
Dammit!
That wasn't enough.
I can't hurt her even a little
bit with something like that.
It's always been like that.
So aloof, and difficult to pin down.
Like a kite without a string,
she can't be restricted.
Even what happened now probably...
...just made her a little mad and
she'll soon forget about it.
She probably never thought about
me in the past two years.
How much those words hurt me.
Oh, the teacher asked me to look
after you back in elementary school.
With me around,
you wouldn't get beat up as much.
And it's rather my policy
not to beat people up.
Or what I went through in those two years.
Well, good luck at your new school.
That's what I hate about her.
My humiliation still can't hurt
you even a little bit.
I'll make you feel it someday, for sure!
The same pain that I felt!
Am I the last one here?
Asaba-kun's not here yet.
Tsubasa-chan, good morning!
You're as cute as ever!
Hey, she didn't scratch today.
She must be in a good mood.
What do we do next?
Well, shall we go to a cafe first?
I want to go to the place where
they have fresh-baked bread.
They serve whole wheat bread
stuffed full of roast beef!
Sounds great!
Hey girls!
Wow, you guys are so cute!
You never find a group of girls
all looking this good.
Right?
Is that little girl your sister?
Are you going somewhere?
How about if we join you?
Shut up.
We have no need of you, so get lost.
We got yelled at by a babe!
You?
Okay, okay, excuse me.
All these girls here are with me.
A freaky dude!
Well, that was a close shave, kitten.
What're you doing dressed up
like a Dadaist for?
Or rather, do we have to walk around
all day with a guy dressed like this?
So, we can borrow the sound effects
CD from the student PA system.
And I called the president of
the wind ensemble last night.
You did all that after you went home?
What a day for you.
Nobody has any time to lose.
Oh, and about the show time...
Put some normal clothes on!
It's a waste!
About this?
Or this!
That's nice! Try this next.
We've digressed already.
Are you sure about these people?
Hey hey hey Tsubasa-chan!
Try this on! Hurry
Two acts?
Yeah. The script's pretty long.
When we actually do it,
I think it will take about two hours.
But a two-hour slot is hard to get.
So I was thinking we could break
it into two parts.
I wouldn't know without asking you,
so what do you think?
Hmm... that's a tough choice...
I'd like to do it all at once,
but it'll be tough physically too...
The problem is whether
the audience would come.
What kind of timeslots would it be?
We're a last-minute entry so
all the good times are out.
Nobody would come at like 9:30 A.M or 4 P.M.
So I thought we could use
the lunch hour.
Right?
And here's the latest!
The wind ensemble won't be using
the gym this year.
Its president is in my section
on the Student Council,
...and since being a
club president is tough,
I often help him out with
work, or trade assignments.
So when I asked him, he was really
eager to give us their slot.
You're just like a politician!
The world works through connections!
Where's the wind ensemble
going to play?
The roof.
They're going to play
the Titanic theme at sunset.
Sweet! Let's go!
My Heart Will Go On, huh?
What a great song.
Celine Dion is the modern songstress.
I can sing that.
I learned it with Kazuma.
Oh my gosh! I want to hear it!
I want to hear it!
Ooh, then shall we treat ourselves
to karaoke after this?
Great idea!
I'll sing Romance by Penicillin!
That's too you!
I'll do Shiina Ringo-san's
Queen of Entertainment!
Good choice!
We'll do Citron .
Not Kiroro?
Hey!
We're short on time, aren't we?
Are you sure you can be playing around?!
...and why do I have to be
the one who's worried?!
It's no big deal.
I'm glad you're finally into it.
As it turned out, Maho-san was?
forced to sing Nakayama Miho's song!
I want to go home...
I'm home!
I'm exhausted.
Sis...
You have to memorize your
lines by tomorrow, right
We're going to do a script reading.
Come on...
I'm pooped, but it feels good.
This is totally different from being
worn out from studying.
I wonder if this is how Arima
feels after practice?
The characters are swamped
by the steadily
advancing preparations for
the Culture Fair.
But unrelated to that,
Miyazawa Yukino and Arima Souichirou,
who worry about what others think,
were reflecting about themselves.
The two of them then?!
A Different Story from Before