Miyazawa-san?
She's really scary when you
make her mad.
She's a corrupted representative!
Like, all she cares about is herself.
But, she was really nice in the beginning.
Yeah, she seemed really helpful.
She was?
Yeah, don't you remember
she looked over your homework?
Oh yeah.
It feels like that was so long ago.
Was it the day before yesterday?
I saw her dancing wildly in the hall
saying that she beat Arima...
...on the English pop quiz.
I got the feeling that
that was who she really was.
She can do ten times the
work of one, to be sure.
I remember well that nobody could...
...defy her when she ordered them around...
...while drinking Gator*bleep* with
this deathly look on her face.
What? Oh, she was the epitome
of a model student at first.
But you can't judge people
by appearances.
She's tougher than she looks.
Shall I say, she's a student who is like dried
squid;
She becomes more interesting the more you chew.
Our sister is an airhead.
Yep, an airhead.
It's awful!
Arima, listen!
Hm? What's up?
Today, I was walking down the hall,
and this guy, as he passed me...
...mumbles "You know, Miyazawa-san's
really more macho than she looks."
What kind of butch word is that?!
How dare he use it to describe a girl!
C-could it have just been your imagination?
No, he definitely said so! I heard him.
I, who used to be called beautiful,
with the grace of a prize-winning carp!
What in the world are you?
WHOA! GROSS! Snot everywhere!
Oh the good old days when I could
leave all annoying things to the guys
and just take the juicy bits.
The feel for ecstasy I've been used to
for so long, no that I was born with...
...can't be changed so easily.
You're still complaining?
You stopped being pretentious, remember?
You just think it's none of your concern.
My ostentatious life, at the height
of its splendor is finally about to
become a thing of the past!
There's no way I can let it go so easily!
You're so naive, Arima-kun.
Just accept that this is
how she'll always be.
When it's coming from you it
pisses me off for some reason!
That's empty, you know.
It just means that, after all,
your love falls far short of
our friendship.
You're the one who's naive, Asapin.
Now don't get jealous...
What did he switch?
There isn't a single millimeter for
you to come between us anymore!!
M-Miyazawa?!
Wh-what's that? What do you mean?
Wh-what do I mean? Well...
What's that reaction...?
N-no way!
What's that mean?
You mean you guys actually?!
J-just shut up.
You shouldn't ask about such things.
How could you?!
Both of you didn't even tell me!
What are you talking about?!
Wait, Hideaki!
Did you see that?
Arima-kun made Asaba-kun cry!
Th-that's not it!
He's misunderstanding things!
Just leave him be.
I told him to leave him be,
but he ran after him anyway.
Don't say I didn't warn him.
Arima's become rather comfortable
in his comedy routine with Asapin lately.
That's just not a good thing.
Could it be that we're the ones
who are playing into his hands?
Really?
Can we?
Can we really still be friends like before?
I'm telling you, it's nothing!
Yeah, don't worry, we'll be like before.
Really?
Um, I'm making a poetry collection,
and I want you to pick the ones you think are good.
I'll print those.
Well, I still have committee work to do now...
What the hell am I doing?
I thought I knew what I was getting into,
but changing yourself into
what you want is pretty hard.
If Arima and I hadn't become
boyfriend and girlfriend, I
wonder what would have happened to me?
If Arima hadn't appeared before me?
Text:A Simulation
Well, knowing me, there's no mistake...
...I would have shrewdly enjoyed the
vain lifestyle just like before...
Text:The Year 20XX
You just don't understand.
The most important thing about
guys is their income!
Their looks come second!
Tsuki & Kano:You're tough, Sis.
Miyazawa:The world is about money, really!
Tsuki & Kano:She doesn't need a husband.
Money money!
I might have gotten myself into trouble.
Miyazawa! Miyazawa!
That's odd, where did she go?
Oh, Arima!
Do you know where Miyazawa is?
Maybe she went home?
If it's Asaba-kun I saw
him walk by crying just now.
We couldn't bring ourselves to
approach him.
O-oh, you can just let him be.
She promised to meet me to
talk about the Culture Fair today...
Tsubasa, you know anything?
She's useless.
Oh I know, Yukinon was drinking juice at
the vending machine corner with Tonami.
Oh yeah... Yeah,
Why don't you ask Tonami-kun?
Thanks
What am I doing?
Miyazawa?!
The only change that happened
is that I stopped being vain,
but my greediness hasn't changed one bit.
Can this count as having changed?
I feel gypped.
Oh, that's enough.
Worrying like this is just
going to get me more depressed.
What about Arima?
I wonder if he thinks about this kind
of thing all the time?
My real parents vanished,
leaving me, their son, behind.
I'm sure they were the shame
of the family.
When my current parents came to get me,
I was told to my face:
That a kid born from such parents
would never amount to anything.
So?
I had to become a perfectly flawless person.
I absolutely had to.
At that time, something occured to me.
Could it be that what I had believed
was me until then was merely a fake
I had created purely by effort?
Was there another real me
somewhere inside?
What if I'm a terrible person?!
What causes Arima to have dark feelings?
What makes him suffer so much?
About the truth
I still don't know anything about
what it really is.
Th-that's... Arima?!
No! No! I don't want to look
Why? Isn't that you? He's crying.
Are you just going to leave him like that?
If you're scared,
I'll go with you.
This is something you have to
solve yourself, Arima.
I don't really know, but I have
a feeling that it is.
All I can do is support you.
Come this way.
Come on. Come on! What are you doing?!
You cannot do that
Arima!
Arima, that's not it.
That's not what Arima wanted.
I felt that everybody, deep down, rejects me
and that they all have malice toward me.
My current parents were the first
ones to alleviate that feeling.
Even so, the thought of having people dislike
me was terrifying just to imagine.
So I behaved so that nobody would dislike me,
that nobody would look down upon me.
Before I knew it, I was called
a model student,
I'm scared but really I was only
the product of my fear of getting hurt
and my refusal to get
involved too deeply with others
Arima.
Sometime I think
I don't think analyzing yourself
is very reliable.
R-really?
I'm sure the reason you ended up the
way you are now isn't something that
can be put into words so easily.
You may not realize it,
but you've been influenced by?
...many more things than you think.
and you became the way you are.
And besides, what you think changes a
lot depending on your mood at the time.
And I like the serious Arima too.
Even when I'm being difficult,
she humors me so easily.
Against Miyazawa, I'm like a child.
Without her, I'm...
I still have to change.
Miyazawa.
I used to have almost absolute confidence,
and never thought about anyone but myself
And yet this change feels so good now.
Oh, Arima! Where's Arima?
Arima...
Hey! Arima! Arima! Hey!
I wonder if we met to change each other.
If so, by changing,
maybe we're going to lose the
necessity to stay as distinct beings.
Well, that's fine too, I think.
We'd seem similar, but we'd be
different in little ways.
Through repeated encounters and farewells
we'll probably continue to change from now on.
Oh, is that really it, Sis?
Isn't that wrapping things up too well?
That's right!
This isn't the time to be dwelling by myself.
We haven't grasped anything definite yet!
And let's promise,
that even if that does happens some day,
that we'll never forget
the things we felt together.
A review of what's happened!
Pardon our abruptness,
but our sister, the masked model
student Miyazawa Yukino...
...in class 1-A of Kanazawa
Prefectural Hokuei High...
...is the ultimate queen of vanity.
She lived only to show off in front of others,
no matter what.
She successfully played the perfect
model student in public...
...seemingly elegant and graceful, blessed
with both beauty and intelligence.
She's so narcissistic!
But because of a certain error on her part,
that mask was finally stripped away!
Oh she's so careless!
The one lucky, or perhaps unlucky,
enough to first find out her true identity
was an unusual person named...
Arima Souichirou! (Sis's classmate)
He was also a perfect model student.
He gets excellent grades,
excels at every sport, and is generally?
...a sociable guy who is friendly to everyone
and who would never make any enemies.
In addition, he was totally a Gucci?
...thoroughbred whose family was a pedigree?
...that went all the way back to the Edo period.
However, he was quite a wily dude himself.
He was rather an evil schemer..
...who made Sis help him with
his own work...
...by taking adantage of the fact that
he had a hold of her weakness!
Sis is in big trouble!
But she ended up feeling love
for the first time,
towards her enemy of all people,
and got herself into a panic.
Sis fell into a total mess of a situation!
After being in a state of ineffectiveness...
...due to her rampant imagination...
...she finally snaps, but!
After a lot of fuss, they make up.
They come to hold a secret as
model students...
...with dual personalities
though how they became that way differed.
And later, after passing through phases as...
...partners in the Student
Assembly, good friends...
...and more than friends but not
quite going steady...
...they finally become a couple.
And, being affected by each other's lives...
...they decide to live for
their own real happiness!
We're so happy for you Sis!
Yeah but, the world isn't that simple.
That's right. Society is a cruel thing!
First, the menace of the Athletic Festival...
...which forced them to be super
busy and not see each other...
...as though to challenge their relationship.
Following which was the appearance
of the delinquent...
...perverted hunk Asaba Hideaki...
...who plotted to demoralize Sis and
interfered with her activities in order...
...to possibly break them up...
...and use Arima-kun once he
became single again...
...so he could carry out his ambition...
the Asaba Mary-Land Project!
Their long-awaited first date ends in failure...
...and they react to it by...
...ignoring their studies...
...and filling their days with...
...rendezvous and misunderstandings!
And so forth...
...Sis faced up to this series of challenges...
...and enriched her life experience!
Sis savors her transient happiness...
And after school when nobody was around
amidst the rolling thunder, they finally
Ohmigod! What's going on?! Eeeek!
God that was embarrassing.
In July of the same year...
...the final exams ended without incident.
The result was that Miyazawa Yukino, who
had been faithfully yielding to her desires...
...dropped in rank precipitously.
But Arima Souichirou, who
had done the same...
...only went down in rank a little bit.
She suspects he had played foul...
...and a rift formed between them already.
Meanwhile, the school...
...taking the matter seriously...
...immediately calls them up and
tries to talk them out of it.
But she surprisingly opposes them
and firmly refuses.
The situation worsens.
However, the matter was easily...
...put to rest with her...
...father's words.
On a roll...
...she goes to the unchaperoned Arima house...
...and lets herself experience her second kiss.
Arima feels gratitude for the importance...
...of her existence for him.
Meanwhile, Miyaza Yukino was about...
...face the greatest crisis of her life.
She was ignored by all the girls in the class
led by Isawa Maho who had independently
analyzed her and figured out her true nature.
There was also an attack by Shibahime
Tsubasa, who had secretly liked Arima.
Although it was something that
she had brought upon herself,
it was a sudden outbreak of multiple problems;
yet Miyazawa Yukino brushes aside
Arima's helping hand
and dauntlessly confronts them by herself.
After a brief deadlock, she snaps due to
Shibahime Tsubasa's harassment,
and loses control of herself.
She goes berserk and plunges
the school into the depths of fear.
This state of absolute terror corners Shibahime
Tsubasa both physically and mentally,
and the situation takes care of itself.
Miyazawa Yukino suddenly acquires
friends for the first time.
A review of what's happened!
...Eh. This is a real drag.
Aya, you're into humanities, so
you just do whatever with it.
I don't want to do it either, it's annoying.
Rika, you do it.
Who, me?
I wouldn't be able to wrap it up well.
Er, um... Maho-san, you do it!
What? I don't want to just be
an exposition character either.
Oh, wouldn't she be perfect for this?
She hasn't spoken much lately anyway.
She took Arima.
...Thank you for the perfect explanation.
Say, can I speak some more?
Go ahead.
When will Shibahime Tsubasa ever be
returned from a beast to a human?
Will that day ever come?
Or is my role here over already?
What happened to the story where
I introduce Kazuma to my friends?!
Well this is the only time left for me.
All joking aside...
...this could seriously be the last time...
...I'm going to speak normally.
Sorry I guess I'm just complaining.
We sympathize wholeheartedly.
Ok, back to the topic at hand...
Well, lots of things happened over
summer vacation.
We did the usual thing and went
to a karaoke bar,
...did window shopping, and hung
out at a cafe.
And we went to the beach.
What else did we do?
I think Yukinon went on a family trip.
Lucky. I want to go to a hot spring.
What an old-geezer...
...thing to say, Tsubaki.
You're still young.
So what? Those who belittle...
...hot springs will cry over it one day.
When you're over 25 you get to...
...understand what a good thing it is.
Really...
Come to think of it, doesn't Arima-kun
seem rather weird lately?
Isn't he just being too self-conscious?
Seriously. You can't understand
everything about other people.
It's questionable how much you
even know about your own self.
But they seem different these days.
I wonder if they went all
the way over the summer.
But they seem so unlikely
to do that kind of thing.
You never know with men and women.
It's all about the mood and the timing.
Well, I wouldn't care.
I'd do it if I wanted to.
It's not something you can criticize others for.
Yeah, yeah.
What is with these people...
So what are we going to do about wrapping it up?
Aren't we almost out of time now?
We should just say whatever.
The long summer vacation is over and
second semester has finally started.
How's that?
Hmm, rather half-hearted...
Ok, then the mysterious transfer student,
Tonami Takefumi, appeared.
And we're still getting ready for the play...
...we're going to do at the Culture Fair.
We just finally started to
get rolling on that too.
It feels like it's going
to be a long 2 weeks.
My screen time was too short!
My screen time! My screen time!
At least like a human! My screen time!
Ok, ok.
Well, this would do just fine.
What'll happen next!
Sis is super busy with?
...all these things happening at once!
But unrelated to that,
I was being followed by an
unidentified shadow!
Is this what they call a stalker?!
Or is it the beginning of spring?!
what to know? See the next act!