What's happened so far!
Arima Souichirou. Excellent grades,
good in all sports...
Generally a sociable guy who
would never make any enemies.
Furthermore, he's a thoroughbred
from a super famous family of doctors...
...dating back to the Edo Period.
Miyazawa Yukino. Elegant and graceful,
blessed with both beauty and intelligence.
Though an ordinary commoner
raised in a middle class family...
...she's just as full of grace
and intellect as Arima.
The two, who captivate the multitudes
around them with their charm,
met in high school.
However,
Arima found out the other day that
his opposite number was a mongrel!
Sis is a moron.
Even worse, he had
confessed his love to her!
But Sis, without a second thought,
flatly turned him down.
And right afterwards, this happened.
Sis is really a moron.
She's a carp on a cutting board!
Having dug her own grave,
Sis is now between a rock and a hard place!
Now, what will you do, Miyazawa Yukino?!
And what about you, Arima Souichirou?!
You can tell that something is
"excellent" with just one glance.
Arima found out everything.
I'll regret it forever.
He's a sharp guy.
I'm sure he figured out
everything just by looking at me.
Everything about me at school is a bluff...
Living in vanity. The very
embodiment of vanity!
That was me -
Miyazawa Yukino's true form.
So, what're you going to do, Arima?
Tell everyone and make a
Laughingstock out of me?
Go around holding me in contempt?
Or are you going to sympathize
with me about how foolish I am...
...like the model student that you are?
Why did Arima, of all
people, have to find out?!
He's the one person I wouldn't want
to laugh at me, or scorn me...or feel
sorry for me!
Hey, guys, Miyazawa was
just looking this way.
Could it be me?
Moron, who'd go out with you?
Yeah, really.
But she's really something.
All slim and feminine and stuff...
Maybe I should go and
confess my love to her...
It's no use.
You'd just end up getting hurt.
I waited for judgement
day with much anxiety.
All those girls who are
smiling at me now...
When they find out tomorrow
that they've been deceived...
...they'll probably look at me
with expressions of disgust!
Uuuuuuu....
By the way, about last lecture...
The teacher's so mean...
And he just talks forever...
I wish he'd give us a break...
Yeah, really.
But, even after several days,
Arima hasn't said anything to me.
It doesn't look like he told anyone...
Even after days and days
passed nothing at all happened.
**Several days several days several...**
Finally, a week later...
Could it be that he just let it slide?
That's it!
It's because he's been brought up
well and has good character!
He wouldn't go around talking behind people's
backs... and doing petty things like that!
That's it!  I'm so LUCKY!
ALRIGHT!
So, I was relieved.
Gotta go to the library.
But at that time,
who would have guessed...
...that a fearsome plot awaited me?
You're letting your face slip.
Am I some kind of demon?
Surprised you, huh?
I know what you're thinking.
I saw you at a bad time, didn't I?
You had even me completely fooled.
I never would have thought that the innocent
Little Miyazawa was this kind of person.
I bet everyone will be so surprised!
I bet it'll be a big sensation.
I wonder how they'll react...
Maybe they'll laugh. Maybe they'll be disgusted.
What is it, Miyazawa?
Don't... don't tell anyone.
Don't tell anyone, p-l-e-a-s-e.
Don't tell anyone, please.
Okay, fine.
Lucky!
Could you do those for me by tonight?
Well, I've got practice to go to, so...
What is this?
Why do I have to do it?
And who was that just now?!
Who the heck was that freaky dude?!
Well then, Arima, translate what we just read.
Yes. ma'am.
He was gasping for breath...
...and it seemed as
if he wanted to speak.
But as he looked greatly pained and sorely tired.
The Emperor...
Now then, Miyazawa, interpret it.
Yes, ma'am.
The words "men" and "women" are used here
to symbolize and express the rise of emotions.
In those times death inside the
court was considered unclean...
...and only the Emperor
was permitted to die there.
The attendant court ladies . . .
Yes, that's correct.
Extremely impressive job from you two.
They echo words of admiration so easily.
None of these people know...
...that I'm currently...
...Arima's lackey!
After that, the
curtain rose on my tragedy.
Evening! Ah, you're really going at it.
Good work. Wow, perfect!
And you're done already.
Incredible. That's my Miyazawa.
Now see here! What do you think you're doing?!
Why're you making me do this stuff?!
Because,
I'm taking advantage of your weakness...
...and turning it to my own ends.
I...I...I know that already!
Don't say it so bluntly!
That's called blackmail.
Haven't you any shame?
Yeah.
But I can't help it.
I'm way busy,
and it's a major help having you sub for me.
You little...
So, you'll be useful to me.
Well, I won't force you.
If you don't want to do it, just say so.
If you've got the guts.
You scheming little bastard!
I never expected this. Who would've
thought he had another side of him too?
I've been my own master for these 15 years...
...showing off, with my head held high.
I've never been so humiliated in my entire life!
What the hell is with him? Dammit!
But, this sounds like a good deal for you.
Riiight?
He's taking the pains to show
you the harsh realities of life.
Not only the emptiness of vanity,
but also that greatness, is all relative.
Not!
He's not that nice of a guy!
Dammit!
But, I have no way
to escape from his trap.
There was nothing I could
do but curse my own fate.
But soon afterwards...
Now I'm tied up with Arima's work all day long!
Hey, did you know Yoshida,
the math teacher, has false teeth?
No way!
That was really...
Hey, pass, pass! Alright...
How could you make a girl do all this work...?
Pretending to cry won't work.
You're actually callous
and tough, aren't you?
None of your business!
What work is it this time?
Making a schedule for the Class Trip Committee.
Gack! Are you doing that too?
Since I was being made to help,
it was certainly clear that Arima was super-busy.
The Student Council...the Service Club
the Class Trip Committee...
on executive committees
for various events...
a part of the main staff for all of them.
And on top of that,
he does club sports...studies...
...and even talks with classmates
who come to him for help.
Of course, I weasel out of most of it.
You're gonna die if this keeps up.
It seems I stand out or something, I guess.
That must be tough.
I would have thought that your looks and brains
would have brought you a better life...
Oh, I see.  I guess so.
Well, since you're here, it's all good.
I'm your dog?
Woof woof.
Arima,
you were Student Council
President in junior high, right?
Yeah. And you?
I did that too.
Well, it must've been tough then.
Uh-uh, not really.
What? How come?
What should I do?
I can't do all this...
...I said, and got a guy to do it for me!
What a fraud!
So that's the kind of person you really were.
Hey! You're doing exactly the same thing!
What? That's not true.
I act normally all the time.
This is all due to your
influence right now.
Oh, so it's my fault? How dare you!
It's true, you know.
Wow, it's pitch-black outside.
Miyazawa, you hungry?
Hungry? Sure.
Then I can treat you to
something...once in a while.
Arima is somehow perfect.
I want steak!
You blockhead.
Where did that come from, I wonder?
Until yesterday, there was nothing at all.
Until recently...
Hey, check it out!
Those two...
It shouldn't have been anywhere at all...
Like, that rumor's gotta be true!
No doubt about it!
You awake?
Practice just finished, so I came over.
You shouldn't fall asleep like that.
Suddenly, he seemed special to me.
Arima seemed special to me.
What was with Arima just then?
What is this sensation?
This feeling I can't place?
My head feels all foggy and I can't sit still.
This is the first time I've felt this way.
Wait! Could it be...
This isn't that
Love" thing I've often heard of, is it?
Like "crush..." and "romance," and
falling for someone?!
No way, not me...!
Ridiculous. I don't believe it.
I guess I just don't understand myseIf.
And yet...What a pain.
Let's's eat!
Hey, you sure come home
Late these days, Sis.
What?
Oh, I've got stuff to do
for the class committee.
That's all?
Well, yeah.
See, you had it all wrong.
Well, I don't know...
Now what?
What, what?
What are you talking about?
But it's really weird!
You started coming home late all of a sudden.
You used to talk a lot about
school, but not these days.
And most importantly,
you stopped wearing your sweats.
Sis, you got a boyfriend, don't you?
Wh....wh...wh...
WHAAAAT??!!
A g...g...guy, is it?
Your father, who loves you more
than anyone in the world...
Of course, I love Tsukino and Kano
more than anyone in the world, too, but...
You pick another man over your father?!
What the heck are you babbling about?
Hey, she's nervous.
I knew it.
I'd love to see a picture.
I wonder if he's good looking?
Probably some hunk.
Even more than me?
No doubt.
Yuki's pretty choosy about looks...
I wonder who she got that from?
I'm telling you,
it's just work!
Yukino!
I swear, they're so inconsiderate...
If I had felt this way after meeting
normally, there wouldn't be any trouble.
That's right. I'm troubled.
Because Arima...
Hey, hey, Miyazawa.
Are you and Arima...going out?
You two are together a lot recently...
But I don't mean anything funny...
You two look really cute together,
and even if we're a bit jealous...
...you seem to be the
most suited for him.
And I was just wondering
what was really going on.
It's true that he said he liked me, but...
Hey, this one brave girl went up to
Arima and asked him the same thing.
And I hear that Arima just
Laughed and didn't answer.
I thought so. I've been thinking...
Where did that confession go inside Arima?
He hasn't brought it up at all since then.
I figured this
would happen, but...
Arima loved the me before
he knew my true identity.
Not the real me.
I fell in love with him after
I knew his true identity, but...
Miyazawa!
Sorry, would you stay late today?
I don't need you for much today,
so it won't take long.
I see. So it completely vanished from within him.
Oh, you're still here.
I saw the classroom lights from outside.
Did it take that long?
It's done already.
I see.
I'm not doing this anymore.
Huh?
I'm finished. I won't help any more.
But if you do that, you'll be in
all sorts of trouble, won't you?
I don't care.
Tell them.
Wait! What're you mad about?
I'm not mad. Let go.
You're mad, aren't you?
If something made you mad
all of a sudden, tell me.
I can't understand this way.
It's okay.
It's not okay!
Let's go...I said let go!
I'm sick of being used!
Miyazawa!
We always talked like friends,
so I'd forgotten.
Arima was just taking
advantage of my weakness.
How could he?!
He totally changed his attitude
when he found out my true identity...
How could he?!
So I'm gonna end it right here.
Wh...wh...why're you following me?
Because you're running away!
Stay away! Stay away!
Won't happen!
Dammit!
You don't have to run away
Like your life depended on it!
I said wait, you little...!
This could look compromising...
You're still running away?!
Aren't you all scraped up?
Show me your face!
So I'm a weirdo!
I'm vain, seIfish, a liar,
a schemer, and I'm greedy!
I'm sure you were disappointed!
But, why did you have to change
your attitude towards me?!
If I'm not acting elegant,
am I that worthless?!
I hate you! Don't touch me!
I'm sorry.
Am I really that weird?
If I'm not the model student,
am I really without any value?
Not at all.
I like you the way you
are right now. It's fun.
F...fun?
Sorry, I didn't mean it that way.
I never intended to tell
anyone from the start.
I didn't want to seriously use you...
I just wanted a reason.
A reason to talk with you.
I thought it would be fun...
It was fun!
I've never talked with
anyone like that before.
But I never thought it was hurting you.
I'm sorry. I won't ask you to help any more.
So that's it.
So it wasn't that he didn't care about me...
I'm glad. I guess I had a good cry.
From that day on, Arima and I
became companions,
sharing the same secret.
So, you're an only child?
Somehow it figures.
*She's helping out after all*
And you?
I've got two little sisters.
Are your sisters cute?
Well, to be totally accurate,
Arima may have misunderstood a bit...
Yeah, they're super obnoxious and SO cute!
I'll show them to you sometime!
"Obnoxious and cute?" Oh, well.
He thinks I snapped because
I was being overworked.
Well, that's okay.
At any rate, I now know that
I'm something special to Arima...
Even if it's not love.
But you really had me going, you know.
I didn't know you were
Like this either.
Yeah...
I'm surprised myseIf.
You might not believe it...
...but I didn't know that
I had this in me...until I met you.
Why does it bother me?
Why do I let myseIf be influenced?
I'm being drawn to you more and more
and becoming somebody else.
I wonder if that's a good thing...
...or a bad thing...
What'll happen next!
The two of them make up! Will
they enter straight into a love-love mode?!
But it won't be that easy!
Arima suddenly turns cold!
Is Sis gonna get dumped?!
Next time:
His Circumstances!