My family was rich.
I was sickly since birth...
...and I grew up being loved to death by
my Mom, Dad, and the old butler and nanny.
I was given as much candy
and toys as I wanted...
...but I didn't have any friends.
You fatso Takefumi!
We're not gonna play with YOU!
I even had metabolic
diseases in third grade.
Tonami-kun! Tonami-kun!
Everyone's talking about how
tall and cool you are.
I wonder if it's true that people from
Okinawa all all good looking.
My height? Well, I play basketball, so...
Playing basketball in Okinawa
that sounds so cool!
Besides, I'm not from Okinawa.
Oh yeah, you used to
live around here, right?
Until seventh grade.
I have a picture. Want to see?
Yeah, yeah!
Which one?
This one.
Yeah Right!
Nice Shot!
And this is what she made us
follow her around for?
But Tsubaki really gets into anything
that has to do with sports.
Just look at her expression.
Doesn't she seem like a totally different
person from this morning?
Well, I guess it'sbetter
than smacking people
who annoy her without a care of
what people think of her.
You listen
Okay, keep your eyes glued
to this one!
Tsubaki said she's going to sink
a dunk shot today no matter what.
Why would someone on the volleyball
team want to sink a dunk shot?
Well, it's Tsubaki...
Ooh, so close!
I want to go back to the classroom already.
Argh, next time for sure.
Just give it up.
Don't blame me if you get hurt.
At some point I got used
to being made fun of.
So?  C'mon, tell us.
Once you accept the fact that you're
worthless anyway...
...it doesn't hurt that much.
Moron, moron!
Give back my sneakers!
Stupid, they're too good for you!
Quit bullying around!!
Thank you.
You saved me
Don't you let them make you cry either!!
(Text:They both annoy her)
She knew judo, karate,
aikido, and boxing...
...and countless guys fell
victim to her fists.
She terrified every guy in school.
That was Sakura Tsubaki.
(Text:But she was nice to girls)
After that, she fixated on me
for some reason.
What?
Just come with me.
This, and this, and this...
And this, and this, and this...
This'll be all, ma'am.
That'll be 280 yen.
280 yen.
What?!
What, I can't use a credit card?
Ok, here.
(Text:10,000 Yen)
This was just for today, okay?
Don't do it any more.
Oh, fine.
Here, have half.
I don't want anything with all those...
...artificial colors and preservatives in it.
*pH buffers, Aspartame, Sodium nitrite, L-Phenyl
compounds, Magnesium phosphate, Malt Extract*
I only eat the candy mommy
buys me from Ginza.
And another time...
Pedal.
You can't even ride a bike?! What a loser!!
Sh...Shut up,
I just always get a ride in daddy's car.
You'll be fine. I'll support you back here.
(Text:Riding double is dangerous!)
Really?
Yeah, sure.
There was no end to Sakura's abuse of me.
Do it.
She made me do her homework,
and then hit me.
What the hell? This is wrong!
I don't make stupid mistakes like this!
I always do what you tell me to,
so I want you to help me when I need it.
Of course, I wouldn't make
you do it for free. Here.
Sure.
Stupid meatball!
Hah, I have Sakura on my side!
Okay Sakura, beat them up!
S...Sakura!
Oh, sorry.
It's time for a TV show
I wanted to watch.
Ask me when nothing's on TV.
Why do you keep hanging
around me anyway?
Don't tell me you like me.
Oh please.
Barbarian girls like you aren't my type.
I have this urge to hit you.
You should stop and think why
you get beat up for once.
It was like I was stuck with the plague
...all the way until seventh grade.
Damn you Sakura...
(Text:But I can't do anything)
Therefore . . .
I was overjoyed when I heard we were moving.
*Yahoo!*
I'll finally be free from this
humiliating life!
Farewell, to the old me who was
forced to be who I wasn't!
But...
I wanted to find out one last thing.
Sakura, why do you keep pestering me?
Oh, the teacher asked me to look
after you back in elementary school.
With me around, you wouldn't get beat up that much.
And it's rather my policy not to
beat people up.
Well, good luck at your new school.
Take care.
She was asked, that was all.
She thoght nothing of me.
For the first time in my life,
I realized my pride was deeply hurt.
That to her, I was a
meaningless existence.
But it was obvious, if you think about it.
I was such a failure.
I knew I'd only be away for
a short while.
I will change.
I will change so much that there'll be no way
she can ignore me the next time we meet.
I'm not going to let it end like this.
Tsubaki, let's go back to class!
Not yet. Not until I get this dunk down.
I know I asked you this before,
but aren't you on the volleyball team?
Yes!
Ah?
Bravo!
Who was that?
He's the one. Tonami Takefumi,
the one from...
Okinawa with the same name
as Tonami-kun.
He's nothing like him!!
Hahahahahahahahahaha!!
It is him!
That stupid girl hasn't changed at all!
No matter. I have changed.
I got taller, I got stronger,
I got over my diseases.
And I got thinner.
I'm not as I was
when I was under her thumb.
I'll let her pay nice and slowly.
Whatcha looking at?
What are you looking at?
That was fast!
The results are out already.
Wow, Yukinon and Arima really
live up to their reputations.
What's the matter, Tsubaki?
That dunk dude is up there too.
You're right. He must be smart.
Not bad.
How did you do?
I'm not smart enough to
be among the top.
Aya, Rika, let's go!
I guess she grew up enough that
she didn't deck me on the spot.
What the hell's his problem?
Shibahime figured it out.
After all, she is a wild animal.
What, Arima?! As in, that Arima-kun?!
No way!
Hey, Arima! The grades are out!
Hurry hurry!
A...Arima-kun!
I made sure Sakura was here,
but I figured Arima-kun would be
at some famous private school!
We're in the same high school?!
Arima-kun and I were in the same
class in middle school.
He was my idol.
Look, we tied for first!
That's great.
Now there'll be no hard feelings.
Hey, doesn't this look like
I'm in third place?
What?
It looks third! And it looks like you're first!
No fair!!
It's so unfair! Even if we put in the
same effort Arima will always be ahead.
There's no hope with Miyazawa.
Oh, come on now, who cares?
Ow, my foot!
*Squish*
I can't believe you!
Aw, all that's left would be to marry
you and get myself among the A's.
Arima Yokuni
Arima Souichiro
Huh? What's the matter?
Oh, nothing...
One more point and I would've
been first place by myself.
I made a careless mistake.
I made a stroke error on one Kanji.
Why do you make such stupid
mistakes when you're so smart?
I...Is that his girlfriend?
Arima-kun was different from
the other kids from the very start.
You could just tell his good upbringing.
His fairness and gentle disposition.
His capacity as a leader.
It was like only he was surrounded
in a special atmosphere.
Luckily for me, no bullying
happened in his class.
Even that violent Sakura...
Hey, go buy me some juice!
Don't be mean to someone in my class.
Arima!
Oh fine.
Later.
She wouldn't lift her hand against Arima.
Wow! Arima-kun, you're so cool!
You're really awesome!
And cool! Thanks, Arima-kun!
Arima!
That's Arima-kun, three years later...
Nice shot, Arima!
He's still so cool! He's beautiful!
Why are you blushing at another guy?
Let's go, Tonami!
Right!
Awesome, Tonami!
Oh, you're the Tonami-kun
who just transferred into 1-B!
A...Arima-kun...
Did you used to live around here?
I know someone with the same name.
Um, th...that's me.
Really? I knew it!
You've changed so much,
I was afraid I had the wrong person.
Yeah, I've changed.
It's good to see you again.
Welcome back.
He remembered me.
There was someone who would welcome me back...
When I had come back to this city
only to get back at Sakura.
It made me so happy.
Arima, who are you bringing?!
This is Tonami-kun.
We were in the same junior high.
It's been a while since
we last saw each other.
Is it okay if Tonami eats
lunch with us?
Hmm, in that case, okay.
No way!
Don't be friends with any guy but me!
Stop suffocating me.
Well, this is Miyazawa-san,
who's in my class...
...and on the Student Council with me.
Hi.
And this is Asaba.
But you can forget his name right away.
No way!
And Miyazawa and I are going out.
It's none of my business,
but Arima sure has strange tastes.
Oh, but I guess she's cute when
she keeps her mouth shut.
Let's have lunch.
Okay Arima, say "aah"
What're you thinking?!
No, I don't want any!
C'mon, say "aah"!
No!
Hey, what the?!
Hideaki you moron, let me go!
No!
Violating someone is so fun!
It's addictive.
Are you all idiots?
You're not eating with
Sakura's gang today?
Sakura?
Yeah, I want to pay attention
to just you sometimes.
Plus, this week...
What?
Aya-chan wrote this screenplay.
She wants us to perform it
at the Culture Fair...
...with Maho-san and Tsubasa-chan.
You should do it. I'd love to see it.
No way! You're just pulling my leg.
I can't act in front of people!
That's why I'm avoiding her!
What?
Are you trying to pit a
play against my dinner show?
Shut up!
Your attitude when you talk
about that pisses me off!
It looks like Arima...changed a little.
I really am back,
I really am back, for the first time in three years.
Sis is still running from Aya-chan in
the days preparing for the Culture Fair.
But unrelated to that,
Tonami Takefumi's plans for
revenge against?
...Tsubaki finally becomes clear!
And the weird friendship that develops...
...between him and Sis blows up a storm!
See next Act, 14 Days Pt. 3!