Miyazawa Yukino's mornings begin early.
And are just as methodical
as the novitiates of Mt. Kouya.
Not a minute of my time goes to waste.
The better part of my
day gets spent studying.
When Arima and I were
going all out on our love power...
...I bailed on studying and
abandoned myself to amusement...
But now I've begun studying again.
I decided to work hard so that our
relationship would be accepted by the school.
At least, that's the official reason.
Actually, it's because I'm mildly humiliated
...that Arima's grades were much better than mine
even though he was slacking off with me.
*Miyazawa Awakens Family*
They're still trying to sleep.
But their sleeping faces really are angelic.
GROSS !
What the hell're you doing
at this hour of the morning ?!
Oh, but now you're awake.
It's so cute how I care about my family.
Breakfast, Let's eat!
See you later!
Oh, Yuki. What about school?
*Once again studying in progress.*
Today's make-up exam day.
Those who don't have make-ups have the day off.
After lunch I'm going over to Arima's house...
...so I'll hang out the futons
and do the laundry before then.
Dammit, it's so frustrating
how Yuki has no weaknesses.
I'm off!
*Departure*
I have a fast-track lifestyle,
but I'm still able to meet Arima.
I don't have feelings for anyone
else the way I do for Arima.
"Because I strove to be perfect,
whenever I was with someone..."
...I always thought that
I had to be the one to push things along.
Because Arima is the one person
I can be on equal terms with...
...I can let myself be
taken care of by him.
Miyazawa, want to come over to
my place on make-up exam day?
I only have practice in the morning.
Sure, I'd love to!
No one else will be home that day.
C...c...come to think of it,
what did he mean by that?!
This is bad. This is BAD.
This is REALLY bad !
Yeah, whatever. I'm sure Arima
doesn't have any ulterior motives.
He's decent about that kind of thing.
Hi. I was just in the shower. Come on in.
S...shower?!
No way!  Not Arima!
He just wanted to freshen up after practice...
Yeah, freshen up...
But this feels different from the usual Arima!
N...no...no way!
B...b...but how can I be
sure that nothing will go on
when we'll be all alone in this huge house?!
He IS a guy, after all!
I feel tired...
Here you go, Souichirou.  Vegetable ramen.
Hot foods are good for you in the summer.
Don't talk to me like a housewife.
Miyazawa, please sit, sit!
Here's some iced tea.
Stop playing the host!
Whaddya think? My cooking's delicious!
It's delicious!
Just the fact that a guy
made it makes it taste bad.
Cooks and chefs are guys, too !
And you're neither.
But, Asapin, I guess you hadn't
been goofing off as much as I thought.
If you're at home on make-up
day, you must've studied a lot.
What?  Make-up day?
I flunked most of my tests.
Y...y...y...you DUMBASS !
What the hell're you doin'
standing around making ramen?!
How the hell did you get into
our school in the first place?
It's not too late!
Get your ass to school!
Dressed like this?
JUST GO!
I'll buy some Jello on my way back!
Get going already!
Sorry this had to happen
right when you got here.
I don't mind.
Want to go to my room?
Sure!  Arima!
What is it?
Miyazawa...
I'll get some drinks, so you can head on up.
We're such glorified kids...
I thought he was going to kiss me.
We're often alone together,
but there hasn't been
much in terms of progress.
We've only kissed that one time.
Speaking of which,
I wonder what's going on there.
Oh, well.
There's books scattered all over.
Must be Asapin's doing.
"Romance of the Three Kingdoms,"
"Kou'u and Ryuuhou..."
So Arima likes long historical novels.
How cute.
"Shiba", "Ikenami", "Yamamoto..."
What's up?
These books.
You want to borrow one?
What kind of books do you read?
Money!
Come to think of it...
What?
This is the first time I've been
to your house besides study group.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Your room's really nice.
It has its own A/C. I'm jealous!
R...really?
Morning practice must be really tough!
I guess. The captain's a morning person, so...
Wow, really?
Yeah, that's right.
I see.
Uh huh.
Say!
Huh?!
Miyazawa, I was wondering...
do you just want some attention ?
Um, actually... yeah.
All right, here's some attention!
Hey, ow!
I guess I'm the only
one who's showing their hand.
You're so cold.
I feel like I'm the only one expressing my love.
I bet you don't really love me all that much.
What?! How could you say that?!
I don't want to hear that from someone
who cares about their
own grades more than me!
Ouch, that hurt.
That's not what's going on at all!
Did I make him mad?
That was supposed to be a joke...
Shall I show you then...
...just how much I love you?
Ah...
It seems that my emotions
get out of control sometimes.
I didn't want to scare you,
so I haven't let them loose yet.
Could this be . . .
Would you like to find out, Miyazawa?
Would you like to find out ?
Provoking me...
We're now
in a delicate balance.
The slender thread of emotion...
...is stretched to the limit.
Y...yes.
That was totally different
from our previous kiss.
I felt like my heart would
fly off somewhere far away.
I was acutely aware
of Arima's presence.
Miyazawa!
I'll walk you home.
That's ok. I'll take the bus back.
I bet my face is all red,
so I'll cool off on the way home.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
It's ok.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
It was a strange day today.
But I got closer to Arima.
And so the days accumulate...
...and the weight of love grows.
I'm home!
Dinner!  Let's eat!
Good night!
Sis...
Are you an elementary
school kid or something?
This is the story of how I met you.
Oh, crap!  It's time for fifth period!
Spring. Not long after starting high school.
April. I was still alone.
I'm sorry. I fell asleep.
I apologize for coming to class late.
Come on now someone who was just
speaker for the incoming class
shouldn't be doing such a thing.
When we're done,
you can clean all the lab equipment.
Wow, Arima, you're covered
in cherry blossom petals.
Oh, these?
There's a row of cherry trees across the river.
Really ? I went over there for lunch break.
I didn't know there was a place like that.
I went there to eat my lunch and read,
but it felt so nice, I dozed off.
Why didn't you take us
with you?  Not fair!
Not fair!
Sorry, sorry.
Why don't we go on a picnic as a class?
Oh, that's a great idea.
With some snacks and stuff?
All right ! Party-time !
Hey, Arima, you're coming, too, aren't you?
What?
Sure, sounds good.
It's decided!
If Arima's going, I'm going, too.
Arima.
Oh, you didn't have to do this.
It's my turn for cleanup duty today.
Miyazawa. It's okay.
It's my own fault, so I'll do it.
Really? But I still feel bad...
Her name is Miyazawa Yukino.
Starting this month,
she became the representative
for class A with me.
She radiates "older sister,"
and is responsible and very smart.
She also does her committee
work very efficiently,
and is a wise and mature person.
Miyazawa,
those are the printouts from the
committee meeting this morning, right?
Give me half of them.
Oh, but I already finished them all myself.
What?!  All of them, by yourself?
Yeah. I had some time...
I'm sorry. I couldn't make it
because of practice this morning...
It's all right. Besides,
you helped me out with the cleanup.
Thank you.
Miyazawa's amazing.
She's nice, and doesn't
seem to have any faults...
I've realized that there really
are people like her in the world.
What the heck are you
talking about, Arima?
You're talking about yourself.
Ah...?
Highest scorer on the entrance exams!
Outstanding in sports!
Handsome!
Nice!
The most popular person in the whole class!
You're perfect!
Ah...?
How can you sit there and
be impressed by someone else?!
You don't know who
you are, do you?!
You're so famous that there's no one
at this school who doesn't know about you!
R...really?
I haven't done anything that conspicuous.
You stand out just by speaking!
You and Miyazawa are peerless!
You can say that again!
It looks like all the girls are
after you, too, you little punk.
Awake or asleep, it's nonstop
"Arima, Arima..."
Don't you get it?
What a pain!
I should be seriously pissed off.
Yeah, you were born
under a lucky star.
Unlike us...
Such a beautiful world.
There was always a
peaceful atmosphere around me.
Arima,
have you gotten used to high school classes yet ?
Yes, more or less.
You're a very smart student.
All of the teachers
enjoy teaching you.
HaHaHa...
Sorry I'm late!
I'll get ready right away!
Well, don't stress yourself too much.
Captain!  You're going
easy on Arima again!
You never give us a break!
Shut up!
Arima is on the Academic Committee!
HaHaHa...
Arima, could you help me with this?
Let's play soccer!
Every day was fun,
and I always thought I was happy.
But...every so often,
there was a fleeting voice.
"Are you really having fun ?" ...it said.
That was inside me...
Almost like ice that never melts.
But the days passed by.
The same quiet, peaceful days.
I'm sorry.
Um, are you going out with anyone?
Um, I...
Do you have someone you like ?
She likes you.
I love you.
Arima!
I love...
Why is it?
I felt like something was wrong.
I felt like this tranquility
was somehow artificial.
Surrounded by laughing classmates...
...there were times when I suddenly
felt everyone was far away.
On those days, I felt afraid.
Because I thought I might not
actually be feeling anything.
Even when I was laughing or
having fun with my friends...
...it felt like it all might be
just brushing off the surface of my heart...
...and that nothing was really
reaching the inside of my heart.
Even when girls told me they liked me,
my heart was totally unmoved.
There was an indelible
suspicion in my heart -
That I'm always alone.
That there wasn't anyone I could
actually call a friend.
I'm actually always alone.
That uncertainty was
always within me.
Why did I come to think like that?
I'm blessed by many more
things than other people.
But...the days flowed past...
The same quiet, peaceful days
that felt like there was
nothing there at all.
So, give twenty copies
to each section, okay?
I'm so tired.
You've got a lot taxing your
stamina, so it must be hard.
You must be busy, too,
with studying and the committee.
I guess. But I figured
that this is the norm.
I've been doing this stuff for a
long time, so I'm used to it.
So you're predisposed to committee work, too?
I don't know how everyone knows,
but I always get picked
for this kind of thing.
Miyazawa, was Hokuei your first choice?
Yeah. Why?
You're so smart.
I was wondering if you
applied to any private schools.
Yeah, but I have two younger sisters.
Besides, I decided not to
spend any money on studying.
I want to place the absolute minimum
financial burden on my parents...
...while getting the
maximum amount of education.
Having that sort of objective in mind
while studying gets me going.
Studying's really fun
when you have a goal.
You're really mature.
Well, I just think that way because
my family isn't that well off.
If we had more money,
I would have wanted to go to a private school.
Some of the classes not in the public
curriculum look pretty interesting.
How about you?
What?
Your family runs a hospital, right?
I'd think it's pretty rare for someone
like you to come to a public school.
Yeah, I guess I have
the same reason as you.
I guess we're both stingy.
That gave me a shock.
I just realized for the first time how
the girl next to me is standing straight...
...with such unclouded eyes.
That she decides everything by herself,
chooses everything by herself.
That she has her own way of living.
She left a strong impression on me
because she was so different from me.
I want to know about her.
I want to know what she's thinking.
I want to ask about so many things.
I want to know if she ever
has doubts or anxieties.
If she ever feels
the same loneliness I do.
I want to know more.
After school, at the
row of cherry trees...
A quiet spring day.
How should I turn her down?
Something was trying to change within me.
Um...What?
Miyazawa...called me out?!
I'm so happy!
U...Um...
Sorry I kept you waiting.
Oh, were you meeting here?
I was just watching the
cherry blossoms for a bit.
What?!
I...I misunderstood!
I misunderstood
S...sorry...
At that moment,
I realized I liked her.
I want to catch her.
I want that girl with such clear eyes to notice me.
My feelings began to overflow.
This is the first time I've ever
wanted something so clearly.
The April breeze bore the
cherry petals aloft into the sky.
Under the cherry trees
in full bloom...
...I fell in love for the first time.
After that, I came upon the surprising
true nature of the girl who seemed to
be a bright beautiful person
...and I began following
an unexpected path myself.
Well, I guess that's how life goes.
I don't regret any of it.
I think it's a good thing.
What'll happen next!
Sis and Arima are totally in love
and have achieved their second kiss!
But a state of emergency
is awaiting her!
It's finally time
to pay the price for what she's done!
Next time on KareKano:
"Atonement by Moratorium."