He is perfect.
He worked hard to stay that way.
It's unlikely that anyone
around him would deny that.
With his grades at school,
his character and personality...
Being "perfect" had become
part of his very being...
...but that was before
he came to know love.
That summer was hot.
After our first date ended in failure...
We made up for it by
going on a lot of dates.
Due to various circumstances, we hadn't been able
to be alone since we started going out...
...so you could say we
felt it was now or never.
Miyazawa !
Where was it again ?
That way, it's a bit of a walk.
It was fun being with Arima.
Since we had led lives of total
hard work and self control until then...
...it was fun being able to be reckless.
Seeing him outside like this,
I realized anew:
Arima is Pretty.
What is it ?
Oh, nothing.
Weren't you glaring at me just now ?
I see the epitome of beauty in him.
He's prettier than most girls...
...he's so calm and elegant...
...and on top of that he's
the smartest in our grade.
He's very athletic,
and from a wealthy family.
Everything he does he does right,
and he hangs out with me,
and he's nice to me...
...and it doesn't look like I have
to worry about him being unfaithful...
He's invulnerable !
Arima's the invulnerable man !
Now that we've got more time together...
I don't know anything besides "Afternoon tea."
*Earl Grey?*
But I still don't understand Arima.
I wonder what's inside
that polished shell of his.
What's he thinking,
what does he feel, what's in his heart...?
That's what I want to know.
I want to watch him forever.
I wonder what he's thinking.
Will I be able to know one day?
That summer was hot.
After our first date ended in failure...
We made up for it by
going on a lot of dates.
Even though it was unavoidable,
I still regret it.
That we weren't really able to be alone
together since we started going out...
...makes me ashamed of myself as a man.
So you could say we
felt it was now or never.
We may be a bit early.
Then why don't we go
this way for a bit ?
It was fun being with Miyazawa.
Since we had led lives of total
hard work and self control until then...
...it was fun being
able to be reckless.
Seeing her outside like this, I realized anew:
Miyazawa is Weird.
*Stare.*
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
Weren't you glaring at me just now?
I bet she's caught up in some
mysterious train of thought again.
I don't think I'll ever figure out
her thought patterns as long as I live.
Sure, I like her,
and I think she's cute...
But I've really gone and
fallen for a weird person.
She's really selfish,
her disposition's rotten to the core...
...her logic circuits are shot,
she's emotional,
she's scary when she gets mad...
...and she gave me the
precious experience...
...of getting a flying kick to the
stomach from the girl I liked.
It's also interesting how
she seriously agonizes on
and off about how weird she is.
Now that we've got more time together,
I never get bored gazing at her unique world.
*Sorry for serving English tea.*
*It's ok.*
*Glug glug.*
It's ok, I like tea.
I bet Miyazawa doesn't know that
I've got a complex towards her.
It's not fair that our grades are the same
and yet she's the one with all the individuality.
When I look at Miyazawa,
I feel like I'm the most constricted,
nondescript person in the world.
I guess the only value I really
have is just "being smart" after all.
I thought I'd be able to
be happy if I were perfect...
Yo, Miyazawa.
Yo, Asaba.  Hallo.
Hallo.
You're getting more tanned every day.
I've been body boarding.
Body boarding...?
Not another fad...
Are you trying to pick up
girls on the beach this time ?
Swimsuit girls are awesome !
The ocean is a paradise for men !
I see...
How about you ?
You went on a date with
Arima yesterday, right?
How'd it go?
Heh heh heh!
YOU know...
Miyazawa, couldn't you respond
a bit more like a girl your age?
We went to the Shinagawa Aquarium...
...and Toshima Amusement Park...
...and we saw three movies...
...and the cake at Tops was really good !
Really ?
During summer vacation we're going to
Edo River or Sumida River to see the fireworks.
We're going to Disneyland, too.
Take me with you.
No way!
Yo, Arima.
Hideaki.
I just saw Miyazawa.
You're getting more tanned every day.
I've been
body boarding.
Finals are coming soon. Make sure to study.
Come on. You're the one
going on all those dates.
Sounds like fun.
I'm studying, so it's okay.
Miyazawa seemed really happy.
Yeah.
She gets to go on a date
with Arima! Lucky her!
I wanna go on one, too!
What're you talking about ?
It's not that fun being with me.
Three months have passed
since I met Miyazawa.
The first month was a one-sided love...
...the second, we became friends...
...and the third, we started going out.
I should've been able to change,
being with Miyazawa.
But I haven't really changed much, after all.
I keep suppressing my feelings.
Reason always comes before my emotions.
Sure, I'm human,
so occasionally I get emotional, but...
I always end up sealing those emotions away.
My emotions have a door,
and I can never open it.
It felt like only you keep changing...
...that someday I won't be able
to keep up with you anymore.
I'm sorry, Arima.
I've got student council business
today, so I can't walk home with you.
That's okay.
I'm really sorry.
Let's walk home together tomorrow, okay?
I'll wait for you, even if you'll be late.
Okay.
Dinnertime!
Hey, Sis, how far have you
gone with your boyfriend?
K...Kano!
N...n...n...now see here!
E...Early! It's too early!
It's all too early for high school students!
Daddy, you're behind the times.
With high school students
these days, anything goes.
A...anything?
Yeah.  Anything
*My daughter, of all people.*
Don't tell our daughters such things
*When I was young, necking was the most we did!*
Dear, times have changed.
Even you...
So, how's it going?
With your boyfriend?
N...n...n...n...nothing's going on!
Hmmmmmmmmmm...
Thought as much.
How boring.
The world's overflowing with the pleasures and
sorrows of the couples mass-produced
from the Athletics Festival, and yet...
Sis is the only one
going at her own pace.
Maybe it's just because Yuki's
out of sync with the world.
I'm so worried.
Your father doesn't mind !
It's better
if nothing's going on...
It would've been so entertaining
if she could cause a family discussion.
She's not that resourceful.
It's better that way,
better that way, Yukino.
Dear, could you pass me the soy sauce?
I can't believe this family !
By the way, Souichirou...
Yes?
Well, never mind.
Okay.
It's just like Kano said.
All those couples
have disappeared.
The freshness guarantee only runs one month...
Nothing lasts more than one summer.
For every meeting,
I guess there has to be a parting.
Ahh, where in the world is true love?
Hallo!
You're certainly a
bargain-full of cheap love.
Where in the world is Arima ?
Okay, five minute break.
I can't believe you!
Aw, c'mon.
Year 1 Class A
Is Miyazawa really having
fun being with me?
Am I actually a good enough guy for her?
Oh, sorry.
Did I wake you?
Was I asleep?
Yeah.
That's right. I'm supposed to
walk home with you today.
Yeah, but I'm sorry for being late.
Darn...And now it's raining.
This is the first time I've seen you sleeping.
You look so neat, even when you're asleep.
Really?
Tsukino kicks around.
And Kano has these sad dreams
sometimes and sobs in her sleep.
It's so cute.
Rain, huh?
Got an umbrella?
Nope.
Me neither.
What should we do?
Let's wait around a bit.
School feels so nice after
everyone's gone home.
Most people would say it's creepy.
Did you wait for me to wake up?
You should've just woken me.
But you were sleeping so soundly.
You're so busy with committees
and practice and all.
We don't see that much of each other,
so I just wanted to be with you.
I know that...
I know that she only
smiles like this around me.
Miyazawa, you're like a little puppy.
Yeah.
I've always been an older sister, and I've been putting
on appearances by myself for so long...
...that this is the first time
I've ever let someone else take care of me.
It feels really good.
But I don't think I want anyone
besides you to take care of me.
I want to be with you...
Was that lightning just now ?
Yeah, it was.
Oh...umm....
Sorry, I'll go cool my head off.
Oh no, this music!
This intro is...!
Why do I have this song running
through my head at a critical time like this?!
It won't stop ringing in my ears!
The refrain just keeps going!
The song won't get out of my head!
I can't stand it!
It's awful! It's awful!
I can't stand it !
What have I done ?
I've done something indecent.
What the hell have I done?!
Now what?
How should I face Miyazawa...?
What do I do?!
U...um...Miyazawa, that was...
I just remembered what
I was going to say back then.
I was saying I didn't want
anyone besides you to take care of me.
Oh, right.
You can let me take care of you, too.
I was thinking that all those
years up through middle school...
...where I only showed off
and hid my true heart were pointless.
But maybe that's not true.
Maybe I could think of it this way:
Maybe all the hard work
has given me the strength to support you.
Then those years will be redeemed.
You don't have to tough it out.
It gets tiring to stand by yourself.
You want someone who'll support you.
Suddenly memory goes back to the past.
Memory returns to the past.
Before they met.
She strove to be perfect, for
vanity, for glory, to be the best.
He strove to be perfect,
because of his birth...
...for the uncle and aunt who raised him,
for the family who scorned him.
You're amazing, Miyazawa!
I hear you came in first during finals again!
You've always been number one.
There's no one who can beat you.
Sis, there's something really neat on TV.
Come and watch with us.
I want to finish this study guide, so I'll pass.
Again? Is it that much fun
to come in 1st place?
Ha Ha Ha...
But
there's nothing else
that feels fun to me.
You're amazing, Arima!
I hear you came in first during finals again!
You've always been number one.
There's no one who can beat you.
Um, please take this.
I'm sorry. I can't accept it.
Are you going out with someone?
Is there someone you love?
I'm sorry.
I had never loved anybody.
There had been nothing
that stirred my heart.
But that was okay.
I'll become a decent person.
I'll become a decent person my
father and mother can be proud of.
As long as my parents
are happy, I'm happy.
Both of their worlds changed
greatly upon entering high school.
I know why
I love you so much.
You always change me.
We can support each other.
Miyazawa holds the key to
unlock the door to my heart.
Yo! Asaba!  Hallo!
Hallo!
You got tanned again.
You're a real stallion, aren't you?
Maybe I should use a UV treatment.
I'll get freckles.
Wasn't that lightning last night really loud?
Yeah. You going on another date this Sunday?
I hope it'll be sunny.
No problemo! It'll be
just fine, rain or shine.
Yo, Hideaki.
Arima!
You got tanned again?!
What about studying?
But, hey, wasn't that lightning
Last night really loud ?
Don't change the subject.
You going on another date this Sunday?
I hope it'll be sunny.
No problemo! It'll
be just fine, rain or shine.
Hmn !?
That's right. It'll be just fine, rain or shine.
We've got a lot ahead of us.
What'll happen next !
Sis gets in the habit of going on a LOT of dates
and is in a state of perfect happiness once again.
But a deep, yawning gulf was awaiting them!
There are pitfalls everywhere in life!
Next time on KareKano,
"The Couple's Estrangement!"