Summery script translated by Camille's fan #207
Edited by SonPanSat
Summery
In the present, at Kanagawa perfecture,
In an ordinary town, this story takes place.
The main character of this story: Miyazawa Yukino
(1st year) appeared as a beautiful, smart, talented,
moral, elegant, graceful, and well educated girl.
But in reality, due to her vanity, she was keeping
apperances of a model student in front of people.
On one bright Sunday, she carelessly revealed
herself to Arima Souichiro (1st year).  He uses her weak
point to make her help him in his work.  After a while,
she explodes and he stops using her.  But, because
he was just using that as an excuse to be close to
her they reconcile.  After that, they were together
more often and formed a new friendship.  It seemed
that everything was going well.
And so...
July: The final exams end.
Arima Souichirou was accepted into this school
with the highest score on the entrance exam.
Miyazawa Yukino became the top
of the class on the following midterms.
The two stood out far from the others.
Surely, anyone would've thought they'd
become good rivals for the next three years
vying to become the valedictorian.
But now, there's...
...love between them!
Hey, you two, keep it down!
It's Sunday! You'll bug the neighbors.
But it's been so LONG since
we've gone out with you!
I'm so happy!
That's true.
I haven't been paying much attention
to them since entering high school.
*During that time, she was paying attention to Arima.*
I haven't been paying much attention
to them since entering high school.
I can't believe they're this excited.
I guess I've got to play with them more.
Hit it, Bro! Hell yeah!
Oh, welcome.
Sorry for dropping by on a Sunday.
Not at all.
My parents are out anyway. Come in.
Hi there.
H...hello.
So this is our older brother...
So, what're they going to do with the sunflowers?
Well, they're in charge of taking
care of the animals in their Jr. high...
And their hamsters are breeding like crazy.
So everyone's supposed to increase the
supply of sunflower seeds to feed them.
But I'm really glad you're
letting us borrow your yard.
Our yard alone isn't big enough.
We're overgrown with sunflowers this year.
Well, that's okay.  Middle school is pretty fun.
*Pero-Pero, hurry up and come here.*
A...Asa-pin!
Yo. Well, if it isn't Miyazawa.
Oh, my god!
What the hell are you doing here?!
Damn, you look nasty!
He's been staying over since yesterday.
Last night, I SLEPT with Arima...
In the same room.
Arima got REALLY lewd last night.
The only thing that's lewd is your brain.
Tsukino, Kano...this pervert is dangerous,
so don't get too close to him, okay?
Arima?!
Okay!
Should I dig here, too?
By the way, are you naked under that?
*Come, Wooflar!*
*His name's Pero-Pero!*
Miyazawa?
How'd finals go?
They didn't go that well.
You too, huh?
Oh, really?
We were goofing off pretty hard.
Well, I guess that's okay.
We goofed off knowing the consequences.
That's okay, but...
I don't really like handing over the place
at the top to someone else...
...after I worked my butt off so hard to get there.
But it's okay.
I was much happier being with you.
Miyazawa...
At that time, we were the very picture of peace.
I thought there was nothing
that could come between us.
We did slide a bit, didn't we?
Oh, well.
Come on,
Let's go have lunch. Miyazawa?
How'd you come in third
when I came in thirteenth?
*A wide, deep gulf appears between them already.*
You've been studying behind my back!
N...no, I didn't!
I wouldn't do something like that!
Why're you being so defensive?
I've been tricked!
I didn't think Arima was some grade
grubbing nerd, who would secretly study!
I said I didn't do that!
Calm down a moment!
Just yesterday you said I was
more important than studying!
I never said anything like that!
Arima Souichirou and
Miyazawa Yukino of class 1-A...
...report immediately to
the student guidance room.
I repeat,
Arima Souichirou and
Miyazawa Yukino of class 1-A...
...report immediately to
the student guidance room.
I wonder what it is?
I really thought that
nothing could come between us.
How may we be of assistance, Mr. Kawashima?
It's the first-year dean.
What's with this elaborate setup ?
You look as though you don't know
why you've been called here.
That's hardly surprising.
You two have never had
any business in here before.
You two are extremely talented students.
Your grades and your attitudes
leave nothing to be desired.
I'm looking forward to the
day when you become people...
...who will increase the
reputation of our school even further.
Now then.
Yes.
Have you two seen the results from finals?
Yes. We were just looking at them.
Your grades have dropped considerably.
It's not like you.
What could be the cause of this?
It's the result of my own negligence.
Is it the same for you, Arima?
Yes.
I intend not to let this happen again in the future.
I see.
By the way, I recently heard a certain rumor.
I'm wondering if there's any truth to it.
That you two are currently more than just friends...
...and that you "went out" a lot
during the crucial time before the exams.
That would cause you to neglect
your studies, wouldn't it?
Is that what you called "negligence"?
Is this an interrogation?
We have no obligation to answer that question!
Of course, we have no desire to meddle in
students' private relationships.
However, you two...
You two have too bright a future ahead of you.
You are people who must
think about their future.
Teacher,
I want to ask...
In other words, you consider our
relationship to be undesirable.
I suppose so.
That it's harmful to our future?
To put it plainly, yes.
You two should understand the
foolishness of taking risks now.
As teachers, we cannot afford to overlook this.
This is for the sake of your futures.
Your futures are too important.
Your studies should come first right now.
Until just a little bit ago,
it was fun being the model student.
I was a crafty, scheming child to begin with.
That was wonderful !
Everyone,
let's try hard, so we can all
play as well as Yukino, okay?
Okaaaay!
It's a really big help
having you lead the class like this.
Yes. Thank you very much !
Ooh, how cute!
Okay, Yukino, see you tomorrow!
Even the teacher is ga-ga over me !
Captivating grown-ups is easier
than taking candy from a baby.
I loved to scheme
since way back when.
I wanted to make myself
look good more than anything.
No one knew how I stayed up until 1 am
practicing the recorder...
...until I coughed up blood
just to be number one in the class.
I said that I loved reading
things like "Momo" by Michael Ende...
...but they didn't know that I secretly
read things like "How to Be a Billionaire..."
...or "How to lncrease Your Fortune A Hundred-Fold."
I could care less about love,
friendship, or trust.
Polishing my techniques for
making myself appear marvelous was
the joy of my life.
I had some bizarre personality,
but I wasn't worried at all.
Because I was "gifted."
I was confident that I was doing well.
That I was living the smart life.
I was on the fast track
to be a high-ranking politician or lawyer.
I was rushing down the elite
course, the runway of life, the
main road, while everyone cheered.
It was great.
I had no doubts whatsoever.
What other wonderful life was there?
But...But...
I found out later that I hadn't
understood anything after all.
Figures.
After all, the two top students in the
grade both had their grades slide at once.
Crud!  I hadn't thought about this part.
I presume you two are sorry
about these grades as well.
Stop going out with each other and
concentrate on studying.
But, sir, I certainly
understand your concerns.
Even so,
I'm not satisfied that you have
sufficient reason to intervene this far.
I find it far more perplexing
that you don't understand.
Are you saying you'd rather waste the
three important years that decide your future?
But...
You can go out with each
other after you get into college.
You two need to think about your future more...
I refuse. I don't like to do that kind of thing.
Of course, I understand how you feel.
But people must sometimes
make sacrifices for their objectives.
You don't get second chances in life.
You two are gifted.
You can have any life
you want in the future.
Even if it seems unreasonable now...
...surely the time will come
when you realize it was for the best.
Just work on polishing yourselves for now.
It's only three years.
I know that.
I thought the same way until just a while ago.
I thought that was the smart way to live.
But I was wrong.
That's a cunning way to live.
I never hesitated because I thought that
I was being the smartest that way.
But then I met Arima.
He was the first friend
who smiled at the real me.
I found out for the first time what it
felt like to be accepted by someone else.
The thrill of laughing with someone else.
How important something I hadn't
even glanced at before could be.
Now I wonder if being the model student
was such a good thing.
Miyazawa!  What kind of way
is that to talk to your teacher?!
Apologize immediately!
I believe that's enough.
I'm not satisfied with your reasons either.
We'll study.
We'll prove that we can do both.
In which case, I trust there'll be no problem?
Don't forget what you've just said.
Return to your classroom.
I had no idea you two
were thinking that way.
Well, the sweet talented beauty image
just went out the window.
I bet the teachers were totally floored.
But why'd they have to yell at us like that?
*Yeah, well...*
There's nothing to worry about.
All we have to do is get
grades they can't complain about.
Besides, we're trying to
change into our real selves.
There's bound to be a bit of conflict.
I guess so. At any rate, I guess we have to study.
Yeah. The security of someone being there for me.
When I'm with Arima, it's nothing but blue skies.
I can honestly feel that I'm right.
That's why I feel so
fortunate that I met Arima.
Even if I get praised by others
or even if I get first place, I
could never feel like this.
I'm home.
Oh, Yuki.
Did something happen to you at school today?
I got a phone call from
your school this afternoon.
They said they had something they wanted
to report directly to the parents...
...and called us in for a conference.
I wonder what it could be about?
But there are still many problems left over.
Morning.
Why'd they have to go this far?
There was no reason to call our parents in.
Arima has a complicated history,
and he really cares about his uncle and aunt who
raised and loved him instead of his real parents.
It must really hurt to have to worry them.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault for talking back without
thinking and making the teachers mad.
Of course not...lt's not your fault.
I thought the same way you did.
How about you?
Did your parents scold you?
M...my parents...?
Say what?
We got called into school about Yukino?
Thirteenth place in finals...
I'll go to her school tomorrow.
Me, me!  I want to go, too!
Why do you want to go so badly?
It's for the sake of my dear little daughter.
And...
I like having to fight for the sake of love !
Mom and Dad had to fight in the old days,
since we married young.
When I asked your mother's father for
her hand in marriage, he beat me up.
You were a bloody pulp.
War with the teachers, is it?
I tremble with eagerness!
Hey, don't make things worse!
Don't worry, your father used to take karate!
Once he gets serious...
That's not it!
Dear, let's take weapons!  Weapons!
Good idea!
Dad!
Both of us will go tomorrow,
so just leave it to us!
Don't worry!
No, they didn't scold me. I'm fine.
Damn!  It's still MAJOR trouble!
My parents are coming!
You can never tell what they're going to do!
Why can't we just do things the way we want?
I know studying is important.
But...
...what good is studying if
emotions have to be sacrificed ?
I couldn't enjoy being the best like that.
Besides, there's something
I want to cherish more than that now.
I was really glad when
you defied the teachers.
We won't be discouraged by this sort of thing...
But the world is rather annoying.
I want to be more like myself.
I want to stay free.
They don't understand even that.
Ah, Mr. Miyazawa.
Thank you for all you've done for our son.
S...she's not worthy, but please
make our daughter happy...
Don't rush things !
Nice tackle...
I think you knocked my guts out.
I can't believe you !
Now now, not in public.
Now then, the reason I have asked
your parents to join us today...
...concerns a matter I judge to be of
grave importance to your children's futures.
Both of them possess
incredible academic talent.
Surely, you also have high
hopes for their futures.
Yes Yes...
*Dad...*
But now, these two have
erred in their judgement.
That they were so absorbed
in their relationship before finals...
...and caused their grades to suffer is unthinkable.
Can this be seen as anything other than a mistake?!
They're about to stray from the proper path.
I want them to hear from their parents as well...
...that no matter what excuses they try to make...
...their relationship would
only interfere with their academics.
That getting swayed by temporary emotions
is not something smart people should do.
Sir, please take that back!
Souichirou...
They completely refuse to hear what we tell them.
I would like you to convince them.
But, sir...
...why do you think that they would stray from
the proper path if they have a relationship?
Why...?!
It's showing in their grades already.
Aren't you worried about
your daughter's future?
But you know,
Yukino's really too smart to be our daughter, right?
Right...
It's a bit annoying.
Up until now, our daughter has chosen
everything she does by herself.
I've never told her to do what I say.
Of course, I understand what you're saying.
But...
...it's precisely because we're
thinking of our daughters' futures...
...that we don't try to repress them.
I feel that repressing children
and forcing them to study
would limit their potential.
I believe children have a
right to think and feel freely.
Studying is very important.
But a single day in
high school is far more...
...important than an entire month
of life after they've grown up.
So you're saying you don't mind?
That you don't care if your children
come to regret it later?
Does that include you, too, Mr. Arima?
Yes.
He's already given us so much.
All we could ever do is praise him...
...and he's never caused us a single problem.
And even if there will be a day
when he faces difficulty in the future...
...I look forward to worrying about it together.
It looks like even my folks
had reasons for what they do.
I guess he wasn't just an overgrown little brother.
*She vaguely saw her father that way.*
Yukino, Yukino!
Mom and Dad are going for tea with the Arima's.
Later!
Yuki, soak the rice for me !
Dad, keep it down at school!
Pardon me for keeping you waiting.
Let's go, shall we?
What do you think?
*My wife knows of a wonderful cafe around here...*
Shall we tell him?
Well, they were doing their jobs
in being worried about us after all.
Now this is the sort of thing
a true model student worries about!
Sir...
What is it?  You haven't left yet?
We're sorry for saying such rude things.
We intend to study properly.
Do what you think is best.
Students these days often have
no idea what they're thinking.
I was happy to be up against students
with some backbone for a change.
Be careful on your way home.
There are things that don't go smoothly.
But sometimes, you come to see things
because they don't go smoothly.
Shall we go?
Yeah.
We're still just small, nameless flowers.
Just small,  barely budding things
supported by something larger.
But we dream...
...of the day we unfold our petals
beneath the clear blue skies.
What'll happen next!
Sis finally got accepted by
the school as a couple.
That day, when no
one else was around...
Could this be a development
in their relationship?!
Next time on KareKano:
"A Day in Her Life" (plus one other)