I've been thinking, and well,
I thought maybe I could
do the play after all...
Really? You'll do it?
Yeah, I thought, if I was going
to keep thinking...
...about it and be indecisive,
I might as well do it...
Uh-huh! I'm so glad!
It'll be my debut as an actress.
Yay, it's going to be on stage!
No! I don't want to be involved in
such an "after school special" thing!
Maho-san!
Maho, you thought that screenplay
was good too, didn't you?
The characters were originally inspired...
...by the three of us,
so each of our roles fits.
No matter what we always say about her,
Aya-chan really observes us well.
Ever since I read it,
the Professor's been
inside my head, and talks.
This must mean that the role is
starting to come alive inside you.
It's wonderful.
I can do a task that is given to me,
but I've never created something myself,
...so I'm really excited.
So come on, let's do it.
If you would be there,
I'd feel much braver.
I'm not doing it.
What's your problem?
If I say we do it, then ya betta do it.
That's my stomach...
You're the one who got the
whole class to ignore me!
I act bright and cheerful,
but I've been afraid of people since then.
Just a little distrust of humanity...
No fair!
Once your heart is wounded
it never goes away.
You're lying! Lying! Goddammit!
Maho-san said she'd do it too.
(Text:"She realized that
resistance was futile")
A play put on by interested students?
Yes. Do you know what
we'd need to do?
Do you know?
No...
I hear our school's theater club
ceased to exist a long time ago.
But this might be difficult.
A play would use a stage
for a couple hours, right?
Something like a food stand
would be a different story,
but the brass band and the music
ensembles wouldn't like that at all.
You can't just say you want to do it,
there are things that are physically
impossible to do in a play.
Even for you, Miyazawa-san.
And you're all beginners right?
Are you sure you can pull it off?
I wonder if this was too sudden after all.
No, just leave this to me!
Negotiating is my area of expertise.
I'll work something out.
Ooh?You're so reliable!
They told you it wouldn't work,
...so you should just give up.
I'm not going to do anything to help.
All I'm going to do is
say my lines, got it?
Ooh, scary.
Maho-san's reverting to her old punk ways.
Wow, so you're really going to do it.
Yeah, but it's hard to be aggressive to
the Student Council President by myself.
I hate to ask when you're busy,
...but could you help me with that?
I'd do anything for you.
Do you think the PTA would like the story?
Yeah, theme-wise?
In that case, you should get
the teachers on your side.
Getting teachers with power to recommend
that it's appropriate to be performed at...
...the Culture Fair would
be the most effective.
Oh yeah!
I knew I could count on you.
Arima, you're so good to have around.
What?
Just call on me whenever you're busy.
I'll help out.
Oh yeah Miyazawa, I got my hands on
a bit of inside information about
the Asaba Hideaki Dinner Show.
Say what?! 1-F has
totally hardened their...
...defenses and won't let anything
out about their plans!
What kind of seductive stage are
they planning?
Come on baby! Ole!
Mitchie?!
(Text:Welcome to Prince Land)
Come on baby!
Takarazuka?!
Come on!
What?! Julie?!
Casablanca!
Character goods!
Notebooks, pencil boards, pencil cases,
telephone cards,
celphone straps, watches, ballpoint pens,
laminated cards, posters,
handkerchiefs, charms, keychains,
diaries, 1/6 scale figures!
A specially made picture book
and fanzines.
Oh boy, that'll sell.
Asapin Official Guidebook!
Asapin Calendar?!
Asapin Illustrated
Asapin Poetry Collection?
Arima-kun!
Going to practice?
No, the reference room.
Arima-kun, I heard you
won the Interhigh!
You really are amazing!
Can I come watch you practice
some time?
It's not worth seeing.
Perhaps he's in a bad mood.
What do you think?
Sawada wrote this?
My specialty is math so I'm not
...an expert at literature,
...but I was surprised. I
didn't know you had such talent.
Nope,
I just wrote down whatever popped in
my head and dressed it up as I saw fit.
It's just a bunch of lies.
It's a work into which Sawada-san
gave her all to express the themes
she wanted to entreat!
So you're saying you'd like
to do this at the Culture Fair?
I think it's good.
This is the sort of thing appropriate
for the Culture Fair.
I'll give it my recommendation.
Thank you very much.
And about the procedures in going
about actually making it work...
we don't really know what to do,
so we would like your guidance.
It would be best to get
a teacher to be an advisor.
You have such a fine work here.
You could get this qualified
as a temporary club.
Oh yeah! So we have to find a teacher
who would be willing to be our advisor.
But who?
Shouldn't it be one of the literature teachers?
I don't know if there's someone we could ask.
I don't know any of them that well...
And we definitely want someone
who has influence in the Student
Council and among the faculty.
When I was a student
I did a small amount of acting...
That is, only if you think I'd be suitable...
That's it!
Yay! We're so lucky that we got
Mr. Kawashima!
He is the Dean of our class!
(Text:Power)
Power! He has power!
Hee hee hee...Just leave it to me...
Now I can get us whatever budget we want!
We think Yukinon's more
helpful than anyone else...
I always thought that Mr. Kawashima was scary.
But he's a really nice teacher when you talk to him.
Attention, all students.
The application deadline for
groups .participating in the
Culture Fair is today at 3 o'clock.
Any group who has not submitted
it should come...
...to the Student Council Room
without delay.
Attention, all students.
The application deadline for groups
participating in the Culture Fair
is today at 3 o'clock.
Any group who has not submitted
it should come to...
Here! I brought the application.
I also have Mr. Kawashima's
recommendation letter.
Our members are Sawada Aya, Shibahime Tsubasa,
Isawa Maho, and Miyazawa Yukino.
We're going to put on a play.
Hey hey, have you heard?
Miyazawa-san and Shibahime-chan
...are going to do a play.
Yeah, I heard!
I wonder what it'll be about?
I want to see it.
I want to see it!
Miyazawa-san!
We'll definitely go see it.
Ok, but don't worry, I'll help out
on the class event too.
Maho, you're going to play a guy?!
I bet you'd look studly!
Tsubasa-chan! You're so cute!!
We'll go see you!
Too noisy!
So scary! But cute!
What?! Sis is going to be in a play!?
Fantasizing
Yaay! Let's go see! Let's go see!
No, you don't have to come.
I'm surprised you decided to do it.
One of my friends is a writer and
when I read it, it was interesting, so...
Really? What's her name?
Oh, I borrowed one of her books.
She's called Sawai Ayaki,
but that's her penname.
Sawai Ayaki?!?
Wh-what's the matter, Kano?
Sawai Ayaki's the person who wrote that
story you were sobbing over the other day!
No way, she's your friend?!
I'm definitely going to see it!
Introduce me to her!
Let me see the script!
O-okay, okay.
Dear! Let's go to Akihabara tomorrow!
We-we have to buy an
appliance like a camcorder!
What about your colleagues?
Will see Ayaki-sama...
Aya-chan must be amazing.
Guess I'll do my best too.
Yo, everyone's talking about how
you're doing a play.
Is that really?
That's right.
You sure you can handle it?
I bet you're going to forget your lines
the moment it starts.
Don't jinx me!
I'll be fine.
I'm used to talking in public from
Student Council.
I'd think the Student Council and
a play are totally different things.
Hee hee hee...
Meanie.
Anyways, what I do doesn't matter.
What about you and your revenge?
Are you doing something about it?
Changing the subject, eh.
I'm not in any hurry, so it's all right.
I'll do it gradually?
True.
There are no aesthetics in carrying out
your revenge simply.
You have to take your time and do it slowly.
That makes it feel so good.
Well,
The time spent elaborating the scheme for
revenge so beautiful it's a work of art.
The feeling of satisfaction in...
...steadily driving them into a trap,
like putting pieces of a
puzzle together, one by one...
That heightens the exultation felt...
...in the moment when you
reach the catastrophe!
Right!
Oh, at times I scare myself.
If I hadn't fallen in love with Arima,
I'm sure I would be devising...
...a scheme like this on him right now.
What?!
We seem to be wholesome at first glance
yet we are secretly vindictive and
insidious within...
I don't like you or anything, but we
are definitely close. I understand you.
Yeah. I don't like you or anything either,
but I feel some kind of kinship with you.
Okay,
We're going to come up with specific
divisions of labor!
Actually, what are the divisions of labor for a play?
Rika-chan's doing the costumes...
Stuff like the set, props,
sound, and lighting?
I don't know either
Yeah, it would be hard to
do everything by ourselves.
That's what stagehands are for.
Maho-san and Tsubasa don't
look like they'll be any help...
In that case, I'll call on the girls on the
volleyball team who have some free time.
We have lots of people, and they're strong.
Really?
Thanks. You're a big help.
No problem.
We can bring things from home for props.
And then the BGM, where
should we play what music...
I really want to be particular.
Sounds like fun!
And what might all these lovely maidens
gathered here be talking about?
Asapin!
Tell me what's troubling you.
I'll grant whatever you desire...
Quit spewing pheromones near me!
Miyazawa, you're so square.
You just get ready for your dinner show.
The folks in my class are doing that,
...so I'm free.
I see, prepararing for the play.
You're doing the set too?
Well in that case, I'll do that.
What, you, Asapin??
(Text:Suspicion)
How could you?! I always get an A in Art!
Oh, but I've seen Asaba-kun's sketches.
They're detailed and really good.
Well, all right.
So, what should we do?
Don't take charge when you just barged in.
Don't you think our group is
getting weirder and weirder?
I bet you just wanted to join a group of girls.
But of course!
Is that what it is!
Miyazawa.
Arima!
Here are the printouts.
Hideaki, what are you doing?
You ask me?
I'm going to help Miyazawa's gang.
That sounds nice.
I want to help too.
You want to join a group of girls?
I'm not you.
You're helping us enough
already by giving advice.
Arima.
Are you all right?
What'll happen next!
The preparations for the play
are going steadily,
and Sis shows off her
lovey-doveyness with Arima.
But unrelated to that, Tonami Takefumi...
...finally admits to Tsubaki that
he hates her!
And the tremendously busy days...
...were about to begin again!
Please see next Act, Bye.