[ How does this show appear in others' eyes? ]
[ Episode 1 Her Circumstances ]
[ To Be Continued ]
[ Episode 2 A Secret for Two ]
What's happened so far!
Our sister, the masked model
student Miyazawa Yukino,
gets her weakness found out by Arima-kun...
...who fully demonstrates his rather dark,
scheming ways and abuses Sis.
Feeling love for the first time
helps to put Sis into big trouble...
...but she finally snaps and the
situation comes to an end.
The two of them settle into
being friends for the time being.
[ To Be Continued ]
[ Episode 3 His Circumstances ]
The story so far.
Suddenly, Arima begins to
treat Miyazawa Yukino coldly.
Yukino feels bewildered by
his unreasonable treatment.
Unable to specify the cause, she
resorts to ignoring him as he
did her, for self-satisfaction.
But her behavior gets results,
and Arima reveals his past
and true feelings to Yukino.
Yukino listens to it all,
and receives a confession
of his love once again.
[ To Be Continued ]
[ Episode 4 Her Problem ]
The story so far.
"Missing her chance to respond to
Arima's reconfession of his love,"
Yukino develops plans to
confess her feelings to him;
but they end up failing in every case.
Upon realizing that this was due to cowardice
from not wanting to get hurt,
she summons her courage and replies to
him not with words, but with her heart.
And the two finally become a couple.
[ That day. They became "a couple." ]
[ A C T 1 4 - 0 ]
[ The Story So Far (The Beginning) ]
[ To Be Continued ]
[ Episode 5 + Episode 5.5 ]
[ Daily Labyrinth ] [ His Desire ]
The story so far.
The two become a publicly recognized couple.
However, the menace of the Athletic Festival,
which made them busy and kept them apart
and the appearance of the
wanton perverted hunk, Asaba Hideaki,
who picked on Yukino
and plotted to use Arima
to fulfill his ambition, the Asaba Mary-Land
and such things come to stand in her way.
[ To Be Continued ]
[ Episode 6 Your Voice that Changes Me ]
The story so far.
Due to the failure of their first date,
the two fervently fill their days with trysts.
However, driven by a daily
increasing fear of losing Yukino...
Arima suddenly finds himself embracing
her amidst the rolling thunder.
Yukino accepts him.
And their lips finally meet.
[ To Be Continued ]
[ Episode 7 The Couple's Estrangement ]
What's happened so far!
Sis's midterm exam ranking drops
because she had been
abandoning herself to her desires!
The school, taking the matter seriously...
calls them down and tries to
talk them out of their relationship.
But she unexpectedly
rebels and steadfastly refuses.
However, the situation is
overthrown with dad's words.
The end!
[ To Be Continued ]
[ Episode 8 + Episode 0.5 ]
[ A Day in Her Life ]
[ Beneath the Cherry Grove in Full Bloom ]
The story so far.
One day, Miyazawa Yukino visits
the empty Arima residence
and lets herself experience the second kiss.
And another piece of Arima's past becomes clear.
[ Act 14.3* ]
[ The Story So Far (The Middle) ]
[ To Be Continued ]
What'll happen next!
Various situations are finally brought to an
end and Sis gets to settle down for a bit.
And so continue the days of
dependence on connection to Arima
through a modern convenience, the telephone.
And the reappearance of Asaba-kun
brings about a change within her.
Next time on KareKano,
That Which is Visible Behind A Voice
and one more!