At the end of the 1990's.
Japan has reached the most dangerous depths of economic crisis and depression since World War II.
There is a series of personal and company bankruptcies...
...increasing rate of unemployment, shocking rise in felonies by delinquent minors.
Indeed, though it is the end of the century, it is most appropriate to call it a time of chaos.
This is the same.
First year room A as the top student of Hokuei Public High School...
...of the Kanagawa prefecture, Yukino Miyazawa, was the ultimate Queen of glory.
Arima, who has changed her, was carrying...
...the burden of his unhappiness by himself, and he was also an honors student.
These secretive two have become intimate with each other, even insofar as they are top students.
They eventually cross the stages of being classroom buddies, friends, more than friends to lovers.
And thus they arrive at a relationship in which we speak...
...of them in terms of His and Her's, they are now boyfriend and girlfriend.
And then, feeling pressure in their relationship...
...they decided together that they would live toward their happiness.
Toward these two who have made these decisions...
...the world has thrown trials, which could even be called cruel, one after the other.
But sweeping away destructive demonic influences, and enduring...
...compounding excruciating situations, now has put the summer vacations behind her...
...and has now taken up the challenge of the Autumn Cultural Festival.
However!
Stage 1
Broadcast Information Meetings
Ah
Oh It's Asapin
He presented himself, and flowed in.
Oh, Miyazawa, you're also doing broadcast and information
Oh! Asabakun
And conversation.
Oh yeah, let's do it.
Well, those two are here too.
And then he appeared, and flowed in again.
Tonamikun
I'm so glad. I just came into this school. I've got no one I know and I don't know this school.
Then stay with me, I'll teach you lots of stuff.
And conversation.
Kinda feels like I'll get used.
Continuing conversation.
Of course
He is silent.
And scornful
Stage 2
This is the tallest tree in this school...
Ouch
Hey, didn't mean to do that.
Opps, sorry.
Dropped it.
Thus she apologizes.
And then smiles.
Unexpected encounter.
Small irritation.
What are you doing up here?
He approaches.
It's the best eating lunch at places like this.
Conversation.
Gorilla! Ha ha ha you're a gorillia!
Guffawing.
You say so, but you look like a gorilla yourself.
Girl looks on with morbid fascination.
Here, some feed.
Irritated again.
Dullness...
And then restfulness.
Hey
Destruction of her pleasure.
N...wha?
You haven't forgotten what I told you the other day, right?
Bringing an end to his endurance.
And thus interjecting.
What are you all confident about?
But she is utterly unmoved.
Yeah.
If you don't like me, I can't help it. Go ahead and not like me.
Grr! What does that mean?
She does not move.
Besides, I like you quite a bit.
Silence.
Eh?!
Shut up
Shaken.
I SAID I DON'T LIKE YOU!
Reasserting.
If I'm not liked, do I have to not like you back?
When I think about it, being with you is kind of fun.
Isn't that enough?
Cannot reach her.
Free flowing...
this gal's heart is always somewhere far away
Any words of mine...
and feelings...
cannot reach her.
It never will reach Sakura
Why?
I don't know
He replies.
That is the first time I ever kissed.
Come to think of it, me too.
He says the same.
And then, questioning...
Why did I do such a thing?
Questioning...
Meeting Room
Next we need to discuss with regard to the topic of...
Stage 3
Prep Room
Ahh, thank you.
She expresses gratitude.
Today I have to arrange and do a check of the proposals of all the participating circles for the events.
And then works on.
I begin writing out notes... until evening into the night.
And then her suffering.
You... you seem to be bogged down, you need any help?
And then empathy.
You're top of the class anyway, so...
No, just your bringing it here for me was enough, thank you.
And then her reply.
What, I'm offering you sincere help.
And then, conversation.
Because if I'm too friendly with other boys, Arima will get lonesome.
And then talking about her love affair.
Arima fan
What are you saying, don't flatter yourself!!
Cause it's true.
Heh, I cannot understand it at all, why is Arima-kun with a girl like this... I'm sure there are plenty other girls he could date who are a lot more suited to him, who is more upstanding, more graceful, more lovely.
He cannot understand.
Cannot understand!!
You probably tricked innocent and unsuspecting Arima-kun into your sneaky trap and now you're using him. That must be it!!
And then, judgement.
And then, utterance.
You probably tricked innocent and unsuspecting Arima-kun into your sneaky trap and now you're using him. That must be it!!
Boo
Boo, wrong!
Wrong
Arima was the one who attacked first.
I can't hear you... it's a lie!!!
Not listening, and then denial
Anyway, whatever became of your revenge scheme?
And then she asked.
Well...
I'm still working on it. I haven't given up.
But you know, to hold a grudge of vengeance for two whole years and be that involved with your feelings against that person.
What?
Oh, nothing.
And then he appears again.
Asapin
Oh this.
I was asked asked to do this by Sawada-san.
And then, conversation again.
Oh this.
I was asked asked to do this by Sawada-san.
Thank you.
And then, conversation again.
Oh well, I better go help out in class.
Do well with your revenge.
And then, parting.
Shut up.
And then, askance.
Long silence.
Long quiet.
What is at the end of it.
What awaits at the end of it.
Hey, you...
Breaking of silence.
You're getting too close to Miyazawa.
Breaking of complacency.
Chasing after Arima.
Breaking all blocks.
You shouldn't casually do things that's not called for.
Breaking up pressure.
Arima really doesn't like it when someone gets too close to Miyazawa, regardless of boy or girl.
What...Arima-kun?
The Arima-kun that you know is just a fabrication.
The breaking of truth.
The real Arima is very temperamental.
He is very possessive.
The breaking of the ghost image.
The real Arima is very temperamental.
He is very possessive.
But I know that Miyazawa will never betray Arima.
But I'm not Just saying this
And the breaking of fictitiousness.
But I know that Miyazawa will never betray Arima.
But I'm not Just saying this
Arima is only truly kind to...
Miyazawa only
And then, fantasy.
Arima is only truly kind to...
Miyazawa only
The reason why Arima overlooks my being with Miyazawa
And then, deception
Is because he knows that I would never touch Miyazawa.
And then, putting himself in his situation.
Huh?
Aren't you over thinking this? What's so great about her anyway?
Not that I don't like her.
But it is the truth.
Aren't you over thinking this? What's so great about her anyway?
Not that I don't like her.
She's a little smart and cute; that's about it.
It is also real.
She's a regular girl
She's not even my type.
Glad to have met her.
Don't you get it?
You're just a brat
And then, the setup
Stage 4
Me and you
The reason why it must be you for me and me for you.
You're scared, right?
Thought I know in my mind, I do not know with my feelings.
Want me to tell you why?
You have realized.
Though I made love to Miyazawa.
That cannot be happy.
It is because you came in contact, that your distance has grown apart.
Now it's as if you're two separate people.
The joy of touching each other is momentary.
That cannot be the goal.
I had never thought this way before.
But now, painfully.
But that Miyazawa can go on without you.
Poor guy.
You thought you could be happy.
Stage 5
Prep Room.
Oh
Meeting again.
You done with the work?
Conversation again.
Yeah, released at last.
Hey, did you see Arima?
Conversation.
No, I haven't seen him.
I see. I can hardly see him because of the play and everything So I at least wanted to go with him.
Conversation.
And the play? Is it fun?
Yeah! it's fun to do this with everyone.
Conversation.
Don't get close to Miyazawa.
What are you saying?!!
She's not the kind of girl I'd be that interested in!
So long
And then, parting.
Later
Maybe...
What I have believed to be myself is nothing but a fraud that was created out of my own efforts.
Maybe there is another real me, inside of me.
His and Her Circumstances
Existence and Nothingness, Born Mutually.
Stage 6
A...
Meeting again.
Arima-kun
Um...
And then, the panic that envelops him, and the hesitations.
He completely hates me...
Insecurity and hopelessness.
Good morning
Good morning.
Hey, have you seen Arima?
Waaah! ...Don't come near me!!
Arima-kun is my best friend, who was kind to me.
I understand now, but at the time, I was a spoiled and truly obnoxious brat, and I can't help it if others didn't like me.
But Arima-kun was not that way.
Everyone would come around Arima-kun, and I would never be teased in that classroom.
Whenever I was alone, he would be next to me, unpretentiously.
And he was frighteningly intelligent.
He was fair
He was kind
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that Miyazawa was that precious to you.
But to be honest, I'm surprised.
That Arima-kun would actually look at me in such a way, with such feelings.
Maybe being in love is something like this.
Such out word feelings?
Hmm?
In that case,
does that mean that
Arima-kun had that
element in him to
begin with?
In that case,
who was the
Arima-kun in Junior High?
Was he just a facade?
Ridiculous!
Arima-kun is not that kind of person
No, wait...
If asked which...
I used to naively believe back then, but...
To coexist fairly with everyone is to...
View everyone as if they were the same.
Huh?
I have opened a hitherto unopened box...
It seems as if...
The Arima that you know is just a fabrication.
That's right...
But that's the real Arima-kun.
Arima
You're strong.
Want me to hold it?
All of his caring feelings are given to Miyazawa
His reactionary feelings and hostility are turned toward all who would get between him and Miyazawa.
Whenever it pertains to Miyazawa, Arima-kun cannot hold back his feelings.
For the first time...
I wanted to know the Arima-kun who was not about my dreams or ideals.
This time for real.
I wanted to be friends with you.
Arima-kun... Your heart... Where is it?
Stage 7
Social Studies Resource Room
What a help, thank you.
No problem, do I put this away?
Miyazawa!
Well, it's just that somewhat, lately I feel that our kinship is lacking.
Princess, does that mean that my efforts are insufficient?
No. We were together all the time during summer vacation...
...and now we're hardly together because we're so busy with all the school activities.
It's so fun being with Arima, that duties I have to do become lonesome.
After this stint is over, let's be glued together to our heart's content.
Glued together.
But maybe at times we might have inappropriate feelings.
Oh, um, yes.
We have crossed the major threshold, and yet, what's with his purity?
Do you want to be with me?
Yes.
I don't know why, but Arima, sometimes you look like you're someone else.
You think so?
Is it a little strange? Am I scary?
No.
Please don't let me go.
Day by day, I am falling apart.
Falling into the dark side
How can you say such a thing?
To want to have you all to myself.
I'd truly love to free you.
On the other hand, I want to take you away from everything.
I don't want anyone to know that I have such feelings.
Stage 8
Student Guidance Room
Sorry, I'm late.
Oh, you're working hard.
Cheese.
Kicking back
Beauty King
Yukino, you're working hard too.
What, are we going to do a reading rehearsal?
Actress Queen
I know all my lines.
I actually wanted to ask Aya-chan something
Actress Queen
Is she here?
About that, but, the situation's changed somewhat.
Doesn't she seem a little nervous?
The novel that she wrote in first semester became so popular...
...that she was accepted to write a monthly for a magazine.
Amazing!
So she's feeling tremendous pressure, and she's been that way ever since yesterday.
Pressure
She's a little on the timid side, so...
I quit! It's no good today.
What, already?
I've been writing and rewriting over and over since yesterday...
...about fifty times, but the perfect lines just don't come.
Really?
There's something going on.
Characters, setting, plot, all these things, if they come to me...
then I can just write smoothly, but if these don't come...
...then I have to keep digging until they do. That's how it is.
I wonder if it's like a slump.
Maybe.
Don't be timid and just write away.
If I write something that I don't enjoy writing, who would enjoy reading it?
The more I cannot write, the more worried I become.
I worry that maybe my writing powers are used up.
She's merely a delicate sixteen year old.
Gosh, writers who can't write are depressing.
You sure you should say that?
You always kick them when they're down.
You can console her sometimes.
She says quite a bit.
Hey, the weather is so nice, why don't we go eat lunch at the river banks?
Materialistic Therapy Method
Aya-chan you too, put some oxygen in your brain.
Gosh it feels so good.
It would feel good to do a rehearsal right here.
that's a great idea.
That's right, maybe making those two into twins would expand the story somewhat.
It seems like it'll work out. Aren't you glad?
Yeah.
What's up? Aren't you going to say, "why don't you just quite the play?"
Um, no.
But if Aya-chan's this busy, we're really in trouble.
What, me? I'm going to do it. I'm the one who started this whole thing.
Yes, yes.
Hey.
Why did you all of a sudden decide to do the play?
You resisted the idea so much at first.
Oh that. Well, I thought that it would be more fun than studying.
I thought that there was something that I wanted to be involved in besides studying.
For me, there is only the world of me and Arima and study.
But for Arima, he has another world besides just us and study, and he goes to the Inter-cups and stuff.
You could say I'm jealous, but I also want to have a world of my own too.
You don't like to lose.
I just think it has to be that way.
And on top of that, Arima likes me.
What? What's with your talking about your love affair? Talking about your love affair?
Arima's world is deeper than mine.
I think that if there is anything that would make me worry or become distressed...
...he would just take it all upon himself.
That's what I thought.
That's why I wanted to just make my own world.
I like to be dependent and pampered by Arima...
...but I don't want to become lazy and complacent.
That's why Arima responds exclusively to Yukino, out of all the girls that he can respond to.
You laugh at me, that's not fair.
I'm always talking about myself. Why don't you tell me about yourself sometime, Maho-san?
No way.
Aw, come on, talk about it!
No I don't want to.
Hey, you lezbos over there, the chimes' ringing.
Stage 9
Contemplating.
For me to understand Arima-kun
I don't understand the falling in love feelings.
Sakura!!
...and... Asaba-kun
Hi. Doing alright?
Don't look the other way.
Of all the classmates, you and I have the worst affinity.
That's because you're just a facade.
Ridiculous!
I'm not just a facade!
You, they say that you only like cute girls.
I can't stand that kind of attitude.
All girls are cute.
Aw, shut up. I just like pretty things, that's all.
It is because of the cruel discernment, that beauty is beauty.
Beauty
Otherwise, it doesn't accord with reason.
It seems that she argues philosophically.
Not so! Absolutely not so!
What does it matter.
Summer clothes are going to be gone this month, so you better get your eyeful.
Look at them.
Look at the momentary brilliant light of those maidens...
...before they go out into the world and are tossed by its rough waves.
Yes, beautiful.
And he too was looking.
And he too was looking
He was looking.
Another parting.
Later
And then, realization.
Oh, Tonami.
And then, an ontological provocation.
FOOOOL!!
Ouch!
Ow, what's with your frightening strength? You're not a woman.
Shut up.
What do you mean by "FOOL"?
Shut up, just said it cause I wanted to say it.
And then, another ontological provocation.
I pity da foo!
Sparkle
Dammit, what's with this irritation
And then.
Unknown actions.
A vague perspective.
Uncertain feelings.
This gal
Was never a kind of person who would be laughing with another guy
It's just that her
personality has
rounded out.
On top of that, she ki...kissed me yesterday.
And she kissed me and...
Feeling a
weird aura
from the back
A sudden question.
Why did I do such a thing?
Disbelief.
No way!
Deception.
Am I a person
who likes men?
Perplexity.
Revelation.
Something remembered.
And panic.
Ultimate question.
Huh?
Complications of memory.
Was Sakura like that? Wasn't she a lot more strong looking...
The moment.
Hmm?
Eternity
There is a link in my mind that is disconnected.
Kindness
Cruelty.
There is something important that is missing.
Hope.
Meaninglessness.
The beginning
What
A beginning that started much too slowly.
Why is she so light?
The beginning of confusion.
Were her arms this thin?
The beginning of suffering.
The beginning of joy.
Yeah, this image of Sakura that's burned into my memory is aggressively more powerful than myself.
The beginning of sadness.
That's why I always thought that she would be absolutely strong.
The beginning of retreat.
Why didn't I realize it all along?
Boink
You.
You help me, then you throw me.
Hey.
He came to realize.
A long time ago, there was no sexual difference between us.
Therefore for the longest time, I haven't been able to name these feelings.
It's a simple matter.
Why did I become so deeply hurt about Sakura thinking nothing of me?
Why did I want Sakura to acknowledge my existence so much?
Why am I unhappy when Sakura is with another guy?
Because I love her.
At the limits of differences.
All this time,
in my heart,
these feelings that
had nowhere to go...
At the limits of boundaries.
To wish, unto the future.
To go unto happiness.
And thus, His and Her Story
Will continue.