nakushita yakusoku wa hoshi ni
Send the lost promises to the stars
omoide wa tokenai
My memories won't fade away
yotsuba no clover sagashinagara kimi no kao
I steal a glance at you as we look for four-leaf clovers,
chirari nusumi mite wa me o sorasu
But then divert my eyes
yasashii ame wa furu watashitachi no ue ni
The gentle rain falls above our heads
surechigau hito no kazu dake dramatic ni naru no
as it becomes as dramatic as the number of people passing by
kowareta taisetsu na mono to
I wonder if we'll ever be able to
itsuka mata aeru hi ga kurukashira
reunite with those precious things that were broken
nokoshita kizuato ga kienai
The scars that were left behind won't go away
sorezore no basho made
Now we must depart
mou ikanakucha
To our own separate ways
Here! They're done!
H-Hagu-chan, what is this dish called?
Pump-Mint.
I arranged mint chocolate ice cream
on top of a microwaved pumpkin.
It's good!
Guys don't like pumpkin as it is, and she's stuffing
it with something even worse like mint chocolate!
D-Doesn't this make you feel like you're eating
chocolate while brushing your teeth?
I wonder if Yamada-san and Hagu-chan always eat things like this...
There's no way.
This is so good!
You'll make a great wife, Hagu-chan.
Oh no, you're embarrassing me, Ayu.
Oh, that's right. I need to give some to Shuu-chan, too.
Here you go, Shuu-chan.
Please eat a lot and do your best at work.
Namu...
Namu: short for Namuamidabutsu ("I sincerely believe in
Amitabha"). Roughly equivalent to the Christian "Amen."
Hagu-chan!
You can't do that!
This is wrong! You're acting like he's dead!
Here! Please eat a lot!
Hagu-chan, may I ask what those yellow
bits that are mixed in with the rice are?
Yeah. This is grapefruit-seasoned rice.
Please pour this boiled whole-apple curry on it and eat.
So you ate food like this all the time, Hanamoto-sensei?
And you've always eaten it obediently, haven't you?
I respect you so much!
But Hanamoto-sensei is so cool.
It's been four months already, hasn't it?
Mongolia, huh? That's amazing.
It's like a man's dream adventure.
I wonder if Shuu-chan is eating well...
What if he lost weight because he doesn't like the food over there?
No, I'm sure he's eating fine.
He might have actually gained weight.
Senpai! Don't say that!
I'm sure Sensei is doing his best, so you'll
have to work just as hard, Hagu-chan.
The school festival is coming up soon.
We need to send him pictures of your work.
Yeah. I'll do my best.
The school festival, huh?
It'll never stand out if you don't make something large.
What should I do?
I still need to finish three more blueprints and two models.
Suffer all you want.
Sheesh. You're becoming all lax because you've graduated!
May I have some more?
You ate it all, Morita-san?!
And he's asking for seconds?!
Morita-san, you have the heart of a hero!
Hey, do seventh graders need to attend the school festival, too?
Of course!
What else should I make?
Ha... Hagu!
What's wrong with this man?
He's been crying for two weeks straight.
Is he sick?
In a way, yes.
Hanamoto, I was an idiot for bringing you along.
Hagu!
By the way, why did we gather tonight?
It wasn't a party to show off our cooking skills?
Was it Health-Sports Day?
Health-Sports Day: an official holiday in Japan (second Monday of October).
It's my birthday.
Get a hold of yourself! Want some Pump-Mint?
Hey!
It's okay.
I'm used to things like this already.
Well then, shall I reveal my special menu?
Though I don't have the ingredients...
I-I'll go buy us a cake!
I already have a present!
Why are you going into my room?!
10 minutes
later
Here, Takemoto-kun. It's a present for you!
My paints!
And what in the world is this?
The game of Twister...
I think.
What's that?
Oh yeah, there was something like that, wasn't there?
Was the game of Twister like this?
I'm sorry, Takemoto!
Only the convenience store was open!
Project
Outcome
But it'll be a whole cake if we connect all of them!
And here are some candles... these were all I could find.
Altar Candles
Hey, Mayama...
How do you play Twister?
I think two people play by placing their hands and
feet on the colors that are called out in turns.
How do you decide the colors?
With these!
I made these and figured we could just draw cards to decide.
Morita-san, aren't there a little too many colors?
I think there's usually just red, blue, yellow, and green.
I figured the more colors, the better.
Well then, we're starting.
First, Morita-san on yellow.
Here.
Next, Takemoto-kun on green.
Okay.
Next, red.
Blue for Takemoto-kun.
Okay.
Purple for Morita-san.
All right.
Next, Takemoto-kun on pink.
Okay.
Note: The thing on the moon is two rabbits making rice cakes. Japanese
people think that's what the dark spots on the moon look like.
Morita-san on orange.
All right!
Takemoto-kun on beige.
Okay!
Morita-san on ocher.
O-Okay!
Takemoto-kun on lapis.
Okay.
Morita-san on white!
Takemoto-kun on black!
Okay!
U-Um...
Isn't today my birthday?
I'm not really happy. In fact, I'm pretty depressed.
Yamada! Yamada!
This is painful... Hurry up and tell us the next color!
Yamada, please hurry and save Takemoto!
Y-You might say that, but...
Next, pale pink.
Gotcha. Pale pink. There!
Next, hurry!
A-At this rate, it's going to turn into a
penalty game instead of a present!
Hold on, Takemoto! I'll help you out!
Having this as your memory of your birthday during
your third year of college is too sorrowful!
That's right! Girls!
Aren't these party games supposed to
be played between guys and girls?
Why aren't you two playing with the birthday boy?
Senpai, that's a nice idea!
Well, we're both wearing skirts.
It's a no-go. I wouldn't want my underwear showing.
Zero Sexiness
I'm sorry, Takemoto. I couldn't help you out.
Yamada! Yamada!
Hurry with the next color!
Hey, Ayu, let's put together a jigsaw puzzle.
Oh, that's so nostalgic. It's a good idea.
Let's use the table over there.
You two change your minds too quickly!
No! You can't!
Takemoto-kun and I are trying so hard!
Are you two demons abandoning us like that?!
Mayama-san, tell us the colors already!
Hurry up and give him the finishing blow!
All right, Takemoto!
Hold on, I'll end your pain soon!
Next, Takemoto, mineral violet!
What kind of color is that, anyway?! That's dubious!
Next, Morita-san, moss green!
Oh, almost! That's permanent green!
Morita-san, it's moss! Moss green!
Is this it?!
Hey, Ayu, how does this game end?
How?
Mayama, how do you end it?
Huh? I don't know.
Mayama! Mayama! Hurry up!
Kill me! Just kill me already!
I see. Thanks, Mom!
You lose when you can't reach your next color,
give up, or lose your balance and fall down!
Okay.
Did you two hear that?
You lose when you can't reach your next color, give up—
I don't care! The next one!
Hurry!
The color... The color of their eyes has changed!
N-Next, carmine red.
Okay!
Opera!
P-P-Permanent yellow deep.
P-Passion blue is next.
W-What are we supposed to do?
Don't ask me that.
It's scary.
Passion blue...
Here you go, Mayama.
Oh, I'm not drinking any more.
Why?
I came on my motor bike.
Bike?
Oh, that's right. You ride that thing to work these days, don't you?
But isn't riding all the way to Meguro
with a 50cc engine a little tough?
No, it's actually really comfortable.
I don't even feel like taking trains anymore.
Your stalking is also a lot easier with a bike, isn't it?
Morita-san! Don't talk about something
that doesn't exist like you've seen it!
Knowing you, I don't need to see it to know.
I mean, we're best—
frie... nds...
I'm going home since I have to go to work early tomorrow!
Drive carefully.
Yep.
Please take care of the rest.
I'm sure that once Takemoto wakes up,
he'll carry Morita-san back with him.
See ya.
Yeah.
I wonder how you're supposed to give up...
Do I just decide to give up and act accordingly?
And move further and further away
from what my heart really wants?
Then will I forget everything someday? The scent of his
brown hair, his cold ear, the warmth of his back...
Everything, including this pain in my heart?
Everything?
Without a trace... as if nothing was there to begin with?
Damn it!
That Morita-san... I need to teach him a lesson once!
What the hell...?
All I do is pass by her place every day on the way back from work,
take a break, drink canned cofffee, and wonder if she's doing well.
It's not like I'm ringing her doorbell.
All I do is look up at her room from outside.
Wait a second...
Could that possibly be stalking?
Damn it! Oh man!
Although they say that a girl becomes more
beautiful when she falls in love...
It's no good for a guy.
Looks like she's still working.
Quietly singing a nostalgic song after brewing coffee...
Ah, she's too far away.
It's wonderful!
Its boldness, detail, and above all, its huge size!
To think that I would be able to see
the birth of two legends at this age!
Oh no, Sensei. You're exaggerating.
Yamada!
With Yamada-kun's graduate thesis and this large bowl...
...as "The Large Bowl vs. the Large Bowl"...
...we will create our department's main exhibit
for the upcoming school festival!
Oh no, the main exhibit?
To begin with, I'm not an undergraduate here anymore.
You can't use a graduate student's work as the main exhibit.
What's okay is okay!
I give my permission!
Yamada! Yamada!
It's okay, right?
The two
are
chums
Well, sure.
Damn it, what is it at an important time like this?
Yes?
Oh! If it isn't Yamada-kun's mother!
Mom?
Yes.
What did you say?!
Your family got wiped out?
Yamada
Liquor Store
Your father, mother, and brother all have
39 °C fevers and can't get out of bed?
We are extremely sorry to say this,
but we will be closed today.
— The store owners
Yeah.
So I'm going home for a bit.
I'm sorry, Hagu-chan.
You'll be alone tonight.
If you're lonely, why don't you ask the landlady
to have Midori-chan come spend the night?
Oh, right!
Who's Midori-chan?
She's a poodle.
She's really cute!
Ayu, say hello to your papa and mama for me!
Bye-bye!
I'm sorry, Hagu-chan. I'll be back tomorrow or the day after!
Bye-bye! Take care!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
See you tomorrow, Hagu-chan.
Yeah!
Bye-bye!
Oh, yeah!
Please make sure to eat dinner!
Yeah.
And make sure to lock the patio door!
And make sure Midori-chan spends the night!
Yeah.
Yamada-san, you sound like a mother.
She'll be fine, Yamada-san.
It's only for one night.
She might not look like that, but Hagu-chan is 19 years old.
Well, that's true.
But... I'm still worried!
I mean, one time my hamster died when I left it for just two days!
My mother was there at her deathbed, but
I couldn't see her before she passed away!
Hamu        Hagu
Hamu as in Hamusutaa - Hamster
Um... Yamada-san... is it really okay to
put those two in the same category?
I mean, I'm really worried.
After all, at night she calls out for Sensei and cries in her sleep.
That's right. Back then...
Hagu-chan seemed to be in high spirits, but her
small, muddy hands were trembling a little.
I wonder how important Hanamoto-sensei is to Hagu-chan...
Now that I think about it, Hagu-chan is always with
Sensei, whether she's at school or at home.
Isn't tonight her first real night alone since she came to Tokyo?
Her first night alone...
How was it for me?
That's right. I had no idea what to do, and...
Hi! I'm Shinobu. What's your name?
Morita-san and the others held a welcome party for me...
...and I...
But there's no one for Hagu-chan right now.
No one.
W-Who is it?
U-Um...
Oh, it's Takemoto-kun! Hold on, I'll open the door.
Come in!
Interpretation:   Who the hell are you?
U-Um...
Who might this lady be?
This is Midori-chan. Isn't she cute?
Y-Yeah, she is.
T-That's right. What am I doing, coming over
to a girl's place at night all of a sudden?
Interpretation: If you try anything funny, I'll fucking kill you.
Takemoto-kun, did you forget something here?
N-No.
U-Um, I was passing by, and... so... um...
Eh? U-Um...
Do you want some tea? Or roasted chestnuts?
Apples?
Or boiled eggs?
Want to put together a jigsaw puzzle?
Yeah... I'm glad I came.
I'm glad.
Oh, hey, Hagu-chan.
I need to go soon.
Why?
W-Why?
Please spend the night here.
And please make me a Versailles kitchen set!
I figured it would be something like that.
Okay? Okay?
O-Okay.
I'll spend the night.
U-Um...
If... If you don't mind...
N-N-N-Next time Yamada-san and Sensei aren't around...
I'll...!
Hagu-chan?
She looks like she'll break if I touch her even a little.
I know that, but something in my heart is struggling.
Shuu-chan, where are my souvenirs?
What is this feeling?
Morita-san!
Will you please sleep in your own room?
I need to wake up early tomorrow, damn it!
akanai mabuta kosutte mieru
I rub my heavy eyelids to reveal
pastel moyou no mirai ni
A future in the shape of pastels
chiribamerareta kigou o tadoru
I follow the scattered symbols
taguri yoseta hyoujou
As my expressions were pulled in closer
nee nandakke sagashiteita mono
Say, what was it that we were looking for again?
are wa soune itsudakke
That's right, exactly when were those days
bokura ga inryoku ni sakarai nagara deatta koro
When we used to meet, denying the attraction
that was forming between us?
sore ga waltz no you dane fushigi sa
It's like a waltz, isn't it? It's quite marveling
sasayaku youna komorebi no kousaten de
We paint away sceneries
futari waltz no youni ne mawari nagara
As we waltz and spin
egaki dashite yuku mono
Where the whispering sunlight falls through the trees and meet.
Next episode: That broach was heavy.