When I was still little...
One day, riding the green bike I always used to ride, I thought...
"How far can I go without turning back?"
I wonder what exactly I was trying to do at that time...
nakushita yakusoku wa hoshi ni
Send the lost promises to the stars
omoide wa tokenai
My memories won't fade away
yotsuba no clover sagashinagara kimi no kao
I steal a glance at you as we look for four-leaf clovers,
chirari nusumi mite wa me o sorasu
But then divert my eyes
yasashii ame wa furu watashitachi no ue ni
The gentle rain falls above our heads
surechigau hito no kazu dake dramatic ni naru no
as it becomes as dramatic as the number of people passing by
kowareta taisetsu na mono to
I wonder if we'll ever be able to
itsuka mata aeru hi ga kurukashira
reunite with those precious things that were broken
nokoshita kizuato ga kienai
The scars that were left behind won't go away
sorezore no basho made
Now we must depart
mou ikanakucha
To our own separate ways
A six-tatami room with no bath, ten minute walk from the college.
Built twenty-five years ago, rent 38,000 yen.
The walls are thin and hardly soundproof.
All residents are students.
The morning sun is bright since it faces east.
I arrived in Tokyo last year after getting into an art college here.
I was surprised to see the campus surrounded by fields...
By the terrible taste of my own cooking...
By the high price of the public baths...
And by the huge amount of homework.
But now it's all just a part of my everyday life.
Mayama-senpai!
Yo, what's up, Takemoto?
Are you full right now?
I've got some croquettes here.
Are there some for me too?
Of course.
Croquettes?!
Can we join?
I've got plenty, so everyone is welcome.
All right!
Do you have any mayo, Senpai?
I'm all out.
Mayo?
Don't tell me you eat even croquettes with mayo, Takemoto.
Is that bad?
Well, not really.
I'll bring some over.
Thank you.
Here's the mayo...
Whoa, that's a lot.
So how did you come across this pile of croquettes?
Well, Morita-senpai told me to share them with everyone...
Morita-san?
Oh, he's back.
Haven't seen him in a while.
Hasn't this guy been gone for like twelve days?
It's been fourteen.
Almost half a month.
I really thought he died somewhere this time.
Now that I think about it, this guy's a bit too shady.
He always just suddenly disappears without saying anything...
And then comes back later looking all worn-out.
He also brings back the most random stuff.
And every time...
There's a mysterious roll of bills in his back pocket.
And it looks like it's getting bigger every time.
Mayama-senpai, what does Morita-senpai do for a job exactly?
I dunno.
He sure is mysterious, isn't he?
If only it were that simple...
Quick! Let me eat those croquettes!
I only have 70 yen left until my next paycheck!
I brought the soy sauce.
I brought some salt.
Hey, those are mine!
Who said that you could take them without asking?
Sup. You think I could get some too?
Go put them back right now!
I brought some Worcestershire sauce.
This is still a damn huge pile.
Probably around ten kilos.
Yeah, I think I'll get sick of eating before it's all gone.
This is from the underground complex at the station.
Looks like he took advantage of the closing time sale too.
Still, why croquettes of all things, Morita-san?
Why croquettes when you have all that money?
Couldn't you have bought for example...
...meat, or meat, or MEAT?!
He must be laughing at us for being so poor!
Don't cry, Hasegawa.
That's exactly what he wants you to do.
It seems like he's looking out for us though.
He did get half with curry and the other half plain.
No, he's probably not looking out for us at all.
But why isn't he sleeping in his own room?
Well, earlier he...
Take this. Share with everyone.
In return, wake me up tomorrow at nine...
Mo-Morita-senpai!
He told me to wake him up in time for his ten o'clock lecture.
It's probably that!
When Morita-san was a freshman, he was an hour short on attendance for a course...
...and so he couldn't graduate and
had to stay back for an extra year.
That must be it!
Morita-san sure is desperate.
Didn't he end up repeating this year too because he overslept?
That means he'll have to attend for a
seventh year if he's late tomorrow?!
Ah, I'm a seventh grader...
That's a huge responsibility...
Seventh grader...
Freshman classes start early, you know.
Plus Morita-senpai usually can't wake up
even with three alarm clocks going off.
No, even six wouldn't be enough.
This is repeat for sure.
No way!
Guys, lend me all the alarm clocks you have!
Don't worry, Takemoto.
Apparently, you can spend up to eight years in college.
That's not the problem here!
I'll be definitely held accountable if he oversleeps.
And when that happens, who knows what he'll do to me...
No!
Be quiet.
What is it?
Cheers!
How did it end up like this?!
We will be momentarily stopping.
Eek! Half past nine!
Senpai, Morita-senpai!
Wake up! It's half past nine already! Please wake up, Senpai!
Morita-senpai!
Ah, you're awake.
Thanks, Takemoto-kun.
Now that I'm awake, let me lie down for five more minutes.
Don't pretend to be wide awake when you're actually sleeping!
I guess it's over.
Mayama-senpai...
Please help me!
Morita-senpai won't even flinch!
Morita-san usually doesn't wake up
for 48 hours after a job, you know.
Just give up and go on ahead to school.
Otherwise you'll end up just like him.
If I do that, my campus life will turn into the
Dark Ages before I even repeat a year!
Morita-senpai, get up!
Well, he has been roughing you up your whole first year.
It looks good on you, Takemoto!
That'll be 1,000 yen!
I'm going to die! He'll kill me!
All right.
Let's give it all we've got.
Coffee
Milk
First we'll try his favorite coffee milk.
It will raise his blood sugar level and stimulate brain activity!
Next...
We'll take a picture of you in front of
the TV as proof of all your efforts.
You should be able to fend away at
least 30% of his curse using this.
All this will only amount to 30%, huh...
Don't worry.
Keep calling his name for the next fifteen minutes.
If he still doesn't wake up after that, just go to school.
I'll let you borrow my kicking board!
You mean the one Morita-san gave you?
Happy birthday, Mayama.
You wanted this, right?
Senpai, what is this?
Come on, can't you tell?
It's a kicking board!
You're not thinking of paying off the 10,000 yen
you borrowed last month with this, are you?
I am.
Well, I don't think I need to...
Well, I'm off to class.
No way!
That's so mean, Mayama-senpai!
Wake him up! You've got fourteen minutes left!
Morita-senpai, please wake up!
The train will be arriving shortly.
Please stand behind the yellow line.
Wh-Why you...
Hagu!
Morita-senpai, wake up! Morita-senpai, wake up!
Morita-senpai, wake up! Wake up, wake up!
Please wake up, Morita-senpai!
Morita-senpai!
Fifteen minutes have passed...
Please don't blame me if you end up repeating again, Senpai!
Repeat?
NO MORE REPEATING!
You!
Kanji on the forehead: "Wind"
S-Senpai!
What the hell is going on...?
Speed
Limit on
Campus
What? Are you hungry?
Oh well.
I'll give you the sausage I didn't finish this morning.
NO...
Here you go...
MORE!
NO...
NO MORE!
NO MORE...
M-Morita-san...
NO MORE!
Then Takemoto...
Hold your horses!
NO...
...more?
You...
You didn't happen to make that scooter out of our trolley, did you?
I knew it!
Thanks to you, we have to carry all the busts by hand.
Do you even know how heavy these things are?
They're fifteen kilos a piece! Fifteen kilos!
Either fix it...
Or pay for the damages!
I didn't do it.
Bullshit.
I'll pretend I didn't see this...
Then who did it?
Mayama-kun did.
Hold up, Mayama?
So you did it?
Well, like it matters who did it now.
Y-You're mistaken...
Go on, compensate!
How cheap...
Hey Mayama, are you listening?
I tell you, I didn't do it...
You can't fool us.
Who else could have possibly done it?
So are you going to fix it or pay for it?
Just in time.
It's the wrong classroom!
Damn it!
Morita-san's got me good this time!
I haven't heard you scream like that in a while, Mayama.
Yeah...
And here I thought I'd finally have some peace of mind...
Since his target changed to Takemoto this year...
S-So was I nothing but a sacrificial offering for the past year?!
That's so mean, Mayama-senpai!
Even Mayama's been roughed up by
Morita for a long time, you know.
Why didn't you ever tell me?!
By the way Hagu, what's a kicking board?
Geez!
Oh, a scooter, huh?
Sensei, who's that little person next to you?
Is she your...
...daughter?
Do you want to fail that bad, Mayama-kun?
This girl is my cousin's daughter!
She'll be attending this school starting this year.
Um, I—
My name is Mayama Takumi.
I'm a fourth year architecture student.
Nice to...
meet... you...
Hanamoto Hagumi, eighteen years old.
She likes to make clothing and play with clay.
Incidentally, her dad is the chief investigator of
Nagano's First Criminal Investigation Section.
He's devoted his life to his daughter for eighteen years...
One false move and you'll be off to kingdom come.
You don't say...
Um...
Would you, um...
like to eat these together?
I... guess you don't.
Aren't you hungry, Hagu?
I see.
So Morita's got some fishy job going on, eh?
Big-hearted as usual, aren't you Hagu?
Isn't she cute?
Here you go.
Ah, thank you.
The cherry blossoms will be blooming soon.
It's gotten quite warm.
How peaceful, really.
He's right.
It's so quiet and relaxing,
but at the same time a bit restless...
Yes.
It's spring.
Such small hands...
Hey, Takemoto...
Ah, I see.
This is...
This is the first time I've seen the moment
when someone falls in love.
Oh geez.
What am I embarrassed about?
It's spring, isn't it?
Indeed.
What?
Are you still hungry?
Oh well.
I guess I'll give you the fish cake I have left over from lunch.
Here you go.
Must be spring.
Indeed.
Ceramics   Workshop
Well done, Yamada-kun!
Such brilliant finger movements.
Ceramics is all about communicating with the clay.
Its voice, however, is very quiet and feeble.
Only those who empty their hearts and
stay true to themselves can hear it.
Say, did you hear about Mayama from architecture?
Mayama?
At that last party Yumi was all...
Again?
What do you mean again?
Mayama is quite notorious you know.
Really? What should I do?
I'm the one who asked her to go out with us...
What's wrong, Yamada-kun?
Ya-Ya-Yamada-kun!
Ah, Morita-san.
Hey, Morita.
Thanks for the croquettes...
Thanks for waking me up, Takemoto-kun.
I can finally graduate.
Thank goodness.
Morita-san!
What you did earlier was...
Did you grow taller again, Mayama?
Are you still in your growth period?
Get real.
Geez, people like you...!
Morita-san?
Hello?
Senpai?
Are you running away, Morita-san?
hitori munashiku bisuketto no
After spending days alone, watching my biscuit go soggy
shiketteru hibi wo hete
deatta kimi ga hajimete no
You laid bare your feeling for the first time
kokoro sarakedaseru
suteki na koibito hachimitsu tokashiteyuku
The wonderful lover melts honey
kogoeru koinu o atatamete
Warming up the shivering puppy
natsukashii asobi ga yomigaeru no wa
We are reminded of our nostalgic ways
akari no basho made tsunawatari shitakara
As we play tight rope to the lamp post
garakuta bakari p-coat no poketto ni shinobasete
Hiding it in her pea coat pocket full of junk
Oh, he's back.
ijippari shy na onna no ko
The headstrong shy girl gives me an angry look
boku o niramitsukeru
Hold this.
okashi na koibito hachimitsu tokashiteyuku
The funny lover melts honey
Hold this!
chouchou musubi o hodoku you ni
To undo the butterfly ties
Korobokkur!
Korobokkur: little people from Ainu legends.
(Litterally "a person under a butterbur leaf.")
mezurashii houseki ga hiroenai nara
If we can't find any rare jewels
Koro...bok...kur...?
What's that supposed to mean?
futari no kakera de maniawaseteshimae
Allow us to get by with pieces of ourselves...
You'll make her cry if you don't stop, Senpai.
Korobokkur, huh?
I guess Hagu's cute no matter what she looks like.
W-What's going on?
When I was still little...
One day, riding the green bike I always used to ride, I thought...
"How far can I go without turning back?"
I wonder what exactly I was trying to do at that time...
akanai mabuta kosutte mieru
I rub my heavy eyelids to reveal
pastel moyou no mirai ni
A future in the shape of pastels
chiribamerareta kigou o tadoru
I follow the scattered symbols
taguri yoseta hyoujou
As my expressions were pulled in closer
nee nandakke sagashiteita mono
Say, what was it that we were looking for again?
are wa soune itsudakke
That's right, exactly when were those days
bokura ga inryoku ni sakarai nagara deatta koro
When we used to meet, denying the attraction
that was forming between us?
sore ga waltz no you dane fushigi sa
It's like a waltz, isn't it? It's quite marveling
sasayaku youna komorebi no kousaten de
We paint away sceneries
futari waltz no youni ne mawari nagara
As we waltz and spin
egaki dashite yuku mono
Where the whispering sunlight falls through the trees and meet.
Next episode: The beginning of two loves.