nakushita yakusoku wa hoshi ni
Send the lost promises to the stars
omoide wa tokenai
My memories won't fade away
yotsuba no clover sagashinagara kimi no kao
I steal a glance at you as we look for four-leaf clovers,
chirari nusumi mite wa me o sorasu
But then divert my eyes
yasashii ame wa furu watashitachi no ue ni
The gentle rain falls above our heads
surechigau hito no kazu dake dramatic ni naru no
as it becomes as dramatic as the number of people passing by
kowareta taisetsu na mono to
I wonder if we'll ever be able to
itsuka mata aeru hi ga kurukashira
reunite with those precious things that were broken
nokoshita kizuato ga kienai
The scars that were left behind won't go away
sorezore no basho made
Now we must depart
mou ikanakucha
To our own separate ways
Ah! Mayama!
I'm so sorry!
There was a misunderstanding with my dad.
It's okay.
Yamada
Liquor Store
Damn you, you little brat!
How dare you make my precious daughter cry!
What the hell did you do to my daughter?!
Actually, I'm gonna kill you!
Dad, you idiot!
He just carried me home!
Mayama!
Why are you always jumping to conclusions?
Don't die!
I-I mean...
Twenty-nine broken sake bottles...
Worth 38,000 yen in all.
An angel!
Does your body hurt?
Are you all right?
Well...
The injuries from being thrown around by your dad aren't that bad.
What? Then did you hit yourself somewhere?
No, actually...
My back and muscle pain from carrying you home is far worse.
I mean, you're so heavy!
W-What did you say, you idiot?
How dare you say something like that to a lady!
That aside, Yamada...
Want to go to this?
Matsunoya Inokashira Branch
100 Yen Beef Bowl (regular)
Matsunoya: a pun on Yoshinoya, a popular beef bowl chain.
A 100 yen beef bowl...
A-A beef bowl for breakfast?
I mean, you like them, don't you?
But you said that you'd be too embarrassed to go alone.
But...
Never mind then. I'll go alone.
Mayama doesn't talk to me with a sad face anymore.
Will you split your raw egg with me?
I'm happy about that right now.
Yeah, sure.
But also a little sad.
I'll finish my assignment, spring break will
come, and I'll already be a third year.
I look forward to working with you again next year, Takemoto-kun.
I can't seem to feel like an upperclassman because
you keep sticking around, Morita-san.
Really?
Please don't drink my drink!
I've already finished it!
Finished! Finished! Finished!
Is he going to keep fooling with me even when I'm a third year?
Drank it all up!
In a way, this is Hell.
The endless torture and eternal pain...
Takemoto, come over here for a second.
What is it?
This picture is... from that time?
Isn't she amazing?
This is the world that Hagu-chan sees?
Hagu-chan...
Hey, this is Shinobu-kun.
What an annoying ringtone...
But that aside, "Shinobu-kun"?!
Okay, I'll be right there.
Is it a job?
I'm going to make money!
Hey, Hagu...
Do you remember the big, tanned man with the
white beard who came to visit me last fall?
I remember!
He's your former teacher and wrote the book that you really like!
What are you talking about?!
There's no way the Yamato would lose to the British fleet!
Yamato: flagship of Japan in WWII, one of the largest ships ever built.
We had Yamamoto Isoroku!
Yamamoto Isoroku: commander of the Japanese Navy during WWII.
How dare you make fun of King George V!
Fool!
You're the fool!
I'm not going to think of you as a teacher anymore!
You two drank a lot of alcohol, talked about ships,
had a huge fight, and were both crying.
Well, you don't need to remember things like that.
The man with the white beard is teaching
at a university in Kyoto now, right?
Is he coming over again? Are you going to fight again?
You see, Hagu...
He asked me to help him write a new book.
It's going to take about a year for the research and survey trip.
I'll have to travel back and forth between
Japan, China, and Mongolia.
And during that time, I'll be teaching a class
with that teacher at the university in Kyoto.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
Are you going, Shuu-chan?
I haven't responded yet.
But if I go...
Would you like to come with me, Hagu?
This is amazing no matter how many times I see it.
From hearing your stories, I agree that we
shouldn't leave Hagumi-chan behind.
But even if we do take her with us,
the trip will be pretty tough on her.
And you see, I think that it'll also place
a significant amount of stress on you.
Well, the same goes for me, of course.
But still...
I'm in a bind.
I do get excited when I think about the pictures
she'd draw if she saw foreign lands.
Hagu, come with us.
The change was gradual, so no one noticed it.
No, it might be that no one tried to notice.
Hagu! Hagu!
Hey, Hagu!
Hey!
Shuu-chan...
Have you gotten used to middle school yet?
Have you made any friends?
Isn't the field day pretty soon?
Hagu?
G-Grandma will worry about me. I need to hurry.
I'm home—
Where were you?
Don't I always tell you to come straight home?
As she got old and gradually lost her sight, my great-aunt...
...was no longer the strong and cheerful woman she once was.
Hagu, may I see your drawings again?
T-They're on top of my desk.
This is...!
The yard during an evening shower, among the blooming azalea...
The afternoon moon, the snowy sunset,
and the faraway thunderhead...
But the vast amount of landscape paintings
were all of the same place.
The two of them were quietly losing a place to go
to inside this large old house in a small village.
Hagu...
Would you like to come to my school
once you graduate from high school?
It's full of kids who draw pictures, just like you.
You might even find people you can get along with.
Then you might be able to show your drawings
to each other or make something together.
I met someone there who I get along with.
Unfortunately, I wasn't very good at drawing, but...
But...
I became able to make a lot more things
than when I used to draw by myself.
I was even able to find what I really wanted to do.
So...
Let's go.
It'll be all right, Hagu.
You can do as you please.
You can just make things out of what you think and feel.
And will you take her with you?
I'm a little worried.
You said before that she collapsed again.
Actually...
She said that she's staying.
Shuu-chan, go for it.
I'll stay here.
I'll be fine. I have friends.
Are you lonely?
I was probably surprised.
And the inside of my head became so white, it was pathetic.
I had decided to cherish Hagu as much as I possibly could.
But a part of me was worried.
Was it really a good idea to drag her out to Tokyo?
Yeah.
Will it actually help Hagu?
I wondered if I wasn't just being egoistic.
Yeah.
The cherry blossoms are blooming again, aren't they?
Doesn't it remind you of the time we first met?
Take good care of yourself, okay?
What a clumsy man...
He hasn't changed a bit.
That's why...
...it stings my heart a little.
Huh?
Hagu-chan, where's Sensei?
Oh, that's right. He's departing soon, isn't he?
He must be busy getting ready.
Hagu-chan, have you made requests for souvenirs yet?
Yeah.
Hagu-chan?
It'll be okay.
A year will go by quickly.
And I'm sure that he'll come back to visit during summer vacation.
Yeah.
aojiroki tamagawa ni omoi ukabete
As I let my thoughts drift over the pallid Tama River
Yeah.
You're already working at Fujiwara Design Office, aren't you?
I heard from Takaido-kun.
Yes, they're really working me hard.
They don't hold back.
suberu you ni odayaka ni kyou ga kureteyuku
The day peacefully slides away
Oh, right.
Here.
And...
Mayama-kun?
kaze no tabibito ni akogareta kokoro yo
Oh, the heart enthralled by the traveler of the wind
It's beautiful.
But it's too loose.
minamo no yosei wa tooi hibi no maboroshi
The water fairies are an illusion from the days long past
It's no good.
I can't take it off like this.
Of course. I made it so that you can't take it off.
I'll learn a lot of things and come back someday.
boku no naka ni kimi no naka ni
They're inside of me and inside of you
I'll definitely come back, even if you won't be waiting for me.
So please stay well until then.
Harada-kun...
See? Isn't he a silly boy?
kaze no tabibito ni akogareta kokoro yo
Oh, the heart enthralled by the traveler of the wind
minamo no yosei wa tooi hibi no maboroshi
The water fairies are an illusion from the days long past
boku no naka ni kimi no naka ni
They're inside of me and inside of you
aojiroki tamagawa ni omoi ukabete
As I let my thoughts drift over the pallid Tama River
Yo.
Oh, Mayama-san...
I'm so sleepy.
Are you all right?
Can you make it to Hanamoto-sensei's farewell party?
I'll be there.
Even if I have to crawl there.
We'll be getting together beforehand.
We're starting at around 6 PM.
Okay.
Hagu-chan?
Hey! Hagu-chan!
What are you doing?
A four-leaf clover?
Yeah.
I already made the pouch for the good luck charm.
Now i just have to put the clover in it.
It's so that Shuu-chan can do his best.
It's so that Shuu-chan won't hurt himself or get sick.
It's so that Shuu-chan's dream will come true.
Hagu-chan...
All right!
I'll help out, too.
Really?
Let's find the clover.
Okay!
What are you looking for?
Ayu!
Why are you dressed like that?
Haven't I told you already?
I'm going to be living with Hagu-chan
while Hanamoto-sensei is gone.
Really?
Yeah.
Then you won't be lonely.
Yeah!
So what are you looking for?
No, that's wrong.
Four-leaf clovers are usually around where people walk.
I see.
As to be expected of Ayu!
I bet it's over here!
Let's look for it!
Roger!
There's a wad of money inside my pocket.
Really... If you tap it, the wad of bills will become two.
What? What? What are you doing? What?!
Digging for treasure?!
No!
What in the world are you guys doing?
Mayama! You came at a good time!
You help us look for it, too!
Please.
Look? For what?
A four-leaf clover.
Okay.
What happened? You're all covered in mud.
I made too much food because you were so late.
So hold on.
I bet you're all hungry.
U-Um, Sensei... Hagu-chan...
Hagu-chan wanted to give you a good luck charm—
Shuu-chan...
You see... there wasn't... a four-leaf clover.
Hagu?
W-What should I do? I couldn't find it.
There wasn't anything like it anywhere.
Why?
Everyone helped me look for it, too.
It was so that Shuu-chan's dream would come true.
It was so that you wouldn't hurt yourself or get sick.
It's all right.
Don't say something like "I couldn't find it."
You've already given me so much, Hagu.
And so we all washed our hands and
sat in front of the steaming pot.
As I looked across the table at everyone's faces, I dreamily
remembered the blue sky that I saw from the riverbank.
The day will surely come when everything
ends and turns into a memory.
But...
I'm sure that I'll reminisce about it again and again.
You were there.
Everyone was there.
The day we searched for that one thing, under the blue sky.
And the scent of the wind permeating through the area.
akanai mabuta kosutte mieru
I rub my heavy eyelids to reveal
pastel moyou no mirai ni
A future in the shape of pastels
chiribamerareta kigou o tadoru
I follow the scattered symbols
taguri yoseta hyoujou
As my expressions were pulled in closer
nee nandakke sagashiteita mono
Say, what was it that we were looking for again?
are wa soune itsudakke
That's right, exactly when were those days
bokura ga inryoku ni sakarai nagara deatta koro
When we used to meet, denying the attraction
that was forming between us?
sore ga waltz no you dane fushigi sa
It's like a waltz, isn't it? It's quite marveling
sasayaku youna komorebi no kousaten de
We paint away sceneries
futari waltz no youni ne mawari nagara
As we waltz and spin
egaki dashite yuku mono
Where the whispering sunlight falls through the trees and meet.
Next episode: Unable to leave you alone.