nakushita yakusoku wa hoshi ni
Send the lost promises to the stars
omoide wa tokenai
My memories won't fade away
yotsuba no clover sagashinagara kimi no kao
I steal a glance at you as we look for four-leaf clovers,
chirari nusumi mite wa me o sorasu
But then divert my eyes
yasashii ame wa furu watashitachi no ue ni
The gentle rain falls above our heads
surechigau hito no kazu dake dramatic ni naru no
as it becomes as dramatic as the number of people passing by
kowareta taisetsu na mono to
I wonder if we'll ever be able to
itsuka mata aeru hi ga kurukashira
reunite with those precious things that were broken
nokoshita kizuato ga kienai
The scars that were left behind won't go away
sorezore no basho made
Now we must depart
mou ikanakucha
To our own separate ways
The cicadas and the crickets are crying together...
At ten o'clock at night, too.
Is this summer or fall?
Which is it?
Do cicadas usually cry this late at night?
Hold up, summer's over already?
I didn't get to go anywhere yet...
And this is supposed to be the last
summer break of my student days.
It's almost been a month, hasn't it?
Since what?
Since Hagu-chan went back home.
Hagu-chan's home is in Nagano, right?
I wonder what she'll bring us back...
She'll probably bring back some nozawana...
Nozawana: prickled turnip leaves, soba: buckwheat noodles.
Or maybe some soba...
Area code 0263?
Who is it?
Hello?
H-Hagu-chan?
No, that's okay.
We're just on our way back from the bath.
Yeah.
That's sweet...
Really?
That's sweet and sour at the same time, Takemoto.
Yeah.
Oh?
What do we want?
Yeah. Shuu-chan-sensei is asking whether
you want some nozawana or some soba.
Senpai, she wants to know whether we
want some nozawana or some soba.
Meat!
They want meat.
Then soba it is!
She wants us to come have soba for dinner,
since they're coming back tomorrow.
Soba?
But I guess...
...she's coming back tomorrow.
Hello?
I've never heard her voice over the phone before.
If feels like my ears keep tingling...
Hello?
Huh?
What was that ring tone just now, Mayama-san?
Wasn't it from a movie?
Oh yeah, it's "Moon River."
Mayama-san, that melody just now—
Takemoto, I'm sorry, but take these back for me.
Later.
I wonder what's up with Mayama-san.
It's a woman.
What? Mayama-san had a girlfriend?
Morita-san, do you know who she is?
Morita-san!
Mayama-senpai!
About tonight's soba party...
What are you doing, Morita-san?
I thought I'd try to cut down on my electricity bill...
That doesn't mean you should use someone else's electricity...
You even brought your console...
Do you think people would normally do this to each other?
Actually, you'll die if you sleep with the
air conditioner and the fan running.
You'll freeze to death, you know.
Ah, such warm air.
Are you all right?
Did you catch a cold?
Can you make it to tonight's soba party?
I'll go.
I want to see her face, since it's been a while.
Besides, if I don't take new pictures, I can't update my site...
You're worried about that?!
Geez, that Morita-san...
Mayama-san doesn't seem to be back either.
What should I do about the soba party...
Oh, it's over here.
Shinobu.
We've just received an urgent request.
Care to help us out?
But I have a soba party to go to...
The deadline is the day after tomorrow, 19:00.
They're willing to pay you in cash if you make the deadline.
I'll be glad to accept!
You caught a cold?
I'm fine.
The 246 seems to be backed up due to construction...
Oh well, I guess I'll just have to take the Komazawa pass.
Shinobu.
You should get some sleep now.
It'll be pretty rough until the day after tomorrow.
So... it's just you, Takemoto?
I'm sorry.
They all went somewhere...
No, it's completely okay.
Then we'll just split the treasure...
...between the three of us!
That smells so great!
It's delicious!
Cow's tongue is best when grilled over charcoal...
...with the windows open and the fans on max.
Hagu.
What did I tell you about vegetables and meat?
Ratio two to one.
That's right. Eat your veggies.
You and Hagu-chan seem really close, Sensei.
Well, I've been looking after her since she was born...
And I attended her field days in place of her dad, after all.
So you could say that I half raised her...
...or should I say that she's like a daughter to me?
Oh, so this is your room?
Yup.
You're not listening at all!
The walls are all covered with books.
Shuu-chan loves books.
Why are these chairs stuck together?
This is where I sleep.
So it's a bed...
What are these dolls with dreadlocks?
That's Jenny-chan.
Daddy and Shuu-chan bought them for me when I was little.
I made the clothes.
I see.
You're pretty skillful.
But how did you make this design...?
It's pretty simple.
Want me to make one?
For me?
Just wait a little bit.
She's got long eyelashes.
They're casting a shadow on her cheeks.
I think I'm really having fun right now.
It's one thing for a grown-up man to be playing dolls with a girl...
But when I think about how she can make such splendid
clay statues that even men can't make...
It amazes me that she makes such small
doll clothes with those same hands...
I guess she is quite feminine, after all.
It's done!
A Neolithic woman!
It's just a piece of cloth...
A Paleolithic woman!
I take back what I just said!
The finished ones are here.
What's that?
A wardrobe.
A wardrobe?
Isn't it just a tissue box?
Can it be that you're just not very good with tools?
Do you want me to make you a wardrobe?
Really?
Can you make one?
Well, I am an architecture major...
And I guess I'm quite used to making models...
What kind do you want?
Maybe one of those with the sliding doors?
This one!
Rococo World
R-Rococo style?!
How long does Takemoto intend to stay?
Geez, he still hasn't gone home yet, eh?
But then again, they're pretty quiet now, even though
they were a bit noisy until a while ago...
He couldn't have!
I'm gonna slice you up, Takemoto!
Rococo...
I see.
I'm sorry, Takemoto.
I shouldn't have doubted you for even a fleeting moment.
Versailles...
I'm really sorry.
As a sign of my apology...
...I'll pay for the materials at least...
Versailles...
T-The sun's so bright.
Impossible...
Well, like I was saying, one of our assignments
during high school for summer...
Why am I even trying so hard?
...was on Natsume Souseki's "Kokoro"...
Rococo?!
W-What is it?
Ah, no...
Sorry!
I can't take this!
tora (tiger) + uma (horse) = torauma (trauma)
I can't get the successive Rococo attacks of the Hanamoto family...
Rococo!
tora (tiger) + uma (horse) = torauma (trauma)
...out of my head!
Rococo!
Huh?
Mayama-san...
I'll be waiting then. Call me if you need anything...
Yes.
If I end up borrowing the chair...
I'll come back here in the afternoon.
I'll call you then since I'll need your help.
I understand.
A woman?
Hey, isn't that Mayama?
With an older woman this time, eh?
She even gave him a lift to school?
He must have spent the night out. What a guy.
Yo.
Mayama-san, that woman...
Mayama!
Guard!
You still haven't broken up with her?
Hurry up and end it!
Yamada...
Actually, how many more girls will
have to cry for you to be satisfied?
Yamada! Yamada! Yamada!
It's none of your business!
It sure is!
I couldn't care less about you sowing your wild oats on sterile land...
But stop showing up to socials and taking girls back
home like they're take-out delivery, will you?
How did you...
A friend of mine from another school has been
flooding me with questions about you!
Ouch...
Ouch is right!
What are you taking a picture for?
I finally bought my 4.32 megapixel camera!
Come on now, what are you taking a picture of?
Long time no see, Yamada.
How's Taro doing?
Back when Yamada-san was a freshman...
She ran the six kilometers to school every morning
in order to help her dog Taro on its diet...
Named
...and has earned the nickname "Iron Lady" from her friends.
Iron Lady
Named
Don't change the subject!
Shouldn't you be more respectful when talking to your senpai?
We're in the same grade level!
When did my girl become so hateful?
Mama doesn't remember raising you this way!
Mama my ass!
Morita-san?
Morita-san's... Morita-san's...!
Damn, he got away!
Mayama, you idiot!
Infirmary
I wonder if Morita-san's going to be okay...
A crutch?
Oh, it's that woman...
But why is she here?
It's been a while, Rika.
I am sorry for calling so suddenly.
No, it's completely okay.
How are you?
Not bad.
What about you?
How's work?
Is your body holding up?
Setting my health aside, it's really inconvenient...
...to only be able to use my right arm standing
up, especially when I'm so busy right now.
I can't even take notes by myself. It's really annoying.
Well, just take it easy.
Though it's probably no use telling you that.
Thanks.
But I'm getting along really great since Mayama-kun's around.
Is he being helpful?
Yes, very much so.
That's good.
I was getting worried about it, since I was the
one who introduced him to you, after all.
It goes without saying that he's very dedicated to his work...
But he's also quick-witted and pretty clever.
He's only 22, but he's rather sneaky...
...and deals with people well, so he's a big help to me.
Are you praising him?
I am.
He's the type you can rely on when working together.
I see.
So what was it again? You say you
need a chair for your photo shoot?
Yeah. Two, three days should be enough.
I wonder who that person was.
She seemed pretty close to Sensei...
What are you looking at, Hagu-chan?
I was thinking of eating these with Shuu-chan-sensei.
I don't think he can eat those right now
because he has a guest over, though.
A guest?
Hagu-chan, are you famished by any chance?
How is it?
Is it good?
It's really good!
Mika was really great right then...
First she drew eyebrows on the dog...
Eyebrows?
On a Shiba dog?
Now that I think about it...
I've never seen Hagu-chan hang out
with friends or anything, have I?
And then, I walked all around town like that, I was dog-tired...
Say, why don't we go to Shimokita today?
There's a shop I want to visit there.
And then, Asami's ex-boyfriend showed up there...
I wonder why all CDs cost 3,000 yen a piece...
I'm broke here.
I'm so hungry.
I want some sweet chestnuts.
This Caramel Macchiato really is something, huh?
Hagu-chan?
I think my... stomach hurts!
What's wrong?
Wait a second...
Hagu-chan!
You'll feel better soon, so lie down a little.
Sensei, she left this...
Oh, thanks.
Is she all right?
She'll be fine once she rests.
I see.
Sensei, who was that woman here just now?
You mean Rika?
She's really beautiful, isn't she?
I'll let her know you said that.
Is she Mayama-san's girlfriend?
W-Well, Morita-san said Mayama-san had a girlfriend...
And Mayama-san left and didn't come back after some phone call...
And then this morning he came to school in a taxi with her, and...
Their relationship isn't like that.
More importantly...
Here!
I've bought you the materials and tools
you need to build Hagu's wardrobe.
I got everything that came to my mind.
A semicircle saw, a pen-shaped router...
A 45 degree cutting board and other miscellaneous materials!
I also have this really effective glue...
Rococo!
Why do you always run away when the going gets tough?
Because you keep following me.
That's because you keep running away.
Are you going to just keep running away like that?
What about your job?
Are you just going to keep working at her office?
Why can't you just tell her that you like her?
Are you just going to go with the flow
like that without saying anything?
Say...
Why is it me?
No matter how much you blow steam at me...
I probably won't change.
You're better off finding another guy.
You should stop looking at me.
Hello?
I'll be there right away.
Well, I've got work to do.
You idiot...
Mayama, you idiot!
I've packed the chair.
Thank you.
Should I come with you too?
No, it's okay.
boku no kotoba ga tarinai no nara
If my words are not enough for you,
But there's the chair, and...
I'll call the staff members who are on location. Don't worry.
Sorry that I held you back for three days.
mune wo naifu de saite eguridashite mo ii
You can rip my chest open and cut out the heart with a knife
But you really helped me out, thank you.
I'll call you again. Bye.
kimi no mayoi to iiwake gurai
Even I have noticed
honto wa boku datte kizuiteta no sa
Your excuses and hesitations.
I never told him...
But he already knew how I felt about him.
itsuka mata anna fuu ni dareka wo nikumu no ka na
Will I someday hate someone like that again?
Maybe if she also can't answer...
While already knowing his feelings...
His love may not come true as well.
datoshitara motto motto
If so, then I will more and more embrace you
And my tears just won't stop flowing when I think about it.
dakishimete toge no you ni kokoro ni sasareba ii
And you can pierce my heart like a splinter,
anata ni zutto zutto nokoreba ii
Just as long as I can remain forever in your memories.
What?
You'd better take in some fluid.
You'll shrivel up if you lose too much water.
Mayama's an idiot.
He's all smiles to other people because
he wants to show them his good side...
But when he can't hide his flaws, he
always gets scared and runs away.
He even gave up on that woman thinking that
he can't make her come to him by himself...
He can't do anything because he's afraid that he'll look bad.
He's such an idiot!
A big idiot!
I don't get it.
Why do you like him so much if you know that he's such an idiot?
That's what I want to know!
I just don't get it!
I've always liked him...
I like him, but I can only think of his bad side...
Yet I think I want to hear his voice...
And hold hands with him, you know!
I see.
You're really amazing.
You're in love, aren't you?
In love.
What are you so calmly observing me for?
Why after all this...
It's love!
Love!
akanai mabuta kosutte mieru
I rub my heavy eyelids to reveal
pastel moyou no mirai ni
A future in the shape of pastels
chiribamerareta kigou o tadoru
I follow the scattered symbols
taguri yoseta hyoujou
As my expressions were pulled in closer
nee nandakke sagashiteita mono
Say, what was it that we were looking for again?
are wa soune itsudakke
That's right, exactly when were those days
bokura ga inryoku ni sakarai nagara deatta koro
When we used to meet, denying the attraction
that was forming between us?
sore ga waltz no you dane fushigi sa
It's like a waltz, isn't it? It's quite marveling
sasayaku youna komorebi no kousaten de
We paint away sceneries
futari waltz no youni ne mawari nagara
As we waltz and spin
egaki dashite yuku mono
Where the whispering sunlight falls through the trees and meet.
Next episode: He and she sway.