nakushita yakusoku wa hoshi ni
Send the lost promises to the stars
omoide wa tokenai
My memories won't fade away
yotsuba no clover sagashinagara kimi no kao
I steal a glance at you as we look for four-leaf clovers,
chirari nusumi mite wa me o sorasu
But then divert my eyes
yasashii ame wa furu watashitachi no ue ni
The gentle rain falls above our heads
surechigau hito no kazu dake dramatic ni naru no
as it becomes as dramatic as the number of people passing by
kowareta taisetsu na mono to
I wonder if we'll ever be able to
itsuka mata aeru hi ga kurukashira
reunite with those precious things that were broken
nokoshita kizuato ga kienai
The scars that were left behind won't go away
sorezore no basho made
Now we must depart
mou ikanakucha
To our own separate ways
It's been odd lately.
I'm here, but it doesn't feel like it.
Something to do...
Things I need to do... as soon as possible...
There should've been a lot of them.
M-My nose hurts.
Do I feel foggy because of the allergies I started having this year?
My sight grows fuzzy from the tearing eyes and running nose.
When I come to, I'm always thinking about the past.
Because the cherry blossom petals are
constantly falling in front of me...
...it feels like I'm rewinding and watching
the same video over and over.
Over and over again.
I wonder if Professor Tange is okay...
How heart-breaking... all because he became affiliated with Morita.
Is he repeating the year again?
I'm finally going to be in the same year as Morita-san.
And we'll finally see the birth of a legendary eighth grader.
And where is the very person who made Professor like that?!
Why isn't he pouring Professor some sake—
What is this?
This is...!
Morita Shinobu
M-Morita-san?
Morita's Zundoko bushi of Love
Zundoko-bushi: a popular Japanese song based on a WWII
naval ballad and remade several times over the years.
The final train comes in like it does every night.
It shakes the red lanterns downstairs as it passes by.
He's singing naturally and blending into some strangers' group.
On top of that, it looks like everyone was waiting for him.
He already has speakers and spotlights
set up, and even made his own flyers.
Even though he couldn't finish his graduate thesis on time!
Man, he's doing it again this year?
This is the fifth time I've seen his Gian recital.
Gian: a boy from Doraemon. He can't sing at
all but makes everyone listen to his singing.
Oh, Mayama-san...
Here are some provisions.
Shinobu!
Mayama, what about your company's cherry blossom
viewing? I heard you were appointed the chair.
It was yesterday, but it turned into a mahjong
tournament due to the rain.
It really caught me by surprise.
I was staking out a spot when it started pouring all of a sudden.
Yes, I understand.
Let's switch things over to a mahjong tournament, then.
I'll make a reservation at Tachikawa.
Yes, that's fine.
I guess I'll get going then.
Mayama?
What's wrong? You're spacing out.
Here, have a drink.
Oh, thank you.
There's a flower petal in your cup.
I see. So you drink it along with the petal.
Well, I need to get going.
There's a toast with everyone from the shopping
district soon, so I need to be there.
Hey, Ayu! It's starting!
Ah, now then...
Here's the further prosperity of the Hamadayama
shopping district! Cheers!
Cheers!
And 25 minutes later...
Oh, so that's Mayama?
What's with his fancy glasses? That poser!
Damn that Ayu! She has absolutely no taste in good men!
What's so good about that four-eyes?
Fish Market, third generation
Ramen Restaurant
third generation
Sushi Restaurant
Butcher, third generation
Electronics Store
third generation
Actually, that man has no taste in good women, either!
Even though our beloved Ayu-sama thinks about him so much...
...he's infatuated with some other woman who won't
even look his way and is essentially a stalker.
What's he thinking? It's absolutely unforgivable!
Why, you spendthrift who doesn't even fear God...!
Now, everyone, hold on a second.
Bread Store, third generation
I can respect his spirit.
What did you say, Ippei?
What are you trying to say?
Now look, everyone.
Her cute face as she's sleeping.
And her beautiful legs!
And her pristine heart.
It hasn't changed a bit since she was in elementary school.
No matter how she's hurting herself over an unrequited love...
...that man doesn't flinch, even while
being showered by Ayu-sama's love!
The spirit of that four-eyes for not just gobbling her up, even after
having this cuteness in front of him for four years...
I definitely accept that!
Ippei!
You're absolutely right, Ippei!
As to be expected from the chair of
the Third Generation Association!
Really, you're so...!
All right, let's toast!
To that four-eyes!
Did you catch a cold?
I just felt a chill.
Gosh, what a bother. I'm totally popular!
Amazing! A mountain of tributes.
This can't be true. A big pile of fan letters...
I just don't understand society anymore.
What will become of Japan if a man like this is praised?
By the way, where's Mouse No. 1?
I don't see her.
Man, what the heck? And I was going
to let her join the Chibi-Hamus.
Chibi-Hamus (Little Hamsters): a reference to Mini Moni, a subgroup
of Morning Musume consisting of the youngest members.
Morita-san, did you by chance dote on a dog or cat and
cause it to become neurotic when you were little?
Why, you...! You're so cute!
How did you know?!
Just as I thought.
What the heck, all of you?!
Fine! I won't let you see her when she's wearing this outfit!
Hagu, I'm kinda hungry.
Do you mind if I start eating?
No.
Wow, they're pretty.
Are they rainbow riceballs?
This green riceball!
I thought it had beefsteak plant, but it's actually mint!
Disgu—
It's good.
Hagu, it's really good.
Yeah, it's good.
May I have another one?
Yeah.
Hagu-chan hasn't been lively lately.
Ever since around the time she went out with Morita-san.
I don't know what happened between the two of them.
But she stopped putting that broach with the little bird on her chest.
I wonder if Morita-san has noticed...
Or hasn't he?
Hanamoto-sensei, where's Hagu-chan?
Well, I asked her to buy me a boxed meal...
...but she should've been back already.
Maybe the store is busy.
I'll go take a look.
Yeah, please do.
Sure.
I've found you!
Why, you Hagusuke, Chibi Hamus!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Have you been well? Yeah? That's great!
What is it? Say something.
Want some sunflower seeds?
You don't seem to be well.
It's kinda cold today, isn't it?
That's right! Here.
Look! A rolled mouse!
Oh, there she is!
Hagu-chan!
What?
Hey... Hey, what's wrong?
Hagu-chan?
Oh, no! You're burning up!
S-Sensei! Hagu-chan!
Hagu-chan is in trouble!
Hagu-chan is...!
I like cherry blossoms.
But... why do I feel relieved when they all scatter?
Is it because I'm released from that melancholy
feeling of lamenting their scattering?
Man, you seem to be pretty popular.
Movie
Society
Let's be
popular
Come to the
Tennis Club!
Railroad
Mania
Club
They're all flyers for attracting new freshmen.
Hey, you, want to join the Tennis Club?
You like light music, right?
Second year
Hey, how about it?
You'll be popular!
Let's do it!
You know, I'm already a fourth-year.
T-Takemoto, want some coffee?
Sensei, where's Hagu-chan?
She's still in bed.
It's been a week already.
And her fever is still at 37.4°C.
So it's not going down?
Well, this really isn't anything new.
The day before a school trip...
...right before the awards ceremony for an art exhibit,
or the day of her interview for an art magazine.
Well, I guess it's something like a wisdom fever.
Wisdom fever?
But it sure is taking a while this time.
I wonder if something happened...
Well, she won't tell me anything. I have no idea.
Lately, the pace of her work has been slowing down, too.
Before, I couldn't keep up no matter how
many new canvases I got for her.
Hagu-chan seems to have been feeling down lately.
Yeah, and I have no idea what happened.
There's nothing I can do for her if I don't know the reason.
My little princess's face makes it seem like
she's going to sleep for a hundred years.
A hundred years...
That sounds like the Sleeping Beauty.
Sleeping Beauty, huh?
Then she's not going to wake up unless
she gets that... you know, a prince's...
Yeah, a prince's ki...
Ki...
Kiss?!
The kanji is actually for the fish "Kisu".
S-Sensei!
Wisdom fever
Deduction
Culprit!!!
laid up
Morita
a kiss from
a prince
Sensei...
Sensei... I know, so please... put away that bat with nails.
Moreover, your diagram is in a loop.
Remember when Hagu went shopping with Morita?
She came back that day and dejectedly told me this...
I-It wasn't fun.
She couldn't tell him that she wanted to go to the restroom.
She couldn't even eat in front of him.
That's why she didn't like it.
What an idiot.
It's because she likes him, of course.
I didn't realize it.
I was simply happy that she could be herself in front of me.
The way she happily ate her flan in front of me was adorable.
Being so nervous that even swallowing becomes
difficult when you're with that person...
If that's called love...
Then really...
I must've been in love all by myself.
All by myself.
Huh?
This is odd. You're home early, Mayama-san.
Well, depends on how you look at it.
I'm sorry. So instead of coming home in the morning after
an all-nighter at work, you came back in the evening?
Well, you see, I'm sleepy but hungry.
But maybe I should just go to sleep.
Though I haven't eaten anything since last night.
Mayama-san...
It's no good. His judgment ability is noticeably impaired.
Judgment Ability
Currently dropping
A-All right. I'll go boil some water.
Please hold on.
Oh, but that's...
Let's eat only one.
What? Who was that?
Please enter your access number.
Please enter the keyword.
Please enter your birthday.
Morita-san's room — the one that nobody could see the inside of?!
The one that has been called the "black hole" of this apartment?!
He's bypassing the SASF security at an amazing speed!
Password accepted.
Access granted.
Amazing!
Even Morita-san himself rarely gets access on his first try!
Mayama's Room.
I can't get into my room.
Why, you...!
Confirming voice. Please state your name.
It's me!
"Me" isn't understandable.
Kaoru! It's Kaoru!
Kaoru...
Who was that again?
Don't mess with me! I'm in a hurry here!
I'm gonna break you, stupid machine!
In that case, Kaoru-san, please recite
your three favorite tongue twisters—
Whoa, he's forcing his way in!
T-This is...
Here it is!
Passport...
Morita-san?
Yamamoto!
Get it to Narita in 50 minutes at all costs!
Roger!
This is Hayashi.
Got it? Don't take your eyes off that idiot.
I can't have him getting lost on top of what's already happened.
Yamamoto just left on a motorcycle with the passport.
I'll also head your way.
Passport...
Narita!
Wait!
Um... is Morita-san going somewhere? Why?
Why? For work.
To Los Angeles.
Los Angeles?
America?
When is he coming back?
Who knows? Maybe in half a year?
Half a year?
Please excuse me. I'm in a hurry.
Who are you, anyway?
Getting into someone's car just like that...
I-I'm Morita-san's junior.
No, I'm his friend!
I-I promised to see him off.
Hey, you know...
C-Can't I?
Seatbelt.
Thank... you!
Damn it. We're stuck.
I guess this is it.
How's the passport?
You got it to him on time? I see.
Not so good over here. I'm stuck at
the entrance due to an inspection.
It was a wasted effort.
I'll just turn around.
H-Hey!
I never got his name.
You moron!
What the hell are you thinking?
I don't get it! Why are you always being so selfish?
He has everything I want in the palm of his hand...
...and he doesn't even bother hiding it.
You'll lose all of them like this!
Don't you get it?!
I... my wallet!
That's right! I was in a hurry, so...
Idiot
H-How am I going to get back?
Are you done seeing him off?
H-He was watching?
U-Um... I...
Okay then, shall we go back?
You're riding with me, right?
Thank you very much.
It feels like I've seen him somewhere before.
Rather, he looks just like him when I take a closer look!
E-Excuse me, are you perhaps Morita-san's older brother?
Why would you think that?
You look a lot like him.
How rude!
Please don't compare me to that wild, money-hungry man!
I-I'm sorry. So you're not?
No, I'm his older brother.
Oh, just as I thought.
But if you took away his ability to make money,
he'd just be a paleolithic caveman!
We're short on time, so I'll speed up.
Please watch out... for your neck.
Okay, we've arrived.
U-Uh, thank you very much.
Despite everything, he drove me to my apartment.
He's a good person.
Oh, hold on.
Normal
Highway
Express
Morita Taxi (personal)
yen
That'll be 47,200 yen.
They really are alike! Is it the DNA?!
I'm s-s-sorry.
I just got in without your permission
and even had you drive me home.
But I only have... I... I...
I'm just kidding.
Well then, thank you very much for today.
Bye, Takemoto-kun.
Please keep taking good care of Shinobu.
Why...?
In his address book, Shinobu wrote "Mayama the
intellectual" and "Takemoto the Shiba dog."
When will Morita-san be back?
Well, I can't tell you exactly when.
But considering the amount of work he accepted,
he shouldn't be able to come back so easily.
Do you want him to come back?
Or do you not?
akanai mabuta kosutte mieru
I rub my heavy eyelids to reveal
pastel moyou no mirai ni
A future in the shape of pastels
chiribamerareta kigou o tadoru
I follow the scattered symbols
taguri yoseta hyoujou
As my expressions were pulled in closer
nee nandakke sagashiteita mono
Say, what was it that we were looking for again?
are wa soune itsudakke
That's right, exactly when were those days
bokura ga inryoku ni sakarai nagara deatta koro
When we used to meet, denying the attraction
that was forming between us?
sore ga waltz no you dane fushigi sa
It's like a waltz, isn't it? It's quite marveling
sasayaku youna komorebi no kousaten de
We paint away sceneries
futari waltz no youni ne mawari nagara
As we waltz and spin
egaki dashite yuku mono
Where the whispering sunlight falls through the trees and meet.
Next episode: Wanting to hear just that one word.