nakushita yakusoku wa hoshi ni
Send the lost promises to the stars
omoide wa tokenai
My memories won't fade away
yotsuba no clover sagashinagara kimi no kao
I steal a glance at you as we look for four-leaf clovers,
chirari nusumi mite wa me o sorasu
But then divert my eyes
yasashii ame wa furu watashitachi no ue ni
The gentle rain falls above our heads
surechigau hito no kazu dake dramatic ni naru no
as it becomes as dramatic as the number of people passing by
kowareta taisetsu na mono to
I wonder if we'll ever be able to
itsuka mata aeru hi ga kurukashira
reunite with those precious things that were broken
nokoshita kizuato ga kienai
The scars that were left behind won't go away
sorezore no basho made
Now we must depart
mou ikanakucha
To our own separate ways
Separation!?
Finally
Splitting!?
Special
Report
The Fujiwara Bros,
Charisma in the World of Architecture
[ Older Bro. · Mario
Younger Bro. · Luigi ]
A Melee at the Party Hall!?
Oh, boy. Such a huge article...
As tall and as loud as they are...
And with the outfits they're sporting...
Even after they returned, it's been pretty crazy...
Yeah.
The "talks" really went all the way from there...
Everyone, gather around! We need to talk!
Fujiwara Design is finished!
We're breaking up!
We'll officially announce the splitting
for the Tottori and Tokyo teams.
Please forgive how selfish we're being, and...
Follow after us!
Tottori, huh? That brings back memories...
Well, I bet the current A Team and B Team will
split up between Tokyo and Tottori, but...
Team
But... I'd like to let Tanaka-san, the newlywed, stay in Tokyo...
Tanaka-san
(B-Team)
Heading to Tottori
I don't want to leave my family behind!
Newlywed
Newly-Built Home
In that case, one member from Tokyo team
will automatically get sent to Tottori...
Um... Miwako-san.
So, who should we send?
I'm a little cold, will you please hold me?
Good morning.
Mayama, where did you go last night?
With Rika-san?
I'm going to the storage, so if you have anything
you want to put away, please take it out.
Hey, you punk! What are you ignoring me for?
I won't fall for your provocations.
Damn it, he's learned.
That's no fun. Have you grown up already?
Actually, we already know everything due to Asai-san's fax.
It's not that easy to escape from our twisted maze of love.
But it looks like Asai-san will be out for a while.
If Asai-san ends up retiring like this...
Rika-san will probably quit.
That's not good.
Not good at all.
I still have my ambition of someday working with her.
I'd like her to continue, no matter how.
A Team
Tokyo
B Team
Tottori
Mayama
Nomiya
Miwako
Yamazaki
Nakano
Takaido
Sakajo
Tanaka
But for that, she'll need a replacement for Asai-san.
Then it's decided.
Although it's a risky bet...
Mayama
Sorry about this, Yamada-san.
Are you okay, Ayu?
Every year, when everyone is finishing up their preparations
for the Hamabi Festival, the flu goes around.
Oh, right. How's Takemoto doing?
He doesn't seem to have a cold, but...
In that case, it'll be fine.
Takemoto isn't the only one acting funny at this time of the year.
The graduate thesis and the job hunting...
A time like that comes for every senior.
Just leave him be.
Oh, Hagu-chan.
Drink.
And please eat this.
Okay. Thanks.
That we finished all the jobs that had
been asked of Harada Design?
Did Rika-kun say that?
There are still jobs left.
She must have held back.
Because she knew that you would get worried.
I told her that maybe she should ask you
to come back, but she won't listen.
That she hurt you.
I felt really at ease when I was with him.
I mean, he doesn't know about Harada-kun.
He doesn't know about my past.
That's why when I was with him, I didn't
have to pretend that I'd gotten over it.
I could concentrate on my work without
worrying about anything else.
And all the while, that boy just quietly stood by my side.
I think that I was truly being saved by him.
Ever since that accident, she's been blaming herself.
If she feels any amount of fun or joy,
she's immediately overcome with guilt and
pushes those things away from her.
Mayama-kun, you might just be one of
those things that she pushed away.
But you see, I wonder...
Exactly what blaming yourself and pushing
everything away, I wonder...
Will lead you to?
I wanted to see her.
I couldn't say anything to her, I only wanted to see her.
So I struggled tremendously and desperately...
Even so... I only learned something small.
The pain which tears my heart apart just thinking about it...
That this pain is enough reason for me
not to distance myself from her.
A lot of information has leaked out already, but as of
this December, Fujiwara Design will split into two.
Nakano
Mayama
The teams will be split according to the board.
Mario-san, please hold on a second!
Mayama isn't staying in Tokyo?
I know it's selfish of us.
But I promise you that he'll be treated well.
So please follow our decision.
What is it at a time like this, Leader?
Have all the complicated talks ended?
How about a walk?
I'm sorry.
I can't go with you.
It's time to say goodbye.
President, I'm sorry.
I...
That's right. Just run like that.
Hey, are you okay with that?
That he's quitting so suddenly?
Ah, youth.
It's certainly a green spring.
But it'll get a little lonely.
No, no, isn't it said that you should make your precious child travel?
That's so true.
Hey, Nomiya, Miwako-san! How can
both of you be so calm about it?
Could it be that I'm being left out of the group?
Yes?
Mayama-kun...
Excuse me.
Mayama-kun?
What are you doing?
I heard from Asai-san.
I'll help out.
Can I bring out the desk that I was using before?
You can just treat me as a temporary employee at first.
I'm pushing myself onto you, after all.
But if you think that I'm useful, please employ me here.
What about Fujiwara Design?
I quit.
Well, it's just how things went.
May I borrow these two monitors?
But... that means, Mayama-kun...
I'll go make some coffee.
Please have some while it's hot.
Why, Mayama-kun?
Didn't I tell you when I left this place?
That I'll come back, even if you're not waiting?
I already said this at the hospital, but I'll say it again.
Please employ me at Harada Design.
I should be more useful than I was before.
The same thing will happen.
I'll end up hurting you again...
It's okay, you can hurt me.
Because I won't be hurt.
The moon calls for her.
In a sweet and endless melody.
But I gently cover her ears.
That's why I came back to this place.
Wedding Ceremony
Oh, I'm so glad it's sunny.
How merry, really.
Having the ceremony in your hometown is the best.
It's in your neighborhood, so everyone can come.
My, my, look at how nervous Tat-chan looks.
And compared to him, just look at how composed the bride is.
Akemi-chan sure is looking beautiful.
But it sure has been a while since a youngster from
the Hamadayama Shopping District got married.
"Grandma, it's a bride!"
Golly, congratulations, Tatsu!
This is such a joyous occasion!
I'm so happy for you!
How fantastic!
One rival has dropped out!!
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
Banzai!
Ayu...
Now everyone, it's celebration sake!
Banzai!
My, this is so festive!
It's excellent!
You look beautiful, Akemi-chan.
We made the right choice to go with white.
Thank you, Aunt Akiko.
It certainly is a wonderful outfit.
But I wonder if it's okay for me to be wearing
white when this is my second wedding?
Of course!
There's no second or fifth time for a joyous occasion.
You're going to keep working at the bar, right?
You should make a lot of requests from your husband now.
And of course, when you do, order from my store.
Oh! Of course... Auntie.
T-The bride's eyes just shined suspiciously!
Now, now, Grandpa.
Oh, the fearsome Misuzu sisters!
Their family has held a firm grip on the wallets, hearts and secrets
of the men of the Hamadayama Shopping District for 52 years.
They intend on squeezing even more money out of us!
Misuzu
Oldest Sister
Akemi
Second Sister
Machiko
Third Sister
Chouko
Welcome!
Second Generation Hostess
Mizue
It's great that we got the first groom out of
the Third Generation Association, but...
So it's Tatsukichi from the sushi restaurant...
They're probably going to start conning us into ordering
expensive sushi now for the rest of our lives...
Sushikichi
Hello? Tatsukichi-san? A party of six, please!
Wow, Tatsu-niichan!
A-Ayu!
Here's some celebration sake!
Congrats.
I'm really happy for you.
I'm happy, but a little... l-l-lonely...
Tatsu-niichan!
A-Ayu!
Now see here, Ayu, Tatsu-san is mine now.
You shouldn't touch him so easily anymore.
A-Ayu...
Hey now, Ayu, how many drinks have you had?
This girl is the biggest problem.
It's also problematic that she doesn't realize it.
Now, now, don't cry, Tatsukichi-san.
I'll make you happy!
I'm s-sorry...
I've always cared about Ayu!
It'll be all your fault, Ayu, if the Hamadayama Shopping
District goes extinct after the third generation.
Ayu is mine!
No, she's mine!
No, mine!
She's mine!
I won't let you have Ayu, she's mine!
Ayu, don't be depressed about failed love for too long.
Switch your mindset and start looking
for a new man and a new job.
Don't be causing problems for your parents for long either.
O-Okay, Akemi-neechan...
That's a good girl.
But in this day and age, there aren't
that many good men or good jobs.
Well, if you really run out of a place to go, come to my place.
We can start Misuzu Store No. 2.
A-Again!
The bride's eyes just shined suspiciously!
The night before the Hamabi Festival
Huh...
This is...
He made a tall object, that's for sure...
I wonder if this was done on purpose?
It looks as if it's about to collapse, but it's not collapsing.
This is Takemoto-kun's?
He has great techniques, but he's a little
lacking in the creativity department...
He's a serious, hard-working student...
but how should we judge this work?
Oh, I'm sorry, professors.
There are so many displays this year, aren't there?
Oh, Hanamoto-kun.
Is this Takemoto-kun's?
That's right. Isn't it a masterpiece?
And this is the title.
Sign: The Tower of Adolescence — Takemoto Yuuta
Oh, indeed!
Now that you mention it...!
This is random yet refined...!
The lack of planning, yet the stoicism that I sense in it...!
Oh, I can understand it!
I understand it.
It really makes me reminisce about those
days when I was so confused as well!
Those days when I kept struggling and striving,
even though I didn't even know who I was!
What's happening? I can't stop the tears...
Me too!
Do your best, Takemoto-kun!
I give this an 80!
No, a 90!
I'm sorry, Takemoto.
I just couldn't hold back anymore.
Yamada
Liquor Store
Good evening.
G-Good evening.
Y-You finished the one from the other day already?
You've been coming around a lot lately...
Oh, really?
Well then, what should I get tonight?
Oh, that's right.
I want to deposit your pay, so can you give me
your account number and cell phone number?
I don't have one.
Moreover, for things like that, if you could
just go through Mayama like usual...
Oh, that's right.
You hadn't heard yet that Mayama quit, Yamada-san?
Huh? He quit?
When?
Two weeks ago?
Why?
Do you know about Rika-san?
The Day of Hamabi Festival
I wonder what happened to Yamada-senpai?
It looks like she's burned out...
I hear she passed out at her store last night.
W-What in the world happened to her?
Let's just leave her be for now...
Oh, poor thing...
Welcome!
Takoyaki
Soba
The Holy Sanctuary of Crepes
The Last Supper
Crepe
Drink
Takemoto Yuuta
The Tower
of
Adolescence
The objet moved!
objet = curio; a novel, possibly bizarre art object
Huh? It's started already?
Pocket warmers?
Ayu.
Ayu!
Yes?
Ayu! I need to talk to you!
Huh?
Ayu!
What are you doing?
U-Um...
Ask Yamada-san.
W-What? You were proposed to by four guys at once?
Yeah...
I see. Well, I don't know what to say...
And so you ran away from them, Yamada-san?
Yeah...
But the four are all older guys from the shopping district
that you've been friends with from long ago, right?
Yeah...
Isn't there anyone among them that you think is kind of nice?
I-I mean... we've always been together since we
were little, and t-they've always been so nice...
I-I just never thought of them like that...
Why does it turn out like this?
We've always been friends and things were going great...
Why do they need to say something like that now?
If they didn't tell me that they liked me,
we could've been friends forever...
Ayu?
Yamada-san already knew how everyone felt.
Stop looking at me.
No matter how many times you get angry
at me, I probably won't change.
Why did you have to fall in love with me?
I... I...!
Ayu...
Sensei...
I see, so you heard about Mayama...
I'd always thought that Mayama was an idiot and a jerk.
I wondered, why can't he like me when
I've liked him so much for so long?
But...
Then in my case...
If the guys from the shopping district pressed me, "Why
aren't we good enough, when we like you so much?"
If they said, "We've liked you for so long,
you need to choose one of us."
What would you do if they said that?
I can't choose one.
They're precious to me.
They're really precious to me!
But I can't ever do that.
I finally understand.
This is how Mayama must have felt... that's why...
It'd be a lot quicker if you just found another man.
Hey, Sensei...
What should I say to everyone?
Do I need to tell everyone now, what I hated to have myself told?
You can only keep trying or give up.
These are the only two choices we humans ever have.
All you can do is to tell them your honest feelings.
The rest is up to them.
To keep trying, or to give up.
Then it'll be their turn to choose.
Wasn't it the same for you?
It's the same for everyone.
I lied about one thing to Yamada-san.
There are actually three choices.
But a path will open up easier when you
believe that there are only two choices.
I won't mention the third choice.
waratta kao ni tsukekomare
Taken advantage of by his smiling face
kuchi ni shita sake ni aorarete, oh
Stimulated by the alcohol she drank
sora misereta toki ururunda face
The tear that wells up when she's shown otherwise
ki ga sukkari sono ki ni natteru
She'd already become all for it
atama kakaete
Holding her head
yume da to omoikonde mo
Even if she tries to pretend that it was a dream
monogataru kare no paper
His paper tells a different story
shiroku samete
Becoming white and discolored
kumo no ue nobori
Ascending above the clouds
gin iro natsu tsunda yoru
The silvery summer's night she was picked up on
shimetsukerareru mistake kienai
She's being constricted by a mistake that won't go away
Next episode: I don't even know my own feelings.