nakushita yakusoku wa hoshi ni
Send the lost promises to the stars
omoide wa tokenai
My memories won't fade away
yotsuba no clover sagashinagara kimi no kao
I steal a glance at you as we look for four-leaf clovers,
chirari nusumi mite wa me o sorasu
But then divert my eyes
yasashii ame wa furu watashitachi no ue ni
The gentle rain falls above our heads
surechigau hito no kazu dake dramatic ni naru no
as it becomes as dramatic as the number of people passing by
kowareta taisetsu na mono to
I wonder if we'll ever be able to
itsuka mata aeru hi ga kurukashira
reunite with those precious things that were broken
nokoshita kizuato ga kienai
The scars that were left behind won't go away
sorezore no basho made
Now we must depart
mou ikanakucha
To our own separate ways
It's dawn...
What nice weather...
Although this light is already torturous...
Mayama, please close the curtain! I'm going to turn into sand!
I can't see the screen...
I'm back!
"Oh, this voice is...!"
Oh, man! That totally woke me up.
Massages sure are nice.
What's with all the tired faces?
You should go get a massage.
I have discount tickets.
Now, let's aim for another lively day of work!
Monkel is a pun on a Japanese energy drink called Yunkel.
Discount tickets to a massage parlor...!
AND a Monkel drink...
On top of that, she's drinking Monkel Royal, marketed
by the industry to people in their fifties...!
That feels good!
"You're wonderful, Miwako-san ☆"
"You're very manly"
My goodness, what's the matter, Leader?
The 7-3 split is a stereotypical Japanese old man hairdo when
they split 70% of their hair one way and 30% the other.
"That (7-3 split ☆) is very cool also"
Oh, so these are what you made the other day?
They're nice.
That's our Nomiya.
You sure are dextrous for a first timer.
On the other hand, your earlier work was better, Mayama.
I just wasn't in the groove that day...
It's because you were too busy getting in our way.
That's right!
I wanted to talk with Yamada-san more.
Yamada is...
You see, she's, well, how should I put it...
A naïve girl, the type you don't see very often these days.
Please don't make any moves on her unless you're serious.
Man, that doesn't sound nice...
He's totally treating us like germs. How rude!
If you're going to say that much, then why
don't you make an attack on her?
"Miwako-san,
"Attack ☆" is an obsolete word"
It seems to me that she likes you, Mayama.
Ah, well, that's...
Then why are you getting in our way?
Why?
Well... I've known her for a while, so...
That's not a valid reason.
That's right! That's right!
Oh, I'll make us some coffee.
Yamada is like a precious friend to me...
So I can't...
Why don't you forget about that and just date her?
You must like her as well, if you think of her as so precious.
You can't share a futon with Takemoto-kun forever.
We sleep in different futons!
Anyway, I'm...!
Aiming for Rika-san?
N-No, I'm not.
First of all, if I was, I would've just stayed there.
Even if it was just part-time or something...
T-That's true...
I mean, if that was the case, you wouldn't
have quit Harada Designs to come here...
Could it be that an issue arose relating to that?
You got too close to Rika-san, things got uncomfortable,
and you couldn't stay around anymore?
Ridiculous!
W-What are you trying to say, Yamazaki-san...?
I-It wasn't like that...
So, please...
P-Please quit already...
Bingo.
Mayama!
What in the world are you thinking?
Rika-san is my idol!
Moreover, how dare you... when she's
been depressed about her husband...!
G-Give up! I give up!
But I don't get it.
Why are you interfering with us when
you're interested in somebody else?
Even we could figure out Yamada-san's feelings,
so there's no way you haven't noticed, right?
And you're not pushing her away, but rather, you're tormenting her.
Maybe it's that you want to keep her "on the bench",
in case your first choice doesn't work out?
What do you mean by that?
"I'll take the unspoiled Yamada-san if Rika-san doesn't work out."
Thinking something like that?
I'm not.
Really?
Not at all.
You said it.
You said that you're not.
I'm going out.
And I'm going straight home from there!
Nomiya-san, where are you going?
Dear me, you should know already without me having to tell you.
I know. Of course I know.
But I'll ask anyway!
Hey! You two! What about your assignments?
They're finished.
By the book, at that.
So fast!
"Miwako-san,
hey, feed me... ☆"
Oh, Mayama. And Nomiya-san...
What's the matter?
The photo shoot suddenly got bumped up.
It's kind of soon, but are the potteries from the other day finished?
I'm sorry that we came up without warning.
It's okay.
Oh, they're over there.
Gotcha.
That's quite an amount.
They're everyone's presentations for the school festival.
School festival, huh?
I'm sorry for coming when you're so busy.
Oh, no, I'm just helping everyone out.
All right.
How's Takemoto doing?
I haven't been going back to the apartment lately.
He's been running around looking for jobs.
And every evening he comes back looking depressed.
He's obsessed with making some tower-like object...
I-I see...
Oh, yeah! And how's Hagu-chan?
Hagu-chan...
All sorts of deities currently visiting
All sorts of people are observing her everyday.
It's a little difficult for me to approach her...
But she's still Hagu-chan on the inside.
I'm sure things will calm down once the Hamabi Festival ends.
Oh, but we still eat together.
We bring the ingredients and cook them here.
Ceramics Second Department
I-I see...
I'm so glad I've graduated already...
That's right! I cooked curry today! Have some with me!
Well, I...
How about you, Nomiya-san?
Oh, can I?
Boy... this is...
But why is the scent of chocolate wafting out of the curry...?
Ta-daa!
And now, the question of the day!
This special curry has a certain hidden ingredient
in it to give it more presence!
I wonder what it could be?
I-It's not hidden at all!
Rather, it's actually manifesting itself all over the place...
Ta-daa!
The answer is: "chocolate"!
Surprised?
So, would you like to have some?
No...
Please don't worry about us...
I see...
That's unfortunate...
And there's so much...
We'll have some!
If it's your home cooking, Yamada-senpai!
I'd like to eat it even if it kills me!
Really?
How does it taste?
I-It's piercing!
It wells up inside me!
I-It surpasses my wildest expectations!
"Piercing"? "Wells up"?
Those are some dubious expressions, but
I sense something sharp coming out...
Now then, let's wrap it up.
Yamada, can you hold it up at that end?
You're really wrapping it up carefully.
Well, these things have no replacements.
I see.
No, Mayama. That goes in B.
Oh, I see. Thanks.
You're really hopeless, Mayama.
Sheesh, you're so much trouble.
I apologize.
That's the last of them.
Oh, it's Miwako-san.
Yes, this is Mayama.
The model?
I'm sorry, Mayama. The leg on the desk
in the meeting room buckled...
So please come right away!
Nomiya-san, there's an emergency
situation for the meeting at nine.
It's being held at Yotsuya, right?
The train would be quicker.
I understand. I'm off.
All right, I'm counting on you.
See you, Mayama.
And why are you so amicably waving your hand with her?
What the hell? I get it already!
Damn that Mayama, he sure is persistent or something...
Huh? Uh oh, Mayama forgot his coat.
Will he be okay?
It gets pretty chilly at night...
Sorry, I forgot my lighter.
He saw me!
He's from Mayama's company, he'll figure
out that this is Mayama's coat!
Oh, here it is.
Good. I thought I'd lost it.
What should I do? I'm so uncool!
Um, Yamada-san.
How should I smooth this over?
Say, are you hungry?
I'm getting hungry.
If you don't mind, will you accompany me?
B-But...
I also want to talk to you about payments, okay?
Okay then...
Right then, let's go.
I should get my coat...
You're already wearing it.
Yamada-san, do you prefer soba or udon?
Soba, I guess.
Soba, is it?
I know a good place then.
It's a little far, so I'll go by highway.
Oh, okay.
I ended up going out wearing Mayama's coat...
It smells like Mayama.
The scent of other people is mysterious.
It's not like he wears anything special, like cologne...
But I know straight away.
The scent of his shampoo, laundry detergent...
And a little bit of...
This must be tobacco...
U-Um...
I was asleep this whole time so I wasn't aware...
B-But where is this place?
We're in Tateshina.
And that lake that we can see outside is Lake Megami.
Ta-Tateshina?
Yeah, I guess it's in the Nagano prefecture.
I came here once for work.
Now, go ahead and eat.
Fresh Soba
The soba here is really good.
U-Um...
Er...
Here's a souvenir.
Oh, soba? That's nice.
Looks like we're having soba for lunch.
"Miwako-san,
what is that? Is it meat?"
But why a souvenir?
I thought you went with Mayama to go get the
potteries at Hamabi yesterday, Nomiya...?
It says "Tateshina" on it.
That's right. I went there.
With Yamada-san.
Yamada!
What's wrong, Mayama?
I hear that you went to Nagano with Nomiya-san last night?
Y-Yeah...
Why would you do such a thing out of the blue?!
B-But...
He asked if I wanted to eat soba.
I thought that it would be a soba restaurant nearby...
But then I got into his car...
And...
And... I fell asleep...
Y-Y-You fell asleep?!
In a car driven by a guy that you don't really know?
In that dangerous man's car?!
Why are you always so naïve?
You shouldn't show an opening so easily in
front of people you don't know very well!
Mayama, you idiot!
So what? It's none of your business what I do, Mayama!
A-Ayu...!
Yamada-san!
The heels on western boots are dangerous!
I hate this!
I don't care about you anymore!
Hello? Mayama-kun?
Yamada-san said that she doesn't care about you anymore.
Youngsters these days give up on things
at the most inconvenient times...
Ceramics Dept.
Inflammable
Flammable
I did it again...
U-Um, thank you for the meal.
Yamada
Liquor Store
Was it good?
Ah, yes.
Really? I'm glad.
I see, so your family runs a liquor store, Yamada-san.
I'll come buy something later.
Then, good luck with the school festival.
Oh, that's right, the coat.
I'll return it to Mayama for you.
Yamada-kun, the tea! The tea!
Professor... what happened to Yamada-san?
Maybe we should leave her alone for now...
That guy is so mean!
The whole time he must've been snickering at me!
I can't take this anymore...
I hate Mayama and that guy... I hate everyone!
Poor thing.
Yamada-san got one hell of an in-law.
You're too protective.
Yes...
Give her a little more space...
Yamada-san is a grown adult now.
Yes...
Senpai, please do your best!
Please have some of this.
Hey, you freshmen! Return to your stations!
Don't bring gifts without my permission!
She's in the middle of her work right now!
If you have some business with her, put it through me!
W-W-We're sorry...
Scat, scat!
Sheesh.
I look away for just one second...! Stupid brats.
Sensei...
I-I know!
Oh, yeah, Rika mentioned that she saw you a little while ago.
W-Where? When?
Well...
I think she said during the summer.
Could it have been at Hibiya Park?
What, you knew?
I knew it!
So it was her, after all!
You haven't seen her since you quit working there, right?
How long has it been now?
But Rika noticed you as well, huh?
No, it's okay.
I haven't seen her face in over a year.
If I was to meet her suddenly...
I'd probably force myself onto her.
F-Force yourself?!
Mayama, you b-beast!
Say what you want.
Well, but maybe that's okay?
Rather than having this standstill continue,
it might bring a chance to the situation...
And if Rika doesn't like it, then I'm sure she'll punch you and flee...
Sensei, I'm going home!
D-Don't take any rash actions!
I'll cool my head as I go home.
One moonlit night, in the summer of two years ago...
I carried her to her bed after she collapsed
in the shower after work...
And just spent several hours looking up at the sky.
Is her painkiller wearing off?
Rika-san, are you all right?
R-Rika-san?
I was having a scary dream, Harada-kun...
I'm so glad that you're by my side...
And then...
As she awoke from her dream, her eyes
became more and more transparent...
For the first time in my life...
I heard the sound of someone's heart being crushed.
Yes, this is Mayama.
Asai-san?
But it really surprised me to hear that
you've been admitted to a hospital.
It seems I've shocked Rika-kun as well.
She's taken care of all the preparations,
registrations, and my treatment.
I'm very thankful, since I don't have any family.
She's here today as well.
I asked her to run an errand for me.
She should be downstairs.
Mayama-kun...
toganai tsuyogari uso de nurikatameta heya
I looked up at the night sky after slipping away
Will his hospitalization last a while?
nukedashite miageta yozora
From that room painted over with my lies and dull bluffs...
Yes...
Rika-san, will you let me work for Harada Design again?
yojireta kanaami o itsumo no you ni tobikoete
Jumping over the bent chain-link fence like always,
I think I can be of more use now.
katai hodo wo kakete iku
I run on the hard pavement.
I think that Fujiwara Design is a good company.
It's full of young people and works swiftly.
With Asai-san's assistance, I've been able to finish all
the jobs that have been asked of Harada Design.
So now I want to have the opportunity to take care of Asai-san.
nitenai bokura wa hosoi ito de tsunagatte iru
The two of us, so dissimilar, are connected by a slender thread...
I knew it...
yoku aru akai yatsu ja naku
Though it's not the common red one.
That's why...
I tried my hardest to stay away from her, to avoid her.
I knew that if I approached her again without adequate words,
she'd just increase the distance between us again, like now.
ochiatta basho wa ookina ki mo zawameki yande
The place we met was quiet, with even the rustling of the large trees still.
I'm going to his room.
futari no kokyuu no todake ga shimite iku
The air was permeated with only the sound of our breaths.
Stay well.
I knew this.
kimi to asobu daremo inai shigaichi
I play with you in the deserted district...
I need to start over.
Again, from the beginning.
How much longer do I have to...?
me to me ga au tabi warau
And we laugh everytime our eyes meet.
yoru o kakete iku ima wa utanaide
We're running through the night, please don't shoot us just yet.
I'll drive you home.
It's raining pretty hard.
horobi no sadame yabutte kakete iku
Breaking our doomed fate, we run...
Where did you get this car?
It's a rental car.
You borrowed it?
Your motorcycle?
I can't ride it in this rain.
I'll pick it up tomorrow.
Please get in.
Mayama-kun... you're going the wrong way.
Please let me drive for a little bit.
Taking advantage of her immobility...
My selfish self takes the wheel.
yoru o kakete iku ima wa utanaide
We're running through the night, please don't shoot us just yet.
The wiper stirs up my heart...
And repeats its dull sound.
And so...
tooku no akari no hou e kakete iku
Towards the far-off light, we run...
Amidst the orange lights, I was slowly sliding
down the large spiral of Daikoku Pier.
waratta kao ni tsukekomare
Taken advantage of by his smiling face
kuchi ni shita sake ni aorarete, oh
Stimulated by the alcohol she drank
sora misereta toki ururunda face
The tear that wells up when she's shown otherwise
ki ga sukkari sono ki ni natteru
She'd alredy become all for it
atama kakaete
Holding her head
yume da to omoikonde mo
Even if she tries to pretend that it was a dream
monogataru kare no paper
His paper tells a different story
shiroku samete
Becoming white and discolored
kumo no ue nobori
Ascending above the clouds
gin iro natsu tsunda yoru
The silvery summer's night she was picked up on
shimetsukerareru mistake kienai
She's being constricted by a mistake that won't go away
Next episode: The moon is calling for her.