nakushita yakusoku wa hoshi ni
Send the lost promises to the stars
omoide wa tokenai
My memories won't fade away
yotsuba no clover sagashinagara kimi no kao
I steal a glance at you as we look for four-leaf clovers,
chirari nusumi mite wa me o sorasu
But then divert my eyes
yasashii ame wa furu watashitachi no ue ni
The gentle rain falls above our heads
surechigau hito no kazu dake dramatic ni naru no
as it becomes as dramatic as the number of people passing by
kowareta taisetsu na mono to
I wonder if we'll ever be able to
itsuka mata aeru hi ga kurukashira
reunite with those precious things that were broken
nokoshita kizuato ga kienai
The scars that were left behind won't go away
sorezore no basho made
Now we must depart
mou ikanakucha
To our own separate ways
December 29th.
We got on the waterbus and went on a short trip.
37th Hamabi Festival
The school festival, exams, submitting assignments,
and working during Christmas...
Central Avenue Shopping District
Travel Agency
After getting through the busy period from October
until now, we all wanted to get out into the open.
It's so c-c-c-cold!
Whose idea was it to ride on this thing?
My ears are gonna fall off!
It's so cold!
My grandma told me that it was fun to ride when
she came to the city from the country.
But... sorry. She did that during spring.
Well, since we came all this way...
Things like this are sometimes fun, too.
Hama-machi
Ryougoku
Let's see...
This boat departs from Ryougoku, goes under
the Rainbow Bridge, circles around Odaiba...
Hamarikyuu
Odaiba Seaside Park
Tokyo Big Site
Kasai
...and arrives at Kasai at 11:55.
So it's about two hours.
The Sumida River sure has a lot of bridges over it!
Oh, that one's really low!
Can we really go under it?
Huh?
I'm cold!
Screw the view! Let's eat!
I'm gonna freeze to death if I don't raise my blood sugar!
Yay!
Sauce katsu!
katsu: anything fried with bread crumbs.
Beef sausage!
Riceballs!
Kabukiage!
kabukiage: a soy sauce-flavored rice cracker.
Crunchy pickled plums!
Itadakimasu!
That's a huge pile.
This is breakfast, right?
And I wondered why they were taking
so long in the convenience store...
So they were buying all this.
Navigation Course
You may board from designated docks
Greater Edo Leisure Trip Course
Tsunade River - Tokyo Harbor - Ara River - Tsunade Water Gate Tour
Days Operational: Sat Sun
Directions to/from Docks
Ryougoku
Hamarikyuu
Odaiba Seaside Park
Kasai
Approx. 3 min. by foot from
Ryougoku Station east entrance
Approx. 7 min. by foot from
Kikuchi City Square Station
Approx. 5 min. by foot
from Odaiba Station
Approx. 5 min. by foot from
Kasai Seaside Park Station
Seni
Sakurabashi
Ryougoku
Echuu Island
Hirai
Hey, now...
You're really going to eat all this in two hours?
Actually, you might be able to.
Senpai, look at this.
What the?!
This receipt is so long! And the total is huge!
Buying a lot of things at the convenience store can get expensive.
It's because you said that all we needed were hard-boiled
eggs when I offered to make a boxed lunch.
If they say that, maybe we should've made a boxed lunch, after all.
No!
That's not true at all.
Making the girls do so much work is rude.
T-That's right!
And I love hard-boiled eggs!
Me too! I'm happy with just these!
Okay then.
Because if we had let them make the boxed lunch...
...who knows what kind of experimental
boxed lunch would have popped up.
Corn Riceballs
Cinnamon-flavored Fried Chicken
Wieners Boiled in Strawberry Jam
Rolled Egg Wrapped Around Marmalade
Corn Riceballs
Cinnamon-flavored Fried Chicken
What are you whispering about?
I-It's nothing!
Takemoto-kun, let's have some hard-boiled eggs.
Y-You're right, Mayama-senpai.
Wow, it's pretty close.
You don't usually get a chance to see airplanes from below.
Haneda Airport must be that way.
Haneda is the original international Tokyo airport,
before Narita was built in the late 80s.
There are plenty of them flying by.
Did you know, Takemoto?
About 700 airplanes take off from and land at Haneda each day.
700?
Yeah. That adds up to one every two minutes,
even if the airport operates all day long.
That's amazing.
That many people use it?
Going far away and coming from far away...
Everyone must be busy.
Hey, Takemoto...
Did something happen?
N-No, nothing happened!
Geez. What are you saying?
No, you've been acting depressed.
It makes me wonder.
Oh no, really, there's nothing!
No, there's something.
Since just before the Hamabi Festival, to be precise.
You've been down ever since.
Did something happen with Hagu-chan?
You're terrible! I was saving that for last, Morita-san!
I've already eaten it all!
Give it back! Give it back!
Ew! Don't regurgitate it!
I see.
So Morita-san gave her a broach.
Yes.
Takemoto...
kazarazu ni kimi no subete to
Now it feels like I can become one...
W-What is it?
So... what are you going to do?
What am I going to do? Nothing.
So you're totally willing to lose.
mazariaesou sa ima sara ne
...with everything that's you without embellishments.
I don't like this winning and losing stuff.
koibito to yoberu jikan wo
I kept the time we could call each other lovers...
So you won't go into the ring.
You're just forfeiting the game itself.
W-What are you trying to say?!
hoshizuna hitotsu ni tojikometa
...in a grain of sea sand.
I mean, Takemoto...
Just think about it.
It's been almost two years.
Two years?
kotoba ja naku rizumu wa tsuzuku
Not words, but rhythm continues...
Idiot! Two years since you came to like Hagu-chan!
W-W-W-W-Wha...
Well, I've known it since day one.
futari ga mada deau mae kara no
...ever since before we met.
Isn't that right?
kurikaesu nami no koe tsumetai hi to samayou
Hearing the voice of the repeating wave we wander with the cold sun.
Two years is a long time.
furueru kata wo daite
Holding your shivering shoulders...
But you've been by her side this whole time,
and you've become great friends with her.
Even with a difficult girl like her.
dokoni mo modoranai
...I won't go back to anywhere.
All the important things like the trust
you've been building up with her...
"kitto mada owaranai yo" to
Saying, "I'm sure it won't end"...
Are you abandoning them all just because you don't want to fight?
sakana ni narenai sakana to ka
...or telling the tale of the fish that couldn't become a fish...
Mayama-san...
It's not something you should give up on so easily.
ikutsu mono tsukuribanashi de kokoro no ichibu wo uruoshite
...you were wetting a part of my heart with the numerous fairy tales.
Just try to remember the time you've spent with her.
kono umi wa bokura no umi sa
This ocean is our ocean.
kakusareta sekai to tsunagu
It connects us to a hidden world.
namariiro ni kagayaku kono umi wa...
This ocean with its metallic glimmer...
kakusareta...
A hidden...
kotoba ja naku...
Not words...
futari ga mada deau mae kara no
We wander along with the cold sun...
konkuriito ni shimikomu tsumetai hi to samayou
...that has been staining the concrete since before we met.
furueru kata wo daite
Holding your shivering shoulders...
doko ni mo modoranai
...I won't go back to anywhere.
Mayama-san...
Hey, Takemoto...
I...
...think I'm going to puke.
What? You're seasick?!
P-Please get a hold of yourself, Mayama-san!
Here's a towel.
Here's a plastic bag. Here, drink this cola.
Aw, geez.
Why are you so high maintenance?
Thanks, Yamada.
He's dead.
Geez.
And yet he thinks he's reliable when
he's actually hopeless and pathetic.
He's such a fool.
I really don't get it.
Why do you still like a guy like that?
Mayama told me "no", but I can't stop liking him that easily.
And feelings like these don't just slip away and
disappear simply because I can't date him.
Oh no...
This is embarrassing.
I'm so uncool.
That's not true.
Not true at all.
I'm the one who should be embarrassed.
And I'm the one who's uncool.
Thank you for your patience, everyone.
This vessel will arrive at the Kasai Seaside Park shortly.
Whoa, there's nothing here.
And there's nobody around as far as I can tell.
Is this really one of the 23 Tokyo districts?
This place is beyond being a park. It's more like a grassland.
And it looks even more pathetic because
it just opened and is still well kept.
Well, I sure am glad we came. It was a great choice!
This nice, empty pocket formed because most
people decide to hang around one stop away.
squeeze
This place is seriously recommended for a date. Yeah!
M-Mayama, why are you acting so happy?
And why are you always so fanatical?
And in the middle of the grassland is an oddly huge ferris wheel!
That ferris wheel is the second largest in Japan.
Second Largest in Japan!
He sure seems happy.
Hey, there's something wrong here!
We walk and walk, but it's not getting any closer!
Is it running away from us?
Could it just be a mirage?
All right! I'm gonna ride it no matter what!
Hey, Ayu, could it be that they're closed today?
Is that wheel even moving? It looks stopped to me.
Ferris Wheel
This thing is extraordinarily huge.
Or rather...
I feel like it might show up in my dreams.
Oh, it's open!
Great! How much is the ticket?
700 yen?
I haven't been on a ferris wheel in a while!
Oh, wait a second.
This...
...is a four-seater.
Let's ride it already!
Interest?
In love
What's wrong?
Oh, it's just that I don't really like high places.
So I guess I'll pass this time.
Don't run away!
We're all getting on!
Hold on. How long does it take to go around?
Let's see...
Seventeen minutes, it says.
Seventeen minutes?
Then that means that once I'm in the gondola...
...I'll be in a closed-off space for 17 minutes?
Hagu-chan, let's go together!
Okay, Ayu!
M-Mayama-san, why don't the three
guys go on a humble ride together?
Hey now, Morita-san!
What are you thinking?!
You two should get plenty of chatting done!
I'm such a thoughtful person!
Thoughtful Person
(You shouldn't get on so recklessly. You'll get scolded.)
Well then, that does it.
It's awkward.
I wonder why...
Why can't we all just smile all the time?
When I was little, I didn't understand why ferris wheels existed.
They were just sluggish and went high up.
I got bored with it after only one ride.
The roller coaster and the loop slider...
I only paid attention to the thrilling rides.
But...
I kind of understand now.
Ferris wheels are for slowly cutting across
the sky with the person you like.
And maybe saying things like, "Isn't this a little scary?"
I guess.
Hagu-chan, get a hold of yourself!
Hey, Morita-san!
(This is dangerous, so please don't ever copy it. You'll
cause the wheel to have an emergency stop.)
This is so scary!
Hagu-chan, get a hold of yourself!
Hagu-chan!
I-I'm sorry.
What?! I apologized properly!
Gaaaan
This is the first time I've seen you apologize, Morita-san!
What?
How rude! Takemoto, you idiot!
When I thought, "Could it be?"...
...it became funny and I loosened up.
Could it be that Morita-san is also uneasy...
...just like me?
Takemoto-kun, Hagu-chan...
I-It's almost time for our ship. Let's get going.
Yamada...
Here.
T-Thank you.
I don't know what Yamada-san and Mayama-san talked about.
And...
Even though I don't know where all of us are headed...
Wow, this is great!
Looks like the boat is all ours again.
Isn't this beautiful?
This is really strange.
Just a few years ago, we didn't even know
what the others of us looked like.
But now we all spend time together like it's a matter of fact...
...watch the sunset together, and say
things like, "Isn't this beautiful?"
Thinking about stuff like that...
But still...
The sunset I see as I stand next to you...
...is so beautiful that it aches my heart.
So beautiful...
As we carry on like that, a new year is approaching.
akanai mabuta kosutte mieru
I rub my heavy eyelids to reveal
pastel moyou no mirai ni
A future in the shape of pastels
chiribamerareta kigou o tadoru
I follow the scattered symbols
taguri yoseta hyoujou
As my expressions were pulled in closer
nee nandakke sagashiteita mono
Say, what was it that we were looking for again?
are wa soune itsudakke
That's right, exactly when were those days
bokura ga inryoku ni sakarai nagara deatta koro
When we used to meet, denying the attraction
that was forming between us?
sore ga waltz no you dane fushigi sa
It's like a waltz, isn't it? It's quite marveling
sasayaku youna komorebi no kousaten de
We paint away sceneries
futari waltz no youni ne mawari nagara
As we waltz and spin
egaki dashite yuku mono
Where the whispering sunlight falls through the trees and meet.
Next episode: Flung around by love.