nakushita yakusoku wa hoshi ni
Send the lost promises to the stars
omoide wa tokenai
My memories won't fade away
yotsuba no clover sagashinagara kimi no kao
I steal a glance at you as we look for four-leaf clovers,
chirari nusumi mite wa me o sorasu
But then divert my eyes
yasashii ame wa furu watashitachi no ue ni
The gentle rain falls above our heads
surechigau hito no kazu dake dramatic ni naru no
as it becomes as dramatic as the number of people passing by
kowareta taisetsu na mono to
I wonder if we'll ever be able to
itsuka mata aeru hi ga kurukashira
reunite with those precious things that were broken
nokoshita kizuato ga kienai
The scars that were left behind won't go away
sorezore no basho made
Now we must depart
mou ikanakucha
To our own separate ways
It sure is spacious now.
The area that the B Team was using opened up, after all.
It's like a sunroom, isn't it, Leader?
Ah, this is relaxing.
I'm really glad we bought this chair.
Miwako-san has transcended geezerdom and
is now in the realm of the old fogies...
She was pretty fond of Mayama, after all...
It's like her child left the nest, so she suddenly aged...
We'll always be together, right, Leader?
Or maybe she's better like this...
Even if she was like a geezer, she was the focus
of my admiration when I first joined...
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Teshigawara Miwako of the planning department.
Actually, I'm really liking the way Miwako-san is right now...
Hey, Yamazaki-kun...
Y-Yes?
The remodeling quote for the Shirakawa mansion...
The flooring is listed as S.B. Terracotta, but
that can be rather irregular in thickness.
You might want to switch over to ones
that are 2 millimeters thinner.
It'll be a problem if they find out after they
lay it down that the door won't open.
Be careful.
I understand! I'll fix it right away! Yes'm!
Forgive my saying that you're better in your new form!
Your geezer-ness is still in its prime!
That's right, Nomiya...
Yes?
Did you ask Yamada-san to make more bowls?
Oh, she's in the middle of the Hamabi Festival right now.
Oh, the memories.
A school festival, huh?
It's been so long for me I can't even remember.
I'm supposed to ask her again once the Hamabi Festival is over.
Sounds good.
Welcome! Welcome!
Hamabi Festival
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, everyone! Really!
I really love all of you, but, um...
Let's just continue to be friends, or siblings, or like...
But I can't be any more than that...
Um... it's not that I think of you guys as any
more or less than siblings or lovers...
A-Ayu, I think that's enough...
I mean, it's not like that at all...
Please give them a break!
Hey.
Ippei-san...
How's everyone doing?
They're all drained.
Last night, they were all drinking until the sun came up...
I'm sorry...
It's not your fault, Ayu.
I'm sorry for not being able to stop everyone.
It's no good for four guys to ask one girl all at once.
They all knew.
That they'd have to give up some day.
But they're all chickens.
They just couldn't bring themselves to ask you, and it took this long.
By giving this or that for excuses...
I wonder if they won't want to talk to or see me anymore.
You just stay the way you've been, Ayu.
I'm sure everyone's all teary-eyed...
But this is a request from the chairman
of the Third Generation Association.
Please help me out again at Christmas, Ayu.
Along with Hagu-chan, of course.
Sure! I'll do my best.
Are you worried about Takemoto?
Shuu-chan...
He was saying that he only has one interview today...
So he should be back by now.
The closing party will be starting soon.
You're hungry, right, Hagu?
Want to go eat the curry that the architecture
department is serving?
'Kay.
I didn't know what skills I had.
But I knew that I liked making things with my own hands...
And I left my house with only that interest to guide me.
What do you wish to accomplish by joining this company?
Ah, yes! Well...
But four years were too short for me to get to know myself...
And even though I've already begun searching
for jobs, I'm still lost and confused.
But I realized something.
The reason why I'm lost.
It's not because I don't have a map.
What I lack is...
A destination.
As of this moment, the 55th Hamadayama
School of Art School Festival is closing.
Hanamoto-kun! Takemoto-kun's tower is...!
Shuu-chan!
It's in pieces...!
Man, now this is rather extravagant, or something...
Why? Who...?
It's fine.
Usually, only the person who made it could do something like this.
B-But this piece is going to be the foundation
for the evaluation of his graduate thesis...
Well, as for that, look.
You've sure done it, Takemoto-kun!
Confronting yourself and the relentless pursuit of your ideas!
The pure soul that can never be tainted!
And the destruction that inevitably ends it all!
This is truly youth!
There is not one shred of deceit in this title!
The Tower of
Adolescence
Hooray for Takemoto-kun!
We'll give you a 100~
Keep at it,
Takemoto-kun~
Ohhhh
Hooray for youth!
See?
Hamadayama Central Avenue Shopping District
Well then, shall we get started?
Now, I'll be counting on you again this year.
bread and cake
Our goal is to sell 1.2 times what we sold last year!
I'll do my best!
I'll be in high spirits!
Oh...
Macchan!
A-Ayu...
Let's do our best today!
Ayu...
It's okay, Ayu.
Call out to them all you want.
Would you like a Christmas cake?
We have tasty Christmas cakes!
Are you all right, Hagu-chan?
Yeah, I-I'm all right.
Takashi-niichan...
Use this stove.
Ichiro-oniichan...
Warm up your legs with these.
You'll catch the flu.
Aren't you glad, Ayu? They're all so nice.
Right, Ayu?
A plea, God...
Please... please... let everyone become happy...
Welcome! We have a white Christmas!
Please let happiness fall equally upon all of us...
As a special deal, all cakes are 10% off!
What did you say!?
Then I'll sell for 15% off!
Someone, please stop these brats!
Just like this snow...
20% off!
My store will go out of business!
And now, why don't we start off with a toast?
Y-Yeah.
Then, cheers.
Cheers...
Why am I here?
I had the feeling that last year was the last time
we would all gather to celebrate Christmas.
But the belief that came to my mind back then was that I was
supposed to be the one that would be missing this Christmas.
I can tell, Takemoto.
What you're thinking about right now!
What a person like you lacks at a time
like this lies in drinking and eating!
Here, here!
40 minutes later
Banzai for Christmas!
Papayapa!
Note: nonsensical words.
Fubanba!
Okay, the engine's been started.
Shuu-chan, let's play this!
Whoa, the memories!
Oh, good idea.
Okay, Takemoto! I challenge you!
I won't lose!
You're so good, Shuu-chan!
This game is from my generation, you know.
Next, Bajiter Blue!
Alrighty, nice and smooth.
You're so cool, Shuu-chan!
Next is Gamboge Nova!
Next is Gamboge Nova...
This, huh...?
It's a little far...
Crunch...
Shuu-chan!
Sensei!
The ambulance! Call the ambulance!
Shuu-chan!
We only have a month until our graduate thesis is due, right?
Yeah, that's right.
I wonder what Morita-san is going to do about his graduate thesis?
Well, all he has to do is finish up the
back half of that macho statue...
But he's already an eighth grader...
If he doesn't come back...
He'll be expelled?!
expulsion
Well, we can forget about that guy, and...
Takemoto.
Yes, I'll do my best.
It's true that I'm lost right now.
But, no matter how I look at it, my lost self
is also hopelessly an essential part of me.
I need to exert everything that my current self has to offer.
That's all I can do for now.
It seems he's put his doubts behind him.
That's actually sort of a pity...
Has he grown up already?
This is looking good, Takemoto.
Sensei...
Do your best at the interviews, use that energy!
Yes, sir!
6 hours later
It was no good...
As to be expected of the super-depressive...
And with nothing changed, the end of the year came...
And I returned home.
To be precise, to the home of my mother's new husband.
Yo! Happy New Year's!
I was worried about a lot of things, yet acted nonchalant...
In solitude, I ended up going in circles.
But my mother, betraying my predictions,
melted in well with Kazu-san's family.
That's why... if I can graduate and get a job...
O-Ouch... what the...?
I need to work hard...
Work harder...
W-Why are you so transparent, Takemoto?
Here it comes! Here it comes!
I can smell it! The fragrant scent of youth!
And even though that's all that's left to do...
Takemoto-kun!
Oh, Yamada-san, Hagu-chan...
We bought some bread for you...
Th-Thank you...
But I'm not very...
Uh oh, a cold?
Yeah, it seems like it.
Blood
Huh?
E-Eh? Um, I-I'm okay...
Please calm down, Yamada-san, Hagu-chan...
Huh...?
Ta-Takemoto-kun!
Sign: Hamadayama Hospital
Shuu-chan...
Sensei...
Apparently he has a stomach ulcer.
He's gonna be hospitalized for a while.
We should contact his parents...
I already did.
They should be here by evening.
Shuu-chan, what about Takemoto-kun's graduate
thesis? There aren't that many days left...
Well, they'll wait for you in a case like
this, provided you submit a form.
But in Takemoto's case... I wonder what we should do...?
My body feels heavy. My extremeties are cold.
I wonder what this sound is?
Dad?
We're almost at Mom's hospital, Yuuta!
Hang in there!
Dad... please don't rush so much...
You'll collapse first, Dad...
And you just got out of the hospital last month...
I'm glad, Yuuta.
They say you have the measles.
You hadn't had it yet, I guess.
You'll get better soon.
My father died two years later.
K-Kazu-san...
You seemed to be having a nightmare...
Yuuta.
We'll find out the results of the tests tomorrow...
But you'll probably be in the hospital for about a week.
A week?
What should I do?
My graduate thesis isn't done yet...
Don't push yourself so hard, Yuuta.
I've been thinking the entire time on my way here...
And I think you'd be okay studying for another year.
But...
Don't worry about tuition.
Dad left you plenty of money.
I-I can't!
Please don't use that money on something like this.
Don't call it "something like this".
I'm begging you.
Mom...
Sheesh, you two certainly are family.
You're so overly serious and stuff...
She just won't depend on me either.
She says stuff like, "I can't cause you trouble."
But you see, every time she says that, I feel
like she's saying to me, "Leave me alone."
Why can't you ever consider the choice of, "It'll be fine,
Kazu-san has money. Let's ask him for help?"
Kazuo-san.
It's not like I want you to owe me
something or push a favor onto you.
But we came together through fate. I just want
you to let me have a part in your lives.
And a thing like that isn't called "trouble".
Kazu-san...
I...
Please let me study for another year.
Please.
Yeah. Just leave it to me.
Um...
Hagu-chan.
Oh, what a cute girl.
Could she be your girlfriend?
Nope.
Y-Yuuta...
Um, here.
Dear me, thank you.
Mitsu-san.
Then, we'll come again tomorrow!
See ya!
Hagu-chan, I... I've decided to stay in
school for another year and study.
Really?
Yeah.
Then we'll be in the same grade starting from spring?
We'll be able to spend time together again.
Yeah... I look forward to it.
At that moment, I felt as if I talked
to her for the first time in a while.
I had been that absorbed in my own issues.
And during that whole time, she had been worrying about me...
So close to me...
Hagu-chan...
I...
Um... I...
So... um...
Argh, this is so exasperating!
Hang in there, Takemoto-kun!
Crap!
Takemoto-kun! Look, a mini-TV. My gift to you!
Thank you very much...
The reception isn't very good... How about this...?
I'm sorry. Takemoto.
How about this? Or this?
Sorry.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, it's the reception ceremony for the Mocademy Awards!
You're right!
I like this a lot.
Everyone's wearing amazing dresses!
It's like a festival, after all.
Next is the visual effects award.
Space Titanic!
I really want to see this!
I've heard about it. The CG is supposed to be amazing.
The space aliens are really cute!
There they are!
They're a little vicious, but that's what's cute about them!
They look like rats.
Don't they kind of look like Hagu-chan?
T-They don't!
Oh, the acceptance speech is starting.
Yeah, those are fun.
Like how they're always a little strained.
waratta kao ni tsukekomare
Taken advantage of by his smiling face
kuchi ni shita sake ni aorarete, oh
Stimulated by the alcohol she drank
sora misereta toki ururunda face
The tear that wells up when she's shown otherwise
ki ga sukkari sono ki ni natteru
She'd already become all for it
atama kakaete
Holding her head
yume da to omoikonde mo
Even if she tries to pretend that it was a dream
monogataru kare no paper
His paper tells a different story
shiroku samete
Becoming white and discolored
kumo no ue nobori
Ascending above the clouds
gin iro natsu tsunda yoru
The silvery summer's night she was picked up on
shimetsukerareru mistake kienai
She's being constricted by a mistake that won't go away
Next episode: That person came back.