nakushita yakusoku wa hoshi ni
Send the lost promises to the stars
omoide wa tokenai
My memories won't fade away
yotsuba no clover sagashinagara kimi no kao
I steal a glance at you as we look for four-leaf clovers,
chirari nusumi mite wa me o sorasu
But then divert my eyes
yasashii ame wa furu watashitachi no ue ni
The gentle rain falls above our heads
surechigau hito no kazu dake dramatic ni naru no
as it becomes as dramatic as the number of people passing by
kowareta taisetsu na mono to
I wonder if we'll ever be able to
itsuka mata aeru hi ga kurukashira
reunite with those precious things that were broken
nokoshita kizuato ga kienai
The scars that were left behind won't go away
sorezoro no basho made
Now we must depart
mou ikanakucha
To our own separate ways
T-This is...
Could this be...?
Yeah.
Morita left it here yesterday.
I knew it!
And I was wondering what Morita-senpai was trying to do by taking Hagu-chan's footprint...
But then, the other day, he...
Sit on this!
No!
I don't wanna!
I'm sick of this!
Help me, Shuu-chan!
I feel sorry for her.
Morita-san has been chasing after her quite persistently these days.
Stop chasing after me!
He's doing it all for his creation, right?
It only took him two or three days to come up with a new creation.
But he sure did a great job with this.
Why won't you apply this kind of skill to your homework, Morita?
What's Hagu-chan doing now, Sensei?
Well, Morita gave her quite a fright...
So she's locked herself in and is now channeling her
stress into her new piece.
Piece?
I've never seen any of her works.
Could I take a look?
Sure, go ahead.
But be gentle about it, since she's concentrating.
I wonder what she's making.
Let's take a look.
A magnum opus!
Petrified State
How do you like it?
Incredible concentration, isn't it?
She doesn't even drink water when she's like this.
This piece will be displayed in the lobby of a new art museum in Yokohama.
A friend of mine who owns a gallery has been looking
out for Hagu ever since she entered high school.
He's been asking to "get Hagumi-san's work at all costs."
Surprised?
You should be.
I'm surprised every time I look at her works as well.
It just feels like it will come to life any moment...
Birds, flowers, or people...
I often talk with that gallery owner.
He says he'd like to become Hagu just once,
to see the world through her eyes.
"I wonder what it would look like," he says.
That ability to stir such emotions in others...
...is probably what talent truly is.
But still, even her footprints are pretty cute.
What's wrong?
Hagu-chan is amazing, isn't she?
Yeah.
I was a bit surprised too.
I'm in... quite a shock.
I entered college thinking I wanted to accomplish something...
But I haven't yet decided what I want to do in the future.
I haven't thought about anything like that...
So watching Hagu-chan made me fret a bit.
Well, it's kind of like how Morita-senpai looks like he's doing whatever he wants...
But he's actually doing something incredible somewhere...
I'm not quite sure about that guy.
But Mayama-senpai, after graduation you're also going to work
at that store design office you're part-timing at, right?
At Rika-san's place, huh?
Well, I'm not too sure just yet.
Kakiage: vegetables dipped in batter and deep-fried.
Oba-chan, another kakiage, please.
Sure.
Here.
You're still a sophomore, Takemoto.
Don't fret and just try something.
Just try out everything that interests you.
There's a lot of things you can learn easily once you give it a go.
Got it, Senpai.
Teppanyaki: food roasted on a hot iron plate.
Want to throw a big teppanyaki party sometime next week?
We could invite Hagu-chan and the
other people from the apartment.
Sounds good. Let's do it!
Your noodles are getting cold.
Got it. I'm digging in!
Quit splashing the soup!
Hello!
Hagu-chan?
What are you doing?
What's this?
Here.
Hagu's Notebook?
Ah, it's the list of things you want to buy?
Yup.
I see. Mules, bags, dresses...
This is expensive!
I didn't know girls' stuff was so expensive!
Are you really going to buy all this?
It's going to cost you a fortune!
Idiot.
She's making this because she can't affort all of it.
U-Um... sorry...
Good morning!
I'm from Asahido Bookstores...
K-Korobokkur!
Ah, excuse me.
I happened to see a picture on the internet
which looked a lot like you...
On the internet?
It's right here. On this site.
Finally
discovered!?
No!
It's Morita-san's doing!
That's the mushroom stool from that other time!
And isn't this that footprint from the day before yesterday?
Morita-san's pushed this a bit too far though.
The banners are scattered all over the site.
I wonder how much he receives for a click.
It's almost like a trap.
50% of the links lead to ads instead of the next page.
What the? 100,000 hits a day?!
Yes, this site is very popular among the fans.
It's updated regularly, plus more and more secret
pages seem to be popping up these days...
Hagu-chan, get a hold of yourself!
Morita-san...
My guardian angel is Gates Almighty!
That person's still alive, Senpai!
I can't say I didn't expect this...
But it seems like he's always running
into money one way or another...
I'm coming in!
Ah, Morita-san?
Morita-senpai?
This is for you.
It's a paperweight of your footprint.
I want that!
He sure got told.
U-Um... could you please sell that to me?
My footprint paperweight!
Owwie...
A-Are you all right?
Are you injured?
If you're hurt, I'll take you to the nurse...
It's all right.
Don't worry about it.
Wow! That's amazing!
But... what is it?
Oh yeah, Morita-san.
How about a teppanyaki party?
We'll invite professor Hanamoto, Hagu-chan
and the guys from the apartment...
I'm going out to work again tonight.
How long will you be out for this time?
Probably for about a week.
We'll wait for you then.
Okay.
I'll see you in a week then.
You better be back, okay?
I'll put my money on him not coming back.
I'm sure he'll be back.
Shall we go?
Yeah.
I'm Yamada Ayumi.
Hanamoto Hagumi.
Morita-senpai sure is late.
Did he really say he was going to be back in a week?
It's already been nine days.
Maybe his work's holding him up.
Should we just throw the party?
Well... but...
Hagu-chan's coming too, you know.
Let's wait, Senpai.
Morita-san may not look like it, but he likes being with people...
It seemed he was looking forward to it, so he'll be sad if we do that.
So let's wait for him.
O-Okay...
There we go.
Morita-san likes being with people?
Perhaps Takemoto was more mature than I thought he was.
Mature, huh...
Welcome...!
C-Can I help you, Mister?
Here.
Give me a pair that fits this foot.
O-One moment please.
That would be these right here...
How much is it?
That'll be 32,000 yen.
Will you pay with a card or...
Oh, I'm in a hurry, so I'll pay with this.
T-Thank you very much!
Yeah.
I see.
It's going smoothly, eh?
I guess my introduction paid off then.
Oh yeah, one of my relatives is going to our college now.
Hanamoto Hagumi.
moshimo kimi ga inaku natteshimattara
If you were ever to disappear,
I know.
Bye.
Yeah.
tatoeba neko ya imomushi ni natteshimattara
If you were to become a cat or a caterpillar,
Summer is already here.
meso meso to naku yo
I would weep then.
Oh, so you're making that?
demo sono uchi tsugou no ii neta ni shiteshimau ka mo
But maybe I would laugh about it later.
nee dakara kyou wa sou itsumo yori
So, let's talk a lot today,
nagai denwa wo shiyou
Longer than our usual calls.
nantonaku kimi ni ushirometai kara
Since I somehow feel guilty,
yasashiku furumatteokou
I'll be nice to you.
Well, I guess the call was worth it.
moshimo kimi to tomodachi ni natteitara
If we would ever become friends,
I wonder if I'm doing this right...
What do you think, Harada?
shitta fuu na kao de jogenshitekureta nara
If you could give me an advice with a knowing face...
I wonder when Morita-senpai's coming back...
Forget about him already and let's eat some meat.
I'm seriously lacking calories these days.
Senpai?
Takemoto, is the teppanyaki party over yet?
We haven't started yet!
We've been waiting for you, Senpai.
Welcome back.
H-Here.
This is for you guys.
Wow, you brought meat for us?
680 yen per kilo... so you held out for the lowest price, huh?
Good job, Senpai!
Everyone will be really glad.
I'm happy too!
Are they related by a bond of trust by any chance?
What is it?
I'll see you around.
Bye!
I guess she really hates him.
Senpai?
Here you go.
Mules!
They're the pink laminate mules!
They're so cute!
I'm so happy!
Mo-Mo-Morita-san!
Shuu-chan, Shuu-chan!
I've got a pair of mules!
Morita-san!
Hold on!
He's...
He's sleeping?
What should we do?
I'll go back to the apartment and lay him down on a futon for now.
He doesn't look too well, and he probably
won't wake up for another 48 hours.
Let's throw the party after he wakes up, Mayama-senpai.
O-Okay.
Later.
Takemoto, you're a really nice guy!
Even after he put you through all that...
You kind of remind me of Sabu...
Sabu (Faithful Dog)
Akita Breed/4 y.o.
Pink mules!
Cute little mules!
I see, Morita got 'em, eh?
But I wonder where he got a hold of such nostalgic sandals.
All the delinquent girls used to sport them back in the day...
I-It's those mules!
Just how much did Morita-senpai pay for them?
Yay! Yay! Yay!
He's so heavy...
Maybe I should have left the meat in the office refrigerator.
Senpai, Hagu-chan seemed really happy, didn't she?
I'm sure she'll forgive you for putting her on your site.
She's got to.
Those sandals really looked nice on her.
And she was... really... happy.
Huh?
Why am I...
It kind of...
...hurts.
But why...
...is my stomach hurting?
Did I eat something bad?
Or maybe...
...I'm hungry?
Geez, he's heavy!
He's gotten heavier as I slowed down.
I better walk faster.
You've gotten a lot heavier all of a sudden, Morita-senpai.
Are you a konaki-jijii?
Konaki-jijii: a Japanese demon, appears as a baby. After being
picked up, gradually gains weight and crushes the victim.
akanai mabuta kosutte mieru
I rub my heavy eyelids to reveal
pastel moyou no mirai ni
A future in the shape of pastels
chiribamerareta kigou o tadoru
I follow the scattered symbols
taguri yoseta hyoujou
As my expressions were pulled in closer
nee nandakke sagashiteita mono
Say, what was it that we were looking for again?
are wa soune itsudakke
That's right, exactly when were those days
bokura ga inryoku ni sakarai nagara deatta koro
When we used to meet, denying the attraction
that was forming between us?
sore ga waltz no you dane fushigi sa
It's like a waltz, isn't it? It's quite marveling
sasayaku youna komorebi no kousaten de
We paint away sceneries
futari waltz no youni ne mawari nagara
As we waltz and spin
egaki dashite yuku mono
Where the whispering sunlight falls through the trees and meet.
Next episode: They were two unrequited feelings.