A curse corrodes Tomoe's body.
Did you remember?
I'll travel back to when the curse was put 500 years ago.
I'll be intruding.
The Tomoe of this era is a merciless supreme youkai.
The injured Tomoe, who was pursed by the villagers, was found by Nanami.
I know this child. Please help him!
I know you're hiding him!
The woman, that you took in, picked up a wounded child last night, isn't it!?
That's right! That fox is undoubtedly disguised as that child!
That woman is definitely a youkai's underling!
Hand over that woman and brat!
Where's Yukiji-san?
Nanami! Don't go out!
But!
Leave it to Lady Yukiji!
I was the one who picked up that child who was clawed by the fox and had collapsed by the river.
All of this is your fault for failing to hunt down that fox, right?
If you understand, then hurry up and go find that fox!
Yukiji.
If you don't hand over the brat obediently, then you'll be suspected.
Maybe you're actually an ally of the youkai.
I only want to protect you, you know.
You understand, right?
Don't touch me with your filthy hands!
If that kid sleeping inside really is the fox,
there's no need to hand him over to you.
I'll tear him apart with my own hands.
Now, now, everyone. What's all this commotion for?
Master Youhei!
A fox youkai has taken refuge in this house!
Youkai.
Don't say such ridiculous things. There's no way something like that could be in our house.
Isn't that right, Yukiji?
Yes, father.
Yukiji is indeed lowborn, but I adopted her because of her beautiful face.
Right now, she's getting proposals from nobles and rich men.
Youkai or whatnot, such strange rumors are intolerable.
Her image before marriage is important after all.
No one in this house is on Tomoe's side, except me.
The wound hasn't healed yet.
Exactly what is this wound from?
At this rate, he won't last long.
I'm an outsider.
I shouldn't interfere with the past.
So please...
Tomoe!
Open your eyes!
The Fox Falls in Love
It's hot.
The wound's not healing.
What's this?
My body suddenly feels lighter.
Woman.
What did you do?
Lady Yukiji!
What's the matter?
Nothing. And where had you gone leaving this boy behind?
For medicine.
Nanami has a very effective medicine for injuries.
I thought of giving it to him.
Oh...?
Nanami.
Yu-Yukiji-san!
Tomo-! I mean, how is Himetaro's condition?
Right now, Fuuta is giving him the medicine.
And you, why are you sitting in a place like this?
It's okay to watch over him from up close.
No. I...
That kid would feel relieved if he sees you, won't he?
You know that kid, right?
Yes.
I can't appear before him.
Because I can't meddle with the past.
I must go to the capital tomorrow on father's order.
I'll return after work's finished.
I'm leaving Fuuta to help you, so rest assured.
It's nothing important.
Seems like the landlord, who proposed marriage, wants to see me.
To accept his generous betrothal money, I'll dress myself as best as I can and go to him.
A-Are you getting married, Yukiji-san!?
Only if he likes me.
Don't make such a worried face, Nanami.
I...
...am not from this village.
My hometown was attacked by a youkai one day, and everything burned to the ground.
That's why, my parents, siblings and people related to me by blood, no one's in this world now.
However...
I wonder why, with you here, I feel the nostalgic warmth and affection of those bygone days.
Nanami,
marrying is a good thing.
I... will create a family of my own blood.
What's this?
My fever... is going down.
Huh?
You've finally opened your eyes, Himetaro!?
Good for you!
Who's he?
The medicine really worked, right!? You must be hungry, right Himeta!?
Here, your favourite *sasamochi.
*Note: sasamochi= rice cake wrapped in bamboo (sasa) leaves
Eat this and wait for me.
I'll grill the fish I caught this morning.
Where's the woman who made these rice cakes?
The woman who carried me here.
Umm...
Please don't tell him anything about me.
The one who saved you is the lady of this house, Yukiji-sama.
The lady is quite busy.
You should rest now.
That's right...
...she was called Yukiji.
The wound that wouldn't heal...
...is gradually healing.
Just what kind of medicine did I take exactly?
Never mind.
Until I've recovered completely, I shall remain here.
And... that woman...
Is he asleep?
Yes, he's asleep.
He just woke up today after all.
He won't recover so suddenly as he's not a youkai.
Pretends
to sleep
That's true.
Get well soon, Himeta.
When you feel better, I'll take you to a good fishing spot.
Yukiji-sama's fishing skills are quite extraordinary.
So get well soon. Okay?
If she knew that I'm a youkai, she wouldn't be able to stay this calm.
If she knew that I'm a youkai...
Rice cakes again?
...that woman... what kind of face would she make?
Have a safe trip, Yukiji-san.
Please take care, my lady.
Please take care of the rest for me, Fuuta.
Nanami too.
Don't leave in my absence.
It's a promise, okay?
Is he asleep?
He's asleep.
Ah?
He hasn't eaten the sasamochi, Fuuta-kun.
Maybe it wasn't tasty?
I had made new ones.
That's not true.
Himeta was very full during the day, since he ate all the fish I had caught.
Himeta... do they mean me?
His wound is healing.
Just a bit longer.
Himeta is quite strong, even though he doesn't appear to be.
That's true.
After my body recovers...
...I plan to abduct this woman.
But some thing is worrying me.
Why does she... only come every night when I'm asleep.
Is he asleep?
Yes, yes, he is asleep.
I'm not asleep!
W-What's this, so you were awake!
It's already time for kids to go to bed.
Here, I'll change your bandage.
What this?
Won't she come in?
You'll feel all better when you wake up.
Boring...
When her hands touch me...
...I feel so good too.
Nanami?
Hey, Nanami!
Fuuta-kun.
Are you alright? You look pale.
Sorry. My mind was just all fuzzy.
You must be tired, right?
Rest up for a while.
It's already been 3 days since Yukiji-san left.
If everything goes well, she could return by tomorrow.
Hey, Fuuta-kun...
Hm?
Himeta looks fine now.
I was thinking about leaving this place tomorrow.
What? Why?
Yukiji-sama told you to not leave, right?
Sorry.
Thank you for everything till now.
Sorry for troubling you.
Why!?
I'm an outsider.
I must not get in the way of Yukiji-san and others.
Wh-What's with that?
A secret.
Your injury's all healed up, right Himeta?
Why is it?
As promised, I'll take you to the fishing spot tomorrow.
That woman didn't show herself.
Hey brat...
What happened to Yukiji?
Don't address her that way! It's Lady Yukiji!
Honestly, I never thought you'd be so foul mouthed. You're just Himetaro too.
I am not Himetaro.
Then what is your name!!?
Himetaro's fine.
Lady Yukiji is going to a rich man's place in the capital.
They are going to talk about their betrothal there.
Amazing, isn't it!? It's a wealthy household!
Lady Yukiji will become the mistress of a much bigger house than this!
Lady Yukiji is the mistress of this house right now, but
long ago, because youkai set her village on fire, she went through a lot of pain.
That's why, I want lady Yukiji to be happy.
yawn
Tch! This is why you're a brat! Go to sleep!
So she will belong to someone else?
Humans are fragile, break easily and become unable to move.
Being unable to move would mean the end of the game.
Once something is broken, it can't go back to the way it was.
If she's going to be by someone else's side,
I'll make her unable to move again.
This game too... will then be over.
Where is that woman?
Rising and leaving the house at night, where is she going?
So be it.
Now then... how should I toy with her?
Woman,
you have...
...caught my attention.
With that blood and flesh,
entertain me till the end!
What's this?
Humans are fragile, break easily and become unable to move.
Although I intended to toy with her....
...do I...
...want this woman... not to die?
Just now, was there someone behind me?
I must hurry.
My body hurts.
I remember this pain.
My body is starting to scream due to time travelling for this long.
The time for me to return to the present is approaching.
Like this, I can't return to the present without finding the fallen god.
Is here alright?
I don't know if he's a fallen god or not,
but I heard from my grandmother that a fiend lives in a pond at the foot of the mountain, up north of the village.
Long ago, it seems that babies were thrown as sacrifices there.
I don't know whether the one Fuuta-kun talked about was the fallen god that I am searching for.
Fallen God
But...
This is the only way I can get a clue right now.
Please! Somehow... let my body hold on a bit longer.
It's dark.
Though it's still daytime too.
A crying voice?
From where?
It hurts, it hurts!
Fa-Fallen god!
You're the fallen god, aren't you!?
On days when my back hurts a lot, I get in a bad mood.
Don't come over here!
Don't run away! Wait!
My body... won't listen to me!
You're the one who nearly drowned yourself.
It's not my fault, you know.
Fallen god,
please tell me the way to undo Tomoe's curse.
Turning youkai to humans!?
You're saying I made such an arrangement!? That's too much! What an awful, wrong charge!
Not right now, I mean, in the near future.
I'm just quietly living in this pond, is all.
100 years ago, I ate human flesh and now am living as a ghost.
It's so rude to be referred to as a fallen god and such!
To begin with, I don't have the power to convert youkai to humans.
As I thought,
this wasn't the place where the fallen god was.
Tomoe...
What should I do from now on?
Such a trick can't be performed by any god, much less a fallen god.
There's only one being who can do it though.
Kuromaro-dono from Mt. Ontake.
He can change youkai into humans.
Kuromaro from Mt. Ontake?
He's a fallen god of old standing who was called a demon in ancient times.
In terms of power, even Ookuninushi of Izumo couldn't stand his ground against this being.
Where's Mt. Ontake? How can I meet Kuromaro!?
You want to meet him?
Yes!
I'm losing the sensation in my legs!
If you want to meet him, then I shall tell you how.
Really!?
But, not just like that.
If you give me all the peach pills you have, then I shall call on Kuromaro-dono here for you.
Kuromaro-dono will come immediately when he's called.
He'll come while being tailed by the grudges of this world, dying everything pitch black in his wake.
If he arrives, this pond will be tainted with black and become uninhabitable.
Trading with your peach pills is not a bad idea.
What will you do, girl?
I understand.
If doing this will help Tomoe...
Peach pills!
With this my back pain will disappear!
Hurry, call Kuromaro....
Kuromaro-donooooooo!!
I've called him, human goddess.
W-Wait a minute! Where is Kuromaro?
Don't be so anxious. My voice has definitely reached Mt. Ontake.
Look at the sky.
The northern sky is darkening.
What?
I told you.
Kuromaro-dono will come immediately.
He has a lot of spare time.
He's coming.
And he's always yearning for company.
A sinister black.
This is...
He's a lonely being.
Beings of the pond,
do you have any business with this Kuromaro?
My hands are numb.
No!
Just a bit more!
Just a bit more...
I can grasp the key to undo the curse!
In just a while, I'll be able to save Tomoe!
It's okay if my body becomes useless!
If this helps Tomoe...!
My voice... won't come out!
Nanami-san.
What?
My body's being pulled!
Time's up.
Return to the present.
Wait! Just a bit more!
Just a bit more and I can save Tomoe!
In just a bit!
Welcome back, Nanami-san.
That was one long time-travel, right?
Mikage-san.
Ah, don't move so much!
Time travel essentially takes a huge toll on you.
This is Mikage shrine.
You've been sleeping here all night since your return.
Tomoe is still alive.
So it's alright.
Rest well till your strength returns.
Mikage-san, you brought me back, didn't you?
Why?
In just a bit, I would have been able to talk to the fallen god too.
I could have saved Tomoe too!
But if I had left you just like that, your body-
I don't care about my body!
I'm going to go back once more to the past, right now!
It's impossible with your body like that.
I... will save Tomoe all by myself!!
Nanami-san!
You're not alone.
Just like you care for Tomoe,
Tomoe, Mizuki and everyone else care about you.
That's why, you should take better care of yourself.
Don't shoulder everything alone.
Even if everyone is far away, they'll be watching over you.
Mikage-san's gentle voice...
...is soothing my strained feelings.
To go back to the past, you must prepare your physical condition.
First, let's replenish your energy.
Are you hungry yet?
N-Now that you mention it...
Right now, everyone is putting your share of ingredients.
Nanami-chan!
You're late.
Nanami-sama!!
Wha? What's happening everyone? Gathering around like that...!
Well, everyone barged in, you see.
Nanami-sama!!
Onikiri-kun! Kotetsu-kun!
Nanami-chaaan!!
I'm sorry, Nanami-chan.
After that, Mikage-san took me back here.
Mizuki...
I rushed here on hearing that your familiar was in grave danger.
That guy should die once and for all.
If there's anything we could do to help, please tell us, okay?
Ryuu-ou, Kamehime-san...
Nanami.
I heard that you're not feeling well.
This is an excellent restorative handed down in my family.
Kurama...
Follow the directions for your recovery and take your medicine properly. Okay?
And here's a souvenir from Nezumi Land.
Kota chose it.
They're sweets.
So you did go to Nemzumi Land.
So? Where's that damn fox right now?
Oh, Tomoe's in here.
Hey fox! So you're dying? How disappointing!
Repay your debt to me first, then die!!
Dear, please behave yourself!
Honestly, it's just as Ryuu-ou says.
Don't cause hardship for Nanami.
A familiar causing trouble for their master is the worst, Tomoe-kun!
That's correct. Hurry and come back!
Right. I need you to transform me into a human once again.
I want to go to another of those humans' theme park with Kota.
Hi-Himemiko-chan...!
That's how it is, so I'm sorry, but please once again.
Thank you everyone.
I wasn't alone.
Tomoe and I... we both have a home where everyone gathers.
Alright! I'll eat a lot to be able to rush back to the past!
Give me some protein!
Okay! Here's Nanami-chan's share.
There isn't any meat in it!
That's why, return to us soon, okay, Tomoe?
Lately...
...I don't have the will to do anything.
Why is that?
I nearly died, or was it that I was reborn?
Since that day,
did something happen to me?
It's unlike me.
This plight is unlike me.
Akura-ou! Where are you, Akura-ou!?
Let's play!
Yo, brother!
Is it alright?
What? What's alright?
Well, that furball over there,
said that you are lovesick.
Me, in love!?
That's stupid!
I laughed hard on hearing that too!
I told him,
my brother's not an idiot who'd be infatuated by a human woman.
But still, you're late.
I came across something interesting outside.
Seems like a young woman, living in a small village by the river, will be having a bridal procession soon.
Anyway, furball heard them say that she's a great beauty.
Her name was... Yukiji, I think.
There aren't many beauties named Yukiji.
If she's really that beautiful, I thought I'd like to take a look myself.
Just a while ago, I gave out an order to a subordinate on the spot.
I told him to pull out the most well dressed bride from that procession and bring her to me.
That's a boring game.
So? When's the bridal procession?
It's after 3 days.
Right, right.
Don't you want to see her?
I'm not really interested.
Then you don't mind me doing whatever I want, right?
I don't mind.
Okay! I'm leaving!
To the past!
Credits:
Raws-UCCUSS(from nyaa.se)
Translation- KH Addicts
Typesetting, Timing, Minor Script Editing- asckj1
Preview
Nanami travelled into the past for the second time.
Yukiji will be marrying a lord.
However, a youkai targeting Yukiji's life appears.
So, to keep her safe, Nanami suggests to be Yukiji's substitute.
Next time, The God becomes a bride.
What's Tomoe's true intention?