It's snow!
Let's have a snowball fight, Onikiri-kun, Kotetsu-kun!
Oh, no, Nanami-sama!
The kimono, you received from Kamehime-sama, will get soaked.
Hurry~!
It's cold today too.
What!?
What's this?
This is a contract between you and me.
I will turn you into a human,
but on the condition,
that you will marry that woman for life.
What is this?
I will grant your wish.
That voice is constantly echoing in my head.
What is that woman's name?
Who's it talking about?
Tomoe! The shrine gate crumbled!
Tomoe-dono's power, that held the shrine together, seems to be fading!
That means...!
That woman's name is...
Yukiji.
She is to be...
...my lifelong partner.
The God
leaps into the Past
Tomoe-kun!
Tomoe-kun?!
What is this?
Tomoe!
Nanami-chan!
Yukiji...
Eh?
Don't look!
Mizuki...
...help me to my room.
Tomoe-kun...!
Did you remember... Tomoe?
...about Yukiji-san...
Nanami-sama, here are the peach pills!
Tomoe, you'll be alright once you take these-!
That sort of thing won't work.
Move and stay over there!
Tomoe-kun! Hang in there!
What should I do?
Somebody help!
Tomoe will... Tomoe will die!
Did you remember, Tomoe?
It's alright now.
I won't let anyone touch you.
Relax and have a good sleep, Tomoe.
Tomoe?
Don't worry, Nanami-san.
Tomoe is inside this mirror.
How joyous!
Mikage-sama has returned home after 20 years!
A feast! Prepare a feast! Prepare the sake!
Shut up, will-o-wisps!
Nanami-chan is my only master.
Mikage-sama returning home is none of my concern.
Delicious!
As expected from the Yonomori shrine's refined sake.
Let's see... you are Mizuki-kun, right?
Also Nanami-san, thank you for being the Mikage shrine's land god for all this time.
What about Tomoe?
Just what were those marks?
Tomoe's heart has frozen right now and he's sleeping inside the mirror.
But he might not last long.
Eh!?
Those marks are a curse that will kill him.
It's not some sickness.
They have been engraved upon him as a price for an ancient agreement.
Tomoe probably has... only 7 days more.
500 years ago, when I first met Tomoe,
the shadow of death was already on his face.
As I thought. These marks are from a curse cast by a wicked fallen god.
You made some kind of contract with a fallen god, didn't you?
I vowed to spend my entire life with a human woman I loved.
Because that woman died, I can't go on living.
But I failed to become a human, so I can't go to the place where Yukiji is, even if I die.
That human girl, did you really like her that much?
I loved her.
More than anyone.
No matter what price I would need to pay,
I wanted to be with her.
If you are a god as you say, will you look after me in my final moments?
Such a pitiful child.
But you don't have to die.
Let me lend you a hand.
The weakened you doesn't know how to heal yourself.
Every time the sun rises and sets, the pain in your heart will slowly heal.
You'll slowly forget.
It's the power of the oblivion.
Although I stopped the curse by making him forget,
Tomoe still remembered.
About Yukiji-san.
The curse, this time, will definitely end up killing him.
No...!
I don't want that!!!
If him remembering it might lead to his death, we just have to make him forget once again, right!?
Eh...?
If he forgets about Yukiji-san, he'll be saved, right!?
Let me see Tomoe!
Nanami-san!
Nanami-san, please return it-
Don't come in!
Tomoe doesn't want you to see his troubled self.
Because he cares for you more than anyone else.
Won't you consider his feelings?
That's a lie! Didn't you say earlier, that even I could save Tomoe?
You said you wanted him to bond with humans!
But Tomoe still doesn't want anything to do with humans.
He has no interest in them!
He's still attached to you.
He won't even take my hand.
He's always looking down on humans and saying harsh things.
But I love such a Tomoe, a lot!
It's not a lie, Nanami-san.
Tomoe loves you.
Because he fell in love with a human, my spell was broken.
Because he loves you, his memories of Yukiji returned.
Because he adores you, my spell was broken.
I feel very happy.
Because Tomoe came to love a human once more.
Thank you, Nanami-san.
Tomoe...!
Tomoe!
Oh no, since I've come back, you don't have to hold back on my account.
Because Nanami-san is this shrine's god right now.
Your sake is really delicious!
Tomoe-kun is on the verge of death! Is this any time to enjoy drinking!?
Fine.
I beg you! Please help Tomoe-kun!
I too want to save him.
I desperately pondered over it for a long time.
But it's impossible!
Pissed
This is all that I can do.
You, too, should do what you can.
I can't do anything.
Not even Mikage-san can remove the curse.
There's no way I can do that.
Nanami-sama...
Tomoe...
As expected, it definitely suits you.
When he gave me this hairpin in autumn, he was still healthy.
That time's...
...the Tomoe from that time...
...That time's...
That...
Nanami-sama, please don't blame yourself like this!
There are things that can't be helped!
That time...
That's right! The Tomoe from that time! The Tomoe from long ago!
Nanami-sama!!
For Tomoe-kun's sake... for Nanami-chan's sake... something I can do...
If I can travel to the past using the time travelling censer and prevent him from making the contract,
then Tomoe won't be killed. The contract will become invalid.
I'll definitely save Tomoe!
Nanami-sama!!!
Excuse me, Mikage-san!
I'll go to the past and stop Tomoe's contract.
I'll use Mizuki's time travelling censer,
Wait a moment, Nanami-sama.
You can't simply go and change the past.
The flow of time is a domain that even the gods must not meddle with.
B-But!
Because the past exists, the present does too.
If the contract had never existed, Tomoe might never have come to this shrine.
Which means, you might be throwing away the future of you meeting Tomoe.
Meeting Tomoe would not exist...?
But... even then...!
That's better than him dying like this!
I want to save him!
Calm down, there still are 6 days, aren't there?
That!!
That's enough!
Mizuki, please take out the time travelling censer.
About that...
Mizuki-dono, with a sombre look on his face, took the censer and went somewhere.
Taking the censer?
Ah!
If Tomoe-kun hadn't come,
I'd still be at the Yonomori shrine, looking at the plum tree, sitting alone like this.
It's lonely, Nanami-chan.
Even then, if it saves Tomoe-kun, if it makes Nanami-chan smile,
I'll carry you to the past.
Mizuki!
You idiot.
Abandoning Mizuki, I could never do something like that!
That which must not change, is not the past, but the present.
For that sake, I'll go back to the past.
The fallen god who made the contract with Tomoe,
would definitely know of a way to undo the curse.
I'll meet the fallen god and bring the key to break the curse.
Be careful, Nanami-chan.
500 years ago is too different from today's world.
If you sense even the slightest danger, please return back immediately.
It's an absolute promise.
Yeah.
The past won't change,
because our fates are all connected by it.
I'm glad.
You finally did it.
Realizing it by yourself is what was important.
Let's meet again later.
Aota's army has a 1000 men, ours has 2000.
Let us settle this before morning, my lord.
Hmph! Our army at Karakuri Castle is equipped and our opponent is not.
Crush the rabble in one go-!
MY LORD!!
Move!
I've kept you all waiting, haven't I?
From now on, I, Akura-ou-sama, will be your army's general.
A DEMON!!
You fiend! How dare you do that to our lord!!
What's that? Looks amazing.
Fire!
Those sticks sure are extremely loud.
I love loud things a lot too.
M-Monster! Help!!
Tomoe...
What the hell!? Don't interfere with my game of siege.
Akura-ou, your body might be immortal,
but that kimono isn't! Return my haori!
It looked fit for a lord...
There's a hole in it now!
Where are you going!? Stay close by!
I'm leaving for 2/3 days.
Till then, you'd better finish your foolish game.
Tch, such an unsociable guy.
For the sake of saving Tomoe, I came to the past, but...
...currently, I am...
...all tied up.
She looks like an ordinary girl, but,
there are pretty looking *youkai too.
*Note: youkai=supernatural beings
I already told you, I'm not a youkai!
Don't lie!
You're an underling of that youkai named Tomoe, right?
Tomoe!?
That face says you know him, isn't it?
This one is definitely a youkai.
Why!?
The men of this village were all informed.
Through a dazzling light in a dream, the voice of god was heard.
To regain our peaceful lives from before, we must exterminate youkai.
First, we start with the leader,
the fox youkai, Tomoe that is!
Tomoe is!?
Ouch-!
This means that god is on mankind's side.
So then, tell me where the fox's lair is!
I don't know anything about that.
Tomoe is being targeted by a god...
If you don't want to be burned, cough up the location of the fox's lair!
You're in the way, everyone.
Huh!?
Well, well, aren't you all loud during the day?
What are you all doing with a lone girl?
The beautiful person... I'd seen that time.
There's no mistake.
This person is...
...Yukiji-san.
It's none of your business! Women shouldn't enter the jail house!
That girl's a woman too, isn't she?
Idiot, this one's a youkai.
That's wrong!
Youkai?
Are you a youkai?
T-That's wrong.
What hate-filled eyes...!
This person... despises youkai!
Is that so...?
That's what she says.
You caught the wrong one. Untie her.
WHAT!?
This one knows about that youkai named Tomoe!
It's because you lot are announcing it all over the village.
If you were called by the voice of the god, how about hurrying to get the youkai's head?
You're just a woman! What's with that tone of speaking!?
Hmph! For taking birth from just a woman's womb, you, too, shouldn't be talking that way.
You there, Sukeroku, aren't you?
Yes!
Will you help me untie that girl?
Yes, Yukiji-san!
Suke!!
Are you alright?
Please forgive them.
Those guys have never really seen a youkai before.
You're not from this village, are you?
Where have you come from?
This person is...
...Yukiji-san.
The person whom Tomoe loves enough to even die for.
What is it?
It's frustrating, but...
...I can understand.
Ouch!
Did they hit you on the face?
It's a mystery...
Why is it...
...that this girl seems so dear to me?
Let's cool down your face.
Come to my house.
What's your name?
It's... Nanami.
Tomoe-sama~!
How dull.
Please look at me.
What's the matter with you today?
Tsukune's mind is always filled with thoughts about Tomoe-sama!
If it's for your sake, I don't mind giving up my life.
You... smell of another man.
It stinks.
No way~! Tomoe-sama~!!
How boring...
...both this woman and this place.
Who are you?
Oh...
...that one's good enough.
You're that fox Tomoe, right?
My name is Ikusagami Takehaya.
I've come on orders from Izumo,
to eradicate all the youkai that disrupt the world.
You're first, fox.
Tomoe-sama!
What's the matter, Tsukune? You can sacrifice yourself now.
I'll watch you, so go on.
You insolent fox!!
A god coming to such a place, just to kill me...
Wild fox, you'll suffer by my hands. You should feel honored.
Hmm...
What!?
This is a divine sword I borrowed from Ookuninushi.
Ama no Hahakiri!!
Die, fox!!
Tomoe-sama...!
Please, escape somewhere.
What's this!?
Tomoe-sama...
...you probably will...
...continue being alone...
...without ever loving anyone, won't you?
Ran away to the human world, did he?
Hmph!
However, that wound will undoubtedly cease his movements.
I've already warned the humans of that world.
Fox, it's also fine if you are tormented to death, by those hot-blooded humans.
Damn it, damn it!!
To think I'd be this humiliated.
Seems like I have to hide myself for a while.
Blood...
Is this my blood?
I'm seeing it for the first time.
No good..!
I... can't move anymore.
I-It's a fox youkai!!
Father!!! Tomoe's here!!!
What did you say!?
Where is he!?
Get him! Get him!
That was delicious! Thank you for the meal!
3 days after arriving in the past, I finally got a chance to bathe and dine today.
I'm so happy!
You seem to have been on a long journey.
You can rest in my house as long as you want.
Yes!
My kimono looks good on you.
I'll give it to you.
Eh?
If you wear the clothes you wore before, you'll be accused again by the village men, right?
Ah...
Thank you very much.
Yukiji-san... is so kind.
Tomoe too, surely, must have been touched by her kindness and fallen for her.
Lady Yukiji, it's terrible!
Fuuta? What's wrong?
The fox, that they were mentioning before, has appeared!
Right now, the village men are cornering him towards the river!
A fox youkai, you say?
A white fox that uses blue flames.
He looks human and seems to be wearing dark clothing.
He seems to have become very weak, so they can take him down.
All able men are going to the river.
Tomoe...It's Tomoe!
The injured Tomoe-kun who collapsed by the riverside was saved by Yukiji.
Seems, that's how their relationship started.
A youkai slaughter?
That sounds great.
We shall have a feast tonight.
Um...!
You don't have to join in. You must be tired, right?
Aren't you going? To where Tomoe is?
Me?
Why?
Because Tomoe's injured...
I don't want to see a youkai's face.
Youkai are better off dead.
Huh!?
Isn't Yukiji-san going to go rescue Tomoe?
We've got him! We've got the fox!
Tomoe!
Hey, Nanami!
My lady, Nanami went towards the river.
I'll follow her.
Go.
I can't leave her be.
Because she somehow resembles Lady Yukiji.
Hey!!
Where is the fox you caught, Sukeroku!?
Here!
If we take this as a hostage, he'll come out, won't he?
My body won't listen to me.
If they hit me with their filthy hoes and sickles...
...someone like me... in a place like this...
...in such a place...
...will die, is it?
A human's coming.
Would a child's appearance...
...disguise me enough?
I might still be discovered because of this wound.
It's going dark before my eyes.
Tomoe!
In an instant, my heart was stolen.
Yes, it's those eyes.
It's alright now, Tomoe.
This is the first woman I have wanted to claim as my own.
What is the matter with that kid?
I heard that foxes can change form.
Perhaps that child is the fox youkai that's been hunted right now.
He's... a child I know...
Please help him.
Nanami, how about you stop hiding and show your face?
I must not get in the way of Tomoe and Yukiji-san's relationship of the past.
My body is burning.
Where is this place?
Get well soon.
Here are your favorite rice cakes.
Who wants cakes?
Who is she?
You're being overly familiar.
Ah, it's you again.
When I return to my original form,
so then,
what shall I do to you?
Preview
She cannot meddle with the past.
Nanami continues to care for Tomoe from the shadows,
and yet Tomoe decides to kill Nanami with his own hands.
Nanami's body has once again reached its limit for time traveling.
Next time, The Fox Falls in Love.
Where will their fate take them?
Credits:
Raws-DVD Rip(from nyaa.se)
Translation- KH Addicts
Typesetting, Timing, Minor Script Editing and Encoding- asckj1