hajimete no kimochi
my first feelings
shonbori no mune ni
upon my downhearted chest
sotto nagerareta hidamarine
a sunny ray of light was gently thrown
hitori aruiteta
walking alone...
sora miageta toki
when I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
spring was near,
misetekureta
it showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
fluttering petals,
sukininatte iino
is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
or will...
tamerau kokoro ga
my hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
put on my brakes,
kurushikute
it's so painful
ikiga tomarisou desu
I can't breathe
Apprehension of Spring
The town I was born in.
The house I was born in.
My father and brother.
It's like I just met them for the first time,
but they're very nostalgic people.
Good morning, brother!
Brother!
Brother! Wait up!
I'm home.
Welcome back, brother.
nitsuke = japanese boiled and seasoned food
Isn't this nitsuke delicious?
Yeah.
My mother taught me how to make it.
Brother!
Eh?
Let's go to the amusement park together again!
Somehow, everything looks like it's sparkling.
A younger sister...?
Good morning, brother!
Umm...
What do you do for lunch usually?
bento = packed lunch
I made a bento today.
If it's alright with you, would you take it with you?
Brother?
Brother!
Brother...
Eh? And then?
He said he was anemic...
Is he sickly?
His complexion hasn't been too good lately.
Hmm...
I want to...
become...
closer to...
my brother.
You don't get along with him?
That's not it, but...
But he seems uncomfortable.
It can't be helped if he's twelve years older than you.
But... more...
since we're siblings.
The fire of envy is burning wildly within my heart...
Thanks for the meal!
That idiot...!
Well, I guess I'll head home.
Good work.
You should hurry up and go home early too.
Isn't your cute little sister waiting?
That's why I don't want to...
Have her make you a meal full of love!
Like the bento from lunch!
Shut up!
There's nothing to worry about!
I'll take care of your membership entrance!
Umm... I'm not interested...
You are...
Glasses...
Glasses...?
Brother!
You!
I came to visit.
So she says.
Why don't we all go out and eat together?
Hurry and finish up your work.
Dad said he would be late today so we should go out and eat.
Brother, what would you like to eat...
Hey! Koushiro!
Idiot! Why did you come all the way here?!
Because...
Listen, I don't want you to ever come to my office again!
Understand?
Brother...
Did I...
Hey, brother...
And stop calling me brother!
Then...
Then what should I call you?
Hey...
It was a chance to become close to a female high school student lawfully.
He was such a jerk!
He went off to work early by himself.
Didn't you say you wanted to be closer yesterday?
I'm so disappointed.
In truth...
I want to play with him and have him help me with homework...
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
Aren't most siblings like that?
All I do is fight with my older sister.
I didn't think he was so mean!
I'm never going to call my brother "brother" again!
Now, now.
Then why don't we go have some fun after school...
and let out all our feelings!
Okay?
Yeah!
Poor girl.
She visited you because she wanted to be closer to you.
That attitude was uncalled for, wasn't it?
Shut up! I know that already.
Then what?
What do you not like about her?
It's nothing.
It's not like I dislike her.
When she's in front of me,
it just makes me want to run away.
What's wrong with you?
Did you go crazy after you got your heart broken?
I forgot...
I forgot about it... completely.
Damn it!
It's so sweet! This is so delicious!
Isn't it, isn't it?
Chocolate caramel ice cream is definitely the best!
Yeah!
Nanoka, you don't know much about the stores around here, right?
Let's go shopping together next time.
I'll show you around!
Yeah!
Hey, Futaba-chan!
What's up?
You're eating it again?
You sure love the ice cream from this place.
She went to the same junior high as me.
I'm Tamaki Youko from class 4. Nice to meet you.
I'm Kohinata Nanoka, nice to meet you too.
Hey, I was going to go karaoke with my friends, so...
do you guys want to come along too?
I'm home.
What are you doing?
Nanoka said...
on the phone that she's going to be late.
What?
She contacted you, so it's fine.
You idiot!
Right now, Nanoka could be surrounded by strange men and might get kidnapped!
If something like that happens...
I... I'll...
You're overreacting.
Ah! I sang a lot!
It was so much fun!
I feel so refreshed.
It's gotten kind of late, huh?
Are you okay, Nanoka?
I called them just in case.
Let's go again next time!
Yeah!
I'll see you tomorrow, then.
See you! Bye!
Try to make up with your brother.
This is the Saeki residence.
This is Nanoka.
Are you stupid?!
What have you been doing until this hour?
Um... no...
Where are you right now?
At the public phone outside the park.
Why did you pass through such a place?
Don't you know there are many perverts around there?
I got it!
I was just going to tell you I'm heading home right now!
Bye!
Hey! Hello?
What's with him?!
He's so arrogant!
I was feeling down...
I know now...
That time...
I didn't know why you cried that time, but...
thanks to that, I didn't have to cry.
Even if I remember about the guy I used to like,
I'm all right now.
But...
Why does it have to be like this?
Get on.
No thanks.
Who do you think I came out here for?
Hurry up and get on.
Brother, you just did that on your own!
Fine...
Call me whatever you wish.
Dad is worried about you,
let's hurry up and go home.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Brother?
What?
Nothing...
As for me,
I was getting irritated from still feeling uncomfortable.
She's my younger sister.
So this is fine.
This is normal, and ordinary.
I continued pedaling as if to tell myself that.
yasashii yume ga
a gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satteyuku
that touches you then leaves
chiisana potto ni wa
in the small pot
daisukina kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly
ii kaori nosete
that carry a sweet scent
itsumo matteita
always waiting...
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment...
futari dakara wakaru koto
things we understand because it's the two of us
kotoba janakute
are not just words
hohoemu dake negaudake
we just smile, we just hope
shizukana sora e
to the quiet sky
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
we'll see each other again tomorrow...
shizukana sora de
at the quiet sky
Chidori goes
I do not intend to misuse the Marriage Consultation office.
I just want to innocently and lawfully become friends with female high school students!
Punishment - Hiding Glasses.
Glasses...