hajimete no kimochi
my first feelings
shonbori no mune ni
upon my downhearted chest
sotto nagerareta hidamarine
a sunny ray of light was gently thrown
hitori aruiteta
walking alone...
sora miageta toki
when I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
spring was near,
misetekureta
it showed me
kowareru omoi wa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
fluttering petals,
sukininatte iino
is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
or will...
tamerau kokoro ga
my hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
put on my brakes,
kurushikute
it's so painful
ikiga tomarisou desu
I can't breathe
First Flower
It's been a while since I've stopped caring about the changing of the seasons.
Shirasugi...
Last stop, Wakase...
Please wait for the express train, it will come after...
How much meaning is there to the fact that it is spring right now?
There's someone else I've fallen in love with.
Oh... Really?
Tsubana. Tsubana.
Please wait until the train comes to a complete stop.
Excuse me, I'm getting off.
Hey... Excuse me.
Hey, you there!
Hey, student!
Umm?
Oh... here...
Oh no... I'm so out of it.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
That's all I have about the next arranged marriage party.
If you don't have any particular questions, then I would like to end the meeting.
Yes!
Odagiri?
This party is restricted to members in their late 20's to early 30's.
However, someday I hope to bring down the membership age to mid-teens,
and have a party restricted to women in their teens...
That's all!
Good work guys.
Let's go eat!
Where do you want to go?
Didn't a new restaurant open up in Kanami?
Really?
Koshiro.
Huh?
You're sorting the membership data files in the back today.
Why?
That face... that smell!
I can't show that to customers.
There should definitely be a demand.
You think so?
From experience, even men my age can only meet teenage girls in an unlawful way.
A demand for you?
Aren't there any opportunities to meet a female high school student?
You just keep working.
I'm ho...me...
I didn't hear about this!
Anyway, you're going to live with Nanoka starting tomorrow night.
Be prepared!
So suddenly...
I wanted to show you Nanoka.
You don't remember her, do you?
Yes I do... I do, but I don't remember her face.
She's a freshman in high school now.
She's 15 years old. She is so cute!
Everyone commutes from far away nowadays.
She can cut her commute time from two hours to one!
Isn't it natural that you let her stay?
Just because you got dumped by your lover,
you don't intend on getting back together with mom, do you?
That's not how it is!
It's not?
No!
She's my daughter!
She's a relative!
Your younger sister!
With my carefree life living with pop,
sometimes there's something I forget about.
I have a mother and a sister who's 12 years younger.
Please introduce her to me!
What the hell are you thinking?
Why were you hiding such an important thing from me?!
I wasn't hiding.
It's basically like I don't know about it.
My parents got divorced.
I met my mom, who took custody of her, a couple times.
But I haven't seen my sister at all.
Customer!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
And...
What kind of partner are you interested in?
Don't get mad.
I'm sorry I came while you're working.
It's all right.
It's my lunch break anyway.
I came to get the keys to my place back.
I thought it'd be better during the day.
Wait a little.
Bye.
Yeah.
You're really letting me go easy.
Sorry...
But...
You dismissed it so lightly.
I just felt like...
Oh, this is all I meant to you.
Koshiro, have you ever loved anyone from the bottom of your heart?
Then what should I have done?
During the party, we're planning to have three events,
so if we could divide the food and have it brought out to match the timing...
Next, concerning the audio equipment...
Thank you for your business.
Same here.
Oh yes
Here. If you'd like it, it's next door.
Oh, thank you very much.  Don't mind if I do.
What do I say to a woman that says she has another man...?
What should I have done?
What a great view.
It's a place that kind of hurts for a bachelor.
So you broke up?
Yeah.
You're so cool about it...
That's what she dislikes about me.
Here, I'll give these to you.
I don't need them.
Why don't you try inviting that girl you broke up with?
Maybe you guys will get back together?
Who the hell's going to get back together with...
Ah! Hello.
Ummm...
Do you remember me?
Yesterday morning.
Yeah, I remember!
I remember you.
Ah, I'm glad.
What a bad man!
Asking out high school girls?
That's not what it is!
Thank you for yesterday.
Then, I'm sorry I'm interrupting your date.
That's wrong too!
Hey!
Eh?
Umm...
Yes?
Here.
Please have these.
Idiot.
Umm...
I'm glad. I was waiting to meet a someone,
but I came too early and I needed to kill time.
Meeting someone?
Yes. My father.
Hey. What would you like to ride?
Are you all right?
What the hell am I doing?
Here.
Wow! Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
It must be boring with me.
That's not true.
Don't you have a boyfriend?
I just broke up with him.
Wow! It's so beautiful!
This...
I received it during my junior high graduation
from the person I liked.
But it wasn't his second button.
I liked him since I was a first-year.
It's not like he's really handsome or anything...
but I really liked him.
I gathered up all my courage and confessed to him but...
He said he's going out with a junior at school.
I didn't know that at all.
If the window could open, I could throw it out from here...
How disappointing.
Don't say you're going to throw it away.
You still like him, don't you?
Then don't say that you're going to throw it away.
But...
I have to forget about him.
He has someone that he's going out with.
We go to different high schools,
and it's not like I'll ever get to see him again.
So why?
Why do you say such things?
You're so straightforward.
Then how...?
How can you love someone so straightforward like that?
I...
I just got dumped too.
Well, it's really different from your situation.
My feelings totally cooled off...
and I don't really know if I really loved her anymore.
But...
That's why...
You should definitely treasure...
the feelings that you have inside you.
Why...?
Why am I...?
I was so surprised.
The cherry blossoms.
Ever since I got rejected, I kept walking with my head down,
so I didn't notice the flowers blooming at all.
When you called me back at the train station,
I noticed it for the first time.
I was really surprised!
The petals were falling like snow,
and for a moment I couldn't tell where I was.
That's the same for me too.
Where is this...
this place that I've always been at?
Is being here unforgivable?
Thank you very much.
Same here.
Umm...
It's nothing.
Well, I have to...
Hey!
Sorry for making you wait!
Dad!
Father?
Huh?!
Oh, you're here too, Koshiro?
It's been a while since you siblings have gotten together.
Did you guys notice right after you met each other?
Hey, what's wrong with the two of you? Let's go!
Hey...!
What should we have for dinner?
Nanoka, what do you want?
Wait...
Daddy...
Brother?
Yes...
I have...
A little sister.
yasashii yume ga
a gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satteyuku
that touches you then leaves
chiisana potto ni wa
in the small pot
daisukina kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly
ii kaori nosete
that carry a sweet scent
itsumo matteita
always waiting...
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment...
futari dakara wakaru koto
things we understand because it's the two of us
kotoba janakute
are not just words
hohoemu dake negaudake
we just smile, we just hope
shizuka na sora e
to the quiet sky
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
we'll see each other again tomorrow...
shizuka na sora de
at the quiet sky
A girl that I got dumped by came to my office, so I was kind of apprehensive.
I went on a date with my younger sister without knowing.
I cried in front of a high school student at my age.
Is this all right?!
Your punishment is Sumaki Nagashi!
WHY?!