hajimete no kimochi
my first feelings
shonbori no mune ni
upon my downhearted chest
sotto nagerareta hidamarine
a sunny ray of light was gently thrown
hitori aruiteta
walking alone...
sora miageta toki
when I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
spring was near,
misetekureta
it showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
fluttering petals,
sukininatte iino
is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
or will...
tamerau kokoro ga
my hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
put on my brakes,
kurushikute
it's so painful
ikiga tomarisou desu
I can't breathe
Evening Shower
Hey.
Are you all right?
What?
Your face.
It's terrible!
Did you get a good rest on your day off?
Yeah.
You look so out of it to me.
That's not true.
You have to fix yourself up for the events at least.
I know.
Are you still brooding over it?
Your break-up?
No way.
Well, it's fine then.
In truth
I don't have any regrets or attachments about getting dumped.
Koshiro, have you ever felt a yearning for someone from the bottom of your heart?
No.
I'm terrible at getting the gist of things.
You don't look that way.
And then I fell down.
Odagiri!
Yes.
But usually I'm pretty calm.
What should we do about today's after-party?
The chief said it's on him.
Really? Yes!
Of course I'm in!
I made a promise today so I'll be leaving first.
Promise?
A movie. I'm watching a movie.
Is it with Nanoka-san?
What's your point?
I can't help it. She forced me to promise her.
I'd love to go with you!
Shut up! You just go and drink with the chief!
Koshiro,
Before when we had a meeting here didn't you flirt with a high school girl?
Was that...?
Flirt?!
With a high school girl?
Idiot! NO!
That was...
That was Nanoka-chan wasn't it?
Why didn't you just say she was your sister in the first place?
Odagiri. Help me carry this.
Yes.
What do you mean flirting with Nanoka san?
No idea.
I don't really get it either.
Why?
Don't look at me like it's so unusual.
But, why?
You had a beard this morning!
We have to look clean for our events or else we would get scolded.
Look clean?
Is it weird?
You look cool!
But it looks painful!
What are you saying...?
This movie is...
Don't get so close!
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
What are you pondering about?
Nothing.
Take out your student ID.
Oh yeah.
What's wrong?
I'm going to go buy the tickets.
What is he thinking, making you come home all alone at this hour?
He said it doesn't matter; just go home first.
That guy is hopeless.
He went off somewhere on his way home right after the movie ended.
Where did that bum go?
I don't know. He didn't say anything.
Hey.
Your uniform's going to get wrinkled.
I don't care.
So?
About earlier.
That was my younger sister.
I don't think I ever told you, but
she's my younger sister whom I've been living apart from until now.
You know my parents are divorced right?
And she's been with my mom the whole time.
We've been living together since this spring because her high school is nearby.
That's it?
Is that really all?
Yeah.
What?
You said you had something to tell me so I was wondering what it was.
It's not a laughing matter!
I didn't want you to think I started going after high school girls after I got dumped.
I was worried for nothing.
It's so like you to worry about stupid appearances and dating high school girls though.
Well, I'm sorry.
I'll never come again.
Dinner..
Have you eaten yet?
Suddenly, a stupid thought passed through my mind.
Which reminds me, it's been 3 months since I last had sex.
But who cares because you can drink.
That's not true.
It is! You're way stronger than me!
Isn't it good?
It's my favorite restaurant.
Yeah.
I come here a lot by myself
What are you saying, stupid?
I'm not stupid. I'm serious.
I don't believe you!
I don't joke around about things like that.
How about Sachiko-chan?
She's just a friend..
No way!
Really...
You...
How's work been lately?
Why?
You used to always tell me that you wanted to quit.
You still remember?
Who would forget after listening to you complain so much?
I thought you weren't listening with your half-hearted replies.
That's not true.
And how is your job?
Normal I guess
I see.
And you?
Did you have an event today?
Yeah
Or did you shave your beard because your high school girlfriend told you to?
I'm saying she's...
What is it?
Nothing.
What?
I was wondering if any taxis would come this way.
If you go a little further you'll come to the main street. It'll be easier to find one there.
I'm moving next month.
I'm quitting my job too
Although thats a little later on.
I see
By the way, my boyfriend is coming now.
Yeah.
What?
He's a very good person.
I see.
Best of luck to you, Koshiro.
Really.
Good night.
What should we do afterwards?
I'm glad I didn't say anything stupid like that.
I'm really glad.
Don't stay up too late!
Yes.
I wasn't going out with her just for the sex.
Have you ever felt a yearning for someone from the bottom of your heart, Koshiro?
But I don't think it's bad.
Is it that big of a deal to fall in love with someone?
Is yearning something you can brag about?
What does it mean to "yearn" anyway?
That idiot!
Brother?
Sorry!
Good morning.
I'm sorry about last night,
for suddenly barging in on you.
I'll be careful next time.
The movie,
let's go see another one.
But you have to go home with me this time.
What?
Nothing.
yasashii yume ga
a gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satteyuku
that touches you then leaves
chiisana potto ni wa
in the small pot
daisukina kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly
ii kaori nosete
that carry a sweet scent
itsumo matteita
always waiting...
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment...
futari dakara wakaru koto
things we understand because it's the two of us
kotoba janakute
are not just words
hohoemu dake negaudake
we just smile, we just hope
shizukana sora e
to the quiet sky
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
we'll see each other again tomorrow...
shizukana sora de
at the quiet sky
Ya... umm... well....
I'm sorry I sniffed it.. I'm sorry I sniffed it.
I'm sorry I sniffed it!
Innocent! Like hell!
I have no dignity.