hajimete no kimochi
my first feelings
shonbori no mune ni
upon my downhearted chest
sotto nagerareta hidamarine
a sunny ray of light was gently thrown
hitori aruiteta
walking alone...
sora miageta toki
when I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
spring was near,
misetekureta
it showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
fluttering petals,
sukininatte iino
is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
or will...
tamerau kokoro ga
my hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
put on my brakes,
kurushikute
it's so painful
ikiga tomarisou desu
I can't breathe
I want to touch her.
I want to hold her tight.
I want to be closer to her.
No...
I am such a pervert.
No!
Wintry moon
It's not like I wanted to hurt her.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Is she... still sleeping?
Nanoka already left.
She wanted to leave early today.
I see...
Come on, let's eat.
She won't even give me a chance to apologize, huh?
No, maybe there isn't even a need for that anymore.
If I just disappear from her life, won't that solve everything?
Don't say it!
You love me like a sister would love her brother.
Saying that you love your sibling like that...
Something's wrong with you.
I know that it's strange.
I got a bit ahead of myself.
"What do you think of me?"
I shouldn't have asked such a shameless question.
But then, why did he...?
You're moving? Why?
A man your age living in your parent's home...
I was so envious of your situation.
Stuff happened.
You... do understand how busy the office is during this season.
We got a Christmas party, and end of the year party, a New Year's party,
and in just a few more weeks there's going to be a Valentine's party.
In other words, it's going to be a hellish time of party planning.
And you say you're moving tomorrow?!
A lot happened.
So I guess you've already found your apartment?
Not yet.
Any likely targets?
None.
Well, what are you going to do?
Who knows?
Then decide now while we're working outside!
Hey, stop.
What do you think?
If there are any conditions you want, let's hear it.
But I believe there's enough to suit you in here already.
Yeah.
It's fine, isn't it?
It's close to the station and there's a convenience store right there, so shopping should be easy too.
This place is closer to the office than my home.
It's a very convenient apartment.
Why do we have to decide on your conditions?
Can he move in tomorrow?
Sure. If I have the deposit and take care of some paperwork,
then I'll be able to talk with the landlord.
Paperwork as in...?
At the very least, the lease contract.
I can wait for the guarantor's seal until tomorrow though.
And if that's the case...
Nanoka!
I thought you went home already.
And what are you gazing at by yourself?
I'm not gazing at anything in particular.
That's such a stupid answer.
Did something happen?
You've seemed so lifeless since this morning.
I'm fine.
It's just that I don't really feel like going home.
That's not "fine" at all, then!
Let's play games as much as we want!
Let's listen to CDs as much as we want!
Let's eat snacks as much as we want!
And can also chit-chat as much as we want.
So cheer up, okay?
Yeah.
Hello Nanoka-chan.
Hello.
What's up with this room?
You should clean this place up.
Stop being so noisy.
I know, I will, so just shut up, sis.
You never do it when no one tells you to.
Geez, Nanoka and I have something important to talk about.
It's a complicated issue that you'll never get,sis.
fukuzatsu = complicated, fuku = clothing
Speaking of clothing, let me borrow that blue shirt.
You said you gave it to me and would never wear it again!
I changed my mind now. Hand it back.
That's so cheap!
Monster! Devil!
Are you sure it's okay?
Huh? You're moving tomorrow, right?
You'll be busy with this and that, right?
I'm sorry.
I'll make sure I pay you back.
Well, what happened?
It's nothing.
You wouldn't be running away in the middle of the night if it really was "nothing".
Don't say such cynical things.
But what you're doing is pretty much a night flight.
I guess so.
Thanks for your work.
What's up with him...?
One more time!
Okay.
That's cheap! Loser goes out!
Give it to me!
Sis, you're being so mean.
All right! All right!
This person is going to become a bride next year.
Can you believe it?
Really?
Yeah, pretty much.
Annual tribute...
She's...
She's...?
Japanese idiom for getting married
She's finally going to pay her annual tribute.
Have you girls found guys yet?
Well, it's the best time for "it".
"It" meaning pure love relationships.
Saying that while your marriage got arranged...
I just meant for relationship purposes.
There's much more to think about when it comes to marriage.
Don't you marry someone because you like him?
I like my fiancé, of course.
But just liking him isn't enough for this arrangement.
There are various constraints in reality.
And then you come to the point where you ask "is this really okay?"
Of course it'll be good.
With you gone, this place will be so much more peaceful!
Yes, yes, I know.
Was that a call from her?
A-ah, yeah, sorry.
S-she said she's staying at a friend's house or something.
I see.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Hey, I'm...
I'll get it.
Hello, this is the Saeki's.
Hello.
Y-yo...
What's up?
I'll be staying at Futaba-chan's home tonight.
O-okay...
Dad just told me that.
And I also said that I'll be back before noon tomorrow.
But I think I'll stay here a bit longer, so...
I see.
-You know...
-I...
-Sorry.
-What?
Brother.
You're not angry?
About what?
About me asking what you thought about me.
We'll be eating first, then.
O-okay.
I asked you such a strange thing.
Ah, you did?
Yeah.
And then you said... I was weird.
Of course I didn't mean it.
But...
You're not weird and I'm not angry.
Really?
Yeah. That aside...
I should be the one apologizing for doing that to you...
Sorry, I know it's my fault.
I don't really care about that.
But...
Just a bit, though.
I'm sorry.
But, I don't really care that much about it.
I see.
I'm glad.
Same here.
To be able to talk with you.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, I...
Yeah?
No, nothing.
What is it?
I said nothing.
But I want to know.
Really, it's nothing.
Brother.
I...
Maybe I'll call off staying over here tonight.
What are you talking about? I'm hanging up.
Okay.
See you.
The food's going to be gone!
Sis, you eat too much.
It's all right, I made these myself.
You won't be able to wear your wedding dress at this rate.
I'm still fine.
The say, "One second of negligence, one lifetime of obesity".
You too.
Nanoka?
What's the matter? Got no appetite?
Or does the food look nasty?
What did you say?!
Of course not.
Then eat up! It's delicious.
That's right. Hey Futaba, grab some for her.
I know already!
But man, it's not like I'm saying no to you living alone.
I know this came out of the blue.
I'm sorry for saying this all of a sudden.
What are you not satisfied with?
Nothing like that.
That can't be!
Or else you wouldn't say you want to move out all of a sudden.
Well, I've been thinking about it for a while.
What is this? Just be sincere and tell me the truth.
Is there anything you're not content with about me?
Or did something happen between you and Nanoka?
No...
What's the matter?
I just felt like coming back.
I came back.
What do you mean you're moving out?
Here.
Thanks.
Come in.
What's the matter?
Can we... sleep together?
I want to be with you.
At least for today.
Hey! Hold it for a second!
I am strange... after all.
Even though we're siblings, I...
I'm saying such selfish things.
It's not strange.
It's fine because we're siblings.
Stuff like this... in reality.
Then why are you moving out, brother?
You know.
I don't.
You should.
Let's make a promise, tonight's the last time.
We won't meet again.
Why?
Why are you saying such things?
That's strange.
Things like "the last time"...
You're not going somewhere that far.
That's strange,
even though we're siblings.
Yeah, even though we're siblings.
I...
I always had something I wanted to say, but couldn't.
You remember when we rode on the ferris wheel?
Even though I wasn't really sure back then,
the truth is..
I was very happy that moment.
That's why at this rate, I...
yasashii yume ga
a gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satteyuku
that touches you then leaves
chiisana potto ni wa
in the small pot
daisukina kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly
ii kaori nosete
that carry a sweet scent
itsumo matteita
always waiting...
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment...
futari dakara wakaru koto
things we understand because it's the two of us
kotoba janakute
are not just words
hohoemu dake negaudake
we just smile, we just hope
shizukana sora e
to the quiet sky
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
we'll see each other again tomorrow...
shizukana sora de
at the quiet sky
Play games, listen to music, eat snacks,
play games again and chit-chat cheerfully!
Master Takahashi's punishment!