hajimete no kimochi
my first feelings
shonbori no mune ni
upon my downhearted chest
sotto nagerareta hidamarine
a sunny ray of light was gently thrown
hitori aruiteta
walking alone...
sora miageta toki
when I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
spring was near,
misetekureta
it showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
fluttering petals,
sukininatte iino
is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
or will...
tamerau kokoro ga
my hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
put on my brakes,
kurushikute
it's so painful
ikiga tomarisou desu
I can't breathe
Gentle breeze
I can't sleep...
Why do I...
...keep thinking about her?
Now that I think about it...
When I was really little,
there were nights when I couldn't get to sleep.
At times like that...
Mom would soothe me by patting my head.
That's weird...
I swear it was somewhere in here...
Ow!
Yeah...
When I was a little kid, without him...
There's nothing we can do.
You're the one who forgot it.
First thing tomorrow morning, we'll ask the bus company. All right?
What a troublesome child you are.
Just like my mom did for me that day,
if I could give something to her,
maybe this feeling would go away.
Suddenly I thought...
Maybe I'm the child.
Or is her innocence the child?
Or...
What do you want?!
How cute!
Is this yours, brother?
Don't just come into my room like that!
How unexpected!
You treasure such a cute teddy bear?
It's not that I'm treasuring it.
Yes you are!
You washed it and cleaned it, right?
No, that wasn't... what I...
But, that way of drying isn't nice!
Right?
If you want it, I'll give it to you.
But...
My mom made it for me when I was a kid.
Isn't it a given for you to have it?
I'll give it to you.
Wait a second!
Here!
This one's mine.
My mother made it for me too.
I'm giving it to you.
I'll keep this one,
so take care of that one, brother.
I don't want this.
No! Take care of it!
Don't bully it!
She is definitely a child...
...so I think.
I'd like to think but...
You came during third period?
When I woke up, the morning show was over.
I thought I should have just come in the afternoon, at first.
You should've just taken the day off.
But you know...
I actually benefited from coming late!
I saw this really cute guy on the train!
What kind?
He was tall, and fair skinned
with really nice hair and really long eye lashes.
He was probably a high school student!
He was wearing a school uniform!
At such an hour?
Yeah! That's the point!
The point?
I was so late,  but he was on the same train car
on the same train at the same time!
Don't you think it's fate?
Yeah, sort of!
Isn't it? Isn't it? I feel a romance coming on!
Romance...?
Loser buys drinks!
Fine, because I'm going to win.
Nanoka?
Was it?
Yeah. Thanks!
You're a life saver.
Are you okay?
You don't look so well.
I'm fine.
Huh?
Koshiro, you're taking tomorrow off too?
Yeah, it's a compensatory day off from last week.
Isn't Wakanai-san's arranged marriage meeting tomorrow?
It was?
Yeah, it was!
Shoot, I completely forgot about it.
I'll come after lunch.
It's okay.
You can take the day off.
I'll go in your place.
That's not okay!
Isn't he extremely shy in front of strangers?
So that he won't get nervous, we have to start from that meeting room,
then go to a nearby cafe, then go to a European restaurant...
I can't leave such an important job
to someone who's been in a daze all the time.
See, there you go lost in thought again.
Anyway, go get some rest tomorrow!
Yeah...
That cute guy you were talking about earlier,
what school does he go to?
I wish I could've found that out...
I've never seen his uniform before.
Maybe it's the all-boys school that was established last year.
But if he was on the same train as you today
there's a chance you could see him again, right?
I want to see what he looks like too!
What? What's wrong?
What should I do?
It's that blonde guy?
Oh my god! Can I believe in fate?
He's the guy from this morning?!
Do you think he's good-looking?
What should I do?
Wait a minute!
I want to take a better look at him!
Nanoka...
Did you see that?
It was Tamaki, right? He was kissing Tamaki, right?
Yeah...
That girl! She said she wasn't interested!
I'll make her spill it all out tomorrow!
I'm home.
You...
Welcome home.
You're early.
What's wrong?
What's that medicine for?
Oh, it's nothing.
Just a pain reliever.
I'm going to go lie down in my room.
Hey, is Nanoka all right?
She was probably up late yesterday or something.
Nanoka...
It looks like the beginning of the rainy season.
The weather in the Kantou region isn't very clear.
There won't be any rain from tonight to tomorrow morning, but
it will most likely rain tomorrow afternoon.
Please don't forget to bring your umbrella when you go out.
Next, tomorrow's weather for each area on Tokyo.
It will be cloudy followed by rain in Tokyo city.
Probability of precipitation in the morning is 60%
In the afternoon it will be 70%...
Aren't you hungry?
Where are you going at this hour?
A walk.
What are you saying? You're not feeling well, right?
I just have really bad menstrual cramps.
First time in three months?
Is that alright?
The doctor told me it's common for girls my age.
I'm sorry for making you worry even though I'm not really sick.
It's alright.
Do you want to go to the convenience store on the way back?
Are you all right? Don't force yourself!
Brother, you're over-exaggerating.
I'm fine.
Today,
I saw my friend kissing a guy.
I wonder if I'm going to kiss someone someday?
I'm going to have you explain everything about yesterday!
I have nothing to explain.
Where did you meet him?
In junior high. We went to the same cram school.
Cram school?
That's something that is unrelated to me!
Ouch!
I said something weird last night...
Brother's probably used to kissing.
He's an adult.
When will I become an adult?
Isn't there any good love rolling around?
What?
Is that strange?
Not really.
See?
Crap!
Shit...
It'll probably stop soon.
When you're in love, even boring things make your heart jump!
That's what makes it really fun!
Yeah!
Oh no... it's gotten worse.
Brother...
Brother!
I'm home.
Did you come to pick me up?
No way.
I was on my way to the store because I ran out of tobacco.
It's true! I only brought one umbrella too!
Yeah.
I know.
Are you all right?
Your stomach ache?
What are you smiling about?
Nothing.
What do you mean?
Weirdo.
yasashii yume ga
a gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satteyuku
that touches you then leaves
chiisana potto ni wa
in the small pot
daisukina kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly
ii kaori nosete
that carry a sweet scent
itsumo matteita
always waiting...
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment...
futari dakara wakaru koto
things we understand because it's the two of us
kotoba janakute
are not just words
hohoemu dake negaudake
we just smile, we just hope
shizukana sora e
to the quiet sky
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
we'll see each other again tomorrow...
shizukana sora de
at the quiet sky
The marriage meeting schedule completely skipped my mind.
I bullied the bear by giving it a noogie with my knuckles.
I stared at her underwear in the laundry.
I can't help it!
It's only natural if you're a man!
Innocent. Suspended sentence.