There's a private school in which students get together. With the power to control the elements
The school was known as the Academy Tnby
But here in this school
Mvzayy housed are trying to create difficulties gave Nasrshvn
,for solving this problem
School decided the group of student council was formed. The student leadership
That magical known as the Organization for Security Mission
Using Gnjyh's called sacred Makn
.Avna trying to stop the people that are going to take offense
When referred to the students as they .mrdm Makn
Hey, Aki-chan, what do you want when you grow up?
.Mykhvam like you get a wonderful woman, Mami
And a wonderful husband like a father to marry
.Ky chan, you're the only elementary school, however it got a big breasts
So one day I was a wonderful husband Geert
Therefore, I try to make my breasts bigger than it is Faghih
.Ag·h do it, truly I am married to a wonderful husband
.Ky chan, you're too greedy
Yes, I Nijō
Mom, why are you calling me like Jl suspended?
Huh? A's marriage proposal?
I said I do not need to do
I can not find my husband .khvdm
Of course, I'm already in a relationship
What you send a picture?
.I understood
Now to work, so I got to hang up, okay?
Yes, I am sure that you send a picture
.See you
Each time that Mom calling, always is about marriage proposal to me.
But it see and what to do?
... I do not have a boyfriend
Sensei .ky
.Hyn class elements of this happened
! Takrv when you come Kvn.bh
Huh? What?
.Jvn mother, help me!
Huh?
.Bgv thing
Yes, this complete
.Takrv kun, thank you
.Ky Sensei ... Please dressing me now
!I'm sorry
... At that moment, I did not even think about
That's going to be everything to me JIT processes
Huh? I'm doing a place like this?
.it's true
One had attacked me.
So, here
That's what Jhnmyh?
.Ky chan, you've finally found your boyfriend you first
.Dvst son, Oyama Takrv still teaching knowledge, and you are a teacher
That's a Jorah this relationship is not right with your mother, but it's not a problem
See this occasion, we give you the gifts were special holidays
, So that the boat was two days Dnbaltvn
This island for two Tast
Please create unforgettable memories
From the side, Mom
.Py wrote: It would have been nice if the girl is my first grandson
Oh, and before thinking?
.I see
I .fkr I realized that what we had been caught in bad shape
.Sorry
Because it's Nevermind be married
Brush a photo of the boy who was supposed to have sent you, but now you are stuck in such a deplorable condition
.Khvb, now we have bigger problems that element on my hand be destroyed
.H, sorry
I .fkr Mom used to prevent element
Mom element of mine Qvytrh
You mean after all the time and we stuck here?
.Mtmynm free when the boat got us out.
Here Avkynvyh island?
For summer training camp here we come
.it's true
Probably for the rest disappeared Shdnmvn Ngranmvnm
Huh?
Oyama dealing Takrv not find yesterday?
Perhaps brush happened
.Khvb, who knows of what things are like that
Probably somewhere around the same, but taking
However, if Aki-sensei has not come to school today
Really?
Together may be the head?
Huh?
.Amkan possible Ndarh.ghyr
.Ah here food
At least hungry Nmymvnym
.Yeah
Did something happen?
... um, Takrv Kun
what?
... um, well, bathroom
Huh?
! Please do not look back, no matter what happens
.OK
! Do not heard
! Impossible one hand I can
Therefore loudly sing
What
! Or listen to me
!So...! I can not pull myself and I
... My grandfather clocks
.Shrmndm
no problem. We have here all the time and deal with it?
.Yes. The front should not take yourself
!Sorry
You've missed what I think about him Sir Terry
What do you mean by these words?
.Ah, sorry, sorry
,Not
... well, normally
! Aki Sensei
! It is as if we are inseparable
! Japan unit numbers
! We could have had more time to go
Without hesitation I want to do something like this
... but it feels like he was ashamed and embarrassed Zdst
...I can not
.Khdaya for all the blessings that you have bestowed upon us thank
How was it?
, Since I live so long only
It's my seasoned tailored
! Super delicious
... when you cook so well, I'm sure it'll be a good wife
In fact, it does not matter
.Bbkhshyd, Takrv Kun
Oh, Zrfa! Come together Bshvrymshvn
.OK
Takeshi Chan. Seriously, where did you go?
Sensei .ky
No need to go to the bathroom
... Even if two day Nariman bathroom
.As the school doctor, will not let you accept such an unhealthy habit
.Bayd go to the bathroom
No, but now
! Thanks for thinking of me, Takrv Kun
But I'm Khvbm.yh ideas
Sensei .ky
.Takrv kun, you can now take the blindfold
Really? Really sure?
.no problem
This was for us to put you Chmdvny
This idea was Mkhsvsm
.Khvb, let's go
.Yes
.listen . Relax
.Ag·h right, you really led me everything
! Status and understand
Huh? what did you say?
!Nothing
.Mmnvn waiting Mvndy.hala, go in the tub
.OK
The use of such a large bathroom when Safa was just the two of us did our .azsh
.it's true
! Calm down! Calm down!
Who would be here all Makn .kashky
.Yeah
! When we came home, whenever you loved me, I Malsht
! Now, relax your mom, son
Did something happen? Do you feel dizzy?
You gonna get out?
No. I'm fine
.Vaqa? Let's see
.Alan do not do
The sides Look
! Is getting worse.
I .fkr much hot water you get out Bvdy.bya
.Not
.I am good
!Not
! Control yourself now, Takrv Kun
! Takrv Kun
Just a dream
... everything just
.Sbh Good, Takrv Kun
Oh, Aki Sensei Dress
Lord, is about what you're talking about?
After much that you go the bathroom stayed intelligence
Tenet suit, I could get knocked up here and force .kly Byarmt
I fell asleep immediately .bdsh
Oh, so
...excuse me
... I have this down
. All we're trying, and I see that part of
.very cute
After today, I can go home.
.Bbkhshyd that you got involved
.do not worry
.Ah, I was done,
.Hy, Takrv Kun
Yes?
.Kl day you stay home tired Knndst
As long as we're here, because I Let us not enjoy this holiday?
Huh?
OK?
are you okay?
.Thankful
.Yhv middle of the day after the storm
Takrv ass! See her?
What I saw?
.Lbas see her Zyrmv.tv
...Sorry
But it was coincidence
I .shvkhy! After that everything that we experience, that's not important
We even went to the bathroom
Sensei .ky
Raad and Cyrenaica. Just
.I know
! There is a time lag between the sound and light to us, so do not close
! I know, I know, but I'm afraid
Can I just stay a while?
.Yes
I have a lot of Msrfm
Even though I'm older, and Mlmtm, I'm dependent on you
.no problem
You've missed a girl, so typical that you want to be afraid of lightning
So do you think?
This is what I believe
.Mmnvn, Takrv Kun
.no problem
Hey, you really think you get me one?
Huh? What do you get?
.Spouse
Spouse?
.Dyrvz, after a meal, you told me
That I can get a good wife
I really think I'm a good wife?
.Existence
.Mtmynm you are
.Ky Sensei, you're beautiful, stylish, and wonderful cooks are
From my point of view, practically a perfect woman
I feel the world in you
Even if a man were ever to be Nzashth?
Just because you are quality flowers
It was hard to hear Return to Mrdayy the nearest Sing
You ... do you think?
!Yes
Even a guy who I admire'm single school does not
...Even me
even you?
Even you, what?
Even I ... I Thsynt
I wanna be your lover?
.Yeah
Rvst you want me to do?
.Yes
.Thankful
You've missed so much kindness, Takrv Kun
This is true
I'm really Thsynt, Aki Sensei
...So
.Alan good position
... Aki-sensei, do you mean
Thunderbolt?
... No, she
! Kagvzvchy
! And forth.
!Sorry
! No, I'm not to blame
... um, I
I have not seen anything! Seen anything
.Lier
.Bbkhshyd, saw
But I think if you do not have to be difficult
Huh?
! Oyama Takrv
.hạrwnh
Senpai .hymgamy
You scrolled doing here?
We are going to give one 's home country
.Kadmy Tnby interesting island Okino
.Hds that we were Karki can be, and hes certainly became our suspect
Chan Takeshi? What are you doing, Aki-sensei's why a place like this it?
! Sw’h understanding renovation, Aaron
Mother Aki Sensei sent us here by force
So, you two, what are you guys here?
In fact, do nothing
.Avm, we had dinner together and we shower together
And slept on a bed
! I do not say
Zimmermann?
Can you explain yourself?
I told you
Aki .madr Sensei element used to handcuffs on me unannounced us
This time we all got together .mjbvr
Element bracelet?
Where is the bracelet that you talk to him?
! Not Disappear
! Thank God, Takrv Kun
!It is not good at all
... Takeshi Chan
! Such a ridiculous lie together Kurdish
Like a real-life situation that you're there you Manga
! Reality blur, believes Ken! Aaron
! Okay, I understand
!Not
! Into the sky, Mvrakvma
!Again
Aki Nijō Sns·h really nice, is not it Aynahv Chan?
Hashem's breast .blh.v Gndst! Even larger than the size K
.Hrdv knowledge as school doctor and his skills as an art teacher very impressive
I do not tell .darm
Hair is super Braqshm
And her skin is so fine
Only students who admired they are not boys, even girls as they admired
You've missed all the time with such a teacher were alone
You've missed a South Island
! Did you two live together
! Welcome to
.I did not do anything
I've used all my strength to control myself and I
After a bad Trtybshv wanted?
! Takrv SAMA, too indecency
... just so that I
! Bahooneh ugly, Oyama Takrv
.Bbkhshyd, the Crow-kun. But thanks
! I could not experience love for the first time
See keep it as a memento
.Aynja celebrated auruycyه
, In order to become a future member of the student council
.Tmasha that's how I practiced spend a hell Salmndarn
"Next episode:" Shrvray student corrupt
.Hfth later, the student was full of love
Now we've done it!
Episode 5
「Begging    Teacher」
m 29 0 b 25 5 22 11 20 17 b 13 17 6 19 0 21 b 3 26 8 30 13 35 b 11 41 10 48 11 54 b 17 52 23 49 29 46 b 34 49 40 52 47 55 b 47 48 46 41 45 35 b 50 30 54 26 58 21 b 52 19 45 17 39 17 b 37 11 33 5 29 0
Episode 6
「Villainous Student Council!」
How to Brush Your Teeth
Guide to Balanced Eating
m 421 36 l 529 83 531 119 421 70
Infirmary
Translated by :
end_boy
Forums‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏animworld‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏net
Translated by :
end_boy
Forums‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏animworld‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏net