Http: // Forums. Animworld. Net Presents anime world
Translation and Editing: DiarY
Tnby Academy,
Where people with special powers. As "elements" was recognized as the accumulation period
However, destruction, when some of the students,
Nasrshvn for evil purposes of use, began.
Academy knew the current state of the
Security .kmyth consisting of students formed
They specialize in the use of weapons Makn holy name,
To control and prevent others were
. Who were known as Makn
Good morning, mowing.
Hurry, Dyrmvn to be!
Every time you play vandalism!
Emma's going to be an example of the use of their Ghryzshvn!
But it does not mean that every time you have the elements to be punished!
Aynahv chan, hurry up!
Mvndyn ashamed that wait.
Mowing?
Do not say you want to bring him to school?
Same kind of thing!
Today I want to play with him.
Ghar recently increased all that much, I do not notice it!
Mowing can understand what he says?
Of course not!
I felt that I just do not want to!
Oh, Bykhya L.
Roadside mowing It's all come so far and I can play with him.
That painful!
If the reports was not going to do nice,
The other is now being worked over.
Up meetings, reports and other paperwork wars
Let us work hard to Tmvmshvn, okay cha chan?
I wait a little, mowing.
Indeed, if they had wanted to work together, okay?
When it ends then?
GSM and not to do so.
Well, let's all do Tlashmvn!
Okay!
Your very last chance!
I'd just rest Lucette card!
That heard the saying "I accept even help a cat"?
Although Byfaydst that I said to a normal cat.
What happened, Tarzan?
Han?
John!
What!?
Han!?
What's going on?
Opps, I...!
What's going on might have been?
Gvsham, Grbst ears!
Zvky Senpai, tail won!
Orochi, one needs to tell you!
Maybe we...
Listen and behave very strange cat!
They are a cat girl!
Glad to be alive!
Ksafta!
Why are you so happy, Tarzan?
What I'm saying!
What if I'm really a cat!
Wait, I see a real cat's meow letters do not mix!
Mowing is an element?
The incident, which was the only conclusion I was!
That's right.
So do not stare at me, Nia!
But why a cat's normal element!
Monzon, or whatever you're called!
When every day is influenced by your element,
Most likely familiar with it and wont!
Familiar and accustomed them?
I think he's better than me.
Maybe that's exactly the question you did!
But did not explain why it happened this time was a cat!
Well, why do not you two people Mvndyn it safe?
Maybe not control!
Hey, how are you bringing others up to normal?
Stupid cat!
Oh damn, they are so funny!
It's a strange feeling!
Harvkv Senpai, the tail is very cute, Nia!
Really, Nia!
If I die, do not Pyshmvn!
This non-Ok, ok!
I can not believe that I was stupid to become a girl cat!
You'll never really my coat!
Wow, how much they Nazn!
Do not resist!
Our bodies naturally act in their instinct!
You can not win in front of us!
I feel miserable!
Immediately, because a thing...
After tight places like Adam was feeling...
Relax, Nia!
Senpai very Nazn Hymgamy cat ears!
G - say cute?
What kind of talk is anybody stupid!
Listen!
The largest is power to control instinct....
Nia!
Bbkhshyn!
In a coffee shop the other of cat!
Miriam, really Urumqi tersebut.
How many cats here!
Of course it is!
This season seasonal why cats love!
Love, huh?
You do not think in it now!
Tonight the moon perfect!
When a cat's instinct to brutalize the game!
Relax!
I'm not a cat!
I see?
@Devkt searches steals this or not!
Takrv SAMA, Nia!
Aynahv Chan?
Right there, right there, Tarzan...
This Mkhsvsyh who tapped their favorite cats!
Well, I can not decide what was then a Grbst!
That's right!
Takeshi, Tarzan...
He laughs...
Aum...
I'm pathetic!
Probably the first time I see a full moon so beautiful!
Takrv SAMA, Nia!
Aynahv Chan What's the matter?
Nothing.
Mowing?
A - This is...
By the time my heart more efficient!
Kind of thing.
Well, Bkhatrh is that all...
Very relaxed.
They behave the same beautiful cats!
Huh? My body moved his mark!
Han?
Damn, this Drdsrsaz·h!
Ppt week blameless nor coward!
What misfortune of being stuck.
Indeed, the mowing Where?
Have not seen him since yesterday!
Aynahv Chan?
Takrv SAMA, Nia!
Dear?
I can not hold myself back.
I want to be with me, come!
He himself was shown!
E - hey, wait, Aynahv Chan...
Aaron!
Um, this...
Cats showing Laqshvn's what they got!
Takeshi, Nia!
So it's really....
We're together, baby!
B - kid?
Takeshi, Nia!
Takrv SAMA, Nia!
A - This is...
Do not tell Gyryshvnh breeding season!
What
After that...
A - Yvsvyy, do not tell...
Hymgamy Senpai, let the cat play together!
I digress again!
The poor Jftay not interested.
I want my life to someone that,
Be strong like my brother!
This is mine, Tarzan!
Even if you have it in your head Nmydmsh, Nia!
Drdsryh being nice guys!
Gann.
I got my Mykharh!
I decide what to do!
Ndadmsh done yet!
Takeshi, Nia!
Let's create a beautiful baby!
Takrv SAMA, Nia!
I love you!
I want to give a child life, Nia!
Takeshi, Nia!
Taکro medal!
Oyama Takrv!
I can take anymore!
I know very Hyfh,
But this is wrong!
Shane up!
I was what?
Embarrassing!
I can not believe I lost my instinct!
Thanked God.
All back to normal!
But this... Yet...
Let's create a couple of kids!
All stimulation!
Kind of thing.
Right now we have the instincts of a cat!
Should the owner of this element, the mowing, the draw here!
Aynahv Chan, sorry, but you must bring it back and the cat...
Well, yesterday Have not seen him!
Gone somewhere.
What
Bkhatrh the Gondi who fled might be raised?
No way.
Mowing can not...
I'm going to look after him.
Aynahv chan!
Currently, mowing and Aynahv Chan Mysprm to you, so that Tarzan!
I thought Hymgamy to mark the rest of the match.
Nia.
Okay.
Takeshi, granddad, take it.
Aynahv Chan.
It did not work.
Mowing...
It's possible that...
Damn, why Come sit down!
What's going on here?
And while I do!
Of Cat Thief!
Pull your hand from my mates.
I have no regrets!
Stop're kids, Nia!
Harvkv Senpai!
I got all my best to give your kids life Senpai.
I'm sure that all of them were cute.
Orochi, Nia!
Bsprsh to me.
To control all the loss and they behave like cats.
Hymgamy, with Ghryzsh with him.
Mowing.
Mowing!
Are you there?
Hey mowing!
Aynjayh really?
It was a guess,
I thought Aynjarv love mowing.
Mowing.
There!
Thanked God.
Come now all back to normal.
But, how are you going to be back to normal Brgrdvnymshvn, Takrv SAMA, Nia!
Oh, right!
Even if Qdrtshm understand, but still do not know how the rest of the bringing back to normal.
So find Krdnshm Byfaydst!
In any case, should Bgyrymsh.
Not move, mowing.
Hold it right there, Wait!
Wait, come!
Mowing.
So like that, mowing?
I'm sorry, Tarzan!
Mowing.
Elemental powers that cat!
It was like a dream!
I slept good.
He said he was feeling lonely.
If you thought all cats jump him into the game.
I'm sorry mowing.
After Myfhmysh.
Huh? Yeah.
So it is've noticed, eh?
Mowing the Manvhara loves you?
The first time we saw each other was Avjayy.
Hrdvmvn mark the memory of Angyzyh.
Always a wave Bahatm.
So it went like this.
Enough of my other cats.
Talk less and work more.
What do I got?
Create cards do, so that Tarzan!
Miriam.
It was funny.
Pooh! Crazy.
You were really funny, Hmygamy Senpai.
Hey!
Just delete it now!
Bgyrsh rice.
But, the reason that girls become only the cat...
After mowing a cat forget!
I'm in love with manga!
Does not count I read or design!
Coase made me love!
No matter Bpvshmsh with my Ngash!
When we combine the manga and Coase made...
Translation and Editing: DiarY
Http‏‏:‏‏//Forums‏‏.‏‏Animworld‏‏.‏‏Net