Student Council Office
Sparks will
emit from this side
Drag
Security Club
There's a private school in which students get together. With the power to control the elements
The school was known as the Academy Tnby
But here in this school
Mvzayy housed are trying to create difficulties gave Nasrshvn
,for solving this problem
School decided the group of student council was formed. The student leadership
That magical known as the Organization for Security Mission
Using Gnjyh's called sacred Makn
.Avna trying to stop the people that are going to take offense
When referred to the students as they .mrdm Makn
... This is a Mhbth, but
.Jhan is about ability for users like us does not know
When we use the element and Maknmvn
.Mytvnym terrible power to summon
Fool that you were drowning Qdrtshvn
And always tapped themselves
... In order to control this type of people
Academy Tnby
, Where those of us living in it.
Student Council was formed after a .sy
In other words,
We need to police ourselves Academy
.... So, going to the point, the head of school holidays
Um ... I ... what was it again?
, While the head of Ghaybh
We are gathering people to join the student council are
So you can establish better security academy
! He's exactly right.
So as an alternative to President
I, Rvkvjv minor, I command you
.Come and join us
! Tagayashy say
... After unlike stole my desire
! Do not give me orders
I Student Council President, Rvkvjv Mynvrym
I secretaries and members of the police, Akim Nijō
.Mnm treasurer, Amado am Tvmyka
...veto
! You're the fourth member, who after his service duties, Tagayashy say
I still did not agree to join you, I
And service tasks do you mean what?
You're the one who's made this Makn, right?
.What a great talent
.Tagayashy kun, please use your skills for student council
I do not .qbvl
.Ag·h Makn want me, then you must pay his expenses
Very meanness! Why do not you any true free?
I Maknm professional repairman
. As a professional, I have Mzdmv
Huh?
!it got bad
With Makny that was true Kun Tagayashy
Security could not establish'll Academy ....
Even in this moment, the possibility of getting students
You've missed a terrible accident that have come about with the element to be caught
! Ok, Dad
! Sure, I joined
!Bravo
.Mmnvn for cooperation
But I have one condition
! I do not want to lend to you or you make Makny
.Hah? So no point in us not
.Ag·h Nkhvay Makn make, so just a worthless offender
Want to see how your body uses Mfydm?
.Gfty body? Perverted
... A-Om
Here's student council, which helps solve problems Academy?
Who says we're solving elements and the Academy will establish security?
That's why we're clean swimming pools?
.Azmvn do want to do it, then he can not decide
Makn menu to be sure you're cleaning? For something you guys need them?
Council 's foot was a new student status
So does this do to gain the trust of students is important
.Gl said, Op Chan
Really?
! Op
Home?
What
Why am I the one who is wearing the same bikini?
By the nature of the student council showed all bad
Is your .khvrak, Aki
! I mean, since these Mhshrn
... said, show all
But only those who are here
What the hell are you guys?
! Hey!
We need some help down there .angar Darren
.Hy, pretty boy
JRT .chtvr hand did she leave me
Girl?
... Saku nuهana
One of the three goddesses Academy Tnby, Sacco Nvhana
.H, the beautiful young lady
But I just got her a love letter
Of course, I was not going the way of love
...Only
.Mahyt me as he was my love Dione
What Mrgshh that guy?
Unfortunately, a man is narcissistic
! Do not be too cocky
! Anasrh
! Op
! He demonstrated knowledge of Mvzyh
Who ngyrtt
!Hold on
.هftyr Maken, fraud
.Avnm a user Maknh
Thou
! Hey!
Why did you shoot him?
.Dfa of his own
what did you say?
! Tagayashy Kun, fast Give clinic
No, you do not need
Just sleeping
This Nsryh shot that puts the impact on mental state
Hypnosis may work, right?
!it's true
.Chy? Why did not you say earlier
No reason to want to explain something Interface
... but I just wanted him to Bfhmvnm
.Nbayd head to head Bzarh
.Dfh the next shot is just a warning and a threat Nmykhvabvntsh.avn
!Hey you
! To join us
Huh?
I do not .qbvl
See what your group was not interested
Please look for another one Bgrdyn
Ah, but you familiar with student council, is not it?
Just heard the gossip,
Ago what are you thinking?
I was accepted .fkr Pyshnhadmv
.Chshmash so it seemed that he was going to join us
.student council
... If approached me for that matter, was impressed, but
Perhaps too high Grftmshvn
Embarrassed, I Mtlt?
No, not a problem
Kaya.sal .kvday first class C.
.Nmrat excellent and skilled in sports
Many fans attracted to good-looking Typshn
But it is extremely narcissistic
.What an interesting person
More Rajbsh know .mykhvam
! If this is a command from're the boss ... Nin Nin
.Khyly the boy favorites
.Mg·h told you? He seemed to be in favor of Grvhmvn
What makes you such a thought?
Women .bsyrt
So, it does not happen like that. Women's intuition told him something that can not
what do you mean?
I want Hyjysh interface, naughty kids?
.Ah, Khdaya.shma two've come together very well
! Explain
! Guys, this is terrible
Home?
This is what the cameras recorded the disciplinary committee
.Hvm? The office of Directors
Look .bdqt
He was in the open?
What's going on?
You head office
We Makn use of a camera that can capture any activity after the users get
, Some of which are almost Makn of someone's hide
But if the thing they use, the camera must be specified
Therefore, they recorded any activity .dvrbyna
Maybe they used a type of remote control Makn?
But now any student you Tnby Academy there with such Makny
So, it could be possible to work out a stranger is?
Yes, probably the same kind of thing
What you got all the criminals stealing a safe that was hard?
Money?
.Asnad administrative matter related to the establishment of the Academy
! Op Chan
.no problem
Why would convict them?
Creation Tnby big secret governments Academy
If such documents in the public's Adaryy
What do you think happens?
.Rsvayy grows
And the nature of the Academy might have been compromised
.The goal fleshly
.Khvb, documents that this time the offender has Tqlbyh
But now enough
To fight the foreign forces have
Unlike expected, we'll need
.Hmvntvr the chairman of the disciplinary committee expected
!Beautiful
!Excellent
And Randy
! He's the one who told Randy to write letter of apology to the Back to School
.Ag·h want to reject the request of a beautiful woman putting this hurt me
But answer me like a prayer, no matter how many times you ask
But do not understand
Why do you disagree strongly with join us?
Even though he's a foreigner and commands within the Academy's mission was to manage post
How do you know it?
We also have our own skilled people facing side
If we have a common goal, why should not we work together?
Kaya .kvday
I do not .qbvl
... because we have a common goal
I do not want you to be a group that
.Mhafzt of the Academy as a joke as they
We're just playing around their .fkr
I'll show .bhsh
People who are in earnest of the game
! Hot passion without doing that than Dmayn that Karshvnv
.Nqth blind and lost his
.Nknh think you can sneak a normal man arrived here after
I was strongly believes that a common man
Let us not enter because of the surrounding fence was Tnby
! Unfortunately, we are not here Information Office
We fountain in the garden is a trap you Gzashtym
! Control of their long-range free
! Tagayashy Kun
.I see. Ironically, it was you, Kodály Kaya
See what you need? I'm just enjoying the evening breeze Mybrn
... so that you're here Nyst.lty
? Because the four eye care was the one who was hiding there.
! You're one of the three goddesses Tnby, Sacco Nvhana
Onah criminal?
.of course not
He is a pure and innocent girl
. However, there is currently controlled
Therefore, he was the one who slipped into the office head
.Drsth, they were controlled from a distance by a real criminal element
When I came here I was a criminal, but you trap
.Ag·h to cut its natural state Grdvnym, we may Ryysshvnv
! Hey! Wait a moment
! Ashtbah.ashtbah
.Bavrm did not find the menu
I .mmknh least Grftmtvn
... You
! Not move from spices
This woman is my hostage
He is everything I ask of it was done
.like this
! Or
Secretly I always do my mission, but they could not match
In exchange for the life of this girl, so my documents
... Well, hurry up
! I do not accept
! Enter the Student Council
Chi Chi? Why dressed like that?
"We also are implementing the program" CUDA join Kayaym
Passion?
! Tvmyka
!Yes
! Stop! Hostages
From inside their shadow 'em, controlled
All Karary did the night shadows to hide his .btvnh
But using light fireworks
. Place it in a trap
! Clever is not it? This is our secretary
! Huh! Do not stare at it that way.
I got my gun towards my goal .dvst adultery unless it is necessary
.Bda you sin sinking
Well, does not want to wait until later. Now I Ghrqt
What
Like a Mrdabh
! I can not move my hands and walk
Who? Who hired you?
So my answer is not .lazm
But I just want to say something
A lot of people are
See you are looking for power potential
If I was free
... could I use this Makn
! Say, it was me
! I'll pay his expenses
...So
! Bean soup, red price you have to pay
A Makn?
But where do you think it fallen?
What
! Bastards
What is this light?
... I Fen shadow
With Makny you made time unemployed
! He summons a lot of power
He is the crazy woman
Gan, Makn What's the name?
Hey, now, who cares for these things?
.You're right
... username wool Maken
.Dstkshh
Dragon Ace!
What annoying
No way ! That's it?
.Mydvny, I'm a genius Nsrm
.Qdrty me so much that I can not go to a regular school
... That's why this place
.Kadmy Tnby ... a special place for me.
We got this place is like a paradise built with our own hands
So if you ask me my life I choose, or the Academy
! No question, I have chosen Tnby
! IGNITE
Dragon Ace!
!Gun
what is this?
This cannon power Nsrh
.Damn
You've missed a lot of consideration
...But
.Angar everything was resolved
So?
Now you want to join the student council?
You've missed, ya'll
... Whatever Bkhvayn're protected from the Academy
! That's not bad Shkhsytvn experience
All of us arriving on the student council, let's welcome
... And so, through this dramatic story
! Who was born student council and the first Makn
Not that great? Not that great?
.I see
Yes, no matter how many times you repeat this story, I never get tired I will not
However, the thirty-seventh time the stories you
He is never tired I can not
... But no matter how many times I hear
! See you sensei Aki high school days should be awesome
I also wear the shameful Nmypvshydm
And the story goes on
.Azay student council and club magical security
... Now, a fool who Nsrsh for stealthy sight
Women .rkhtknh used in-test
... such a waste deviant
! Should be punished
! Obey
Getting deviant I can not change one or two failures
! Right there Vasa
! You're the same guy last time
! You guys again.
! Guys, step back Nkshyn
! Obey
Every thing you want to do this
In our location
In heaven we will protect it.
.Azay Makn who had inherited the responsibility Mybrn
In the meantime, you'll Mrdmyd
! Japan unit numbers
! Asklay stupid
! I did not say that you can go to here
The last part
And so, in the long Makn
Student Council Office
Sparks will
emit from this side
Drag
Security Club
Translated by :
end_boy
Forums‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏animworld‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏net
Translated by :
end_boy
Forums‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏animworld‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏net