Usui Kengo
Ooyama Takeru
leaves Aho
Minaya Uruchi
Security Club
There's a private school in which students get together. With the power to control the elements
The school was known as the Academy Tnby
But here in this school
Mvzayy knowledge that had created problems trying to bring .nasrshvn
,for solving this problem
The school council decided the group of students, student leadership at the tactical
That magical known as the Organization for Security Mission
Using Gnjyh's called sacred Makn
.Avna trying to stop the people that are going to take offense
When referred to the students as they .mrdm Makn
Let seemed this time of year we have a new member
This 4 this year when the first Salyh to join Makn
.Khvb, the two so as not Bhsshvn
.it's true. However, they die
.Ksayy between Lapashvn things they were removed from the list
San Aynahv what?
...Good
! Mowing, love
He is a pure heart. But I do not think student council lead to pain
Those who were excluded goal Srshvnh
... which means
What I learned next candidate member of the Council?
.Yes. Nsrt habits writings, and serious nature
All of these traits makes you eligible for .zv to have the student council
I Jvnh're right?
If your heart wants to join us, nitrogen want. In a special training camp now you
... training camp?
!I understood! I will try my best
... I am a member of the student council
And Haruka Senpai's likely next president
! I'm a member, I am always with him in one organization
.Yvrvchy Sun, Krvatt loose
Now that like me you are a member of student council
.Bayd check account status parlors
! Excuse me, boss Harvkv
.Bzar you make it
!No way
! His face is too close
! She smells so good
And if out of Josh Svtyntm
.Khvb, now better
Yes, this is great
.This is great
! ywhww
!Yeah
.Vav, your training camp deep in Kvhstanh
.Yh quiet place with fresh air
Really?
Quiet place with fresh air, huh?
with .yvrvchy
Huh?
The intent is good, but you did not want to bring too much pressure
.Ykm rest and tea
.Yes
.Ah, Yvrvchy Sun, a little cream the Svrtth
Huh?
I clean .brat
What if something happen?
.Khvb, we
.Ah, yeah
Huh?
.Mntzrt we Minaya Sun
What
.Aynja where I taught the art of the ninja Yvkachan
I hope these exercises overcome Yvrvchy Sun
with .mynaya
, To become a member of student council
.Nyaz to have the courage to enter the next stage door
First, tests that are brave enough or not
So, what do you mean
, Um, I'm jumping the result did not give
But I really do not want the bungee jumping, going?
.no problem
wait! No problem what do you mean?
!wait
Now, Minaya Sun
.Shjatt Show and go to the next step
! No! I can not jump from here.
But ... But if I can not
.Nmytvnm with Senpai Harvkv Bakery time you have student council
! Yvrvchy Sun, the show me Shjatt
! Jump me a hug
! Harvkv Senpai! Yvrvchy completely Mkhlsth
! I want to go to the next step
, Minaya san, I'll join the student council
.Yh life full of turmoil in Antzarth
.Dstgah rodeo to prevent the launch of Mvqyth
... No matter how you look at it, this
.Dstgah Svarkaryh
...no but
.Dstgah Svarkaryh, Minaya Sun
No, too mired
... But if I can make it up, Senpai Harvkv
.Angar ready
!it's impossible! Impossible! Impossible
This is absolutely impossible.
... Harvkv Senpai
... Harvkv age
! Harvkv Senpai
! E-e-Haro-Haro-hacking
! Harrow-hack-hack-Haro
.Khvdt suppressed and even fire can be cold
.Khvasth of secularism the full resolution cleaner and brush
... Harvkv Senpai! I'm all
!Focus
! Remove worldly desires! Remove worldly desires
! Do not think of other things
! Yes, Yvrvchy Sun, hard work
!Focus
! Harvkv Senpai
.Angar rehearsals are going well Yvrvchy Sun
.Yes. It's an interesting way to overcome tests began thinking about Amaya Harvkvyh
.Ahsasatsh partly non-natural
.Ahsasat again become a great power was stronger than
.Avna may combine to form a strong body, like you and eruption
Is .blh.ahtmalsh
... However,
.Ag·h feelings is a way, not to become a real partner up
This is what I wanted to say, right?
I hope during his later work was realized
I had a good training camp card.
.Shnydm well it back on scam
...So
... I would like to say I agree with you, but
Still some other things that should not complete
, Minaya Sun for next week
I want to secretly monitor all the activities of Vice President, Amaya got under way have
And everything that you view reports
Muppet puppets, huh?
See all seemed to have fun
Perhaps I should have a hobby
.Nbayd to something I think
The focus on Kar.kar
What a doll made of Harvkv Senpai?
that...?
! Japan unit numbers
Haruka Senpai! Why such a freakin doll making?
... I heaven
21: 15 minute bathroom
Began to clean up his left arm
, And continued on his chest
, And while the washed area Shkms
Max .yh moment he pulled the skin of the navel
I added .vzn
After eating ice cream
.Dndvnashv brushed and went to bed
.Yvrvchy san, thank you for the hard work you've got to stand up menu
No, you do not need to thank me.
! Everyone does this, do this do that I'm a member of student council
After that you were a member of student council
.Rvz·hay sweet together starts Bvdnmvn
Senpai .harvkv
What do you mean sweet days?
...I mean
.Harvkv Senpai, can not
!Not
What if something happen?
What should I do, Senpai Harvkv?
Ham really larger .synh
! Trowel me too! Thankful
.neither nor
!Come with me
... What! As long as the breasts is
! What are you saying? Takeshi stupid
.Tkalyfm over
.Takh Chan, thank you waited
I finish .tkalyfm
! Yai
! Haruka Senpai exactly after my work
.Harvnh, if you finish homework, give of my transcript
This is exactly what he said,
what are you saying?
.Bayd do the homework yourself.
In addition, we have the same goal.
After one not Tkalyfmvnm
.Ah, right
.Khdaya, so that Chan, much confusion
Even if he is a pitiful waste, Senpai good work he is having .darh Harvey
.Sbr now, the only doll
Why am I so upset?
...But
! Aaron
! Takeshi stupid
! Japan unit numbers
... This is nothing! As long as there's Chest
.Hrf that's exactly what the real doll, putting an increased Oyama Takrv
! Aaron
... but mine
Senpai really is not .harvkv
He is never say it will not.
, Harvkv Senpai all the bad things it knows, the lack of values
E. inherently distorted
... I understand it was not quite like
.it's true
At first I wanted to be like Senpai Harvkv
... I wanted her to the point where I can be useful, but later
, So I should be the one to know what he thinks about
And mostly what they do.
...but me
Huh? Namzdyt as the Council of Midi-dropout?
but why?
My dream was to join student council I
And with Harvkv Senpai Together we work, who admire
. With this goal in my mind I could come after the exercises
But I realized that my feelings now.
.All was selfish and one-sided
.Shkhsy like me, could not believe the feelings of others
Still inexperienced for my position
I learn eligible to join the student council
Let seemed finally realized you were
Huh?
.Drsth still inexperienced
But you could understand this reality
That the conditions you become the student council got a future .zv
Huh?
They were people who realized their mistakes are those who have dreamed .balakhrh way to find out.
Now the only thing you need to do a walk in the right path
Yes, your goal may still be out of reach, but should be able to handle it
! Senpai, I'll do my best
I'm definitely a member of student council
So, let's start
Huh?
Um, this ...?
with .mynaya
You want to get that perfect someone who Mvzyh student council, right?
.Ag·h like that, you have to complete training
I .mntzrt, Yvrychy Sun
, I let quite Rvshnt
I like my little sister, I am compassionate
.Khryd sudden a teddy bear
Then you start to move and spoke
All the latest women's demands
"Next episode:" Her name Rvdvlh
When nitrogen was passing, the only thing you hear is moaning Sdan
.Karmvn over
Episode 6
「Villainous Student Council!」
Episode 7
「His Name Is Rudol!」
Student Council Meeting Minutes
Security Club
Usui Kengo
Ooyama Takeru
leaves Aho
Minaya Uruchi
Security Club
Translated by :
end_boy
Forums‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏animworld‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏net
Translated by :
end_boy
Forums‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏animworld‏‏‏‏‏‏.‏‏‏‏‏‏net