Http: // Forums. Animworld. Net Presents anime world
Translation and Editing: DiarY
Tnby Academy,
Where people with special powers. As "elements" was recognized as the accumulation period
However, destruction, when some of the students,
Nasrshvn for evil purposes of use, began.
Academy knew the current state of the
Security .kmyth consisting of students formed
They specialize in the use of weapons Makn holy name,
To control and prevent others were
. Who were known as Makn
I am calling a student of yoga Amado Force Base
I just heard that...
Theft and assault that took place on Tnby
By Shymvyanagy Mahyrv, 21-year-old was
Member of the Academy
Now moving out of the building.
Well...
Field Jlvmvn standing
So please Trtybshv this
Necessarily
Let's go, Aynahv.
Eyes!
Maken laptop هak!
Maken nukl kamudu!
So you're now Makn members.
In terms of coming up strong.
However...
What is your opinion about this?
Oh, they are striped.
Why are you so euphoric because?
Enough other.
He's...
One of the eight original Makn
Mwrạḵwmw!?
Aaron!
Why the "Nsrt" Why do you use?
What's wrong is from my own strength I use?
I see.
So as a member, who Makn
I am letting go of my power, do not stop.
Oh, do not hit the scary talk.
No matter how strong you are but a woman and she!
I still got a little modesty.
As a boy I is not got.
Oh, an elephant.
Well, today was supposed to be cold... Totally am...
Without Dfayd now!
Takeshi chan!
Great.
Now Geert cast!
Aaron!
Maken atrnal amprur!
Takeshi chan!
He Kjayh?
Aaron!
Miriam, strength lyric!
Condition sleep, Aaron?
Are you wounded?
who are you?
Who am I?
Aaron, actually...
... Ktdه the Teesta
part 2
「I love my ass Takrv ♥」
Do not think there is external damage,
Mghzysh waves and Nbzshm typical rate.
I also took a blood test,
But something was not changed.
Then we extract Hafzshv,
Well, this is not always related to Hafzsh
I tried "Nsrsh" I check the time,
But his presence I could feel Harvkv.
This means that...
May not be...?
That's right.
Criminal "element" and "Makn" it was him.
Maken Ono?
Hạrwḵw!
Harvkv Senpai!
are you awake?
You...
what?
what is your name?
Takrv.
Oyama Takrv.
Takrv ass.
Something to remember me?
Please please marry me!
Please... Please marry me
What!?
Harvnh, what you say it yourself?
Well, you let me look embarrassing situation,
I can not marry someone.
That's why...
I feel like a real man to accept this responsibility.
Serious things were going to go?
SAMA Takrv my candidate!
Now that's bleeding!
So... I do not care who I (2).
So comfortable it was delivered?
So let's deal with it!
I wish us happy!
Event - Aaron...
We offender, Shymvyanagy Mahyrv
Makn Harvkv memory and took away Senpai?
Yeah.
Mvrakvmv strongest available between 8 Makn
If he was abusing his power...
So then we have to ask where it was earlier.
Mvrakvmv, Hmyntvrm Harvkv San memory.
Maken yesterday members of Ulan dnbalsn.
I see.
As expected Photos Almlt Sryh nitrogen.
Well, Harvkv San How are you?
Bkhatrh loss was Hafzsh discomfort?
Well, I...
I...?
I feel happy.
Go right ahead, Takrv ass.
بگو ‏"‏آ‏"‏
Aaron!
A
If Namrdyh Harvkv Senpai just do that.
Go right ahead, Takrv SAMA.
Khvshmzst?
Um, yeah.
How are you to me?
Well - Khvshmzst.
Takrv kun, from here is eat.
Hymgamy Sun, carefully listen
I want Harvkv San Consider the following,
And sure it happened between him and Oyama Nmyvfth ass.
Okay, I'll do whatever I can.
Even if you find the culprits are sure to succeed,
If you ignored the wants of Makn Harvkv Senpai, what are you doing?
Of course I will fight,
The Avlshm wanted to fight someone who is Kvrakvmv.
It was strange.
Uncle snpay?
Do not you think Takrv Oyama had the opportunity memory loss Harvkv Senpai
It's an interesting and strange things interesting, huh?
Probably the same kind of thing.
Even those efficient?
Maybe.
Anything faster memory should move it back.
Otherwise, here's condition worse.
تا yebr - when!
تاکر ru - when!
Takrv - kun!
Takrv ass!
Pshtsht came face-wash.
I... Hard ndạrn, Miriam...!
As wife...
No, as a secondary wife
May their forth, blur Rekewti blow!
He hit me cut!
I'm Tmyzt!
how's it?
Takrv Kun, an acute phase?
Feel!
Feel it now!
Hey, what the hell are you doing? You're - - - -
Aynahv is beautiful, do you wash!
I wash forwards, okay?
Namrdyh Aynahv chan!
Why?
Not...
Oh, that is my Makn...
Avyamasa for power.
I do not care what will happen for me.
Here you see is when we were training dojo.
Here is when we see the amusement park,
Here is when you see a scam tips.
Broadly Aaron?
Do not remembered anything?
Takrv ass.
what?
Mygzrvndym time together since childhood always right?
The fate of us put together.
Well, you can call it let boyhood friends.
Childhood friend?
So you can not remember anything?
So do not answer, Takrv.
With the condition that Hafzsh missing,
What does that come to mind.
Zvky'll have to wait for others to make fun of all offenders got stuck.
What if,
The offender interlock Brngrdh bring his memory?
It also has a professional hit.
Allowing it to be true.
Come to believe that...
That certainly before crossbar.
Amaya Harvkv.
Seventeen-year-old.
The second year, the Academy Tnby,
Deputy Palestinian students.
Or so it seems!
Takrv ass!
So you were here.
Could not sleep.
You're trying to remember something about you bring?
No, I was thinking about you.
From?
A picture of all its Bchgymvn under contract, right?
When I look at them I realized something.
I looked up to as a kid.
Even if Josh was Hafzm the head,
I any longer the only relationship I knew, right?
Nmyzashtym put together and did not behave like lovers together.
Uh huh.
What was a coward.
But after losing Hafzm was a good thing.
What!?
That's the second time I was in love with someone.
Miriam.
There was progress, huh?
If I take so I knew I was a member of the group.
Hạrwḵw?
It's possible that...
M - Mydvstm!
E - Harvey - not!
Good morning, Takrv ass!
Good morning.
Here - here, here - a kiss!?
What!? No way!
Miriam?
What are you doing, Harvkv?
I do not remember much larger rep am!
I do not remember that you're older.
Also, I have lost Hafzm.
Nitrogen ask what the hell are you doing?
I had already decided!
Who decided?
I do not want to be the number 2.
I want my legal wife.
Han!?
Aum...
If you get help Hafzm,
You're a second year student, Aoyama are.
I have lost Hafzm,
That's why I came back the first year!
Is that so?
Such a decision impressive!
Let's start after class, okay?
What!?
Well, go to page 48 of the book.
That's right.
Eco-san, Byvkv Kun invited to his room...
If you continue to get this... I'll...
Die.
No problem Zvky Senpai Nevermind'll find the culprits?
I just got around that we want to look useless.
He was convicted of theft and assault,
Makn Harvkv stole the ball cock.
What do you think then?
Then what?
What was that?
It happens.
Taکro medal!
Let's have lunch together.
Han?
What!?
SAMA Takrv Where?
Kun Avyamv before going Senpai Amaya.
This is Senpai Harvkv Dmyh Wow!
Very quick shot.
Miriam.
The protection he got, right?
Yeah.
After we doing here?
I'm sorry, Takrv ass.
I lied.
How much power.
Really awesome.
Until this Makn hold,
I think even I'm not God.
No, up on us,
I was just impressed by the power Mvrakvmv.
Wish I had a good fight,
And as I think I have a real fight with Mvrakvmv.
Zvky Senpai.
As if you're still stuck cargo tragic situation.
So what?
Maken هak!
Let's see how you put up with this.
Dark Claw!
Did you do, Senpai Zvky.
The fight was over.
Now, bring back the memory Harvkv.
What if I disagree?
what did you say?
Card was good, Zvky San.
Boss.
We'll arrange the rest Kararv.
Is not it, Yuka-san?
Yes.
Aaron, administrative chyḵạr rolleyes?
Really, you know that's s already China!
What - why?
I want you
Take your arms,
Take me to the top, Takrv ass.
Takrv Kun, Please Give beautiful Trtybm.
what?
What is his current clothes?
My God, you know what it is.
I do not know.
Nmykhvamm know.
I'm gonna make you bring back the memory Harvkv, okay?
Miriam...
Strange strangers!
Let's not stop.
Nizar make a girl feel embarrassed.
Even if Ayntvrm that you say,
I know,
I'm gonna do it.
Even before returning Hafzm.
Oh no!
I finished the boss.
Card was good.
Takrv ass...
Z - SAMA Yuka, I have 'em back time.
Mygrdvnm take them!
More!
Not seven, not seven!
Aaron, acknowledge Back?
What to do, you...
Catch the goal.
That was unexpected.
Notwithstanding bgyrsh!
Well, it's good to finally have your memory back.
Yeah, thank God.
Hymgamy Sun, Aynahv chan!
I was ashamed that Ngrantvn!
Hmyntvrm,
I do not remember what my performance,
When my memory was the replacement.
Overall I feel that things got strange.
But they are not my actual memory component.
After my performance in 'em, do not
Okay, so that Chan?
B - Yes!
Think I am dare!
Eyes!
As if I treat you like a child.
That's right.
Could not be like that.
Uh wear!
Why are you suddenly confess!
My memory a Ahmqh!
I'm a fool, fool, fool!
Translation and Editing: DiarY
Http‏‏:‏‏//Forums‏‏.‏‏Animworld‏‏.‏‏Net