Http: // Forums. Animworld. Net Presents anime world
Translation and Editing: DiarY
Tnby Academy,
Where people with special powers. As "elements" was recognized as the accumulation period
However, destruction, when some of the students,
Nasrshvn for evil purposes of use, began.
Academy knew the current state of the
Security .kmyth consisting of students formed
They specialize in the use of weapons Makn holy name,
To control and prevent others were
. Who were known as Makn
! Takeshi stupid
.Psr, really wet Rqm
You live the other girls
How many times before I hit enter?
.Wạq‘ terrible, Aaron
I got home late so I took .dvydnm
Senpai Harvnh .sday anger and rage that u
!I knew
SAMA Takrv beaten to death one more time!
! Hold on, Takrv SAMA
See I can not remember anything from my hand
I can now die .fkr
.Aynahv - Chan
.Nbayd not spoiled
.N should
.OK
... God, every morning the same setup
You never get tired of this efficient sit down?
! Good morning, Kodama - Senpai
Oh, good morning
...good morning
.Avyama Takrv
I've never Karat of the pains?
If looking at me with these eyes went bad Hyzt
It was .ntyjsh
! I think you're understanding Milk
, Because he
.Dvbarh arrive late to school
After Nsrt use and short corrugated now.
I .kly takes time to clean this mess Cairo
! Run, hurry up, hurry up
You guys again?
If you do not hurry
Principal's anger floor .bayd wolf Taste
.Takrv - SAMA, to leave
See I do not think, just go
.Bashh, now officially late
Maken kamudu!
!Safe
.Thankful
.Good
... .. Now, all of you go to a special section
! Takrv
Yvsvyy, what?
.Yh situation before coming
! What - what the situation Sksyh
This is a super-awesome location,
But we did not know anything about it
... This
.Vhshtnakh
.Aynahv chan, let's bring the door
.OK
.Kysh, creed, cut cartoon show that is not rejected
However, the work who is this?
.Yvsvyy
You know who's the girl you see?
.Sal first, Kynvshyta Yvmyka Chan
.Zv Archery Club
Fully perform and Supplies
Mark's main objectives.
.Harvnh, I want to ask about the Kynvshyta Sun
Can you come with me?
That's it, let's go
.Aynahv chan, please give this issue the President report
! Obey
.Nmyzarm It's a shame so to finish
Huh unanimously canceled, Miriam?
.Gft one night to the bathroom and saw a black thing
.Angar not remember the rest
Recently there was something suspicious?
It's like a chase or anything like that?
.Angar could not remember anything about this case is the
If there is a possibility that the attacker does not have a personal intentions,
So it's possible there was another similar case
.Slam, Nao - chan
What, again something Chsbvndn information to the board?
Now two were
.Sal Third, Sakura Adachi - San Shymvnya Saki - Sun
Let them seemed Sbgahy Club Theater after training target
.Qbla any incident like this occurred
So it was not personal...
! Boss, and Yucca Senpai
For kids, I know that I have another victim
, As a statement on my behalf, head of student
I ask all members of the student Makn And when they get together for an emergency meeting to hear
you understood?
!Yes
In the case of serial robberies that occurred last night.
Until now we had six victims.
The only common attacks,
.Aynh that all victims are female
Believe motivated the perpetrator of the sexual pleasure of it.
, According to my personal information banks
The guilty man is too much .ahtmalsh
Anyone whose personality is so deviant
All the things you personal toilet and the girl happened
. For this reason, I want to restrict access to these places
And I put this area under tight security protection
Haruka - san, Aynahv - Sun, and Kodama - San .msyvl protect personal places are
.the eye
.Atat
.I understood
.Kymy -Chan and Chacha - San careful dressing room Astkhrn
!OK
! The eyes
Zvky - San Aruch - San responsible .mraqbt rest of the room the girls are
!the eye
! The eyes
.Yvka - Sun and I'll put here Dstvratmvn
Um, then what about us?
What should we do?
Since the aim of the rooms Dkhtrvnst,
So you guys do not have to do this
You are free check of your patrol school grounds
G.-eye
You've missed it, do not we let him was another victim offender
Both go hand in hand student committee and security committee to resolve the case after the body
! Obey
Thief series underwear, huh?
God, this duplex Zmvnh what young people think?
Minor, sure as the principal does not require you to do anything about it?
No, everything row
, Misunderstandings between children should be solved by their
.Hmvntvry we had already done it
Just tell, a former member who Nijō Makn Aki - Sensei?
.it's true
So we got to Chyzshvnm failure, huh?
This could be an opportunity for us. In the room the girls room Astrahtshvn
Did not know which way?
I .shvkhy
But now the use of that room was limited ...
I think Mjrmmvn It 's difficult times.
I hope you are right.
Hey, thief Karshv his underwear again!
What!?
Monet's math teacher...
I did not think about teachers also take targeted.
Rkb us up!
Indeed, so that Chan Ngash do not like.
Miriam.
Do not know the motive of the offender,
But I know who is the next person.
What
This is based on a series of events,
Put forward a specific pattern.
You pass the offender's pattern?
what do you mean?
Harvnh... Not all listen.
The Kynvshyta Yvmyka to Imai Sensei,
We have a total of 7 to the victim.
In fact,
Bra size for each of the victims Mypvshydn,
Respectively increased.
Well - so what?
Well, I do know that the next person who is the captain's target.
Sink your teeth into a moment.
Bras by Runner's Senpai Adachi,
Was wearing a size "F" field.
If the second, Size should "never" be?
This is... The mark, hide,
The main pattern.
This action?
That's right.
Yes, Adachi Senpai size "F" wears,
But his chest Sayz·h "B" are!
Just fill Svtynsh was!
I mean, with the pillow!
Oh, how are you so confident?
I Yvsvyy a few moments ago, we were Senpai Adachi.
A review of her breasts from two different angles,
We could have done a mutiny of his hot chest,
And could not even meet her breast understand the actual size.
The result was that...
His chest Sayz·h "no" were!
Here's the result of our research as breast lovers,
The girls began to stick to the chest.
United breasts theory
What we call the theory of Matt breasts....
I did not need him to tell Qsmtshv.
Eyes!
But if the conclusion Takeshi kun's true,
Until now, many have sacrificed...
A, B, C, D, E, F, G...
That the victim's next of his chest Sayz·h "H" s!
Q - Saیzh "Aچ"!!?
In this school there someone that her breasts are so helpful?
A - Avmm...
Well... Say that...
That's it!
Ykym that is so close to us!
I just Andazsta my breasts!
Kurbon qdrtt God!
Yuka-san, please check the medical school,
M - you can not find someone else with the breast size?
Well, the information we have,
It just Harvkv San Chacha San breasts size "H" numbers.
Ksym If abortion is Ayshala up!
Exactly!
Well, the school board, minor Rvkvjv us.
Her breast size "O" s!
Who is the God of this size there!
I've got, school doctor Aki Nijō were Sensei!
Look!
Sayz·h his chest "when" were!
‏"‏کِی"‏‏!‏‏!‏؟
So the king breasts!
In any case, if the conclusions of Oyama San true,
Constructed next harvkv offering or placing with Uncle!
So the best Frstmvnh!
If those 2 to use as bait and to stimulate the offender, we can...
Nkhyrm, you can not!
Do not do it in any way possible!
Chacha Senpai aside,
You are such a danger was let Harvkv Senpai!
what about me ?
I'll do it!
Harvkv Senpai!
I should have charged his victim!
So, I'll put my bait!
Logging is not, Aaron?
Bkhvayn truth, a little scared,
But Takeshi Chan...
Not... Believe that all of you as members of "Who Makn" scrolled protect me.
Of course we are!
Aaron!
I Mnzvrtv!
Well then,
Harvkv San cha your way through the dressing room that it's hard to wait Mymvnn pool,
I Rfyqtm, let the bait go alone.
We'll guard the front entrance.
S already know what the offender might be that we have a plan,
Finally, I want to caution everyone to follow them.
So instead we Aqaba, huh?
He can not help it!
I promised that I care Harvnh!
A - Online...
The latest issue of "the STR" as the pearl of the Madeleine Mikko Chan.
Oh, what's here?
I'm going to work!
Miriam...
Miriam...!
Yvsvyy, a new expert not?
Someone got Saddam!
If I tell you something!
Okay, Go thy work!
Falling wore Why?
Take the easy target criminals!
Rngshvn not talk, do not you?
New sewn!
Bykhyalyt to feel jealous,
But we must be careful.
I do not know what nothing was Jvvnvr on.
Do not worry!
It's just a way of entering the room were!
Han, what's the other?
Uncle rear face!
Sam Lyk!
Dear?
N - cute.
What
What is the other?
Is great!
Any Given Mrdvnst!
Hymgamy Sun, president ordered me to take food inside!
Okay, I understand.
Each Dvtatvn're here, that's great!
Bras're not going to meet again!
Yvsvyy late.
What's that strange sound was?
Yvsvyy, what are you doing here?
Do not say that...?
Now, meet open bra!
Currently, the size of the "H" am.
Just left school board and Aki-sensei!
Aaron, redistribute snpạy!
What's going on?
Forward way, do not!
Once you're guilty!
Why do you do it?
Bnal see!
Svaltv I'll answer with a question!
You think stealing bras Zdnshvn girls and see why so?
What
N I ask you, so there is no reason other than instinct?
You're a man, right?
I do not like the things I got to do?
This - not like this...
It depends just as much instinct.
Wait and see.
Look...
As a man, how is the life!
Stupid?
Life as this man look like?
The country's social system!
As a citizen, no reason not to follow your basic instincts.
Fun in the passage of the instincts,
You've got to anything but not become distracted!
If a clear say...
A philistine!
Sexuality out of control!
So my fist with my right Rystsh!
Why are you talking the same mental?
Catch the goal!
Sacred Fist!
Again went too far, huh?
No, it was enough to that!
Head!
Shdst seems to be case closed!
Aaron!
Aaron, was cautious!
Takeshi chan!
Where is the crime?
Do not worry, Grftymsh!
That way, great.
Ashamed that I did not rescue earlier.
No, I was a little scared,
But something I believed!
That's all... You've come, do help me!
Miriam...
Chan Takeshi?
Why I do this because my status?
The main way criminals like Ndydt!
The problem is not!
Here, I've fallen and I feel happy that you've saved,
I think it's pretty cool for a moment scam.
Takeshi stupid...
Catch the goal!
I can eat more!
As a result of the arrest report underwear thief had my hands!
Kids cartoon was great!
Used with permission.
Really...
Incidentally trouble getting back together like this happens.
Well, I think I'm not normal Tnby Academy.
Such cases were later to become good memories.
Just like when we were one of Makn.
Security Committee
where are you?
Who is the other?
I'm Amaya Harvkv.
The renovation, Aaron?
The next part about forgetting something?
That's right!
Next:
I love my ass Takrv
It really happens!
part 2
「I love my ass Takrv ♥」
Translation and Editing: DiarY
Http‏‏:‏‏//Forums‏‏.‏‏Animworld‏‏.‏‏Net