Http: // Forums. Animworld. Net Presents anime world
Translation and Editing: DiarY
Tnby Academy,
Where people with special powers. As "elements" was recognized as the accumulation period
However, destruction, when some of the students,
Nasrshvn for evil purposes of use, began.
Academy knew the current state of the
Security .kmyth consisting of students formed
They specialize in the use of weapons Makn holy name,
To control and prevent others were
. Who were known as Makn
No, keeping San.
Stop it.
As always side's manga.
Universal bothers him is not good.
very?
Anyway, do not go to the center?
Not yet.
Hey, she manga do you like?
I love it!
I feel that,
Our good will come along.
Well, page 32 Drsytvn the open book.
Uncle.
Kimi that kind of thing.
Do not you think it strange behavior of their two new people?
Now that Hrfshv did you...
When exercise and sleep.
Happened?
The two men reading a lot of manga various.
You may find some other entertainment.
Em every night...
No, there is not!
Still got to sleep early.
I'm going to stay up all night....
No way.
No, do not!
It's not.
Still got to sleep early.
I'm going to stay up all night....
Hey, you two wait see...
Of...!
What a shame...
Hey, this is real?
Even Kvdvma together?
No, not the way that you think.
This...
We arrived on time?
This series meets lesbians or something like that, what is?
Outside away!
We're flying!
Ten men?
Yeah, Tnby manga festival.
An event that gathered together after all manga Dvstarv period.
Their performance was broadcast fans, as well as a change of clothes Competition was also held.
Briefly speaking, we are going to participate in it.
Really?
I am part of Coase bridge,
She read you stories of their fans!
Competition change clothes what?
Competition that includes running short Coase was made.
What we had just a few moments ago we were with Kodama Chan...
I could show you a little time to write,
He helped me.
That way, then the story was.
I told you.
That's why you didnt sleep recently after class...
I was struggling to finish my Mangam.
Of course...
what?
Kimi ignored in favor of you and Kaygv as a model.
Model?
Only after a series of Lbasatvn figure and Mychsbyn to each other...
NEVER do not.
I will not let you do this to him.
Honestly, I find the character that was hard to be kind to me.
But do not worry, it's Nmyzarym Vzyfmvn affect you when Makn.
Kimi?
Let you be alone.
Getting enough sleep these days.
Necessary to give a little rest to him.
So... I...
One should tell you.
Got it.
I will help you.
But...
So I see,
I can not leave you alone 2 people.
I'll help!
Me too!
Of course, not as a model.
And she was involved in this incident.
Okay, I'll be there wherever Hymgamy Senpai.
Well, then the other can not help it!
Now we need all the Tlashmvn.
Yes!
I'll still do it?
Ghlghlkm praises.
Even if you say it like this...
Why I'm I do?
This promotion Zhs Grftntvn Tmrynyh mark.
And Tmrynyh mark the progress of my photography skills.
And this was part of my collection.
Stop it!
Not move.
One other round.
Kimi?
Not move.
Another one!
Takrv Hey, can not see!
Takrv, it was hurting me!
But now!
It's over.
Designs done?
Show us.
I want to see.
This is... What the hell?
It was a scene that Hao Kun Kun and Midori...
The Koru aka Kun Kun and Myavrdn pressure.
Very Good stopped.
Look here.
This is an error which drew very well thought of.
Do not you think?
Oh, yeah.
Design and letters Gzarysh good.
Card does not speak.
Taking one of the essential.
Here you go, thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad! I've been waiting to read it.
What's the population.
Yeah, just like a real festival.
Multilateral treaty!
Turn the mirror world, eventually committing
Colin new liner, Prysma Leah!
How cute.
Cute.
How cute!
Hey, Hymgamy Sun and Sun Zvky.
Really here?
Yeah.
Should be ok.
"Something" that've never Nmyvfth a high school student.
You're going somewhere to be sold here.
None of the one that you want is not here!
And - but...
I do not!
Okay.
Finally, a change of clothes that match've been waiting for,
Starts!
Really, what they got 2?
His spell hundred.
Threatening.
Sorry!
I am Nzashtn.
Let it go, Lbastv change.
Oh, Kimi, how are you?
You are now the festival what it feels like?
Really fun!
Even Dastanayy written Bvdmm sold!
to purchase?
Yeah, buy it all.
It all?
As one of the associations that loved the original design Ktabshvn to me now.
Counter-attacking group of...
It was quite detailed.
Well, doing things on a regular basis is important.
Like all Bhrsh you go.
How do you, Chacha?
It was fun?
Of course, it was great!
I liked everything I did!
I know that the same kind of thing!
However, Carmon not over yet!
Do you need the best Khatrmvn build here.
You're right.
Yes!
Well, the first input side.
The anonymous, please sit on the scene.
Sorry, thanks for waiting Mvndyn.
The first team started Karshv.
Really? It was quiet.
Thank you, Kimi.
Han?
Mark, mark, racing to join me up.
Really happy.
Come to finally have some fun!
Okay!
My clothes...
This...
are you OK?
Here go quickly.
Okay.
This...
A main Makn.
Kids.
Damn, this guy is very stiff and hard.
Maken nakl: kamudu
Thanks Aynahv.
Leave it to me!
Brin Ayzakvchy, Gakvsvchy.
Makn tablet: Comic Star
Bring Taght, now Myarmt out.
Swap!
Embarrassed, I indulged.
Why is that doing things the territory of the series.
I just wanted to play a little.
Maken scale kmprsur!
Myzarymsh here and...
Physical drive!
Now, to go from here.
Okay!
Kimi!
Can not we let him stay that way.
Yeah.
All kids.... Hard work to make essential right.
In no way Nmybkhshm 'em!
What a sight.
Really kind of thing.
But we soon...
Yeah, this is inevitable.
Under controlled conditions.
Got you make it happen?
Han?
Why are you professional?
We Atfaqatym the same victim.
What fools you say?
If the chaos and anarchy,
Nyvftadh am treated as if it happened...
Once you're likely to feel guilty.
Why did you do it?
There was no particular reason.
We wanted to look 'em when we are suffering, we really liked our group.
This best-in-!
People after they experience a little of his fantasy manga.
You should thank us do both.
You...
Han?
You're like manga and anime, right?
Even do...
You can not be a nuisance for people Bbkhshmtvn entertainment.
We care about the rest Nmydym!
No problem as long as we were happy.
Maken scale kmprsur
Makn tablet: Comics Star
The physical drive that I got the fist explosion am!
It's over?
Succeeded, Kimi.
But...
But... Gndkary the time came.
Why all this hard effort.
It's over Shdst.
Just have to do it again.
Yeah...
You're right...
Hey, wait!
Why do it again're Mydyn?
Over, is not it?
Decided to participate next year.
So, again, we need to help you.
E - Hey, stop it.
He's...
No problem. I Mychsbm very slowly.
Pam's hand and you want to close?
We arrived just in time?
This series meets lesbians or something like that, what is?
No way.
As if you're flying first Japanese're Chrvaz.
Translation and Editing: DiarY
Http‏‏:‏‏//Forums‏‏.‏‏Animworld‏‏.‏‏Net