mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
lord-animetion
chiisai koto ni kuyo kuyo shite
, I used to worry about the small things
itsumo watashi tameratetta no
It was hesitant all the time
demo kimi ga oshietekureta fumidasu yuuki
.Olkink showed me how the courage to take the first step
isshoni hiroi suteeji he
, Together on the big circuit
tobikonde ikou
! To jump
donna chiisai negaigoto ga atte kanaete ageru
I will make even small your wish come true
mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara kowagarazu ni
See, to hold our hands tightly, do not be afraid
ichi ni san
! Three, two, one
Is
!Come on
donna toki demo shinjiteru
Whatever the case, I have confidence because I can see the future in front of my eyes
me no maeni mirai aru kara ne
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
kitto
....Certainly
todoku Fly Away
.Snsal him, shaved away
Zero-Kon
.Oday Haruko Amaya, a student of the second year of the Academy Tenby
.Sidik my childhood I have moved Aoyama Takeru here just a new student
, However, his fiancee announced herself, Cochea-chan Aanaho
, And my colleague, Hemegama Kodama-san
.Boutriqh what became with him in the room
It only is inappropriate for boys and girls
.Alven they do not know each other and live together under one roof
The reason you switch. Therefore, to them
.Bbah good, Takeru-sama
.Bbah good ... painful
.Asvh on this
.But should bear this in mind wherever you are
. I'm sorry, I thought that Takeru-sama will be lonely
.Aanaho-chan, you should you stop these surprises
.Alaftor will be ready soon
. So, wash your face and come here quickly
... A-black
K-How can this happen?
. Not once, but twice
... holy eyes
. From likely they need to touch Tnqata
. I have facilitated the command you
.Enbga you have to thank me
.Hassana, dine and otherwise will be delayed
. This is true
.Aatdakimas
How to look like?
.إنها لذيذة
.وأيضًا... بطريقة ما, إنها تذكّرني بالماضي
.أنت محق, إنها لذيذة
.أنتِ محظوظة, حبيبكِ [ تاكي-تشان ] قد أشاد بكِ
!هيميغامي-سان
هل أنتِ متأكدة من أن لا بأس إذا قاموا بإعادتنا؟
!أوه, لا
لماذا يجب علي أن أركض أيضًا؟
.لن أسمح لشخص يشاركني في الغرفة بأن يتأخر
.ولكنكِ سبب تأخرنا
.لا تهتمي, فقط إركضي
.حسنًا
...كل شيء قد سار بسرعة في يوم أمس لأنني لم أستطع قطعها معًا, ولكن
...هذا الماكين
...[ وتاكي-تشان يحظى بـ[ خطيبة
.أتساءل ما الذي يجري هنا
!هيي, أيها الأطفال
هل تريدون مني حقًا أن أشعل مروحتي الورقية في اليوم الأول للفصل؟
.حسنًا, هنالك ثلاثة أشخاص أصبحن بأمان بصعوبة
...أوه, تاكيرو-ساما لا زال
ما الذي تفعله؟
.لقد تأخر
.أعتقد أن لدي عمل لأفعله
.لقد تمنيت ألا تستخدميني في مثل هذه المهمات الوضيعة
.هيميغامي-سان
.كم أنت محظوظ, لست متأخرًا
تاكيرو, هل أنت بخير؟
.أجل, بطريقة ما
ما كان هذا؟
.[ قوة هيميغامي, [ الخفية
.تستطيع استخدام قِواها الخفية لتحريك الأشياء الحقيقية
.من جميع مستخدمات الماكين, هي الوحيدة التي بإمكانها استخدام هذه القوة
.هذه الأعين
.تمامًا مثل ذلك الوقت
.هاروكو-سان
.الرئيسة
...للتفكير بأن نائبة الرئيسة قد وصلت في الوقت المحدد
كيف بإمكانكِ أن تكونِ قدوة جيدة للطلبة الجدد إذا كنتِ متراخية هكذا؟
.أنا آسفة, فوران-سان
هارو-ني, من هذه؟
.رئيسة مجلس الطلبة, تاكاكي فوران-سان
.بطريقة ما, إنها قائدة هذه المدرسة
.هي مشهورة لكونها صارمة جدًا في القوانين
!نائبة الرئيسة
!نعم
،على الرغم من أننا أصبحنا مدرسة مُختلطة الآن
.ومع ذلك لا ينبغي عليكِ أن تكونِ قريبة جدًا من فتى بينما نتحدث
.لقد أسأتِ الفهم
.تاكي...لا, أوياما-كُن هو صديق طفولتي
صديق طفولتكِ؟
.دُب
.دمية الدُب
.الرئيسة
.سروال داخلي بنّاتي بشكل غير متوقع
!لا
.يا إلهي, هيا إلى الفصل
.إنه هنا
.آ-آسف لتأخرنا
.أوه, يا إلهي
.ومعكما, سيكتمل الموجودين في الفصل
.أ-أجل
أليس هذا الرجل من يوم أمس؟
مع فتاة؟
ألا يعلم بأن توجد قواعد سلوكية هنا؟
.أتساءل إذا كانت حبيبته
.حسنًا, حسنًا, الجميع, كونوا هادئين
Mwalimtkm. I am prepared, Amadou Tomika
.Saidh meet you
... and help teacher preparation is
! O boys
! Rejoice and Amrhawwa
! I loved the beautiful Tenby Academy
! Rocoju Minori-chan, come
.Of course
.Walan, to begin work
! Listen to me, O damned
There .sakon physical examination in the clinic
physical? Suddenly?
!Okay! All the ladies, to the hall
If .hassana, will begone, Takeru-sama
.Ohar that boys call daggers in Chapter
But, physical examination, huh?
A mixed school. These
...This means
! O parameter
Oh my God? What is the matter?
! I have an upset stomach! Can I use the toilet?
.Ooh, my God, this is terrible
Still Dikma. What time, so hurried
!thank you very much
!Come on
, This is the place, I can see the clinic here
! This is the biggest addition to being a mixed school
What do you do?
... I'm really interested in something of this tree
! ... as well as the hole in the curtains
! The same thing for me
!do not copy me
. Please line up according to Orkamcn located in the list
.Okay
!just awesome
.this is embarrassing
.do not worry
.Tabab is a woman
.Ston points
.Orbah seventy points
.Aa her bra nice
Where I purchased?
Internet sites. In
.Atnan Fifty points
.Tsah Fifty points
. This skirt is too narrow
.Spon points
.Otsael to the extent has matured
.Osmanih sixty points
. You are so beautiful, I'm jealous
.Spon points
Increased my weight. I have
Very .mtokhrh now
.Khmsh seventy points
Huge .tbdo you naked
.Deina Olmshma
! It's a very Ntath
! Eighty points
! Eighty-five points
Do you wear a walk today?
. I have an appointment with Habibi later
. I have understood, it is on a mission
, Has a lover, there are no points
! Hundred and twenty points
! Those crazy yesterday girl
. This is true, this is true
! Aflleha, Aflleha
Hei, what do you do?
... P-in fact
... Yeah, that girl
whats your problem?
Do not you want to let other people to look at Echtlsoa fiancée?
.Alomr is not so
. She is not my fiancee
.Taquero-sama
! Ninety-five points
Where?
! Bombing
Really wonderful day. Today
! It's paradise
I Should Arsaleckma there?
The To the real heavens
Obviously. From that you did not learn the lesson this morning
Are you ... Hemegama-Seenba?
Seems that you want me to uproot your eyes
. It's really pretty close
do you know her?
.Ho is not my friend
.Algayt and dirty is that sneaking and staring at girls when Tqmn switched clothes
Hemegama-Seenba, why are you here?
.Good question
Maybe to unleash divine punishment on those who threaten the safety of girls
, If you were you really men
.Fla Ttzlla here, such as the worm
.Bdla, approached directly to the lady and fall in love Mark
No., there is something wrong, Madam
!Okay! We have learned our lesson
. Although I have surprised you
Yourself. You have held back instead of letting the anger Balheijan
.Ohar something
.Qlba beats like yesterday
.Dmaia boil again
. We have this since the morning
No. There is no doubt about the mark on his chest
But, why not feel anything?
LORD ANIMATION: translation
shx: production
.next one
.Agaf straight
.Okay
.Don't move
.Ogel, So Stay
.Hassana, stuck out
.Epeshkl deeper, please
.Yes thats right
What is that... ?
.هذا سريع جدًا
تمسّك هناك, حسنًا؟
.حسنًا, والآن قم بمسح ذراعك
.التالي, من فضلك
.حسنًا
ماذا حدث لوجهك؟
.لـ-لقد تعثرت
كن حذرًا, حسنًا؟
...الطالبات هنا كثيرات بالفعل
...ولكن يوجد بعض المعلّمات
ما الذي يضحكك؟
.لقد كنت أتساءل عن فائدة هذه
.أوه, هذا الشيء الصغير
.إنها تدعى كيرونبو وتُستخدم لفحص توافقك مع الماكين
.هنالك العديد من النماذج المقلّدة والجاهزة للتوزيع
.ماكين... ما زلت لم أفهم هذا الشيء
!ضعها بسرعة
.لقد تم جعلها حية بالفعل
.لست حاسوبًا
!لا يمكنني كشف توافقه مع الماكين من هذا الأحمق
ما الذي تعنيه؟
!إنها المرة الأولى
.الشيء نفسه هنا, إنها المرة الأولى بالنسبة لي
.أرجو المعذرة
.هاروكو-سينباي
.هارو-ني
تاكي-تشان... أعني, لم يتم تحديد الماكين الخاص بأوياما؟
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا ممكنًا؟
...أيتها المديرة... إذا لم يستطيعوا قياس الماكين الخاص به, إذًا
.أجل, أنتِ مُحقة
.لا يمكن لهذا
إذًا, يتوجب علي العيش أكثر من شهر واحد لكوني غير قادر على استخدام الماكين؟
.حسنًا, هذا سينفع نوعًا ما
.من الجميل حقًا أن بإمكانك البقاء متفائلاً
.شعاري في الحياة: خذ الأمور بسهولة
إنها بالإنجليزية, أليس كذلك؟
.أنت حقًا ذكي, تاكيرو-ساما
.أنا آسفة
هل يمكنكِ رمي الكرة إلى هنا؟
.أجل, بالطبع
.إنها قادمة
.لقد حصلت عليها
.أعتقد أن أفضل شيء في الفتاة عندما تبتسم
.ليس مجددًا
:إلى محاربين أكاديمية تينبي
.أخرج! نحن نختار المجندين الجُدد من أجل النادي
نادي التجنيد, هاه؟
.يُطلب من طلبة أكاديمية تينبي بالدخول إلى نادٍ واحد على الأقل
على الرغم من أن هذه المدرسة غريبة جدًا في العديد من الأشياء, ولكن هذا الشيء نموذجي
إيناهو-تشان, هل قررتِ النادي الذي تودين الانضمام إليه؟
.أجل, نفس النادي الذي سينضم إليه تاكيرو-ساما
هل هنالك خطب ما؟
...لا, أمم
لماذا وعدتِ بحمايتي؟
ولماذا تقولين بأنكِ خطيبتي؟
ألا تتذكر؟
هـ-هل قلت شيء خاطئ؟
.إنه سِر
. If you do not know, it is the secret
.But tried to remember later please
. I did not get breakfast this morning
. The I was on a hurry, so I forgot my lunch and my wallet
... Nations
As you like. All
H.-Well, that's what I expected
You are you like snacks, right?
.Yup
E-Haro-nee?
.Ha is lunch
.Shkra Lak, Harrow-nee
To what extent do you have listened to our words?
"Why I promised protected me?"
Starting from nothing. All here
I could appear as early You do time because the air was heavy
A. It's not-so
Oh really?
. This is true
.Sozhb to lose some of the clubs after school
Haruo-nee, do you give me a tour?
.this is not possible
.However, it is the person you are dealing with
, Although I created ten years ago
! Element measuring Kironnebo is the best invention I have
Even if Aki said that you have manufactured pieces of junk?
! Genius does not need to cut scrap
! It's true! He is a genius, damn
In any case, why you are not able to classify three of the students this year?
!three?
I was told that. I have my Almckin can not be measured
.Hassana, it is known to be used Cochea Aanaho Almckin
. I think that this is not a surprise on the scale failure
The third person who can not be measured
That girl. She is located there
. It's a real problem
...I apologize
The inability to detect a person element
Is a big problem?
! It is a huge problem
-Fajra genius inventor will have hinted
You know that depending on your feature
You will be able to use it in different ways, is not it?
Yes, but we can not know the rules of use Almckin from now?
! These [now] is the problem
.Hassana, I think you Staanon more during the G
Jay? ]
.Mbarzac Tenby Academy
! McCain supply! reflector
Never Taatalim, is not it?
! McCain supply! Spark
!Okay
. But, I've heard that you can enjoy after the approval of fencing both sides
Would not things be fine as long as you Tervdin these Duels?
A.-I think so
.Bjanb, I do not want to fight against girls
.Okay
. This bias sexual, Takeru
.Afattaat better than you think
,not only this
.But there are girls Tstkhaddmn own them Almckin outside Duels
, And when this happens they will not be protected by others
.But himself
Is this e-school so serious?
. You really have to denigrating here without knowing anything about this school
.He will be fine
Takeru-advisors will protect toxic
Again, how long it will take until you can measure Almckin for this child?
Than you think you're talking to him?
Months. I think that enough time
! Just accept it, dreaded
SAL-I understood
If, is the son of the prophet, huh?
.Yup
.Ldi the same eyes
And the other person?
.Alotflh with Almckin which we were talking about earlier
... What has is
.Mckin Kamodu
One of the eight heads Almckin sealed snakes .alosmanih in the Holy Mountain, Omanohara
. As you know, I wanted to create something beyond the eight indigenous Almckin
. [Soon, will not be able to launch a sober thing [tradition
. Even if the originals were made by the gods themselves
! What a fast ball
.she's amazing
. I have jumped too high
. This is impossible
.Very beautiful
! Be interested, okay?
. In fact, I've been interested in
Did you like something, Takeru-sama?
E-Do you think so?
.Stupid
.Volleyball? I have a bad feeling about this
!as I expected
!it's coming
NIS-Thank you, Aanaho-chan
.Bahm amazers
. If, everyone entering the club according to their Almckin on
. This is true
. It's to help them through their ingredients
Any club you want to join him, Takeru-sama?
.Otsael about this
Maybe a literary arts club or something
... to see ... Game Retro Association estimate
... confectionery industry Club Research
Images of late anemic at night club show?
What is that...?
!that's it
! Will join this
Take pictures of the Photography Club?
! If, you will also join them
... take pictures? Does it make sense
.Very good
.Tbidin very beautiful, Aanaho-chan
!you are the best
! You are really ideal
.Taquero-sama
Very .latifh, very beautiful
!Beautiful
! Ltyfh vjydh
Spahtk clothes hinder my way, can you pull it?
! Aanaho-chan, this is an art
, And your body is a beautiful piece of art
! Sculpted by the gods themselves
! valan
! Be brave and Akhalaaha
! Well, Takeru-sama
! I will be brave
!No
!No! No! No
! I will not let this never
... Harrow-nee
What-what was this?
... T-Takeru, as you know
Why not think about joining the Disciplinary Committee?
! It's better than that, you can easily do
Disciplinary Committee?
.Yup
Disciplinary .alganh
... Disciplinary Committee
Girls Mzhlat, as you know
Episode 2
What?
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
Vahdasnan
One Two Three
!one two Three
kakushitetatte ne mawari ni ha kitto bareteru
I try to hide it, but I'm sure that everyone knows this already
kitto
Sure
demo chikasugite mo ne kimochi nante ienai
Although we are very close relatives, I can not tell you what I feel
nante
...But
se no takasa itsu kara watashi yori chotto takakute
I've matured and become a little longer to me before I know it
chotto
Slightly
nanoni kodomo mitai na kao wo shite waraundane
However, you still have those childish smile
shite
Childish
me wo michau to yowai no
I feel weak when I look into your eyes
kizutte yo
Please, notice me
yappari kizukanaide my baby
You do not see me this way after all, oh baby
bi-bi-bi-bikkuri masuka ne
Are you surprised?
suki ni naru nante
I fell in love?
za-za-za-zaiza to nattara
.... If necessary
mamoru kedo kimi no haato madowasu kehai ga shitara
I will defend you, but your heart sends me mixed signals
mo ippo baby baby my day suki to tsugetai
Another step will say that I love you
Sure
...My heart
meki
unfailing
sukaato ni koi ni juudan kakushiteru
! I love Obi bullet under Tnorca
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
Preview of Hemegama
.Oday Hemegama Kodama of the Disciplinary Committee
My partner in the room, Haruko, is really a partner .saih, given the habits of others effective
.Olknha make delicious meals
Next Episode Title
Hello to the McCain-Ki
! If you want Bagraha, now is your chance