mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
lord-animetion
chiisai koto ni kuyo kuyo shite
, I used to worry about the small things
itsumo watashi tameratetta no
It was hesitant all the time
demo kimi ga oshietekureta fumidasu yuuki
.Olkink showed me how the courage to take the first step
isshoni hiroi suteeji he
, Together on the big circuit
tobikonde ikou
! To jump
donna chiisai negaigoto ga atte kanaete ageru
I will make even small your wish come true
mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara kowagarazu ni
See, to hold our hands tightly, do not be afraid
ichi ni san
! Three, two, one
Is
!Come on
donna toki demo shinjiteru
Whatever the case, I have confidence because I can see the future in front of my eyes
me no maeni mirai aru kara ne
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
kitto
....Certainly
todoku Fly Away
.Snsal him, shaved away
Zero-Kon
!Come on
! Hurried in Khtuatcma
! Do Tzmian yourselves by boys]? Stopped this folly
.Ashl you say this
I can not really do it, you spin a hundred times around the campus is the first thing you should do in Almckin-Ki?
.Mham-Almckin so much harder than normal activities
! Strength and endurance are two important
.Abzl your best, Takeru-sama
... That may be, but
We do not have what it takes ...
.Astmra
.Taquero, Kengo
.Ltgeraa all the way to the end
Disciplinary Committee
, Perhaps Droskma may accumulate to a certain extent
But is considered [McCain] is a special case, individual arms .ihamlha any student, all McCain is connected to a particular person element
... Almckin which we use sometimes
Although I have taken time from my busy schedule ... to Talimkma
! What a insolence
A.-I'm sorry
Trakhittma. If, I can not Orakma members of the Disciplinary Committee
! Orkdha on campus fifty times so Tstiqza properly
.no, that's impossible
Please, O President, we can not do something else?
A.-It Khtokma
.After pondering the ... This should Aoukzkma O boys
!Here
.Miao Miao
. Today, it is a cat
.it is a cat
! What-What do you think about where the hell?
Look. But, now they Mestiqzan
.Alrouh healthy lives in healthy body
.However, you all beginners
.Ontma O boys are considered a particular problem, because of the strength Rgpetkma mundane
.Rkza shaped Aroagma, a departure from the mundane Rgbatkma
No. I think that I have loving sex
.I am a normal person
.Rkz, focused
! Showed a Hemegama-Seenba over Ruatk
! You work seriously
. From very important not to allow external disturbances to lose your focus
Did you understand?
... I do not want to dissipate my focus
! By external disturbances ...
! Ye are not at all two centers
.I'm tired
How you ended up so?
.Balaudh to the old days, you simply ignored it
You avoid your business. I have all these years
No., I am sure I have been exhausted at the time also
.Aanaho-chan is fine
.Ogel, I'm still refreshed
, Is there anything that can help me
Such as pain relievers?
.Asvh, we have carried us
I go to buy advisors will tomorrow, refrain from getting yourself until the day comes tomorrow
.Olcunnina infected everywhere
. If this is true, I will give you a massage, Takeru-sama
How do you feel, Takeru-sama?
.It's a nice feeling
So, what about here?
A.-It is a great
Odlk your back also advisors will, Takeru-sama
. It's okay, I feel the pain when there are a lot Tdlkina
No. prevent yourself
.Anh feeling good
.Taquero-sama, your body often harsh
A.-I? I mean, there's no
.this is what you want
.it's a wonderful feeling
Place your .antzer
.Here
.vhna
.vhna Ibid.
. This stunning, Haruko-Seenba
You know all about making Takeru-sama happy, right?
... e-this was not what I want Balill
It just that when we were young, you Odlleke often when .nntha practice martial arts
. I think that in these circumstances, we must together rubbed
.Yup
What? Do you have a problem with this?
.not at all
.Enbga be grateful because you have two girls Tqoman Ptdlakk
A.-order
.as I expected
.Currently, it emits no power even slightly
I feel his strength. Until again, I will not be able to classify what I felt at the time
...Is he a friend
Or an enemy?
Really harsh. You
E-Do you think so?
.Oaldlal you are out of your own dojo
what about that?
Tguenita in a strong massage, right?
BC-very strong
.Hemegama-san
.Ouyama Takeru
.Gda is a holiday
.rafqny
Without complaints, okay?
H.-Well
. [I wonder about the meaning of the word that Condi [accompanied me
. But it became clear that they wanted me carrying shopping bags
You .walan want to meet with me out, even though we live together
No. I know what you think about it
.Tbdo like you hate me or perhaps bear a grudge against me
Will you be okay with this?
No. This seems to be true
Olstma worried about what will happen in Miedahma?
.Bataba, as well as
I expected. Also, here is
.Oatdhir to keep you waiting
Today. We have a wonderful weather
.Zerova suitable for shopping
.Kudama-Seenba wears beautiful clothes
. It's really serious about it
is this real?
Follow me close, okay?
Is there any speeches?
.Omm, no, I think that you have good these clothes
.Bataba is also
.However, it will continue to carry my bags for me
.Anh your punishment for your opinion on voyeurism
.Okay
... e-this period
.Snbaka our eyes on them as hard as we can
.Mvhom, Vice-Chairperson
.Llenbdo pursuit
I do know the existence of such a place in Tenby
Did not you know?
Different .tinba in terms of national standards
. It's with the care, school activities, and even different in the composition of its campus
, In a way, it is considered like an independent state
E-Is this?
.Ifterd it is sold next week
! Doll commercials: Hazuki-chan
Rumors say that the fine details and simple craft
.Hma that will make this a prominent attraction of the spirit
I do prepared hesitate anymore
... Nations
.Taal with me, Takeru
A.-order
.Ooh, there is a new branch
.Ooh, you informed
. We have obtained yesterday
. If you will take it
.Omm, Shabak, and the second row of the decoration looks great
. This brand is very rare
. Thank you very much for your purchase from us often
.Ltotin to visit us again
E-Is Ststraen more?
.I can not see
Do you have already surrendered?
.Adhir trivial for boy
. But, I think that you have purchased enough
. Do not be afraid, our stop next will be the last for this morning
What do we do, Vice-President?
Income target. We have to shop X
. This naturally, we will continue monitoring
What kind of shop that are in it?
... to see this ...
...I apologize
What is the matter?
Is nothing wrong with this?
There is nothing wrong in what?
.Kona here
.do not worry
I do not worry?
. But if you see what your choice, you'll drown in a daydream about it
Any one you prefer?
this is?
Or this?
... Nations, in fact
Speak freely, just tell me
this is?
Or this?
... mmm
this is?
Or this?
If, any one?
If you are ... you will be questioned them
! They are great ways
.Takyrv
Now Oejrebhma advisors will
.Abaky here until I get out of the room
. Do not move, not even one millimeter
Concept?
. If moved even a small part, I will kill you
M.-concept
.Otsael why she wanted me to come shopping with them
.Ohla and easy, ladies
Maybe it's my imagination
What is .otsael
This man ... who made the smell look like the smell of my older brother?
.How this beautiful
.Wonderful
.Ldehm many beautiful things
There .onzern
. This is really beautiful
.Tbdo acceptable
Excuse me, Hemegama-san ...?
What is the matter?
Did you finish yet?
.wait a little bit
Hit my arms. I have Baltkhaddr
.Thml slightly
I liked this. I have
! You are scattering my focus
Oh, what it was ...?
who is this?
! This is impossible
.After Amadak Throughout this period, the embezzlement of your actions in consideration can not be described
Let's start with ...
! Immediate death
.Mkanna next afternoon
.Present
.Otsael about who was
Seems like a hit
. If, business as usual
.Llosv, it was wrong Ahoudark here
Sorry-A. THE
LORD ANIMATION: translation
shx: production
McCarron
! Hello Baudtkma, sir and madam
Excuse me, what is this place?
.Anh cafe maid
Do not you know about them?
. In fact, I've heard about them
Is there a seat next to the window is available?
.Ogel, Madam
.Lthzy good day, Sir
... Excuse me, why do you tooking me
.Sir, Madam
.Mreha Palace to you both McCarron
, Azuki, is Khademtkma nice for today
... will soothe the pain Ojdzisadkma care and Che
.lnry
.Sakhz usual, light roast beef
. As for this person ... Just Bring him an omelet
.Oumilet: scrambled eggs dish is quickly with butter or oil in the pan
M-What happened with you, Hemegama?
Why Thoudrin this person with you?
Oh, screamed
Waitress, do you talk to the customer it has become one of the Sadatk, really acceptable way?
.Azukin
.Concept
.Sohoudr off your food
...for this reason
.Enbga be comfortable in the waiting time, please
.I will kill you
, If she told anyone
.Fssov kill
.Azuki-san looks angry
.Olknha look beautiful, I want to wear the same outfit
Oh really?
Anyway, I'm surprised that there is no .alktar customers in this center establishments
. In fact, Tenby does not have a lot of students
... In addition, Director
Director?
.Jba, screamed, Azuki-chan ,. She lost her senses again
. We should act with more grace and honor to work
. Apparently, there are a lot of students are afraid of it
.Amcunnina see why
.Asvh to make you waitin
What is the matter?
. I hate green peas
,sir
, If you pamper yourself
.Vhma what will happen to you
Download. So eat
Q.-will eat it
.Sidi and Madam, for a wonderful Thzia Byuma
How was that?
Dining experience is interesting, do not you agree?
. I have wasted a handful of years in vain
.But, I was due to see Azuki-so Seenba
.Ouaqk
, When I saw her wearing so for the first time
. We have been unable to speak
E. Is this true?
. But, I think it may have loveable best in this outfit
Oh, do you think I look better?
What do I do?
The only reason I narrated from here
! Is the feeling of the mark on his chest
.After forgot about this and got caught fun
! Hemegama Kodama, will not live this life grim
What do you talk about?
Maybe for the next shop that Sivhba him?
Do you buy more?
I began to feel bad. I have for him
Excuse me, is there what speeches?
.Otsael If you have affected loathing again
. From very difficult to understand girls
.Ouyama Takeru
. Just watched
Tguenita
.Alta will bring out the true color choices
What is the matter?
...I want
M-What you are doing?
! A-I want to see your chest naked
Y-chest?
.antzra fsdtito
! M-there?
! B claimed Tanaka
! A claimed Koaabashi
! Ski- C claimed YAMADA
Hemegama
! Together, we three have formed a fan club Hemegama Kodama
So, what do you want?
. We have captured our hearts
.Okadd joined together to love your
. In our eyes, Kodama-sama, you are gods
.Ologel our gods, we are ready to do anything, anywhere
. We clean up the road towards him Tttaghin
We cleaned up the road. We Tttaghin him
. We inspect shops where you purchased
290 285 l 326 281 330 434 288 434 288 478 298 550 330 552 330 497 288
Kodama 00
We have created a map Kodama
.Onkhtt to use it as a device for the training of new recruits
.Ogbea fully
. We're not the only ones who were Ntakbhma
.Ldeha club fans? It is amazing
. If, this is a reputation fan club
.Anhm really obsessed
, Lanna hunger multi jbna
. We can not forgive this worm that stand beside you
.Ogel, we will get rid of it by force, if necessary
.Lnrbt his hands and feet
I wonder if the admission test this year in Tenby
It consisted of a battle. You may for being the best of the insane
!attack
.Qoumoua RIKEN your heads, O fools
Is there remained a fool one?
No., not
.Ohdavi a little different from their goals
. I have come here to Mbarzatk
! McCain blade, Snake
. I have understood, I understood
,However
What people challenge to a duel without following the proper procedures
. She is not a valid way to a warrior
! O despicable beast
! Hey, bitch, I'll teach you a lesson
O despicable, you're Kamigarri, right?
. You half right and half wrong
Half, as you say?
, If you got all the data relating to students on Tenby
.Amcunnina join the Kamigarri, I have promised me this
Kamigarri?
What do you talk about?
... vlhza
! Astslma yourself
! Takyrv
! Disappeared mark
! Hemegama-san
! I Omsktk
. This is Sthsalin it from your opponent
What is that...?
E-Is this really Takeru?
Seems very brave
.Alnh, I wished to be inside the lake of Malacca
! Do you think you can under defeats under these circumstances?
What do you think yourself?
. How dare you attack the girl undefended
! I ask you what you think yourself
Is this your answer?
.Alamh on his chest
.I understand
. If, he has the same power of my brother
, It is probably equally matched in lives
! Blood Index
E-huh? What have you done...?
Do not you remember?
.No
Excuse me, I ... Are you disturbed again?
. I have saved me
.Thank you
My feelings. This sincere
! I have been a violation of the purity of Kodama-san
Vice
! Kill him! Kill him
What?
Haruo-ni? Aanaho-chan? Even Usui exists here?
! P-freaky
! I have lost faith in your
!damn you! Take all this fun for yourself
! Kiss me now
! Let me I have the used-kiss with Hemegama Seenba
What would you say the hell?
! Stop, you pervert, help me
! I'll give you my favor, kiss
!Kiss! Kiss
!Stop
Episode four
! The enemy is in Tenby Academy
! I will die if I did
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
Vahdasnan
One Two Three
!one two Three
kakushitetatte ne mawari ni ha kitto bareteru
I try to hide it, but I'm sure that everyone knows this already
kitto
Sure
demo chikasugite mo ne kimochi nante ienai
Although we are very close relatives, I can not tell you what I feel
nante
...But
se no takasa itsu kara watashi yori chotto takakute
I've matured and become a little longer to me before I know it
chotto
Slightly
nanoni kodomo mitai na kao wo shite waraundane
However, you still have those childish smile
shite
Childish
me wo michau to yowai no
I feel weak when I look into your eyes
kizutte yo
Please, notice me
yappari kizukanaide my baby
You do not see me this way after all, oh baby
bi-bi-bi-bikkuri masuka ne
Are you surprised?
suki ni naru nante
I fell in love?
za-za-za-zaiza to nattara
.... If necessary
mamoru kedo kimi no haato madowasu kehai ga shitara
I will defend you, but your heart sends me mixed signals
mo ippo baby baby my day suki to tsugetai
Another step will say that I love you
Sure
...My heart
meki
unfailing
sukaato ni koi ni juudan kakushiteru
! I love Obi bullet under Tnorca
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
Preview of Hemegama
.Oday Hemegama, Ashqh Bear doll
, Even if new students were able to use their own Almckin
.Vsasabon pain if you do not use them correctly
. Although this is not frustrates me
Next Episode
The strongest girl in Tenby
. But the rest of you need to practice seriously