mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
lord-animetion
chiisai koto ni kuyo kuyo shite
, I used to worry about the small things
itsumo watashi tameratetta no
It was hesitant all the time
demo kimi ga oshietekureta fumidasu yuuki
.Olkink showed me how the courage to take the first step
isshoni hiroi suteeji he
, Together on the big circuit
tobikonde ikou
! To jump
donna chiisai negaigoto ga atte kanaete ageru
I will make even small your wish come true
mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara kowagarazu ni
See, to hold our hands tightly, do not be afraid
ichi ni san
! Three, two, one
Is
!Come on
donna toki demo shinjiteru
Whatever the case, I have confidence because I can see the future in front of my eyes
me no maeni mirai aru kara ne
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
kitto
....Certainly
todoku Fly Away
.Snsal him, shaved away
Zero-Kon
,everybody
.Aciloa on your seat
.Ood to give you someone
Will remain with us as a student exchange
.So begins summer vacation
.Hi! It claimed Sheria Otsuka
!No way
! Star superstar who came to Japan just?
! Sheria Otsuka?
Is it real?
! I am well pleased to meet you all
.Ooh, I did not know that Sheria-san was such fame
How do you know that?
.Ldeha piles of fans all over the world
.she is really beautiful
.Olknha does not hold a candle Hemegama-Seenba
! All the way
.Yup
! Takeru-Be
! I've found
. We are actually in the same chapter
Makes you believe that fate, right?
!not at all
! Takeru-sama fiance
.Zmillete, Aanaho-chan
! I have already been settled and it will become Takeru-sama wife
.Ooh, how I word
When will the concert?
Winds?
How many children who will Tnajabunh?
What? You did not decide anything yet?
! In this case, I will settle with Takeru from now on
. This is impossible
.Aanaho-chan, you must give up to those exploited
.Bjanb So, it will be dead after a few seconds
.Takyrv
Just what number you need?
.Alba, Cool
.Ozar me over your courage, my beautiful boy
.good luck
...sorry
Chapter violent. This is surprisingly
!How this beautiful
You do know that I Bamk.cma knitting
What Thakinh?
... We imitate
.Ushaha ...
The atmosphere. We have started to become cool
.We love knitting
.I see
I remembered that parameter. I have had told us Bonkma may Tjoltma around the world to help those in need
...Helping the needy
.Yup
!so sweet
Hei, any countries that were you in?
! Tell us
.Anhma with great success
.seems like that
.Kltahma really Jamiltan
Add. They good neighbors and Sadegtan
.But the best thing in them is the color of their hair Paradoxical
! And the color of her skin white iced
They are like a pair of princesses Almassabtan curse
.Movernma them live puppet
.Aa him likened to a harsh
No. I certification that they like in our lifetime
.you are right
.Hia, even you
.Yup
! Ah, they do not stop Adhasha
! It was so nice
! G-very high
Azuki. But still the best, as we expected
What was this?
Have you been able to do this complex as simple as the jump?
. This is not an element that surrounds them
Halo. It's really dark
! I've cut it down well
I do I know you are good at cooking too, Dimitora-san
No., I'm good only with knives
.I useless in actual cooking
! It's burning
I can not. I know when the heat becomes too high
It seems that this group will have to start from scratch
! In this case the first taste Tbouktna, my teacher
!it is not fair
.Vhmt, I understood
Everyone eat food advisors will, so Qmn to form a description of
! Everyone boulevards
.Anh just a strange place
These girls have our strengths such as special, right?
.However, they live like girls Adiyat
. We have traveled around the world
. In every town we visited, these girls were outcasts
if?
. This place is our Committee
.Enbga that Tstmtaa with us here
. This will be difficult, but I will do what I can
What happened this time?
. I think you stumbled upon the ants nest again
.Mkhtih
, And now, kept your place
... to see, first aid
Oh? where is she?
.She's here
.Ooh, it is difficult to access
. Just a little bit more
Excuse me, do you want me to help you?
.I will be fine
! O nurse
Are you fine?
A.-order
.I will live
.I am surprised
Why are you obsessed with it?
! Takeru-Be handsome knight
! I was destined to meet
.Hmm, it seems that
. This place is our Committee
.Enbga that Tstmtaa with us here
No. The time does not matter where as long as you fell in love with someone
We receive new orders. So, Take Action as you wish
Will you recognize him?
Are you going to do?
Sheria, what will you doing?
! I go on a date
.but I can not
.Hiria, do not worry about it
Connie. Just as you
. It's right
.Lst need to pretend
.I will help you
!Me too
...everybody
.Hdvina is Aoyama Takeru
Chapter .1-B
No. It seems kind that defends the dignity
Has hobbies. Not
.Madelh Sports Average
.Mahtm in huge breast girls
! If Sheria of its kind favorite
! Very large breasts
. What still do not understand what you consider it Sheria
.Anh very easy target
No. I would like to say this
.But there are three girls surrounded by goal down
.Cochea Aanaho
Other .mptdoh
In such separation. It's our goal
. It's claim to his fiancee, but we did not see any evidence of that
.Aa her from a strange girl
.Omaya Haruko
.Mostagdh
Childhood goal. It's friendly
, This is linked to the two romantic relationship
. But it seems they often order the target
Other .omostagdh, Hemegama Kodama
. It's does not appear to be interested
.After that was later with the target
Really like paradise. This
There is a great possibility that these three will Taatdakhln with attempts Sheria to target dating
. This leaves us with one thing of work
... eliminate
.For competitions ...
Suitable .hl
. It's an easy task, but we must not be complacent
. We Alvenus
Do it for advisors will for Sheria
.Taquero-Be
LORD ANIMATION: translation
shx: production
.Hi
.Ogel, hello
Do you dissolve your homework?
Why behave like a stupid boy in the drama?
I do not. I do this to be stupid
What speeches?
, It has been two months since I came here
! So far did not call me one of them to go out with them later
. This made me wonder why I came to Tenby
! E-This is ...?
You feel similarly, is not it?
A.-order, this is true
Lmaza ttata?
! I've been thinking how I could to have the Bhabibh, just like you
.But, you have one
How do you feel today, Takeru-sama?
.Aanaho-chan
.Tbdo very happy
H-really?
.Bataba he seems happy
! Beautiful fiancee found after I turn straight to here
Beautiful fiancee]? ]
... or-Usui
.Ltkon higher than that, I've been on a date with Hemegama-Seenba
! And Amaya-Seenba are made every day with lunch
.Ovouk all, all of them Mentqlat students, pets, your Concerned
Why are all the time fun, you bastard?
! Let me subscribe to it
! It's not my fault for being the main character
! I am beautiful fiancee
[.Thiat, Aoyama-Takeru-sama]
[.I could not you out of my head at the moment I saw you the first time]
Intellectual glasses can only hide part]
[Eyes. From emotional
[! Here is the brave Tsnek]
, Only once]
[! I'd like to do as the Romans do, I want Maangtk
,I beg you ]
[.Orjo meet me
[.Sokon await in the car park after school]
[Sign., The girl that I was impressed by your]
!finally
! The only thing that they wanted all boys high school strongly
Habibi to Aoyama-sama Takeru
. But, I never expected that I have the one
.Olknha did not tell me about her identity
! I can not be sure, but I bet it will be beautiful and emotional girl
!Certainly
Disciplinary Committee
! Do Tsedkan it?
! I have received a love letter! A Love Letter
! Takeru received a love letter unknown
Maybe they gave to the wrong person
.Taki-Chan received a love letter
.Otsael for the type of girl that I Sent
. This ambiguity must eat you
! For-not really
Random girl wants to fall for Ptaquero
! This does not mean nothing to me
No. Takdei yourself
probably
Strange .qguat had captured Tenby
.Icomon to bring girls under their control, and now makes them strangely Taatsreven
.Alven always behave strangely are boys
.Chksa What is certainly acting strangely
...sorry
.Chksa What threw a lot of garbage behind the school
!Oh really?
What? She does not talk about the message of love?
Who would like to do something obscene?
. This what I want of you know
Both adopted.
.Orjo start the investigation immediately
We take. We have the permission of the parameters
!I see
! If you can both rely on us
! Miracles Tenby, Kodama and I, I will do it! We are dynamic duo
! We will do it in the blink of an eye! We will find the culprit and will apply justice
!No! Men must stay away
Since when we became [Dynamic Duo]?
!seriously
.However, the students' preparation has ended
.Oaha boys and girls, be careful as you were returning home
... Takeru-sama, with the promise
! That bastard
Takeru-sama?
! I have my predecessors
! Takeru-sama
Takeru-sama?
What is that?
A-more?
! F-Fast! Candy as far as the eye can see
! I am sure that the gods of sweets have prepared these bags for the poor, who are like me
!thank you very much
! T-Takeru-sama
This dessert was you, right, Takeru-sama?
!Uh! thank you very much
YOU REALLY care about me after all
.Ooh, do not leave me again
! Takeru-sama
You do not talk too much today, is not it, Takeru-sama?
! Well, the time has come light meal
! This delicious meal
... thinking that it was simple
.Lkhaddalla ...
No. There is one here yet
Maybe it was just a joke
... e-Is it possible that this Aloossuy
. It should also be
! I'm sure that he has attracted me here until he gets what he wants
! Likely that he is now in his committee
!Curse! Do not think it end
! O dirty prankster who has failed
! Maybe the time has come to step down and surrender to me
What would it?
To speak of him, Takeru-Be?
! U-Sheria-san
Do you exercise ridicule or something?
Ah ... no, excuse me, Sheria-san, what Tflih here?
Excuse me, I have read my right?
Does this mean that you are you girl?
.Hassana, to go
We go to where?
.Mkan What fun
A long time ago. I have since I walked on the streets so
H-really?
.In the outside, I can not go out alone at all
.Almsourin Itbona
.Oohaana under the lights make me cry
.Vhmt, you are singing star, after all
.Haa, Hei, see
who is this girl?
.she is really beautiful
. I am glad I came to Tenby
Oh really?
.Lonna I met you, Takeru-Be
... Excuse me, Sheria-san
! Let's go from here
... And-but this place
.Orad to be alone with you
.Anh very scary home
Do not you want it?
. I do not like it
Who behind this corrupt Prank?
. This does not look like a normal joke
... Hemegama-san, I think that I have to do
.Ofterd you worried about Takeru
... e-this is not
. But the most important, someone was watching us long ago
who are you
Venus?
How do you notice?
. I have completely hidden Halta
, Perhaps this one may deceive amateur
. But I am not
Why are you doing it?
. Apparently, this was probably planning to spent
.Ooh, as it expected from Hemegama Kodama
No. How wonderful that scared you Kamigarri
. As expected, stank, O girls Kamigarri
.For any case, I want you both to stay here for a longer period
U-Sheria-san?
Where did you go?
M-What is this?
Is there someone trying to tamper with Balmckin-Ki?
.Takyrv-ken
are you ready?
! Stop, Hemegama-san
! You can not protrusive out! It is against school rules
. You should make criminals pay for their crimes
...No way
! Stop it also
! Takeru-sama, cohesion
what happened to you?
Aanaho-chan?
! Haruko-Seenba and Kodama-Seenba
! Takeru-sama stopped moving suddenly
Takeru-sama? Do you mean that the statue?
. You are wrong, it's not a statue, he Takeru-sama
.Anh Statue
! Takeru-sama, how this happened?
. I have always had a statue
Appropriate timing.
.With three goals in one place, I've become my job easy
.I see
.Hrictk, Sheria, has lured Takeru abroad
How long...?
Do not let the goal notes -
.- keep this secret
.Alvhl is not allowed -
Meet him
ice cream
Shopping
Mahal Café
In a secret room S &amp; M
Shopping
Mahal Café
In a secret room S &amp; M
[In a secret room? S &amp; M]
It means sadistic and sadistic is the person who loves to torture: S
Means Almassoche and Almassoche the person who likes to punish: M
... in the secret room
.As
!Mother
! Aanaho-chan
!Certainly
! Antzerana
! You should not pass
Long overdue. We have
. We have already got to the last step of the task
.Hiria, is our desire to achieve your desires
I pray for advisors will success
! To our success
. Do not let the goal notes - .abaka it a secret - .alvhl is not allowed -
!There
... this building
Since when it is located here?
. All things have become suspicious
.Ln opens
Very strong. Seems
! Haruko-Seenba
! Leave it up to me
! Fist McCain
! Open
! [All I will sing my songs for you in this special event [song Sheria music
! I will start singing now
Sheria-san
Song and music?
Song
And
Music
. I will not sleep tonight
! Takeru-Be, do you listen?
!There are more
! Concern was really a waste of time
. But, I am pleased that something bad did not happen
No. Trechaa never Hracetkma
.Ldehm more devious schemes for Takeru in the store
.Yes right
E.-this strange
. It's really beautiful and also huge nipples
If, why I was not attracted to it?
The eighth
.Hiria will do its best for you
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
Vahdasnan
One Two Three
!one two Three
kakushitetatte ne mawari ni ha kitto bareteru
I try to hide it, but I'm sure that everyone knows this already
kitto
Sure
demo chikasugite mo ne kimochi nante ienai
Although we are very close relatives, I can not tell you what I feel
nante
...But
se no takasa itsu kara watashi yori chotto takakute
I've matured and become a little longer to me before I know it
chotto
Slightly
nanoni kodomo mitai na kao wo shite waraundane
However, you still have those childish smile
shite
Childish
me wo michau to yowai no
I feel weak when I look into your eyes
kizutte yo
Please, notice me
yappari kizukanaide my baby
You do not see me this way after all, oh baby
bi-bi-bi-bikkuri masuka ne
Are you surprised?
suki ni naru nante
I fell in love?
za-za-za-zaiza to nattara
.... If necessary
mamoru kedo kimi no haato madowasu kehai ga shitara
I will defend you, but your heart sends me mixed signals
mo ippo baby baby my day suki to tsugetai
Another step will say that I love you
Sure
...My heart
meki
unfailing
sukaato ni koi ni juudan kakushiteru
! I love Obi bullet under Tnorca
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
Preview of Hemegama
.Hemegama likes to spend her evenings to relax, eat dried plums, drink green tea
! Concert swimming pool? This is a trend for taking obscene
. I am enjoying
! Maybe I do not know what's going on there, but I Soshakk and Sodek in a watery grave
Next Episode Title
Storm ends the battle of the Knights of the swimming pool