mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
lord-animetion
chiisai koto ni kuyo kuyo shite
, I used to worry about the small things
itsumo watashi tameratetta no
It was hesitant all the time
demo kimi ga oshietekureta fumidasu yuuki
.Olkink showed me how the courage to take the first step
isshoni hiroi suteeji he
, Together on the big circuit
tobikonde ikou
! To jump
donna chiisai negaigoto ga atte kanaete ageru
I will make even small your wish come true
mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara kowagarazu ni
See, to hold our hands tightly, do not be afraid
ichi ni san
! Three, two, one
Is
!Come on
donna toki demo shinjiteru
Whatever the case, I have confidence because I can see the future in front of my eyes
me no maeni mirai aru kara ne
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
kitto
....Certainly
todoku Fly Away
.Snsal him, shaved away
Zero-Kon
! Rescued me
No. I can swim, so I can not save them
.Antzera, I would seek help
.Taquero-Be
Advisors will save you
.But Takeru-Be can not swim
. [At that time, I thought, I want to change
. I have wanted to become strong like Takei-chan
.Onqzna, Takei-chan
Kenkibo
Haruo-ni did not come to school?
. This is true
.Enbga to leave early for the work of the Student Council
Do you have any evidence?
.not at all
.Bagm on her, she does not leave school, even
. I think that we must search in the school grounds. First, it should also help
.Okay
, It is best to tell the McCain-members to others about it
. So do not worry needlessly
.I see
... believing that Haruo-ni have disappeared
... This is only
Where disappeared Haruo-ni?
Aanaho-chan, what's up?
.Taquero-sama, I've been looking for you
.Hassana, nothing wrong with this
What is that?
.Anh protective charm
I heard you. I have you in danger when they all worked the last time
. From my duty to protect you, I am sorry
.However, there are many times I was not next to you
. Thank you, Aanaho-chan
.Ooadha, not your eyes away from me and Haruko-Seenba
.Talma I love Haruko-Seenba, so I hope not to crash her feelings
.Aanaho-chan
.Aa her speed
, When we were in the McCain-Ki
. We have received many help from our teachers
.Walan, the sons of teachers have entered Almckin-Ki
Vestigial has been brought to the battle against Kamigarri
. On the potential he expected it, and he sent his son
If, the amount wheel can not be stopped at all?
.Ouyama Takeru, Haruko Amaya, who you're looking for, is in our hands
What did you say?
. If you want to restore them, to come to the summit Omanohara
. Do not tell anyone, to come alone
who are you? And why I took Haruo-ni?
YAMATO. I Kikyo
.Balillt, I Kamigarri
Kamigarri?
, Although I do not know the real strength
. If you make me the strongest I have, I'm very thankful to you
If you are Kamigarri?
Where Haruo-ni?
. I have come here finally, Aoyama Takeru
. In recent battles, I have dared to Aharaja
. So, today I will answer you religion
. You must be well aware of my strength in the garden preparation
. If you want to save Haruko Amaya, you will need to do what I say
It resisted. If, you'll know what will happen to her
.Vcentha her more miserable than the President of the hamburger
... Harrow-nee
... because of me
.Hassana, I am ready at any time
.Okhberni one thing
What is the purpose of the power that you have?
.Boutriqh what, I said something interesting
No. okay, I'll tell you
.Qota has the purpose to protect my pride
.Aldafa serve this powerful base of living organisms
. I just do not want to be one of the weak
I have come to Tenby to achieve also the force, is not it?
...In this case
...I also
.Orad to become stronger
... However, I
Do you want to say it to protect someone?
. If, Ahezmna, and protect
.that girl
No. I can accept such fighting
Over the racist inside you. I have
That was almost. We have such an explosion inside me
... If they are such a force
It .fla matter if you hit hard
.But not intrusive Haruo-ni in the matter
. This matter has nothing to do with them
,In this case
.Hajmna at full strength
.Alchks who is not fighting is not appropriate for the protection of any person
Why does this make Takeru?
.Jba, despite being next to him always
You have not understood anything, right?
. You can tell that I always give him what he wanted
This .bmsadk
Fear and anger of something precious is taken
.Ho such as the trigger to blow up all the hidden forces
...Expensive thing
.Taki-chan has lost something precious to him that day also
.Mom
!Stop
What speeches?
Is not your strength exists to protect anyone?
Or you say that you know that this is impossible
And that you have lost the desire to save the girl?
I do not able to protect my mother at that time
... vhty now, Haro-Injured
.Ostma well, Takeru
Force for fighting
. She is not never going to be subjected to someone or to be used for special ambitions
.Bl you need to protect yourself and your opponents in order to stop fighting
My mother wanted to. I have Takeru to become a strong man sincerely
Sincerely strong?
.Elloukv battles and the protection of all, the real power
! I-I want her
.Onzern to this
What is the matter?
.Hah? It's beautiful
.Anzera, look
. You are right, it is bright
. This light as well as Growl, I am afraid that I only listen to him
Does it make sense?
.Nodzuchi, get out
.Hadhar, O Princess
.Azhba and discover what is happening in Omanohara
There .sokon after a period
.Concept
...This
...that person
Huge .kmyat elements come out of this sacred mountain
Is this evil energy sacred monster, Yamata no Oorotche?
.Mdhishh
It is absorbed elements of the blood index through his mouth?
.Andlaa anger make it absorb the elements to the maximum extent
. Finally, it can become rough even in his body breaks
How it will end?
LORD ANIMATION: translation
shx: production
! McCain-Ki
.Mckin-Ki
.Ottalaa to work with you
, As Kagazuchi and Aicazuchi not Izala recovering
. I have stayed alongside Princess
. In such a time, things will be easier for me if they were here
M-What?
What do you intend to do?
.When this person up here, the entire school will be destroyed
.Aajla or later, Tenby will govern by us
. If we can use it to remove all Akabbatna, it will be two birds with one stone
... Taki-chan ... everyone
!No way
.Keme, see
Do you incline the great dragon inside the forest?
Gradually narrowed down. But he
.Takyrv
.Thank you both
. We have saved us
What happened, Azuki-Seenba?
.I do not know
... dragon came from the forest to us and
. I did not understand you at all
... Excuse me, Aoyama-Be, is
... Takeru-sama
.Anh fly
.Alomr as if a group of elements
I browser extensions, it seems that it is surrounded by the devil
. In this case, let me Otrdh
Certainly. You are doing so deliberately
Change. We have such a time when the intervention in my battle
.For any case, we can not stop it only by force
.Oaha dreaded, wake up
.Taquero-sama, please stop
. See, it has become a very interesting
Likely. From that Aoyama Takeru's ability existed since birth
, Even though we did not notice it before, given the severe Rose which was done in Omanohara
Maybe it may be close to the lineage of us
What are you saying?
.Taquero ... It's impossible to be Takei-chan Mthelkma
Takei was. We have always-chan boy who sacrifices himself for the sake of others
But on that day when he was not able to protect his mother from the man who challenged our dojo
. I have left it a deep wound in his heart
For this reason Takei-chan possibility can not see the people they hurt during the fighting today
Reason. Therefore, Takei-chan is not Mthelkma who want to control others to fight
. Only national chattering
.Salam Tenby Academy you will find the end of the day anyway
I allow .ln
.Osttia move my body
.you
.Haruko, Asuraei to return to Tenby Academy
We have to evacuate the road. We have already escape
.Da this place for us
.Asvh for being late
.Dymytvra-San valjmy
.Hia, Go ahead, Haruko-san
We have three. We have to reform the space dimensions
.Anh shortcut to school
. Thank you, everyone
There is no paradise
.Opalnsph us, it is a place of important memories
.Osraei and go
Takeru is .tola-Be
Ttgeron. How to do this
. I will not Osamgn Bfltkn This
The reason I told you. Therefore, Ms. Ootohama
.Mmarcetk make us lose the school itself
. It's orders from the top, I ask you to be cautious
I remember this advisors will, Akkaya
.No way
Why is this happening?
.Anh absorbs the surrounding elements
. If we approached him, we will absorb our personnel
.Ln long until it becomes Takeru-sama is unable to prospect
How do we stop it?
.Currently, Takeru has lost his conscience, which follows his instinct only
... If we can give them a shock is unmatched
...Unmatched
shock?
... This light
Did something else happen?
.Aldu is breaking space
.Haruko-Seenba
Why it fell from the sky?
. As expected, the heroine has fallen from the sky
. We have pulled the Murakomo
.Haruko-Seenba, something I'll let you Takeru-sama
Do you intend to collide with the blood Takeru index using one of the eight Almckin?
Maybe both may fail and would pull inside the huge spiral element
.Murakomo of the eight Almckin can disperse the aura of Satan
My ability .sostkhaddm harmful to disperse the negative elements that made Takei-chan becomes rough
.preparedness
. Use my strength, O blade
.This is bad
. I have sucked Murakomo element
what is happening?
.Qoh frenzy that will destroy Takeru inside
... Harrow-nee
.Taki-chan
.Haruko
Takeru, are you okay?
.Taquero-sama
!What?
! Haruko-Seenba, your chest, your chest
O ...
.I m happy
.Harv-Reed, S. Lak
. Although they have made us anxious, they like a miracle
... Takeru-sama
Fltha. We have, Haruko
Nice work, right?
.Haro-chan, good work
... breast Haruko-Seenba
Bouyama. You take care of a lot Takeru
.Oorotche-san, it's not so
...I'm not
It made me see. I have
. With that power, you have the qualifications to enter Kamigarri
.Ltota with us
. We will prepare a battlefield suitable for you to take advantage of them
.Aoma what, this place will fall under our management
What did you say?
. From the best for you not to resist
K.-jokingly Enough
. I do not know about Kamigarri or anything, but I will not let you go
.Alomr like what he said Aoyama-san
.Alriash
.Achttaf Haruko-san and disturbing the peace of our school
. I have already heard your plans from the teacher Akkaya
Of the Akkaya?
.Salam and its Tenby Academy will be protected by us, Almckin-Ki
The reason you must. For this to return home
Well, how will it?
.Satojb you take all of us ordered
... O damned
.Gid, I will settle this in one day
How to .ottalaa in front of war against thee Kamigarri
.Ouyama Takeru, I will remember your name
.Azhb and training in order to improve your ability
.good
.Since the incident, Aanaho-chan, Takeru, and I have begun training the morning
.Mhla, you exaggerate too much
.Mzhl, Takeru-sama
.Gbe like me can try and see the results
.Tmask, Takeru-sama
. Therefore, why I told you not to strain yourself
.Kadh, the main Wewoka with the work of the students are busy Council
No. You will use Almckin in front of others randomly
Keep calm all the time, the concept of?
.Ooh, teacher Akkaya
where is he?
.Anh person looks like him
O ...
.Hafeza calm, Keep calm
.Azuki-san, working hard and hard
...Madam
. In fact, I've always wanted to visit this place
Spread over maid advisors will Aldugan next, so allow me to draw graphics
.Mounasph, Hemegama-san spends most of her time shopping with Kengo-san
Which is better?
.Ozn that this is the best
.vkanny sartdyha
. Although it is in the first year, Oorotche-san is very studious and reliable
.Alkhasr will listen to the demands of the winner will be a duty on it until next year
. If not agree in the matter, we are, Almckin-Ki, will not forgive this
. I am a student in the second year of the Academy Tenby, Amaya Haruko
President of the Almckin. I-Club in order, which protect the peace and order within the school
If you come to our town, visit us
The To erotic daily our pleasure of our school, Tenby Academy
Episode Twelve
Guards herb garden