mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
lord-animetion
chiisai koto ni kuyo kuyo shite
, I used to worry about the small things
itsumo watashi tameratetta no
It was hesitant all the time
demo kimi ga oshietekureta fumidasu yuuki
.Olkink showed me how the courage to take the first step
isshoni hiroi suteeji he
, Together on the big circuit
tobikonde ikou
! To jump
donna chiisai negaigoto ga atte kanaete ageru
I will make even small your wish come true
mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara kowagarazu ni
See, to hold our hands tightly, do not be afraid
ichi ni san
! Three, two, one
Is
!Come on
donna toki demo shinjiteru
Whatever the case, I have confidence because I can see the future in front of my eyes
me no maeni mirai aru kara ne
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
kitto
....Certainly
todoku Fly Away
.Snsal him, shaved away
Zero-Kon
. This is your Almckin
.Daha on the ground
McCain you have set up. I have the most suitable for someone like you who do not fight girls
If, this is Almckin?
.Olknha disappeared inside my body
. There are two types of Almckin
Internal .one rely heavily on convergence
.Lonk can not be used without a true affinity, it is very rare
. Where the types Almckin can be activated at any time, it is very convenient
.However, when the opponent activates its Almckin, you can not use that you have
What do you mean?
.Pachtsar, McCain has your ability to remove McCain's opponent
... By the way, I've called it to burn ultra-Jin-sama's name for Drago
.Aattaak label for this very bad person, I usually think of names
... Given the strength, should your name be Almckin
... This Almckin by the school principal designation
When, where, and against those who Sostkhaddmha?
.He like this happened last time
. I should prepare for this moment
They .anhm cause trouble again
, Like what we were doing in the past
I hope they use their hands to protect the peace and order in the school
If you become. So the experience of those who entered the Academy Tenby
.Okaya and I were not able to overcome this experience
Kenkibo
: Today's topic Summer Training Camp
What is the summer training camp?
... According to Haro-nee
, On an island filled with white beaches and tempting Ocean Blue
Practices. We will race during the day, and learn new techniques Almckin
. At night, there will be a meal surrounded by nature
At rest, we bathe outdoors in the forest, so we can revitalize our bodies tired
E-Is there such a camp?
They are real. We have looked
. I do not think that anyone would be naked only in the bathroom, I think
. Although the time has come almost the training camp for the annual summer
, For unforeseen reasons for this year
Request. We will help everyone
What is the matter?
Other .babarh, everyone paid the price for their own camp this year
Pay the price themselves?
How could this happen?
.So it once a year
. This tyranny
.Okadd already bought a swimsuit for this year
. In fact, we will have to work anyway, so it does not matter
... The first training camp with me Haruko-Seenba
... Listen, Low Budget
!you are
Do you think of the wrong in this case?
.Okay
, Nations, according to the book of accounts
This year .msariv on snacks, which, including the cake, have risen dramatically
. [Next was the manga clothes outfit, which provided under the framework [Articles
. In fact, nations
.Ually headed, there are expenses not classified in albums bearing pictures and dolls
.I do not know koalas, what-chan
.I do not know what the small-chan's brother, Bo-chan also
Do I need other records listed?
SAL-No Thanks
When my wallet. Just be empty
I do I know that we will have to pay
. I do not have any money so
.Palmthel, no, behind me
Director of the school, what Talekaya?
.Ooh, you guys
.Sidik me asked me to publish this
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Inside Marz shopping Tenby, maid cafe macaron .ldeha on your limited supply
We are hiring for today! You can earn a lot of money
Macaron
Day special limited supply] This means that they have some paid services are good, right?
! Work for the day! Agni much money
.Ah, I think so
...This
. With this, we can solve our financial crisis
.Yup
. Many people are here
Why there are many customers?
...This
Can I see this?
.welcome Sir
E-If this is the maid?
.Ltyfh, separate ltyfh
. People are waiting behind you, how much of this annoying
What would you like to ask?
. From the Vice-Chairperson, I would like to request everything
.Lleom only, we will contest eat cake
.No way
I share advisors will
Strapping maid comic for women as well as
. I have always wanted to read this
.Fattrh long, I've thought about fighting and I wear this
There is something wrong, but it does not matter
Etc-maids in the shop
what are you doing?
.Hemegama
. You're going there Taiqin
Macaron
A-O Director, What is the meaning of this?
. Many of the customers are served by members of the McCain-Ki
.Anhen employed a temporary time
All these were brought in. The customers also
I do I know that you are connected to them
. Today will be busy, so national change quickly
,Oh really
.Oualemder says that he is not aware of the matter
. All the guests are students from my school, too
... I am afraid that the mastermind behind this
Served basis to be one person
. We have finished the change
.Ooh, Azuki-Seenba
.Hi
This person is
!You are
You dreaded, I have a deal with the manager job, huh?
This was. We have the only way to earn enough money for the camp
.Fl things that are not necessary
How do I work Kazuki now?
M.-Hey, do not tell this
.Chksa what had wanted to see you so, too
, Kurigasa
Are you here as well?
Protect, what should I say?
.Because men in the school had they caused a stir, I have come to see what is going on
You too, huh?
.Gentlemen
There is nothing wrong Aloumilet popular with cedar honey?
! Or rather, ask
A.-order
.I beg you
No., this is annoying
. One of the three of you enough
.Qoma so please
. If, repeated request list
.Hadhar, folk Aloumilet rice with honey
Huh? Not okay with this?
Roles were reversed. We have
.Ogel, yes, I understand
What now?
.Three seconds
.Aanaho wins
.Walan, the following
. [Cake contest all you can eat
.Alvaiz will have a full year of free drinks in the shop macaron
. If you lose, you will pay the full price
.Tmhli a little otherwise we will not have any competitor
.Alkekh here is very delicious
.Aa her mischievous way to deal with customers
. People will complain of serious this
.Omm, Haruo-nee to take care of these
.A wonderful
.Beautiful
.she is beautiful
.Asvh for your patience, Madam
.Ah, this is embarrassing
.I am stressed
.slowly
.Hah? Ah, I can not stop
.Asvh
And other advisors will bring one
Ah, what will I do?
.Ltokhve time, Vice-Chairperson
... Vice-Chairperson also movements
.ltyfh separate
. It's that provide services, not to mention other services
.you are right
.Oh no
what is next?
. On the left a little, no, turn right
Huh? At any point?
.There
.Mrahy, I did it
.Mbaat ice cream is the most important
What Tflih?
.Mreha, Azuki
. We aim to Guinness World Record
.Ashron balls of ice cream
! Do not play in the kitchen
. This is not a game, we challenge the world
.Yup
... sorry waiting for you, would you like
Why are you gathered here?
Is this how you should talk to Mnzemik?
Organizers?
Did not I tell you about my friend?
...This means
.Llmadrsh this shop for OB
? OB
.Anh shortcut is not something
the monster? = Beast and O do not mean to
.I know that
.Sidik Old, OB = Old Boy
Thus .mnadhati is considered arrogant, again-chan
.Director
.Dona introduce myself, I am an old friend of the school, Katherine
Are not Fujioka Guru?
.Km this annoying, I'm Catherine now
Macaron
My school days. During and even after the shop opened, it was Minori-chan always support me
Really. I am grateful to her for that
.Oatunai More
What is wrong with this view?
.Although that I do not have great abilities, Tenby still Taatqublna
.Osubht able to be here and thanks to my friends at that time
.Gid, you still have some audacity
.Asv, I'm busy now, see you later
.Yup
.Abzl your best
Oh, you do not still have something to say?
No., I am somewhat envious
I'm still able to. What you to be so even after graduation
Will we be similarly?
. Do not utter such embarrassing things
, Instead of worrying about the future, focused on your business
.Oaha temporary server
.I know that
Friends, huh?
. This person should be similarly
No. less than more
. We have all this in the past
,Oh really
. This makes me think that this was the best time
.Ootohama, I have entered
.thank you brother
But, that's OK?
This is done without permission?
We experience. We only property
. Although its impact is stunning, perhaps it may be funny like a joke
LORD ANIMATION: translation
shx: production
.Mckin-Ki
.Sidta, happy birthday
Hot .anh, so be careful, Sir
. From Mr. who asked this? Ojbni
.Soqom making an original dessert this time
.Chksa relieving me in cleaning
. If this situation continues, we will be among the table tools
.Odaa, Sir
Friends of the past, huh?
What speeches?
. Do not look healthy
. This is the first time that I have the customers where this
I go and advisors will rest a little
Can I let the rest of you?
.Oh ya
.Khz things easily please
What is the matter?
.nothing
. We should do what we can to order as well as Director
.Tvdil Napolitan pasta and fruit parfait
Done finishing soda bread with honey and cream
.Htair power cream pudding ready
.Altaulh number two, Asuraei
.Present
.Tbak contained fried chicken and power
.calamity
.Aanaho-chan
. I am very sorry, O customer
Are you fine?
.Yes, I am fine
A. THE-sorry
Do you Toveta?
No., Takeru-sama
And to rejoice. If we work hard
. Thank you, Takeru-sama
.Aanaho will work hard
Beautifully marked., Takeru
What speeches, Vice-President?
I've been in a daze, not you so well?
Huh?
No., I was thinking of the new milk ice preparation
.that's easy
.Asv, Make one quickly
.Concept
.Taquero, you can extract milk from here
Long ago. We have a period, breast-Ni Haruo
.Asvh, sorry
You do Tkona wearing bra
See me again. I have been
.Sozhb to deliver publications
. I'm sorry, Vice-Chairperson
. I have slightly overestimated
.I harmless
However, their size is still huge again, is not it?
.Alkhademh located in love with huge breasts
Haruo-ni caught in love?
.Harv-nee
... This e-
What? Problem with your parents?
No., not at all
.Mktobh well
Flat chest?
! Stupid
Who is a flat chest?
A. for [heart] love
!that's love
.Kadh, Hemegama sensitive to small jokes breast
No., I think it creates humor herself now
. You, Takeru
The Haruko still distributes publications?
Strapping for customers we serve
I came out. I have a long time
.Ah, excuse me, I will go to help
Is he worried about Haruko?
.Klihama, but they are not aware of it at all
who is this girl?
. It's Vice-President of the Student Council, Haruko-Amaya San
. It's also president of the club, who Kenkibo where there is Takeru Aoyama
. If at that time
.So discovered the real power of the man who Qaomina, you will not Artah
.Walan After thinking about it, I've seen me many times in the past
, Although I felt was a joke when I was a small
I know. I have Takei-chan long ago, too
Do you become jealous now?
No., these were not my intention
... McCain lock, gate
... It was my gate of the heavens
, To look at them well this time
Real .lqotk
What about these, you dreaded?
Approaching a girl to wear So, are you retarded or what?
.be cerfull
.Mckin this man may be a copy of the original dish, but very lethal
What speeches this person?
... In this case, I will use again McCain-san
. If your opponent activated, you can not use
,In other words
I can not win against this alien force?
.Taki-chan, cohesion
Are you okay, Takeru?
... Harrow-nee
.Taki-chan
Advisors will protect you
.Progress
throat
.Mckin Falcon
.Amna a touch present in our store, Mr.
. Thank you, Azuki-san
who is this person?
.I do not know
.For any case, let us see his face first
.Wait
Director of the school?
Director?
Lmaza?
Is that?
... What did I
... Minori-chan, Is it possible that I have again
.Ahido, no one was injured
. Thank you, Minori-chan
.Olkny I knew it had been my control
.Such this time
That time?
Cano. I have Kamigarri
Years. Before, they tried to judge Tenby Academy
We used Almckin. We have to fight for self-protect us, but many have been controlling them
.Guru-Be is one of these victims
They were controlled by Kamigarri?
It was a
This is also the case with them?
.Asv, I have caused trouble to everyone again
I thought. I have finally had become a benefit for all
.Lst at fault
Unexpected dull View.
No. I have a choice, it is a novice at this level
.But to make it use its real power, should you pay a little more
. I am disgusted
So always. You, Ootohama
.Kikao-Oni-sama
. I have called me grandpa here suddenly
.Azaam that he had discovered a new promising young
. I have come here to join the game
.Aljd will not say anything, but he will watch everything
Let me tell you the plan. If I had thought of while we eat
,Of course
.Olkny hate doing things half sincerity
Episode XI
Day special offer for macaron Limited
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
Vahdasnan
One Two Three
!one two Three
kakushitetatte ne mawari ni ha kitto bareteru
I try to hide it, but I'm sure that everyone knows this already
kitto
Sure
demo chikasugite mo ne kimochi nante ienai
Although we are very close relatives, I can not tell you what I feel
nante
...But
se no takasa itsu kara watashi yori chotto takakute
I've matured and become a little longer to me before I know it
chotto
Slightly
nanoni kodomo mitai na kao wo shite waraundane
However, you still have those childish smile
shite
Childish
me wo michau to yowai no
I feel weak when I look into your eyes
kizutte yo
Please, notice me
yappari kizukanaide my baby
You do not see me this way after all, oh baby
bi-bi-bi-bikkuri masuka ne
Are you surprised?
suki ni naru nante
I fell in love?
za-za-za-zaiza to nattara
.... If necessary
mamoru kedo kimi no haato madowasu kehai ga shitara
I will defend you, but your heart sends me mixed signals
mo ippo baby baby my day suki to tsugetai
Another step will say that I love you
Sure
...My heart
meki
unfailing
sukaato ni koi ni juudan kakushiteru
! I love Obi bullet under Tnorca
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
Preview of Hemegama
.I grandmother short blonde, Hemegama Kodama
. Finally, we have come to the last episode, but when I think about secession, I would feel lonely
.Mounasph, I'll tell you, no matter what happens, I will stay high school girl Forever
Next Episode Title
Guards herb garden
Concept?