mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
lord-animetion
chiisai koto ni kuyo kuyo shite
, I used to worry about the small things
itsumo watashi tameratetta no
It was hesitant all the time
demo kimi ga oshietekureta fumidasu yuuki
.Olkink showed me how the courage to take the first step
isshoni hiroi suteeji he
, Together on the big circuit
tobikonde ikou
! To jump
donna chiisai negaigoto ga atte kanaete ageru
I will make even small your wish come true
mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara kowagarazu ni
See, to hold our hands tightly, do not be afraid
ichi ni san
! Three, two, one
Is
!Come on
donna toki demo shinjiteru
Whatever the case, I have confidence because I can see the future in front of my eyes
me no maeni mirai aru kara ne
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
kitto
....Certainly
todoku Fly Away
.Snsal him, shaved away
Zero-Kon
It is raining, do you know?
You may also have cold advisors will
.Almatar does not bother me, I think
Okay with this. I also
, Such a rainy day, eight years
I was fine. I have to be a single
Then I met him for the first time
... Takeru-sama
Aanaho-chan?
.Taquero-sama
What speeches?
. In fact, Excuse me, see
Strapping Thalia separation Sports
We are working for advisors will our personnel
.Asvh, will you leave off
.Taquero-sama
What?
. At that time, when it was also raining
at that time?
It was raining. We have only so
What .otsael speeches
Different .tbdo is unusually
.Hassana, everyone sitting
.Bekm, focused your energies inside the crystal balls that we have delivered
Black whirlpools have appeared on Kratkm, is not it?
. This is Anasrkm
. From easy but it meets them difficult to control
. First, imagine the formation icon in the center of the ball
.Oaao, this stunning
.Alsoda, things Injectors that collects in the middle
. This is really difficult
. If I stopped focusing even a second, they go back to normal
.Haruko-Seenba immediately did it completely, I think
. In fact, Haruo-nee is considered a special case
. Even if they can use Almckin which is incredible
, Talking about Haruko-Seenba
What happened to the one who is behind all these attacks?
.Ooh, is
. I am not remember anything you might have done
.Tmama such as victims
.Because been manipulated Bzkryatea
.Otsael if they really lacked memory
!you
What Dikma to Taathdtha him in the middle of a quarterly?
!painful
.Sorry
.Ln improves one of you as long as they believe that ye simply as a crystal ball
.Anasrk it will be even more useful than your Almckin as long as you listen to them
Do you want me proof of this?
... I never
.Hassana, if you insist too much, I'll do it
! Kurigasa
Do you Tqsidina?
!Come on
Are you sure about this, O Director?
.Jsudai metal will become supernatural if McCain used steel
.Seetm Shakk If you get them
No. should worry about good children older
. Just focused on defending yourself
. If you do not, you'll get seriously injured
, First foot
, And then hips
. It is then Qdatk - the place where your item's energy focus
.Tsourha as in the diagram
, When they do, even if you do not have McCain
! You can do things so
Roeetma. Do you, just so
! As if we did this
. As expected from the director of the school, so it is of course a strong component
. We have been very strong
.Ooh, Heck
I was excited. I think a little bit
! Kurigasa-san
Are you fine?
.What? this is no thing
Thick body. I have
.I'm fine
.do not worry
Thick skull. I have
,at that time
... Takeru-sama has said
the shopping?
.Seetm Student Council held a meeting for a long time today
. I have developed a shopping list and money in this circumstance
So, can you do it?
.Of course
. I wish to go away soon
! Iaaa
!Interesting
This was fantastic. We have, Aanaho-chan
Are not you scared?
.not at all
.Taquero-Be, you should try it too
Aanaho, where are you?
.Taquero-Be, see you later
.Good-bye
.Almadhirh, Aanaho-chan
From me. I have Haruo-ni asked that I shop for dinner
Will you come with me?
.Okay
.Bataba, Takeru-sama
. I am glad you came, I've greatly helped me
Happy .I for being able to buy some new snacks
.Oday Aoyama Takeru
! Claimed Aanaho
Excuse me, Takeru-sama, what speeches?
.Aanaho-chan
...I have to
Yeah?
, To tell you the truth
I was thinking about. I have something that I was thinking about it since we went shopping
What is the?
I was holding on. I have this
and that is...?
.Orjok, I can not restrain myself anymore
.Tojd park there
... .I need to do [this], Aanaho-chan
You do not you mind if I did it, right?
.V-in fact, it is assumed that I promised to marry you
...let it go
, If you insist, Takeru-sama
If you will ...
!Sorry! Hold this for me
! I am leaving now
Takeru-sama?
.I'm sorry
Really it was to kill me. I have
Good .hee you did it at the right time
.Olknha still pouring down
. This is true
. Since that time, it was just raining like today
since then?
How long?
Do not you remember?
.Anh about you, Takeru-sama
About me?
...rain Rain
Can not you remember?
Can not you at least give me a hint?
A hint?
! Nations, if, swing
swing?
.Orjouhh, huh? There are no ones here
.Asv, another hint
.promise
... Is it possible that this thing about me is
! It's true! It's the first time that we met
Hmm, what was that?
Was it something new?
.Asv, I just can not remember the thing
What is .okhbrenne
No. I can do this
, You have to remember this yourself must
... Because if you are the only one that I remember
.Fssov be boring
.I understand
I remember when I tell advisors will
.Onzera, rain has become heavier
... We should
.Haa, let's continue this dialogue in the housing
.Taquero-sama, please Go to the house without me
are you mad at me?
.not at all
. I just want to stay here for a longer period
.Aanaho-chan
.Sokon okay, I'll be back soon
...let it go
.Orjo to leave me
.Sokdr you if I did, Takeru-sama
, Perhaps only became selfish
. But I want him to remember
... After all, this anniversary has
... the most expensive thing
.promise
Still Ttjnpin work again?
.Sokon more roughness you during the exercise day
!قِفي! لا يمكنكِ أن تكوني مُتعبة بالفعل
!ألا يمكنكِ الوقوف، إيناهو؟
!توقف عن ذلك
.توقف عن ذلك
LORD ANIMATION :ترجمة
shx :إنتاج
هل كانت تلك...؟ هل يمكن أن تكون...؟
...تاكيرو-ساما
.هو لم يتذكر وعدنا منذ ذلك الوقت
هل أنت وحيد؟
هل تريد أن تأتي؟
،لقد كانت تمطر لمدة أيام
.ولكن هذا لا يُبشّر بالخير
.غرفتي بأكملها أصبحت مليئة بالملابس القذرة
.لقد عدت
ألهذا السبب تركت إيناهو-تشان وحيدة؟
.ولكنها طلبت مني ذلك
ومع ذلك، أليست متأخرة قليلاً؟
.أوياما تاكيرو
،أنا لا أعلم ما الذي حدث بينك وبين إيناهو
،ولكن حتى لو كانا بعيدان عن بعضهما البعض
.هولاء المقدّر لبعضهما البعض سوف يلتقيان
،هؤلاء اللذان ليسا كذلك
،حتى لو كانا يروا بعضهما البعض كل يوم
.لن يترابطا أبدًا
،رؤيتها تدعوك بخطيبها
.على المرء أن يتفرض بأنكما زوجان مُقدّر لهما
،إذا كانت مشاعرها لأجلك بهذه الطريقة
.ينبغي عليك أن تكون أكثر إمتنانًا لها
.سوف أذهب للبحث عنها
.أوسوي
هل عادت إيناهو-تشان إلى المنزل؟
كيف علمت بهذا؟
I saw her look. I have a single moments before
Where you saw?
the garden?
. If you have reason
. I think that you must be well
.Aanaho-chan obsessed with your
! Where you saw?
She was leaving. We have shopping area
Without an umbrella. From
What did you do to her?
.nothing
! If you have not done anything, so why are you cry?
Aanaho-chan ... she was crying?
!Yup
... But, Usui, I did not do
! It does not matter what I did
! Will make you pay the price to make this good girl hurt
... But, but
, I'm on my way now
! I can not forgive myself
, Perhaps I may be a lover boy sex
! But you are the worst
A.-I hurry
!get out of my way
I thought you just. I have stupid, dear boy loving sex
did you change your mind?
.llhzh
. This is not enough
By the way, what I bought?
Will you be okay after becoming wet?
! No, do not worry
.Anh is not something important anyway
.Oha plastic covered
! Oh damn
! A-you stupid, many lust, pervert, Indecent
.Ogel, as I said, Madam
No. I can do this
, You have to remember this yourself
... because I'm the only one that if you remember
Boring notes. It would
!I'm sorry! I have not been an idea of ​​how important this is for you
! I am very sorry for the national response without thinking
Oh, is it possible that you are hungry?
.Me too
.It's weird
When I became sad. So, I'm still hungry
! Aanaho-chan
...this voice
Hei, my cat, why flee away?
!wait
Aanaho-chan, where are you?
Are you also looking for someone?
!No benefit! I will not do it in a timely fashion
.Tsour as flowing in your body
I survived miraculously there. We have
!No way
! McCain, Kamodu
! Heikkn Haatosca
. Thank you very much, Takeru-sama
Saved this cat. I have life
! E-Aanaho-chan! hang in there
! Aanaho-chan! hang in there
What is the matter?
Is not this painful?
A.-I'm okay
Thick skull. I have
.Walan I like you
, When the largest
! I will become your wife
, If when larger
Became more powerful advisors will
! I will take care of your well, Aanaho-chan
T-Takeru-sama, why are you ...?
Not you like it?
.I did not say that
. I'm sorry, I still can not remember the promise
.But I will try to do what I can to do so
Can you give me more time?
.Yup
.Ooadha, I've been my rescue by you
.But in the day, it will become more powerful
! I will take care of your well, Aanaho-chan
Somewhere inside. In Takeru-sama, his memories have survived
. I have promised the same thing exactly as at that time
.Mchaaara has not changed
. This alone is enough to make me happy
! This attraction! He is guilty
We were worried about you. We have
.I'm so sorry
Is there anything would you like to talk about it?
.I'm fine
Oh really?
.Monge: Japanese word meaning cross
.Because Monge looking for me
Rice?
.Ldi cross on his forehead
Simple. You think
In fact, the desire to stay close to their loved ones
Something must .ho people and cats to be shared
E-Hemegama-san, what are you talking about?
I did. I was not talking about you in particular
! Haruko-Seenba, I Ahmrat
! This is because hot air here
. I wish to get out as soon as possible
The sixth
When the rain falls in Tenby
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
Vahdasnan
One Two Three
!one two Three
kakushitetatte ne mawari ni ha kitto bareteru
I try to hide it, but I'm sure that everyone knows this already
kitto
Sure
demo chikasugite mo ne kimochi nante ienai
Although we are very close relatives, I can not tell you what I feel
nante
...But
se no takasa itsu kara watashi yori chotto takakute
I've matured and become a little longer to me before I know it
chotto
Slightly
nanoni kodomo mitai na kao wo shite waraundane
However, you still have those childish smile
shite
Childish
me wo michau to yowai no
I feel weak when I look into your eyes
kizutte yo
Please, notice me
yappari kizukanaide my baby
You do not see me this way after all, oh baby
bi-bi-bi-bikkuri masuka ne
Are you surprised?
suki ni naru nante
I fell in love?
za-za-za-zaiza to nattara
.... If necessary
mamoru kedo kimi no haato madowasu kehai ga shitara
I will defend you, but your heart sends me mixed signals
mo ippo baby baby my day suki to tsugetai
Another step will say that I love you
Sure
...My heart
meki
unfailing
sukaato ni koi ni juudan kakushiteru
! I love Obi bullet under Tnorca
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
Preview of Hemegama
.Oday Hemegama, friendly to all cats
.He suddenly fall from the sky at the end of the first quarter approaching
No. I think it would be a great predictor
Next Episode
The gods descend on Tenby
Mgflan is available. For sufficient to Tenby Academy