mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
lord-animetion
chiisai koto ni kuyo kuyo shite
, I used to worry about the small things
itsumo watashi tameratetta no
It was hesitant all the time
demo kimi ga oshietekureta fumidasu yuuki
.Olkink showed me how the courage to take the first step
isshoni hiroi suteeji he
, Together on the big circuit
tobikonde ikou
! To jump
donna chiisai negaigoto ga atte kanaete ageru
I will make even small your wish come true
mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara kowagarazu ni
See, to hold our hands tightly, do not be afraid
ichi ni san
! Three, two, one
Is
!Come on
donna toki demo shinjiteru
Whatever the case, I have confidence because I can see the future in front of my eyes
me no maeni mirai aru kara ne
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
kitto
....Certainly
todoku Fly Away
.Snsal him, shaved away
Zero-Kon
What are the [Altodabebh Committee]?
.Bbassath, it is a security force for the Academy Tenby
.I President, and Hemegama-san and one of the members
... Haruo-ni is the main and that girl is
.I understand
.Taquero-sama, if I joined, I would do ideals
I ended. I have said I'll think it
. This is not surprising
.Vho has not yet Balmckin
Maybe I was pressing too much
...I feel sleepy
.Aanaho-chan? Kodama-san? I have carried out my shampoo
... Can you tell me to come over
.Ha-Haro-nee
How many times I told you to take notice before entering the bathroom?
! Takei-stupid
Are you okay, Takeru-sama?
I used to this. I have
.Astmaa to me, Haruo-ni
Can you tell me more about the disciplinary committee?
Do you decide to join?
. In fact, not yet
I thought. I have just that I should know more before I decide
.Okay
. If, let the Vice President of the Student Council, explains
Student Council
Well, at the Academy of Tenby
President
It represents the student body by
Vice-Chairperson
Student council. People
, Since it was our duty is to deal with all kinds of battles within the school
Done establishment of an executive committee for users of magic to help us resolve
.Ooedaaha were selected from students of the first and second year
In addition, the club supports the Committee. [Executive called by the Disciplinary Committee
Do you Tsamaana?
! A-order
Student Council
Disciplinary Committee
The Executive Committee for users of magic
. But, we were not active recently, the number of members of the lower
, However, the school has become mixed this year
. So, there is a great opportunity to break out fighting again
for this reason
.I, the main Haruko Amaya, I have decided to complete the club's activities
! In other words, if there is peace in Tenby academic or not it depends on us
, So that students make Ihzawa days filled with fun and joy
! We, the Disciplinary Committee, we must strive to serve
. This all, we have finished the explanation
Concept?
!Yup! I understand
You are Vice-President of the Student Council, Haruko Amaya, right?
.I a new student, Usui Kengo
!nice to meet you
!this person
! Harrow-nee, Ahtrsy
! Beware of what exactly?
...In fact
! Haruko-Seenba
! Let her and will
! I have defeated the intruder
. I have understood it wrongly, Minaya-san
It was an accident. We have
.accident
accident?
.Anh friend of my childhood, Aoyama Takeru-san
Are you okay, Takeru-sama?
.Anh new student, like you
Childhood friend
.Lharuko-Seenba
.nice to meet you
.Oday Minaya Oorotche
In fact. I love pasta and Haruko-Seenba
.Ool insects and insects with short legs, a fool who wears glasses
.nice to meet you
.Manaya-san was my friend since we were in junior high
. It's a very nice girl, so I hope to become friends
! What a lie
Duel in sports stadiums?
! That's right, please to tatin off
are you serious?
If you win, Q-will you become a baby, right?
.Yup
. If I win, you Stadena Sttrkny alone
Azuki-san, you again?
Oh, Vice-President, I have delayed
Why Tqatlin this time?
Stupid. The teaching of the first or second stage is the duty of adults
Hey, is not that ...?
do you know him?
Kay .Koroa
.Anh a strange man who was not his sweetheart for a period of fifteen years and eight months
.Aa her trivial information
Oh my God, the duel on something so trivial?
, Although I have to admit this
, Contrary to those who hide their feelings
.Alrgel which shows his emotions has a good chance of success
.Obaltala must begin fencing
, From here, there are two different paths
.Alve will not cross each other never
, To reveal your blood
, To reveal your sign
You have to your soul. You must show here in Tenby
... flame path
! It must be engraved in the heavens ...
What 's your?
Allen assaultive?
No. I want to Defeat new students so bad
I do without advisors will use my Almckin, too
.Ltota
. You are confident too much, but this is what I love you
! Well if, to bicker
! It is solid
.Onzera to my Almckin
! McCain steel, McCain iron
! Full metal
!Well done
! Tachinama
! I will change the bet
! If you win, it will have to pay for my outfit
.Hee the same applies to my bill for dry cleaning
.I don't mind
.Gm approval of the changes
. This natural for Azuki-san
What everyone's speeches?
What you, Takeru?
.Tbdo worried
Not to make you feel something strange?
! Man hits girl
.do not worry
.Azuki-san strong
.Oafattaat more than you think are strong, Takeru
... or possibly
That fighting with the girls concerns a lot?
! You are on the verge of completion
!it's the end
-Your I stand so! Stop
. He who must stop
! You can not, Takeru
.Altdechl in a duel with another person is not MANLY
E.-this is very dangerous
.Uharuko-right Seenba
... Azuki-san is
! Girls are not vulnerable as you think
...let it go
... If you hit a girl hurt
...I
! S-feet
! Open your defense
!Stop
! Takei-chan
! Takeru-sama
! What is this person?
. Do not stand in my way, O insect
Where did you go?
what the hell?
...you are
! This is not feasible, will never be at better than a full metal
! I've talked a lot
You should open your mouth until you talk, is not it?
What saved me. This
! Azuki-san! Down, down, oh, I mean, Oalak
In paradise. I ...
.Alvaizh: Hinatsu Azuki
! All of you, forget what you have seen
,You are
! O novice stupid
.Pfdilk, I have embarrassed myself
Why intervened?
Do you tamper Bembarzac others have become a new habit for new students?
. It's right, Takeru
You have to respect a code of school rules
.Oont did not enjoy Balmckin yet, you risk it if I stepped into a duel
!seriously
.Sorry
...let it go
. But it was amazing
.Taquero-sama, you are very strong even take such a punch
. In fact, I have been in the region
!that's not the point
! A-order! I'm sorry
.Tmask yourself so you get your Almckin, Takeru-sama
...let it go
, If you look at his good and his valiant
.Taki-chan has not changed even a little
.Haro-ni, I understand now that the girls are strong
, But if you are fighting
On them. They must do this in fair conditions
Fencing ... under fair conditions
.Hamaih this goal is the duty of the Disciplinary Committee
. If this is the case, it will join the Disciplinary Committee
... If I returned his strength
. I have a sense that I have felt it before, somewhere
but why?
Why follow me?
Disciplinary Committee
!Why! Because I want to join the Disciplinary Committee
It is the only club located for me. It is the place where Hemegama-Seenba be the
.Alambarzac that will be fought in Tenby Academy will be fair all
.Somutir on this
The reason I joined. Therefore, the Disciplinary Committee
.excuse me
! Claimed Takeru Aoyama, a new student
LORD ANIMATION: translation
SHX: production
It's great, is not it?
Is .bataba well, it is large with a nice layout
I do not have an idea about a place like this hidden somewhere here
But, why the Disciplinary Committee will be welcome for new entrants
In Hot Springs?
.who knows
Oh, my God, we have three new entrants this year, is not it?
. I am very happy with this
M.-hello Welcome
.Hassana, in order to improve the links between new and old members
. I think that we have to rest a little bit, I think
.Ontm O new members can be applied yourselves there
. I think that this is what she said
. But, no problem as this
. This gives us a chance to see the girls and they dressed in swimming
.you are right
!Let's go
.Asvh to Antzarkme
.Anh beautiful open bathroom
.Oldah great view
.Aliapan beautiful
.Ogel, already
.O_kal very beautiful
... O boys
.Tbdo Oaenkma drift into places inappropriate
Maybe I must Aattaikma light cleansing
! We did not see anything
Calendar-but in this case, it would be impossible to control myself
.Otsael if appropriate
! Stop looking at so
H.-Well
! A-O boys
... This is scary inappropriately
! Him-that's why I did not want the boys to come here
.well now
... We are here to keep the club alive and improve it, so it is very important that
I have. I have Anbtaa I've seen somewhere before
Tomika parameter. It's sister
.I understand now
. You know a lot of random things
,For this reason
As a representative of the Student Council, I, Amadou yucca, I'll be as
.Halqh arrived disciplinary committee and everyone
. First, the President of the Student Council, Takaki-san Foran
Takaky eruption
.nice to meet you
.Naibh President, ःaruko-Amaya San
Amaya Haruko
nice to meet you
.Thelattkm
.Alskrterh, Sato Kimi-san
Kimi Sato
.Msrorh meet you
, Freshman first year of the Executive Committee for users of magic
.Manaya-san Oorotche
Minaya Oorotche
.Srrt to meet you, Aoyama-Takeru-san
. It is the second year, Hinatsu Azuki-san
Hinatsu Azuki
All of you, Abzloa your best, okay?
.Talibh second year in the Disciplinary Committee, Icaza Chacha-san
Icaza Chacha
.nice to meet you
. Finally, Hemegama-Kodama-san
Hemegama Kodama
... As for new entrants in the Disciplinary Committee, Nations
!Here
Keshia Aanaho
.Talibh, Keshia Aanaho
! Please Balkaikn
.Talib, Aoyama Takeru
Aoyama Takeru
.Srrt Balkaikn
. The same thing here, Usui Kengo, student
Usui Kengo
Advisors will love me
, And a faculty member
.Najo Aki
. I wish to become great friends
!painful
Our Student Council, the Executive Committee for users of .shr, the Disciplinary Committee and all of them together here
. Many of overlapping responsibilities, so we will think together one big family
, We all have different duties
. But we should respect each other As colleagues
... Now, this way
!Okay
.Ooh, it is my fault, it is my fault
. I have slipped my hand
.that's unfortunate
.Lo we were thirty centimeters from the right, it was a fatal blow
To hit what exactly?
.Alsme close here
.Balnzer from here to heaven it makes me feel that I could reach the paradise
.Very refreshing
Do you like this place?
.Ogel, it is the first time for being in an open bathroom
And how was the shampoo?
It was fantastic. We have
. I am glad to hear this
. Thank you very much, it's a wonderful feeling
Do you make your hair beautiful and soft as I told you?
.Ogel, I am happy to the same shampoo that my usage you have
Strapping the same smell now
.Ah, thank you, I am very happy
Hemegama-san?
M-What is this?
.Osadat
! Haruko! How dare you make a great lap
-Hemegama-san, Ahidia only and
! Do Fgarin to women with decency toward us flat-breasted virgins
... for-this was not what I wanted
! I suppose that you are afraid of his eyes drift toward Chacha and Aki instead of you
! E-This is not true at all
, If Ordtehma that Tndja more
! I will have to Odllekema for you
.Kudama-san is always emotional on the breasts
. As if they just want to be emotional about the Disciplinary Committee
.Amwalimh Aki
.Haro-chan and Chacha have a large chest, but you have released a really big
Can I Olmshma?
.Ogel, if you want it
. If, I will do it
.Aa God, kids these days
Huge, what is the size of your chest strap?
What do you think? , J or, I, H
!K
. It's a very large I think that your size greater than that
.not at all
What do you think?
But I do not know, the big Idaya is something completely different, is not it?
[This has been renamed to [team-building crawfish
! But in fact, torture blocks Festival
I thought that I had. I have arrived at the border before, but I now really at the end of chordal
Hey, is this ...?
! subdued
DBS?
!There! There
.Db Moon: a type of Asian bears
.Anh Bear Moon
In this great .unmuzj
Alice Banda?
. I am sure that he is trying to turn into a human being
. There moisture, beautiful girls here black pig
.Hn do not you think that this is a big problem
.For any case, this will fix the problem before discovered
Yes, Should I shoot him? Or should I get him out of here?
! This silliness
! There should be better than the use of force method
! It is right! It's a bear, you know?
! If you kicked him, you'll really get angry
What do want me to do?
what about
Expel him away without hurt them?
... Yes, but
.Nsttia did, even if it was crazy
Is not this true, O President?
.Ogel, because we McCain-Ki
McCain-ki? ]
. This is true
.Mckin-Ki
...do not tell me
! As a vector to us? ...
. I have understood, if this is their plan
They will never learn, is not it?
! Feltmuta
Are you both okay, you both?
.Yup
!he is back
What speeches this thing?
Why are we only haunt us?
! Like I know this
!Okay
.Astmra by running in this direction
!Very beautiful
!here we are
! McCain measure, the compressor
! Crush the goal! Pave the path
! It is a plate! It gets bigger
! This is impossible
! Haruko
! Invited me
! It depends on you now
Q.-will destroy the rocks
.do not worry
! McCain painting, comic star
... as a result of drawing
!the pillow
! Doll on the pillow looks nice
! It looks very comfortable
I have hit the rocks just, right?
.Yup
. But, it seems that he had signed a cushion
. This is the power of Kimi-san: that change the physical state of things
! Attack Kimi-san star comic
, Allowing them to use their imagination to highlight the special effects, or highlight the effects
. From the manga and turn it into reality in this way
Do you Vhmtma?
McCain Chacha scale compressor
.Tmcnha of changing blocks sizes and rigid things
.Hma the best type of partners
Fantastic, if this is the ability of the disciplinary committee, huh?
. This is true
And when the Executive Committee adds to users of magic
.You can get the charm of the band disciplinary
...Briefly
.Mckin-Off ...
.I understand
For this reason is
! The Nchcan,
.Right
If .hassana, to do this again
, All new club members
Hi
! The Nchcan,
! Banner: Mubarak hello, new members
What? I took a long time to Tvthiaa?
.Hassana, the time has come to move to the second part of the welcoming party
.Lnokl, to eat
.Ogel, I'm really hungry
! Hello to the McCain-Ki
Episode 3
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
Vahdasnan
One Two Three
!one two Three
kakushitetatte ne mawari ni ha kitto bareteru
I try to hide it, but I'm sure that everyone knows this already
kitto
Sure
demo chikasugite mo ne kimochi nante ienai
Although we are very close relatives, I can not tell you what I feel
nante
...But
se no takasa itsu kara watashi yori chotto takakute
I've matured and become a little longer to me before I know it
chotto
Slightly
nanoni kodomo mitai na kao wo shite waraundane
However, you still have those childish smile
shite
Childish
me wo michau to yowai no
I feel weak when I look into your eyes
kizutte yo
Please, notice me
yappari kizukanaide my baby
You do not see me this way after all, oh baby
bi-bi-bi-bikkuri masuka ne
Are you surprised?
suki ni naru nante
I fell in love?
za-za-za-zaiza to nattara
.... If necessary
mamoru kedo kimi no haato madowasu kehai ga shitara
I will defend you, but your heart sends me mixed signals
mo ippo baby baby my day suki to tsugetai
Another step will say that I love you
Sure
...My heart
meki
unfailing
sukaato ni koi ni juudan kakushiteru
! I love Obi bullet under Tnorca
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
Preview of Hemegama
.Ogel, I am aware that I Hemegama Kodama of the same flat chest category
. However, it seems that there are many men who roam around me
! Will cast severe punishment for these bastards
Next Episode
! The enemy is in Tenby
! I look forward to it