mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
lord-animetion
chiisai koto ni kuyo kuyo shite
, I used to worry about the small things
itsumo watashi tameratetta no
It was hesitant all the time
demo kimi ga oshietekureta fumidasu yuuki
.Olkink showed me how the courage to take the first step
isshoni hiroi suteeji he
, Together on the big circuit
tobikonde ikou
! To jump
donna chiisai negaigoto ga atte kanaete ageru
I will make even small your wish come true
mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara kowagarazu ni
See, to hold our hands tightly, do not be afraid
ichi ni san
! Three, two, one
Is
!Come on
donna toki demo shinjiteru
Whatever the case, I have confidence because I can see the future in front of my eyes
me no maeni mirai aru kara ne
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
kitto
....Certainly
todoku Fly Away
.Snsal him, shaved away
Zero-Kon
.the weather is hot
.Jaw very hot
Why so hot
.Lonh summer
What speeches?
. In fact, there is a heroine with a beautiful silver hair in the window
What? The heroine is a beautiful silver hair?
.wait
No. There is a girl like that on my list
.Ah, delicious
. This must be what Tflih during the summer
.Haruko-Seenba, thank you for your treatment
.Oatdt to eat this in the park with Takei-chan all the time
But is nothing wrong with this In doing?
. In fact, we need to relax in each period
Problems on the rise since becoming .mokhtlth school since it was Chdidna abroad
. This is true
. We may remain for a long period of our President in the afternoon as well as
.O_khasossa when the teacher became Akkaya away
. This is true
.Ikva, we have said embarrassing things too much
What is [true], Haruko-san?
.Alriash
, Quite comfortable
.But do not forget your role as vice president of the Student Council
.Ogel, I'll be careful, O President
,And also
Other .edoh of the team Alvenus had reached Tenby
.Ood you to that person behind the ninety
Those behind the member?
Approval. I myself
.I'm here
When I arrived there?
Are you new the member of Alvenus?
. This is true
.Srrt Balkaikn, McCain-Key members
.Ooh, this risk
.Raiah, such as ninja
Is it possible to be a ninja from the outside?
Huh?
... eyes
.Ah, you're wrong
.Alomr is not that I do not I can vision, but I closed my eyes for different reasons
, Thanks to this
Audio has become the best. I have
What is that?
What happened?
.Allon beige and white color
.Ooh, this beautiful picture
Mr. Frog. This
Is this your strength?
.Oadhirana, I wanted to know what is common among girls Japanese high school
. I love the girls who Mthelkn
where did you go?
Where the heroine is a beautiful silver hair?
.I do not know
Heck, how to be the only one who has seen the person?
Oh my God, why are you always Mtnmra Ali?
What are you saying?
divine?
What Tzninh you're talking to him?
. I was talking to a person who looks at the eyes of savages, of course
. You, who Asthakrna
Who will look to a girl from elementary school like you?
Has become an expert in. We have psychology, O stupid
What?
I sat on your knees. If I begged and now, perhaps you may forgive you
. This is good, what about licking my shoes
You, my witness, this is a battle
.Feltsra
Will you let them?
Ah, I have no choice, right?
. Just to be safe, go and contact Pkinkibo
. I have understood, do not get involved again
.Walan, to start the battle
Path of the sun
. You should be printed in the sky
.Mcn engagement: Kitso
.Ltsna Pride
My .alkatso able to put a discount to the area where it can be punched up to each other
. If apologized now, I'll let you after you go to lick my shoes ten times
.Oaha Stinking
. This stench makes me vomit
.Kvak jokingly
.Mckin range: the preparation of the park
.You're really stupid
. Although you're trying to put yourself in a good position, in the end, you walk in the territory
what is happening?
.Klihama did not Athrca long ago
The battle was decided. We have
Huh?
Small .ochta can create a special area
. When someone enters Almckin, the territory of the doll house, it will become under the control of my little sister
Now, where do I start playing?
.Dhirall
.Mckin my little sister can make a doll tied opponent
.Alodharar resulting from the doll moves to rival a hundred times
.Toagafi about it
.Talma you have already won, should you stop
What?
Do you intend to stand in my way?
. If, to make you already doll
.Feltcil on your knees in front of me
. From here the fun begins
.Alomr not because the enemy girl
. I just can not forgive the fact that the weak is the one who is beaten
What?
.No way
.Ldermih out of control
.Ooagafi Almckin your off
. This man dares to Mquaomte
.I will kill you
...that girl
Where do you come from?
,from here
. From the best that you stop
M-What do you mean?
Do you Tomarena?
... It does not matter very seriously in the matter
. I have exceeded that slightly
If anything happens, what Statzmen to do with it?
I was joking. I have a little
.Bdla me, you should care about the job that you received
.Trakhy work will tell the grandfather, President Kamigarri
Are you fine?
.Yup
.Almadhirh, this battle has stopped
, Emergency measures have been taken
. But it is still in pain
.Anh need treatment immediately
.Yup
Takeru, are you okay?
.Taquero-sama
He claimed Minerva from Martha Alvenus
. From today onwards, I'll get to Tenby Academy
Maybe a very short period of time may be, but to look forward to working together
Kenkibo
, Aoyama-san, in fact
Countermeasures taken yesterday on that knowledge
It caused difficulties. You may inside the school
.I understand
In addition, you did not pass the exam until your feature
Huh? How do you know this?
. I have received a report from the school principal
.Alsatrh elements on something that is essential when using Almckin
.Edo Almckin-Ki never failed before
... Therefore,
! Do you expel?
LORD ANIMATION: translation
shx: production
.Mckin-Ki
If you fail. Just configuration exam, I think
.Hassana, do not be frustrating
.Almckin-so is not considered life like for you
. I want to be with Takeru-sama all the time
... and also my post Kkhtaibth
. This is true
Banished from your eyes. If Takei-chan for a moment, you'll chase another girl
.Aa him from a bad excuse
.Alomr has nothing to do with me
What happened?
Is there a problem for you?
.Ooh, you are the heroine with a beautiful silver hair
I thought. Also, it's not here, it's not on my list
Minerva-san. It's, which has come here yesterday
! Why are you the only one who knows it again? O despicable
.just chill
.I see
.Achtbar training tomorrow after school
.Harith to get the talent, learn everything in one day is possible
In this case, why not ask everyone for help
...This means
.He such as training camp
training camp?
Amaya Haruko
Cochea Aanaho
Hemegama Kodama
Aoyama Takeru
What is this meaning, Takeru-Be?
. This is the case that I wanted to see her
It seems that you misunderstood something
.Alomr is not so
Huh?
. Many of the women Taatnafsn to get the man it is quite like the story of the harem
Is not this is the standard in this country?
What state are you talking about?
.For any case, we should prepare dinner
What is called?
. [I gave him the name of [Monge
.Taki-chan, do your best in practice
Huh? just me?
Try hard doing it yourself is the right way, right?
Later advisors will Otvkdk
.Mvhom, invited me
., Come, O fugitive
... Hey, Usui
. Although they Gbean, but beautiful friendship
Are the four you always here?
.Ogel, every day becomes a fun
. In fact, it does not become boring
Happened. We have to live together because of the allocation of housing
Oh? What it is supposed to [an event] to be?
Hemegama-san, this again?
.Hassana, I have a question for the three Ogelkn stank
What is the?
Is there something about Balmckin-Ki?
Is there someone you love him?
Huh?
What?
.Althdt on love is part of the training camp
. First, Hemegama-san, please Go ahead
Why start out with me?
... I do not have a lot to talk about
.Vhmt, I will talk
.Hassana, no matter what
.Akhr once I liked where someone was a long time ago
, Even if we meet again
No. We can be together
. How should I say it? I've always been very close to me and is still far away from me
.Walohm, it should be more interested Dikma things to talk about
... about it ... I know it is related to him, but
A.-It's not about Btaki-chan
. [We have said only done
. If, the matter is true
What about you, Aanaho-san?
.Ogel, I love Takeru-sama
. This does not work at all
.For this rate, you will not be able to hit five meters away tomorrow's exam
Are you disturbed by the fact that you are not able to stop the battle again?
...shut up
. I do not know why it has become complicated with those things and I do not want to even know
. But if you think you are right, just make your way to
... Usui, you
. I just do what I want to do as well as
The reason I can. Therefore, enjoy this paradise
... In the future, I want to live in a big white house with Takeru-sama, nanny big dog
.Ah, of course, and with us Monge
.Oona I also want to have the three boys and two girls
.Hmm ... There is nothing wrong if they were more, too
Do you have such a detailed planning already for your future?
... valan
Oh, what's the problem?
. I think that the time has come to lose its progress in training
I come also advisors will
. In fact, no need for it
.You can cook a delicious meal for him
Off advisors will help her
. This is true
.Haruko, just do what you can do
What suits you best. This
.Aanaho-chan, will make a lot, so excited about being
Well, by the way, what Sentboukh?
.For any case, we will cook a lot
.Lo I could control with breathing element
.Bamkana achieve miracles
Do you do it?
. This can not be imagined
.Amcunnina feeling the amount of elements is increasing suddenly
.Wonderful! I finally Osptha
Most importantly, do this from Fltk?
A.-I do not know
.Sidta, someone here
.I know that
It seems that it is not the other person Takeru
What about off the game hide and seek?
.Minerva
. If, I Ahztna
I Tlahakan or rather, Mracpti, right?
.Ogel, you have so beautiful there Hechegama
What?
Maybe, Hemegama-san, too
You can see the element itself?
If, how do you look in your eyes?
Why Minerva-san allowed to go alone?
.Hemegama Kodama bearing evidence of what they want Kamigarri, Yamato O'Kane
First, I would like Minerva
.Bon continue to implement our mission yet, so we will not be late too much
.Alqaid Akkaya, I would like to ask one question
Why we ordered us to live as students in ordinary Tenby Academy?
. This is true
Good timing.
.Ood to ask you about something, too
Do you Ohabptn this school?
.Ogel, I love Takeru and his friends-Be
. Although most of them are stupid, in general, they are not bad
I love this school. I
As well as .tlbh
What about Dimitora?
,I do not know
, But compared to the discrimination and persecution of the ability of users in the outside world
. This is very cozy place
After many problems, I still Fattening this place Baldavi?
.Naibh leader, your words is unusual
No. currently reassuring answer for me
I have seen the real bodies, is not it?
, Hemegama-san, before the outbreak of Chtmk Omanohara
. We are from Alvenus We have received orders to Bjelbk Kamigarri
What you said?
Madam .okonna'll let you take you so easily
.Aa them guards accredited
No. Tqll of my business
.Aa his hasty Hachegama
.Kagutsoca
.Aa him foolish man
.Tmhl Aicazuchi
This .khve
What is this light?
... illuminating swung the machete
.Sidta, I'm sorry
.Gid, if you want it, you'll take all your fellow together
.Antzera Please, I do not have any intention to conceal, your
. We have been our mandate to investigate the strength of students Tenby
So what?
. Today, I have seen such a boy carrying spiritual your waves
It intrigued me. I have
Do you mean Takeru, huh?
Do you plan that already Tokhve?
Maybe, but I have just arrived
Also, it seems that I will love this place
. Because there are many beautiful girls as well as wonderful Breasts
... Do not tell me that Haruko and others
No. worry, both of which do not Tzala here
.Taquero-sama
.Taki-chan
. You can get a degree of success easily now
. As promised, I'm going to re-Aqaltk of the club
.Thanana
Be careful from now on
.Ostmr to complete your work for McCain-Ki
.Concept
.Boutriqh what I have avoided expulsion
.Ooh, Sheria-san
.Oaha Selfish
Why you did not invite me to the training camp?
... No, excuse me, it's not really
.Hiria, I have read that the Japanese men deliberately to be Bardeen towards women as they want
Love Student Council
. All of this is written in this book
Oh really?
Why did not you say this early?
I understand. We have, and we will study health only two of us tonight
!You are
.Mmnoa sexual intercourse between heterosexual
.Taquero-sama, cohesion
.Almadhirh, Nations, for
.Taquero, it should be disqualified after all
The tenth episode
Girls of light and shadow
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
Vahdasnan
One Two Three
!one two Three
kakushitetatte ne mawari ni ha kitto bareteru
I try to hide it, but I'm sure that everyone knows this already
kitto
Sure
demo chikasugite mo ne kimochi nante ienai
Although we are very close relatives, I can not tell you what I feel
nante
...But
se no takasa itsu kara watashi yori chotto takakute
I've matured and become a little longer to me before I know it
chotto
Slightly
nanoni kodomo mitai na kao wo shite waraundane
However, you still have those childish smile
shite
Childish
me wo michau to yowai no
I feel weak when I look into your eyes
kizutte yo
Please, notice me
yappari kizukanaide my baby
You do not see me this way after all, oh baby
bi-bi-bi-bikkuri masuka ne
Are you surprised?
suki ni naru nante
I fell in love?
za-za-za-zaiza to nattara
.... If necessary
mamoru kedo kimi no haato madowasu kehai ga shitara
I will defend you, but your heart sends me mixed signals
mo ippo baby baby my day suki to tsugetai
Another step will say that I love you
Sure
...My heart
meki
unfailing
sukaato ni koi ni juudan kakushiteru
! I love Obi bullet under Tnorca
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
Preview of Hemegama
.I'm tired
. This time, I'll let it as a
.Ogel, I love Takeru-sama, very much, very
... Take your time, Aanaho-chan, on Takei-chan, I also
Next Episode Title
Day special offer for macaron Limited
.Kltakma not Tsalehan Preview at all