mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
lord-animetion
chiisai koto ni kuyo kuyo shite
, I used to worry about the small things
itsumo watashi tameratetta no
It was hesitant all the time
demo kimi ga oshietekureta fumidasu yuuki
.Olkink showed me how the courage to take the first step
isshoni hiroi suteeji he
, Together on the big circuit
tobikonde ikou
! To jump
donna chiisai negaigoto ga atte kanaete ageru
I will make even small your wish come true
mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara kowagarazu ni
See, to hold our hands tightly, do not be afraid
ichi ni san
! Three, two, one
Is
!Come on
donna toki demo shinjiteru
Whatever the case, I have confidence because I can see the future in front of my eyes
me no maeni mirai aru kara ne
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
kitto
....Certainly
todoku Fly Away
.Snsal him, shaved away
Zero-Kon
.Omaya Haruko talk
Aoyama. We have Takeru managed to become a member of Almckin-Ki
.Lonh still has no Almckin, I have faced many difficulties
Also .otbdo that Hemegama-san has taken are interested in
, I went shopping
, To a cafe maid
... and then ... are
! P-though I do not care about it
.Taquero-sama
.S-Good morning, Haruo-ni
.Bbah good, it is very rare to see take place very early
, P-in fact, to tell you the truth
I do not able to conceal emotions since a duel Azuki
. I do not even remember what happened at the time
. I really do not understand all the things in Tenby is also well
. But, I think that I have some strength
. Not only for me but also to protect the people around me
You mean Hemegama-san, right?
... A-Ntzry! Harrow-nee
Maybe she really angry this time
!what the hell?
Foolish
! And whoa! this is healthy
.Mak green color bright eyes hurt
, This is intended
Disciplinary Committee
! Harrow-nee
! You know the extent of my hatred for peas
.I help you to stop being a picky
I wanted to develop your power to protect the people, right?
A.-order, but this is exaggerated
, If this is what you really thinks of
.You can make your lunch from now on
... If you want to become stronger
.Aatna yourself by yourself
Calendar-but ... I can not cook
! Ntzry, Harrow-nee
! N-Vice-Chairperson
M-What Tflanh you two here?
.I-Oh my God, what a daring you to do it in broad daylight
! Do you listen to yourself?
! A-It's not like I wanted to look! It was an accident
!wild
! If, I show the real face in the past, you pervert
SAL-I understood it wrongly
.I did not do anything
! Haro-Ni, word and shyya, freedom, Haro-Injured
... Aoyama Takeru-san
! I ... I'm not a big sister
What do I do?
. In the end, I have gone without lunch
Is this my fault?
.I do not understand that
...This is like
...Did you understand? If you win
.Well Well
Chacha-san, and Azuki-san?
! Ready, starting
! Winner: Chacha
. As agreed upon, the budget remains the same
! T-awesome
.in a blink of an eye
But, why it ended Mbarzathma?
! Aoyama Takeru
I was looking for you. I have, my bad
T-lousy?
... Please, budget ... budget
No. One has the opportunity for girls to Almckin
Nations, what was that?
Kanu. We have been negotiating on the top of the club's budget
Any club is not satisfied allocated .lhm by the Council of quotas can do so
.Anh looks like a business meeting
The work of this meeting?
.Alba in the Disciplinary Committee are busy Baltvaaudhat with various clubs
. We are the only ones that we can not help in this
Is this true?
.. I understand, if, any club we should go
. Do not get me wrong in
.Mptdi like you are still a few experience to deal with the budget negotiations
. We have there have been many violent incidents in the school grounds recently
It seems that the victims of these incidents do not remember anything from them
, Since they fought the unknown opponent
. From clear that they can not be in fair duels
. This case is shrouded in mystery
, Minaya-san and Aoyama-Be
.Ood that you two of you Tgeraa a thorough investigation of the victims
! Do not Tenseea that Trsla us updates, only for necessary
...sorry
.Hnalk one thing I would like to make him clear
.I do not love you
Why is this openness?
, Pain after you discover what your strength
.Oona do not see you on an equal footing
, But you still a member of Almckin-Ki
.Oona One of the Disciplinary Committee
. I should do it proudly
Maybe I do not like it, but let's work together
... Oorotche-san, I'll be happy for
No. calling me by my first name
. I have become very friendly
A.-I wonder if they really want to work with me
! As I said it
, If we stop our actions
! The society in which we knew would die
! I agree
No. Tdeihm they seize their rhetoric and Oafiqi simply, Kimi
! But I envy them
!I beg you
Commander Z
! Manga does not belong to Japan alone
298 67 l 322 565 1059 567 1033
Commander Z
.Hdvina is the answer to the demands of the world
Azari them the possibility of our fame
... We hope to be produced and marketed to the world
.For any case, I can see how Atwejtk on this subject
Request your budget advisors will move my to the top of our list at the present time
Really exhausted. I
What speeches?
I was just thinking. I have you become soft recently, Haruo-chan
Do you become so, really?
. In the past, I was Vice President of the perfect student council
Is it possible that you have changed because of Aoyama-Be?
! M-what you are saying, Kimi?
... I Takei-chan
.Mejrd childhood friends
. It should be hungry now
! P-In any case, it is very cocky and lazy to be gustatory
, It leaves the dirty washed accumulates
, Which is a picky with his food
! When the repaired school uniform button, has said he did not notice this until
...And also
. If you care about it very much
.nothing special
No. Nothing special for all these three
! Stop this noise spam
Easy to say. From this
.please enter
This should be more than provide you, right?
Thank-NIS
. It's actually nicer than I expected
Are you fine?
Seems that Htertk has ruined
. I have made a lot for lunch
. If you wanted to, it, I can share with
. At first I was a little girl broken
, But after spending more time with this powerful and gentle girl
My feelings. I have become stronger
I think it will be difficult, can I count on you?
!Yup! I will do what I can
I was burning in the stomach, do you have any juice?
! Drink from the fountain
! Ah, this has been a good
. But, I feel that I have become used as a tool
.Orad to show that I am useful
! This is true
Sent to other advisors will of the Disciplinary Committee message
Disciplinary Committee with you, right?
.Hnalk something I would like to talk to you about it
! B-course
What is the?
Talking to me? What can it be?
Are you you want me?
.Haa, you
N-Yes?
You are looking for the person who attacked the students, right?
How do you know about this?
I .lonna know who did it
are you serious?
Will keep it a secret, is not it?
.Hecma I know that I can trust your
.Alsid member of the Disciplinary Committee
.Ooh, claimed Takeru Aoyama
.I see
Aoyama Takeru, for?
! McCain acquirable, Media
! I can not move
LORD ANIMATION: translation
shx: production
. This is not useful
! I can not lift my feet from the ground
.Toagaf act by force and calling your friends for help
. Whenever fought, the more become your ability to move your legs less
.Walan, faster
. I do not care about your Almckin
... All I want to know is
. If you real Janiya that behind all these incidents
! Fluorochrome by
! McCain sword, Perseus
. Just Astslma
, As long as I maintain a racist
.Tlk optical stilettos will Ttardek
RO-fabulous
No. wonder that it was chosen as the executing
Maybe you may be able to win
Why are you standing there?
Destroy the reputation of advisors will Almckin-ki being a heavy load
! Â-sorry, Oorotche-san
! I told you not to use my first name
! It Minaya for you
I understand now. I have, you really surprising
.Manaya-san Oorotche
! S-feet
If your feet become in the regions
I invite you .When your full name, you will not Tkona able to move anymore
. Although I've hunt small fry
. Even though I tried hard to stir up trouble
... If this means
.Anh senior members of the McCain-error in order to not accepting the challenge of never
. Therefore, why will I get them even come to me instead
.Hassana, the time of punishment has come
!Curse
... We are by the two, we can not
! This is true
! Harrow-nee
!Do not do it
They gave us this task. We have
! We can not disturb adults about it
...let it go
! One will not respect us if we continue to rely on others
! Do you say that we must stand idly by and do nothing?
, Behave like the pathetic asshole
! Just Stay, watched
I said that I would like. I have to protect everyone
! Now see to
Not a word of them?
. This is true
, You have sent them Breda
. But for some reason did not reach them
.Hnalk the chance that they were arrested in the parks
!No way
! Harrow-Teshan
Now, now, because you go to ask for help?
! I really do not care if you Stqdan the last moments to cry and sigh of pain
! I will not cry
I like advisors will Haruko-Seenba: respectable and powerful
! It will become like a wonderful
... Mina-san
!get ready
... This light
! Harrow-Teshan
.Keme, please
! Now, knock
, McCain painting
! Star comics
! Wave effect rush
It seems that I have arrived at the right time
I've hunt hunting big, huh?
.Oha Vice-Chairperson
! Haruko Amaya
.Oaao, as we expected of you
. You are able to resist while you're surrounded by a lot of racist
Ordinary. People can not stand
.Haruko-Seenba
... I'm sorry, I did not
You did a good job. I have
.Seenba ...
what do you want?
Why Tnhdran down?
...my goal
.Ogel, I remember now
This is because of the elite. All Almckin-so that Thdiati has never accepted
. So I set up the scheme to attract them
. I understand what you tell
. But I can not Msamehtk
Taven. You dear people
... So what do you get it will not be a duel
! But punishment
, McCain lock
! Heaven's Gate
My own .mckin opens the door to the dimension alternately
. On the other hand, stamped force Almckin
... McCain Haruo-ni
.Anna I see for the first time
! Divide the heavens
! McCain Murakomo
.I understand
. If this is Murakomo, the most destructive of the eight real Almckin
.Hassana If, put you in touch and let's get out Ntbarz
.this is not possible
To lift the entire seal, the gate of heaven on my anger We Lunch
.Ually the amount of discount skill
I'm not. You are strong enough until we get out
... But, if you use a little anger only
! Enough joke
! I can unleash its power
M. McCain-my
Do you break it?
! Seenba
.I'm so sorry
.Do not apologize
. We have ended up now
.Ooh, you're beautiful when you become a little dirty
. You are saving, right? You need to cohere
...Yup
I apologize. I also
... I've Mgtra myself this morning
Now. Until, I still useless
Sorry. I, Minaya-san
Not to send Ojbertk. We have to help
. So, we both are wrong
! But, Haruo-ni, Almckin your really stunning
! I will train hard, so that I can become the strongest
.Otsael If you will get a strong Almckin
! Surely do
But only if I worked hard as usual, okay?
!Thanks
. I think that I have heard screams
Are you sure that they do not need our help?
.Haruko went for help, so there is no need to worry
No. There is a spirit in this school is able to stand in her face
If you are the strongest in Tenby?
! Haruko-Seenba really amazing
It was really. I have useless, she can not even make out the blade sheared
. In fact, there is no problem
.Afattaat will you come to us in a timely fashion
.Deina only reduce our movements until then
.OK brother
.Ottalaa this
Haruo-ni, good work - Takeru
! Haruko-Seenba
! Aoyama Takeru
!Sorry
.Taki-chan, [good work] you also
.Tamha delicious
The fifth
The strongest girl in Tenby
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
Vahdasnan
One Two Three
!one two Three
kakushitetatte ne mawari ni ha kitto bareteru
I try to hide it, but I'm sure that everyone knows this already
kitto
Sure
demo chikasugite mo ne kimochi nante ienai
Although we are very close relatives, I can not tell you what I feel
nante
...But
se no takasa itsu kara watashi yori chotto takakute
I've matured and become a little longer to me before I know it
chotto
Slightly
nanoni kodomo mitai na kao wo shite waraundane
However, you still have those childish smile
shite
Childish
me wo michau to yowai no
I feel weak when I look into your eyes
kizutte yo
Please, notice me
yappari kizukanaide my baby
You do not see me this way after all, oh baby
bi-bi-bi-bikkuri masuka ne
Are you surprised?
suki ni naru nante
I fell in love?
za-za-za-zaiza to nattara
.... If necessary
mamoru kedo kimi no haato madowasu kehai ga shitara
I will defend you, but your heart sends me mixed signals
mo ippo baby baby my day suki to tsugetai
Another step will say that I love you
Sure
...My heart
meki
unfailing
sukaato ni koi ni juudan kakushiteru
! I love Obi bullet under Tnorca
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
Preview of Hemegama
! I have lines were not practical in this episode
.But, the strongest girl in Tenby] certainly made her more irritations in front of her childhood friend
What? Is the secret of you will be questioned about the engagement?
Next Episode
When the rain falls in Tenby
.Ood to know more about this myself