mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
lord-animetion
chiisai koto ni kuyo kuyo shite
, I used to worry about the small things
itsumo watashi tameratetta no
It was hesitant all the time
demo kimi ga oshietekureta fumidasu yuuki
.Olkink showed me how the courage to take the first step
isshoni hiroi suteeji he
, Together on the big circuit
tobikonde ikou
! To jump
donna chiisai negaigoto ga atte kanaete ageru
I will make even small your wish come true
mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara kowagarazu ni
See, to hold our hands tightly, do not be afraid
ichi ni san
! Three, two, one
Is
!Come on
donna toki demo shinjiteru
Whatever the case, I have confidence because I can see the future in front of my eyes
me no maeni mirai aru kara ne
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
kitto
....Certainly
todoku Fly Away
.Snsal him, shaved away
Zero-Kon
.Omaya Haruko talk
.Hiria, from Alvenus, it became clear star famous singing
. I have used a bold step to go on a date with Takeru
Teamwork. We have been shown by members of Venus in support of an impressive
.But purpose of the period, which was given to Takeru for Special Offer
.Sbb what, I felt very much relieved
! Finally, I came this day
. This best chance to get a girl since the school began
No. We can not miss the opportunity on the day of the main event
.Yup
.Lonna did not score here for Almckin or for the use of elements
! We did this in order to acquire the experience perfect in high school, in order to acquire beautiful times we live with no regrets
!exactly
... for this goal, we
. We should be bold, whatever the obstacles we face
! You can not start the race without making a great effort
! Without a start, you can not cross the goal
!Let's go! To our Committee Glorious
... Three days ago
, My disciples men
. First, I would like to thank you for coming today
, Since I have many things to say it
: There is one thing in my mind now
Could you forget that inequality? Could you forget the lack of sanity?
!No! You can not
! Listen
! And now the time has come for the advancement of
! Men in Tenby
Disciplinary Committee
What is that?
, A list, do not
.Srkhat emotional boys
Emotional screams?
Did you hear, O President?
.Bhon schedule of classes for swimming throughout the year, this is it
A.-order
Girls. I have sought for separate chapters, and this is what we are doing
! This is the problem
If you're upset because you will not be able to ogle a girl in the swimming pool?
Why all boys in Tenby completely fools?
Azuki-Seenba, you're sewing?
. This strange deed Onotah you
Do you have a problem with this?
! Hey, what do you mean by strange laborers Onotah]?
.Aah, it is my fault
. I am ashamed to say this, in this modern society we had to move away from the labels [masculine] and [feminine] a long time ago
!For this reason
! You must swim classes mixed MAKE
. If, this is the true color choices
.But does not seem to be fair to accept the request for a proposal on their own boys
.Of course! For this reason you add this
We will use this to decide
Battle of the Knights of water?
! That sounds fun
.Oh really
.Alba of the school are very excited for the competition
.But, it was supposed to develop the Battle of the Knights during the turbulent period of civil war
.Ofterd battle knights much more competitive than volleyball for this country
What is going on?
.Anh on mixed swimming pool
! Wait a moment, O President
Is there something wrong?
Haruko-san, do not compromise the spirit that the settlement of the conflict in Tenby physical competition, rather than the popular vote?
.Olcunnina already got permission from the faculty was established student schedules
!it is too late
.Jba, still you act as usual
Do you mean that you do not have confidence
That we girls are unable to win in front of the new boys?
!-For will not win
No. There is a chance for it
.of course no
.good
. This is true
.Ohar had been booby-for approval of that
.Mthalaa
. Because this is what exactly will happen
! But it seems that everyone is looking forward to it, it has been a long time since I enjoyed competition
.Yup
! Yes, yes, they say that participation in the festival is the most fun
I made a mistake. I have to say again
.nothing important
.Bagdih, since we mixed we had to deal with the boys stupid non-stop
!Right! Boys sundowners to the credibility of Tenby
, Even since it was mixed Tenby
I was worried. I have about the place you see him
.Alriash, I have heard that the teacher Akkaya will participate in the Battle of the Knights
E. Is this true?
. In fact, I do not mind doing it once
.Christzawn including a rude awakening much today, after all
!Damn you
! I Osotm understanding
! We need more than thirty centimeters to reach the mythical paradise
!are you serious? But we are very close
Excuse me, Can we start?
! Wait a little
.Not yet
! Do Jnntma already?
... Kurigasa-Be
What speeches?
! What speeches ?! Everything the speeches
What was this?
!painful
! I have heard of people who are in a quarterly
. After all the fuss in order to get a cavalry battle
.Sokon in such team, O losers
What's more, do you really expect us to fight against the higher grades students?
.But Azuki-Seenba one of them
.Kurigasa, dreaded
... But, if you're
.Walovdil of that, we have a secret weapon
! McCain-Ki's Bousaya Kagichiro can hide one's appearance and existence of the enemy
!What?
...this means
... Excuse me, in fact
McCain .anh on my chameleon
.Amcunnina hide your appearance, but I can not hide you are
Damn! After raising my hopes, and you want me to make me a fool?
, If he can not hide our presence
.Hemegama-Seenba still Ttrsdna
. I have started to feel concerned about the Battle of the Knights
No., no need to worry
!he is back
.Markh knights just a simple trick to pave the way for the main event
! We will do everything we can to get to own our Committee
! Everyone, time has come finally
The referee
Outstanding
Follow-up
607 605 l 616 572 745 562 740
605 605 l 616 572 745 562 740
843 576 l 859 526 1019 521 1004
We will now begin the Battle of the Knights of water
! To make the decision on swimming students mixed swimming lessons
! Sheria, you rule
! We can do it
! For mixed classes
Team. All has six groups, one of which is led by a teacher
Be a heated battle advisors will in cold water
! Vice-President! you can do it
! For win
! And fought, girls Tenby
! Do not think Tejebn
. From the head loses the ring is not eligible
.However, if the passenger fell to the water, the team will come out already
.Almjmuah that will endure to the end to win for their team
! Everyone, your best Abzloa
! You will exclaim
The referee
Outstanding
267 656 l 269 605 464 606 456
! Teacher Akkaya
! Oh, how this shameful
Have you reached the age of puberty yet?
.Osubht dating back to the past memories of my days in the emotional high school
! I am excited here kindled
! I started my blood boiling
A.-day, we certainly will make sure to deliver our feelings to Hemegama-san
! I mean, it's my chance to tell her what I feel
!You are
! You can not be enjoyed by
! Hemegama-san is the property of the whole club
! It is not the property of one, you fools
! Azuki-Seenba, religion response time has come
Royal .sodjalk
Did you understand?
.Tktekna flawless
.we will win
. You can count on
! This game is the focus of our school for Kamal
! Takeru-Be
, I'm not good at swimming
If sunk. So, be sure to save me
.Hiria-san, I did not know that you do not swim Tsttiein
.she's lying
.Baltokid lie
! Depended upon you
! We can not make fun of us novices
!of course no
.Enbga to have the day off
. Why should I be bearing? I am one of the most beautiful women in the school
!Oh really
.Afattaan in this school they do not have a taste
. This makes me cool
Screamed, screamed?
, But, according to initial popular vote
.Clakma has been Dekma in a high place like Azuki
. I have been chosen Azuki-san because her name comes first alphabet
.V-in fact, I think I can let it this time
, Excuse me, yucca-san
...I think you
.Chjaa everyone is the side of being a member of the Board
But, how do you relate to the battle knights our mission?
. Not related
. But as long as that has been selected, we can not undo the challenge
...we
.Snchahd on the bench again ...
! Now, we will start this tournament with our announcement this duel officially
! Pride one
! Nahrin Mtdfiqin
... tracks
! ... us open windows
... The Holy Blood which is within us
! Must flow ...
! Akeshvo Our Brands
! For victory
! Guided by our souls
! Guided us to justice
... it is our place to stand
! Next to Tenby, divine sun ...
LORD ANIMATION: translation
shx: production
.Tktekna clear and simple, we will achieve victory, which is our priority
.Ologel win, we will Nhzy one Baktalat against one after the start of the battle
. Although the aim Takeru will have different
.When _ibikun in the battle, Arise, save time by not falling into the water
. At the same time must Takeru took the head ring
Do you Tqsdna?
. If you discount, the Aanaho-chan will not resist
Takeru-sama?
! I am not happy about it, but this is a sport
, I'm sorry, Takeru-sama
. As I said, this is a sport
! This means that I will not lose, no matter what
.Oossuy, idiot
! Your plan has completely failed
.Ldjal matters worse, so it seems a bit fight as well
! Can not O_it! If you do, you'll Thzmna
...In this case
Some advisors will let you know the magic words
.Astkhaddmha If you are about to defeat
Takeru-sama?
! Valan leisure
Oh?
! Immediately after the start of the battle, the boys team get the head of the League
What happened, Aanaho-chan?
SAL-He told me that everyone is talking about obesity my arms
Worse. You
.the worst
.Ogel, worse
! You are, Usui, do not join them
Were excluded. We have one team of girls
... Our mission in life
! Is approaching Hemegama-san only ...
What speeches?
I'm not sure. I
! ... There is something strange, you, you
Our vision can not?
.Yup
, If he is still practicing for a long time in Tenby
.Vanh it will be able to see these things
.However, you will not be able to move forward
! Hemegama-san
! We are from Hemegama fan club we have a message for you
, Even if you're the youngest girl in the girls group
! We are still think you're the best woman
! This will never change
! To be honest, I think that smaller is better
those people! How dare your call washing board?
.Haka, they are the rudest men who can Tejelhm
!you
! Aptaada
! Well, should I answer pathetic to Srechtkm
One fell. We have boys team
, Given the strength of the electricity attack Hemegama
. We have been eliminated completely boys her club
They have learned. I wish this
. If I lost my temper, terrible things happen
Angry face
! Also beautiful, at least in my opinion
! Hemegama has cost lethargy
.Oossuy
! League took the head from behind it makes them ineligible
Maybe because I talked a lot
... Besides, I also love your chest ma
! No one cares what you love
.Walan, an update on the current situation
.Oossuy barely avoided falling under the water, this is safe
Is it time
Boys team. What is still in the lead
For our mission?
After. Not, I think
.However, the numbers alone do not achieve victory
What speeches?
Seems that you become a little bit stronger
! But you still do not compare me
.I know this
...for this reason
for this reason?
! That's why this is my only choice
.Jba, Aoyama has a trump card up his sleeve
.Anh usual oblique
Is still an idiot. What
.Certainly
! Why, you stupid Takei
League of my head?
! I Altqtoh
! Safely boys team
.Ouyama Takeru was not fully submerged in the water
! You, cohesion
. Just wait a moment please
! He holds the League head in his right hand
What happened here?
! Replay to watch
. This is Deputy our President, I have hit him directly on the jaw
.Ah, here is
! I grabbed her
.Oomaya grabbed her head while the League is a bird
! This is how wonderful, what a superhero movement
.Asv, Harrow-Apr
Are you okay, Azuki?
It was so soon. We have
, But fencing in such a height
.Atojb to jump up out of his head to the League
If you jumped. But, perhaps you may fall in the swimming pool
! Come on, come
! I thought that you are not so weak
Huh? Of which invites them Baldaevh?
! I grabbed your
! Movement is so beautiful
! Strike made Kurigasa fall to the ground
! I've got your head League
! Kurigasa ineligible
! And now the results are uncertain again
.exactly
Fighting. We have reached a turning point is expected
Precisely for this reason
Not. You must loosen from your defense if even a second
!Damn
.Khtef League head and then return safely to the Persians was really wonderful
. Although I did not understand his squad
. Also that the teacher Nijo fainted by someone, and he is not qualified
It happened. We have at the moment
Na-not qualified?
! Do not care, just let me
!I can not breathe
Now. I have three against two
! It seems I am the only one who can Mjaratk
I was afraid. I have that this will happen
.Hassana, I deal with him, it's you
! Dr. Aki, cohesive
! Honor McCain-you to camping
! Arkli the back of that person is arrogant
! Teacher Akkaya
! We are in this to win
.I do not think so
.Taquero-Be, you should consider only
Why is it always?
!it is not fair
! It seems that one of the boys has impressed
! Do not worry about them
! We'll attack pincer
.Ooh? They have divided the boys
Do you attack will try pincher?
! Sheria has launched its movement towards them secret
! No one of the boys groups, attacked from both sides, are able to approach them
.Olknha has returned to the horses
. It's not only interested Balmanga
Are you okay, Takeru?
.G-often
The strength. We have an incredible, I thought that my bones have broken
.Ndjemat vocals these days are more stringent than the previous
!liar
! Now the girls have the opportunity to fight
From the moment which I arrived in Tenby
! It was fate decreed for me this battle inevitable
.Aki, so the cook Osamta illustrious
.good idea
! Display real fight shipping element in the air
! What a wonderful view of our graduates
! Akkaya
. We have reduced the Hracetk, Aki
... I was attracted to that side of you or
! Why do you talk on top of someone else's summit?
Chancellor suffered. We have faculty sad defeat, so also the teacher team likewise
! This means that Sheria is the only one that remained in the girls team
, While the boys team still have two teams in the battle
Sheria strength have shown earlier
You will be able to. Do you win the game or not
What is the side that will bring this glorious victory?
.Hiria, do not Ttrajaa, even if you Tqatlin Takeru
.I will not do
. If we are against this, we must expel our methods
!Yup! Like my thoughts exactly
! Even after they showed him the extent of my strength! Still did not give up
! Takeru-Be, you are very cool
What about me?
, Therefore,
.Somutir to win a place in your heart.
... This e-
Since when has been dropped to the swimming pool Sheria clothes?
.Khvd guard the tiger, make her skin alive
... This I, Usui Kengo
! Did not work
! Usui Out of Competition
! Service for the fans do not exist today
! Sheria has hidden inside a bikini swimming pool school clothes
No., this serves the fans so much
. I have done so intentionally
.Certainly
Now bendy. I have one set of each side
! This duel one against one will decide the battle
.Sokhrj all I have, Takeru-Be
All you have?
What will happen to me?
.Dimitora, your turn
.Knowledge
Huh? What is that?
.Dimitora, one of the carriers, the forces used water Almckin
!Yay
! E-Are you serious?
! Arise, be gone
...Is that
Minerva?
.You have reached
! I've got it
! He took her head Aoyama League
.I lost
! Team that remains is a group Aoyama
...This means
! Boys team is the winner
Why suddenly stopped, Dimitora?
. We have reached the last Edotna
does this mean...?
.Yup
Now we implement our mission advisors will
, To investigate the capabilities of technology students in Tenby
.Oachtaar goals
The first day of the separation of mixed swimming pool
! It is the day
.Eumana first to separate the mixed swimming pool
! Sweat, our spirit, and our intelligence has brought us a victory in the Battle of the Knights
! Finally, our hard work has paid off
! Let us go to heaven
!Yup
! Mixed swimming pool, now
What is that...?
, I can see that they are here
.Olkny I still can not see the girls themselves
. In fact, girls have sought me that is to Ohohin visuals with the help of my Almckin
!Did you do that?
. In fact, I will give some of the little fan service
Haruo-nee, where are you?
.Chksaa, I do not mind if you can see me
! Sheria took position in a swimming suit?
.Ohar sorry about them
!Did you do? Did you do?
No. We can allow peace Tenby to become threatened
! Hemegama-san
... emotional battle
The ninth
Storm ends the battle of the Knights of the swimming pool
! It was for nothing? ...
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
Vahdasnan
One Two Three
!one two Three
kakushitetatte ne mawari ni ha kitto bareteru
I try to hide it, but I'm sure that everyone knows this already
kitto
Sure
demo chikasugite mo ne kimochi nante ienai
Although we are very close relatives, I can not tell you what I feel
nante
...But
se no takasa itsu kara watashi yori chotto takakute
I've matured and become a little longer to me before I know it
chotto
Slightly
nanoni kodomo mitai na kao wo shite waraundane
However, you still have those childish smile
shite
Childish
me wo michau to yowai no
I feel weak when I look into your eyes
kizutte yo
Please, notice me
yappari kizukanaide my baby
You do not see me this way after all, oh baby
bi-bi-bi-bikkuri masuka ne
Are you surprised?
suki ni naru nante
I fell in love?
za-za-za-zaiza to nattara
.... If necessary
mamoru kedo kimi no haato madowasu kehai ga shitara
I will defend you, but your heart sends me mixed signals
mo ippo baby baby my day suki to tsugetai
Another step will say that I love you
Sure
...My heart
meki
unfailing
sukaato ni koi ni juudan kakushiteru
! I love Obi bullet under Tnorca
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
Preview of Hemegama
.I, Hemegama, best springs on swimming pools
. In fact, there is still another member of Alvenus
! Even if the number of crew members became larger, McCain-Ki! You will receive many of the characters
!What?! Do Sttalegan fire on members Regulars?
Next Episode Title
Girls of light and shadow
I will not be, right?