mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
lord-animetion
chiisai koto ni kuyo kuyo shite
, I used to worry about the small things
itsumo watashi tameratetta no
It was hesitant all the time
demo kimi ga oshietekureta fumidasu yuuki
.Olkink showed me how the courage to take the first step
isshoni hiroi suteeji he
, Together on the big circuit
tobikonde ikou
! To jump
donna chiisai negaigoto ga atte kanaete ageru
I will make even small your wish come true
mada shiranai sekai no hate demo
Being next to me made me feel
kimi to nara yukeru ki ga suru yo
I could go to the ends of the world unknown
hora gyutto te wo nigittara kowagarazu ni
See, to hold our hands tightly, do not be afraid
ichi ni san
! Three, two, one
Is
!Come on
donna toki demo shinjiteru
Whatever the case, I have confidence because I can see the future in front of my eyes
me no maeni mirai aru kara ne
hora gyutto te wo nigittara bouken ha hajimaru
See, to hold our hands tightly, the adventure will begin now
kitto
....Certainly
todoku Fly Away
.Snsal him, shaved away
Zero-Kon
. Here Amaya Haruko
.Ouyama Takeru really fool
.Ho not even soon to know the feelings of girls
The reason has been received. Therefore, a light Bhjar with Aanaho-chan since the
. I have realized that what he did wrong, has apologized
.Mounasph, we have a small cat named Monge live with us now
Seriously. Do not try, Dumitora
.Oaam our lives go the existence of God
.Sakon part of your life, no matter where you are
. This is my home
.Walba here my family
.Ln forget this never, no matter where I will go to him or with whom I
! Dvmytvra
.Dumitora certainly look nice today
...Mission
. If, I'll go
!everybody
! Thank you for the fans who remained loyal all the time
! Now to the last song for this evening! The blazing enthusiasm together
, The criminal, who robbed the wrong bank
It took the hostages now. You may now in confrontation with police
.Now, we will send negotiators to the inside
It seems that I will not be the last option
! I'll take one of you as a shield and then will run away
What ninety him, sister?
They gave me five seconds, okay?
! Your hands up and to Look
.Asvh to make you waiting for
! I want to visit Akihabara in Tokyo as soon as possible
.Afattaat Japanese certainly Cute
. I wish to be many of them from the two types
.Ost Special Administrative Region, BF-201 We are at a point
We also received .okadd downs allowed in Tenby Academy
... I repeat, here
.Aloda here is fine
.Thanks
.Sobr Commander of Bonkma were you wonderful
... Please Wait, you can not
Was adopted. Both of you, Aerrero, Rero
!it has finished
! I have finally ended
! Takyrv
!where are you?
This bell-e.
.poor fellow
.Ooh, Vice-Chairperson
Have you seen Takeru?
where is he?
.Aadh be behind you
... A-Excuse
... huh? This e-
! I interpret it
To Takeru? What happened
. In fact, it has happened since ten minutes and ten seconds.
. We have found two girls in the yard, which were about to jump on each other
!You are! Because you nauseous
The reason jumped Aoyama. Therefore, Takeru to separate them
...and then
... as Turkey, you are not allowed to as b
!What do you do?
!Foolish
! O deviant
... I've just ... Please
. At the time of the arrival of Amaya-Seenba, the matter has ended
I understand. I have, I feel your pain, sir
You, not still alive?
A.-order
.Asv because it took me a long time, but I have something interesting
McCain. This is your
This is my Almckin?
Sorry. I, Takeru
!We'll talk later
I wonder what's speeches Goin-san?
.who knows
.Hassana, display time has come
! Venus
! Everyone, Osran
Seems like a big box here
.Aml that we meet with people Mslin to spend time
...what if
A long time ago. I have, Minori
I grew up. I have to be extra beautiful
I grew older. Whenever, the more it becomes more radiant
... so that I barely Omahh naked eye
Why are you here, Akkaya
Exchange of students?
.Ogel, you'll receive a message from Kamigarri about this must
.Hardh the mind as in the past
. In fact, in other words, girls here are the students who talked about them surrogate
.Amaa, they Ckln Venus
I understand it. I have
But what I want to know is why you are not here?
Simply put, Kamigarri suspect someone is in this academy
.Ihol open the seal head of the eight snakes forces
.But, the head of the eight snakes just a fairy tale
. What, I have made me think about it even a little
,However
.Kamigarri convinced otherwise
There is an organization using Almckin elements
.Da'm this country from the shadows
But the real roots
.Altarej back
.Balaudh to the era when the gods created this world already
.Oolik who opposed their rule have formed an army
The army. This was called Kamigarri
, It is true that this specialty Tenby
.Gers elements with sparkling Omanohara, has seen an extraordinary increase in power over the past two years
.Icolon that monster gods sleep in Tenby
.Oiatkaddon the fact that someone will break the seal
. If I realized that these facts true, you can not ignore this issue
.Or something like
For this reason they have for submitting search for the culprit?
! I was
! Akkaya
!damn you! what are you doing here?
! Tommy-chan and Aki
! Fifth wheel again
A long time ago. I have
.Ajlh fifth? O despicable
.Ooh, not insults, please
.Bdoua of the day, I will be a temporary milestone in Tenby
.Ottalaa to work with you, McCain Smith
What?
! You, Slow down, Akkaya
,for one time
! We were all part of the McCain-Ki
Cano has once in the McCain-Ki?
.Aa her beautiful lady
.nice to meet you
.I part of Venus
.Olabd current President of the McCain-Ki
! A-order
! It is a very sophisticated
Do you prefer to accompany us to the Disciplinary Committee?
!I'd like it
.Thank you
. From here, prefer
! Hello, my beautiful boy
Are you also a member of the McCain-Ki?
.nice to meet you
.Yup
.Asmh is Kodai Akkaya
We were all members. We have McCain-Ki
,Finally
! Girls from Alvenus will join the McCain-Ki in the summer
.Nakdm all of ourselves
!Yup
Twins. We
.Orero Vinaan
Calendar Rero Vinaan
.Hatin girls Hlutin like honey
.Oh really
.I Media Dumitora
We .ln be here for a long time, but I hope that we work together
! I hope so too! In order to acquire homosexuality sexual Islam
No. I think it is the appropriate way to express, no matter what
.مرحبًا، أنا شيريا أوتسكا
!سررت بلقائكم
.يبدو أنه تمت إضافة صدور ثقيلة العديمة الفائدة
.شيريا تبدو مألوفة
.أظن أن لا حاجة لتقديم نفسي
.نحن فقط ننظر إلى أولئك الذين لديهم القوة الكافية لكونهم أصدقائنا
.ليس لديّ أية نية للتآخي [ تصبح أختًا ] مع الضعفاء
!كيف بإمكانكِ قول هذا؟
.في الحقيقة، أنا أوافقها
.على الرغم من أن هذا تصرف غير مهذب
.ديميتورا! لقد أصبحتِ أيضًا غير مهذبة
.لنكون واضحات
.نحن في فينوس قاتلنا كثيرًا في المعارك الخطرة
.لذا بإمكاننا إكمال مهامنا
.نحن فخورات جدًا بشأن هذا
.بالتأكيد
،طالما أنكِ تحدّين نفسكِ لساحة لعب المدرسة هذه
.لن تكونوا قادرين على فهم ما تعنيه المعارك
ما الذي تعنيه المعارك حقًا؟
!ما هذه السخرية
.إنهن تعتقدن بوضوح بأنهن أفضل منا
.لا يمكنني السماح لهن بإهانتنا من دون رد الدين
!أ-أزوكي-سان
.يظنون بأنهن جنود [ النخبة ] اللاتي سافرن حول العالم
.أنتِ تتحدثين بتكبّر، إذا كنتِ حقًا بهذه القوة، ينبغي عليكِ أن تكوني قادرة على هزيمتنا بسهولة
.Hnalk saying in Japan say that the barking dog has no bite
. You remarkably like a bitch at the moment
!What?
. I say that Tenby is a playground for children Mhaksin
! A-O damned
If this is what you think about it, why we can not settle this dueling?
. Also Taatmnin
Seems we got ourselves the idea of ​​[access competitor] quickly
... In the end, these two girls Sthzia friendship taboo
!not at all
. But, we do not allow Balambarzac between members of the so-Almckin
This means that the best way that Thzia these two girls to fight fair
! Is a sports competition
LORD ANIMATION: translation
shx: production
.Walan, I will explain the rules of this game
. It's like volleyball game three against three
.Alvriv first who gets 15 points wins
, You should be linked to both teams at the arrival point 14
.Alvriv the first to win two points wins
.Ltjunb this, we gave him the club activity
The reason will be the referee. For this club counselor, doctor Nijo
I did. I did not rule at all
Why three against three?
We have enough members of the team, right?
. This is true for McCain-Ki, but Venus have only five members
. If you are scared too much, you will not object to if you play six people in your team
! Enough, stop it, Yan
.Hiria, we've got to this point by pushing down our borders
... even if it's just a game
!Come on! Come on
! McCain-Ki
!Come on! Come on! McCain-Ki
When they changed their clothes off?
! Hemegama-Seenba, Abzli effort
! Cheers for the defeat, is not it?
. I think you are right
! To start the game
! Ball, McCain-Ki
.Lnzar them
... to show them
! Our real
We are not Villains
! So you can defeat us this blind force
! Haruko
... the ball
Do you paste the component when the ball beat her?
Haruko! Are you fine?
, I do not agree to this battle
, But as head of the Disciplinary Committee
! I can not accept defeat
.Ooh? The strongest in Tenby has excited
Maybe it may be a great turning point for this battle
! Haruko-Seenba, keep this high spirit
! Haruo-chan, Killers
.فقط راقب، أيها الولد الجميل
!إرسال
.إنه تعادل
.الفريق الأول الذي يحرز النقطتان يفوز
!إرسال الكرة، فينوس
!استمعن
!لقد وصلنا إلى هذا الحد! لن أسمح بالفشل
!هيا! هيا! ماكين-كي
!هيا! هيا! تينبي
!هاروكو-سينباي! أنا أؤمن بكِ
!هيميغامي-سينباي، أنا لكِ إلى الأبد
أجل، ولكن ماذا سيحدث إذا خسرنا؟
.إذا خسر فينوس، فسوف تنضمون لماكين-كي
،وإذا خسر ماكين-كي
.فسوف نقوم بإيقاف جميع أنشطة النادي لمدة شهر كامل
.هذا جيد
.من الأفضل لكنّ جميعًا بأن تكنّ مرتفعات طالما أننا هنا
.أتساءل هل ستكنّ بخير
.إذا خسرنا، سوف نقوم بإيقاف جميع أنشطة النادي لمدة شهر كامل
.ولكن يبدو في رأيي أننا نقوم بعمل جيد
.يبدو هكذا
هل لاحظتنّ هذا؟
.أعينهن برّاقة
!أجل، إنهن كذلك حقًا
لمساواة بقوى الآخرين وبمستوى المهارة
...والشعور بالسعادة للقتال ضد الآخرين
.إنها المرة الأولى لفتيات فينوس
،إنها التجربة التي تحتجنّ إليهن
.لديّ شكوكي، ولكنكِ قوية بشكل لا يُصدق
،ومع ذلك
!نحن سوف نفوز
(B) seriously?
!Curse
! I've Bagdhaba, O damned
.Aa you mood
! If they sign up again, you'll end up ordered
.Hmm, it seems that we are in a little problem
How can you to be cool all the time?
Thus I was born. We have
.Hiria, this is the last point
Get it for us
.Dimitora
... I do not want extremism to things, but
! But I hate the loss also
! Sorry
!No way
! This cute, Haruko
! Chacha! Adharbhe by your compressor
! I got it, here we are
.No way
Very .gaamadh
.Such magic
.Ontn are fighting messily
! Shut up
! You began this
what is happening?
.For least, certainly they do not are playing volleyball anymore
Why did you come with these girls from the clouds?
Explain the details of advisors will later
.Currently, let's see these girls even win Tqmn
.Dimitora
Is serious. It's
M-What?
.eye for an eye
M-What should we do?
.Aa God, exactly as I expected
! Dimitora! Do not go further than that
It continued. If so, it can not be stopped
! What a formidable force
! Controls Banasrha completely easily
! I will bring biscuits tomorrow
!I love her
Are you blind were hit?
, If Qmtn take the battle to the limit
! If, you will take care of myself Bomrkin
! Good, Arise, be gone, Haruko
! It's public battle
! Azari them, O Rep.
Haruo-Ne ... Allen Tbarzha seriously, is not it?
! Harrow-nee! Ahtrsy
Harrow-nee?
! Beautiful boy
! I have used your body as a shield to protect me
... In fact, Excuse me, I
! You Persian Shining
.Orad already thank you
Orgena our defense. We have a little
. Thank you to protect our friend
If, from the winner now?
No. I could be happy if you do not know
. But as far as the importance of the game, we are in the gray area
... But if ye Taathdtn about the forces of McCain-Key Venus
.Enbga be settled this matter
.Yup
.Okther of K
!everybody
Are you in Modekm?
. If, at the time the image capture has come
! Valan, abtsmva
! I've just remembered
... Sheria is Oottska
Divine decline in Tenby
The seventh
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
Vahdasnan
One Two Three
!one two Three
kakushitetatte ne mawari ni ha kitto bareteru
I try to hide it, but I'm sure that everyone knows this already
kitto
Sure
demo chikasugite mo ne kimochi nante ienai
Although we are very close relatives, I can not tell you what I feel
nante
...But
se no takasa itsu kara watashi yori chotto takakute
I've matured and become a little longer to me before I know it
chotto
Slightly
nanoni kodomo mitai na kao wo shite waraundane
However, you still have those childish smile
shite
Childish
me wo michau to yowai no
I feel weak when I look into your eyes
kizutte yo
Please, notice me
yappari kizukanaide my baby
You do not see me this way after all, oh baby
bi-bi-bi-bikkuri masuka ne
Are you surprised?
suki ni naru nante
I fell in love?
za-za-za-zaiza to nattara
.... If necessary
mamoru kedo kimi no haato madowasu kehai ga shitara
I will defend you, but your heart sends me mixed signals
mo ippo baby baby my day suki to tsugetai
Another step will say that I love you
Sure
...My heart
meki
unfailing
sukaato ni koi ni juudan kakushiteru
! I love Obi bullet under Tnorca
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
sunao ni itai no yo
I want to tell you what I feel
sukiyotte itai no yo
[I want to tell [I love you
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One
the unit
One Two
One, two
One Two Three
!one two Three
Preview of Hemegama
I am. It's, Cairo Hemegama
. Even among the new recruits, there is one interested in this stupid boy
... First Haruko, and then Aanaho
.Hiria will do its best for you
Next Episode
Just what you love Him in that silly, the owner of medical glasses?