Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
I want to go back to that time again.
I want to be small again. Minami-kun.
Where are you, Chiyomi?
Over here, Minami-kun!
In Tokyo?
What are you thinking?
So, I told you yesterday. The dance workshop.
Please, I really want to do it.
So, please let me stay with you.
On that day, you fainted at the sound of thunder. Then, you woke up finding yourself small. Correct?
I see! If I do the same thing here again...
So, it's impossible after all.
Are you okay?
I'm a fool after all. I caught a cold.
Hello.
Nomura-san...
Dad, Mom, Asuka, how are you doing?
I am doing fine here... in T-Tokyo...
That's not good. They will know you're lying right away.
I'm so nervous...
Okay then, I'm shooting one more time.
Dad, Mom, Asuka, how are you doing?
I am doing fine in Tokyo.
I know you are worried about me, but I'm fine. I'll send you another video some time.
Good. It went okay.
Nothing strange is captured.
It's been almost a week since my body became strange like this.
There is no sign of me getting back to normal.
Oh right. They won't know it is from Minami-kun even if you send it from there, right?
Right. I got a free email address that is different from mine.
I had stopped talking to Minami-kun before I knew it although I used to love him when we were kids.
I thought we would be like this forever.
Okay then, why don't you input your dad's address?
But, it was Minami-kun who found me when I had become like this.
h... a... n... a...
It's more difficult than I expected.
do... ro... bo...
ne.jp... Send!
Okay.
I can't show what I look like now to my family or friends.
So, I am living together with Minami-kun, which is quite fascinating.
Minami Kun No Koibito
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito
♫ I am not good at talking in similitudes ♫
♫ So I can't do a good job telling a tale ♫
♫ But, I will tell you an amazing story ♫
♫ of you and I ♫
♫ It is not a small story that will fit in a pocket ♫
♫ God played a trick ♫
♫ And a dramatic time began ♫
♫ The shape of happiness you and I imagined ♫
♫ doesn't have a name ♫
♫ But if it is a world I create with you, it's okay ♫
♫ I will write words that won't be erased like a magic ♫
♫ and turn the page ♫
♫ It is like a sequel to a fairy tale ♫
♫ We can smile forever ♫
♫ To a place over the rainbow ♫
♫ I can go, as long as I am with you ♫
♫ Let's imagine ♫
♫ a story with a happy ending ♫
~Episode 4~ [Do your best, Minami-kun]Dad, Mom, Asuka, how are you?
It's Chiyomi. Honey, it's Chiyomi.
We are not fine. How could we be?
Because of Chiyomi, we are worn out and look older.
Be quiet, honey.
I know you are worried about me, but I am fine.
I will send you another video some time.
What? That's all?
Hah~?
What's this uncool dress? Did she have these kinds of clothes?
She hasn't said anything we want to know.
Well, you are right, but aren't we happy just to see that she's doing okay?
It's so frustrating.
That's so unfashionable. Look at that ribbon.
Why doesn't she just call us instead of doing annoying thing like this?
Well, maybe she can't call us because she is scared of you two.
- What are you saying? You are the one who hit her.- Huh?
It's domestic violence, Dad.
Hey, you are mistaken. That's not it.
Right? Right? That's not it, right?
Hello, this is Horikiri residence. Chiyomi?!
- You know what...- Eh? Chiyomi? Hey, hey.
Hey, Chiyomi? It's you?
Y... Yeah. It's me. Did you see the video?
We watched it now. What have you been doing?
Well, the workshop...
How long is the workshop? Isn't it too long?
Well, it's kind of getting longer.
The organizer has an artistic temperament, you know...
- Artistic temperament... Gosh.- Hey, give it to me.
Hello, Chiyomi. What happened to your cellphone?
It broke.
- It broke? Get a new one.- I don't have money.
I will send you money. Where should I send it? Where are you?
Well... I want to focus on the dance,
so I won't have it fixed and will endure loneliness.
Why are you talking like a trainee monk?
Anyway, please trust me. This is a pay phone. Oh, I'll be running out of 10 yen coins.
Hey, Chiyomi?
It's going to run out.
Chiyomi, hey. Chiyomi?
How can you tell a lie like that?
I know.
But, I can't possibly tell them the truth.
I can't let them see how I am now.
You are enduring loneliness...
What?
You idiot, Minami-kun.
Idiot? Hey.
I'm still weak after getting sick. Don't vent your anger on me.
I didn't vent my anger...
Right. He was sick in bed with fever yesterday.
No. Stop it!
Minami-kun.
Minami-kun!
Chiyomi...
You are causing me such trouble. Idiot.
Minami-kun?
Idiot!
Eh? He is talking in his sleep?
What's with you?
So, Horikiri-san is the only one absent.
You have to prepare for the college entrance exam. Take care of your health, okay?
Excuse me, Sensei.
Yes, Nomura-san?
Has Horikiri-san contacted you?
Her parents called me and said that she is still in Tokyo.
It's cold.
- May I have another one?- Sure.
Amippe, why don't you eat this?
Ouch.
What? What's the matter, Riku?
Ah, I think I heard Horikiri-shi's voice.
Don't touch it!
Sorry.
What's the matter, Minami?
What's the matter with Minami?
- He didn't have to get so mad.- Scary.
Ouch...
Are you okay?
I think I am. It hurts.
Minami-kun.
Minami!
Oh. I finally found you.
Give me a break. Why do I have to do that?
So, I'm not asking you to come back to the kendo club. Just participate in one match.
That's not right. I have quit the kendo club already, you know.
Takatori got injured. Without him, we won't have enough people to participate in the competition.
Then, you don't have to participate in it.
Come on. We are fighting against Awa-Higashi High School.
Every year, freshmen join our club after watching the matches.
Just give up. I can't do it.
I'm begging you. If no freshmen joined us this year, the kendo club would be abolished.
Abolished?
The kendo club with a long history at Tateyama Daiichi High School would dissapper.
And, Awa-Higashi got a transfer student who finished 5th in the national competition last year.
5th in the national competition?
We can't beat him, but you might be able to win.
Even if you don't, you might have a good match with him.
I am begging you, Minami!
I am sorry. Ask someone else.
If there was someone else, I wouldn't be asking you.
I made up my mind to enter a med school right after graduation. I won't have time to participate in it.
Hey, Minami. Please! We are best friends, aren't we?
I will call you later. I'll be waiting for you.
My Little Lover: Minami Kun No Koibito
Here you go.
What's wrong? You'd normally gobble it up.
Well...
You know...
Huh?
Every morning, you wake up early and go for a run. Then you practice swings, don't you?
That's to build up my stamina. I won't be able to survive the college entrance exams without it.
Why don't you participate in the match?
You heard me there...
Yabuki-kun is your best friend, isn't he?
He is not. He is just saying it himself.
I don't think you would fail the exam just by participating in the match for just one day.
I know you want to do kendo.
You are itching to do it!
Huh? What are you saying?
Are you scared, by any chance?
Scared?
You just don't want to find yourself being defeated by the opponent.
Shut up.
It's okay to be defeated. You haven't practiced kendo for a while.
It won't be uncool even if you were defeated because you have done your best on what you like.
I said, shut up!
The Minami-kun I love...
is not such a coward!
Umm... I didn't mean it...
Don't talk big.
I am sorry.
You can't do anything without me.
Minami-kun.
I was looking for you.
Nomura-san.
You often eat alone on the rooftop, don't you?
Umm... because it feels nice.
Then, I will eat with you here from now on.
Eh? Ah...
Hmm?
I won't be able to eat if you do that.
Ah, no.
Eh? Why?
By any chance, do you have someone else in mind?
Ah, no. That's not the case, but...
- Horikiri-san.- Eh?
Did Horikiri-san really go to Tokyo?
Why are you asking me such a question?
I was just saying. Hey...
Can I see you after school today?
Minami-kun...
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
What's this? If they want to study, they can go to the library.
Why at a cafe? It's like a date.
You don't have to answer it? It's been ringing several times.
Ah... It's okay.
Minami-kun. I don't understand this.
Where?
Eh?
Oh, Minami-kun.
Nomura?
You were hungry.
Ah, no...
To hide it, you had a fake cough like that.
Do you want to eat something?
They have sandwiches.
Yeah.
Your father disappeared, right?
Why does she have to ask such a thing?
That is a taboo question to ask Minami-kun.
He didn't disappear...
He got a lover and left us. I don't consider him as my dad.
Eh? Why are you telling that to her with no hesitation?
I'm the same. The one who gave birth to me left us, too.
I don't consider her my mom.
What's this atmosphere? It seems as if they understand each other without words.
Well then.
Yeah. See you tomorrow.
Yup.
Minami-kun.
Oh, you've never kissed before?
Minami-kun...
May I reserve here as well?
R... Reserve?
I hate it! It is so loud.
See you.
My Little Lover: Minami Kun No Koibito
You idiot, Minami! How can you not know how I feel?
Your father disappeared, right?
He didn't disappear...
He got a lover and left us. I don't consider him as my dad.
- Men! (a kendo term)- Good!
- Men!- Good!
- Good!- Men!
- More!- Men!
That's right.
- Good.- Men!
Men!
Here you go.
Hey, Minami-kun.
What?
Your dad influenced you to start kendo, right?
What are you saying, all of a sudden?
Even now, you practice swings every day even though you quit kendo for the college entrance exam.
Is it because you want to somehow stay connected with your dad who left you?
You idiot!
You used to love your dad, and you might still...
Cut it out!
I have forgotten about him already. I don't even think about him.
That's a lie.
Because you have changed so much since then.
Of course! My dad deserted and left my mom and grandma.
I had to protect those two who got abandoned. I had to change!
What are you saying?
Minami-kun...
You couldn't possibly understand it.
I don't understand.
I don't, but...
I have always wanted to be of help to you.
Help? I don't need it.
I will be a doctor no matter what and give my mom and grandma a comfortable life.
I don't need help from anyone.
Minami-kun...
So, I don't have time to spend on club activities or a superficial friendship.
That is...
the real reason why you won't participate in the match, huh?
- You were up?- I couldn't sleep for some reason.
You've been studying till this late?
Well... I couldn't sleep, either.
Can I ask you a question?
What?
Mom,
you don't have a grudge against him?
Him?
That guy... who is my father.
Noboru-chan?
No grudge?
Hmm. I wonder. I think there was a time I did.
I'm asking you seriously.
I'm sorry. Well...
Every day I have lived with all my might.
So, I had no time to have a grudge or anything.
You had no time?
Right. Of course I have had a hard time after he left me,
but I wouldn't have met you if I hadn't gotten married to Noboru-chan.
I wouldn't be living with your grandma like this, either.
So, that evens things up, you know.
That evens thing up?
That's because...
I have a cute son like this,
and I am happy now.
You are my most beloved son.
You should loosen up more.
Hey, you stink. Come on!
Young man, grow quickly and become 20.
Mom, you are drunk.
What's this ruckus?
I'm sorry, Grandma. Mom is drunk.
Oh, my. You got drunk with such little alcohol? Shame on you.
Eh?
Well, I guess I have to drink with you.
Grandma!
Mom!
- You are drunk.- Okay, okay.
Thank you.
Pour me more.
Okay, let me offer you a drink now.
Thank you.
Okay.
Cheers!
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
Minami! Fight!
Do your best!
He had stubbornly insisted on not participating in the matches,
but he said he would do it, for some reason.
Do your best! Do your best! Do your best!
- Do your best! Do your best! - Men! Men!
Do your best!
Tateyama No.1 High School vs. Awa-Higashi High School
Awa-Higashi High School is really strong this year, unlike last year.
I am so sorry.
We all lost.
That's Izumi.
He sure is strong, having made the 5th in the national competition.
Even Minami is no match for him.
Well, in any case,
'senpo,' 'jiho,' 'chuken' and 'fukusho' all lost,(kendo terms that describe an order of team members to fight)
we are losing, that's for sure.
Takatori, it's not your place to say that.
But, even if Minami wins, we are losing by 4:1.
At this rate, there will be no freshmen joining us.
Our club will be abolished, huh...
What's with you guys? Instead of saying such rubbish, cheer on Minami-kun.
Go for it! Go for it!
Minami-kun! Watch out!
Oh, I want to cheer him on in a loud voice.
Minami-kun, do your best!
Minami-kun, go for it!
Go for it, Minami-kun.
Minami senpai, fight!
Minami-kun, go for it!
Minami senpai!
Go for it!
Never give up!
Tsuki~!(kendo term)
Tsuki ari! (awarding of the tsuki point)
You did it!
He won! Yes!
Minami-kun.
Nihon-me.(second round)
Minami almost won. Too bad.
After getting a point, he was doing a great job.
That izumi... he was so strong. We can't beat him.
I am glad I got injured.
Ouch. I was just joking.
Oh? Where's Minami?
Damn...
Minami-kun.
My Little Lover: Minami Kun No Koibito
[Author: Moon Bunny MichaelaBlue Fairy - Episode11]
It's still not updated.
["Chobiko in the pocket" New]
Eh?
[Author: Moon Bunny Michaela Title: Chobiko in the pocket]The memory in the womb... If it really exists,
maybe it is like this.
The place is dark, but
it is warm, and you can always hear the sound of the beloved one's heart beat.
You realize that you have been surrounded, protected and nurtured
by its absolute tenderness.
That's the very first memory of happiness.
Horikiri-shi.
It's her new work.
Chiyomi?
Eh? Is this Chiyomi?
RIght. It's Horikiri-shi. Does it look like her?
Eh? What's this? Chiyomi?
Eh? You made it, Riku?
Yeah. I haven't slept a wink making this.
Hey, let me see it.
Cool. It does look like her quite a bit.
Riku, I didn't know you had a special skill like this.
It's not that I have a special skill. It was my first time to make a figurine.
First time? Why?
Right. Why did you make something like this?
Well, I just thought I would like to
put something like this here.
Chiyomi in your pocket?
This is bad. Takagi is getting pervy. That's far out.
- What? You like Chiyomi?- Do you, Riku-kun?
Yeah. I love Horikiri-shi.
Whoa! Seriously?
That's bad. It's weird.
Horikiri-shi also knows my feelings for her.
Oh, really?
- Wow. Can you say such a thing in the classroom?- I couldn't.
He is a perv, though.
Minami-kun. He should have woken me up.
I'm home.
[Drying a plastic modelDO NOT ENTER!!(I'll clean the room myself)]
Hey, why did you go to school without me?
What are you saying? You didn't wake up even though I tried.
- Oh, did you get Monthly Dance Times?- Huh?
Eh? I sent you an email, asking you to buy one for me.
- Email?- Right.
I sent it to the address you used to send the video. You didn't notice it?
Ah... Sorry, it ran out of battery.
Eh~!
I guess I have no choice.
Let's go.
You just came home though.
Monthly Dance... What was it?
- You want it, right?- Yeah.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
♫ A casual encounter ♫
♫ gave me this great beginning ♫
♫ Everyday I was with you ♫
♫ I was slowly loving you, more and more ♫
♫ When we walk shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ It is like the moon in the sky ♫
♫ You are right here but even if I stretched my arm ♫
♫ I won't be able to reach you ♫
♫ I simply love you ♫♫ You are always in my heart ♫
♫ It almost hurts me ♫♫ Forever ♫
♫ I just want to be honest and ♫♫ tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Forever and ever ♫♫ Please ♫
♫ Be with me ♫
♫ I wish our days last ♫
♫ Forever ♫
~Preview~Recently, a lot of burglaries have been reported around here.
No way. Is he a burgler?
What should I do?
I have to let Minami-kun know.
That's it.
Hah? Who the hell are you?
Don't kid me, you brat!
What should I do? Minami-kun.
Chiyomi!