Timing and Subtitles brought to you byThe Little Lover Team@Viki.
Moon Bunny Michaela!
Ah... Shhhh.
You are famous now in the on-line novel world.[User Name: Moon Bunny Michaela]
I love... Moon Bunny Michaela.
I love... Horikiri Chiyomi.
I've liked Minami-kun...
all this time.
I'm not going to take the entrance exam. I know exactly what I want to do.
You are so spoiled and easy going.
I want to get back to that time again.
I want to be little again.
Minami-kun...
Why?
I became the One-Inch-Princess?
No way...
Can't be!
Stay away!
Don't come this way!
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito
♫ I am not good at talking in similitudes ♫
♫ So I can't do a good job telling a tale ♫
♫ But, I will tell you an amazing story ♫
♫ of you and I ♫
♫ It is not a small story ♫
♫ that will fit in a pocket ♫
♫ God played a trick ♫
♫ And a dramatic time began ♫
♫ The shape of happiness you and I imagined ♫
♫ doesn't have a name ♫
♫ But if it is a world I create with you, it's okay ♫
♫ I will write words that won't be erased like a magic ♫
♫ and turn the page ♫
♫ It is like a sequel to the fairy tale ♫ ♫ We can smile forever ♫
♫ To a place over the rainbow ♫
♫ I can go, as long as I am with you ♫
♫ Let's imagine ♫
♫ a story with a happy ending ♫
Stay away! Don't come any closer!
Go away!
Come. Don't go off the road.
Come now. Let's go.
Run!
~Episode 2: Living Together~What do I do?
What should I do?
Please find her.
I am counting on you, Sakaizawa-chan.
Well, Chiyomi-chan is adolescent. You'd better not make too much of a fuss.
I will keep this a secret myself.
- Thank you.  - It's fine.
Shunichi. Oh!
Our next-door neighbor Chiyomi-chan disappeared.
Disappeared?
She hasn't come home since she went out last night.
I heard that from a police officer outside.
Why do you say such a thing? You're so mean.
We used to be so close.
I don't like you anymore.
She doesn't pick up her cellphone either.
Last night, the police officer saw Chiyomi-chan around Misaki Park.
It was so stormy, you know.
I am worried.
- Shunichi?- I'm going out for a run.
Chiyomi...
Chiyomi? Chiyomi!
Chiyomi! Chiyomi! Chiyomi!
Minami-kun!
Chiyomi?
Chiyomi? Where are you, Chiyomi?
Here, I'm here! Minami-kun!
Over here!
Minami-kun!
Chiyomi...
It's not a dream!
It's me, Chiyomi!
Minami-kun!
Minami-kun...
Chiyomi...
You are up early, as always.
- Good morning. - Hi.
Hey, hey. Have you heard about Chiyomi-chan?
Yes... I heard a bit about it from Mom.
Right. She ran away from home.
Chiyomi-chan seems to have suffered from domestic violence.
It's between you and me, but
I think she eloped with her boyfriend.
What?
I see.
Don't tell anyone.
Chiyomi-chan is an adolescent after all.
It'll be a problem if a bad rumor spreads.
See you later.
Elope?
Things are getting serious.
Domestic violence is bad.
No, it's not DV --
Well, you have to teach her a lesson when necessary.
But, she hasn't come home since last night.
Hey, I told you not to make a ruckus.
Gosh, people in this town are loose lipped.
When I think about it, it is your fault, Sakaizawa-chan...
What am I going to do?
What else can we do?
We have no choice but to explain what happend.
Wait, wait, Minami-kun!
What is it?
I can't go back like this!
Eat it when you get hungry.
Thanks!
Listen. Don't touch my stuff unnecessarily.
Also, don't ever let my mom and grandma see you.
My grandma's always at home.
I understand!
Um...
What is it? What's wrong?
I don't need this flower pot since the plant is dead.
What?
Shunichi, come eat your breakfast!
I'm coming now.
That was close!
Ohno-sensei.
What is it?
Well, what happened to Horikiri-san?
I got a call from Chiyomi's mom last night. I am so worried.
Right, you are good friends of Horikiri-san.
She doesn't really have a cold, does she?
There's no need for you to worry.
But, I know you can't help it.
The school talked with her parents and decided not to make a big deal out of this.
Ohno sensei. Ohno sensei!
Sasaki sensei.
I heard about it. Horikiri in your class
has disappeared, right?
Disappeared? Horikiri?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byThe Little Lover Team @Viki
So, this is Minami-kun's room, huh.
He is so perfect at school, but
he can't organize his room.
He still plays
with Kendama.
He is so funny.
Maybe not.
There is no telling how long it has been here.
He surely is a good student. His notebook is so organized.
What?
This is...
me?
One, two. One, two.
My goodness. This sure is a boy's room.
So, his grandma cleans his room.
He shouldn't have left this out here.
Alright!
Really...
He left a window open.
Okay.
Okay, it's done.
It's cold!
Oh, it's cold! It's so cold!
I wonder what Chiyomi is doing now.
I wonder if she's eating properly.
Can I sit here?
Yeah.
As I thought, those two...
Nomura-san is aggressive.
Hey, Minami! Is Minami here?
Let's eat lunch together.
Why don't you eat in your classroom?
What are you saying? I came because I'm concerned about you.
If I didn't come, you would be eating lunch alone again...
Hello.
Waaah! Pheromone!
What is it? You're noisy.
When did you start dating Nomura-san. You didn't even tell me.
We just work as class reps together.
Class reps.
Ah, I see.
Well,
you came here to tell me to go back to Kendo Club, right?
It's not that.
I'm not going back. It was my plan to quit the club at the end of winter in 11th grade.
Huh? You are so heartless.
Oh, by the way, I heard from Sasaki...
Sasaki?
You forgot already? He is the supervisor for Kendo Club.
Ah. That big guy with a big mouth.
And, he told me that your neighbor has disappeared.
It seems you didin't like her, but I have thought she was pretty nice.
Ah, of course you are also pretty, Nomura-san.
Thank you very much.
Huh. I see.
She acts pure, but there is no telling what she has been doing behind the scenes.
Pheromone...!!
What's the matter, Minami?
All of a sudden,
a person becomes small...
- Do you think that's possible?- What?
What are you talking about?
Ah, no...
What? Minami-kun?
Sorry, Nomura. Tell sensei that I am going home early.
Going home early? You don't feel well?
Right... I don't feel well.
Oh, hey.
Welcome home.
I'm home.
Why...
is he in such a hurry?
Chiyomi!
Chiyomi?
Grandma, did you clean my room?
I did.
Minami-kun! Minami-kun!
Minami-kun! Here!
I'm right here!
I'm saved!
Thanks!
What's going on?
No, it's nothing.
Okay.
I was feeling helpless.
Thank you very much for coming back.
You know, people are making a big deal out of your disappearance at school.
What? Really?
Oh, right. Minami-kun, people in this town are forming a search party.
Search party?
I left my clothes and shoes over there, right?
It's going to be a problem if they find them.
They might think this is an abduction, rape and murder case.
Abuduction, rape and murder case? Gosh.
Chiyomi-chan!
Well, I hope we won't find her here.
If she just ran away from home, she wouldn't come to this kind of place.
Chiyomi-chan!
- Chiyomi-chan!- Chiyomi-chan!
Chiyomi-chan.
What am I doing here?
Oh.
How dare she made me do this kind of thing.
Oh? Minami-kun, what are you doing at this hour? What about school?
Ah, ah...
I have an upset stomach.
Ah, I see.
Chiyomi-chan hasn't come home yet. Did anything unusual happen at school?
No...
Not really.
What's that? Did you go shopping?
I got some medicine for my stomach
to stockpile it.
Ah, it hurts... Sorry, excuse me.
Hm...
He was definitely suspicious of me.
You are okay. That officer can be a bit dumb.
Why don't you go home?
Why aren't you going home?
Because...
Not sure about Dad, but Mom will...
You saw One-Inch-Princess?
Yeah, the One-Inch-Princess.
What are you saying? Of course that isn't true.
But she was really there. At the river, with Minami-kun...
Stop it. I'm busy.
No way.
It's OK, parents are like that.
Parents are...
Parents are not like that!
They will be in such a shock. I'm sure they will worry a lot.
Then what are you expecting me to do?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
At least let them know that you are safe.
Withhold the number...
Here.
I don't know what to say.
Shunichi, Shunichi!
What's wrong?
They found items they think are Chiyomi-chan's at Misaki Park.
I asked her to go buy some soy sauce for me in that rain...
It's not your fault.
If I didn't say that.
Don't cry. It's not like anything happened.
Ri-chan...
Mi-chan, Oba-chan...
Ri-chan, we heard.
Sorry for causing so much trouble.
Emiko-san, thank you... Thank you.
Really...
Takagi... Mikimoto...
Minami...
We were worried about Chiyomi
so I went to Misaki Park with Riku.
This is the soy sauce that Chiyomi bought last...
the fingerprints...-Ami-ppe. (Her Nickname)
Everyone, don't get too depressed.
We don't know anything yet.
But, now, we can't handle it on our own.
There is a possibility someone abducted her.
Actually, I think so, too.
After looking for her in a frenzy all day,
there is one thing I was concerned about.
There is one person that is really suspicious
in here.
A suspicious person...
that is...
a suspicious person... a suspicious person...
a suspicious person...
That is...
You!
Huh?
Huh? Me?
No... why?
I've been worried about Horikiri-shi since yesterday...
worried about Chiyomi-san, so I went looking for her with Ami-ppe.
So, you let it slip.
You've been worried since yesterday?
The only people who knew Chiyomi-chan went missing yesterday were the family members and
just me.
Ah, I called Ami-chan yesterday...
Yes, Oba-san called me to ask if Choyomi was with me.
And then I called Riku immediately.
Why do you tell people so easily?
Especially to someone of opposite sex.
Of course... there is possibility of disappearance... or something greater than that.
But, that's because we were all friends.-I...
It's because... I like Chiyomi-san.
It's the truth.
Yesterday, I told her how I feel.
See, just as I said.
You told her your feeling to Chiyomi-chan yesterday, and she rejected you.
-Because you resented her...-What are you saying?
She did not reject me. I totally have a chance.
Oh, he was on a date with Onee-chan (older sister) day before yesterday.
- What? Is that true?-Well... not really a date but...
So it's you!
Bring Chiyomi back...
Where did you take her?
Sorry but they are busy right now...
Are you Chiyomi-chan?
Hello, Chiyomi?
-Chiyomi!  -Let go! Is this Chiyomi?
Yes.
I'm sorry to make you worry.
I wanted to call you but my phone broke.
You idiot. Where are you calling from? Hurry back.
No one is mad at you anymore.
I'm sorry, that's impossible.
Impossible? Why is it impossible?
Right now... I'm in Tokyo.
In Tokyo?!
What are you thinking?
Chiyomi, do you know how worried we were?
I told you yesterday. The dance workshop.
Please, I really want to do this.
Please believe me. I won't do anything that will make you worry.
I will not approve. I will not approve, you idiot.
Chiyomi, Chiyomi?
Anyway, I am fine.
I just wanted to tell you that for now. Bye.
W, w, wait... Where are you in Tokyo? Where are you staying?
I'll call you again later. Bye.
Wait Chiyomi.
Chiyomi, Chiyomi, wait!
Hello Chiyomi? Hello, Hello Chiyomi?, Chiyo-
Ah, what a relief!
- Let us know when she's back.-Sorry for the trouble.
-Sorry.-See you tomorrow.
Sorry.
-I'm glad she is safe.-Sorry.
-Thank you so much.-It's fine.
I told you we would easily find her.
She just ran away.
Minaki kun No Koibito  My Little Lover
Welcome back.
What are you planning on doing?
What do you mean...
You told me to tell them I'm fine.
Why did you say Tokyo? You're not going home?
I'm going home, of course.
I want to go home.
When I return to normal size.
"When I return to normal size", eh?
I can't go back like this.
Dad and Mom will be sad.
So...
It was better when they were mad at me.
I'm sure that's true, but...
And so...
I won't stay like this forever.
I should get back to normal soon.
So please!
Until then, can I stay here...
Let me stay by your side.
Hey wait, what are you talking about?!
Please. I won't be too much of a trouble.
Just let me stay here.
What a good feeling!
This bath is just my size!
Are you some creature?
Sorry, Minami-kun. I can't reach the soap.
Can you get it for me?
I'm sorry, please.
-Don't look!  -I won't look!
What do you mean, just let me stay.
Sorry I made you wait!
I'm going in now.
That scared me.
Minami-kun is muscular...
So comfy!
Excuse me,
Minami-kun?
What is it?
Thank you very much.
Thank you for taking care of me.
It's fine.
But...
It's okay.
This is the first time we're sleeping together.
Of course.
This is my first time in your room.
I got my own room when I went into Jr. High.
This is the first time I'm letting a girl in here.
I see.
About Nomura-san,
do you like her?
What?
Yesterday, you were with Nomura-san...
Why don't you ask my father?
I'm sure you're find a good way.
A good way?
My father is well know at the Med School here.
He can give out scholarships too.
If you are interested in it.
Interested...
Don't you think it's a good idea?
I have things to do.
Your eyelashes are long.
Minami-kun.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
♫ A casual encounter ♫
♫ gave me this great beginning ♫
♫ Everyday I was with you ♫
♫ I was slowly loving you, more and more ♫
♫ When we walk shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ It is like the moon in the sky ♫
♫ You are right here but even if I stretched my arm ♫
♫ I won't be able to reach you ♫
♫ I simply love you ♫♫ You are always in my heart ♫
♫ It almost hurts me ♫♫ Forever ♫
♫ I just want to be honest and ♫♫ tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Forever and ever ♫♫ Please ♫
♫ Be with me ♫
♫ I wish our days last ♫
♫ Forever ♫
[Preview]Beautiful princess, please marry me.
I want more normal clothes.
This is so good.
You can't... No...
According to Grandma, there is a legendary mallet here.
When you shake it on a night of a full moon, she gets big.
This is amazing.
Now, I can get back to normal.
Minami Kun No Koibito  My Little Lover