Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
I won't take the entrance exam. I know exactly what I want to do.
You are so spoiled and easy going.
I want to go back to that time.
I want to be small again.
Minami-kun.
Where are you Chiyomi?
Here, over here, Minami-kun!
Chiyomi-chan has been missing?
In Tokyo?!
What are you thinking?
I told you yesterday. The dance workshop.
So, please let me stay by your side.
Hey wait, why do I have to do that?
Princess, please wake up.
What's the matter?
Oh, you are a prince from the neighboring country.
Our princess suddenly passed away today, being cast a spell by a witch.
Oh. How pitiful.
My, how beautiful this princess is.
(It's a pity) such a beautiful princess passed away.
Please accept my love
and come to life again.
The witch's spell is broken.
The princess came to life!
Prince...
Hooray! Hooray!
You helped me, right?
Yes.
My beautiful princess.
Please marry me.
Yes.
Great!
The prince's kiss broke the witch's spell,
and the two have lived
happily ever after!
It doesn't dry.
As for me, could a prince's kiss
return me to the original size?
How in the world is it possible?
Yeah, right.
First of all, do you have the qualities to be called a princess?
So, who is the prince?
Well, I don't have any particular person in mind...
Is it Takagi? Takagi Riku?
- He confessed to you, didn't he?- Eh?
Well, I understand how you got carried away being confessed to.
But, don't you have to think of a more realistic way of returning to the original size?
I am not getting carried away. I'm seriously thinking...
Nooooo!
- Don't look at me. Look away!- Ouch!
Minami Kun No Koibito
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito
♫ I am not good at talking in similitudes ♫
♫ So I can't do a good job telling a tale ♫
♫ But, I will tell you an amazing story ♫
♫ of you and I ♫
♫ It is not a small story that will fit in a pocket ♫
♫ God played a trick ♫
♫ And a dramatic time began ♫
♫ The shape of happiness you and I imagined ♫
♫ doesn't have a name ♫
♫ But if it is a world I create with you, it's okay ♫
♫ I will write words that won't be erased like a magic ♫
♫ and turn the page ♫
♫ It is like a sequel to the fairy tale ♫ ♫ We can smile forever ♫
♫ To a place over the rainbow ♫ ♫ I can go, as long as I am with you ♫
♫ Let's imagine a story with a happy ending ♫
~Episode 3~Lucky Mallet of Love
I'm sorry I'm causing you trouble because Minami suddenly went to Tokyo.
- Old pictures, right?- Yes.
It is still April, and I know it is too soon.
We decided to put our pictures from childhood in the yearbook.
I found it. Here you go.
I know she should choose them by herself, but tomorrow is the due date.
I am sorry. She doesn't even pick up a phone.
Hey, come here a bit.
Okay, I'm coming.
Okay then. I'll choose them for her.
Thank you. Our shop is busy at this time of day.
- Did you find it?- Yeah.
- Is this it?- Yeah, that's it.
Wow, this is good. I can wear decent clothes now.
Onii-chan (big bro)!
Onii-chan!
Oh, no!
- Wow, Onii-chan. Welcome!- Asuka-chan.
I'm so glad you came.
What's wrong?
Eh? Well, it's a drag.
I was choosing pictures for the yearbook.
It doesn't matter which picture you choose. Onee-chan (big sis) always looks the same.
See? They are all the same.
You are right.
She looks happy.
Next day
Go ahead.
I feel comfortable.
Chiba Prefectural Tateyama No.1 High School
Sei Shonagon and Murasaki Shikibu are
said to be the two great female writers in the Heian period (794 to 1185).
And they had written very famous books.
Murasaki Shikibu wrote "Tales of Genji."
I didn't think I could come to school again.
Sei Shonagon hadn't written anything
about Murasaki Shikibu.
Murasaki Shikibu badly criticized Sei Shonagon
in her book, "The Diary of Lady Murasaki."
That tells us what kind of writers they were.
Things go along as usual without me.
Okay, this is it for today.
- Let's go eat pancakes.- pancakes? Okay.
- How about this?- I want more normal clothes.
Normal clothes...
I don't know too much about women's clothes.
Then...
- How about this?- It's not cute.
- How about this?- Weird.
Then, how about this?
That's cute!
Then, I'll get this.
Hmm?
Gross.
It's so good!
Don't get my uniform dirty.
Being small is nice at a time like this.
I can eat more than usual.
You are so carefree.
Sorry.
It's been four days already.
No sign of getting back to normal size?
I don't know.
I see.
Yup.
I'm sorry.
Eat quickly. It's gonna melt.
Ah.
Hmm?
One-inch princess.
- One-inch princess?- Yeah.
It is an old legend in this region.
It is a story about a cute princess who is small like one-inch boy.
A small princess? I wanto to see her!
But in the end, she became big again,
got married and had many children.
And she became people's protective god.
How did she become big?
She became big by shaking the lucky mallet stolen from an ogre
on a night of a full moon.
A lucky mallet.
Eh?
Well... No, no, no.
Ah, Minami-kun.
What are you doing here?
You left school in a hurry, but
you are eating ice cream alone.
You are kind of cute.
I have no choice. I have to get in there.
Hmm?
May I have a bite?
Cold.
Nomura! Sorry.
I'm in a hurry.
Hey, wait!
What's with him?
Sayori-chan!
You scared me. You disappeared so suddenly.
Masaya...
What's with your face?
Nothing.
- Sorry. You wanted to eat this?- No.
So, it is true that Feromone has a golfer boyfriend.
Ah, Minami, Minami.
According to Grandma,
this place has the legendary lucky mallet.
I have seen it. It is displayed only at festivals.
They say it brings you luck only by looking at it.
So, what was it? On a night of a full moon,
you are supposed to shake the mallet while you make a wish. Was it?
Right.
From where can I go in?
Minami-kun.
I can go in from there, right?
Here we go!
Be careful.
Oh.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
Minami-kun. Over here!
Over here!
It is convenient to be small in this kind of situation.
Ahem.
This is the real lucky mallet.
Seriously?
Please, please get me back
to my normal size.
Please!
Amazing. Really amazing.
I can now go back
to the world I lived and the life I used to have.
I don't like you anymore.
Hmm?
Eh?
What?
Didn't work.
No way. It was shining.
It really looked like it was gonna work.
This way.
Shoot!
- Hurry.- Who is there? A thief?
Oh? Shunichi-kun?
So, you have been worried that much.
Not worried.
Right.
Why don't you take it easy?
Ohno sensei said that you would be able to pass med school with no problem.
Sorry for doing a weird thing.
But, I am somewhat relieved.
I have thought that you would pretend to be strong, sayting you wouldn't believe in God.
You still have a cute side.
It's okay to whine sometimes.
And, you don't have to force yourself to limit the colleges of your choice.
Eh?
You were going to choose only those with tuition waver programs, right?
Why?
The hospital director told me that his daughter is concerned (about you).
Right.
It is true that it's hard to make ends meet for us.
I know how hard you have been working.
You have been working harder than anyone else in order to protect me and your grandma.
I don't want you to overstrain yourself anymore.
Minami-kun.
Shunichi.
You can aim for a med school you really want to go.
Don't underestimate me.
It is super easy for me to let you go to a college you like.
Okay?
Super easy...
A storm is coming, it seems.
Your grandma is not home, she's traveling. Shall we order pizza?
Yup.
Let's hurry.
I'm sorry, Minami-kun.
It's my fault.
It doesn't matter, it can't be helped.
Yah!
Minami-Kun?
The day when you became small
was like this, right?
Right.
Okay.
Shall we make another foolish attempt?
What?
Minami Kun No Koibito My Little Lover
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
This is where you became small.
That day, you fainted at the sound of thunder. Then you woke up finding yourself small. Correct?
I see!
If I do the same thing here again...
That could be possible.
These are your clothes.
You washed them.
I couldn't have left them as they were.
Thank you.
So, I will come pick you up in the morning.
Eh? Wait!
You are going?
You were alone on that day, werent' you?
But...
It's too much to be by myself in this storm.
I am small, so I might die before becoming big.
Fairies lose their magical power when they fall in love.
And, they will also lose their smile.
They will age instantly,
fall into a deep sleep
and never wake up.
If they are loved back
by those they love,
they will be humans in exchange for losing their magical power.
Humans age, but they have a smile.
In the short period (of their lives),
they can get joy, sadness, anger
and loneliness.
Chris hesitated.
"Is this love?"
"If it is..."
She doesn't know yet
that asking herself that question
itself is
a beginning of love already.
It hasn't been updated.
I wonder if Horikiri-shi is doing okay.
It's morning..?
Already?
Hmm?
I am big again.
Hooray!
Eh?
Where is Minami-kun?
Minami-kun. I am big again, back to myself again.
Thank you.
It's all thanks to Minami-kun.
What a relief.
Hey, no...
Stop it.
How awful.
Huh?
Was it a dream?
It's impossible after all.
Huh?
Hey Minami-kun, are you alright?
Minami-kun?
I see.
You couldn't return to original size.
Are you alright?
I am a fool after all.
I caught a cold, it seems.
Oh!
You have a high fever.
Nobody's home. What should I do?
Oh, right. I have to bring down the fever.
I'm finally here.
Chiyomi.
I couldn't bring anything.
Water, ice cubes or anything at all.
All I could do was just come back here.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry and stay here.
Once upon a time, there lived an old man called 'Old Bamboo-Cutter.'
He cut bamboos in mountains and fields and used them for a variety of things.
His name was Sanuki no Miyatsuko.
He thought it was strange and approached it. Then the bamboo shined inside.
Minami Kun No Koibito  My Little Lover
His fever is going up.
I wish I could cool him down.
I'm sorry, did I wake you up?
No.
You are feeling sick?
I feel foggy.
Who can it be?
Are you okay? Can you walk?
I'm okay.
Are you hungry?
A little.
I'll bring you something, too.
I'm sorry, at a time like this.
Thank you.
1,000 yen per meal. Pay me back later.
Hello?
Here we are.
We're coming in.
- It is spacious and beautiful.- It is like a newly built home.
So, you are all by yourself?
Yes.
It was good timing then. Here.
You have a fever, right? We brought you food.
Since you have a fever, you'll get udon noodles. Yabuki and I will -
I'm fine.
You don't want it? It's not good for you if you don't eat anything.
I'm not hungry.
Actually, we came here because you are sick, but I have someting else to --
- I'm not going back to the kendo club.- Don't make such a hasty decision.
I have already decided.
Ah... That might be the case, but
let's talk about your talent in kendo that you are not even aware of --
No, thank you.
He is so unapproachable.
Come on, Minami. Why don't you just listen to him?
Give me a break!
Would you please leave?
Let's talk about kendo some other time --
I won't.
Then, let's go, Yabuki.
If you are worried about something, tell me any time.
I will do my best to consult you.
Okay.
You should also be interested in real women.
- Thank you for having us.- So long.
(An obscene magazine)
Oh.
Sorry for doing this without asking you.
I was looking for information on how to bring down fever.
I learned that it is good to cool the carotid artery and the armpits.
I know.
Oh, you knew.
My mom is a nurse.
I see.
That makes sense.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Umm... I am really sorry.
I caused you even to have fever.
Don't worry. I did it myself.
They came again?
What's with them?
Don't you have to answer the door?
No.
I forgot to lock it.
Hello. Minami-kun.
Nomura?
Go hide yourself.
Minami-kun. Are you there?
Yes.
Ah.
Nomura-san.
Nomura.
Sorry for coming in without asking.
It's okay.
Why?
Well, I heard you were staying home sick, and I got worried.
I see. Thanks.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I feel a little foggy.
This...
I am not hungry, so...
How is it?
Good.
Really? I'm glad.
It was delicious. Thank you.
I will make it any time if you like it.
Minami-kun?
You have a high fever. Sorry I didn't notice.
Lie down and rest.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
Minami-kun.
Thank you.
Don't worry and rest.
I'm sorry, Minami-kun.
I...I can't do anything for you.
No! Don't!
Minami-kun.
Minami-kun!
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
♫ A casual encounter ♫
♫ gave me this great beginning ♫
♫ Everyday I was with you ♫
♫ I was slowly loving you, more and more ♫
♫ When we walk shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ It is like the moon in the sky ♫
♫ You are right here but even if I stretched my arm ♫
♫ I won't be able to reach you ♫
♫ I simply love you ♫♫ You are always in my heart ♫
♫ It almost hurts me ♫♫ Forever ♫
♫ I just want to be honest and ♫♫ tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Forever and ever ♫♫ Please ♫
♫ Be with me ♫
♫ I wish our days last ♫
♫ Forever ♫
~Preview~Give me a break. Why do I have to do that?
Please, Minami. If we don't get any freshmen this year, the club will be canceled.
I know you want to do kendo.
I know you are itching to do it.
Minami-kun's dad left you, right?
I am like you. The one I gave birth to me left us.
Mom, don't you have grudge against him?
Give it your best, Minami-kun!
This drama is a fiction.