I want to go back to that time again.
I want to become small again.
Minami-kun...
Where are you Chiyomi?
Here! I'm over here, Minami-kun!
You're in Tokyo?
Hey, what are you thinking?
So, I told you yesterday.
About the dance workshop.
Please let me stay with you.
Horikiri-shi.
A new work...[Title: Chobiko (a small girl) in a Pocket]
I wanted to...
put something like this in here.
Do you like Chiyomi?
I do... like Horikiri-shi.
Did he see me?
- Chiyomi is not at the workshop.- Eh?
Are you really Onee-chan? (big sister)
Asuka, I'm sorry.
As always, you roll around so much in your sleep.
Minami-kun...
Hurry up and get up. We'll be late.
Were you watching me?
How can you sleep like that.
- I'm changing, so look away.- Okay.
It's been 4 weeks since I became small.
A lot has happened...
Here you go.
Thank you for the meal.
It's been a while since Grandma made a meal.
Yay! I can eat delicious meals again starting today.
What do you mean by that?
I tried hard while Grandma was in the hospital.
Lately, we have been in synch with each other.
We came this far.
Things are going really well lately
between us.
You couldn't cook anything unless I was beside you, right?
Well, that is true.
It's great you admit that.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito
♫ I am not good at talking in similitudes♫
♫ So I can't do a good job telling a tale ♫
♫ But, I will tell you an amazing story ♫
♫ of you and I ♫
♫ It is not a small story ♫
♫ that will fit in a pocket ♫
♫ God played a trick ♫
♫ And a dramatic time began ♫
♫ The shape of happiness you and I imagined ♫
♫ doesn't have a name ♫
♫ But if it is a world I create with you, it's okay ♫
♫ I will write words that won't be erased like a magic ♫
♫ and turn the page ♫
♫ It is like a sequel to the fairy tale ♫
♫ We can smile forever ♫
♫ To a place over the rainbow ♫
♫ I can go, as long as I am with you ♫
♫ Let's imagine ♫
♫ a story with a happy ending ♫
~Episode 9: Our Trip to a Hot Spiring~Onii-chan!
Good morning, Asuka-chan. What's the matter?
Eh? Did something happen again?
We're in trouble. Mom is going to ask the police to search for you, Onee-chan.
- What?- What?
Well, asking the police to search for her...
Don't you think you are making too big of a deal?
He is right. If you overdo it, Onee-chan might not feel comfortable coming back...
It's been four weeks already.
She hasn't been home for four weeks, which is a big deal.
Besides, don't you think it is strange that we can't contact her?
How can I stay calm?
Yeah, I guess that is a problem.
Mom...
[Online Novel NOVELING][Author: Moon Bunny Michaela] [Title: Chobiko In a Pocket]
Wow, she is doing such a great job.
What are you reading?
This is an online novel that Horikiri-san has been writing.
Horikiri?
-You mean Horikiri from 3-A class who has been missing?-Shhh...
Horikiri. Oh, on-line novel.
Moon?
- Who? Who do you think it is?-This novel?
Minami!
- Do you have a minute?-Eh?
I have something to ask you.
What? This is Horikiri?
I haven't heard the name for a long time. Let me see.
"Chobiko in a Pocket"?
- What's this?- Well,
I heard she is an on-line novel writer.
Seriously?
Moon Bunny Michaela is her pen name.
- Wow!- Moon Bunny Michaela?
What's this about?
Is it true?
- Yeah.- Wait. Isn't she supposed to be in Tokyo for the dance workshop?
Yeah, right.
Horikiri-shi is in trouble.
Ri...Riku?
How dare you play dumb until now.
There are tons of things I want to ask you,
- such as your Chobiko...- Huh?
Chobiko?
I'm talking about the figurine in your pocket.
What?
You are still playing dumb?
Gosh, you are so good at acting.
You might as well become an actor.
Riku, do you know about this?
What?
They say it is Chiyomi.
Moon Bunny Michaela. She writes online novels...
Horikiri-san is now very famous.
Moon Bunny Michaela, was it?
Did you know about it?
No...
Is that so?
My goodness, now he knows!
I will be in trouble if he reads it. What should I do?
Wait. Minami-kun is not the type who reads something like that.
Well, I guess it'll be okay.
It sure is Chiyomi.
This is 'Chiyomi's World.'
Then, what you are saying is
that Chiyomi has been writing... online novels?
It definitely is Chiyomi.
I am relieved. Ever since I heard she hadn't attended the workshop,
I was really worried.
But, it is good that she is updating it frequently, at least.
But why did she have to leave the house?
That's right. She didn't have to do this secretly.
Well, I suppose she felt shy about showing it to you.
But, why did she hide it from us?
Right?
I'm sorry.
Actually, I did know
- that Horikiri-shi was Moon Bunny Michaela.- Eh?
I'm sorry, Amippe.
I didn't want to say something that Horikiri-shi had kept secret.
Hey, that's not good. You should have told us about it first thing.
I'm sorry.
On the day I told her that I knew about it
and how I love Moon Bunny Michaela and Horikiri-shi,
she disappeared.
So, I felt responsible.
Takagi-san, it is not your fault.
The reason why Onee-chan disappeared
has nothing to do with her writing activities as Moon Bunny Michaela.
... That's what I think.
You should have told us if you knew about it.
I am sorry. I thought it would be better if Onee-chan told you about it herself after she came back.
Oh... She has been thinking about these kinds of things.
And, she is... how should I say... expressing herself?
I didn't know she had this kind of talent.
Now that I think about it,
she told us she saw a tiny person and got really excited about it.
You saw One-inch Princess?
Yes, One-inch Princess.
What are you saying? That's not possible.
But, she was really there.
- On the river. I was with Minami-kun --- That's enough. I am busy.
Maybe she really did see her.
She does have the tendency to daydream.
You know, there is not a clear distinction between reality and a dream for children.
Maybe I shouldn't have scolded her that much.
I wonder if...
Onee-chan became a tiny person for real?
Hey, what are you saying?
But, she must have had a lot of things she wanted to say but couldn't.
Shunichi is late.
He said he'd go for a run but hasn't come back yet.
What is he doing, leaving Chiyomi-chan behind?
What?
[The Big Guy prepared this red dress for me.]
[He must have just casually chosen it.]
[Even so, he wouldn't have given me something that didn't suit me.]
[Today, I am feeling love towards him, in the red dress.]
[When I am in his pocket, I am the closest person to him.]
[I feel his body heat and heartbeat, ]
[and I can get closer to him than any other women of his kind.]
[I am the closest to him, and yet, I am the farthest.]
[Every time I dream of my wish coming true,]
[I deny the possibility, thinking that Big Guy wouldn't possibly love me.]
[That's what I force myself to think.]
[I'll be happy just to be beside him.]
[I love the Big Guy, more than anyone in the world.]
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byThe Little Lover Team @Viki.
My Little LoverMinami Kun No Koibito
Minami-kun, did something happen?
You have been quiet since you came home.
Ah... Well...
Yes, who is it?
I am Takagi. I'm Shunichi-kun's classmate.
Takagi?!
Why is he here?
Oh, welcome.
Shunichi, Takagi-kun is here.
Come down.
Shunichi-kun's room is upstairs, right?
It's okay. I am going to his room.
Huh?
Oh, really?
Hey, hide somewhere.
Okay.
What's the matter?
Why did you come here all of a sudden?
I want to talk to you as a man, face to face.
Let me come in.
Hey!
I was studying right now.
- Make it short if you need to talk.- Your figurine doll...
Does she sleep here at night?
Oh! Well...
This is actually...
That is undoubtedly a bed for a figurine!
What? What are you saying?
I just put a towel in it. That's all.
You are playing dumb?
Then, shall I put my figurine on it?
Look. It's just the right size!
Hey, what are you talking about?
I am not interested in figurines or that kind.
Don't try to deny it.
I saw Horikiri-shi peeking out of your pocket in the classroom.
- What?- What?
That was really well made.
Riku thought I was a figurine.
That's fine.
That's not what I want to ask you the most.
Minami.
You love Horikiri-shi, don't you?
Riku...
I can tell because I like creating things.
The reason why you can make a figurine that looks so real is because you love her that much.
W-What are you saying?
She is my childhood friend, but...
That's not all, is it?
Why are you playing dumb?
I am not.
It is you, isn't it?
The "Big Guy."
Why are you covering it up?
I... love Horikiri-shi.
So, I got jealous when I read "Chobiko in a Pocket."
I wished I had been the "Big Guy."
I don't know what you are talking about...
Then, what is this?!
Show me your figurine.
- I'm telling you, I don't have a figurine...- Where is it?
Hey, stop! Stop it!
Hey, where is it?
Stop it! I'm telling you to stop!
Oh... They are so young...
This is...
what I gave Horikiri-shi.
It's cute! Did you make it yourself?
It's great!
That means...
Horikiri-shi is here.
Let me see Horikiri-shi.
You know where she is, don't you?
- Let me see her!- That is...
impossible.
Impossible?
Then, let me ask you.
What is Horikiri-shi to you?
What do you mean?
Let me tell you this at least.
Don't make Horikiri-shi sad.
If you read Chobiko, you would know
that she is in a one-sided love relationship.
She believes that her feelings won't be returned.
That's all your fault!
My fault?
You haven't told her how you feel about her, have you?
Why do you make her suffer?
If you love her... tell her.
Tell her how you feel about her.
I became afraid of
loving someone.
When I was in middle school,
my dad left us.
Damn you!
You know, my dad must have thought
that he would cherish my mom forever.
But...
People's feelings change.
Mine might too.
So, because you didn't want to hurt Horikiri-shi...
I decided not to love anyone.
I didn't want to be like my dad.
But, Takagi.
You...
When you hung around with Chiyomi, I got upset for some reason.
Were you jealous of me?
You were?
I don't have a right to get jealous though.
That night,
Chiyomi told me how she felt about me.
But I...
If I had accepted her feelings then...
You need to tell her how you're feeling now.
You need to tell her.
"Big Guy" is you.
"Big Guy" actually loves Chobiko--
Chiyomi, I love you! I'm in love with you, Chiyomi!
Hey, why are you saying it to me?
You're not in a one-sided love.
You're... already a part of me!
Minami...
Minami-kun!
Chiyomi?
I just heard Horikiri-shi's voice.
Minami-kun...
Me, too... I need you.
No way.
Minami-kun.
She spoke.
Thank you, Minami-kun.
Now, I finally know
how you feel about me.
I was the same.
Until that night,
I tried not to acknowledge my feelings.
Horikiri-shi...
Hey, Minami. Is this a figurine?
Riku. I am sorry.
On the night when you confessed to me, I became like this.
You became like this ?
Are you Horikiri-shi?
Yes.
Eh? What?
You became Chobiko for real.
Yes, I did.
You are turned off, aren't you?
No. I am not, but...
Cute...
Yeah, you are cute.
Did Minami give you the red dress?
When I became small, I had nothing to wear, so he bought it for me.
I see.
She was always wearing that before that.
Thank you.
Without it, when Minami-kun came to find me,
I wouldn't have been able to come out.
Chiyomi! Chiyomi!
Here! I'm over here! Minami-kun!
Minami-kun!
Without it, I wouldn't have been able to live on like this.
I see.
I was of help to you... a bit.
This was the first thing that protected me.
I thought that the reason why Chobiko is a tiny person
was because it was a figurative expression you came up with.
I never thought it was real.
I wanted to give you a response,
but I thought I needed to get back to the original size.
Of course.
But, you gave me a response a long time ago.
What?
When I read Chobiko, I knew it was not me.
If Minami feels the same way as you, there is no chance for me.
Takagi...
Okay then,
I am leaving Horikiri-shi in your care.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
I looked into 'The legend of One-inch Princess.'
I found out that using the lucky mallet is not enough.
What?
You tried the lucky mallet, right?
Yes.
Apparently, that accomplishes just half a mission.
In the original story, after One-inch Princess used the mallet,
she prayed, facing the morning sun at Akebono Cape and she became big.
Akebono Cape?
Why don't you go there?
My Little LoverMinami Kun No Koibito
Why are you all of sudden going on a trip alone?
It's not that exaggerated. It's just over night.
A change of pace is necessary at times. Here, take some onigiri (rice balls).
Thank you Grandma. See you.
You didn't forget anything, did you?
I got everything.
I'm going.
Good morning.
Oh, Minami-kun. Good morning.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byThe Little Love Team @Viki.
Hello.
Yes.
- Welcome.- Welcome.
Can I stay here tonight?
- Are you alone?- Yes.
Sure, come on in.
- Please fill this out.- Yes.
Mom, isn't he a high school student?
Don't be so nosy about our customers.
- Here you go.- Thank you.
Please enjoy.
Here.
We're here.
They think you are alone.
Well, we are living as one now.
I'm so happy that you brought me here. Thank you.
Wow, it is so beautiful.
Yeah, it is.
- It feels great.-Yeah.
This is the first time we're taking time with our bath.
You're right. Normally, we take turns.
- What should I do if all of a sudden I got big right now?- Eh?
You're right.
I guess there is "onsen (hot spring) therapy".
Oh boy, what should we do?
They'll get mad. You're supposed to be alone, but now, there are two people.
That's not what I was saying.
Then, I'll borrow your yukata (kimono robe).
Then what should I wear?
Oh yeah.
Then you would be in your underwear.
Are you serious?
Just your underwear!
This looks good.
Can I have a small plate?
I don't like hot food, so I like to put a small portion on it to cool it off.
Certainly.
- Thank you for this meal.- Thank you for this meal.
This is so good!
Yeah, it is.
This feels like the best meal of my life.
I never thought a day would come when we could eat a meal together like this.
Yeah.
You're right.
Excuse me.
- This is good right?- Yeah, it's good.
This one is so fresh
This one is good, too.
Wait a minute.
- This is too hot.- It's hot?
It's true, Mom.
I clearly heard a woman's voice,
He was probably watching TV.
No, I think he has someone with him.
If you think about it,
it's weird to ask for another plate when he's all alone.
He's pretending he can't eat hot food. He's lying to us.
Hey...
Welcome back.
Thank you.
Excuse me... about what time is tomorrow's sunrise?
- Oh, you are going to the cape.- Yes.
Let's see.. About this time, people who go see it leave around 4:00.
I see. Thank you.
I hear people receive blessings there.
Usually, a couple or
a newly-wed couple goes there.
I'd like to be happy with my girlfriend.
Have a good night.
Enjoy your stay.
He was alone.
Don't be rude to customers.
This is known as a relaxing place to stay.
So he does have a girlfriend.
That was a short lived romance.
But, you can't fall for customers. I tell you that all the time.
I don't want to hear that from you.
Minami-kun no KoibitoMy Little Lover
I can hear
your heart beating nervously.
I am...
nervous.
Me too.
Are you okay?
I am...
not okay.
But...
it hasn't been
okay since you've come.
Really?
Minami-kun?
Since I waited this long,
I might as well wait until tomorrow for the second one.
The second one?
You remembered.
Ah, we are here.
This is it.
You don't want to miss it, so keep looking up at the sky.
Yeah.
Minami-kun, what are these?
If you didn't have clothes to put on, we're in big trouble.
I...
like Chiyomi.
I like you a lot.
Minami-kun...
I...
had the most fun when we went to the mountain and river everyday
looking for One-inch Princess.
Me too. I had the most fun during that time.
I always wanted to be with you like that again some day.
You can.
I won't run away from you any more.
I love you, Chiyomi.
Minami-kun...
Chiyomi, look.
Dear God, please return me to my normal size. Please.
I hope I can be with my beloved Minami-kun forever. Please... Please...
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byThe Little Lover Team @Viki.
♫ A casual encounter ♫
♫ gave me this great beginning ♫
♫ Everyday I was with you ♫
♫ I was slowly loving you more and more ♫
♫ When we walk shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ It is like the moon in the sky ♫
♫ You are right here ♫♫ but even if I stretched my arm ♫
♫ I won't be able to reach you ♫
♫ I simply love you ♫♫ You are always in my heart ♫
♫ It almost hurts me ♫♫ Forever ♫
♫ I just want to be honest and ♫♫ tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Forever and ever ♫♫ Please, be with me ♫
♫ I wish our days last ♫♫ Forever ♫
[Preview - The Last Episode - Good-bye Chiyomi, Good-bye Minami-kun]- Why? Do I have to stay like this foever?
The two have to be dating for sure.
Let's forget about each other when we get back.
Let's pretend all of this never happened.
Minami-kun!
I love you, Chiyomi.
Let's stay together. It's a promise...
Minami-kun no KoibitoMy Little Lover