I want to go back to that time again.
I want to become small again.
Minami-kun...
Where are you, Chiyomi?
Here! I'm over here! Minami-kun!
You're in Tokyo?
Hey, what are you thinking?
So, I told you yesterday.
About the dance workshop.
Please, I really want to do it.
Please let me stay with you.
Hey, wait a minute. Why do you have to do that?
Your father...
He disappeared, right?
He made a lover and left us.
I don't consider him my father.
You idiot!
Could it be...
a burglar?
[A burglar is here.][from Chiyomi ]-What's wrong?
Sorry. I'm going home.
- Hey, Minami-kun?- Sorry!
Hey, what are you doing?
- Why did you come?- Let's not do this kind of thing.
Hey, you sent her the divorce paper for sure, right?
I sure did. When I called her the other day, she said she had already signed it.
Then why...?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byThe My Little Lover Team @Viki.
To be able to see beloved person's sleeping face,
for girls,
is a very happy thing, I think.
Even though I became small like this,
that kind of feeling doesn't change.
Eh?
Ch... Chiyomi?
Seriously?
This time,
I am like this...
It'll be okay.
Minami-kun.
I'll protect you.
H- Hey.
Hey, wait a minute.
It feels so cushiony here.
Unexpectedly, she has...
I can't move!
I can't breathe.
Sorry, get me out of here.
I can't stay there after all.
Nomura!
Hey.
May I... kiss you?
Eh?
But, I am small like this.
How cute.
I feel like eating you.
She's gonna eat me!
Minami-kun, are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Good morning, Minami-kun.
Good morning.
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito
♫ I am not good at talking in similitudes♫
♫ So I can't do a good job telling a tale♫
♫ But, I will tell you an amazing story ♫
♫ of you and I♫
♫ It is not a small story ♫
♫ that will fit in a pocket♫
♫ God played a trick ♫
♫ And a dramatic time began ♫
♫ The shape of happiness ♫
♫ you and I imagined ♫
♫ doesn't have a name♫
♫ But if it is a world I create with you, ♫
♫ it's okay ♫
♫ I will write words that won't be erased like a magic ♫
♫ and turn the page ♫
♫ It is like a sequel to the fairy tale ♫
♫ We can smile forever ♫
♫ To a place over the rainbow ♫
♫ I can go, as long as I am with you ♫
♫ Let's imagine ♫
♫ a story with a happy ending ♫
~Episode 6~I know I can't be the one
Amippe, were you able to get in touch with Horikiri-shi?
Ah... Well...
Oh?
There isn't a person named Horikiri-san at our workshop.
No way. It is Horikiri Chiyomi. Chiyomi.
Right. We don't have Horikiri-san or Chiyomi-san.
- Sorry. I forgot to do that.- Eh?
I'm sorry. I will e-mail her today again.
I'll tell her that you are worried about her.
I hope Horikiri-shi would contact me soon.
Sorry, may I go through?
Sorry.
Amippe... Riku...
Did he see me?
It seems our eyes met just momentarily.
What's the matter?
Minami...
Huh?
Well...
It looks like her.
Did you really make this, Takagi-kun?
Yup.
Don't be so rough with it.
Oh my...
What's with her?
He got a figurine, too...?
That looked so real.
Riku?
Okay.
[ Nomura Hospital ]
[ Director's Office ]
Come in.
Dad, it's me.
Ah, good timing, Sayori.
Ah...
This is my daughter, Sayori.
Hi.
Sayori, she is Dr. Koide Reiko, a visiting professor at Hokuryo University Hospital.
She will work at this hospital.
Nice to meet you, Sayori-chan.
Nice to meet you.
Well then, Dr. Nomura. I'm leaving now.
Oh, okay.
Excuse me.
What's the matter? It's rare for you to come here.
Is there something you want me to buy?
I don't want anything...
If you want something, you can just name it.
It's about Minami-kun...
Oh, about that.
Dad,
did you like Minami-kun's mom a long time ago?
What are you saying?
I asked her to come work here because I've known her for long and wanted to help her,...
Dad...
But, my offer to recommend him to Takasu University, which you requested, was turned down.
It was turned down?
There is nothing I can say about it anymore.
Sayori.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
Eh? What is it?
Right.
I am thinking about getting remarried.
What?
It's time I could get happy, right?
With whom?
Well, Dr. Koide you met now. She is attractive, right?
Wait, Sayori. Sayori.
Go ahead! Get married or whatever.
Sayori...
But, do you think you will be happy with such marriage?
Have you ever wondered how Mom felt when she left us?
We can't talk about it here. Let's talk at home.
What? It'll cause you trouble if I talk about it here?
You care about how you appear to other people more than your daughter's feelings.
Be quiet, Sayori!!
Sayori...
Sayori-chan.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The My Little Lover Team @Viki.
Excuse me.
What's this?
Oh...
Onii-chan did bring these here.
What? Handmade?
Could it be...
Just wait.
I'm just about to finish making this cute clothes.
Is Onii-chan a perv?
No way, no way.
By chance... in here, too...?
Onii-chan. I'm sorry.
Oh? It's e-mail screen.
Eh? What is this?
Onii-chan's e-mail address is 'issun-hime' (one-inch princess)?
I'm home.
Grandma.
Ah, welcome home.
How are you feeling?
Onii-chan, welcome home.
Ah... Asuka-chan.
Asuka?
W-Why are you here?
It's so nice of her.
She came to see how I was doing.
You're better than expected. I'm relieved.
Also, I thought I would ask you to help me study, so I was waiting upstairs.
What's she thinking?
My Little LoverMinami Kun No Koibito
Ah... It's messy here.
That's okay. I don't mind.
Yea...
Let's see...
Which one should I get help on...?
Asuka-chan.
You know, I am a man, so...
It's not right for a girl to come into a man's room.
Does that mean...
You see me as a girl?
Eh?
I don't mind.
You can attack me.
Asuka...
Onii-chan, are you panicking?
Asuka-chan! Which part do you not understand?
Oh right. Well, let's see...
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Okay, Sayori-chan. Come on in.
Come this way, please.
Hello.
What?
Oh, we have a visitor?
Nomura...
Hello, Minami-kun.
Make yourself at home. Have a seat over there.
This time, it's Nomura-san...?
What a day.
It's delicious.
- Yes, it is. - it is delicious, Sayori-chan.
You cook well.
Really?
Does it taste good, Minami-kun?
Ah... Yeah, it tastes good.
I am sorry I had you cook for us although you are our guest.
Don't worry about it.
We don't have a mother, so I always cook myself.
I am sorry I intruded on you when you have not been feeling well.
Don't worry about it. I am completely well now.
She has a big appetite.
Yeah. It really tastes good.
This is nice.
I always eat alone.
Oh... I am sorry. I'm being weird...
That's okay. You should just let it out.
Grandma.
Were you shocked to hear your father was getting remarried?
I... I have been attached to my dad.
When my mom left us,
I thought I didn't care.
I disliked my mom who was always whining and crying.
It is opposite from our case.
You know,
It is best to forget about the person who left you.
But...
Lately, I have come to understand how my mom felt.
She was left alone by my dad for a long time.
Even when I cooked dinner and waited for him,
we couldn't eat together, day after day.
I thought " Ah...my mom was the same."
The one who leaves has a reason to do so as well.
And yet, my dad is about to make the same mistake.
He didn't love my mom.
He married her just because she was a daughter of a professor he had been obliged to.
Actually...
he loved someone else.
I think my mom was lonely.
I'm sorry to tell you this...
My home situation is (nothing) compared with Minami-kun's...
It's okay.
Poor girl.
Minami-kun.
I left a bath towel in the room.
Would you please get it for me?
Ah... yeah.
My Little LoverMinami Kun No Koibito
You had a rough day today, didn't you?
Yeah...
Nomura-san's home situation is similar to yours.
That's why you are...
What?
Nothing.
"That's why I am..." what?
Forget about it. It's nothing.
Minami-kun. Are you still up?
Hey!
What?
Were you asleep?
No.
I can't sleep. May I come in a bit?
Eh? What?
Ah... Hey.
I heard from my dad.
Your mom turned down my dad's offer to recommend you to the university.
Yeah...
Are you okay with that?
Just because you'd get a full scholorship, you're going to a school so far away?
On top of that, there are many restrictions after you graduate from the medical school.
I'm applying to other national universities.
If you apply to Takasu Medical University, my dad will arrange a scholorship for you.
And, you don't have to leave here.
I appreciate your gesture.
But, I am not cut out for that kind of thing.
Sorry...
Thank you though.
Hmm?
You know how I feel about you, right?
Eh?
How long are we going to stay like this?
Oh no. Get away from him, Nomura-san.
Do you not... like me?
Well...
Minami-kun...
Do you like someone else?
Eh?
Could it be... Horikiri-san?
Of course not.
Then... Is it okay for me to do something like this?
No! Minami-kun!
So cute. I feel like eating you.
Ah...
She's going to eat me.
I'm sorry.
This kind of thing... I...
What kind of thing?
I am sorry but I don't want to do this kind of thing.
Rather than this, there are things I need to do now.
Never mind.
Eh?
Minami-kun is like a virgin.
You know...
my feeling can get hurt.
Nomura...
Good night.
Hey.
It is okay now.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
Chiyomi?
Why are you crying?
I am okay.
You are not okay.
I'm saying, I am okay.
The reason why the big man is kind to me
is because I am small.
The one who is suitable for him is his own kind, the big woman.
The big woman can embrace him and comfort him gently.
All I can do is to dance on his palm.
[Chobiko in Pocket - New]
It's updated.
I am nothing but a burden for him.
I mustn't have such an ambitious dream as to be loved by him.
Horikiri-shi...
I have known this from the start...
but I can't stop crying.
Minami-kun...
Eh?
What?
Hey, Nomura?
Minami-kun, you too.
Ah... Hey.
Wait...Hey.
Minami-kun!
Oh?
Horikiri-san. You were here.
Let me go. Let me go, Nomura-san.
You are so noisy.
Ouch.
Minami-kun!
Minami-kun. Let me out!
Chiyomi!
Minami-kun. Don't do that.
Hey, get away from him. Nooo!
Don't worry about it. Okay?
- Minami-kun!- We can't do this.
Because Chiyomi is...
Minami-kun! Minami-kun!
No, you can't do it. Hey!
Noooo!!!
I am going home then.
Okay.
Minami kun No Koibito My Little Lover
I'm giving back what you left.
Oh, how was it? It was great right?
Never... lend me something like this again.
I got it.
What you need is not something like this, right?
Ok.
Karaoke...
What am I supposed to do at a place like this?  I'm not going to sing!
It's a party.
A party?
Know what? You are popular but too uptight.
Finally, you are getting horny like a normal person, right? You need to let it go.
I'm leaving.
W, w, wait. 2 college girls...
are coming.
See?
Things like this doesn't happen often. Amazing.
-They are already close by.-Let me go.
- I'm telling you they are here.- Let me go.
Hey! I'm Nanami. Thank you for waiting.
I'm Hiroe-chan. Nice to meet you.
You are a real high school students.
Are you by chance a virgin?
That one maybe, but this pretty one probably isn't.
It's other way around. I have already... but
Minami... I mean he is... probably.
Seriously?
You don't have to be scared.
You are a virgin, right? So cute!
- I'll get going...- Hey!
Minami...
Sorry... Yabuki.
Chiyomi?
Chiyomi.
Minami-kun.
Minami-kun, your grandma saw me just now.
What?
She saw you?
I was out during the day, and when I came back...
Oh no. Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go!
Oh wow.
Grandma, there is a reason for this.
Oh wow... you were right here.
I looked for you for a long time.
Grandma, aren't you surprised?
I figured everyone would be shocked since I look like this.
You are so small... you look cute.
Ha? That's it?
Then, Grandma gave me some snack, and then we chatted.
She said, "go home now."
But she didn't say anything just now.
She was making a meal as usual.
Do you smell something burning?
Eh?
What? That legless floor chair costs 30,000 yen?
That is such a rip off.
I have never heard of a legless floor chair that costs 30,000 yen.
We are going to add another body pillow to this.
Wow, what a deal.
Grandma, you left the gas on.
Who would buy such legless floor chairs.
Whoever buys this is dumb.
Grandma. Fire.
Eh?
Oh, Noboru.
I found something unusual today. Do you know what it is?
Grandma...
An one-inch princess.
An one-inch princess came to my room to visit.
An one-inch princess...
One-inch princess... One-inch princess.
I hope she will come and visit again.
Onee-chan (big sister), I wish you would send emails more often.
[From Issunhime@beeble.co.jp](Issun-hime= One-inch princess)
This address is...
What? Onii-chan's (big brother) mail address is "Issunhime"?
[From: Issunhime@beeble.co.jp]
Issun-hime... (one-inch princess)
Does this mean Onee-chan was sending us email from that device?
So that means Onii-chan and Onee-chan are...
I wonder if Grandma is ok?
I wonder what happened all of sudden.
I'm worried.
I thought you don't eat late at night.
It's still before 10:00.
What do you mean?
So sweet. It tastes good.
- Convenience store's pudding is pretty good.- Yeah.
You got caramel on your face.
Eh? Where?
Right there. On the left.
Right here. Here.
It feeles like Minami-kun is nicer now. Or is it just me?
I guess it's just me.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
♫ A casual encounter ♫
♫ gave me this great beginning ♫
♫ Everyday, I was with you ♫
♫ I was slowly loving you more and more ♫
♫ When we walk shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ It is like the moon in the sky ♫
♫ You are right here, but even if I stretched my arm ♫
♫ I won't be able to reach you ♫
♫ I simply love you ♫♫ You are always in my heart ♫
♫ It almost hurts me ♫♫ Forever ♫
♫ I just want to be honest and tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Forever and ever ♫♫ Please be with me ♫
♫ I wish our days last ♫
♫ Forever ♫
Preview: Episode 7A Proposal after 18 years-My Dad never proposed to my Mom.
Ha?
I don't think he really liked me.
Grandma, you made this?
Horikiri-si was in a love that wouldn't come true.
If that's the case, I wonder who was the guy.
I can't take it any more.
Please Onii-chan, if you know where Onee-chan is, please tell me.
Our house is a mess because she isn't there.
Asuka-chan...
Dad, please say it using words...
Minami kun No Koibito My Little Lover