I want to go back to that time again.
I want to become small again.
Minami-kun...
Where are you, Chiyomi?
Here! I'm over here! Minami-kun!
You're in Tokyo?
Hey, what are you thinking?
So, I told you yesterday.
About the dance workshop.
Please let me stay with you.
Your dad disappeared, right?
He made a lover and left us. I don't consider him as my dad.
Damn you!
Could she be... a burglar?
You really sent her the divorce paper, didn't you?
I sure did. She said she signed it when I called her the other day.
Then, why didn't she turn it in already?
What?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
Here you go.
The sea breeze feels so nice.
It's been already three weeks since I started living with Minami-kun.
My feelings for Minami-kun has been growing rapidly.
Don't worry. If we are busted,
I will take responsibility and protect you.
Protect me? What do you mean by that?
What the word means.
Hey, Minami-kun.
What do you actually think of me? I want to know.
Minami-kun.
Hmm? What is it?
Nothing.
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito
♫ I am not good at talking in similitudes♫
♫ So I can't do a good job telling a tale ♫
♫ But, I will tell you an amazing story ♫
♫ of you and I ♫
♫ It is not a small story ♫
♫ that will fit in a pocket ♫
♫ God played a trick ♫
♫ And a dramatic time began ♫
♫ The shape of happiness you and I imagined ♫
♫ doesn't have a name ♫
♫ But if it is a world I create with you, ♫
♫ it's okay ♫
♫ I will write words that won't be erased like a magic ♫
♫ and turn the page ♫
♫ It is like a sequel to the fairy tale ♫
♫ We can smile forever ♫
♫ To a place over the rainbow ♫
♫ I can go, as long as I am with you ♫
♫ a story with a happy ending ♫
~Episode 8~A Blue Fairy
I'm home.
Grandma.
Grandma!
Grandma!?
[ Nomura Hospital ]
I wonder if Grandma would be okay.
Shunichi!
How is Grandma?
She is okay for today.
But, she needs to get examined thoroughly.
So, she is staying here for tests.
Shunichi, can you turn in this paper at the office?
Okay.
Oh, I am sorry. I have to...
Oh, okay.
- Wait here a sec.- Sure.
What is it?
Eh? Oh.
Ouch! Ouch, ouch...
I found a goodie!
Oh? You are Onee-chan's (big sister)...
Chiyomi?
I see.
Even you don't know where Horikiri-shi is.
That's right.
Ah! Ouch.
You can't run away from me, Fairy-san.
Fairy?
Well, this might not have anything to with Chobiko,(Chobiko = A Small Child)
but I saw a tiny person, too.
What?
I saw one at our neighbor's window last night.
Your neighbor... Could it be Minami's?
Yes.
Ah, but... you wouldn't believe me, right?
- I guess it was just an illusion...- No, it is possible.
Eh? Do you believe me?
That was probably... a figurine.
A figurine?
Minami... he made such an elaborate figurine...
Is that your mom?
She looks like a sweet mom.
Mom doen't like Miyu.(Miyu is her name.)
Eh?
Mama!
Miyu, you told Dr. Koide that you didn't want to have a surgery, didn't you?
Do you know how much people are worried about you?
Don't cause me any more trouble.
If you keep saying you won't have one,
you won't get better.
She is here.
Minami-kun!
Hello.
This is my mother.
- And, this is my son.- Oh, I see.
Minami-kun, I am here.
Miyu-chan, would you be nice to our Granny?
Minami-kun, please see me.
Miyu, do you want to eat something?... I see.
I have some more work to do, so I will go for now.
If you keep sulking like this, you won't get better.
Well then, excuse me.
Have a good day.
Emi-chan.
-Grandma? -Mom, are you awake?
-Yes. Where am I?-You are in the hospital.
Mom, you collapsed in the living room.
Yeah that's right. And Noboru saved me, right?
Mom, from today, you are staying at the hospital for tests.
I see. I'm sorry to cause you trouble.
It's no problem. You should take it easy since you are here.
My neighbor is so cute.
Nice to meet you.
I think I will have fun staying here.
- I'm on the night shift today, so find something to eat for dinner.- Okay.
- Okay Mom. I'm going back to work.- Alright.
Well, I will be going too since I left something.
What?
What did you leave?
Something...
I'm here! I'm the one you left!
Chiyomi.
Chiyomi!
Oh, I see. Fairy-san's name is One-inch Princess.
Ah... Yes, it is.(Speaking like princess from long ago)
I am One-inch Princess.
You know, One-inch Princess,
appears before a person who needs her.
A person who needs her?
That's right.
She will appear before those who work very hard to be happy.
So, if you tie her up or bully her, she will disappear.
Oh, I see. I'm sorry, Fairy-san.
So, I'm Fairy after all.
Because you are a fairy to me.
But I am a bad child.
You might disappear.
Eh? You are a good child.
No. I keep doing things Mom doesn't like.
I make Mom angry all the time.
Mom doen't laugh probably because of me.
That's why I got sick.
That's not true.
It is true.
Then, why don't you show your pictures to your mom?
Then, I think your mom will be happy.
I can't. I can't show them to her. She only thinks of me as a bad child.
She wouldn't be happy to see these pictures.
Mom would be happy if I didn't exist.
Miyu-chan...
That's not true.
A mom who doesn't love her own child?
There isn't even one mom like that in the world.
That's not true.
It's true.
Any mom loves her own child very much.
Miyu-chan, you are so considerate of your mom.
And, you are a person who should be happy.
That's why One-inch Princess visited you. Right?
Eh?
That's right.
You should sleep now.
Okay. Good night.
Good night.
Oh no. It's hard for me to get out of here now.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byThe Little Lover Team@Viki.
Miyu...
I am sorry... for making you suffer.
My Little LoverMinami Kun No Koibito
Minami-kun,
Thank you very much for taking care of me.
But,
I have to say good-bye to you.
What do you mean?
I can't live in the same world as you.
It is...
time for me to go back to the moon.
Go back to the moon?
Hey, wait a second.
Thank you.
And,
good-bye, Minami-kun.
Chiyomi.
Chiyomi!
Hey, Chiyomi.
Chiyomi. Hey!
Hey! Chiyomi!
Chiyomi! Hey!
Chiyomi!
Hey, Chiyomi!
Chiyomi~!
Chiyomi.
[Nomura Hospital]
Noboru.
Did you find what you were looking for?
Grandma.
No. I... you know...
Were you looking for One-inch Princess?
What?
One-inch Princess is here.
Chiyomi.
Minami-kun.
You fool.
You made me worry so much.
Minami-kun
Shunichi!
What? What's the matter?
I am going to deliver a change of clothes to grandma.
Ah, I'll go, too.
Oh yeah? Then I will go buy some cake at our neighbor's, and wait for you there.
Okay.
Chiyomi, wake up. We're going to the hospital.
- Miyu-chan might be worried.- Yeah.
Thank you for coming on your day off.
No, don't worry. Grandma is my best friend.
Oh my.
Thank you.
But, will Grandma be okay to eat this much?
That's for the nurses.
They are taking care of Grandma, so I got them.
Yeah, I see.
Sorry. I am sorry.
- I will bring a towel now.- Are you okay?
Oh, no...
Here.
Ah, thank you.
You carry such a sensible thing with you, huh.
Even my shorts are wet...
Why don't you go back home and change your clothes?
Yes, I will. It's cold.
Oh, gosh.
What? Onii-chan (big brother) has such a cute stuff.
Hmm?
Dad, Mom and Asuka, how are you doing?
I am in Tokyo...
They are the same.
That means... Could it be...?
I see. Miyu-chan said such things about her mom.
Yeah.
But, her mom is worried about Miyu-chan for sure.
Because yesterday...
Miyu, I am sorry for making you suffer.
- Minami-kun.- Hmm?
Can't we do something about it?
Onii-chan.
Asuka-chan.
Who were you talking with?
Eh?
Ah... I was talking to myself.
Oh no.
What is that?
What are you hiding?
Would you show it to me?
This isn't... anything...
Could it be...
Onee-chan? (Big Sister)
I knew it.
Hey.
Let me see Onee-chan.
Asuka.
What's going on?
Well, that is...
I don't know...
Nobody knows.
Are you really Onee-chan?
I'm sorry, Asuka.
No...
I am sorry I didn't notice it.
Asuka-chan...
Hey.
Is there anything I can do for you?
My Little LoverMinami Kun No Koibito
She loves her mom so much.
Yeah.
- She is coming now.-Yeah.
Okay, here we are.
Miyu-chan, wait here until your mom comes, okay?
Miyu-chan.
Fairy-san!
I came here to use magic on you.
Do you want to know how your mom really feels?
Excuse me, Miyu-chan's mom!
Please come with me. It's about Miyu-chan.
Miyu!
Miyu. Miyu?
It seems she feels much better.
Miyu-chan started to have pain suddenly.
When I was about to call a nurse, she said mom would worry so don't.
But, I was worried, so...
Miyu, you should call me when you are in pain.
Miyu-chan was drawing pictures of you a while ago.
They are all pictures of you and Miyu-chan.
I'm sorry, Miyu...
I couldn't understand your feelings.
I couldn't tell you my true feelings.
You must have had hard time. I'm sorry.
You are so important to me.
I love you so much, so very much!
So, please...
stay with me. Please...
Please get well.
Mom...
What's the matter?
- Doctor, please.-Oh no...
Please save Miyu.
- Please.- I understand.
So, what happened to Miyu-chan?
It seems she had pain suddenly.
What's happening?
Doctor? How's Miyu...?
Did something good happen to you?
Eh?
You look really happy.
She is fine.
You don't have to worry.
Well, call me if anything happens again.
Yes. Thank you very much.
- Doctor.- What is it?
I think...
I will have a surgery.
Miyu!
Let's set a date for the surgery later.
Yes. Thank you very much.
What happened?
- Let's do our best!- I will do my best!
I will do my best!
Good girl.
I'm so relieved.
Timing and subtitles brought to you byThe Little Lover Team @Viki.
Minami-kun...
Do you have a minute?
Nomura-san...
Sorry to call you out so suddenly.
Don't worry.
You might have guessed by now
but I wanted to make things clear between us.
If you are going to reject me, I want you to reject me properly.
You see, I have to make plans for my future romance, too.
Do you love... Horikiri-san?
I... finally realized
that, for a long time,
I have loved Chiyomi... all along.
So... I'm sorry.
Oh, what a humiliating way to be rejected.
Thank you.
Well then... I am going first.
At least, see me off until I am out of your sight.
Okay.
Grandma Toyo is not nice.
Poor Kotoko.
That's right.
What is Minami-kun talking about with Nomura-san?
So, he should be kind to her.
No, that's not right. That's not how Irie-kun is.
My Little LoverMinami Kun No Koibito
Was it... Kanae-san?
How is she doing?
I feel bad about what happened.
Don't worry. Time has passed.
In October, we are going to have a baby.
I see.
Congratulations.
Then, we have all the more reason to do the right thing.
- Here you go.- What's that?
The divorce paper you gave me.
I saw you here yesterday, so I brought it with me, thinking I might run into you.
Sorry for being late.
But, I wanted to hand it to you in person.
But, what a lousy disguise.
You have zero talent in deceiving people, as before.
That guy...
You idiot!
Hey, Nomura-kun!
Do you know how much Emi-chan suffered because of you?
Nomura...
She's been working from morning to night, all by herself.
She supported her family and raised her kid.
Do you know how hard it was for her? Do you?
Emiko, Shunichi... I am sorry.
Emiko.
- I will take my mom with me --- I won't let you take her.
I decided to protect Mom and Grandma when you left us.
That's what I decided to do.
I am sorry... Grandma is our important family.
I see.
Shunichi, I am leaving your mom and grandma in your care.
You don't have to tell me. I know.
Oh, Shunichi. You should continue with kendo.
You don't want to quit right after you lost.
You should protect your partner this time.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, no... Can Irie-kun work hard to make it?
Minami-kun! Could it be that he and Nomura-san...?
Grandma. I'm going now.
Ah, okay. Thank you.
Sorry, but I will stay a little longer.
Hey, Princess. Let's go.
Sure.
Fairy-san.
Hmm?
Thank you for the wonderful magic.
You are welcome.
See you later.
Eh? Eh? what's happening, Minami-kun?
Don't you ever leave me.
This is... where you belong now.
Eh? What did you say?
Well... nothing.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
♫ A casual encounter ♫
♫ gave me this great beginning ♫
♫ Everyday I was with you ♫
♫ I was slowly loving you more and more ♫
♫ When we walk shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ It is like the moon in the sky ♫
♫ You are right here ♫♫ but even if I stretched my arm ♫
♫ I won't be able to reach you ♫
♫ I simply love you ♫
♫ You are always in my heart ♫
♫ I just want to be honest and ♫♫ tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Forever and ever ♫♫ Please ♫
♫ Be with me ♫
♫ I wish our days last ♫
♫ Forever ♫
~Preview~What? Is this Horikiri?[ Episode 9: A hot spring trip for the two of us ]
It seems that she is an on-line novel writer.
They found it out. I will be in trouble if Minami-kun reads it.
We're in trouble. Mom is going to ask the police to search for her.
Eh?
You are the "Big Guy", aren't you?
After he shook the mallet on One-inch Princess, he prayed in the morning light with her at Akebono Cape. Then she grew big.
It's like we are on a secret trip.
God, please grow me back to the original size.
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito