- I'll leave Horikiri-shi in your care.
Okay.
By the way,
When I looked into "The Legend of One-Inch Princess",
I found out that using the lucky mallet is not enough.
What?
In the original story, after the One-inch Princess used the mallet,
she prayed, facing the morning sun, at Akebono Cape and she became big.
Akebono Cape?
Why don't you go?
Please, make me big, and return me to my original self.
Please return Chiyomi to her original self.
The day has finally come when I can return to my original self.
Where are you, Chiyomi?
Right here! I am here, Minami-kun!
Ever since Minami-kun, who I've liked since when I was little, has rescued me,
I've felt happiness being close to the person I like, and sadness...
The Minami-kun that I like is not a coward like that.
You can't do anything without me.
Your fever is going up.
Being impatient with myself for not being able to do a thing.
Being disappointed at myself...
A lot happened.
- That you really like Chobiko...  - I like Chiyomi.
It's not one sided-love.
You are...
already a part of me.
Minami-kun...
I finally found out that Minami-kun was feeling the same way.
Now, our feelings became one.
I want to get back to how I was... for Minami-kun.
~Last Episode~Good bye Chiyomi, Good bye Minami-kun
Why?
Am I going to stay like this forever?
Don't worry.
I'm sure there is another way.
But... what else can we do?
Don't worry.
I'm here with you.
Minami-kun...
But, that Takagi...
he was so confident, but what is this?
Thank you very much.
Thank you for taking care of me during my stay.
Well... Since we came all the way out here,
shall we skip school for a day and stay one more night somewhere?
He's not heading back now, is he?
I'll Leave Horikiri-shi in your care.
Okay.
In the original story, after the One-inch Princess used the mallet,
she prayed, facing the morning sun, at Akebono Cape and she became big.
Akebono Cape?
Why don't you go?
Those two are definitely seeing each other.
Somewhere, they will meet up.
Chiyomi, is there any place you want to go?
Yeah.
Where? Where do you want to go?
Please take me home.
Home?
Not Minami-kun's house,
but my house.
Chiyomi?
I'm going to tell my parents about what's been going on.
Wait a minute. It's not like you can't get back to normal forever.
I can't continue to be your burden like this forever.
It's okay with me. I don't think of it as a burden.
Minami-kun...
Minami-kun is talking to himself all this time. Is he okay?
Let's forget about each other when we get home.
Everything up until now...
let's forget about them.
What are you saying?
I can't possibly do that.
You can't become happy being with me like this.
There's nothing I can do for you.
Don't worry about that. I'm saying it's okay.
I don't like it.
I don't want to live being a burden to you.
Minami-kun, you will someday regret it.
I'll regret more if I'm not with you.
I...
no matter how you are, I will protect you.
And I won't leave your side.
Minami-kun...
I love you.
Let's stay together forever.
I'm sorry.
Let's end this.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
Minami-kun!
Chiyomi...
Oops.
He's not moving.
-Seriously?-Ouch...
What should we do? This is not good.
What are we going to do?
Shut up! I don't know!
What are you guys doing?
Let's go. Hurry up and get in the car.
Minami-kun.
Minami-kun!
Hey...
Minami-kun. Hey, Minami-kun!
Minami-kun. Minami-kun...
Minami-kun, are you okay?
Minami-kun! Hey, Minami-kun!
Minami-kun!
Ch, Chiyomi?
Mom...
Minami-kun is...
Maybe Onee-chan (big sister) did really turn into a dwarf.
Mom! Minami-kun is not moving!
What should we do?
- Chiyomi, calm down.- What should we do?
There's nothing you can do right now. Let's calm down first...
Hello? There was an accident. Please come quickly.
[Nomura Hospital]
[Operating Room]
Doctor, how is Shunichi?
How is he doing?
The surgery was a success.
We removed the bleeding in the brain.
There were no other damages, so all we have to do is wait for him to regain his consciousness.
I'm sure there will be no aftereffect either.
Dr. Kawamura, thank you so much.
Thank you.
So he was Minami-san's child.
Since he is young, I'm sure he'll recover quickly.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
That's great.
Minami-kun...
Thank goodness...
Here we are.
I'm home.
Hey, where is Chiyomi?
- She's in here.- Here?
Dad, I'm home.
I'm sorry to have made you worry for a long time.
Chi...Chi...Chi...Chi...
I'm Chiyomi.
What~~~~!!!!
I see.
Asuka, why didn't you tell us if you knew?
I did tell you. I said she might have become a tiny person.
That sounded like a joke.
You wouldn't have believed me if I told you anyway.
- But, even so...- It's alright now.
She came home safely like this.
Dad...
Hey, you are so small and cute.
Welcome home, Chiyomi.
Welcome home.
I'm so happy for you.
I'm home.
He's been asleep this whole time.
He just had the surgery yesterday...
This is to be expected?
It's strange.
The anesthesia has worn off a long time ago. He should be awake by now.
Eh?
So cute.
Chiyomi.
- Chiyomi.- What's the matter, Mom?
Minami-kun hasn't regained consciousness yet.
What?
My Little LoverMinami Kun No Koibito
Dad... What went wrong?
Ricchan, thank you (for coming).
Minami-kun...
What's going on?
He should be awake by now.
I was told that it is clearly not normal for him
to be in a coma for a long time like this.
But, wasn't he recovering nicely?
There is a chance that he wouldn't regain consciousness.
No way...!
Dad!
Minami-san, the doctor wants to talk to you about our plans going forward.
Okay.
Ricchan, may I ask you to (stay here) for a while?
- I am going, too.- Me, too.
Minami-kun...
Mom.
Hmm?
Would you leave us alone for a little bit?
Okay.
Minami-kun.
Wake up.
Wake up... please.
I'm sorry, Minami-kun...
I was only thinking about myself.
Even if I couldn't get back to how I used to be,
I would have been happy just to be beside you.
I will never leave you.
Even if you didn't wake up.
I love you, Minami-kun.
Let's stay together forever.
Minami-kun...
Minami-kun!
Chiyomi...
Yeah, I'm Chiyomi. Do you recognize me?
You were safe...
Minami-kun.
I'm so relieved.
I'm so happy.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
Chiyomi.
Minami-kun.
Minami-kun, I...
Chiyomi?
Yes, Minami-kun.
- Chiyomi.-Yes.
- Chiyomi.- Yes.
Can you wear something?
Don't look!
- Not yet!- I won't look.
It's okay now.
I can't believe...
a kiss really worked...
I wonder if a prince's kiss
would return me to my original size.
There is no way that would work.
My goodness.
Holding back (a kiss) backfired.
What?
I should have kissed you sooner.
♫ I am not good at talking in similitudes♫
♫ So I can't do a good job telling a tale ♫
♫ But, I will tell you an amazing story ♫
Let's kiss a lot from now on.
♫ It is not a small story ♫
♫ that will fit in a pocket ♫
♫ God played a trick ♫
♫ And a dramatic time began ♫
♫ The shape of happiness you and I imagined ♫
Chiyomi, they are back--
♫ It doesn't have a name♫♫’But if it is a world I create with you, it's okay ♫
Shunichi!?
Chiyomi-chan!?
Oh... my... goodness...
♫ We can smile forever ♫
♫ To a place over the rainbow ♫
♫ I can go, as long as I am with you ♫
♫Let's imagine more♫♫Let's keep imagining♫
♫ a story with a happy ending ♫
- Oh, it's Horikiri.- Horikiri, Horikiri!
Chiyomi~!
- What have you been doing?- There has been a big fuss because of you.
Well, I've been on "mushashugyo".(go out to perfect one's skills)
What~? Mushashugyo? Come on.
Hey, Minami. Are you okay?
Yeah, I am okay.
Hey, don't go ahead of me. I'm still weak.
Sorry. Forgive me.
Goodness.
What is this unusual atmosphere?
What's up with Horikiri and Minami?
Didn't they used to fight like cats and dogs?
By any chance... while Horikiri was missing...?
Could it be you and Minami-kun are...?
Yeah. We are dating.
Hey, Minami-kun!
It's okay. It's better to make these kinds of things clear.
- Ami...- Amippe!
I'm sorry...
for making you worry.
You fool.
I was so worried about you.
Amippe, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Okay, let's do it.
This is Chiyomi's choreography.
We only have one month until the contest.
- Let's give it all we've got!- Okay!
Okay, Yuka-rin, play the music!
Okay. Starting the music.
♫No matter how early it is in the morning♫♫No matter how cold it is♫
♫Your facial expressions keep changing♫
♫You wrap various kinds of secrets in a uniform♫
♫You are the only one who knows about them♫♫ And you don't tell me about them♫
♫ Our youth is always kept wrapped♫
♫ You'll never know what it is like unless you open it ♫
♫ To see whether it is sweet or sour ♫
♫ We are in the middle of taste testing it ♫
♫ Give me, give me, give me, give me a candy♫♫ Give me a 'candy chance' to me♫♫ I know how you really feel♫
♫ The taste spreads in my heart♫♫ Is this the taste of love? ♫
♫ Hey, give all of them to me ♫♫ You are Candy-chan♫
♫ Candy-chan, Candy-chan, Candy-chan, Candy-chan♫♫ Candy-chan, you are Candy-chan♫
♫ Candy-chan, Candy-chan, Candy-chan, Candy-chan♫
Wow, you guys are so cute.
Chiyomi, Minami-kun, congratulations on your marriage.
Thank you very much.
They are members of the Tateyama No.1 High School Dance Club that the bride belonged to.
That's right. We got married as soon as we graduated from high school.
The dance you saw, which Chiyomi-chan used to dance, placed No.1 in last year's dance contest.
Next one up is Ueno Yuka-san, a freshman in the dance club, who is going to be the next leader.
She wrote a song for the two.
Please enjoy.
Yay, we can listen to Yuka-rin's song.
Chiyomi-senpai, Minami-san. Congratulations.
I am going to sing with all my heart, wishing happiness for your future.
Please enjoy. "Just Staying Beside You."
♫ A casual encounter ♫
♫ gave me this great beginning ♫
♫ Everyday I was with you ♫
♫ I was slowly loving you more and more ♫
♫ When we walk shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ It is like the moon in the sky ♫
♫ You are right here ♫♫ but even if I stretched my arm ♫
♫ I won't be able to reach you ♫
♫ I simply love you ♫♫ You are always in my heart ♫
♫ It almost hurts me ♫♫ Forever ♫
♫ I just want to be honest and ♫♫ tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Forever and ever ♫♫ Please, be with me ♫
She sings well. Right?
You're right.
♫ In words casually spoken to me♫
Finally, we came this far, didn't we?♫ I found your sweetness♫
It is like a dream even now.
You think so?
You don't think so?
I... never thought of marrying anyone but you.
♫ The moon we have in the sky again♫
♫ shines on me ♫
♫ as if it wraps me around♫
My, you're still crying? Straighten your back and get a hold of yourself.
You've been crying since the ceremony.
Well, when I think about many memories.
I just get overwhelmed with emotion.
Chiyomi, who was so small,
who really got small...
You are beautiful.
Oh no. When I think about it, it makes me cry.
Okay, okay.
I always thought they would end up getting together.
Me, too.
So cute.
- A boy or a girl?- A boy.
He is a boy. He is cute, isn't he?
Isn't onee-chan pretty?(onee-chan: it is used to call older women)
Are you next, Dad and Dr. Reiko?
- What?- Sayori...
You are a good match unexpectedly.
Sayori-chan...
What? Unexpectedly? What do you mean?
Okay, here we go. Cheese fondue.
Thank you. Let's see.
Oh, you look cute in it.
- I'm so happy.- Because I'm good.
Me too. Me too. Me too.
- I want to take a picture with you too, Takagi-san.- Okay.
May I call you Onii-chan (big brother) from now on?
- What?- Onii-chan!
Asuka-chan...
Well, your Onii-chan is over there, right?
- Riku, let's take another picture.- Onii-chan.
- Onii-chan.- Me, too. Me, too.
I should have taken a picture of Chiyomi when she was a tiny person.
I'm regretting it now.
We have one.
See?
There's Chiyomi!
- What?- Look.
Chiyomi!
Yeah, I am in it.
You're here.
My Little LoverMinami Kun No Koibito
Since the day I became small,
it's been exactly a year today.
- Well then, I'm going.- Um.
Are you okay? Are you done packing?
Ah!
I forgot to pack sweatpants and shoes.
What do you think you are going there for?
Minami-kun successfully entered a medical university where he could commute from home.
He became a medical student in April this year.
I moved to Minami-kun's house.
Well, I just moved to our neighbor's house though.
We've been having a sweet married-life.
It will be so hard for me to be away from you for two weeks.
Well, I sure will feel that way. But, today, I am going to Tokyo
to participate in the dance workshop I was supposed to go to last year.
This time, you will work hard to become a dancing writer, right?
After I finish writing this, I'll be going.
Are you about to finish it?
It is getting to the best part of the story now.
The best part?
The big guy took Chobiko to a place.
The place was...
Be careful.
Wow, this place brings back memories.
It seems as if it happened a long time ago.
Yeah.
It makes me remember the time when I became small.
Is that all you remember?
What?
It is not a well-made crown, but...
Chiyomi... I love you.
I want you to stay with me forever.
Let's get married.
When she put her face on the big guy's chest,
She heard his heartbeat she used to listen to.
Chiyomi, look.
The two kept looking at the rainbow for a long time.
That was the same kind of rainbow that they saw when they were kids.
That rainbow might have been our future.
Chobiko is not in a pocket anymore.
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito
♫ When we were children♫
♫ We were always innocent♫
♫ We were always together ♫
♫ and holding hands, weren't we? ♫
♫ It's like my true feelings♫
♫ that I hid away deep inside a bag♫
♫ It's hard to tell you♫
♫ Even if it is not romantic ♫
♫ In the memorable time we spent together ♫
♫ We didn't make promises ♫
♫ But it will be okay if we create our future together♫
♫ The world that shines like a rainbow ♫
♫ The memories that will never fade ♫
♫ Even after you wake up from a fairy tale ♫♫ I will be with you forever♫
♫ Beyond the place where the stars shine on♫
♫ I can go as long as I am with you ♫
♫ Yes, I want to believe in a miracle ♫
♫ that shines so brightly♫
♫ In all the precious moments I cut out of time, ♫
♫ You are in every single one of them♫♫ And I now know what it means ♫
♫ My heart throbs, and I take a breath ♫
♫ And I knock on the door in your heart ♫
♫ When I embrace the sound of love ♫
♫ that is like a secret I can't tell anyone, it starts to resonate ♫
♫ To a place over the rainbow ♫
♫ I can go, as long as I am with you ♫
♫ Let's imagine more ♫
♫ Let's keep imagining ♫
♫ a story with a happy ending ♫
Channel Managers: kalmendarez, ursuulee
This drama is fiction.
My Little LoverMinami Kun No Koibito
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byThe Little Lover Team @Viki