And, the one-inch-boy, wearing a needle sword
that his grandfather made,
rode a soup bowl
his grandmother prepared as a boat
and headed for Kyoto.
He is so cool even though he is small!
Right. Even though he is small,
he is very brave.
I want to see him.
Oh, come to think of it, there is a legend in this area
that is called 'one-inch-princess.'
- One-inch-princess?- One-inch-princess?
Really? Does she really exist?
I don't know...
I wonder.
- One-inch-princess!- One-inch-princess!
Where are you?
Where?
One-inch-princess!
Where are you? Over there?
Come out, one-inch-princess.
I am sure she is here.
For example, under the grass like this.
Oh, it's a frog. Over there?
- Over here.- One-inch-princess!
Where is she?
Ah... I got wet.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byThe Little Lover Team @Viki
What's the matter? Are you okay?
- One-inch-princess.- Eh?
She was really here.
I saw her now. See over there?
Since she floated from that way...
I love you very much, Chiyomi.
Me, too. I love you very much, Minami-kun.
Then, shall we stay together forever?
Eh?
Yup. Let's stay together.
Let's promise.
Let's make a pinky promise. If you lie, I will make you swallow a thousand needles.
Pinky swear!
Minami-kun, look.
Wow, cool.
I was asleep.
It's morning.
Why did I have that dream now?
Okay, I'll work on it a little bit more.
Memories from your childhood are not reliable.[User Name: Moon Bunny Michaela]
The real memories and fantasies are all mixed in.
And, I don't know what was true and what was not.
Did one-inch-princess really exist?
Was that beautiful rainbow an illusion?
And, how about the promise I made with Minami-kun?
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito
♫ I am not good at talking in similitudes ♫
♫ So I can't do a good job telling a tale ♫
♫ But, I will tell you an amazing story ♫
♫ of you and I ♫
♫ It is not a small story ♫
♫ that will fit in a pocket ♫
♫ God played a trick ♫
♫ And a dramatic time began ♫
♫ The shape of happiness you and I imagined ♫
♫ doesn't have a name ♫
♫ But if it is a world I create with you, it's okay ♫
♫ I will write words that won't be erased like a magic ♫
♫ and turn the page ♫
♫ It is like a sequel to a fairy tale ♫
♫ We can smile forever ♫
♫ To a place over the rainbow ♫
♫ I can go, as long as I am with you ♫
♫ Let's imagine ♫
♫ a story with a happy ending ♫
Good morning.
~Episode 1~You'll be late on the first day of the new school year, Chiyomi.
I will just have vegetable juice today.
Right, the new school year starts today.
Lilac flowers are beautiful at this time of the year. Lilacs have meaning that...
You went to bed late last night?
I'll bet you watched dance videos or something on your computer.
No, I didn't.
Have you been studying?
Well, yeah, sort of.
You need to pull yourself together. You are a 12th grader now, having to take a college exam.
Okay, okay.
Asuka, you too. You are a 9th grader from today.
My goodness. You have to be aware that you are lazy, taking after your father.
Okay, I know. Thank you for the meal.
Hey, Honey. You have to tell them, too.
I am LAZY, you know.
Chiyomi-chan, would you give this to Shunichi?
He left this bento lunch.
Sorry. Here.
Oh, okay.
Ah, bento...
I am sorry.
This is from your mom.
Well, I...
What was that? Can't be happening.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byThe Little Lover Team @Viki
Chiyomi? Hey, Chiyomi!
Eh?
What?
What's the matter, Horikiri-shi?(-shi is a formal/honorific ending for names.)
Ah, nothing's the matter.
- Well, I am so glad we are in the same class, Ami.- We are taking the same subjects, right?
I am glad I am with Riku. Please show me your homework again.
Please.
So, you value me only for that reason?
- It's not that.- It's not that.
That didn't sound sincere.
Nomura-san is also in this class.
Eh?
- Pheromone?- Pheromone?
Ah, Nomura-san.
I don't like seeing boys' eyes becoming heart-shaped, looking at Pheromone.
Hey, look.
Wow, she is so cute!
Far out!
We are in the same class as Pheromone. We are super lucky.
Yeah, I wanna date her. I feel like melting.
I am different.
Minami-kun.
Okay, the male class rep will be Minami-kun.
Minami-kun. Thank you very much.
Wow, if Minami-kun becomes one, maybe I should run for one.
No way. I want to be the class rep with Minami-kun, too.
Your neighbor is really popular, as always.
He is so rude, though.
Okay, the female rep next.
Nomura-san.
Horikiri-san.
- Nomura-san.- Why me? My grades are not good.
Well, last year, at the school festival...
We have a crepe shop. Please come.
Here is our crepe shop. Would you like to come?
That's because our class couldn't sell crepe at all.
But, at the athletic meeting, too...
Go, Go, Go.
That's because our class wasn't doing well...
People now see you as a person who'll give behind-the-scenes support.
Horikiri-san.
Okay, this is the last one.
No way.
Okay, I want to ask Horikiri-san to be the female class rep.
Eh, but...
Why don't you do it?
May I ask you to do it?
Eh, well. Oh, no...
Excuse me, sensei.
What is it, Nomura-san?
I want to run for the class rep.
Well, but, now Horikiri-san was...
Horikiri-san, do you want to be the class rep?
I...
It doesn't matter.
I want to be the class rep.
Sensei,
The one who wants to do it should do it.
That's true.
Okay, it seems Horikiri-san is reluctant anyway...
Maybe I will ask Nomura-san to do it since she volunteered.
Is that okay, Horikiri-san?
Horikiri-san?
Yes, it's fine.
Okay, the female class rep will be Nomura-san.
Let's give her a big hand.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Me, too.
♫ Give me, give me, give me. Give me a candy! ♫♫ Give me a candy chance! ♫
♫ I know how you really feel ♫
♫ Is this the taste of romance ♫ ♫ that's spreading in my heart?
♫ Give me one, too ♫♫ You are candy-chan ♫
Hey, the competition is arond the corner. So, I want to review the choreography.
- Would you help me?- Eh?
- Okay. Count on me.- Really?
- Let's do it.- What I want to do is
a cool move.
My Little Lover
I am so tired.
Choreography for the competition...
That'll be fun.
What kind of dance should we do?
You know what?
You must be tired from working hard.
Oh, Riku. It's unusual (to see you now). You were working with the Hand Craft Club this late?
Eh?
Oh, well... Yeah.
What's wrong Horikiri-shi?
You see...
Huh? No way!
This is your favorite dance team, Chiyomi. Cool!
I want to audition for it, too!
- The audition is held in Tokyo?- Eh, Tokyo?
I can't do it. I have to study for the college entrance exam. My mom won't okay it, first of all.
You think so, too?
And, if I pass it, I have to stay in Tokyo.
- Stay in Tokyo?- Eh, what are you going to do if you pass?
Are you going to quit school? Your parents won't let you do it.
You are right, but...
What? Are you serious?
A little.
Ah, Chiyomi?
Let's talk about this some other time.
I have to go somewhere from now.
Oh, is that so?
Riku. Would you go home with Chiyomi?
Yeah.
Then, see you.
Huh? Hey, wait!
Horikiri-shi, are you interested in romance?
It's not that I am not interested, but I don't believe in that kind of stuff.
You don't believe in it...
Well then,
have you ever liked anyone?
I did when I was little.
But I forgot about it.
I see.
Ah...
Recently,
on the internet,
I got interested in this online novel.
Online novel?
Yes.
Hanadoroboh (Flower Thief)Zakka (variety goods) &amp; Cafe
Thank you for walking me home.
No problem.
Umm... What I mentioned earlier,
Moon Bunny Michaela's "Blue Fairy,"
is really interesting.
I really like it...
Yup.
Like (it).(He wants to say "I like you.")
Is that so?
Then, I will read it.
Ah... why don't you?
Yup.
See you.
- Horikiri-shi! - What?
Well...
What is it?
It's nothing.
Well...
I will tell you tomorrow.
Okay, I see.
- Bye, bye.  - Bye, bye.
Riku has been reading it.
Okay.
Fairies lose their magical power when they fall in love.
And, they will also lose their smile.
They will age instantly, fall into a deep sleep
and never wake up.[Author: Moon Bunny Michaela / Title: Blue Fairy]
But, if they are loved back by those they love,
they will be humans in exchange for losing their magical power.
Humans age, but...
Moon Bunny Michaela!
- Sensei! - It's ok, it's ok.
I haven't told anyone.
No one at all!
I think it's fine to tell... you're just doing what you like to do.
No way. I'll be so embarrassed that I won't be able to come to school.
You are a celebrity in the online novel world.
No, it's just dumb luck.
When I wrote about what's been collected inside of me, it just happened.
I guess that is the mental scenary
that is inside of your heart.
No, no, it's not something that big.
What is it?
First of all,
this.
It's for you.
But it's not my birthday.
I know.
I wanted to give this to you the other day.
But, I couldn't.
What could it be?
It's cute!
- Did you make this yourself?- Yeah.
Wow!
The moon and a bunny?
Is this... perhaps...
I...
am a fan of Moon Bunny Michaela.
So,
I wanted you to have it.
You knew?
I'm sorry.
I did...
Then,
you knew yesterday.
Yesterday...
I couldn't say anything more.
What?
You knew.
I see.
What are they mumbling?
There, just say it.
I wanted to tell you...
I...
love (it).(He wants to say "I love you.")
I love Moon Bunny Michaela.
Thank you.
I love
you, Horikiri-shi!
You, Horikiri Chiyomi!
Yes!
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito
I know that you are now...
worrying about various things.
So, I know this is not the right time.
But,
I wanted to let you know how I feel.
I thought I needed to put my name in.
So, I won't rush you to answer me.
Riku...
If you like someone else, I'll give up.
But,
if that's not it,
I'll keep raising my hand.
For a long time.
He's such a good guy.
We get along.
He's nice.
More than that, he has good taste by noticing me.
Oh, no.
I didn't bring an umbrella.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byThe Little Lover Team@Viki.
Minami-kun, you're aiming for Med School, right?
Why?
Why am I crying?
I really love you, Chiyomi.
Me, too!
I...
like Minami-kun.
All this time...
Tokyo?
What are you saying, Chiyomi?
The dance group I admire, Solo, is having a workshop.
But,
you don't have to go now when you're studying for the college entrance exam. You can do it next year.
I want to go now. It has to be now.
No, you can't!
For someone who is clueless as you to go to Tokyo alone? I'm against it.
I am also against it.
You can just dance when you get to college.
What do you mean just dance?
Just to let you know, I have no intention of going to college.
I'm not going to take the entrance exams!
I already know what I want to do.
Going to college is just a waste of time!
What are you saying?
You were able to get into a decent high school.
What are you going to do if you're not going to college?
That's right. Your mom is right.
If you regret it later, it'll be too late.
Why do you collude at times like this?
Mom, you never listened to your parents!
What are you saying, Chiyomi?
You guys had to get married because you got pregnant with me!
Dad!
Chiyomi, we're not done talking.
The lightening is getting closer.
What?
Chiyomi-chan?
[We are out of soy sauce. Can you by it, haha]
I can't believe you're asking me to go on an errand at a time like this.
You even misspelled "buy".
What is it?
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito
Hey,
Minami-kun, you're aiming for Med School, right?
Maybe I'm being too forward but
what are you going to do about tuition?
You're mother is a single mom, right?
Why don't you ask my dad?
I'm sure you'll find a way.
Minami-kun.
What is it?
If you don't have anything, I'm going.
Why do you ignore me?
I'm asking, why do you ignore me?
I'm not ignoring you.
You are.
You don't look like that when you're with Nomura-san.
You were with Nomura-san this whole time?
Are you dating Nomura-san?
What are you saying?
It's none of your business.
That's right.
It's none of my business.
Sorry, for being abrupt.
What is this?
By the way, don't show up wherever I go.
Me?
You were just there.
When Nomura and I were walking.
That's not really...
Well, I don't really care.
I came out now because I had a fight with my parents.
A fight?
When I told them I'm not going to college,
Dad and Mom got angry.
You're not going to college?
I have something I want to do.
But they won't even listen to me. All they say is, college, college.
You are so easy going.
Eh?
You are so spoiled, and easy going.
Why?
Why do you say things like that?
You are horrible.
We were so close before.
Why?
It's obvious.
I don't like you anymore.
Hey!
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Umbrella... Wait!
This is...
She's not back yet. She's not answering her phone, either.
It's so weird. I thought that text message made it easier for her to come back.
Ok, I'm going to look for her.
But it's raining hard.
That's why I'm going.
You guys are so loud.
It's Chiyomi! Chiyomi!
Is Chiyomi-chan back yet?
- No. Why?- I thought so.
I just saw Chiyomi-chan by the Misaki Park.
He hit her. It's domestic violence.
What are you saying?
So, that's why she was crying.
Don't do that. I will arrest you.
Please.
What do you mean? What are you guys saying?
Take me there.
- Get my coat.- Okay.
Dad, your shoes.
- Here.- This way.
It's not going to stop raining.
Wait.
It's dead. What?
- Shunichi.- Wait, wait.
- Shunichi!- Wait.
I'm sorry.
You idiot!
Shunichi, let's go inside.
I'm leaving.
Good morning.
It's obvious.
I don't like you anymore.
Why are we like this now?
Before, we got along so well.
I want to get back to how we were then.
I want to be small again.
Minami-kun...
Why?
Why do you say things like that? You're horrible.
We were so close before.
Why?
Eh?
Eh? Why?
Have I... become the one-inch princess?
No way.
No way!!!
♫ A casual ♫
♫ encounter ♫
♫ gave me this great beginning ♫
♫ Everyday ♫
♫ I was with you ♫
♫ I was slowly loving you ♫
♫ more and more ♫
♫ When we walk shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ It is like the moon in the sky ♫
♫ You are right here ♫♫ but even if I stretched my arm ♫
♫ I won't be able to reach you ♫
♫ I simply love you ♫♫ You are always in my heart ♫
♫ It almost hurts me ♫♫ Forever ♫
♫ I just want to be honest and ♫♫ tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Forever and ever ♫♫ Please ♫
♫ Be with me ♫
♫ I wish our days last ♫
♫ Forever ♫
[Preview ~Episode 2~ Suddenly Living Together]-Where are you, Chiyomi?
I'm right here.
Minami-kun!
Chiyomi-chan is missing?
Between you and me, I think she ran away with a boy.
What?
They'll think it's a kidnap, rape, murder case.
- Chiyomi-chan.- Chiyomi-chan.
There is one person who seems suspicious here.
This bath is just my side.[This drama is fiction.]
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito