One-inch Princess?
Really? Does she really exist?
I wonder.
You didn't listen your parents either, right?
What are you saying, Chiyomi?
You got married just because you had me, didn't you?
I want to get back to that time again.
I want to become small again.
Minami-kun...
Where are you, Chiyomi?
Here! I'm over here! Minami-kun!
You're in Tokyo?
Hey, what are you thinking?
So, I told you yesterday.
About the dance workshop.
Please let me stay with you.
Hey, wait a minute. Why do you have to do that?
You know, my feelings can get hurt too.
Why are you crying?
Leave me alone!
No way. It's Horikiri Chiyomi. Chiyomi.
Right. We don't have a person named Horikiri-san or Chiyomi-san here.
This address...[sender: issunhime@beeble.co.jp]
That means... Onii-chan (big bro) and Onee-chan (big sis) are...
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
That's clothes for One-inch Princess.
One-inch Princess?
You know, a legendary princess around here who is like a dwarf.
She said she saw her yesterday.
A princess like a dwarf?
Yesterday, she almost started a fire if Shunichi were not here.
She did?
Grandma. You left a pot on the stove unattended.
Eh?
Oh, it's you, Noboru.
What?
I'm glad she got better, but...
I see...
Then, I will come visit here when you are not home as often as possible.
Sorry, Ricchan. I know you're going through tough time because of Chiyomi-chan.
Don't worry. It will help me get my mind off of that, you know.
Well then, I'll get going.
-Thanks.- Sure.
Obachan (auntie), I'll come visit again.
Okay, see you.
I'm sorry, Mom.
My Little Lover - Minami Kun No Koibito
♫ I am not good at talking in similitudes♫
♫ So I can't do a good job telling a tale♫
♫ But, I will tell you an amazing story ♫
♫ of you and I♫
♫ It is not a small story ♫
♫ that will fit in a pocket ♫
♫ God played a trick ♫
♫ And a dramatic time began ♫
♫ The shape of happiness you and I imagined ♫
♫ doesn't have a name ♫
♫ But if it is a world I create with you, ♫
♫ it's okay ♫
♫ I will write words that won't be erased like a magic ♫
♫ and turn the page ♫
♫ It is like a sequel to the fairy tale ♫
♫ We can smile forever ♫
♫ To a place over the rainbow ♫
♫ I can go, as long as I am with you ♫
♫ Let's imagine ♫
♫ a story with a happy ending ♫
~Episode 7~A proposal after 18 years
- What? You're going to stay at home?- Right.
Grandma saw you, didn't she?
She will want to see you again and look for you.
She'll look for One-inch Princess. Not me.
She is losing her mind now, so it might be okay...
No, it won't be okay. Not at all.
Please! I am worried about Grandma.
I will contact you as soon as something happens.
Pheromone Nomura is absent again.
It sucks!
It's meaningless to come to school if I can't smell her.
Oh, yeah? Good for you.
I finally received an e-mail from Horikiri-shi a while ago.
What did she say?
She only wrote about the workshop.
She said it's been hard but fun. I'm relieved she's doing well.
Well, I don't mean to be gready but wanted to receive a video.
You know, about the workshop...
Yeah?
Actually, it seems she has not been attending the workshop.
What?
[Legend of One-inch Princess]
Takagi-kun.
Sensei.
Oh, so you have known that Moon Bunny Michaela was Horikiri-san.
Yes.
She must have based "Chobiko in a Pocket" on this.
The setting of the stories are similar.
I wonder why Horikiri-san started writing a new story though.
"Blue Fairy" was getting into a really interesting part of the story.
Perhaps, something happened to her state of mind, I think.
Something happened to her state of mind...?
When I wrote what's been collecting inside me, it happend...
I guess that is a mental scenary that is inside your heart.
"Chobiko in a Pocket"...
That must be the mental scenary in her mind right now.
Could it be that she became Chobiko?
Eh?
I'm kidding.
Oh, but it could be...
What?
Horikiri-shi might be having impossible love.
What makes you say so?
Chobiko loves the big guy who she can't possibly be together with.
The gap in the height of them might represent the alienation she feels for him from not being able to be with him.
I see...
If that's the case, who is the big guy?
Could the big guy be...?
Okay, I'm going.
I'm borrowing this first. I'll give it to you when I'm done.
Okay.
He has also been reading it?
Did he get inspired, after reading it, to make the figurine, like me?
One-inch Princess, come on out.
Are you there?
There you are!
Did you make this for me, Grandma?
Well, One-inch Princess should be dressed like that, you know.
I'm so happy. It's beautiful. Thank you so much.
I am really happy. (She's using old Japanese.)
Oh? Someone came.
It's Mitsuko.
Coming.
- Hide somewhere a bit, okay?- Yup.
I think he doesn't want to see my face.
Why? You used to get along well.
Well, I wonder if he hasn't loved me that much from the beginning.
He used to love someone very much.
Because she broke his heart, he just got together with me who was around him.
Okay, it's ready.
It must be under there.
We got two children, and the restaurant business keeps us busy.
So, I have been living, not thinking about those things.
But, since Chiyomi's gone, I see him more often now.
Consequently, we've been fighting a lot.
But, Master has been really in love with you since he married you, hasn't he?
That's not true. Because... I haven't been proposed.
- What?- What!?
Oh, is that right?
Yeah. It's just that, since we had Chiyomi, we decided to to the right thing.
So, it was true that they had a shotgun wedding.
That stupid Joji.
Sorry to say such a thing about your husband.
I just remembered his face from the time when he was a mischievous rascal.
Don't worry about it. 'Stupid Joji' is good enough.
But, you know, that 'stupid Joji,'
I was happy he got serious about working ever since he married you.
Before that, he... What was it? He...
Heavy metal?
That's right. 'Stupid Joji' used to play heavy metal rock.
He sang, dressed in such crazy fashion like this.
He didn't work hard, despite his age, and said he would go to Tokyo and have success.
Tokyo? Dad...
♫Ah~! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! I'm... I'm... Come on!
No way. It's not possible.
But, since he married you, he has worked really hard.
He saved up money for down payment and opened a restaurant.
So, he is who he is today
all thanks to you, Ricchan.
That's not true.
You know, Ricchan,
you got together with him because you loved him very much, didn't you?
Mom.
I think so.
See? The fact that you got jealous now
proves that you love him. Don't you think so?
I am not sure about it now.
You've been working too hard.
What?
You should slack off a bit.
Slacking off,
it is also important.
Why desn't she reply to me?
My Little LoverMinami Kun No Koibito
- Welcome home, Shunichi.- Hello there.
Hello.
What should I do? Minami-kun's home.
Thank you, you two.
You helped me a lot. This is a thank you gift. Why don't you put it in your shop?
- Wow, it's great.- Thank you.
Not at all.
Alstroemeria is called 'Lily of the Incas' and 'Peruvian Lily.' It's flower meaning is...
You don't have to tell me. I won't be able to memorize it.
It's no good. She doesn't pick up the phone.
Oh, you are Chiyomi's... It's been long.
- Hello.- Hello.
Could it be...
she went there again?
- Here you go. - Thanks.
Oh, Minami-kun.
Hello.
- Oh, hi.- Hello.
- Want some cake?- No, I'll drink something.
Wow, it's unusual.
- You usually have a takeout.- I wanted to have a coffee break.
- Here you go.- Well then, may I have ice coffee?- Sure.
- It makes me so happy.- Chiyomi...
Where is she?
Minami-kun, you are doing great.
I heard you've been studying.
I wish Chiyomi would learn from you.
I can't expect too much from her because she is my daughter.
I hope she would go to college at least.
But, Chiyomi-san is a hardworking person, too.
She might not be good at studying,
but she is talented in other areas, like writing...
Oh, well, you know,
she has actually been working hard to pursue her dream to be a dancer.
- Riku.- I respect her
who has that aspect.
Okay, here’s your ice coffee.
Minami-kun. Grandma saw me a while ago.
Chiyomi... She was found by Grandma again?
You are Takagi-kun, right? Thank you.
Thank you for worrying about Chiyomi like that.
- Thank you for the coffee.- That was quick.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
Oh, Minami-kun.
- Sorry I stayed long.- It's okay.
Your grandma gave me energy.
- Well then, excuse me.- Oh, okay.
It's okay now, One-inch Princess.
I'm sorry we talked so long.
It's been like this whenever Ricchan comes here.
But, since she comes with gifts, I feel okay about it.
So long now.
We couldn't tell them after all.
That's because I started talking like that. I'm sorry.
It can't be helped. I'll bet Chiyomi had a reason to tell a lie.
Yeah.
But, should we have told them anyway?
That Chiyomi hasn't been attending the workshop?
Where in the world is Chiyomi?
What do you mean by that?
Hey, what do you mean by that?
You know, I used to get jealous of Noboru. He was smart and good-looking.
- Right.- He won the national Kendo championship.-Yup.
Imagine how it was to have a neighbor like him.
- On top of that, his wife was Emi-chan.- Yeah, Emi-chan.
When we were in high school,
- we used to ride a train to go see Emi-chan.- That's right.
Everyone was talking about her then.
But, that bastard Noboru...
Come on! You too have a cute wife.
Let me tell you something. Men are romantics.
We want to keep our sweet and sour memories.
That's right.
Oh.
Welcome back.
You're back, Ricchan.
Where have you been? It's been so busy here, but I couldn't get in touch with you.
I was at Obachan's (auntie) next door.
You were acting silly, saying "Emi-chan, Emi-chan" when we have a situation about Chiyomi.
Hey, stop that. We have customers. Talk about it later.
Later when? I know you're going drinking at night.
I got it. Don't talk about it now though.
Then when? When can we have a serious talk?
Chiyomi... she hasn't been attending the workshop.
What? Then, where is Chiyomi?
Have no idea. Why don't you find her?
You have no idea? It's about our child!
You are so quick to lose it like that. I can't take it anymore.
Oh, hey.
That "Obi" is looks good, too.
Oh, that's right. I have tasty "yokan" (Japanese sweet made of red bean paste)
I'm going to cut some, so wait a minute.
Hey.
Oh, Minami-kun.
What are you doing? I told you not to get around.
Sorry.
Yes.
There are so many guests today.
This is our chance. Come here.
- But, Grandma will...- Ha?
Yes.
Oh, Asuka-chan.
Hello. Is Oni-chan (big brother) here?
He just went out, but I'm sure he'll be back soon.
- Why don't you come in and wait.- Yes.
Come on in.
Oh, Shuichi, you were here.
Oni-chan...
Asuka-chan.
I need to talk to you.
W, wait a second...
Ah.
Minami-kun no KoibitoMy Little Lover
W, wait, Asuka-chan.
What's wrong?
Oni-chan, you know where Onee-chan (big sister) is, don't you?
Eh?
Are you concerned about something?
Well, no...
It's fine... you can go.
Eh?
We can have Yokan later.
Onee-chan is using this tablet to send emails right?
Eh?
I'm sorry.
When I came over the other day, I saw it.
What?
The Email sent box was open.
Ouch!
Ouch...
The email was Onee-chan's address.
Asuka-chan... that is... well...
Onee-chan used this, right?
It's impossible for her to not use this.
Please, Oni-chan, if you know where Onee-chan is, can you please tell me?
Our home is a mess because Onee-chan isn't there.
Asuka-chan...
You knew that Onee-chan didn't go to the (dance) workshop, right?
She's horrible...
Asuka-chan.
Chiyomi has her reasons.
But, she just can't say anything right now.
She's suffering too.
She struggling to figure out how to come with smiling.
So, can you...
can you wait just a little bit more?
Oni-chan, does that mean
you guys are... having a relationship?
Eh?
If you you two are talking about things that you can't tell parents or family...
Isn't that what it means?
Oni-chan?
Chiyomi is...
protect Chiyomi right now.
Right now, Chiyomi needs me.
Sorry for not saying anything until now.
I...
liked you...
What?
I liked you, too.
But forget it. Sorry.
I believe you.
Sorry to bother you.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
Minami-kun.
Chiyomi.
Are you okay? You look like a defeated soldier.
This is... well...
What should we do now?
Grandma totally believes in your existence.
We can't fool her much longer.
Sorry...
Oh, by the way, I found out that Dad never proposed to my Mom.
Ha?
Minami-kun no KoibitoMy Little Lover
I know.. I get it.
- Right?-Yeah.
You know, when I married her
- I quit my favorite heavy metal music.- Yeah, you did.
- And, I worked physical labor, and saved money...- Yeah...
I opened the store.
- I'm selling Zakka (Various Goods) and flowers there.- Yeah, you did.
I've been working hard!
Yeah, you are... You sure are!
- I haven't had an affair either.-You're great. So great!
I could never do that.
Sure, sometimes, I may look at other women and get a weird smile.
- You mean Emi-chan!-Yeah, it's Emi-chan!
But I can smile like that because...
because I love my wife.
I get it!
Yes, this is Izakaya (Japanese bar) Gantaro.
Who is this? I can't hear you very well.
That's right. That's something women just don't understand.
Chiyomi-chan? Are you really Chiyomi-chan?
Hey, it's Chiyomi-chan.
Why don't you get Etsu-chan. Tell her Chiyomi-chan is calling.
You're right.
Is this Chiyomi?
Dad.
You idiot!
Where are you? Is it true you are not at the workshop?
Where are you wandering around?
I am just wandering around... I can't tell you where I am though.
But, just like you tried to make your heavy metal dream come true
I am also struggling right now.
How do you know about that?
I know... that for mom and for us, you quit playing heavy metal music and
you worked really hard for us.
Is this room wired?
- What?- Wired?
- Is there a bug?- What?
Of course not.
But...
Dad, are you listening?
Yeah.
I know that you are working hard for Mom and for us
that you are always thinking about us.
I am really, really grateful.
Yeah.
But, Mom is...
Mom is much more girlie than you think.
Even now, she loves you very much.
I think she gets insecure not knowing how you feel.
She's like that, but
you be surprised how girlie she really is.
She's a girl.
Even now, she wants to believe that
you didn't marry her just because you had me.
She wants to believe that you got married
because you two were attracted to each other.
Um.
So,
So, please put your feelings in words.
In words?
Yeah.
Dad, that is so important for a girl.
I got it.
Thank you.
Bye.
W, wait, Chiyomi.
You... I think you are misunderstanding...
so let me say this.
Your Dad...
Your Dad did not marry your Mom because we had you.
It's because
I loved, and loved her a lot, and that's why I married her.
Even now.
I love your mom.
I've fallen for her.
Yeah.
Ritsuko...
Hey Dad... what's wrong?
Chiyomi, I forgot about something important.
No, actually, it's something I've been wondering for a while...
Eh? What is it?
Putting my wishes through these alstroemeria flowers.
I'm sorry for
not being able to say this until now.
Thank you so much for being with someone like me
for the last 18 years.
Will you...
Will you marry me?
No... please stay by my side forever.
What wish did you
make on this flower?
The language of flower for alstroemeria is
"Hope for the future"
"Self-sacrificing Love"
Look forward to being with you.
Stop it.
I rushed over, so look at what I'm wearing!
I accepted your proposal looking like this? Oh no.
Chiyomi's call.
Chiyomi? Chiyomi?
- Mom-Chiyomi.
I'm happy for you.
Chiyomi, thank you.
Chiyomi? Chiyomi!
What happened?
She hung up.
Oh boy, what's with her...
Well, but it turned out okay.
Chiyomi-chan was worried as well.
She is such a good kid.
To celebrate, why don't we have another round?
I'll prepare some feast.
How did... Onii-chan?
Get closer... get closer.
Ok, I'm going to take it.
You look stiff.
Where is Asuka-chan?
Oh? Where is Asuka-chan?
Where did she go?
- We're about to take a picture.- Okay.
Oh, Minami-kun!
I brought him over.
It's better to have a bigger crowd.
He finally proposed to Ri-chan after being married for 18 years.
Let's take a picture.
Ok. Here we go.
What? A picture?
Oh I see. I wish I could be in the picture.
Ok, Ok...
Hey, why don't you get in the picture?
Eh? But...
Here.
I was shocked since you took me out of the pocket.
But because of that, you were in the important picture.
I know... but
if anyone noticed...
It's fine. No one will notice.
But...
Don't worry. Even if we're busted,
I'll take responsibility and protect you.
What do you mean by protect me?
What the word means.
No... I don't want to misunderstand.
That's not what he meant...
But... What should I do?
I can't stop being excited.
♫ It's mixed in with the Thank You's ♫
♫ I'm just little bit worried♫
♫ I wish our time together will continue on ♫
♫ Even though I'm about to cry♫
Onee-chan, where did you go?♫ I hope that this moment ♫
♫ which we call happiness will continue forever♫
♫ I hope something will change ♫
♫ That will be our story ♫
It's so pretty.♫ I hope my wish will come true♫
♫ When I look upon the sky ♫♫ I saw something twinkle ♫
♫ It's a sweet and small story♫♫ That spreads in my heart♫
Eh?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Little Lover Team @Viki
♫ A casual ♫♫ encounter ♫
♫ gave me this great beginning ♫
♫ Everyday ♫♫ I was with you ♫
♫ I was slowly loving you ♫♫ more and more ♫
♫ When we walk shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ It is like the moon in the sky ♫
♫ You are right here ♫♫ but even if I stretched my arm ♫
♫ I won't be able to reach you ♫
♫ I simply love you ♫
♫ You are always in my heart ♫
♫ I just want to be honest and ♫♫ tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Forever and ever ♫♫ Please ♫
♫ Be with me ♫
♫ I wish our days last ♫
♫ Forever ♫
~Preview~Episode 8: A Blue Fairy
I found something cool!
Chiyomi...
You can't run away, Fairy-san.
A Fairy?
Thank you... and...
Good bye.
Chiyomi!
Mom doesn't like me.
That is not true.
Any mom loves her own child.
Fairy-san!
Do you want to know your mom's true feelings?
Minami-kun no KoibitoMy Little Lover