Huh...
He's a pretty good swimmer.
Azure Waters
Well, better get moving.
Oh, sorry about that.
Did the smoke get to you?
His skin is unusually cold...
even for someone who's been swimming.
Yuuta?
Yuuta!
What is it?!
Excuse me. What happened to him?
I'm sorry. I think it was my fault.
He must have breathed in my cigarette smoke.
Mommy.
You certainly caught a lot again today, didn't you?
All right, let's get ourselves home.
Um...
Was there something else?
From what I saw just now,
that boy is quite the swimmer.
But does he happen to have
difficulty with running?
So what if he does?
And is he always very thirsty,
perhaps even unusually so?
Mushi-Shi
What is it that you're getting at?
Of the many strange symptoms
noted in mushi-shi records, this boy exhibits several:
low body temperature,
a delay in speech,
and, the rarest, webbing between the fingers.
And what about it?
If you're looking for trouble—
Presuming their cause to be mushi-related,
I have medicine that can mitigate his symptoms.
Surely, you've noticed that these differences separate your son from other children.
It no doubt worries you.
He's swimming?
Even in his sleep?
Your boy is afflicted with an Uko, or "Rain" mushi.
Separately, each Uko is too tiny to be seen by the naked eye.
But often, they mingle with the rain
and flow into rivers.
There, they come together
and form what resembles a big blue fish...
and flow into the sea to breed.
Their offspring mingle with water vapor from the sea
and then fall as rain on mountains and rivers.
They lead a rather simple existence.
But on occasion, an Uko may get left behind while the others continue onward,
and to avoid being eaten, it may take up residence in a larger creature, such as a salamander.
And in extremely rare cases,
even a half-drowned human may become its host.
Although the person survives from nearly drowning,
they often display symptoms like your son's,
and forcibly removing the Uko is impossible.
One can only hope for a flash flood.
Uko sometimes leave their hosts to try to ride
the flood's turbulent waters and reach the sea.
But there's no telling when that might happen.
For now, first things first.
Give him this medicine, and watch over him.
Yuuta?
Yuuta!
How many times have I told you not to come here at night?!
You had another dream about water, didn't you?
Yeah...
Mommy!
My, you caught a big one today, didn't you?
Over here.
Got it!
What do you want?
You should get lost.
I heard that kid's body is as cold as a fish.
He can't be human.
Gross...
Here...
What now?
Wow... That thing is huge!
Lots. Over there.
Let's play together!
That way!
You suck!
Huh?
Hey, your body's not really all that cold.
You're right...
Where did you hear that from, then?
No idea.
Hey, Mommy?
Yes?
Where does the river come from?
It comes from a valley deep in the mountains.
Where does that water come from?
It comes down from the clouds in the sky.
Then where do the clouds in the sky come from?
Hmm...
Oh, yes. They're born from the sea.
The sea?
That's where this river goes.
It's a place with lots and lots of water.
Lots?
How much is that?
Hmm...
Well, I've never seen it either...
but I've heard that there's water as far as the eye can see.
Wow...
So the sea, the river, the rain,
and the clouds are all the same thing?
That's right.
They may look different,
but they're actually all the same.
I see.
What's wrong?
Nothing at all.
Yuuta!
Cut it out.
Hey.
You look well.
Oh, you're that old guy with the smoke.
"Old"...
Well, it seems you're fine with the smoke now, though.
Hmm... I guess so.
It appears that the medicine is working.
It is.
His body is much warmer now.
And before, he used to want nearly
two whole liters of water every day,
but now, he only wants about seven-tenths as much.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you so much.
May I have more of the medicine you gave him?
First, I must caution you that this is about as much as you can ever hope from it.
After all, the mushi is still in him.
Since Uko do not typically choose humans as hosts,
it's likely that its ties to him are not that deep.
However, in the cases with salamanders,
after only a few years, the hosts become one with the Uko and vanish into the waters.
As you well know, this mushi is rather troublesome.
I see...
But he's going to be okay, isn't he?
Probably.
We should be able to use the medicine to keep his symptoms at bay.
If that's enough for you,
I can come back again with more of the same medicine.
Well, I'll give you a discount.
Yes. That's enough for me.
Old man—
Don't call me that.
When will you be back?
Hmm...
Early autumn, probably.
See you then.
And don't drown anymore.
But I never drowned.
Liar.
You must have forgotten.
Hey, Yuuta!
Okay, see you later.
Yuuta? Hurry inside.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Are you thirsty?
You can't go to the river!
I have to go.
What are you—
Wait!
Yuuta!
Yuuta, where are you?
Ginko!
I heard there's been a lot of rain here lately.
If it keeps raining, there may be a flash flood.
While it's not without risk,
if we succeed, we may be able to extract the Uko from him.
If you'd like to try, I'll help you.
I'm sorry.
You've got to be strong.
But... if we manage to do this,
you'll finally get to be like the other children,
and the other villagers will be able to accept you.
Please stay still!
It's not safe.
I have to...
I have to go now.
What are you talking about?!
Stop!
Absolutely not!
I'm not going to let you go!
Yuuta.
Wake up.
It's morning.
Yuuta, please say something.
Mommy...
Thank goodness!
Mommy, what's wrong?
Even though the rain was so scary before,
it's not scary anymore.
Yes, you're right.
Did the Uko leave?
Hey, Mommy?
I'm thirsty.
Okay.
The river's all muddy now,
so let's go to the well near the mountains.
He's still thirsty.
Is the Uko still in him?
What is it?
Something's wrong.
He's burning up.
Let's try to give him some water.
Yuuta...
Yuuta!
Yuu...
Where...
Where did you go?
Where are you?
Hey, Mommy?
Where does the river come from?
It comes from a valley deep in the mountains.
Where does that water come from?
It comes down from the clouds in the sky.
Then where do the clouds in the sky come from?
They're born from the sea.
The sea?
That's where this river goes.
It's a place with lots and lots of water.
Why did he...
He told me earlier that he'd never drowned before.
It was you who drowned in the river, wasn't it?
Yes.
It happened about ten months before he was born.
The current is strong today, for some reason.
I wonder if it rained a lot up in the mountains...
When I came to, I was on the riverbank.
But my husband...
His body was found at the bottom of the river.
Before long, I found out that I was with his child.
I felt so grateful that our child had been safe within me.
Just one more push!
Keep at it!
Almost there!
Taki...
I'm so sorry...
When he was born, his body was ice-cold.
But...
he was still alive.
Even though everyone was afraid of him,
I was so happy.
And even though he may not have been normal,
he still managed to live this long.
So why? Why did this have to happen now?
Some say...
an unborn child, floating within its mother's womb,
is closer to a creature of water than to a human.
Back then, that may have been why your son became the Uko's host.
Then, as he continued growing within your womb,
they became so intertwined
that they became inseparable.
This is... This is all my fault,
for becoming possessed by such a creature.
The day you almost drowned,
the only reason your son survived was that the Uko happened to save you.
Otherwise, both of you would have died.
But he lived.
Right here, by your side...
he lived.
So the sea, the river, the rain,
and the clouds are all the same thing?
That's right.
They may look different,
but they're all actually the same.
Yuuta, where are you now?
Are you in the river?
The sea?
The rain?
What's wrong?
It's not scary anymore.
You're right.
You're everywhere.
Azure Waters
Lightning's End
"Lightning's End."