And we broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we sewed
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
Like I used to
Hm?
The Valley of the Welling Tide
Huh?
Mom! That guy came back to life!
What are you saying?
You know he wasn't dead.
Are you feeling all right?
Where am I?
It seems your leg injury had weakened you
and caused you to pass out.
My husband found you and carried you
back to our home last night.
I see.
Where is your husband?
I'd like to thank him for saving me.
He went to till our land on the mountain slopes.
He won't be back until tomorrow.
No need to rush me!
I'll get you something to fill you up right away.
Thank you!
It's like I've entered paradise.
Don't hold yourself back. Eat your fill.
Ow!
Well, if you insist.
Was that a green field of rice I just saw?
Nah, couldn't have been.
It's the middle of winter, after all.
Is that the sound of a hoe?
Is someone outside tilling at this hour?
Good morning.
Oh, hello, Ginko.
Is your leg better already?
Yes, thanks to you.
Your husband hasn't returned yet?
Well, he came back around dawn,
but he left again right after breakfast.
He's in the fields out back at the moment.
I didn't imagine it after all.
What's going on?
Is it possible spring came without my realizing it?
Can't be.
Man, don't tell me I'm actually still out there
freezing to death and this is all just a dream.
Oh, hey.
Feeling better already?
Even so, you probably shouldn't push yourself.
Yeah...
You saved my life.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
You've had a rough time, so feel free to rest here as long as you need.
I'm in your debt.
You know, these rice paddies are very impressive, especially given the time of year.
What's your secret?
I don't have any.
I just work on them nonstop.
He gives off a sweet scent...
So you didn't do anything special?
Nah.
I've got a lot of endurance.
I can work day and night without feeling a bit of fatigue.
I consider these rice paddies as the fruits of my labor.
This scent...
Is it kouki?
No, not quite.
What was this scent, again?
Honey, I made tea.
All right. I'll take a break, then.
Would you like some help?
Huh?
Oh, no.
You should be taking it easy.
Are you the husband's father?
Yeah.
Then I take it that his mother is...
That's correct.
She passed away a long time ago.
You lost her about a year after she gave birth to your son, correct?
How did you know that?
And the circumstances of her death were strange, weren't they?
I happen to be a mushi-shi, you see.
It's not easy for me to say this,
but I believe your son may be under the influence of mushi.
Are there other details you'd care to share with me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
If my hunch is right,
the lives of both your son and your daughter-in-law are in danger.
Mushi-shi or not,
I won't have you saying anything untoward to my son.
If you're going to repay our kindness by doing us harm, please leave.
Please don't ever tell him.
Huh? Come, now.
You didn't finish your vegetables again.
But...
You want to become tough like your dad, don't you?
You'd better clean your plate, then!
That's more like it. Attaboy!
Mom, can I have more?
Oh, look who's suddenly eager!
Really? You're a mushi-shi, huh?
So what's this important thing you have to tell me?
You have to get more rest.
You've gone far beyond your body's natural limits.
I'm grateful for your concern, but I'm fine, really.
I've been this way for as long as I can remember.
You can barely get a good night's rest, right?
Yeah...
My body gets restless when I try to sleep.
I'm back out in the fields before I know it.
Although you're likely unaware of it,
it's a mushi that's responsible for all this.
You're wrong. It's my free will that's responsible.
Before, this place was just a desolate, empty valley.
I've toiled for years to transform it into this.
I worked day and night, day after day...
I'm the one who made the valley into what it is today.
I wanted a better life for my family.
I wanted to make sure they'd never suffer.
All of this came from what I wanted.
Would you still want it if you knew it was built on the sacrifice of your mother's life?
What?
That's enough!
I already told you not to say anything to him.
It's in his own best interests to know.
That is not your decision to make.
Don't interfere any further
with this family, or this valley.
Houichi, are you going to
till the fields on the slopes again?
Yeah.
I want another paddy ready to go by spring.
What you heard earlier today... Is it bothering you?
About Mom?
After she gave birth to me,
she grew weaker and died, right?
I feel bad for you, Dad.
I'm the one who took Mom from you.
That's exactly why I have to keep working.
Houichi!
I apologize for stepping over the line earlier today.
It's fine.
Here.
This is a mushi purge.
Should there come a time when you feel it's necessary, feel free to use it.
You were right before.
I don't have the right
to take away this valley's prosperity.
I'll be leaving in the morning.
Thank you for taking care of me all this time.
Honey?
You should come inside soo—
Honey!
Dad!
Are you okay?
Are you in pain at all?
No.
I see.
Well, you should stay and rest awhile, at least.
No need. I just got careless.
You're overreacting.
Honey, you're working too hard!
I'm fine, really!
Houichi!
Take a seat over there.
There's something I have to tell you.
Would you all mind giving us some privacy?
I need you to take this tale to heart.
I'm here now, Houichi.
You must be hungry again.
Chiyo, you're still unable to produce milk?
Yes...
It's probably because I haven't been able to feed you properly either.
Back then, the valley was flush with new immigrants,
so everyone was barely scraping by.
No one could afford to share their milk with us,
and we were at our wits' end.
What are we going to do?
If we don't find Houichi some milk soon...
I wonder what that is.
What a sweet smell.
Huh? Look!
That pond is pure white.
It's sweet.
You suckled on it with single-minded intensity.
And the following day...
Honey!
Chiyo finally started producing milk.
Maybe that white water was some kind of medicine.
Thank goodness.
I'm so glad.
But we never found that white pond again, no matter how much we searched.
You drank your mother's milk and grew steadily.
However, almost as if in counter to your growth,
Chiyo's health deteriorated.
Are you all right?
Your face looks really pale.
I'm fine.
And I'm producing a lot of milk, too.
Then, one day...
Ouch!
What is it?
It's... breast milk.
How is this possible?
I sought out doctors far and wide for answers,
but not one of them believed me.
Then, around the time you were to be weaned...
Honey?
Hm?
Please don't ever tell him about my illness... okay?
I want him to be happy,
so he mustn't know the truth.
Chiyo...
I would've liked to have watched over him,
but I don't think I'll be able to.
What are you saying? Don't be silly.
He'll be all right, now.
Thank goodness.
I'm so glad...
Chiyo...
Hey!
Stay with me, Chiyo!
Chiyo!
It was tragic.
Yet even with her last breath,
your mother wished only for your happiness.
So my body grew this strong
because I suckled the blood of my own mother.
What caused you to do that
was a Chishio, or "Milk Tide" mushi.
The Chishio is a parasite
that seeks out a newborn to be its host
and then turns the bodily fluids of the newborn's mother into milk for its own nourishment.
As the host matures,
it starts to exude a particular scent
that promotes the growth of nearby plants.
The Chishio then pushes its host
to neglect sleep and keep eating,
focusing on building its own strength.
Once its host collapses from exhaustion,
the Chishio leaves its host
and ensnares yet another infant.
So these rice paddies were all thanks to the mushi...
Of course, you're the one who actually cultivated them.
If or when you decide to take the mushi purge,
just let your dad know.
I cannot give up this power.
I'm no longer an infant who needs someone to protect him.
Now I, too, have a family I must protect...
even if it means I must use
the same power that killed my mother.
Sorry, Mom. I only ever bring you pain.
Thank goodness.
I'm so glad...
Chiyo, he's become a fine father.
Milk turns to blood,
nourishes the earth, and then returns to it.
Thus,
the earth is imbued with a living, welling tide.
Several years later,
the valley came to endure
the first of several harsh winters.
Hey, it's lunchtime.
All right!
Good. We're hungry.
But even now, the valley
echoes with laughter and joy.
The
Valley
of
the
Welling
Tide
The
Depths
of
Winter
"The Depths of Winter."