They seem strange and alien.
Primitive and peculiar,
they are unlike any flora or fauna known to us.
Since time immemorial,
men have feared these misshapen entities,
which came to be known as "mushi."
Mushi
And we broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we sewed
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
Like I used to
Yuri!
Where are you?!
Shigeru!
Over there.
She's been taken by the mountains.
Mud Grass
He's going to take a look at our warts.
He's just a mushi-shi, though.
Wouldn't a doctor be more helpful?
Hmm...
When did these begin to appear?
Everyone started to get them three days ago.
They make the legs go numb,
and they're very painful.
Everyone's having a hard time.
Someone must have gone into the mountains.
No wonder we're all infected by death.
"Infected by death"?
Four days ago, one of our fellow villagers died.
According to our customs,
we must put our dead in one of the swamps in those mountains
and leave them there.
Within just seven days,
even their bones vanish completely, leaving behind only their clothes.
It is our belief that the dead return to the mountains.
For those seven days, however,
our customs also dictate
that it is forbidden to enter the mountains.
According to legend,
a villager long ago violated that rule
and returned from the mountains
with a pestilence that ravaged the entire village.
Now, we're all afraid the same thing has happened.
These must be Mukurosou seedlings.
It's a mushi that decomposes corpses
and turns them into mud, down to the bones.
When a live animal steps on them, it inadvertently spreads them.
Other animals that step on the spread seedlings become their hosts.
The villagers' legend matches these details.
That confirms it.
All right. Please allow me to try this.
It fell off!
The wart just fell right off!
And the numbness in my legs is gone too!
Ah, here they are.
Now to just sprinkle salt on the "grass" itself...
Um...
Oh, do you need some medicine as well?
Can you please take a look at my uncle?
No matter how many times I pull them out,
they grow right back.
When I touched them, they spread to my hands.
The medicine has no effect.
This is a very different case from the others.
Are you the one who went into the mountains?
Yes.
The one who passed away was my younger brother.
I took his son, and we went up there to pay our respects.
Why risk violating custom?
All this time, I thought it was just an old wives' tale.
Ten years ago, my daughter went missing.
When we checked the mountains, we only found her clothes.
Everyone said it was the mountains that took her.
But the more I thought about it, the more I realized that
no one who went into the mountains back then got sick.
That's why I thought it would be fine.
When you saw your brother's body,
was it in the process of "returning" to the mountains?
Yes.
I want to see Dad.
Leaving him in the mountains
all alone like that is just too mean.
You're right.
Let's go say good-bye to him one last time.
What's this stupid grass doing on him?!
Get off!
Dad really has become part of the mountains.
This grass is continuing to live on in Dad's stead.
Come now, let's head back.
You're all alone now.
Hey, would you like to come live with me?
You can even think of me as your father. How's that?
Come, let's go home.
Don't cry anymore.
Ever since that night,
I've had this grass growing from my legs,
and it keeps on growing.
That's strange.
According to records, there have been others who developed
symptoms after stepping on a body that had turned to "mud."
However, all of them were able to be cured by medicine.
So what's different in this case?
Is it because he was related to the deceased?
Can't be. If that were the cause,
the nephew would have the same condition.
Something else must be afoot.
They intentionally went to the body's location
and stepped on the "mud."
If it got on them only when they went to pay their respects...
If I may ask, how did your brother die?
Sousuke, please go outside for a bit.
He fell from a cliff.
He must have landed badly,
because by the time I got to him, he was already...
He was always fond of me.
We were very close.
I took his death hard.
Is my uncle all better now?
Not yet. There are still a few things I need to figure out.
What about you, though?
Don't you want me to treat you too?
No, that's okay.
This grass is with me in Dad's place.
But doesn't it hurt?
If you ask me, I doubt your dad
would have wanted to cause you pain.
Anyway, I guess you need more time to think about it,
so I'll just leave the medicine with your uncle.
Use it when you're ready.
Hey, what sort of relationship did your dad and uncle have with each other?
Dad loved my uncle.
When I was little, he used to tell me lots of stories about their adventures together.
But in the last few years,
Dad didn't mention him at all.
Brother.
Brother, I need to talk to you.
What is it, Shinobu?
You look so serious.
You know you can tell me anything.
Brother!
I'm so sorry!
Yuri's death...
It was all my fault.
I didn't know she was there...
and I crushed her under the cart.
Brother!
I just couldn't bear to tell you...
so I took her to the mountains.
I'm sorry!
Brother...
I'm so sorry.
Now I have a son of my own.
Every time I look at him, what I did haunts me.
I don't know how I could do such a thing—
Brother...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry...
Stop it!
Stop it already.
You're dead!
Or are you still alive after all?
Listen, Sousuke...
A long time ago, I did something truly unforgivable to someone.
So if something should ever happen to me,
please don't hate anyone for it.
Don't look so sad.
You know that all of us return
to the mountains someday, don't you?
So there's nothing for you to worry about.
After some thought, I came up with a hypothesis.
In any case, I'd like you to hear it out.
Growing on your legs is a Mukurosou, or "Corpse Grass" mushi.
Although its most common form resembles mud,
it reacts to the scent of death from a dead body,
and it sprouts like a plant.
Those who step on its seedlings become its hosts.
It may try to sprout from the living,
but it never grows past those "warts."
In your case, however,
it is reacting as though you are dead.
One possible explanation is
that the scent of death is clinging to you.
Just what are you insinuating?
I have no intention of pursuing
this line of inquiry.
But if I am right,
if you somehow cleanse yourself so that no scent of death remains on your body,
the medicine should work.
If what I've said is relevant at all, you should try it.
That is all I have to say.
Did you kill Dad?
Where did you get a crazy idea like that?
I heard everything.
I overheard your conversation with the mushi-shi just now.
And did you tell anyone else about what you heard?
No.
I won't tell anyone.
Dad told me not to hate anyone.
And you've been really good to me, Uncle!
But why?
What made you do such a terrible thing?
Back then, I simply couldn't control my rage.
But even if I had managed to control it that day,
I'm sure it would've ended the same way eventually.
I bet you'll kill me one day too...
My legs!
Sousuke—
Hurry—
Help—
Ugh!
What the heck did I just step in?
You should watch where you step.
In the end,
you couldn't make it back to the mountains...
Mud Grass
The
Tree
of
Eternity
"The Tree of Eternity."