And we broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we sewed
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
Like I used to
I can hear thunder rumbling in the distance.
Whenever lightning approaches, I feel restless.
Come...
This way.
Lightning's End
I'm sorry.
Mother, I'm sorry!
Mother!
I'm scared!
Please help me!
Mother!
Hm?
That must be it.
Is something wrong with that tree?
I heard it's been struck by lightning multiple times.
It must trouble you and your family.
So I thought there may be an underlying cause.
What kind of a cause?
Although that tree is magnificent,
there are other large trees in its vicinity.
Therefore, it's possible that it's been struck by lightning so many times
because other factors are involved.
For example, it may be inhabited by a mushi.
A mushi?
Yes.
I am Ginko, a mushi-shi.
So would it be possible for me
to see the tree in your backyard?
Please wait here.
I must ask my husband first.
Seems there aren't any in this tree.
If that's the case...
has anyone in your household been struck by lightning?
Come in, Reki.
Now then, would you mind showing me your abdomen?
There it is.
Whenever there's thunder and lightning,
does it start to feel hot around your navel?
How long ago was he hit by lightning?
The first time was five years ago,
under that tree.
Since then, he's been hit about three more times...
all while he was under that tree.
It's a miracle he survived.
Indeed.
I see.
As I suspected, the cause is a mushi.
It is?
It is a Shouraishi,
or "Lightning Summoner" mushi.
Typically, it hovers in the sky
and eats lightning to sustain itself.
However, its larvae sometimes fall
to the surface when lightning strikes.
After a Shouraishi larva falls,
it is unable to return to the sky on its own.
It may therefore hide in a nearby tree hollow,
or if a person is nearby,
it may enter his body through the navel
and hide there instead.
While it remains in its host's body,
it discharges electricity
and calls lightning down to it.
It does so in order to eat the lightning and eventually emerge as an adult.
I see.
Since the Shouraishi eats lightning,
the host may be struck by lightning,
but he does not usually die as a result.
However, if it continues to happen,
it will eventually prove fatal.
When there is lightning, it would be best if he hid in a nearby cave of some sort.
I often tell him to go into the cellar,
but he refuses to listen.
Well, there are ways to extract the Shouraishi from him.
We would simply need to make
an infusion out of his umbilical cord.
If it's all right, may we use it to help him?
Oh, but I'm not quite sure where I put it...
Shino!
Why are you always like this?!
This is Reki's life we're talking about here!
Find it immediately!
Okay—
It's fine.
I don't mind it.
Reki, please return to your room for now.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm certain she has it somewhere around here.
Can you wait here for her?
Now then, I must get back to work myself.
If it's not too rude, I'd like to ask a personal question.
Are your wife and son related by blood?
Yes.
My wife seems to struggle
with how to relate to our son.
However, she did give birth to him.
Mother.
Mother!
Please help me!
I don't want to go through
with this arranged marriage.
There's someone else I wish to marry!
Mother?
Mother!
Shino!
What is the meaning of this?!
I don't want to have this child.
No matter what,
I'm sure I won't love him.
Come inside.
It's not safe up there.
Reki?
What are you looking at?
The clouds.
How's it look?
Do you think any of them are thunder clouds?
Nah...
Yeah, you're right.
It's fine weather.
So, are you always on the lookout for thunder clouds?
Yeah.
Well then, why don't you ever try to run away from the lightning?
Aren't you scared?
I am.
But I like it.
It's strong, and it's beautiful too.
Neither Father nor Mother look me in the eye.
But the lightning does. It always comes right for me.
Still, you can't predict the time when it might kill you.
That doesn't matter.
It would have been better
if I'd never been born anyway.
Did you find it?
It's nowhere to be found...
I must have been careless and thrown it away somehow.
There are other means.
We can even open him up to remove it.
However, I'm not certain
your son will allow us to do that.
It's because he's angry at his mother...
for being this way.
That's why he has lightning strike right in front of me...
He is punishing me.
And why shouldn't he?
I'm his mother,
and yet I haven't shown him any real affection.
Still,
I just don't know how
to love him.
I wonder what's going on here.
He is punishing me.
Is that really what he's doing?
Is that really why he sits up there,
on that tree, and calls lightning down to himself?
Hey, buddy!
You should stay away from that tree!
It attracts lightning!
Huh?
Oh, right.
But it's sunny, so it should be fine,
don't you think?
The clouds are already forming, though.
Clouds around here get huge in no time.
So just be careful.
Hey, let's get going.
Right.
Knock on wood.
This is...
Have you ever asked him why he waits for the lightning
specifically on top of that tree?
I already know the answer.
There's another possible explanation.
That tree, specifically, poses the lowest risk
of others' being harmed by the lightning that strikes him.
It is also relatively far from your home,
so the house is always safe from the lightning.
At the same time, however,
it's close enough for him to rush to
as soon as he notices lightning approaching.
Moreover, whenever the villagers hear thunder,
they know to stay away from that tree.
You're saying...
you never once considered that possibility?
He still hasn't gotten back yet.
Do you have any idea where he might have gone?
No.
He may intend to call the lightning down elsewhere so that I cannot interfere.
Are there any other places
where it may be easy for him to do so?
An open area with few people, for instance.
There is a meadow on the outskirts of the village.
Let's go.
We have to stop him.
What are you doing?
You've got to come too.
He wouldn't listen to me anyway.
You're the only one who can stop him.
It has to be you.
Come back.
Why?
You might die.
I don't care.
Come on, you've got to be more direct with him!
Tell him that you want him to live!
I can't.
No matter what,
I can't bring myself to think that way.
Mother—
Okay...
Let's die together, then.
In my next life,
I'm sure I'll be born as a mother who can properly love her child.
He protected you.
Yes.
And yet you still...
I don't know.
After that,
their son was taken in by a relative.
Perhaps that was the path this particular mother and her child had to take.
Lightning's End
Mud Grass
"Mud Grass."