Wait!
Oh, there's my mom.
I'd better go.
First one out.
Oh, me too.
Bye, Akane.
See you tomorrow!
Who's there?
Why don't we play togeth—
Lingering Crimson
The sun is setting.
I'd better head home.
But where am I?
Mushi-Shi
I'd better hurry home.
Good grief.
The days are already getting so short.
Hm?
Are you sure this is the right way?
Don't you fret.
This way's just fine.
How reassuring.
So, Granny, why were you out there in the first place?
About that...
I wish I knew.
Hey!
Where are you, Granny?
Granny?
Mikage!
That's my husband!
Hey, Youkichi!
I'm over here!
Really, I cannot thank you enough.
I wasn't quite sure what I'd gotten myself into, to be honest.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
My legs aren't what they used to be, you see.
I can't make it that far into the mountains anymore.
If you hadn't met her when you did,
I just don't know what might have happened.
We may not have much to offer,
but please, at least rest here before you go.
Thanks.
Still...
it concerns me that she doesn't
know why she ventured out there.
It's not the first time.
She's been doing it quite a bit lately.
Some days, at dusk,
usually when there's a beautiful sunset,
she'll say, "I'm going home,"
and then she'll try to leave.
Oh?
I've heard that, in rare cases,
people start saying things
like that as they get older.
It's almost as though they
temporarily regress to their childhood.
Even if not consciously, she may be
trying to return to her childhood home.
Well, she and I are both
getting on in years, to say the least.
It's only natural that we're
starting to show our age.
There you go again,
treating me like I've gone senile.
I didn't say anything untrue, did I?!
I still work much harder than you, you know.
Why, you can't even cook rice on your own.
What would you do without me, huh?
Get off your high horse already.
If you hate being called senile so much,
then quit acting like it!
We have company!
Don't raise your voice in front of our guest!
Look who's talking!
Ah, so you're a mushi-shi?
Oh?
We used to have one here, remember?
He helped us out when our baby had convulsions and when our rice fields became diseased.
Oh yes, that's right.
You sure this will make my knee better?
Yes.
Huh... it does feel better.
Really?
I'll treat it again tomorrow morning,
and then it should be completely cured.
That's terrific news.
I'm in your debt.
Hey, Ginko.
It's about Mikage.
If someone doesn't remember her past at all,
is it possible for her to remember her childhood as she gets older?
It's hard to say, without knowing more.
I see.
Your wife has no memory of her past?
Yeah.
One day a long time ago,
she just suddenly showed up in our village.
It doesn't usually cross my mind anymore.
Still,
whenever I remember that day...
honestly,
I can't help but wonder what it was all about.
Wait!
Bye, Akane.
See you tomorrow!
Hm?
Akane.
Hey, You.
You haven't gone home yet?
I'm waiting for my dad to get back from the fields first.
Ah, okay.
Well, make sure you get home before it gets too dark, okay?
Okay.
Bye.
Yeah, see you tomorrow!
Good evening!
Have you seen my daughter, Akane?
No...
Youkichi, have you seen her?
Akane!
Akane?
Who... are you?
None of us ever saw Akane again.
What's your name?
What village are you from?
What's wrong with her?
How ominous.
Maybe she's the child of a demon or something.
So you're saying Akane was eaten by a demon?
Shh!
Quiet.
Before long, Akane's father volunteered to take her in.
If you think about it,
you have to feel for the poor girl.
Yeah...
She's trying so hard.
That new girl never comes and plays with us.
She's no fun.
What?
You'd better quit pretending to be Akane, you hear?
It's not like I want to do this either, you know!
But Dad gave it to me, so what choice do I have?!
I have to wear it!
H-Hey, Mikage!
Eventually, we accepted Mikage as one of us.
And after some time,
she and I were married.
We raised our children together.
We grew old together.
After spending our lives with each other,
I was sure that even our bones would be buried together.
But since she started saying, "I'm going home,"
I feel like I can't be so sure of that anymore.
I must sound crazy.
It's possible that she may remember where she's from one day.
If or when she does, I wonder if she'll want to go back there.
At dusk, one person vanishes, and another takes his place...
I've heard of this happening before.
It's sometimes due to an Oomagadoki, or "Great Witching Hour" mushi,
which only appears in this world at dusk.
A person who has been engulfed by it
will appear at dusk as a shadow
without a physical body.
Then, if someone else steps on that shadow or if the shadow steps on them,
that person will trade places with the shadow's owner, becoming engulfed by the Oomagadoki in exchange.
At least, that's the assumption.
After all,
those who have appeared in such a manner have no memory of their pasts,
which means there's no real proof.
So you're saying... Akane traded places with Mikage?
But then, what happened to Akane after that?
No way of knowing.
However, it's possible she traded places with
someone else in the same way and is living elsewhere.
Can't you figure out where she may have reappeared?
It is said that the Oomagadoki exists in a different world from ours.
No one can tell when and where
our worlds may become connected.
I see.
Then I hope Akane's found happiness somewhere too.
Hey, I'm bored of this game.
Let's play cat's cradle instead.
Sure.
Hey, why don't we play shadow tag together?
Huh?
Who... are you?
Thanks to you, my knee's all better.
That's good to hear.
Come to think of it, there are others in the village who have similar problems with their legs.
Do you think you could see to them as well?
You can stay here another night too, if you'd like.
Well then, I think I'll take you up on that offer.
Mikage, I'm going to go catch some fish for Ginko.
Okay.
But don't push yourself too hard just because your knee's better.
I know.
I'll be back by evening, all right?
All right.
Be careful!
Whoa!
Something weird just came out of my knee!
But it feels a bit better now...
How about my husband—
This is just a bruise.
Hey, I'm back.
I got a big catch to—
Mikage?
My wife! She's gone!
It's nowhere near sunset, though.
You sure she didn't just step out for a bit?
She took the lantern too!
Maybe she finally remembered where she's from,
and...
Where... am I?
There's no one here.
The sun is always setting here.
So lonely...
It's so lonely here.
I'm scared.
I bet... this is that shadow's fault.
This is all because that shadow stepped on mine.
Bye.
Yeah, see you tomorrow!
Who's there?
Why don't we play togeth—
This is all because that shadow stepped on mine.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Akane.
Could that be her?
Mikage?
What happened?
Did you remember everything?
So you were just going to leave without saying anything?
Do you really want to go home that badly?!
That's not why at all.
From the bottom of my heart, I was so happy.
Meeting Dad and you made me truly happy.
But it shouldn't have been me.
I... sacrificed Akane.
I wanted to trade places with her,
so I stepped on her shadow.
I... I took everything from her.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry I took Akane from you.
You don't need to apologize to me.
I was happy too, you know.
I've been happy all this time.
And it's thanks to you.
Come now, let's go home.
Let's go back to our home.
Some years later,
an epidemic took Mikage's life.
It's said that the two lived happily together until she passed.
But then...
Akane?
It's you, isn't it, Akane?!
It's me, Youkichi!
Why are you still in that thing?
I see...
You probably couldn't step on someone else's shadow.
You always were such a gentle, kindhearted girl.
I'm sorry.
I married the girl who stepped on your shadow.
Do you think I'm a terrible person?
Do you hate her, to this day?
Then please, just step on my shadow.
Please!
Akane, you have to come back!
Akane?!
Where are you going?
Wait!
Don't go, Akane!
Hm?
Where are you from?
Akane?
O-Oh my goodness!
Hey!
It's Akane!
Akane's finally come back!
Lingering Crimson
The Hidden Cove
"The Hidden Cove."