And we broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we sewed
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
Like I used to
In the mountains, toward the end of winter,
a deep, quiet, whisper-like sound may be heard.
Hm? Shouldn't be long now.
It heralds the awakening
of the mountain's springtime mushi.
It is the sound of the quiet voices of the
mountain lords discussing when to have the awakening.
The Depths of Winter
Damn.
I was hoping to cross this River of Light
before the mushi awaken...
but it sounds like they'll come earlier than expected this year.
Newly awakened, hungry mushi are such a pain to deal with.
Looks like I won't be able to make it there just yet.
It wasn't particularly urgent anyway.
I'll just hole myself up here for a few days.
It's still pretty cold...
but by the time I wake up, spring should be here.
I wonder if the coast is clear yet.
It's oddly quiet, though.
Huh?
What the hell?
Damn.
Did I misread the signs somehow?
Just what is going on here?
The snow should have thawed by now.
The wind-whistling Oroshibue are still here...
though I guess they don't look like they're at their full midwinter strength.
There's no snow left on the next mountain over.
Does it get more sunlight than this one?
Hm?
That's...
Those Oroshibue are migrating.
They're going back north.
The flock here isn't joining them yet?
Huh?
I doubled back somehow.
I've been heading downhill the whole time,
so why am I still walking in circles?
The mountain has been sealed.
There was nothing amiss on the mountain when I arrived, though.
Damn.
Well, that explains why winter mushi
like the Oroshibue haven't migrated yet.
What in the world happened here?
I should go ask the mountain lord.
I... can't hear his voice anymore.
Even the mountain's Mugura are nowhere to be found.
Maybe I'll try using kouki to summon him.
On second thought,
I don't know exactly what's happening here,
so I'd better not.
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Hm... Who's the lord here?
Map of the
River of Light
Serpent
Lord
Well, I'm sure I'll run into him if I follow the stream.
I'd better get to it right away.
It's not just the lord I can't find.
There's not a single beast in sight.
But now that I'm taking a closer look,
there are signs of landslides throughout the mountain.
They must have happened
during the typhoons back in autumn.
They did a lot of damage.
Did the lord seal the entire mountain
and force it to hibernate
so that it could heal its wounds?
But when in a weakened state, hibernation can just as easily kill as it can save.
In the next mountain over, it's already spring...
but this one has yet to awaken.
From the looks of it, this mountain is at death's door.
And if I don't find a way out of here,
I may share its fate.
Hm?
Something over there was watching me just now.
The water here somehow isn't frozen over.
Hm?
The mountain lord!
Hey!
Hey, Mountain Lord!
Just how long do you plan on keeping the mountain sealed?
Shouldn't you just give up now?
It's already spring everywhere else!
Hm?
What's with them?
They're flocking together.
They're heading toward me!
What's with this swamp?
It's bottomless!
What is this place?
It seems like mud,
and yet I can breathe.
Everyone's asleep down here?
There's kouki bubbling up from the bottom, too.
So everyone's been here healing themselves the whole time.
I see now.
So the mountain wasn't dead after all.
Thank goodness.
I'm glad.
It's... finally spring?
Hm?
The Oroshibue are still here, though.
My kouki...
Hey, stop that!
They're finally migrating.
The mountain is no longer sealed.
Huh?
Crap. It's starting.
Damn.
The mushi tobacco's probably ruined now too.
Either way, I'd better hurry.
I made it out.
That was easier than I thought it'd be, though.
Maybe it's because the mountain's not back to its full strength?
Or is it possible that the
mountain lord restrained the mushi?
In any case, I can't believe I lost everything, including my kouki.
Then again, it did go to helping those weakened Oroshibue migrate.
Wait a minute.
Did he let me into the mountain...
just to get at my kouki?
So, was all that...
orchestrated by the mountain lord?
No matter.
It's spring, now.
Winter departs.
The mountains laugh.
The meadows awaken in splendor.
Mushi-Shi         The Next Chapter
Second Half Scheduled to Air This Fall