They seem strange and alien.
Primitive and peculiar,
they are unlike any flora or fauna known to us.
Since time immemorial,
men have feared these misshapen entities,
which came to be known as "mushi."
Mushi
And we broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we sewed
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
Like I used to
We can't take much more of this.
Yeah.
When will it finally rain?
Would you like me to divine when the rains will come?
Huh?
Worry not.
You will be blessed by rain in two days from now.
Rain!
It's raining!
Hey, bring the jugs out! Quickly!
Her divination came true!
The rain's here!
Hooray!
Cloudless Rain
Water that soaks not into the earth but instead creeps along its surface
is but an illusion.
Though you may pursue it,
you will never reach it.
Praying for rain, are they?
Unfortunately,
the weather seems unwilling to provide it.
Oh, hello.
Do you know of any watering holes around here?
I need to replenish my supply.
Then you should spend a few days here.
The rains will soon come.
What?
She smelled of rain.
Worry not.
The heavens will soon bless us with rain.
Thank goodness.
We're saved.
Teru!
I'm glad you came.
Yasu...
Now, Miss Teru.
Please rest at my place.
Let us hold a banquet tomorrow.
You're all welcome to attend.
I'm a traveler passing through.
Could you spare me some water?
Sorry. We don't have enough right now.
But it will rain soon.
How do you know?
Whenever that girl foretells rain, it rains.
She has never been wrong.
Oh?
That's rather curious.
Huh?
Look. There's a big puddle.
That's a mirage.
No matter how fast you run,
you'll never catch it.
Really?
Hey, let's try anyway.
Huh?
If you really want to.
Hey, Teru! Wait!
I'm digging a well there right now.
The one in the village always dries up during summer.
I guess I can take a break once the rain is here, though.
I'm sure.
Will you go away again when that happens?
Yes.
Why?
You'd rather travel around all by yourself instead of settling down here with me?
I've told you already.
I don't plan on living in any one place.
Then at least come by more often.
I can't do that, either.
Why not?
I'm sorry.
Hey.
You decided to stay?
Yeah.
I'm curious to see how you'll make it rain.
I only came here to foretell the rain's arrival.
Do you think anyone is capable of causing the rain?
No normal person could.
Of course.
Anyone able to do that
would no longer be human.
Teru, rain!
It's finally raining.
Blessed rain!
An epidemic's broken out.
It's all because of this ceaseless rain.
When will this rain... finally end?
Ryou!
Stay with us!
No!
Ryou—
Why did this happen?
I want to howl and cry,
but I can't even shed a tear.
Your aunt has agreed to take care of you for a while.
No!
I want to stay here.
We have no more food.
Please be brave.
Once things improve,
you can live here again.
What horrible rain.
Wasn't that girl's home village devastated by rain?
If this keeps up, we'll suffer the same fate.
It's as though she brought the rain with her.
The village is back to normal!
No way. How can that be?
I don't know how this happened to me.
All I know is that I have no home to return to
and no place I can make my own.
I don't even have tears I can shed to accept that fact.
We only have food from our stockpile,
so it's nothing special, but please help yourself.
Shouldn't you save the celebrations until after the rain comes?
People don't want to wait anymore.
Is today too early to hope?
Yeah.
Hey, Miss Teru, do you think it'll be much longer?
I'm sure it'll come very soon.
I wonder what's wrong.
Normally it would be here by now.
Still no rain.
What could be the problem?
This isn't good.
I'd better finish the well soon.
Elder! Please let us talk to Miss Teru!
What's going on?!
It'll rain very soon.
How many days have you been saying that for?!
We've used up all our water!
Hey!
We have an emergency!
It's Yasu!
Yasu!
Hang in there!
Can anyone spare a little more water?
No... That was the last we had.
Miss Teru!
The rain! When will it rain?!
Te... ru...
It'll be fine.
I'm sure it'll rain soon!
No...
Not again! No!
The rain's here!
It's raining!
Rain!
It's finally raining!
Yasu, just wait.
We'll bring you some water right away.
Ah...
Thank goodness.
It's beautiful.
Leaving already?
You don't look too happy,
even though it rained just like you wanted.
Did you still need something from me?
I noticed something while watching you over the past few days.
Even in this heat, I haven't seen a single drop of sweat on you.
I'm guessing you can't shed tears either.
You're right.
Sometimes, I wish I could.
So, have you ever caught something you shouldn't have been able to?
Something I shouldn't have been able to catch...
Hey!
Teru, wait!
Look! That puddle isn't running away!
What?
See?
I'm almost there.
So?
Where's the puddle?
Huh?
What?
Told you. It was a mirage.
But it was right here.
You must've imagined it.
Yeah...
Come on. Let's go home.
Okay.
The mirage...
That is one form of the Amefurashi, or "Rainmaker" mushi.
They normally hang suspended in air like fine water droplets,
but they fall to the ground once they gather enough moisture to cause rain to form.
Then they return to the air as the water evaporates
and gather rain again.
But when the land is stricken by drought and there is no moisture in the air,
they pool near the ground's surface
and take on a mirage-like appearance.
Aside from the fact that they are alive,
they are essentially a natural phenomenon.
We call such mushi "drifters."
They wander without a purpose.
When you came in contact with them,
they took over the moisture within your body.
And now they continually rise from you, gathering rain.
Then...
They did all this?
I want them out of my body at once.
I've had enough of this.
There's no treatment for drifters.
You can only wait for their lifespan to reach an end.
But...
When will that be?
I don't know.
But if it's taking longer for the rain to appear,
it may mean that they are weakening.
It's nothing to despair about.
This rain of mine...
has claimed the lives of many people.
Today, I almost killed again.
You will have to shoulder the burden of those lives.
But you were not at fault,
and neither were the Amefurashi.
It was just an unfortunate twist of fate.
Still, you've already figured out a relatively good way to coexist with the Amefurashi.
I'm sure it's not all bad.
Teru!
Thanks!
I owe you my life!
Come again, okay?
Promise me you will!
Once the rain stops
and I can shed true tears again,
I will put down roots.
Until then,
I will continue to drift like the clouds
with the rain by my side.
Ah, thank goodness.
I feel alive again.
What a strange rain, though.
Maybe, but it's beautiful all the same.
Cloudless
Rain
The
Wind
Raiser
"The Wind Raiser."