mata sonna kao wo shite
There you go, making that face again,
kuchibiru kamishimete
biting onto your lips.
yowasa wo kakushiteru kedo
You're hiding your weak side,
sono hitomi no oku
but deep in those eyes,
uzukumaru kimi ga
I can see you cowering.
honto no kokoro nara
If you had a true heart,
omotte, naite, hito yonde, fuwande
you would care, cry, call for someone and worry.
nande itai no mottenda
Why are you holding onto the pain?
boku ni sotto azukete yo
Share some of it with me.
sugu ja muri to omou no naraba
If you don't think it's possible right away,
sukoshi zutsu de ii
you can do it slowly, bit by bit.
tsubasa no nai bokura kitto
We don't have wings,
tobenai toki mitsuketeru dake
but I'm sure we're only finding times that we can't fly.
koe no kagiri kimi wo yobu yo
I'll call for you to the limits of my voice
mayowanai you ni
so that you won't get lost.
fuwari kokoro maiagare
Soar up to the sky with your gentle heart,
ano kaze ni nosete issei erose
ride on that wind, and get it all at once.
Ever since I was small, I would...
sometimes see strange things.
A kappa?
Water...
W-Water...
Later.
Natsume-kun, don't forget, okay?
Eh?
"Eh?" I'm talking about tonight's test of courage.
Do I have to go?
I don't really feel up to it.
I asked you to come because we didn't have enough people.
Aren't you being a bit anti-social?
Or is it that you have something more important to do?
That's not it.
The old school building is going to be demolished next week,
so this year's test of courage will be the last one.
Make sure you come, since we'll be waiting.
During the dark nights of summer, there are more lurking Youkai.
Will I be okay if I do the test of courage?
You're here, Natsume.
Is that your cat?
Why'd you follow me?
Come on, it looks fun.
You need me as a bodyguard for times like this, right?
That may be true, but...
Did that cat just make a strange noise?
N-No, you're probably just imagining it.
Oh...
Make sure you don't talk in front of anyone!
You're a real handful, you know.
What'd you say?
All right, I got it already.
The instructions are to go in pairs,
write your names on the wall at the end of the second floor hall,
and then come back.
We haven't set up people to scare you, so you can be scared safely.
We'll decide the pairings through a lottery
ranging from one to twenty.
All right. Everyone draw a lot.
There's a story about this building.
In the past, there was a god of fortune who loved humans,
and he would appear as a child to play among the villagers.
However,
there was a greedy merchant who wanted more riches,
and he locked him up in his cellar.
After that, the merchant would reap huge profits because of the fortune power.
But in the dark cellar, the God of Youth mourned and mourned,
grew to resent people,
and eventually became an evil spectre.
The merchant's house became bankrupt,
and eventually this school building was erected on this spot of bad luck.
The God of Youth lamented that he became an abominable Ayakashi,
and even now he wanders this place, or so they say.
Why are you telling me this?
No real reason.
So everyone drew one?
Then show your lots on the count of three.
One, two...
Huh? We're missing one lot.
There were twenty numbers, though.
We have one person too many.
Calm down!
It's probably just someone who came and didn't bother to sign up!
The committee did this on purpose, didn't they?
No!
Maybe someone took two.
Is there something here?
I'm not sure.
Is it the thing Sasada talked about earlier?
Well, if he's here,
then he must be strong enough that even I can't sense him.
It's getting interesting.
Sensei.
It can't be...
It can't be the Book of Friends' fault, can it?
We should've been paired up with girls.
Yeah.
It's run-down, but it kind of makes you feel sad that it's going to be demolished.
We haven't seen anyone else yet.
That's true, now that you mention it.
Which way were we supposed to go, again?
What are you doing here alone?
What about the password?
Hey, are you okay?
So, you've awakened.
Where have I seen that face before?
Never mind that.
Not only have you defiled me, but now you're stealing my home?
People are such selfish beings.
Natsume-kun!
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Wait!
What's wrong?
There's no one there.
Y-Yeah...
Where's Nishimura-kun?
Hey, did you see my partner, Kitamoto-kun?
I took my eyes off of him for a second, and then we got separated.
No.
The first group still hasn't returned either.
Where is everyone?
I see.
Everyone was taken away by him.
Who were you calling out to earlier?
Hey, Natsume-kun,
you can see them, can't you?
You do strange things sometimes.
You're startled when there's nothing there,
and talk when there's no one there.
Hey, what can you see?
Are they things not of this world?
If that's the case,
I'll keep it a secret from everyone.
Could you help me?
So, what is it? You can see them, can't you?
Nyanko-sensei!
So she wasn't an Ayakashi.
Probably.
It's no use.
It seems like there's a barrier around the entire school building and we can't get out.
Could you go and see if there's a way out somewhere, sensei?
What?
What a slave driver.
W-What's with that look?
This form will be more convenient.
Something...
Something like a dodgeball came flying at me...
Who's this?
Ah, well...
She's part of the dodgeball club,
and came to get her ball that got away.
So we had a dodgeball club.
All right, I'll go take a look around.
I'll look for a way out,
so relax.
She seemed pretty conceited.
Sh-She's the captain, after all.
It's a person! A person!
It's a person!
So, people are still around here.
We must report this to Shigure-sama.
Hey, you low-level punks!
Our eyes met!
Run away!
When I was in middle school,
there was a district event, so I participated in a test of courage here.
I cried and ran around the school building,
and when I got home, I realized I had lost something precious.
In a panic, I went back to the school to search for it alone.
I was scared and disheartened,
but I couldn't find it at all.
And then...
What have you been doing this entire time?
I-I dropped my charm.
It's very precious to me.
Find it quickly and leave immediately.
And after that,
I didn't give up and continued to look for it for a while,
but I couldn't find it.
And just when I was about to give up...
Hey.
Is this it?
Yes! That's it!
Thank goodness...
I had almost given up.
This is a memento from my mother.
What's that stick, though?
An impure being such as myself cannot touch anything that is pure.
You're done now, aren't you?
Hurry up and leave.
Impure?
What are you talking...
about?
With the way he talked and his presence,
I wondered if he was a ghost.
So I looked it up and learned the story about the God of Youth.
I also learned that "impure" meant "defiled."
After that, I would come here every day.
I wanted to thank him, and so called for him to come out.
And I wanted to say, "You're not impure!"
But in the end, he never showed himself to me.
That's why, if you can see things like that,
I want you to help me.
This place is going to be demolished,
so I thought that this was my last chance.
Sorry for saying it like that earlier.
It's okay.
You really can't see them, Natsume-kun?
Yeah.
I see.
No one came back.
Where is everyone?
Natsume-kun?
Where are you?
Nyanko-sensei!
His servants are low-level, but he's a surprisingly big one.
His name seems to be in the Book of Friends as well.
The Ayakashi's name is Shigure.
Shigure...
He's a real bother, so let's leave now.
It's a powerful barrier, but I can manage to break it.
Get on.
What about everyone?
Forget them.
You don't like people, right?
You have nightmares about your childhood, don't you?
That...
That may be true...
But even so, we can't leave them alone.
I want do things that I can do!
Natsume-kun!
Where are you?
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah.
The underlings are gathering.
He's on the roof, Natsume.
Yeah.
The roof?
Who's "he?"
Do you mean...
Him?
Where are you going, Sasada?
To see him!
He's on the roof, isn't he?
Well...
I want to tell him!
I want to tell him how precious this charm is,
and how happy I was that he found it!
Watch out!
Take Sasada somewhere safe, sensei.
I'm counting on you!
What are you planning to do?
Make him stop.
I'll return his name and persuade him!
Na...
Natsume-kun!
Oh? I was wondering where you had gone,
and now you've come to me?
Please stop this.
I refuse.
I hate people.
They turned me into this abominable Ayakashi,
entered this place as if to make fun of me,
and even tried to steal my home.
I will never return them.
I want to see your parents crying and mourning.
There's a girl who wants to see you.
The other girl left inside the building.
Why won't you see her?
You wouldn't understand, Natsume-dono.
You're Reiko's relative, aren't you?
You could have just used the Book of Friends to make me obey.
What a kind person.
Then that makes things easier. I will return your name.
I don't need it!
I don't need liberation!
I no longer need that defiled name.
You should have just burnt it up!
Shigure-sama, I return your name.
A name that belongs to a kind being who helped support a girl's heart.
Come out! Please!
That noisy one has come again.
I want to thank you! I just have to!
I just wanted to drive her out quickly,
and so I helped her.
Day after day,
and never giving up...
What a bizarre being.
If an impure being such as myself touched her...
Would I really defile her?
Please! Just once!
I see, just by meeting her once...
Please!
You...
You won't come again...
Thank you, Natsume.
I will go.
I'm tired from being unreasonable.
Shigure-sama!
Sasada said...
She said that you're not impure!
She said you saved her!
You don't need to believe in a person's words,
but at least believe in Sasada's...
Natsume-kun!
Are you okay?
I am sorry, child.
Only you and Reiko did not fear me for being impure.
Thank you.
Natsume-kun.
Sasada.
Natsume-kun, last night, I...
Yeah, what happened?
Everyone was on the roof and sleeping.
Ah, yeah.
Sasada, the truth is that for a moment, I saw Shigure-sama touch you.
I saw your hearts trying to connect.
I wonder if you felt anything.
hi no tsukurishi zora ni
On that day where the sky was ablaze,
sashikomu hitosuji no hi
and rays of light were piercing through,
yuudachi no ameagari ni
the evening rain had stopped,
kizuku natsu no nioi
I noticed the scent of summer.
hishimeku hikari ga terasu
Among the crowded, shining lights,
omoi ni mimi wo sumaseba
I turned my ear to my thoughts,
kikoeshi tomo no omokage
and I could hear traces of my dear friends.
natsu yuuzora kawarirazu
The summer evening sky
azayaka na sugisarishi hibi
and the vivid passing days were just the same,
kokoro no mama warai atta
and so I laughed; it was just like
ano natsu no omoide yo
my memory of that summer.
The one ticket that Reiko-san left behind.
If you visit the old train station, there is one Youkai there.
What a slow-looking guy. We should just leave him alone.
I am Santou.
Please! I want to see Mikuri!