mata sonna kao wo shite
There you go, making that face again,
kuchibiru kamishimete
biting onto your lips.
yowasa wo kakushiteru kedo
You're hiding your weak side,
sono hitomi no oku
but deep in those eyes,
uzukumaru kimi ga
I can see you cowering.
honto no kokoro nara
If you had a true heart,
omotte, naite, hito yonde, fuwande
you would care, cry, call for someone and worry.
nande itai no mottenda
Why are you holding onto the pain?
boku ni sotto azukete yo
Share some of it with me.
sugu ja muri to omou no naraba
If you don't think it's possible right away,
sukoshi zutsu de ii
you can do it slowly, bit by bit.
tsubasa no nai bokura kitto
We don't have wings,
tobenai toki mitsuketeru dake
but I'm sure we're only finding times that we can't fly.
koe no kagiri kimi wo yobu yo
I'll call for you to the limits of my voice
mayowanai you ni
so that you won't get lost.
fuwari kokoro maiagare
Soar up to the sky with your gentle heart,
ano kaze ni nosete issei erose
ride on that wind, and get it all at once.
The human hat is still here.
It's all white and pretty, like snow.
No one will pick you up?
Want to come home with me?
It's so pretty.
I'm going to show mom.
Mom...
No, I can't be crying when I'm going to become a man!
From now on, I have to live on my own!
I'm going now, Touko-san.
Take care and have fun.
I will.
Takashi.
Yes?
You're going to the hot spring reserve on your study trip, right?
Yes.
Ah, I'm sorry for having you pay for the trip.
You don't need to worry about that.
I just have a small favor to ask of you.
There's a pottery in the mountains near the hot springs,
so could you pick up some tea cups for me?
I received a call saying that they were almost done.
Could I ask you to do this?
Of course, Shigeru-san.
What a weird laugh, Natsume.
Sensei, when did you get in?
Isn't it natural for your bodyguard to follow you?
That's true, but...
So, what are you so happy about?
It feels good to be asked to do a favor for someone else.
Great people will eventually meet their ruin,
much like dust before the wind.
All right, let's end the morning class here.
You have free time until lunch.
All right! What should we do?
We've got to go to the hot spring first!
Right, Natsume?
Sorry, I have some business to take care of.
Oh, really?
Ah, I'm sure it's in this area.
Ah, over there.
Hey, you weak little fox!
You're still hanging around the forest?
You're an eyesore, you useless brat!
Leave the forest, you useless brat!
Useless brat?
Leave!
Stop!
W-Who is he?
What are you doing bullying this little child?
Are you a human child?
How dare a human child look down on us!
How impetuous! I'll kill you!
Oh well.
You're a real busybody as always, Natsume.
It couldn't be helped.
Still, what a waste of time.
We have to come back again.
It can't be helped, the tea cups won't be finished baking until tomorrow.
Humans are such troublesome creatures.
They go so far just for a container for food,
yet they could just buy it at the local super market.
You're being brutally frank saying that.
A body isn't a container, though.
What are you talking about?
I hate humans,
but...
Natsume, it's going your way!
All right, all right!
Nice!
Natsume, don't sleep.
Natsume...
It bounced off you and hit me earlier.
Sorry, sorry.
I wonder what dinner will be, right, Natsume?
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Natsume laughs often,
but it seems kind of fake.
His words, his gestures, his aura,
they all seem kind of fake.
Maybe he's not really a human.
Maybe he's like me and is disguised as a human.
Maybe he's lonely like me.
He should live in the forest with me, then!
Right, mom?
Damn, I'm going back tomorrow,
and I'd feel bad if it got attached to me.
It's too late.
Shut up, sensei.
This is the worst.
We can't go get the tea cups now.
Who knows if we can even make it back to class now.
Natsume-dono.
Am I just hearing things?
Thank you.
Mom, I'm useful now.
He said "Thank you" to me.
I'm not useless anymore, right?
I'll go gather mushrooms tomorrow.
I'll gather a lot and share some with Natsume!
Oh, you're still here, you little fox?
He just doesn't learn.
We told you to get lost!
We don't need any useless brats in this forest!
You're wrong!
I'm not useless anymore!
Damn it!
I'll kill you, you little brat!
I told you to stop!
Damn him!
The one from yesterday!
Were my fists not enough for you?
Natsume-dono...
Natsume-dono!
Who is it?
Have you forgotten, Natsume Reiko-dono?
You said you would come and return my name in the spring.
Damn Reiko, she's as cruel as always.
Spring? How many springs have passed already?
You're the one who called me?
Sensei, take care of the tea cups.
Take it, Sawarabi.
It's your name.
Eh, Natsume?!
The owner of the Book of Friends?
Thank you for returning it.
The Book of Friends?
I've heard of it.
When they have their names written in it, it serves as a contract and they are then bound to the owner.
He'll take our names!
Run away!
What are they saying?
There's no way he'd take your names when he just returned one.
My name is written on it.
Please make me your follower!
I'm sure I'll be useful to you!
I don't need it.
Is it because I'm weak?
Is it because I won't be useful?
I don't want us to be bound like this.
We aren't master and follower.
Right?
I think we have a different relationship.
My, what a wonderful color.
I'm going to change.
The townsfolk introduced me to a good pottery.
Our family has grown, so I thought this was a good chance.
This is yours, Takashi.
Thank you.
It's just like that little fox said.
About what, Natsume?
It's not about whether you're useful or useless.
I don't get it at all.
It really is pretty!
I want to show it to Natsume too.
Natsume...
I want to see Natsume.
I can't be crying when I'm going to become a man!
I've already decided to become strong and to be helpful to Natsume!
Do you want to see Natsume that much?
I've heard the rumors.
You met the owner of the Book of Friends, Natsume, didn't you?
You still can't disguise yourself as a human?
If you can fill me up with fish, then I'll tell you a way to see Natsume.
Will you tell me how to see Natsume now?
What a foolish little fox.
You were tricked.
You're always alone because you're so stupid.
Natsume already forgot about you a long time ago.
Take this, little fox.
It's medicine that will allow you to become a human for one day.
Medicine to become a human?
If you want to see him, you can go see him yourself.
That's all there is to it.
That's right, I just have to go see him!
All right, I'm a fox too!
Once I go to the world of humans, I can follow Natsume's scent!
I'll be going now, mom.
I wonder if Natsume is feeling lonely being by himself.
Natsume's scent?
Natsume...
It's Natsume's scent.
I want to see him!
Hey, hey! Watch where you're going!
Where's Natsume?
Natsume?
Oh, are you okay by yourself?
Where's your mother?
I'm fine by myself.
I want to see him.
I want to see him!
Where is he?
Where's Natsume?
Natsume!
There it is!
Pull it in! Pull it in!
It's huge!
You again, Natsume?
You caught a whole bunch.
Sorry.
What are you eating?
It's Natsume's scent!
He's nearby!
I can see him!
It's all fried!
It's the landlocked masu salmon Natsume caught!
Well, well, what a fine salmon you caught!
Let's eat, Takashi.
Okay.
Yours has the skin, Takashi, so is that okay?
Yes, it's fine with me.
If you don't like anything, tell me, okay?
Shigure-san doesn't like green peppers.
He's like a kid, right?
The truth is, when I was young, I didn't like them either.
I see, so I've got a friend here too!
Here.
Let's see.
Well, this salmon is pretty good, Touko-san.
Then maybe I'll have some too.
Go ahead.
How is it?
It's good!
That's great, Natsume looked like he was having fun!
He wasn't lonely!
I...
I was the lonely one.
Wait!
So,
it was the little fox from before.
Thank you.
You came to see me, right?
You've got a cute hat.
Let's go have dinner and then I'll take you home.
I have to remember the way.
I'll go see you next time.
Okay!
You're a good kid.
When I was lonely, I was afraid of going out.
I didn't even think of doing something about it.
So,
I probably didn't notice many things.
hi no tsukurishi zora ni
On that day where the sky was ablaze,
sashikomu hitosuji no hi
and rays of light were piercing through,
yuudachi no ameagari ni
the evening rain had stopped,
kizuku natsu no nioi
I noticed the scent of summer.
hishimeku hikari ga terasu
Among the crowded, shining lights,
omoi ni mimi wo sumaseba
I turned my ear to my thoughts,
kikoeshi tomo no omokage
and I could hear traces of my dear friends.
natsu yuuzora kawarirazu
The summer evening sky
azayaka na sugisarishi hibi
and the vivid passing days were just the same,
kokoro no mama warai atta
and so I laughed; it was just like
ano natsu no omoide yo
my memory of that summer.
That person could see Youkai.
They exchanged their feelings and became important to each other.
But one day...
He can't see Ayakashi anymore?
If he is happy, then I don't mind.
Are you sure,
Kio?