Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
15 years earlier
Anno Domini 2000
Father...
Episode 12
The Value of a Miracle is...
Thanks, Shinji, you really saved
us from that rainstorm.
Where's Misato?
I guess she must still be asleep.
She's been working all
night recently.
That's right, she has a tough job.
We've got to be quiet.
Don't wake her up.
What are you doing in here?!
Taking shelter from the rain.
You guys are after me, aren't you?
Well, I'm changing and if
you peep, I'll kill you!
Shut up, idiot!
Who would want to see you
changing clothes?!
She's way too self-conscious.
Sorry for disturbing you!
Hi, how's it going?
Shinji, don't be late tonight, we're
having a harmonics test.
Right.
Did you hear that, Asuka?
Yes, Ma'am!
Congratulations on
your promotion!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
You're most welcome.
See you later.
See you!
What's up? Did something
happen to Misato?
Didn't you see her badge?
The number of lines
increased to two.
That means that she's been
promoted from Captain to Major.
Really? I didn't notice that.
Yeah, I wonder when...
Are you serious? What a
bunch of dweebs!
Haven't you got any sympathy?
Don't you know how hard it is to
foster two jr. High kids at her age?
We're the only ones who have
some human compassion.
Units 00 and 02 are both on the
edge of the contamination zone.
They've reached their limit.
Unit 01 can still tolerate a little
more though, can't he?
Lower the graph depth
another 0.3.
He's almost reached the
contamination zone.
And he's still getting these
readings? He's wonderful.
His harmonics and sync ratio are
rapidly catching up with Asuka's.
It is a talent, isn't it?
He was born to pilot an
Eva, wasn't he?
Not that he wants to.
I know he's not happy.
Test completed. Good work.
Excellent work, Shinji.
What do you mean?
Your harmonics value increased
by eight points since the last test.
That's very good.
But still it's fifty points
lower than mine!
Yes, but he increased it by eight
points in only ten days.
That's really something.
It's not so great!
Are you happy with
your little praise?
I'm going home now! Idiot!
...and here's a message for
"Mr. Waaa" of Tokyo-2.
Having your girlfriend dump you
isn't really such a big deal.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Having your girlfriend dump you
isn't really such a big deal.
Thanks.
When I was a kid, everyone lived
in dirty huts and barely had food.
But I'm not really all that thrilled.
When I was a kid, everyone lived
in dirty huts and barely had food.
But I'm not really all that thrilled.
We couldn't really afford to be
depressed about relationships.
I understand.
We couldn't really afford to be
depressed about relationships.
I'm not happy when I get praised either.
We couldn't really afford to be
depressed about relationships.
All it does is make Asuka angry.
We couldn't really afford to be
depressed about relationships.
All it does is make Asuka angry.
You should be glad your parents
are alive and you have food to eat.
I don't know why she gets so mad.
Only now in these better, peaceful
times do you have such hardships.
That bothers you?
Only now in these better, peaceful
times do you have such hardships.
That bothers you?
You got that, Mr. Waaa?
Yes.
That's because you always watch
everyone else's faces.
You got that, Mr. Waaa?
That's because you always watch
everyone else's faces.
Congratulations!
Thanks, guys!
Thank you, Mister Suzuhara.
No, no. This wasn't my brainchild,
it was this guy right here.
That's right! I, Kensuke Aida
was the planner!
Thank you, Mister Aida.
Oh, you're welcome! But it's
not such a big deal, really.
By the way, why is the
class rep here?
Because I invited her.
Right?
Rei too?
Yes, I invited her,
but that girl is one
strange customer.
Darn, why is Mister Kaji so late?
Oh, is Mister Kaji that
really cool guy?
Oh, yeah!
He's so much better than these
dweebs that it's like night and day.
It's an insult to compare
him to them.
What did you say?!
How dare you?
Is it still difficult for you to be here
in this kind of situation?
I'm okay.
I'm just not used to being with
so many people.
Why do they have to
make so much noise like that?
Your promotion...
That means someone noticed the
work you've been doing, right?
Yeah, I suppose.
That's why they're happy.
But you don't look very
happy at all.
Oh, I'm happy. I am.
But that's not the reason
I work here.
Then why did you join NERV?
Well, I don't remember. It's been
a long time since then.
That's got to be Kaji!
I came directly from HQ. We just
happened to meet on the way.
That's rather suspicious.
Hey, are you jealous?
Absolutely not.
Anyhow, I'd like to give you my
fondest regards, Major Katsuragi.
I suppose I'll have to be polite
to you from now on.
What are you trying
to say, you jerk?
It's unprecedented for both the
Commander and Vice-Commander
to leave Japan together.
I guess they must really count
on old Katsuragi here.
My father's not here?
Commander Ikari is at the South
Pole at the moment.
Nothing living can exist in the
world of death we call Antarctica.
Or should I simply call it Hell?
Nevertheless, we,
Mankind, are here.
We're living things,
and we're alive.
That's because we're under
the protection of science.
Science is the power of Man.
That arrogance is what caused the
tragedy of fifteen years ago,
the Second Impact.
And here is the end result.
This is a greater punishment
than we deserve.
This is the real Dead Sea.
Yet this is a world that has been
purified, purged of the original sin.
I'd rather live in a world where
people can live,
no matter how stained with sin.
Report from the bridge.
Telegram received from
NERV Headquarters.
An Angel has been detected in
orbit above the Indian Ocean.
The Angel appeared suddenly,
two minutes ago.
Send Search Satellite
Number 6 to that orbit.
T-minus two minutes to contact.
The target has been sighted.
That's impressive.
I don't believe it.
Satellite Number 6 is closing
for contact with the target.
Start data search.
Data transmission commencing.
Reception confirmed.
Was that an AT Field?
It's a new way of using it.
What incredibly destructive power.
That's an AT Field!
It uses kinetic energy too.
This Angel is, itself,
like a huge bomb.
In any case, the first blast missed
its target and hit the Pacific.
Two hours later, the second
shot struck there.
Since then, it has been steadily
correcting the error ratio.
That means it's learning.
An N2 air bomb had
no effect on it.
The Angel has been missing
since then.
It's probably coming here.
Yes, and next time it
may drop itself.
So, that will give us a
third Ashinoko lake?
All five Fuji lakes will be fused into
a single body linked to the Pacific,
destroying this Headquarters
in the process.
Can we reach the Commander?
It's impossible due to the Angel's
powerful jamming.
What is the Magi's judgment?
They unanimously agree in
recommending evacuation.
What will you do?
You're the one who's in
charge of all this now.
Notify all of the ministries
concerned
of this D-17 Declaration as
provided for by NERV's authority.
All residents within radius of
50km are to evacuate immediately.
Also, ask Matsushiro to
backup the Magi.
Are we going to evacuate as well?
No, but it's not necessary to
place everyone at risk.
A D-17 Special Declaration has
been made by the government.
All residents must evacuate to
their designated locations.
Beginning with the 6th
and 7th blocks,
move according to your district
chief's direction immediately.
The evacuation of the
city is complete.
The evacuation of noncombatant
and D Class personnel
by Alarm C has been completed.
Are you serious?
Yes, I am.
You'll risk all three Evas with your
irresponsible selfishness?
The chance of success is
only 0.00001%!
That's not even one in
ten thousand!
It's not zero. I just trust the Evas.
Major Katsuragi!
I'm in charge.
I have to do what I have to do,
and destroying Angels is my duty.
Your duty? You must be kidding.
This is for your own sake, isn't it?
This is just your revenge
against the Angels!
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Catch it in our hands?
That's right. We'll position the
Evas in the estimated drop zone.
You'll catch it while maintaining
your AT Fields at full strength.
What if the Angel doesn't come
down where you expect it to?
We'll be a little put out.
What if the Evas aren't able to
withstand the shock?
We'll be put out in that case too.
What's our probability of success?
God only knows. I have no idea.
If we succeed, it'll be a miracle.
It's not until we've done all we can to
cause a miracle that it becomes viable.
You mean, we've got to be willing
to sacrifice ourselves?
I'm sorry, but we have no other
options for this operation.
How can you call this
an operation?!
No, you can't really call it that.
You can refuse to do it,
if you wish.
So, are you okay with this?
Regulations say you're supposed
to write a will. Have you done so?
I don't need to. I'm not
going to die just yet.
Neither do I. There is no use for it.
Not me, either.
Again, I'm sorry.
But once this is over, I'll treat
you all to a steak dinner.
What? Really?
I promise.
Yeah!
Don't forget!
You can count on it.
I guess she thinks a steak dinner
is supposed to impress us.
Does she really think a steak
dinner will impress us?
The Second Impact generation
has really cheap standards.
She can't help it.
What was with that fake
cheer you made?
I just wanted to make her feel
a little easier about it.
Now, since she's going to treat us,
I'd better figure out where to go.
You've got to join us this time.
No, I won't.
Why not?
I dislike meat.
Because of the Angel's ECM
jamming, we've lost track of it.
Since it's impossible to calculate
the collision point exactly,
the Magi's estimated a drop
zone based on the data
that had been collected
before it was lost.
This is it.
The range is this wide?
The distance from one side
to the other is enormous.
Given the size of the
target's AT Field,
it could totally annihilate HQ by
hitting any of these locations.
Given that, we'll disperse the Evas
at each of these three points.
And on what grounds is
this dispersal based?
Intuition.
Intuition?
Yes, a woman's intuition.
How sloppy! Our miracle is getting
farther and farther away.
Misato has never won the lottery.
Say...
What?
Asuka, why do you pilot an Eva?
To exhibit my talent to the
world, of course.
You mean to prove that you exist?
Yeah, more or less.
You're not going to ask her?
I've asked Ayanami before.
My, how intimate the
two of you are.
It's not like that.
Now, what about you, Shinji?
I don't know.
You don't know?
What are you, stupid?
Maybe I am.
I suppose you really are.
Twenty minutes to estimated
time of impact.
You must all evacuate now.
I can take care of this myself.
No, this is our job as well.
That's right. We can't let the kids
risk their lives by themselves.
They'll be fine.
No matter how badly the Evas
might be damaged,
their AT Fields will protect them.
Inside an Eva is the
safest place to be.
Shinji, yesterday you asked
me why I joined NERV.
My father was a man who
lived for his research,
for his dreams, to the
exclusion of all else.
I could never forgive him for that.
In fact, I even hated him.
Just like my father.
He never took care of me,
my mother or the family.
His friends always said he was
very sensitive and delicate.
But the truth was that he was
just a weak person
who didn't want to face reality,
the reality called his family.
He was like a kid.
So I agreed with my mother when
she decided to divorce him,
because she was always crying.
He was depressed about it,
but I laughed at him because
he deserved what he got.
But he sacrificed himself
to save my life during
the Second Impact.
Then, I didn't know whether
I hated him or loved him.
The only thing that
was clear to me
was I wanted to destroy the Angels
who caused the Second Impact.
So, in order to do that,
I joined NERV.
It might be that I still hate him,
and just want to avenge my father,
so that I can free myself of him.
I mustn't run away. I mustn't run
away. I mustn't run away.
Right!
I must NOT run away.
The Target has been sighted
at maximum magnification.
Distance is approximately 25,000.
Here it is.
All Evas, start your engines.
All we have is a rough estimated
trajectory from optical sightings.
So the Magi will guide you until
the distance is 10,000 meters.
After that, you'll have to use
your own judgment.
I'm placing my trust in you.
The Angel is approaching,
distance 20,000.
Commence operation.
Here we go!
Start!
Distance 12,000!
AT Field, full spread!
Unit 02! Spread your field!
I'm doing it!
Do it now!
Our wireless communications
have been restored.
We're receiving a message from
Commander Ikari in Antarctica.
Connect him here.
Yes, Ma'am.
I'm very sorry, Sir.
My irresponsible judgment, has
caused Unit 01 to incur damage.
It was completely my fault.
That is not a problem. Destroying
Angels is the Evas' purpose.
It was fortunate that the amount
of damage was minimal.
Excellent work, Major Katsuragi.
Thank you, Sir.
And on that subject, is the
pilot of Unit 01 there?
Yes!
I've received the report.
Good work, Shinji.
Right!
Now, Major Katsuragi, I'll leave
the rest of this in your hands.
Yes, Sir.
Next station is New Miyanoshita,
New Miyanoshita.
The exit will switch to the left
side at the next station.
Now, you're going to have
to fulfill your promise.
Of course!
I've withdrawn enough I can even
pay for a full French dinner.
Although, before payday
comes along again...
Take it easy, we know
how poor you are.
This'll be fine.
And even Wonder Girl says she'll
join us for ramen noodles.
I'll have a garlic ramen
with no roast pork.
I'll have shark-fin soup ramen
with roast pork. Large!
There you go!
Say, Misato?
What?
When I heard my father's
words today,
I think I finally understood
the good part of being
praised by someone.
And I also realized
that the reason I pilot my Eva is
to hear those words from him.
That's why you're a pilot?
You really are an idiot.
To be continued...
Preview
After a simulated plug activation
trouble occurs, and Central Dogma is invaded.
NERV is forced to accept a course of self-destruction.
Next Episode:
"Angel Invades"
Next time, fan service!