Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Once again, I owe you.
You're not going to pay me
back anyway, are you?
About the materials they wanted
under Freedom of Information,
I handled it by giving them
some falsified data.
The government is proceeding
with legal action,
but that will be blocked
any day now.
So, should I do something about
that project as well?
No, judging by the material you
sent me, it would appear
that further intervention
is unnecessary.
Then, I'll continue with the plan.
Episode: 7
A Human Work
Good morning.
G'morning.
This is the way to start
your morning!
Not with coffee?
A traditional Japanese breakfast
begins with rice, Miso and sake.
Not all Japanese breakfasts,
just Misato's.
What's that suppose to mean?
By the way, who was supposed
to do the cooking today?
Now I know why you're still single
at your age, Misato.
Well, excuse me, but are you
saying that I'm lazy?
And sloppy too.
Leave me alone!
I'm done.
Are you really going to come
to school today?
Of course. It's your parent-teacher
meeting after all.
But you're so busy with your work.
No problem. This is part of my
responsibilities anyway.
It's part of your job?
Hi!
Oh, thanks for coming!
Yes, he's getting ready.
Misato, you shouldn't go
out like that.
It's embarrassing.
I know.
Good morning, Mr. Ikari.
We're taking off now, Misato!
Take care!
Come on!
How ironic.
It's good that it's getting easier
for him to express himself.
Yes? He just left. Please
stand guard over him.
There! She came!
Cool! Who is she?
Is she Ikari's guardian?
What?! He's got a babe like
that for a guardian?!
Those guys are such dorks.
She's gorgeous, truly gorgeous!
Is that so?
It's amazing someone so beautiful
could be NERV's Ops Director.
Is that so?
My mom dressed up just for a counseling session...
Thank God that Shinji's such a baby, Kensuke.
Yeah, Shinji's no rival for us!
My mom dressed up just for a counseling session...
Don't you think she's silly?
You guys don't know what a slob she is.
Man, I wish she were my girlfriend!
Yeah, and you'd have to put
up with a lot of trouble.
You just don't get it, do you,
Mr. Big Shot?
You just keep the Earth safe,
and we'll take care of Misato!
Unit 01 has achieved the
required cooling level.
Shifting operations to Stage 2.
Keeping the Earth safe...
That's what Eva is for.
Come to think of it,
just what is the Eva?
The entry plug smells
a lot like blood.
But I feel so comfortable and
relaxed here. Why?
Now that I think of it, I don't
know anything about Eva.
What's the status of Unit 00's
bio-chest components?
It was seriously damaged.
We'll have to make a new one,
even if it requires a bigger budget.
Will our job get any simpler
when we get Unit 02?
It could go just the other way.
Disposing of the dead Angels
costs a bundle.
Yeah, this place is ridiculously
under-financed,
especially since mankind's future
rests on what we do here.
It can't be helped.
"Man cannot live by Eva alone."
All those survivors need
money to live too.
Money!
So, is the Commander off
to another conference?
Yes, he's on board,
and en route now.
Thank God, a little
peace and quiet.
Excuse me, do you
mind if I sit here?
The revised budget for the
sample collection
passed quite easily, didn't it?
The Committee's main concern
is for their own survival.
They aren't stingy when their own
lives are at stake.
Yes, they used to think there
were no more Angels.
But I have more good news.
All of the permanent members
of the Security Council
except the U.S. have approved the
budget for Eva Unit 06.
It's just a matter of time before
the U.S. approves it as well.
The Americans seem to be allergic
to unemployment.
And what about your country?
We will participate beginning with
the construction of Unit 08.
The plans for the second
installation project are still viable.
However, a pilot has not
yet been found.
The Angels have returned.
We have no choice but
to defeat them.
We don't want another
Second Impact either.
You're saying that the Second
Impact wasn't...
Yes, the history texts say it was a
disaster caused by a meteorite,
but sometimes the true facts
have been concealed.
Fifteen years ago in Antarctica,
we discovered the being known
as the first "Angel".
However, in the middle
of the investigation,
for unknown reasons,
the Angel exploded.
That is the real truth behind
the Second Impact.
Then, the things we're
doing here are to...
To prevent a probable Third
Impact from happening.
That is the purpose of NERV
and the Evangelions.
By the way, the event will occur
tomorrow as scheduled.
I understand.
Good morning.
I'm going to Old Tokyo
on business.
I'll probably be back late tonight,
so have delivery for dinner.
Later.
Okay.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Abandoned Area #28
(Former Tokyo Metropolis)
It's hard to believe this used to be
the flourishing capital of Tokyo.
We're here.
Why are they having it
in a place like this?
Is the SSDF getting involved?
The Strategic Self Defense Force?
No, they're not allowed to.
I see, so that's why they can
do whatever they like.
Good afternoon, welcome
to this demonstration
of Japan Heavy Chemical
Industrial's new product.
Reserved for the guests from NERV
of Japan Heavy Chemical
Industrial's new product.
Thank you for attending.
You will be observing the offical
demonstration in the control room,
but we'll be taking your
questions here.
Yes!
The famous Dr. Ritsuko Akagi.
It is our honor to have you here.
May I ask a question?
Of course, certainly!
According to our earlier briefing,
this unit is equipped with an
internal nuclear reactor, correct?
Yes, this is one of our product's
most distinguished features.
150 days of consecutive operating
power is assured.
But from a safety perspective, isn't
incorporating a nuclear reactor
into a weapon designed for
hand-to-hand combat risky?
It's better than a weapon that
won't work for over five minutes.
But in an emergency there could
be problems with remote control.
Still it's more humane
than a system
that induces great mental stress,
and causes mental instability.
Cut it out. It just makes you look childish.
And there's still the issue
of manual control.
A weapon that cannot be
controlled is insane.
I believe that it is safer than an
extremely dangerous weapon
that can run out of control,
and go berserk.
It's like a hysterical woman!
In other words, completely
out of control!
Our pilots and technology are up
to the task of controlling it.
So, you're saying that science and
courage will tame that beast?
Are you serious?
Yes, of course I'm serious!
Because it depends on something
as vague as the human heart,
NERV has allowed the situation
to get completely out of control.
That's why the UN had to approve
a huge increae in your budget.
As a result, 20,000 people in
several countries are starving.
Of course, the actual cause of all
this is still under investigation.
Why don't you at least take
responsibility for your handiwork?
I envy you. It must be nice to be
protected by a supra-legal act.
It doesn't matter what you say.
The fact is that NERV has the only
weapon that can best the enemy.
You mean the AT field?
It's just matter of time now.
NERV's day in the sun
will not last forever.
Reserved for the guests from NERV
Damn it! Idiot! Who does
he think he is?!
That S.O.B.'s just pissed at being
cut out of the profit loop!
That god damn son of a bitch!
Damn it! Damn it!
Cut that out. Behave yourself.
He's just a show-off, begging
for praise and adulation.
He's petty, not worthy of attention.
But how did he know about
the AT field?!
How could something so
classified leak out?
Intelligence must be
dragging its ass.
We're about to start the
JA activation test.
Don't worry, there's no risk at all.
Make yourselves comfortable,
and watch through that window.
Ready to begin.
Start the test.
Discharge the power core.
Pressure levels nominal.
Coolant system circulation nominal.
Release the control rods.
The reactor has exceeded
threshold levels.
Output is nominal.
Begin walk cycle.
Walking. Forward ahead, slow.
Forward right leg.
Roger. Walk, forward ahead slow.
Balance is nominal.
Power core status nominal.
Roger.
Now, forward left leg.
Keep her steady.
It walks! Now that's something
to be proud of.
What's wrong?
This is odd. The pressure inside
the reactor is increasing.
The temperature of the primary
coolant system is also rising!
Open the release valve.
Insert the neutron-
deceleration fluid.
No effect!
The pump output isn't increasing!
Shut off the power.
Emergency stop!
Abort signal transmission confirmed.
It's not accepting it!
The radio circuit is being blocked!
It's out of control!
It can't be!
No! Oh, God! Run away!
That robot is as badly behaved
as the guy who built it.
The compression valve is
operating irregularly!
The control rods aren't working!
Possibility of meltdown imminent!
It's unbelievable.
JA's been programmed to handle
all possible contingencies!
This kind of thing can't happen!
Yet, the fact is, the danger of a
meltdown is now before us!
Under the circumstances, our only
option is to wait for it to stop.
And what is the estimated
probability of an automatic stop?
0.00002%! We'd better
hope for a miracle!
Determined efforts are better
than a miracle!
Tell me how to stop that thing!
We've tried every possible option.
No, there's got to be a last resort,
a way to wipe everything out.
Give me the password.
The password to delete all
programming is top secret.
I can't authorize it.
I'm not allowed to tell you!
Then get the clearance!
Right now!
It's me. Let me speak to
Mr. Manda in Tokyo 2.
That's right, the Director
of Internal Affairs.
Well, I'll have to delegate this
to Mr. Yasugi. Ask him.
I can't give authorization for such
an important matter on the phone.
Could you submit a
written request?
So, now I need to get
Mr. Yoshizawa's permission?
What? Yes, I've already got an
approval from Mr. Witz.
Yes... yes, okay.
The evasion of responsibility...
A written order of clearance
will be sent.
That will make this an
official operation.
We can't wait for it! Once that
thing explodes, it'll be too late!
Jet Alone is heading for Atsugi.
Time is running out.
I'll take responsibility
for this myself.
Excuse me.
Hey, Hyuga?
I've arranged it with Atsugi. Bring
Shinji, Unit 01 and the F module.
Yes, this is an emergency.
This is pointless. Call this off,
Captain Katsuragi.
Do you have any idea as
to how to stop it?
By inputting a direct
command manually.
Are you serious?
Yes.
But the interior must be flooded
with radioactivity!
It's too risky!
But if I make it,
everyone will be saved.
The hatch can be opened as
soon as our signal is cut off.
You'll be able to enter through
the back pack.
"Hope".
That's the password to delete
the programming.
Thank you.
JA is the target.
There's a danger of meltdown
in five minutes.
Therefore, we cannot allow it to
get any closer to a populated area.
Hyuga?
Yes, Ma'am?
As soon as you drop off Eva,
ascend to a safe altitude.
Affirmative.
And Shinji...
Yes.
Run alongside the target,
and place me on its back.
Then restrain the target
as best you can.
Are you going to get inside?
Yeah.
That's crazy!
I know, but there just
isn't any other way.
But it's too dangerous!
No problem.
Eva can withstand a
direct explosion.
Not that! I meant for you, Misato!
Well, I've got to give it
my best shot,
or else I'll regret it for
the rest of my life.
Target sighted.
Here we go.
Eva approaching drop position.
Docking release!
Roger!
We've caught up with it!
We've got less than four minutes.
Put me on, now!
Don't think! Just do it!
Misato!
Be careful.
Talk about hot.
This looks bad.
Stop, you bastard!
Misato! Hurry!
I'm here.
Error?
What in the hell is this?
There's no doubt! The program
must have been altered!
The power reactor is just 0.2
points short of critical!
The control rods won't function!
Guess I'll try the long shot.
Misato, get out of there!
Move! Move, damn you!
Misato!
0.1 to critical!
My God! It's going to explode!
Christ, it's all over.
Misato!
She did it!
Internal pressure decreasing!
All readings are nominal!
We're saved!
Hooray, hooray! She's done it!
That crazy fool.
Misato, are you all right?!
Misato?!
Yeah, I'm okay, not in the
greatest shape though.
You're alive! I'm so glad! You're
all right! You're really all right!
Oh, thank Heaven. I'm so
impressed! It's a miracle!
Yeah...
But the miracle was set
up by someone.
Recovery of Unit 01 is complete.
No danger of radioactive
contamination.
Except for Captain Katsuragi's
operation,
everything went according to plan.
Good work.
G'morning.
Now, let me at that shower!
Where are my bra and panties?
Good morning, Mr. Ikari!
Good morning.
I'm taking off!
Take care!
Misato is just so cool!
I thought so too, but she's sloppy,
embarrassing and lazy at home.
She's not embarrassed
about it, but I am.
How nice for you.
What do you mean?
He really is a kid.
Yeah, he sure is.
How come?
She lets you see a side of her that
she won't show to anyone else.
That means she's your family.
TO BE CONTINUED...
Preview
EVA 02 and its pilot embarked from
Wilhelmshaven, Germany for Japan.
Shinji gets confused because
of a strong-willed girl.
Next episode:
"Asuka strikes!"