Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Hey, Shinji, did you change
the soup stock?
Yeah, to dried fish flavor.
It's a gift from Ritsuko.
Too hot!
I'm sorry.
You're always apologizing! Do you
always think you're to blame?
Shinji, apologies are your
conditioned reflex
to any kind of confrontation!
I'm sorry.
Exactly like that. You're
too self-deprecating!
Now, now, that's just his way.
It's so easy to just accept his
pathetic habits, isn't it?!
But haven't you been a little
too easy on Shinji lately?
Have I?
Maybe you and Kaji have
hooked up again,
but the fact that you're happy
doesn't mean you can ignore us.
There's nothing between
Kaji and me.
Hey, Katsuragi, I've found a bar
that serves a decent drink.
How about tonight? Bye!
I've never seen anyone involved in
such an indecent relationship!
You're supposed to be our
guardian! You hypocrite!
It's disgusting!
Episode 16
Deadly Illness, then...
B-type harmonics test, all green.
Projected adjustment values
have been cleared.
You look tired, Misato.
Yeah, for a lot of private reasons.
Kaji?
Shut up!
Well, how's the Third Child doing?
Take a look.
Let me see.
I hope that knowing this will
boost his confidence.
Can you hear me, Shinji?
Misato, how were my test scores?
Yes! You are Number One!
I lost! He beat us easily.
He beat us so easily that
it's pissing me off!
He's great, wonderful, awesome,
too awesome!
The invincible Shinji!
So that makes our job a
little easier, right?
But it also means we'll have to do
our best to not be left behind.
Goodbye.
Next stop is Seisho Kabuse.
Next stop, Seisho Kabuse.
Convenient to the Bashar, used
books and video game stores...
Good.
Five minutes until evacuation of
the Western District is completed.
Target is advancing slowly at two
point five kilometers per hour.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
What's going on? The observation
center in Fuji...
Didn't detect it. It just suddenly
appeared directly above us.
Pattern Orange. No
AT Field detected.
What is this?
A new kind of Angel?
The MAGI are withholding
judgment.
Damn! A situation like this and
Commander Ikari's not here.
Can you all hear me?
I've sent you all of the
target's data.
This is all we know right now.
Approach it carefully and
observe its reactions,
and, if possible, lure it outside
of the city limits.
Two of you will back up
the other, got that?
All right, Ma'am, but I think Shinji
ought to take the point.
Well, this is a job for the
highest rated, bravest,
Number One synchro-ratio
holder, right?
Or don't you feel up to it, Shinji?
No, I can do it.
I'll show you how it ought
to be done, Asuka.
What was that?!
Hey, you two cut it out.
Isn't that what you said, Misato?
"You are Number One!"
Well, that was...
Combat is a man's job, after all.
Talk about out of date!
Unit 02 will back him up.
Unit 00 will back him up as well.
I can't believe those kids are doing
this without my orders.
Shinji's getting more manly,
isn't he?
No, I'm going to have to chew
him out when he gets back.
You might just be a good teacher.
Ayanami, Asuka, are you
in position yet?
Not yet.
You know an Eva can't
move that fast.
Not there yet?
I'll have to stop it myself.
It disappeared!
What?!
Pattern Blue! Angel confirmed!
Directly beneath Unit 01!
A shadow?!
What is this?! I can't believe it!
Shinji, get out of there! Shinji?!
Ikari?
You idiot, what are you doing?!
Misato, what's going on?!
Misato? Asuka! Ayanami! Help me!
Misato?! Can you hear me, Misato?! Misato!
Eject the plug! Send the signal!
No response! It's not working!
Misato! Misato!
Shinji!
Asuka! Rei! Rescue Unit 01! Hurry!
That idiot. He can get an A on a
test but not in the real world.
It disappeared again.
Asuka, be careful.
A shadow?
The city is sinking!
Asuka, Rei, pull back.
Bu...
Wait!
Unit 01 and Ikari are
still in there.
This is an order. Retreat.
Major Katsuragi must feel awful.
They reeled the umbilical
cable back in,
but the other end was missing.
Without power...
There's not much energy in the
internal batteries.
If Shinji doesn't waste it groping
blindly in the dark,
if he stays in the most minimal
life-support mode,
then he can survive for
sixteen hours.
Second Tank Battalion deployed.
Roger. Hold your current
positions and stand-by.
Sub laser circuit has been opened.
Transmitting data now.
Confirmed. New line
transmitting data.
The UN forces have completely
surrounded it.
Shadow status?
It hasn't moved.
It stopped spreading once it
reached a diameter of 600 meters.
By the way, is there a use for
those ground troops?
They're supposed to allow
us to apply pressure.
Oh, well.
Taking matters into his own hands,
defying Operations.
He got what he was asking for.
Just because he got a little
better score than mine,
he had to go and show me
how it ought to be done.
What a dumpkoff!
What? Are my comments about
Shinji pissing you off?
Do you pilot Eva just for the
praise of others?
No, I don't need anybody's
approval but my own!
Cut it out, you two!
Yes, he acted arbitrarily and
without consultation.
So, I'll just have to punish him
when he comes back.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
I never thought sleeping could
be this exhausting.
Still nothing but white noise.
No radar or sonar reflections at
all. This space must be too big.
It's been twelve hours since I
switched to life-support mode.
My life will end in four
or five hours.
I'm hungry.
So, that shadow is actually
the Angel's body?
Correct. It's six hundred eighty
meters in diameter
with a thickness of three
nanometers.
Sustained within that ultra-thin
space is an inverted AT Field.
Abstract mathematics defines the
region within as a Sea of Dirac.
It could be connected
to another universe.
What about the sphere?
It disappears when the imaginary
circuit of the body closes.
The object in the sky is
only a shadow.
So the black shadow that
swallowed Unit 01 is the target.
Then there's no way that
we can fight it.
The water is getting cloudy!
The purification system
is breaking down.
It smells in here.
Blood! This place smells
like blood!
No, I hate this place!
Why can't I open this lock?
Open up! Let me out!
Misato, tell me what's going on!
Misato! Asuka! Ayanami!
Dr. Ritsuko!
Father...
Please, someone help me.
A forced Eva salvage?
It's the only possibility
that might work.
We would drop all 992 existing
N2 mines into its center,
while simultaneously activating
the AT Fields of the other Evas
disrupting the circuit enclosing
the Angel's pocket interior.
If we concentrate enough power
into the same microsecond,
we might destroy the Angel and
the Dirac Sea that makes it up.
But the damage to the Eva would
be... Shinji wouldn't...
What kind of rescue
operation is this?
This operation's priority is
to recover the Eva itself.
That the body may be damaged or
destroyed has no bearing.
Now wait a second!
The pilot's life is not our concern.
If Shinji's lost, it's your fault.
Just remember that!
Why are you and Commander Ikari
so worried about Unit 01?
What in the hell is an Eva?
I've given you all the information.
You're lying!
Misato, trust me.
I'm taking command of
this entire operation.
Forward all flights to Kansai
International Airport.
Contact Air Traffic Control and the
JADF's Air Transport divisions.
The Second Impact, the
Instrumentality Project, Adam...
There are so many secrets that
I'm in the dark about.
Who's that?
Who?
Shinji Ikari.
That's me.
I am you. This self incorporates
another self.
The self has always been
composed of two selves.
Two?
Yes, the self which is observed
and the self which observes itself.
To expound, the Shinji Ikari
that exists in your mind
is only one Shinji Ikari.
There's also the Shinji Ikari in
Misato Katsuragi's mind,
the Shinji Ikari in
Asuka Sohryu's mind,
Rei Ayanami's mind,
and the Shinji Ikari in
Gendou Ikari's mind.
All are different Shinji Ikari's,
but each of them is a
true Shinji Ikari.
Your fear is of the Shinji Ikari's
who exist in the minds of others.
I'm just afraid of being hated.
You're afraid of being hurt.
Who is bad?
Father is.
The father who deserted us.
No, I'm the one who's bad.
You're always apologizing! Do you
always think you're to blame?
I'm worthless.
No, you just believe that
you're worthless.
Don't you trust your father?
I thought I hated my father,
but now I'm not sure.
Good work, Shinji.
My father called me by my name.
I was praised by my father!
Will you spend your life
regurgitating
and re-digesting those few
pleasant memories?
If I trust their words, it's enough
to keep me alive.
Even though you know you're
deceiving yourself?
Everybody does it! That's how
everyone survives.
If you will not believe that you
can change yourself,
you will be unable to continue.
This world is filled with too much
pain and suffering to keep going.
For example, you can't swim?
Humans aren't made to float!
That is self-deception.
I don't care what you
want to call it!
You've been shutting your eyes to
that which you wished to avoid.
His sister was injured
during the incident.
Who cares what the others say?!
Go away!
No, I don't want
to hear this!
See? You're running
from reality again.
No one can justify life by linking
happy moments into a rosary.
In particular, I cannot.
I've found something I can do to
feel good. Something I want to do!
What's wrong with that?!
In theory, the entry plug's
energy reserves
should be reaching their
expiration point.
The plug suit's life support system
will be getting close to redline.
Advance the schedule
by twelve minutes.
Let's do it while there's a chance
that Shinji's still alive.
Father, am I unwanted?
Father!
It was really yourself that
you ran away from.
That's right! He may be guilty
of killing his own wife.
He killed his own wife.
No! Mother was...
Smiling...
You did a good job.
Shinji, you must not run away.
Do your best.
I hate this place.
I hate this loneliness.
No...
The heating and the oxygen
circulation are already out.
I'm cold.
It's useless, the suit is
giving out too.
This is the end.
I'm tired of...
Everything.
Mother?
Is this enough?
Well, that's good for you.
Evas are in position
and standing by.
AT Fields are ready to generate.
Roger.
T-minus sixty seconds
to mine drop.
What's going on?!
Status report!
Unknown!
All meters and gauges are
going off the scale.
But we haven't done anything yet.
No way, Shinji?!
It's impossible!
Unit 01 's power level
has to be at zero.
I... Am I piloting a
thing like that?
My God, what kind of monster
have we copied from?
I know that the Evas aren't just
copies of the first Angel.
But what is NERV going
to do with them
once all the Angels have
been destroyed?
Shinji?! Shinji?! Shinji?!
Shinji?! Are you all right, Shinji?!
I just wanted to see them again.
Didn't you say you were
going to punish him?
I've never seen the Eva looking
as horrible as it did today.
Are the Evas really on our side?
They may hate us.
I think that Major Katsuragi may
have noticed something.
I see. Let her be for now.
If Rei or Shinji were to find
out the Eva's secrets,
they'd never forgive us.
You can just rest today. We'll
take care of everything.
But I'm fine now.
Well, that's good for you.
It still smells like blood.
To be continued...
Preview
Eva Unit 04 under development
in Nevada, explodes...
...during its activation experiment
along with NERV 2nd Command.
The old men of Seele modify their scenario
themselves and the Fourth Child is selected.
Next time:
"The Fourth Child."