Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
NERV Headquarters
Experiment Station-02
22 days earlier.
Commence activation.
Connecting main power
to all circuits.
Power supply connected.
Commencing activation system.
Activation voltage is approaching
critical level. 0.5, 0.2...
Rising.
Begin the second phase of the activation system.
Pilot has begun link-up.
Start system Phase 2.
Synapses inserted.
Junctions connecting.
Transmitting pulse.
All circuits are operational.
No problems with initial contact.
Power supplied to Brachial
muscles in both arms.
All nerve links checking
out normal.
Check list satisfactory up to 2550.
Prepare for third stage connection.
Clear up to 2580.
Counting down to the
absolute borderline.
0.9...
0.7...
0.5...
0.4...
0.3...
The pulses are flowing backward!
Something's going wrong
in the third stage!
Rejection occurring in the
nerve center elements!
Cease contact! Break all circuits
through number six!
Negative! The signal's not
being received!
Unit 00 is out of control!
Abort the experiment.
Shut off the power supply.
Yes, Sir!
Unit 00 has switched to
standby power!
Thirty-five seconds until it comes
to a complete stop.
It's dangerous! Stay back!
Auto ejection system activating!
Damn it!
Complete shutdown in ten seconds. 9...
Use the special Bakelite! Hurry!
8...
7...
Rei!
6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
Zero!
Rei, are you all right?
Rei!
I see.
Rei,
Beyond Her Heart
Rei Ayanami, age fourteen.
The first test subject chosen by
following the Marduk Report.
The First Child.
She is the designated pilot
for Evangelion Unit 00.
Her past has been eradicated. All
her personal records were erased.
So, what caused the accident
during the last experiment?
We still don't know.
However, we believe that
mental instability
on the part of the pilot was
a primary cause.
Mental instability? In Rei?
Yes, her mind became much more
disturbed than we had anticipated.
So, what did happen?
I don't know.
But she could have...
Did something occur to you?
No, that can't be it.
The demolition of block B-3
has been completed.
All technical department personnel
are to submit their data
to the analysis group.
So this is our enemy.
I see. Everything except the
core remains intact.
This is a perfect sample.
Thank you, this will help us a lot.
So, did you find anything new?
What the heck is this?
That's the code number for
"cannot be analyzed".
You mean, you don't know
what this is?
Correct. We do know the Angel
is composed of a type of matter
characterized by both particulate
and wave properties, like light.
But you've at least found its
power source, haven't you?
Something like that anyway.
But we haven't been able to figure
out any of its operating principles.
We've found something completely
outside our experience.
The world is filled with mysteries.
For example, take a look at this.
This is the Angel's inherent
wave pattern.
What? Let me see.
Could this be...
Yes. Although they are composed
of a different form of matter,
their actual composition,
in terms of the arrangement
and spacing of the pattern, falls
within a 99.89% match of humans.
Unbelievable, 99.89%.
We must acknowledge our limited
level of understanding once again.
Bring it down... slowly...
We must acknowledge our limited
level of understanding once again.
Okay!
We must acknowledge our limited
level of understanding once again.
Okay!
Keep going. Stop.
This is the core?
How's the rest of it?
It's pretty deteriorated. We can't
expect to use it as a reference.
That's not a problem.
Dispose ofthe remnants.
Yes, Sir.
What's wrong?
Well, nothing's wrong.
Are you aware that when you
say "nothing" that way,
it's the same as asking others
to pay attention to you?
Well, it's just that my father seems
to have burned his hands.
Burned?
I was just wondering
how it happened.
Burns? Do you know anything
about those burns?
It was before you arrived at NERV.
Unit 00 went berserk during the
activation experiments.
You've heard about that, right?
Yes.
The pilot was trapped inside.
Ayanami was the pilot, wasn't she?
It was Commander Ikari
who rescued her.
He opened the super-heated
hatch with his bare hands.
My father did that?
That's how he burned his hands.
Go, Hideko!
You lose!
You've got to treat us to
pizza if you lose!
There, go for it!
You won't make it!
Now, let's sink a shot!
Oh my gosh! Those guys
are looking at us!
Perverts!
Oh my gosh! Those guys
are looking at us!
Man, they've all got such
incredible breasts.
Suzuhara's ogling us! Gross!
Hi, Shinji!
Hey, Big Shot!
What're you looking at so intently?
Nothing!
I think you're looking at
Ayanami! Right?
No!
Oh, come on, dude. Am I stupid?
Ayanami's boobs...
Ayanami's thighs...
Ayanami's...
...calves!
I told you, it's nothing like that.
Then, what were you looking at?
You can't fool me.
I was just wondering why
she's always alone.
Come to think of it,
she hasn't had any friends since
she started here in the 7th grade.
There's just something about her
that makes her hard to talk to.
She's probably just got
a lousy personality.
You're both Eva pilots, right? You
should know her better than us.
He's right.
Well, I've hardly spoken to her.
Eva Unit 01 is now entering the
third stage cooling process.
Lower all systems to
Phase 3 in Cage 6.
The earlier harmonics and
synchronization tests were good.
All numerical conditions
have been satisfied.
Roger. Transmit the results
to Balthazar.
Roger.
Transmit the full range of the entry
plug's personal data to Melchior.
Data transmitting.
This is Melchior, roger.
Circuits connected.
Initiating third stage
cooling process.
CBL circulation has begun.
Vent liquid wastes to the second
purification system.
The protein walls are in good
condition. No problems detected.
T-Minus 1,050 minutes until the
Unit 00 re-activation experiment.
What is this?!
It's curry.
So you're still eating
this instant stuff.
Look, you're a guest, so you've
got no right to complain.
Here, Misato...
Oh, here.
Here, put all of that into this!
Are you serious?
Oh, don't you know how
good this is?
Okay...
Ordinary curry flavored instant
ramen can't compare to this!
Let's eat!
The trick is to put less hot
water in the soup.
Misato cooked this, didn't she?
Yes.
Oh, can you tell?
Yes, by its taste.
How can she make something
ready-to-eat taste so awful?
Next time, invite me when
it's Shinji's turn to cook.
Shinji, you really ought to move.
You shouldn't let one bad
roommate ruin your life.
I'm used to it now.
He's right, Ritsuko.
Never underestimate the ability
of the human animal
to adapt to its environment.
And anyway, if he does move...
Shinji, why don't you bring
me another one, please?
Right.
Shinji, why don't you bring
me another one, please?
Right.
He's going to have to go through
a lot of trouble and red tape.
He just got his permanent
security card, you know.
Oh, I almost forgot!
Shinji, would you do me a favor?
What is it?
Rei Ayanami's renewal card.
I keep forgetting to
give this to her.
Would you mind delivering it
before you go to headquarters?
Sure.
What's the matter? You're staring
at Rei's picture, aren't you?
No!
Oh, I think you are, Shinji.
Oh, come on! You're embarrassed,
aren't you?
Well, you've got an official excuse
to go to Rei's place now.
This is your chance, isn't it?
Stop teasing me!
But I love teasing you.
You always go ballistic!
Just like Misato.
I just find it strange that I know
so little about Ayanami,
even though we're both Eva pilots.
She's a very nice girl, but
she's like your father.
She's not very adept at...
Not adept at what?
Living.
Excuse me?
Excuse me, it's Shinji Ikari.
I'm coming in, Miss Ayanami!
Are these hers?
Well...
I didn't mean...
Will you get off?
I...
What is it?
Well, I mean, I was...
I was asked to, so...
What was it? The card, your card...
It's been renewed!
So I was asked to deliver it.
I didn't mean for any of
this to happen.
Ritsuko said she forgot
to give it to you.
It's true. I rang your bell,
but there was no reply,
and the door was unlocked. So...
Central Dogma is currently
open to the public.
Group 3 should proceed directly
to the fourth gate.
This is your new card. Ritsuko
asked me to deliver it to you.
I'm sorry.
About what?
Aren't you going to have a
re-activation experiment today?
Say, aren't you scared?
Aren't you afraid of
piloting Unit 00?
Why?
I heard that you were hurt pretty
badly in an earlier experiment,
so I thought you might be...
Aren't you Commander Ikari's son?
Yeah.
Don't you have faith in your
own father's work?
Of course not! How could
I trust him?
What?
Rei, are you all right?
Rei...
The pilot was trapped inside.
It was Commander Ikari
who rescued her.
He opened the super-heated
hatch with his bare hands.
That's how he burned his hands.
Rei.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
We will now commence the Unit 00
re-activation experiment.
Commence first connection.
Connecting main power supply.
Activation voltage has passed
the critical point.
Roger.
Shift format to Phase 2.
Connecting pilot to Unit 00.
Open circuits.
Pulse and harmonics are normal.
No problems detected.
In sync. All links completed.
Central Nerve System elements
are nominal.
Re-calculating, no
error corrections.
Checklist is satisfactory
up to 2590.
Approaching the critical mark.
2.5 more.
1.7...
1.2...
1.0...
0.8...
0.6...
0.5...
0.4...
0.3...
0.2...
0.1, and rising.
Borderline cleared.
Unit 00 has been activated.
Roger.
Beginning interlock test.
Unidentified object approaching.
It may be the fifth Angel.
Stop the test.
Go to first stage alert.
You're not going to use Unit 00?
She's not ready to fight yet.
What's the status on Unit 01?
It'll be ready in 380 seconds.
Engage!
Yes, Sir.
Rei.
Re-activation was successfully
completed. Return now.
The target is passing
over Tonosawa.
Unit 01 is beginning
launch preparation.
Releasing primary lock bolts.
Release confirmed.
Roger.
Removing secondary restraints.
The target is now intruding into
Lake Ashino airspace.
Eva Unit 01 is ready for launch.
Launch!
We're detecting a high energy
reaction from inside the target!
What?!
It's accelerating, and
massing upon itself!
Is it possible?
No, dodge it!
Shinji!
TO BE CONTINUED...
Preview
Shinji was saved.
But the wound
makes him babble.
Rei gives him
the cold shoulder.
Will Shinji's hope and power from all over
Japan be able to pierce through the Angel?
Next time:
"The Decisive Battle in Tokyo-3."