Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Lucky!
I'm so lucky that I can go
shopping with you today, Kaji!
What the?! Isn't this the swimsuit section?
Please allow us to announce a call for a customer.
Hey! Hey! How do you like this?
Mr. Yamazaki, your friend is waiting for you.
Easy, school girl. You're a little young for that.
You're just being an old fuddy-duddy, Kaji.
Please come to Customer Service on the first floor.
This is what's in fashion these days.
Oh, really?
I'm anxious about this school trip.
I just know we'll have a great time.
And where are you going
for the trip?
Okinawa!
We're even scheduled to
go scuba diving!
Scuba diving...
It's been three years since
I've gone diving.
Say, where did you go
for your school trip?
Well, we didn't have one.
Why not?
Because of the Second Impact.
Episode 10:
Magma Diver
I can't go on the trip?!
Right.
Why not?!
Because you're on stand-by
for combat duty.
You never told me anything
about that!
I just told you.
Who in the hell decided that?!
Me, the Operations Planning
Manager.
Hey, why don't you stop slurping
that tea, and say something!
Be a man!
Actually, I kind of anticipated
it would be like this.
And you've already given up?
How pathetic. Nothing's more
useless than a housebroken male.
Please don't talk about
me like that.
I know how you must feel,
but there's no other way.
There's always the possibility of
an Angel attack while you're gone.
It's always stand-by!
Stand-by, stand-by, stand-by!
We've always got to be ready to defend
against an enemy who may not even come!
Why don't you try to find out
where they are, and attack first?!
If we could do that, we'd
have already done it.
Look, think of this as an
opportunity to catch up.
While the rest of your
class is on the trip,
the two of you can study.
Or do you think I don't
know about these?
If you thought you had to tell me
what your test scores were,
you made a big mistake. Finding
out what your grades are
is quite simple for me.
It's ridiculous. This school's
grades are meaningless!
The old fashioned grading system
used here means nothing to me.
When in Rome, do as
the Romans do.
You could at least try to adjust
to Japanese school life.
No way!
Asuka, I'll bring you
some souvenirs!
Well, it's just too bad for you guys!
Don't feel bad, I'll have enough
fun for both of you!
Post the survey data on Mt. Asama
from Balthasar to Melchior
as soon as possible.
A school trip?
That's pretty casual behavior
for times like these.
Well, it's because the times
are so hard
that they want to have a little
fun while they can.
What are you up to?
Studying physics.
You're such an obedient
student, Mr. Big Shot.
Well, I'd have to anyway.
Ta da!
Since I can't go scuba diving in
Okinawa, I'm going to do it here!
Really?
What're you working on?
Let me see.
You can't solve an easy
problem like this?
There! Here you go!
It's so easy.
How can you solve a difficult
problem like this,
and not make good grades
on your tests?
Because I couldn't figure out
what the questions said.
You mean you couldn't read the
questions in Japanese?
Right, I haven't learned
all of the Kanji yet.
I didn't have to study it in college.
College?
Yeah, I graduated last year.
What does this one say?
It's about thermal expansion.
Thermal expansion?
That's kid stuff!
To put it simply,
things expand when they get hot,
and shrink when they get cold.
Well, it sounds easy
enough in theory.
If I were to warm up my breasts,
do you think they'd grow bigger?
How would I know such things?!
You're such a boring little boy.
Watch this, Shinji!
Back roll entry!
This just isn't clear enough.
But the report from Mt. Asama
Earthquake Research indicates
that we should take a closer
look at this shadow.
Of course, we can't ignore this.
What's Magi's judgment?
Fifty-fifty.
Is someone there yet?
Captain Katsuragi's
already on site.
You've gone too deep.
Not yet. Descend another
500, please.
Depth 1200. The pressure
resistant partition is cracking.
Ms. Katsuragi!
If it breaks, we'll pay for the
damage. 200 more, please.
We're monitoring a reaction!
Begin analysis!
Right!
The probe has imploded due
to the extreme pressure.
Did you get a result?
Just barely. The pattern is blue.
Then there's no doubt.
It's an Angel.
From now on, this laboratory will
be completely sealed off.
It's under NERV's jurisdiction now!
Any and all access to the outside
world is prohibited.
All records of the events of the
past six hours are classified.
I need an A-17 from Commander
Ikari, top priority!
Watch what you're saying.
This is an open line.
I know. Switch to the
scrambled line.
A-17?!
An offensive attack?
Correct.
Unacceptable, it's too dangerous.
Have you forgotten what happened
fifteen years ago?
This is our chance
to move from a defensive posture
to an offensive one.
The risk is enormous.
However, I'm sure you're aware
how important it is
to obtain a living Angel as
a sample, aren't you?
We will not tolerate failure.
Failure?
If we fail, it will result in the
extinction of the human race.
Are you really going to do it?
This is an Angel?
Yes, it's something like a chrysalis
priorto reaching the adult stage.
This operation's prime objective
is to capture this Angel.
We must capture it alive, as close
to its original state as possible.
And if we fail?
Then you must destroy it
immediately. Do you understand?
Roger!
The designated pilot for the actual operation is...
Hey, let me! I dive!
I know it's going to be me.
Asuka!
You will carry out the mission
using Unit 02.
Sure! It'll be easy.
And me?
Unit 00 does not conform to the
special equipment we'll be using.
Rei and Unit 00 will remain at
headquarters on stand-by.
Yes.
Oh, too bad.
You don't get to go to
the hot springs.
Now an A-17 has been ordered,
we must scramble immediately.
Get ready.
Roger!
This heat resistant plug suit
doesn't seem any different.
Press the switch on
your right wrist.
Oh, no!
What is this?
Unit 02 is also ready.
No! What is this?
The suit is designed to protect you
from heat, pressure and radiation.
This is Type-D equipment, for combat
under extreme environmental duress.
Is that my Unit 02?
No way! I quit!
I don't want to appear in public
in this dorky outfit!
This is the sort of
thing Shinji's for!
I'm so disappointed.
I was anticipating seeing
Asuka's gallant figure!
No!
Really, I can't let Kaji see me
in this awful looking thing.
We're having problems?
Well, yes.
Excuse me, but I can...
I'll go in Unit 02.
No, I don't want you
touching my Unit 02!
I'd rather do it than let
her take my place.
I'm sorry about the look.
Please, forgive me.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Eva Units 01 and 02 have arrived.
Have both units stand-by
in position.
Move in the laser bore,
and ready the crane.
Roger.
Hey, isn't Kaji here yet?
That male buffoon won't be here.
It's not any of his business.
Damn! I wanted him to
see how great I am.
An A-17 has been ordered.
That includes the freeze
of all current assets.
I assume that means some people
will be getting into a bit of trouble.
Why didn't you stop them?
I had no excuse for stopping it.
This order is an official one.
Surely you must know that if NERV
fails, the whole world will perish.
They're not that arrogant.
What are those?
The U.N. and the Air Force
will be on stand-by alert...
...until this mission has
been completed.
Will they help us?
No, they're here to clean up...
...in case we fail.
What do you mean?
They will use N2 depth charges to
destroy the Angel, and us with it.
That's dreadful!
Who would order
something like that?
Commander Ikari.
Laser operation, complete.
The bore path has been secured.
The Type D equipment is
functioning normally.
Unit 02 is in position to dispatch.
Roger.
Asuka, are you ready?
Anytime you are.
Launch!
It looks hot!
Unit 02 is entering the lava.
Watch this, Shinji!
Giant Stroke Entry!
Current depth: 170.
Speed of descent: 20.
No problems detected.
Visibility is zero. I can't
see a thing.
Switching to CT monitor.
Even with this, the range of
clarity is no more than 120.
Depth is 400...
450...
500...
550...
600...
650...
900...
950...
1000...
1020...
We're over the maximum
safety depth.
Depth is 1300. Unit 02 has reached
estimated target level.
Asuka? Can you see anything?
No reactions detected.
It's not here.
The lava circulation is faster
than we thought.
The target's velocity doesn't
match our predictions.
Hurry up and re-calculate.
Continue the operation.
Maintain descent.
Depth is 1350.
1400...
A crack has occurred in the
second coolant pipe.
Depth is 1480.
We're over the maximum
allowed depth.
It hasn't contacted the target yet?
Go on.
How's it going, Asuka?
I'm okay. I just want to finish this
and take a shower, ASAP.
There's a nice hot springs near
here. We'll hit it once we're done.
Just hang in there just
a little longer.
Maximum allowed depth plus 120.
Eva Unit 02 has lost its
progressive knife.
Maximum allowed depth plus 200.
Captain Katsuragi,
we've got to stop!
Have you forgotten that there's a
human being in there?
I am in charge of this operation.
Proceed, please.
Misato's right. I'm okay.
I can go on.
Depth 1780.
Unit 02 has reached the
corrected target depth.
There it is!
Target in sight.
Prepare to capture.
Due to the motion of the currents
moving you and the target,
you'll have just one chance
to make contact.
I know. Just leave it to me.
30 to contact.
Relative velocity 2.2 on the axis.
Electromagnetic cage spread.
No problems detected.
The target has been captured.
Nice, Asuka.
Operation completed.
I'm coming up now.
Are you all right, Asuka?
Who do you think you're asking?
Fear is worse than danger itself.
It was an easy assignment.
But this isn't a plug suit.
It's a sauna suit!
I want to take a bath.
The tension let loose all at once.
Yeah?
You were scared about this operation, weren't you?
Yes, if it'd gone wrong, there
might have been another disaster.
Right, Second Impact.
Nobody would want to
repeat that again.
What's going on?!
Oh no! It's started to hatch!
It's much earlier than
we predicted!
Status of the cage?!
There's no way it can
withstand this!
Abort the capture!
Jettison the cage!
We're changing the operation!
Destroying the Angel
is now top priority!
Unit 02, withdraw, and
prepare for combat!
This is what I've waited for!
Damn, I forgot I dropped the knife!
It's right in front of me!
Releasing ballast!
It's fast!
This is no good. I've lost it.
In addition to that, I've got lousy
visibility, I'm too hot,
and this disgusting suit's stuck
to my body with sweat.
This really sucks.
Asuka!
We'll drop you Unit 01's knife.
Catch it!
Roger!
Oh, no! Have you
dropped it, Shinji?
Contact with knife, 40 seconds.
The Angel is approaching rapidly!
No! Go away!
Hurry up with it!
Come on!
What the hell?!
Unbelievable! How could it open
its mouth in such an environment?
Its construction must
be incredible!
The left leg is damaged!
The heat shields!
Damn you!
If it can withstand such a high
heat, high pressure environment,
then the progressive knife will
be useless against it!
Then what's the solution?
I know! Like the one earlier!
Eat this!
I understand! Thermal expansion!
Transfer all coolant pressure
to cable three! Hurry!
I've done it, but...
Is this the end? Looks
like that's that.
Shinji?
Idiot! What a show off!
Hello?
Are the NERV personnel here?
Yes!
I need your signature here.
Thanks so much.
From Kaji?
What is this?
The bath is over there, to the left.
Bath - Men
This feels like heaven.
I never thought a bath
could feel this good.
Shinji, can you hear me?
Yes, Ma'am!
Would you throw me the
body shampoo?
We ran out of ours.
Here it comes.
Roger.
Ouch!
You idiot! You dork, watch
where you're throwing!
Sorry.
He hit me in my most
essential part!
Let me take a look.
Wow, your skin is so soft
and smooth, Asuka!
Don't! You're tickling me!
How about right here?
Don't touch that!
Come on, what gives?
It expanded.
How embarrassing!
Oh, this? I got this in
the Second Impact.
You know all about my
past, don't you?
Well, yeah. It's a part of my job.
It's all ancient history now.
We should just forget.
To be continued...
Preview
When Tokyo-3's power
supply is cut off,
an Angel arrives at NERV HQ to
find it completely locked up.
Can the kids make it to headquarters
in time to intercept the Angel?
Next episode:
"In the Still Darkness"
You can expect more fanservice!