Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
The second and third
Ashino Lakes,
I hope there won't be any
more of those.
I received a complaint from
Chairman Keel about the delay.
He came directly to me.
He was very upset. He even
threatened to dismiss you.
Adam is growing well,
and work on the dummy plugs for
the Eva Project is proceeding.
What are those old men of Seele
complaining about now?
The all-important Instrumentality
Project is behind schedule.
All the projects are linked.
There are no problems.
Including Rei?
Well, never mind.
By the way, what should
we do about that man?
Leave him alone for now. The
same with the Marduk Institute.
I agree, let him work
for us for a while.
Kyoto
What started here, sixteen
years ago?
Episode 15
A Lie and Silence
It's me.
Yes, so it is.
Shannon Bio, a foreign
chemical firm.
It has been here for nine years,
and not a single change.
The Marduk Institute has 108
affiliated companies.
106 of them are dummy
corporations.
And this is the 107th?
This is the corporate registration.
And you want me to take a look at
the board of directors, don't you?
You know about it already?
I know all of the names.
The Marduk Institute is supposed
to be an advisory body
controlled by the Instrumentality
Committee to select Eva pilots.
What it really does is not clear.
Your duty is to investigate NERV.
Getting involved in the Marduk
Institute is inappropriate.
Well, be that as it may, I want
to see everything for myself.
Hi, this is Kaji.
I'm out right now.
Please leave your name
and message.
Help me, Kaji! Don't touch me,
you pervert!
That'll do it!
What's going on?
Well, I want to go out tomorrow.
So I've been calling Kaji to ask
him to take me, but he's been out.
He's always out lately.
So, you'll have time tomorrow?
Regrettably so.
Then, I have a favor to ask of you.
Well, it's like this...
A date?!
A friend of my big sister, Kodama,
keeps asking me to introduce
you to him.
I beg you!
Get to work!
I'm sorry.
YOU! Get to work!
Microsis operation complete.
Graph measurement complete.
Which dress will you wear tomorrow?
Synch ratio is normal.
For the wedding?
I wore the pink suit for
Kiyomi's wedding,
and the dark blue dress
for Kotoko's shower.
What about the orange one?
You haven't worn that one
lately, have you?
Well, there's a reason for that.
It's too tight?
Yeah, so what?!
Should I get a new one
on the way home?
It's an extra expense.
We've been invited to so
many showers lately,
that the cost of all the gifts
is starting to add up.
Everyone's just rushing to get
married before they're thirty.
No one wants to be the
last one still single.
Okay, you can take off now.
Good work.
I'm tired of these stupid tests.
By the way, Shinji looks even more
downcast than usual today.
That's because of tomorrow.
Yes, tomorrow.
Tomorrow, I have to see my father.
What should I talk to him about?
Why do you ask me?
Because I've seen you talking
happily with him.
Say, my father, what kind
of person is he?
I don't know.
I see.
You've been watching me because
you wanted to ask me that?
When we were cleaning today,
you were squeezing the cloth.
The way you squeezed
it was like a mother.
A mother?
I thought it was like a mother.
I think you'll make a good
mother, Ayanami.
You're embarrassing me.
You're the one who caused us to break up!
I'm home.
What's up?
I was wrong. I must've been crazy.
You'd better go to bed. Aren't you
going on a date tomorrow?
I was wrong. I must've been crazy.
You'd better go to bed. Aren't you
going on a date tomorrow?
I don't care how you were!
Yeah, with a hunk.
I'm different now anyway!
Hey, that's right, let me use your lavender perfume!
But I still love you!
Absolutely not.
Jeez, cheapskate!
But I still love you!
You can't turn back the clock!
It's not for kids.
Is Shinji in his room?
You can't turn back the clock!
We can't go back to that time!
He's been shut up since he got back.
But I still love you!
It looks like he doesn't want to see his father.
I tell you, it's impossible!
If he doesn't want to, why doesn't he just say so?
I don't understand the Japanese.
I tell you, it's impossible!
It took me three years to forget you!
Well, he doesn't really hate him.
That's the problem.
It took me three years to forget you!
Go away!
Well done, Shinji.
Shinji?
I'm opening the door.
Are you scared? Of seeing
your father by yourself?
Don't run away.
Unless you step forward,
nothing will change.
I know that!
You'll begin to realize,
after that first step, it's just as
important to take another step.
Anyway, go see him tomorrow
with your chin held high,
because you'll be seeing
your mother too.
Well, good night.
Hey, you bought a new dress for
tomorrow, didn't you? Let me see!
Oh, you want to see?
It's an expensive one.
The price doesn't always
reflect the design.
Tell me about it.
Did you pick one to Kaji's taste?
I don't think so. Not anymore.
The next day.
Well!
See you...
Later.
Place three bags in your heart...
Ladybugs with red, blue
and yellow dresses...
Now let us proceed with
the reception.
Ryoji Kaji
Little Ryoji's late.
That idiot has never been on
time in his entire life!
For your dates, you mean?
He's always on time for work.
Hey, girls! You look
marvelous today.
I couldn't get off work.
I don't believe that. You never
do anything anyway.
Why didn't you shave?
That stubble's awful.
Look, your necktie is crooked.
Well, thank you.
You two act like you're married.
Good point, Ri-chan.
Who the hell would marry
this dork?
It's been three years since the last
time we came here together.
I ran away then,
and haven't been back since.
My mother is resting here?
I don't really believe that.
I don't even remember her face.
Man survives by forgetting
his memories,
but there are some things a
man should never forget.
Yui taught me about the
irreplaceable things.
I come here to confirm that.
You have no pictures of her?
There are none.
This grave is just a decoration,
too. There's no corpse.
So, the teacher was right.
You threw them away.
I keep everything in my heart.
That is enough.
Time's up. I'm leaving now.
Father!
Well, I'm glad we could talk today.
Indeed...
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Not bad! I didn't know you played.
I've been studying since I was
five, but I'm not very good.
I don't really have any talent.
Perseverance is power.
I'm impressed.
I started studying because
my teacher told me to,
but I could have quit anytime.
So, why didn't you?
Because nobody told me to stop.
I should have known!
You came back early. I thought
you'd have dinner too.
He was just so boring!
So, while he was waiting in line
for the roller coaster, I left.
That's harsh.
Really, Kaji is the only cool guy.
It's getting late.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Are you going to leave me alone?
High heels...
We haven't really gotten together
to drink lately, have we?
Misato's drinking too
much, isn't she?
She's acting a little out of control.
Sometimes one drinks to keep
oneself under control.
We all do.
As someone who lived with her,
your words carry a weight of truth.
Well, I did live with her,
but that was before she started
wearing heels like a real woman.
That's not how we saw it back
when we were in school.
I was a kid.
That wasn't really life.
Kid's play is what it was.
Life isn't that easy.
Oh yeah, I forgot to give you this.
A souvenir from a cat.
Oh, thank you. You're very honest.
Only with the ladies. When it
comes to work, I'm less so.
I somehow doubt that.
What about Misato?
I lost once before.
It's not my style to keep fighting
a battle I'm sure to lose.
I think you still have a
chance to win.
What about you?
It's my policy to never
talk about myself.
There's nothing amusing
about me.
Why is Katsuragi taking so long?
Fixing her make-up maybe?
What were you doing in Kyoto?
No, that's from Matsushiro.
Don't try to fool me.
Your fingers will get burned if you
get involved in this too deeply.
That's the advice of a friend.
I'll take it seriously,
but I'd prefer to be burned by the
heat of my passion for you.
Should I buy you some fireworks?
But I'd prefer to be burned by the
heat of my passion for you.
Should I buy you some fireworks?
Welcome back!
You never change, do you?
Of course I change, living
means changing.
Homeostasis and transistasis.
What are those?
One is a force for the status quo,
and the other's a force for change.
Anything that contains these two
conflicting forces is alive.
Like men and women.
Well, I'll be leaving now. I've
still got some work to do.
Really?
Sorry to hear it.
Later.
Hey, Shinji? It's me.
I'm with Kaji. We're going
to be out drinking.
Yes... Okay, later.
Was it Misato?
Yes, she'll be late, so don't
wait up for her.
Is she going to stay out
until morning?
I don't think so, she's with Kaji.
Are you an idiot?
That guarantees it!
Drinking so much you throw up
like a kid. How old are you?
I know, but I'm not a kid.
Well, neither of us are.
Damn right.
I can't believe you wear
high heels, Katsuragi.
Time's really flown.
Rough face... You need to shave.
I can walk now. Thank you.
Kaji, do you think I've changed?
You're even more beautiful.
I'm sorry that I insisted on
breaking up with you.
When I said I had somebody else,
you knew that was a lie,
didn't you?
No.
It's just that I realized
you were so much like
my late father, Kaji.
When I realized that I
wanted a man
like my father, I was scared.
I was so afraid.
Being with you, Kaji...
Being a woman...
Everything scared me.
I hated my father, but fell in love
with someone just like him.
I chose to break everything
off and join NERV.
However, it turned out that my
father had worked for NERV too.
I tried to bury my feelings
by swearing vengeance
against the Angels.
That was your decision, Katsuragi.
You don't have to be sorry.
No, that wasn't a decision!
I just escaped from reality.
Escaped from the reality
called Father!
I'm just like Shinji.
I'm a coward.
I'm really sorry. I had to get
drunk just to tell you this.
That's enough.
I'm just a child myself.
I have no right to tell
Shinji anything.
That's enough!
I'm a coward! I just use men when I need to.
In the past, Kaji, I may have just...
just used you!
I'm so pathetic!
That's enough! Stop it!
I can't stand myself!
Hey, Shinji, do you
want to kiss me?
What?
A kiss. A kiss? You've never
kissed a girl, have you?
What?
A kiss. A kiss? You've never
kissed a girl, have you?
Then, let's do it.
But why?
Because I'm bored.
Is that a reason?!
Do you not want to kiss on the
anniversary of your mom's death?
Afraid she may be watching
you from Heaven?
It's not that.
Are you scared?
Why would I be scared of a kiss?!
You brushed your teeth,
didn't you?
Then, here I come.
Stop breathing, it tickles me.
I should never kiss to kill time!
All right, here we are. Hang on.
Kaji!
Well, I'll be leaving now.
Why don't you stay with us, Kaji?
I'd be laughed at if I went
to work in this.
It'll be okay.
Hey, Kaji, it'll...
Later.
Lavender perfume...
Please take care of Katsuragi.
Sure.
Well, night.
Goodnight.
What's wrong? You look sad.
It's because you kissed me!
The next day
Well, let me call the girl's roll.
Ayanami...
Oh, Ayanami's absent again?
NERV Headquarter
Underground Central Section
Central Dogma
2008 meters below the surface
Terminal Dogma
Hi, how are you feeling today?
I'm sober now, thanks.
I'm glad to hear that.
Is this your real job,
or your other job?
What do you think?
Ryoji Kaji of NERV's Special
Inspection Department...
At the same time, Ryoji Kaji of the
Japanese Department of Interior.
Oh, so you know.
You underestimate NERV.
Is this an order from
Commander Ikari?
No, my sole discretion.
If you keep doing this
other job, you'll die.
As long as Commander Ikari is
using me too, I can still do it.
However, let me apologize for
using you, Major Katsuragi.
It'll make us even for your
help yesterday.
Thanks very much, but...
The Commander and Ritsuko are
hiding something from you, and...
This is it.
This is...
Eva? No!
Impossible...
Yes, this is the source of everything
since the Second Impact.
The most important factor.
This is Adam.
Adam? Why is the
First Angel here?
You're right.
I don't know NERV at all.
To be continued...
Preview
Ikari Shinji finally surpasses Asuka and
scores the highest in the synchro test.
However, his overconfidence draws him into
Dirac's Ocean, with only little time to survive.
Next time:
"Deadly illness, then..."
Next time, service, service.