Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Anno Domini 2015.
The third angel ...
The attack of Sachiel.
Conventional weaponry is
ineffective against the angel.
The UN transfers full
command authority to NERV.
The angel arrives
at NERV headquarters.
At the same day, the
Third Child arrives aswell.
Shinji Ikari.
He agrees to pilot the Eva.
The first sortie
of Evangelion-01.
NERV's first mission.
Eva-01, head damage.
Out of control.
Complete silence.
But then...
Running Amok
Although there was a great deal
of damage as a result,
the fact that a boy with no
prior experience
completed a mission against
an unknown enemy
makes Shinji Ikari deserving
of special notice.
Eva-01 erodes
the enemy's AT field.
However, for the Department
of Strategic Operations,
it was a battle that revealed
many problems.
Angel destroyed.
Intercept systems destroyed.
Eva-01, medium damage.
The suffering of the
victims was not mentioned.
My sister's only in the
second grade.
She got hurt in that stupid
disturbance,
and she was hurt by our own
stupid robot, not by the enemy.
I can't forgive anyone who did
something so stupid.
I'm going to let them
feel my anger,
and teach the jerks who hurt
my sister a lesson.
The fourth angel
The attack of Shamusiel.
Interception effectivity
back then: 48,2%
Mission performance
of Neo-Tokyo 3: 96,8%
We'd already had a lot of
evacuation training at the school,
so we didn't really think
it was so serious.
All the guys acted like jerks,
like they were on a field trip,
and none of the girls
were afraid either.
The angel arrives at Neo-Tokyo 3.
The second battle at Neo-Tokyo 3.
External power cable severed.
Regardless of this accident,
the angel was destroyed.
As a result, NERV salvages
an angel in its original form.
However, the final
report is still missing.
The fifth angel.
The attack of Ramiel.
Captain Katsuragis "Yashima-Plan"
against the enemy is approved
First Child.
The designated pilot of Eva-00.
Rei Ayanami.
Her first sortie with the
repaired Eva-00.
In this night, the angel
penetrates the Geo-Front.
The "Yashima-Plan"
is executed.
Ikari didn't tell me anything, so
this is just a guess on my part.
I think Ayanami tried
to sacrifice herself
to protect Unit 01 from the
enemy's particle beam attack.
I'm really sure about this,
and the reason I'm so positive
is Ayanami herself.
She seems to hold little respect
for the value of her own existence.
"Yashima-Plan" successful.
She seems to hold little respect
for the value of her own existence.
It's not just that she's more
pessimistic than most teenagers,
Eva-00, severely damaged. Pilot survives
it's something much, much more.
The sixth angel.
The encounter with Gagiel.
This did not occur in accordance
with our scenario.
Nevertheless, the result was within
the projected parameters.
We can make the necessary
adjustments.
Second Child.
The designated pilot of Eva-02.
Soryu Asuka Langley.
Her first sortie with Eva-02.
Melee at high sea.
and...
...the first underwater fight.
At the heights of Old-Ito,
Angel destroyed.
The UN Navy lost a third of its
entire fleet in this encounter.
The lost ships belonged to your
country. The damage is negligible.
True, it's fortunate that so much
of the damage was minor.
The seventh angel.
The attack of Israfel,
which can split and remerge.
However, a synchronized attack
of Eva-01 and Eva-02...
...destroys the angel.
The eighth angel.
Sandarphone is located
in the depths of the Asama-Volcano.
NERV releases special directive A-17.
With the highest priority
a capture mission is commenced.
Capture in the electromagnetic
cage is temporarily succesful...
but the magnetic cage is damaged.
Mission aborted.
New objective:
Termination of the angel.
Eva-02 continues the operation.
Angel destroyed.
Repair and regeneration
of Eva-00 complete.
Eva-00 operational.
The ninth angel.
The attack of Matriel.
During the simultaneous
mission of the three Evas
the angel is destroyed.
The tenth angel.
The attack of Tzachquiel.
The target falling
from the stratosphere
is directly intercepted
by the three Evas
Angel destroyed.
The eleventh angel.
Attack unconfirmed. Rumors about
success in compromising the HQ.
This is no good.
It's happening too early.
That's true. This did not occur in
accordance with our predictions
of when an Angel would
invade NERV.
And to make it worse, you let it
intrude into Central Dogma itself.
If contact had occurred then,
our entire project could have
ended in disaster.
The report to this committee
was in error.
There is no truth behind this
tale of an Angel invasion.
Are you saying the Eleventh
Angel's intrusion did not occur?
Correct.
Speak with caution, Ikari.
Making false statements to this
conference is punishable by death.
Check the MAGI's recorders.
Nothing concerning such an
incident was recorded.
This is absurd. Hiding the
truth is your specialty.
The time schedule follows what
the Dead Sea Scrolls prescribes.
All right.
We won't discuss any possible
guilt or punishment this time.
But let me remind you that you
cannot create a new scenario.
I understand.
Everything is proceeding
according to Seele's plan.
Episode 14
Weaving a Story
Mountain...
Heavy are the mountains, but
that changes over time.
Sky...
Blue sky.
What your eyes can't see.
What your eyes can see.
Sun...
There is only one.
Water... Comforting.
Commander Ikari?
Flower...
So many alike.
So many useless.
Sky...
Red, red sky.
Red is the color.
Red is the color I hate.
Water flowing.
Blood...
The smell of blood.
A woman who never bleeds.
From the red earth comes man,
from the soil.
Born of man and woman is Man.
Town... A human creation.
Eva... A human creation as well.
What is a human?
A creation of God?
Is it a human creation?
The things I possess are
my life and soul.
I am a vessel for my heart.
Entry Plug, the throne for a soul.
Who is this? This is me.
Who am I? What am I? What am I?
What am I? What am I?
I am myself.
This, that which is, is myself.
That which is formed is me.
This is the me that can be seen,
yet feels as if this is not myself.
A strange feeling.
I feel as if my body is melting.
I can no longer see myself.
My shape is fading.
I feel the presence of someone
who is not me.
Who is there, beyond me here?
Ikari?
I know this person. She is
Captain Katsuragi.
Doctor Akagi...
Others...
Classmates...
The pilot of Unit 02.
Commander Ikari?
Who are you?
So, how does it feel to be piloting
Unit 01 for the first time?
It smells like Ikari.
First compatibility test
Subject: Rei Ayanami
Her synch ratio is almost the
same as with Unit 00.
Unit 00 and 01's personal data
patterns are also almost identical.
That's what makes this synch
experiment possible.
Error is plus or minus zero point
zero three. Harmonics are normal.
No compatibility problems
detected between Rei and Unit 01.
Okay, the experiment
is finished, Rei.
You can get out now.
Understood.
87. unit synthesis test.
Subject: Soryu Asuka Langley.
Data bank for Unit 02 complete.
Harmonics are all normal.
Pilot status normal.
Of course!
First compatibility test
Subject: Shinji Ikari.
What about Unit 00's
personal data?
Already reconfigured.
Currently reconfirming.
Subject status?
He's a bit nervous, but no
problems in his nerve patterns.
This is his first time in Unit 00,
and his first time piloting any
other Eva. That's natural.
Nonsense, why should he care?
That's what makes him Shinji.
I know, and that's why he's stupid.
Speaking of which, why am I not
taking the compatibility test?
You don't want to pilot any
other Evas, do you?
Darn right.
Certainly, Unit 02 wouldn't
be compatible.
Entry has commenced.
LCL electrolyzed.
Initiating first connection.
Shinji, how do you feel in
Unit 00's entry plug?
It feels kind of odd.
A sense of incompatibility?
Not like that, but...
It smells like Rei.
What does that mean?
He's a pervert!
Data received. Reconfirming.
Pattern green.
Main power supply
connection complete.
All restraints are normal.
Acknowledged.
Now let's shift to the second stage
of the mutual compatibility tests.
Unit 00 will enter into
second contact.
How is it?
As I thought, the synch ratio is lower than Unit 01.
Harmonics are all normal.
But these are still good readings.
This means that we can
implement the plan.
The dummy system, you mean?
I disagree.
I understand your feelings on this,
but we always have to be prepared
in order to guarantee our survival.
I highly respect you, Ma'am,
and I will do my duty,
but I am not convinced
about this project.
People with a fastidious nature
will always feel some difficulty
living amongst others.
Once you've been sullied, you'll
regretfully find the truth in this.
Initiating third connection.
Self state of psycho-graph
is stable.
Hey, Shinji, what's it like? Mom's
breast? Or inside her womb?
Asuka, stop interrupting.
The noise can penetrate.
Yes, Ma'am.
Why do they spoil Shinji?
Commence connecting the
A-10 nerve connections.
Harmonics level up twenty.
What is this? Something's trying
to get into my brain.
Ayanami?
Rei Ayanami?
This impression is Rei, isn't it?
Ayanami?
Isn't it her?
What is it?
We've got a problem occurring
in the pilot's nerve pulse.
Mental contamination is taking place.
Impossible! That can't happen
at this plug depth.
It's not from the plug.
The intrusion's coming
from the Eva.
Unit 00 is out of control!
Shut off all circuits!
Cut the power supply!
Eva has switched to
backup power.
The Eva is still active.
How's Shinji?
The circuit is closed.
We can't monitor him!
Unit 00 is rejecting Shinji?
Negative! The auto ejection's
not working!
The same thing as before?
Is it going to try to
absorb Shinji?
Rei, get back! Rei!
Activation will be terminated in ten...
9...
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
Zero!
Unit 00 has ceased activation.
Hurry up and rescue the pilot!
I don't believe this. Did Unit 00
just try to kill Rei?
Was this somehow related to
the earlier berserk incident
when Rei was the pilot?
I can't tell you much right now.
I only know we must reconfigure
Unit 00 for Rei's personal data,
and run a new synch test between
them as soon as possible.
As Director of Strategic Ops, I ask
you do so as soon as possible,
before it creates more problems.
I understand that, Major Katsuragi.
Unit 00 wanted to attack me.
I'm sure of it.
And now the next contestant
for the World's Most Amazing
Exhibition is, Math Puppy!
Wow, that sounds awesome!
Here we go, math genius puppy,
Kana, from Niigata!
Wan!
He sounds good. Do you
understand me?
Wan!
Oh, right. Now let's ask him.
What is 325 minus 324?
Wan!
That's amazing! He's correct!
Again... I hate this ceiling.
Wan!
Shinji's conscious. No signs
of mental contamination.
He doesn't remember
what happened.
I see.
Hi! I'm doing fine,
but the world is worrisome due to
terrorism in the Nansa islands.
Misato and Kaji won't tell me about her,
but the world is worrisome due to
terrorism in the Nansa islands.
Misato and Kaji won't tell me about her,
This year long heat creates some
crazy bastards, you know?
And Shinji doesn't know anything.
This year long heat creates some
crazy bastards, you know?
And Shinji doesn't know anything.
What I can't stand is those idiots
that involve innocent people!
Just what is the First Child?
What I can't stand is those idiots
that involve innocent people!
About that Angel invasion that
deviated from the plan.
The committee is applying
pressure over the incident.
They're just riff-raff who can't do
anything except complain.
We hold all the tiles. There
is nothing they can do.
But we don't want to irritate them.
If SEELE starts interfering,
there could be trouble.
Everything has been carried out
as the scenario required.
There is no problem.
What about the Unit 00 incident?
That wasn't in my scenario.
It will not interfere.
The re-synchronization test for Rei
and Unit 00 was successful.
Ikari is too concerned about Rei.
What is the status of the
Adam Project?
Proceeding smoothly. It is less
than two percent behind schedule.
Then, the Lance of Longinus is...
It's going as we planned.
Rei is carrying out the operation.
To be continued...
Vorschau
Misato feels pressure while many
of her friends get married.
Her twenties are almost over,
and the thirties are arriving fast.
Is a reunion with
Kaji her last chance?
Next episode:
"A Lie and Silence"