Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
A.D. 2015
As of 01:12:30 PM today, a special
state of emergency has been declared
for the Kanto and Chubu regions
surrounding the Tokai district.
All residents must evacuate to their
designated shelters immediately.
Repeating: As of 01:12:30 PM today,
the Kanto and Chubu regions
surrounding the Tokai district
have been declared to be under
a state of emergency.
All residents must evacuate to their
designated shelters immediately.
Why did I have to lose him now?
Christ, why at a time like this?
Due to the special emergency,
all lines are currently unavailable.
It's no use.
I shouldn't have come here after all.
[Look here!!]
Well, I guess we won't be meeting here.
I'll have to go to a shelter.
The unidentified object is
coming toward us.
We've got it on visual. I'm putting
it on the main screen.
It's been fifteen years, hasn't it?
Yes. Well, now we're sure.
It's the Angels.
EPISODE 1:
ANGEL ATTACK
Every missile hit the target!
I'm sorry! Were you waiting long?
The target is still operational.
It's still heading towards Tokyo 3.
The Air Defense Force doesn't have
the firepower to stop it!
Hit it with everything we've got!
Mobilize all the units from Atsugi and
scramble the squadrons from lruma!
Forget about the budget!
Destroy the target at any cost!
Why?! That was a direct hit!
The tank battalion's been annihilated.
Guided missiles and artillery
have no effect either.
Damn it! We gave it everything we've
got and we're not even touching it!
Is it protected by an AT field?
Yes. Conventional weapons are
no match for the Angels.
Yes Sir, I understand. We'll
execute the plan at once.
Hey, wait a second.
They're going to use an N2-mine?!
Get down!
We did it!
Sorry, but it looks like you won't
be getting a shot at it.
Shock wave approaching.
Are you all right?
Yeah, but my mouth is full of dirt.
That's okay. Now then, let's go!
Push!
There.
Thanks for the hand. I
really appreciate it.
Thank you too, Miss Katsuragi.
Just Misato is fine.
I'm glad we've met at last,
Shinji Ikari.
Yeah...
What's the target's status?
We're unable to confirm due to
all the EMP interference.
It must have been finished. You saw
the size of that explosion.
Sensors restored.
We've got an energy reading at
the explosion's epicenter!
It can't be!
Visual display restored.
That was our last resort.
No effect, I can't believe it!
It's a God-damned demon!
Yes. Don't worry about it.
His safety is my top priority, so could
you get a car train ready for us?
The express one.
Right. Well, I volunteered
to pick him up,
so it's my duty to make sure
he gets there. See ya!
But this sucks! I just had this car
restored, and now it's a wreck.
33 loan repayments to go...
and the repair costs....
Um, Misato....
33 loan repayments to go...
and the repair costs....
Um, Misato....
Even worse, my only good
clothes have been ruined....
Excuse me, Misato?
What?
Are you sure you can just take those?
Never mind about that!
It's an emergency, and we need a
working car right now, right?
And I am a government
official, after all,
so everything's going to be
perfectly fine, okay?
I don't think anyone will buy that.
Don't get so snotty. You're not as
cute as I thought you were.
You think so?
Oh, did I upset you?
Sorry, sorry! You're just
a kid, after all.
So are you. You're not as mature
as I thought you were.
As we predicted, it's
regenerating itself.
If it couldn't, it wouldn't be a practical
autonomous invasion weapon.
Impressive. It appears it can even
upgrade its own operational functions.
And it's also getting smarter.
It will renew its assault
any minute now.
The gates are now closing. Please stand clear.
The special agency, Nerv?
Yes, it's a secret organization under
the control of the United Nations.
The gates are now closing. Please stand clear.
Yes, it's a secret organization under
the control of the United Nations.
This is a B-22 Special Express departing for G33-1.
It's the one my father belongs to, isn't it?
Well, yeah... do you know what he does?
This is a B-22 Special Express departing for G33-1.
This train will bypass all other stations.
My teachers told me it was important
to the safety of the human race.
From this point on, command of the
operation will be entrusted to you.
Show us that you're capable.
Yes, Sir.
Mr. Ikari, we must admit that our
weapons have no effect on the target.
But are you sure you can
beat these things?
It's what NERV was created for.
We're all praying that you're correct.
The target is still stationary.
Our current ability to intercept is only 7.5%.
Even the UN forces are exhausted.
What are you going to do?
I intend to activate Unit 01.
Unit 01? But we have no pilot.
That's not a problem. Another spare
will be delivered soon.
Are you taking me to my father?
Yes. Yes, I think so.
Father...
Oh, yes. Didn't you get an
ID card from your dad?
Yes.
This is it.
Thanks.
[Note: Come here!]
Here, read this.
NERV...
My father's agency.
Am I going to work for him?
Of course.
He wouldn't have sent me a letter
unless he needed me for something.
It looks like you don't get
along with your dad.
It's the same with me.
Awesome!
It's a real Geo-Front!
That's right. This is our secret base:
NERV Headquarters.
This is the key to rebuilding our world.
A fortress for all Mankind.
NEON GENESIS
EVANGELION
What on Earth? Isn't this
the right way?
Central Dogma's closed passages remain sealed.
This is why I hate wearing skirts here.
Opening block B-26 in sequence.
And where in the heck is Ritsuko?
I'm sorry. I'm just not used
to this place yet.
We passed this spot just
a little while ago.
Don't worry about it.
And anyway, they make these systems
to be used, you know.
Would the chairperson of E Project,
Technical Department Division 1,
Dr. Ritsuko Akagi,
contact Captain Misato Katsuragi of
Operations, Division 1, immediately.
I don't believe it. Has she
gotten lost again?
Hiya, Ritsuko.
Why are you wasting my time,
Captain Katsuragi?
Aren't you aware that we're short
on both time and manpower?
Sorry!
Is this the boy?
Right. According to the Marduk report,
he's the Third Child.
I'm glad to meet you.
Sure.
He's just like his dad. The
unfriendly part, that is.
Handle the rest of this.
Their first meeting in over three years.
Vice Commander, the target
has started moving again.
Right. Assume battle stations,
Level One.
Repeat. Battle stations, Level One.
Prepare for ground-unit interception.
Here we go.
It sounds pretty serious.
So, how's Unit 01 doing?
It's currently undergoing refrigeration,
using the B-type equipment.
Does it really work? It's never
worked before, has it?
The possibility of activation
is 0.000000001%.
We call it, pathetically enough,
the O-9 System.
Does that mean it doesn't work?
Oh, don't be insulting.
It's "O," not "zero."
Well, it's just a number.
Anyway, it's a bit too late to be
saying, "Sorry, it didn't work".
It's so dark.
A face? A giant robot?
You won't find this in the manual.
This is Man's ultimate humanoid
fighting machine,
the first model of the synthetic life
form Evangelion, Unit 01.
Built here in secret, it is
Mankind's last hope.
Is this part of what my father's
been doing?
Correct.
It's been a while.
Father...
We're moving out.
Moving out?! Unit 00's still
in cryo-stasis, isn't it?
Wait a second. You're going
to use Unit 01?
There's no other way.
Now wait, Rei can't do it yet, can she?
We've got no pilot!
One's just been delivered.
Are you serious?
Shinji Ikari...
Yes?
You will pilot it.
But even Rei Ayanami took seven
months to synchronize with her Eva.
It's impossible for him to do it!
He just got here!
He just has to sit in the seat.
We don't expect more than that.
But...
Repelling that Angel is our
ultimate priority.
If putting someone who has a chance
of synchronizing into an Eva unit
gives us even the slightest chance,
then we have to do it.
You do understand that, don't you,
Captain Katsuragi?
I suppose...
Father, why did you send for me?
You know exactly why.
So, you're asking me to take this thing
and go out there and fight?
Precisely.
No way! How can you do something
like this to me?
I knew you didn't want me!
I called you because I have
a need for you.
Why me?
Because no one else can.
No, I can't...
I've never even seen anything like
this before! I can't do this!
You will be instructed.
But there's no way!
I can't pilot it!
If you're going to pilot it, do it now
and quickly. If not, then leave!
It must have detected our location.
Shinji, we don't have any time.
Get into it.
No! I didn't come for this!
This is all wrong!
Shinji, just why did you come here?
You must confront your father and
you must confront yourself.
I know it! But I just can't!
Fuyutsuki...
Wake up Rei.
Can we use her?
She isn't dead.
I understand.
Rei...
Yes?
Our spare is unusable.
You will do it again.
Yes, Sir.
Reconfigure Unit 01's system
to Rei, then re-activate!
Roger. Call off the present work,
and begin re-activation.
I knew it. I'm not needed after all.
Watch out!
The Eva moved!
How could it?!
It broke off the right arm-restraint!
No, that's impossible!
It didn't have an entry plug inserted!
It's not possible!
It reacted without any interface?!
Or was it protecting something?
It protected him?
We can do it.
I mustn't run away. I mustn't run away.
I MUSTN'T RUN AWAY!
Let me do it. I'll pilot it.
Cooling process, completed.
Right arm repairs, completed.
Cage now in position for docking.
Signal plug terminator has been ejected.
Roger. Inserting entry plug.
Plug fixed in place.
Connecting Unit 01.
Filling the entry plug.
What is this stuff?
Don't worry. Once your lungs
are filled with LCL,
your blood will be oxygenated directly.
You'll get used to it.
I feel nauseous.
Stop whining! You're a boy,
aren't you?!
Connecting main power.
All circuits transmitting power.
Roger.
Connecting secondary contacts.
A-10 nerve connection, normal.
Configure the language logic
interface for Japanese.
All preliminary contacts established.
Performance nominal.
Bi-directional circuits are open.
Synchronization ratio at 41.3%
Amazing.
Harmonics are all normal.
No disturbances identified.
We can do it.
Prepare to launch!
Disengage primary lock bolts!
Disengage confirmed. Disengaging
the umbilical bridge.
Disengage secondary lock bolts.
Disengage primary restraints.
Disengage secondary restraints.
Release safety locks numbers
one through fifteen.
Internal batteries fully charged.
External battery outlet, normal.
Roger. Move Eva Unit 01
to the ejector pad.
Launch path is clear.
All systems green.
Ready for launch.
Roger.
Can we really do this?
Of course.
Unless we defeat the Angels,
we have no future.
Ikari, are you sure about this?
Launch!
Shinji, don't get killed out there.
TO BE CONTINUED
Preview
Eva defeats the Angel,
but that's only the beginning.
Shinji runs away from his father
and insists on staying alone...
...and Misato tries to help him.
Next time: "Unknown Ceilings"
Oh yeah, and I'll have fanservice for you as well!