Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Correct, I have already arranged
it with the committee.
The cargo left from Sasebo
Port yesterday,
and is now making its way here
across the Pacific ocean.
A MIG-55 D transport helicopter!
I'd never have believed I'd
get chance to fly in one.
Thank God I have a buddy
like you, Shinji!
I thought you guys must be sick
of being cramped up,
so I just invited you on a date!
What?! Today is really a date?
I bought this cap for
today, Misato!
Where are we headed?
We'll take a little jaunt across the
Pacific on that gorgeous cruiser.
Wow! Five aircraft carriers and
four battleships! What a fleet!
I'm absolutely sure the best thing
in life is having a great buddy!
That's your "gorgeous cruiser"?
Yeah, she sure is gorgeous!
That's the pride of the U.N.,
the glorious regular carrier
"Over the Rainbow"!
It's huge.
I'm surprised that such
a relic is still afloat.
Naw, it's not so bad.
It's a vintage model from just
before the Second Impact.
Damn, give me a break!
That shrew's gone and brought
a socket for that kid's toy,
so the little gophers
can run amuck!
Oh! Cool! Awesome!
Cool! Incredible!
Cool! Mega-cool! Wow!
This is way too cool!
This kind of thing brings a tear
to the heart of a real man!
Cool! Awesome! Neat! Wow! Wow!
Hey, wait! Wait!
Damn it!
Stop! Stop, now!
Hello, Misato.
How have you been?
Fine. How 'bout you? You've
grown some, haven't you?
And how!
I'm not just taller, my figure's
filled out as well.
Let me introduce you.
This is the pilot of Evangelion
Unit 02, the Second Child,
Asuka Langley Sohryu.
Episode 8
Asuka
Arrives at Japan
What did you do that for?!
That's the viewing fee. Quite
a bargain, don't you think?
What? You think it's worth that?!
Here, take a look at mine!
You insolent dork!
So, which one is the famous
Third Child?
Don't tell me it's him.
Don't worry, here he is.
Well, he looks kind of dull.
I thought you were the leader
of this gang of Boy Scouts,
but I was obviously mistaken.
Thank you for your
understanding, Captain.
Oh no, thank you for giving me the
opportunity to baby-sit more kids.
We appreciate your assistance in
the marine transport of Unit 02.
Here are the specs for the
emergency power supply socket.
In the first place, I'd never
approve any request
to activate that toy while at sea.
Why don't you just think of this as
being prepared for an emergency?
That's why the Pacific
Fleet is guarding it.
When did the U.N. transform us
into a bloody cargo service?
It was just after a certain
organization was established.
Guarding a toy! What a grandiose
assignment for the Pacific Fleet!
It's still not enough considering
the importance of the Eva.
Would you sign this document?
Not yet. Eva Unit 02 and its pilot
have been entrusted to us
by the Third Branch in Germany.
I won't let you just waltz in,
and do as you please!
Then, when will you transfer
them to us?
Once we've unloaded in
New Yokosuka.
The ocean is our jurisdiction.
You will follow our orders here.
I understand.
However, I should remind you that,
in the case of an emergency,
our, NERV's, authority
overrides yours.
She's cool!
She looks like Ritsuko.
Well, you're as gallant as always.
Kaji!
Mr. Kaji, I must insist that you not
invite yourself onto the bridge.
Oh, sorry about that.
Well, excuse us. Transport us to
New Yokosuka as ordered.
This is a date?
Well, excuse us. Transport us to
New Yokosuka as ordered.
Cool! This is just cool!
Well, excuse us. Transport us to
New Yokosuka as ordered.
Those kids are really going
to save the Earth?
Times have changed.
I understand that Congress has
pinned its hopes on that robot.
On that toy? Idiots!
If they've got money to blow,
they ought to give us a little more.
What are you doing here?!
Accompanying her.
I'm on a business trip
from Germany.
Man, was I careless. I should
have anticipated this.
Hey! Don't touch me!
I can't help it!
Squadron 3 will sortie as scheduled.
My God, why are you so cold?
Do you have a boyfriend now?
Because your fire has gone out.
Outside it's a red hot summer, over 100 degrees.
That's none of your business, is it?
How can you be so mean?
Outside it's a red hot summer, over 100 degrees.
What is this freezing cold?
My heart is below freezing.
You're living with Katsuragi here, aren't you?
My beer is frozen too. I need a coat.
Yes.
Your heart has too much air conditioning.
So, tell me, is she still wild in bed?
Why don't you raise the temperature?
You're the air conditioner.
Wha... wha...
You're so stupid, venting your heat externally.
What are you implying?!
The more heat you vent, the colder my heart.
So, she hasn't changed, has she, Shinji Ikari?
Then, let us warm your frozen body together!
Well...
I'm sorry, you can't light my heart,
How do you know my name?
Well, I ought to know you.
I'm sorry, you can't light my heart,
Put logs on my fire, and stoke me with oil.
You're pretty famous in our business.
Who is it? It can't be... Is it that guy?
The Third Child, who piloted an
Eva in battle with no training.
Who is it? It can't be... Is it that guy?
The Third Child, who piloted an
Eva in battle with no training.
No, it's this puppy.
It was just luck.
You're telling me that I lost to this puppy?
Luck is a part of your destiny. It's a talent.
Yes, he's a good boy.
Well, I'll see you later.
And he's faithful, unlike some people!
See you.
This has got to be a bad joke.
No, a nightmare.
So, what do you think about
Mister Shinji Ikari?
He's boring. That's the great Third
Child? What a disappointment.
Yet his sync ratio was well over
40% in combat with no training.
That can't be!
That captain's attitude
gets on my nerves.
He's got a lot of pride.
Too much pride's bound to make
him cynical about us.
That Mr. Kaji is pretty lively.
He hasn't changed at all, that jerk.
Hey, Third Child!
Come with me!
Red? I didn't know that
Unit 02 was red.
The color isn't the only difference.
After all, Units 00 and 01
were created
as part of a developing process,
prototype and test type.
The fact that it synchronized with
an untrained pilot like you
is proof of that.
However, Unit 02 is
a little different.
Created for actual combat
conditions,
this is the world's first
true Evangelion.
This is the final model!
What was that?
An undersea shock wave!
Something exploded nearby!
What's that?
Is that an Angel?!
Is that a real one?
Oh, my gosh! We've got to go
back, and find Misato.
This is my chance!
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
All ships maintain formation,
and take evasive action!
Status report!
The Cymbeline's gone silent. Titus
Andronicus can't locate the target!
Damn it! What in the hell
is going on here?!
Hello, NERV delivery.
Would you like to order
information on this enemy
and countermeasures to
use against it?
This is a combat situation! No
unauthorized personnel allowed!
This is just my opinion, but I'd say
this must be an Angel attack.
All ships, fire at will!
It's pointless.
An AT field can't be penetrated
with this kind of fire power.
But why is an Angel here?
My God, is it after Unit 02?
Where are you taking me?
Just wait there a second.
I can't believe this.
Don't peep, you pervert!
Sorry!
Why are all boys such
perverted jerks?
Here we go, Asuka.
Why won't it sink?!
I knew it. Only an Eva can beat it!
Let's go.
Come with me!
Hey, what are these
entry-plug suits for?
Are you dense?
We're going to beat it
with my Unit 02!
No way! Do you have approval
from Misato?
I'll get permission after
I've beaten it.
Now, I'll show you how
magnificent my piloting is!
Just don't disturb me.
This is odd. It seems to be
looking for something.
I didn't expect to see
an Angel here.
This isn't how it's supposed
to be, is it?
This is what Unit 02 is for,
and I've generously provided
a second pilot as a reserve.
If worse comes to worst,
you can escape by yourself.
I know.
L.C.L. Füllung!
[Fill in the L.C.L.!]
Anfang der Bewegung!
[Initiating the startup sequence!]
Anfang des Nervenanschlusses!
[Connecting the neural interface!]
Auslösen von Linksneigung!
[Release of the left pitch]
Synchro, Start!
Program error? What happened?
Thought noise! I told you
not to disturb me.
What do you mean?
You're thinking in Japanese,
aren't you? Think in German.
Oh, okay. Baumkuchen...
Fine, stop trying. Switch the
language to basic Japanese.
Evangelion Unit 02, activate.
Telexfrom the Othello! Unit 02
is in the process of activation.
What the...
Nice going, Asuka!
No! Abort the activation
sequence! Reset it!
I don't care! Asuka! Go for it!
What are you doing?! Eva and its
pilot are under our control!
You're violating my
command authority!
What are you talking about?
This is an emergency!
Who gives a damn about
your procedures?
You and your procedures!
You're not serious?!
You do know that Unit 02 is still
using the type-B equipment?
If we fall in the sea,
we're done for!
And if we don't, we'll
be fine, all right?
Shinji, are you in there too?
Yes.
Kids! Two kids!
This is a good opportunity...
Asuka, launch!
It's coming!
Launching!
Where is it?
That way!
We've only got 58 seconds left!
I am well aware of that! Misato!
Get the external power supply
socket onto the flight deck.
I've got it.
What is she going to do?
Here we go! Jump!
Jump?
Run!
The power socket is in place!
Reactor connection completed!
The deck is ready for Eva landing!
All hands, prepare for impact!
I can't believe this!
Eva 02, landing on deck!
No! What a waste!
Target is approaching rapidly!
It's coming! 9 o'clock!
Switching to external power!
Switch completed.
But we don't have any weapons.
The progressive knife should
be good enough.
It's bigger than I thought.
That's what I figured!
What are they going to do?!
Hand-to-hand combat is the
best way to defeat Angels.
Good work, Asuka!
This isn't a game! Look at the
mess you've made of the deck!
See?! It's sinking!
Asuka!
It's impossible to fight under water
with the type-B equipment!
You never know,
unless you try!
What a waste!
How much cable is left?
Another 1,200 meters!
What are you going to do?
We can deal with it somehow.
I've got to do something.
The cable's going to run out!
Brace for the shock!
Damn it!
Eva missed the target!
I've got time to change the disk.
My God! A Yak 38 Custom!
Hey, Katsuragi!
Kaji!
I've got something to deliver,
so I'll be taking off now.
Launch!
Take care of the rest of this,
Captain Katsuragi.
He ran away. I don't believe it!
The target is approaching
Eva again!
It's coming again!
I'll finish it off this time.
What?! It's not working!
That's because this is
B-type equipment.
What're you going to do?!
What am I going to do?
You're the Third Child, aren't
you? Do something!
Here it comes!
A mouth?!
That's because it's an Angel.
Eva 02 has entered the
target's body.
Does that mean that the
Eva's been eaten?
This is like fishing!
Fishing? Yes, fishing!
From a bad situation
to a worse one.
Shut up!
Hey, get off me already,
you pervert!
But we've got to free ourselves.
Asuka, do you read me?
Don't let go of it!
Captain...
What?
I'm requesting your cooperation.
A point-blank assault by two of
the surviving battleships?!
Correct.
We'll scuttle two of the
evacuated battleships
on top of the umbilical
cable to set a trap.
When the Eva opens the target's
mouth, both ships will rush in.
They will fire all of their
bow turret cannons,
and then self-destruct,
destroying the target.
That's absurd!
Absurd, perhaps, but
not impossible.
I understand.
All hands abandon ship! Repeat,
all hands, abandon ship!
The frigates will rescue
the lifeboats!
But what about the Eva?
Not to worry. They'll be fine.
Hey! Don't use Unit 02
without my permission!
Do the two of you understand
the operation?
I'll do my best.
I'm counting on you.
All ships, open the Kingston valve!
Scuttle at point Z.
Roger!
Cable reverse!
Eva has started to surface!
T-minus 70 to contact!
Hey, you're touching my... get off!
But we've got to open its mouth,
or we'll be killed!
T-minus 60 to contact.
Status on the Angel's mouth?
It's still not open!
Both battleships are sinking
towards the target.
Eva is continuing to surface,
T-minus 50 to contact.
No, it won't open!
No time left!
Target has passed beneath
the Tempest!
Hurry! Or you won't make it!
Don't get any strange ideas.
What?
Anyway, just concentrate
on your thoughts.
You can say that again!
T-minus 20 to contact!
T-minus 15 to contact!
Open! Open! Open! Open!
Fire!
Neo-Yokosuka (Old-Odawara)
Christ! That was rather
spectacular!
I had to improvise. I should have
anticipated underwater combat.
It's rare for you to regret anything.
Is this some kind of self-analysis?
Cut it out. We've collected
a lot of valuable data.
Yeah.
Misato...
This really is something special.
A pair of... Look!
I don't believe this!
They broke their synchronization
ratio records, didn't they?
For only seven seconds. It must
have been due to the danger.
Hey, where's Kaji?
He ran off. That idiot's got to be
back at headquarters by now!
It was a pretty eventful trip.
Was it caused by this, I wonder?
It's already restored itself this far.
It's frozen inside dura-bakelite,
but it's still alive.
This is the keystone of the Human
Instrumentality Project, isn't it?
Correct.
This is the first human being.
Adam.
She may have looked cute,
but she was a real bitch.
Well, we won't have
to see her again.
Yeah, old Mister Big Shot has
to see her at work though.
I really feel sorry for you.
My name is Asuka Langley Sohryu.
I'm very pleased to meet you.
To be continued...
Preview
It's the first combination
attack with two Evas...
...but Shinji and Asuka's
minds are out of synch.
Misato develops a plan to coach
them into perfect unison.
Next time:
"Momentarily Unite the Minds"
And, of course, fanservice!