Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Is he going to skip school again?
Shinji, wake up! How long are you
going to keep skipping school?
It's been five days now. Unit 01 has
already been completely repaired.
You're the pilot. Are you going
to just leave it like that?!
Shinji?!
He's run away. That's not
too surprising.
Episode 04:
Rain, Escape and Afterwards
Shinji?
Well...
We're Shinji's classmates, Aida
and Suzuhara, Ma'am.
Aida and Suzuhara?
Yes, Ma'am!
I'm Suzuhara.
Aren't you the boys who got
in Unit 01's entry plug?
Yes, Ma'am!
We're sorry for causing
so much trouble.
The reason we came here today is that
Ikari's been absent ever since then.
So, we came to see if he was okay.
Shinji? He's at the NERV training
facility right now.
Oh, I see.
These are the printouts that were
building up on Shinji's desk.
Oh, sorry for your trouble. Thank you.
Well, we'll be leaving now.
Please say "hi" to Shinji for us.
Yeah, I will. Bye.
This is an unexpected development.
She was a real babe, wasn't she?
Shinji, you idiot!
Jerk!
The next station is Naga'o Toge,
Naga'o Toge.
The exit will switch to the right side.
Thank you for using the
Tokyo 3 Loop Line.
This train will be going out
of service at this station.
Please, make sure you take all of your
belongings as you exit the train.
I've got to go back.
Hey there! We're offering
you a great bargain!
Hot young babes serving
heavenly refreshment!
Special services to heal your tired
body, services to fill you with energy!
You really couldn't detect it, Doctor?!
Yes. An object only ten millimeters
in diameter
crashed into Antarctica at close
to the speed of light.
The technology we had was unable to
predict or prevent such a thing.
It's like hell out there! Just what
is the purpose of science?!
The atmospheric flux caused by the
change in the Earth's axis
has decreased by 3%.
So, it's getting a little better?
No, there's still a tidal wave
approaching at 230 meters a second!
Doctor! We must evacuate!
It's my duty to remain here.
Doctor, choosing death is easy,
but you have an obligation to
watch this living hell!
Idiot.
He's only fourteen years old.
It seems so cruel, making him bear
the burden of mankind's destiny.
We have no choice. We have to use
fourteen year olds to pilot the Evas.
I know.
So, has he called or made contact?
Nothing?
Nothing. I don't think he's going
to come back again.
What are you going to do?
Nothing really.
If he's not going to come back,
that's okay too.
Why?
Because of what happened
after that last battle.
Why did you ignore my order?
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who's in charge of
your operations, right?
Yes.
You're supposed to obey my orders,
you know! Do you understand?
Yes.
I'm warning you, never do it again.
Do you really understand
what I'm saying?!
Yes.
You're not going to get out of this by
just saying yes to everything I say.
I know that. That's enough, isn't it?
We won the battle anyway.
Listen, it may seem easy to go along
with whatever anyone else wants,
but if you get into the Eva with
that attitude, it'll kill you!
I don't care.
It'd be nice if I could say you've
got the right attitude,
but if you expect to get any praise out
of me, you're wrong, Shinji Ikari.
That's not the point. In any case, I'm
the only one who can pilot it, aren't I?
I'll do it.
I see.
If piloting an Eva means nothing
but pain to him,
he shouldn't get into it again.
Otherwise, I'm sure he'll be killed.
But we need pilots.
Captain!
Aida, go on ahead!
But I can't go and leave you behind!
You fool!
No!
There!
The new kid?
Ikari!
Toji was sorry about that.
He said that his kid sister scolded him
and said that, "it was the robot
who saved our lives!"
That's pretty embarrassing, being
chewed out by a second grader.
Right?
I like it at night because those
noisy cicadas don't chirp.
Although I remember that it was
pretty quiet when I was a kid,
there've been more of them each year.
The ecosystem is returning
to its former state.
That's what Misato said.
I see, Misato said so.
I really envy you.
Living with such a beautiful woman
and piloting the Evangelion.
Oh God, I wish I could get behind
the controls just once!
You shouldn't. I think your mother
would be worried.
Oh, don't worry about that.
I don't have one.
I'm the same as you.
You'll have something to eat,
won't you?
Yeah.
Do you usually do this sort of thing?
Well, sure.
Is this some kind of training for
guerilla warfare or something?
How could I fight with toys like those?
It's just for fun.
You're Shinji Ikari, aren't you?
Yes.
We're from NERV Security Intelligence.
Under Article 8 of the Security Act,
we're taking you to NERV HQ.
All right?
Yes.
And all you did was stand there?
That's easy for you to say!
But it's like I said, they were NERV
Security Intelligence, professionals.
So what?! Don't you have
any balls at all?!
Sissy!
Pervert!
Only an idiot fights when he
knows he can't win.
Balls have nothing to do with it.
Long time, no see.
Yes.
Do you feel any better after wandering
around for two days?
I don't know.
The Eva is on standby.
Will you pilot it?
Or won't you?
You're not going to scold
me for running away?
Of course not. I'm not related
to you, am I?
If I say that I won't pilot Unit 01,
what will you do with it?
I suppose that Rei will do it.
Won't you pilot it?
It seems unrealistic for you to
force everything on her.
Don't worry. I'll pilot it.
But you don't want to do it?
Of course not. To begin with, it's not
something that comes to me naturally.
But Ayanami, Miss Misato
and Miss Ritsuko...
Cut that out!
This has nothing to do with any of us!
If you don't like it, get out of here!
Just forget all about Eva and us and
go back to where you came from!
We don't need someone with
that attitude piloting.
The Third Child is leaving
Tokyo 3 tomorrow.
Then, we'll reconfigure Unit 01's
system for Rei.
But...
Regardless of the results of Unit 00's
re-activation experiments,
we'll move on to experimenting
with Unit 01.
According to the Marduk
Organization's report,
the Fourth Child hasn't been found yet.
That means we can't get
any pilot recruits?
Excuse me, where is Miss Misato?
I'd like to say good-bye.
You're no longer NERV personnel.
Therefore, we can't give you
any information.
Ikari!
You left this stuff behind!
Could you excuse me for a moment?
Thank you.
Hey, Toji. Come on, say something!
Ikari, I'm sorry I hit you twice.
Please, hit me back!
I can't do that.
Please! Otherwise, I won't be satisfied.
See? He's a pretty embarrassing
guy, isn't he?
But if it'll put an end to this dispute,
why don't you go ahead and hit him?
But...
Hurry up! You don't have
much time, do you?
Okay, but only once.
Okay! Come on!
Hold it!
Stop. Don't hold back.
Right.
Ouch...
How did you know I'd come here?
It was just a hunch. We've seen dozens
of classmates off before.
If you're leaving, we'll have to leave
this city sometime soon,
but we can't blame you for that.
We saw how you suffered in the Eva.
And if anyone tries to blame you,
I'm gonna give them a head butt!
Hey, don't look so gloomy.
Take care.
Good luck!
Well...
Your time is up.
I'm the one who deserves to be hit!
I'm mean, cowardly, dishonest, weak,
sneaky and a sissy.
Don't give us any more trouble.
He's gone.
Do you really think this
is for the best?
The Hedgehog's Dilemma.
The closer we become, the more
deeply we hurt each other.
Now I understand.
That boy...
He can't let others know how
he feels in any other way.
The Express Linear Train, bound for
Atsugi is arriving on Track 2.
For your safety, please step back to
the area inside the yellow lines.
The train arriving on Track 2 is for
special government use only
and departs at 4:20 for Atsugi.
No civilians are allowed
inside the fence.
Please be aware that the
boarding of this train
by unauthorized persons
is strictly prohibited.
Hang in there.
Hey, look!
Hey, it's that babe!
The local train bound for Gora
is now arriving on Track 4.
For your own safety, please stay
inside the yellow lines.
If you're accompanying
small children,
please ensure that they are
properly supervised.
The train arriving on Track 4 is the
local shuttle to Gora departing at 4:32.
If this is your train, please step inside
and wait until departure.
The train is now approaching.
Please stay behind the yellow line.
I... I'm home.
Welcome home.
TO BE CONTINUED...
Ayanami Rei lives with
minimal contact with others.
Shinji is at a loss to see this girl
who's closer to his father than he.
Before the wound in
his heart heals up...
...the light from an Angel
burns the chest of Eva Unit 01.
The next episode:
Rei, Beyond Her Heart