Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Where's Asuka?
She's already left. It would seem
that she doesn't want to face me.
But why?
Shinji, sometimes a woman's heart
is too difficult to understand.
By the way...
Go ahead.
Is the rumor that Unit 04
disappeared true?
I heard that there was some kind
of accident, and it exploded.
Yes, it's true.
Unit 04 is gone, along with the
Second Branch of NERV.
It happened while they were
testing the S2 engine.
But don't worry, we'll
be all right.
All three of our Evas are
functioning properly.
And our pilots and staff
are in good shape too.
I heard that Unit 03 is being
brought here from America.
You're performing the activation
tests at Matsushiro, aren't you?
I'll be out for four days or so,
but Kaji will be taking care of
you two, so don't worry.
But what about the test?
Ritsuko will be supervising
everything.
There won't be any problems.
And what about the pilot?!
Well, about the pilot...
Yes?
Good morning!
I've come to ask you for your help,
Major Katsuragi!
Please! Make me the pilot
for Evangelion Unit 03!
Episode 18:
The Judgment of Life
So, Shinji still doesn't know yet?
I just couldn't find a chance
to tell him.
I'm worried.
I just can't figure out what
he's thinking about.
Pull yourself together.
You're the one who wanted
to be his guardian.
I know you're right, but...
When will you be acquiring
the pilot?
Well, tomorrow. There are still
some things to be arranged.
Still, the new pilot might
tell Shinji himself.
I don't think so.
He wasn't enthused enough
to be bragging about it.
He was only willing to accept
under the condition that his sister
be transferred to our hospital
here at Headquarters.
How can Misato be this cruel?
I'm eager to be a pilot so she
could at least use me as a backup.
Right, Toji?
What's up? You left before me,
but you're late.
What, no fight between the
newlyweds today?
I just didn't want to see
your ugly faces!
You three damn stooges!
Ah, the precious moment of
lunch time! Hey, where's Toji?
He's gone.
Gone? Without his lunch? Him?
That's impossible!
He's been acting odd lately.
Suzuhara...
Oh, Ayanami, if you're looking
for Shinji, he isn't here.
You know about it, don't you?
And Sohryu knows about
it too, doesn't she?
So Shinji's the only one
who doesn't know.
It's pretty rare for you to be
concerned about someone else.
Really? I'm not sure I understand.
You care about Shinji.
Do I?
Maybe that's true.
Yeah, you do.
Hikari!
Let's have lunch together!
Two hours late, and then,
finally, he arrives.
He's the first guy to ever make
me wait this long.
Yeah, because you never waited
for the guy when you were dating.
This was the so called
Second Impact.
At that time I was living in a
place called Nebukawa,
but the rising water levels caused
by the melting of Antarctica
have buried it beneath the sea.
Sorry, newcomer, but I
had to clobber you!
I had to hit you, or I wouldn't
have been satisfied.
I'm sorry, Asuka. You always
walk home with Ikari.
Forget it. The only reason I'm with
Shinji is because of my work.
And right now I don't feel
like looking at him.
This is about Suzuhara, isn't it?
Yes, how did you know?
It's pretty obvious.
The three stooges are the only
ones who can't see it.
Ikari seems naive.
Actually, he's just a dolt.
He's an idiot too.
He hasn't got any idea as to
how to relate to others.
Really?
I think Suzuhara might
like Ayanami.
Suzuhara?! He likes
that smart ass?!
Well, they seemed to be very
sociable during lunch.
Don't worry. It'll never happen.
She's 10,000 times denser than
Shinji is about communication!
Really?
Really!
Can I ask you one thing?
What?
What do you see in a simple
minded stooge like that?
His compassion...
It was a mistake to get back together with you!
How can you say that now?
Well...
I can still change my life.
Kaji sure spends a lot of time in the tub.
There are lots of pitfalls in life,
but you just have to dig your way out.
I wonder who's going to pilot Unit 03?
And I'm the pitfall?
I don't have to live in sorrow.
You mean you haven't heard yet?
There is always hope after depression.
Who is it?
And I'm the pronoun for your depression?
The only reason I came back was to break up again.
I don't know.
This is too mean.
That was refreshing!
A man who sucks at kissing never works out!
What? Are you two fighting again?
My kissing sucks?
I don't believe it!
Not just your kissing!
Are you two always like this when Katsuragi's gone?
Not just my kissing?!
I knew it!
No!
I want to be happy because you're here tonight.
I knew it!
Why did I repeat the same mistake?
But I can't, not tonight.
Yes, this mistake must be corrected!
I must start a new life free of regret!
I understand. Let's go to bed.
Before you do that,
why don't you get dressed and make the bed?
Sleep is the best thing for these situations.
Are you asleep yet, Kaji?
No, not yet.
What's my father like?
Well, there's a surprise question.
I thought you'd ask
about Katsuragi.
It seems like you're always
with my father.
Commander Fuyutsuki is the one
who's always with him.
Have you been asking around
about your father?
I haven't been around him much.
So, you don't really know him?
But I've learned a lot
about him lately.
About his work, about
my mother, so...
No, you're wrong. You only believe
that you've learned.
The fact is that people really don't
understand themselves,
much less each other.
Understanding one hundred
percent of anything is impossible.
That's why we spend so much
time trying to understand
our own motivations and
those of others.
That's what makes life
so interesting.
Does that mean that you don't
understand Misato either?
The kanji we use for the word "she"
literally means "woman far away".
Women will always be on
the distant shore
of a great gulf of
misunderstanding.
The current dividing men and
women is deeper than the ocean.
I don't understand what being
an adult must be like.
T-minus 300 minutes to
Unit 03 activation test.
Main power supply, no problems.
Second apotheosis is nominal.
Coolant systems are normal.
Repairs to left arm crimp
lock completed.
Roger. Team B, commence
operation.
No problems detected in the
data link to Unit 01.
It's ready enough for
combat duty now.
Well, how nice for you.
Now that was a half-hearted reply.
Are you aware that this unit
will be assigned to you once
it's passed its tests?
The exclusive control
of four Evas...
If you wanted to, you could
destroy the world.
Have you told Shinji yet?
I'll tell him when this
test is over.
The Fourth Child has arrived.
Second squad, begin readying the
entry vehicle immediately.
He's not here yet, Asuka.
He may not come today.
I thought we might eat
together today.
Do you want this?
Unit 03's already in
Japan, isn't it?
Yeah, it got here yesterday.
I knew it. Who's going to pilot it?
Toji maybe? He's absent today,
so maybe it's him.
No way!
Entry plug repairs completed.
Initiating first connection.
Transmitting pulse.
Graph readout is normal.
All checklists up to 1350
have been cleared.
No problems found in initial
contact phase.
Roger. Shift the operation
to phase two.
All nerve links are normal.
All checklists up to 2550
have been cleared.
Harmonics are normal.
We are now exceeding the
absolute border.
Abort the test! Break the circuit!
No good! Mission failure! High
energy readings detected in body!
Impossible!
An Angel?!
An explosion has occurred
in Matsushiro.
Damage level unknown.
Send the rescue squad
and the Third Troop.
Take care of it before the
SSDF gets involved.
Roger.
Movement of an unidentified
object detected at the site.
Wavelength pattern is orange.
It's not confirmed as an Angel.
Go to first stage alert.
All personnel go to
first stage alert.
Prepare for ground combat.
Launch all Evas!
Disperse in the maximum
intercept zone.
Air transport is scheduled
to go in twenty.
An accident in Matsushiro?!
No way! What happened
to Misato?
Contact hasn't been restored yet.
But, then, what will we do?
Stop whining! There's nothing
else we can do now!
But how can we fight the
Angel by ourselves?
Commander Ikari will take
command now.
My father will...
The target's image has been
captured at Mt. Nobe.
Transferring to main monitor.
As I thought...
Transmit the abort signal.
Force eject the entry plug.
Not working. Neither abort signal
nor plug ejection code accepted.
What about the pilot?
He's still breathing and his heart's
beating, but probably...
Abandon Evangelion
Unit 03 at this time.
List it as the Thirteenth Angel.
But!
Disperse the battle line at
Mt. Nobe as planned.
Destroy the target.
Target is approaching.
All units prepare for
ground combat.
No way!
An angel? Is this an Angel?!
Correct, this is the target.
You said that this is the target,
but this is an Eva, isn't it?!
But that's...
How could it have been possessed
by an Angel?
Is it piloted by a human too,
a child like us?
You still don't know?!
The pilot of Unit 03 is...
Asuka?
Asuka?!
Eva Unit 02 has gone silent!
The pilot has ejected. Recovery
squad is heading for retrieval.
Target is moving towards Unit 00!
Rei, avoid close range combat
and stop the target.
I'm sending Unit 01 in now.
Roger.
He's the pilot.
The Angel is invading
Unit 00's left arm.
The nerve systems are
being corrupted.
Cut off the left arm. Immediately!
But you've got to sever the
neural connection first!
Cut it off.
Yes, Sir.
Unit 00 is severely damaged.
The pilot is wounded.
No way...
The target is approaching you.
It will contact you in T-minus 20.
You must destroy it.
But this target is...
Operated by a person, isn't it?
Another child my own age.
An entry plug!
There is a person in there,
just as I thought.
Life support is breaking down.
The pilot's life is in danger.
No! Cut the synch ratio to 60%!
Wait!
But Ikari, the pilot could be killed.
Shinji, why don't you fight?
There's a person in there, Father!
Irrelevant! It is an Angel!
Our enemy!
But... but I can't!
I must help him! I can't kill!
If you don't, you will die.
I'd rather die!
Cut all synchronization between
the pilot and Unit 01. Do it now.
Cut it?
Correct. Switch the control circuit
to the dummy plug.
But the dummy plug still isn't
functioning properly.
Without Dr. Akagi's approval...
It's still better than the pilot.
Do it!
Yes, Sir.
What is this?
What in the hell are you
doing, Father?!
Signal acknowledgment,
confirmed.
Control system switching
is complete.
All nerves linked to the
dummy system.
32.8% of Emotional Elements are
unclear. It can't be monitored.
Irrelevant. Open the system.
Begin the attack.
Is this the power of
the dummy plug?
System status nominal.
Gain still increasing.
Stop this!
Father, no! Stop doing this now!
Damn! Stop!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop!
Eva Unit 03, no, I mean,
the target is completely silent.
How about if I cook this?
Kodama, Nozomi and I...
this recipe is for four.
I sure hope he's going to
eat tomorrow.
We've found a survivor here too!
Third squad, erase 807 data.
Second squad, remove liner block.
Am I still alive?
Blockade all of Highway 20!
Kaji?
Run it from Shinanosakai through Kobuchizawa.
You were lucky, Katsuragi.
The public relations department is handling this.
Where's Ritsuko?
Don't worry.
Two survivors found in the eighth shaft.
She's wasn't hurt as bad as you.
Roger, rescue squad.
I see.
The fire in the temporary cage is...
What about Unit 03?
It was destroyed, as an Angel, by Unit 01.
The fire in the temporary cage is...
Roger, after reconfirmation...
Abandon the Roadway 23!
Yes, Sir. Under 800 meters...
I... I haven't told Shinji anything.
Shinji...
Misato, so you're safe?
I...
I'm sorry.
I had something important to
tell you, but... I'm sorry.
Misato, I...
I killed...
My father forced me to...
I begged him, but...
Shinji, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Report from the entry
plug recovery team.
The pilot's life signs are
confirmed.
He's alive?!
Unit 03's pilot is...
The Fourth Child is...
Toji?
Shinji?
Shinji?!
To be continued...
Preview
On his own, Shinji decides to
quit his position as a pilot.
Once again, the separation begins.
As an Angel destroys Unit 02 and
Unit 00, Shinji makes his decision.
Next episode: "A Man's Fight"