Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Cool! I won a free ice cream bar!
Laundromat
Open 24 hours
Boy, the cost of doing laundry
has been killing me lately.
I just wish I had the time to wash
my clothes for myself.
You should appreciate the fact
you can at least sleep at home.
Don't forget your ticket!
Train arriving.
Hello, Vice Commander.
Good morning, Sir.
Good morning, Sir!
Good morning.
You're quite early today.
Well, I have to go uptown as
Ikari's representative.
I see. Isn't today the City Council's
regular meeting?
It's a boring job.
He always forces the most
tedious work on me.
Without the Magi's help,
I couldn't do it.
Speaking of which, election
day is coming up, isn't it?
The City Council has
no authority at all.
Actually, the Magi run
everything now.
The Magi? You mean the three
super computers?
Government by majority decision
of three different computers.
It's a sort of democratic system.
And the council just obeys
their decisions?
It's a most effective form
of government.
This truly is a City of Science.
We are fortunate to live in an era
when Science reigns supreme.
Talk about old fashioned
viewpoints.
Come to think of it, don't you have
an experiment to run on Unit 00?
Yes, we're going to run the second
prolonged activation test at 10:30.
I'm expecting good news.
Abort experiment! Cut the circuit!
Switching circuits.
Power supply restored.
This component is the
problem again.
Yes. I think the problem is that
the conversion efficiency
is 0.008 lower than our
theoretical calculations.
It's within the tolerance
though, barely.
What are we going to do?
Let's try it again using the
same configuration,
but lower the reciprocal
conversion rate by 0.01.
Roger.
Now, let's recommence the
reactivation experiment.
Episode 11:
In the Still Dark
Hey, hold up!
Man, I've never had to
run this much!
So, what's with the black
expression?
It's from seeing your loathsome
face first thing in the morning.
Yes, hold just a moment please.
What?
Well, Father...
What? Hurry up.
Well,
I'm supposed to
tell my parent that an interview
for Advanced Vocational Education
is going to be held at school.
I've delegated things like that
to Captain Katsuragi.
Don't bother me with
such nonsense.
Don't forward any more
of these calls to...
What?
A black out?
No, it can't be. It's not possible.
Something's strange. An accident?
Perhaps Dr. Akagi
made a mistake?
The main power supply
has been interrupted.
Voltage level is zero!
It's not my fault.
What do you think?
It'll switch to the backup
power supply soon.
No, the backup circuits
aren't working.
That can't be.
Which circuits are functioning?
Only one point two percent!
Only nine circuits out of 2,567!
Connect all remaining live circuits
to the Magi and Central Dogma.
But that could interfere with
life support systems.
Do it! That's our top priority!
Nozomu Takahashi, wants a happier government.
Boy, she's such a lazy slob.
We need your support for this honest candidate.
Can't Katsuragi at least pick up her own laundry?
Thank you!
Maybe Commander Ikari
was just really busy?
I doubt it.
It wasn't like he hung up. It was
more like a mechanical failure.
Hey, are you a man or what?
Stop letting every little
incident bother you!
What?
What do you think you're doing?
Here, let me try that!
Damn! It must be broken!
Heave...
Ho!
We'd better head for the
command station.
It's been seven minutes and the
power hasn't been restored. This...
...is very unusual.
What's the backup power
system here?
There are three circuits, main,
sub and reserve.
It's virtually impossible for all
of those to fail at once.
Then that means...
...the circuit breakers didn't
go on their own.
Someone must have blown
them intentionally.
Regardless of the cause,
it would be disastrous if an Angel
were to attack right now.
Radar has detected an
unidentified object.
Projected landing point is in
the former Atami region.
It must be number eight.
I agree, it must be an Angel.
What are we going to do?
Go to alert status. That's
the procedure, anyway.
This one's destination
has to be Tokyo-3.
I agree. Well, this is no job for us.
The Angel has landed.
It's still advancing.
What about Tokyo-3?
It's still silent.
What in the hell are those
NERV guys doing?
I never thought I'd actually have
to use one of these trap exits.
I thought they were just holdovers
kept for our peace of mind.
To provide is to prevent.
This one doesn't work either!
None of the facilities work.
This is odd.
Could this mean that something's
happened down in the Geo-Front?
It is natural to assume that.
In any case, let's try to make
contact with NERV Headquarters.
No, the emergency phones aren't
getting through either.
No, there's no answer on Line 77.
No, no response.
Not here either. So the main and
emergency cables are both down.
What do we do now?
What're you doing?
What are you, stupid? I'm looking
for my emergency manual.
Anyway, let's go to NERV
Headquarters.
Yeah, but first we'll need to
decide who will be group leader.
And naturally, I am the leader.
Any objections?
Now, let's go.
We can proceed through
Route 07, right here.
But the doors don't work.
We can open it manually.
There you go, Shinji.
That's your job.
I don't believe it! You want
to control everything,
but you always defer to
me at times like this.
Damn those Joint Staff bastards!
They always defer to us at times like this.
What does the government say?
Those Tokyo-2 buttheads?
They're getting ready to run.
The Angel is still advancing.
In any case, we must
contact NERV.
But how?
By going there yourself.
This is the 3rd District ASDF!
An unidentified object is moving
toward this area.
All residents must evacuate to
their designated shelters.
Big trouble! I've got to report
this to Headquarters!
But how?
Remember Takahashi remains
calm even in situations like this!
Please support candidate
Takahashi!
Lucky!
It's too hot.
Yeah, the air conditioners are out.
Katsuragi, if you're so hot, why
don't you take off your shirt?
There's no reason for shyness
between you and me.
Don't even think about trying to
take advantage of this situation.
Okay, okay!
It's getting even worse. Now,
the air is getting stagnant.
Hard to believe this facility represents
the most advanced technology on Earth.
But look at the Commander
and Vice Commander.
Even in this much heat, they're
cool and in command.
It's getting warmer.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
...along with the declaration of
emergency in this district.
Emergency vehicle!
Passing through!
Oh, my! Excuse me, it's blocked!
It's okay! Charge!
This is an emergency!
Everything is permitted!
Aye, Sir!
No! Let me off!
This Geo-Front was designed to
be a self-sufficient colony,
even when isolated
from the outside.
Theoretically, it's impossible
for all of the power sources
to be shut down at once.
You mean that someone
caused it to happen?
Their purpose would be
to map this facility.
So they could determine HQ's
structure through the restoration?
Disrespectful bastards.
I'll run a dummy program
through the Magi.
That will make it harder for them
to get a complete picture.
I'll leave it to you.
Yes, Sir.
I can't believe the first havoc
wreaked upon our headquarters
wasn't caused by an Angel, but by
another member of our species.
One of Mankind's greatest
enemies is Man himself.
But it usually only takes
two minutes.
Are you sure this is the right way?
Yes, I'm sure! If we can get past
this point we'll be there.
Haven't I heard that four
times already?
Picky! You always focus on the
most insubstantial little tidbits.
Silence, please.
What now, Wonder Girl?
A man's voice.
Ang... proaching...
That's Hyuga!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
An Angel is approaching!
Repeat, an Angel is approaching!
An Angel?!
We can't waste any more time.
Let's take a short cut.
Hey, I'm the leader! Don't take any
initiatives without my permission!
Now then, where is this short cut?
This may be the quickest way,
but we look really stupid.
Say, just what do you think
the Angels are?
Why are you talking about that
at a time like this?
Angels are messengers of God but
our enemies are named after them.
So, why are we fighting them?
What are you, stupid? Strange
beings started attacking us.
When someone's attacking you,
you can't just sit and do nothing.
To the right!
I think the correct path is to the left.
Stop bothering me!
What do you think, Shinji?
Well...
I'm not sure.
Damn, I'm the leader, so just
shut up, and follow me!
I expected that this would be a
little odd. The path is going up.
What do you mean, "expected?"
You always nit-pick and worry!
Look, this has got to
be it this time!
Well, we've visually confirmed
the Angel's presence.
Now, we know we have to hurry.
Angel is approaching! Immediate
Eva dispatch will be necessary!
Oh, my gosh!
Fuyutsuki, take care
of the rest of this.
Ikari?
I will help prepare for the
launch in the cage.
Are you serious?
You mean by hand?
We have a diesel generator
for such emergencies.
But...
We have no pilots!
Not again!
This way.
I've heard that you're the
Commander's favorite, aren't you?
You're a favored smart ass who's
treated differently than us.
Stop it! This isn't the time for that!
You've always got that smug
look on your face.
Do you think you can act superior
just because you're treated better?
I don't act superior.
And I'm not treated better either.
I know that quite well.
Roger. Ejection of the termination
plug is complete.
Good, prepare to insert
the entry plug.
But the pilots aren't here yet.
Don't worry, they'll come.
There's no way I can open
this with my hands.
It can't be helped. We'll have to
break into a duct to get through.
This First Child isn't someone
to mess with.
She'll do anything to accomplish
her objectives.
She's a real self-righteous bitch.
The plug is fixed and ready.
Now, we just have to
wait for the kids.
If you dare look forward,
I'll kill you!
You jerk! Ignoramus! Nincompoop!
I told you not to look!
I have to see to go forward!
Ah, there you are.
Prepare for entry!
Roger, open the hatches manually.
How are the Evas?
They're in standby.
How? Nothing's working.
It was all done by hand.
It was the Commander's idea.
My father's?
Commander Ikari believed in you
three, and prepared everything.
Plugs inserted.
All units activated using
backup power supply.
Remove primary lock bolts.
Hydraulic locks numbers 2
through 32, released.
Zero pressure.
The situation is free.
Go ahead and remove
the restraints.
Begin the attack!
The target has stopped
right above us.
Get ready! Hurry up!
The emergency batteries
have been installed!
Well, we're ready.
Launch!
Geez! I look so pathetic!
We're approaching a vertical shaft.
This is still pathetic.
Watch out! Dodge!
No!
It appears the target is going to
invade HQ using liquid solvent.
What'll we do?
We're going to beat it, of course.
Sure, but how?
We dropped our rifles, and the
battery packs are running out.
They won't last more than
another three minutes.
I have a plan.
One of us will take the defensive
position, and stay here.
Their job is to neutralize
the Angel's AT Field,
and to protect the offensive
player from that acid.
The backup player
will go down, pick up the rifles,
and hand them to the offense.
The offense will then fire a volley
to destroy the target.
How does that sound?
I see, I will take the defense.
Sorry, but it's not you.
It's me.
It's too dangerous!
That's why.
I'll feel bad if I don't repay you for
the one I owe you from last time.
Shinji will be the offense.
Wonder Girl is the backup.
Got it?
Understood.
Here we go!
CHARGE!
Ayanami!
Asuka, get out of the way!
Now, we're even.
Oh, damn it! Why doesn't it open?!
This is a desperate situation!
I've got to go to the bathroom!
Hey, I told you not to look up!
Okay! Yes, Ma'am!
Disgusting...
It's ironic.
Without electricity and artificial
light, the sky looks so beautiful.
But without the lights, it's as if
there were no humans there.
See? I feel much more
comfortable this way.
Man has always feared the Darkness, so
he scrapes away at its edges with fire.
He creates life by diminishing
the Darkness.
A philosopher!
Is that what makes Mankind
a special species?
Is that why the Angels
keep attacking us?
What are you, stupid?
Who knows what they think?
To be continued...
Preview
Misato's career has been a crusade
to exterminate the Angels.
Shinji finds a similar
sentiment within himself.
The largest Angel yet comes
flying through the stratosphere,
making many people abandon all hope.
Next time:
"The Value of a Miracle"
Watch it with everyone together.