Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Are you ready, Shinji?
Yes.
Release the final safety lock!
Evangelion Unit 01, lift off!
Shinji, just concentrate on
walking right now.
Walk...
It walked!
Shinji, are you okay?
Hurry! Get up!
Shinji, calm down! That's not your arm!
What's going on with the
Eva's defense system?
The signal's not working!
The field's not unfolding!
Have we failed?
Left arm damaged!
The circuits have snapped!
Shinji, dodge!
There's a crack on the front
of the brain case!
The armor won't last much longer!
The head's been damaged!
Extent of damage, unknown!
The control nerves are breaking off!
We're not getting any readings
on the pilot!
Shinji!
This ceiling is unfamiliar.
EPISODE 2:
UNKNOWN CEILINGS
So, the Angels have returned?
It's so sudden.
It's the same as it was
fifteen years ago.
A disaster comes as it will,
without warning.
On the positive side, our previous
investments will not go to waste.
You can't be sure about that yet.
If it doesn't pay off, it's a
waste all the same.
Correct. Now that the Angels have
become common knowledge,
we have to manipulate the
information to avoid trouble.
NERV must take care of
these matters quickly.
It's already been taken care of.
You may rest assure of that.
In regards to the declaration
of the state of emergency,
government officials
have announced...
This incident was...
UN forces in Japan...
Public scenario B-22, as we thought.
So, we're hushing up the truth again?
No, there's no threat of contamination
from the center of the explosion.
But at least our Public Relation people are thrilled.
No, there's no threat of contamination
from the center of the explosion.
But at least our Public Relation people are thrilled.
The only Angel samples collected
were adhered to the Eva.
Now that they've finally got something to do.
The only Angel samples collected
were adhered to the Eva.
We're being pretty casual about it.
The only Angel samples collected
were adhered to the Eva.
We're being pretty casual about it.
Correct, as in the model simulation,
approximately 99.9% of it evaporated.
I don't think so. I think we're all scared to death.
Correct, as in the model simulation,
approximately 99.9% of it evaporated.
Of course we are.
Well, we must acknowledge that.
Speaking of which, Mr. Ikari,
isn't there a better way to
utilize NERV and Eva?
We're referring to the repair
costs for Unit 01,
which when added to the
costs for Unit 00,
are enough to bankrupt
an entire country.
We also understand that you gave that
particular toy to your son, didn't you?
Manpower, time and money.
How much more will be wasted
by you and your family?
And that is not your only
responsibility.
The Human Enhancement Project,
that should be your top priority.
Yes, in these desperate circumstances
that project is our only hope.
Do you understand?
In any case, the Angel is no excuse
for delaying that project's schedule.
However, we will consider
adjusting the budget.
Now, the rest of this meeting
concerns only us.
Your presence here was
appreciated, Mr. Ikari.
Ikari, you do understand there can
be no turning back, don't you?
I know.
Mankind has no time left.
Air conditioning has just got to be
mankind's greatest treasure.
It's the triumph of science over nature.
Shinji's woken up.
How is he?
No external injuries. His memory
is a bit muddled, however.
You don't think it could
be brain damage?
The doctor said that there was
nothing to worry about.
Really?
I suppose he did have a
pretty hectic day.
His cranial nerves must have
taken a lot of strain.
Don't you mean his heart?
Okay, go on.
Yeah, that way. Stop.
If Eva and this city both operate
at their full potential,
maybe we can make it through this.
Are you going to defeat the Angels?
You're always such an optimist.
Sometimes you need a little wishful
thinking just to keep on living.
I see your point. Your attitude makes
me feel a little more at ease.
See ya!
Dr. Ugai of Internal Department
One, Dr. Ugai,
please call Dr. Azuma of the First
Surgical Department immediately.
The medical conference on the B
Experiment will be held as scheduled.
All supervisors please proceed
to conference room two.
Are you sure?
They don't want to live together?
I think that living apart is natural
for Ikari and his son.
And being together is unnatural?
Alone?
Right. His room will be in the Sixth
Block, just beyond this one.
Is that satisfactory?
Yes.
Are you sure? Shinji...
It's fine. Being alone is okay with me.
I'm alone anyway.
What?!
So, I said, I'll take care of Shinji.
I've already got permission
from the brass.
Hey, it's not like I'm going to
"put the moves" on him.
Of course you're not! How could you
even think of such a thing?
You're always like that. Shame on you!
She just can't take a joke.
Well, we'll have to have a
party tonight, right?
What for?
What for? A welcoming party for my
new roommate, of course!
So, you're going to move after all?
Yes. I'd never have dreamt that this
city would become a battlefield.
Yeah.
My husband's saying that our kid and
I should move, at the very least.
Don't I know it.
This city may be a fortress, but that's
no guarantee of safety.
Just remembering it gives
me the chills.
Really.
I hope you don't mind if we make
a little stop on the way.
Where?
Someplace really cool.
So desolate. This city seems so lonely.
It's time.
Amazing! The buildings are growing!
This city is a fortress, designed to
protect against the Angels.
This is Tokyo 3.
This is our city.
And it's the city that you saved.
NEON GENESIS
EVANGELION
Your things should have already
been delivered, Shinji.
I just moved into this apartment too.
Come on in.
Pardon the intrusion.
Shinji, this is your home now.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
As you can see, the place
is a little bit messy.
Make yourself comfortable.
You call this
a "little bit" messy?
Oh! Sorry! Could you put
the food in the fridge?
Sure.
Ice,
snacks
and tons of beer.
What kind of a life does she lead?
Excuse me. What's in the other fridge?
Oh, don't mind that. He's
probably still sleeping!
Sleeping?
Let's eat!
Let's eat.
Life just doesn't get any
better than this!
Don't you want to eat? It's good,
even if it is all instant.
I'm sorry, I'm just not used to it.
That's no excuse! You
can't be so finicky.
No, that's not what I... well...
Isn't this nice?
Having two for dinner instead
of eating alone!
Yeah...
Here we go for the next one.
Paper, stone and scissors...
Pon! Pon! Pon! Pon!
Sorry, Shinji.
Okay! That was a pretty fair way of
splitting our daily chores, right?
Yeah.
This is your home now, so make
yourself comfortable,
and take advantage of everything
here, except me.
Yes.
Man, yes, yes, yes. Is that all you
say? It's getting on my nerves.
You're a boy, aren't you?
Act like a man! Okay?
Yes.
Okay, that's just the way you are.
Well, why don't you go take a bath
and scrub away those bad memories.
Bathing cleanses both
the mind and soul.
Miss Misato!
What?
A p... p... p...
Oh, him? He's one of those new
warm water penguins.
What was that?
His name is Pen-pen.
He's your other roommate.
Why don't you cover that up?
I guess I'm not being as
nice as I ought to.
Of course, he's probably already
made up his mind about me.
Misato Katsuragi.
She's not a bad person.
Bathing cleanses both
the mind and soul.
But bad memories always seem to
find me when I'm in the bath.
Like my father
and Rei Ayanami.
So, how was Rei today?
You did see her at the hospital
this afternoon, didn't you?
She'll be ready to work
again in twenty days.
By then, we'll be ready to re-activate
Unit 00 from cryo-stasis.
It's so hard on these poor children.
There is no one else who
can pilot the Evas.
As long as they survive, that
is what I'll have them do.
With no regard to what
they may want?
Yeah, after all the horrible
stuff he went through,
I doubt that he'll pilot it again.
Maintaining him is part
of your job, Misato.
I'm just scared. I don't know
how to deal with him.
Grumbling already? It was your idea
to take him in, you know.
Shut up!
I was just thinking of Shinji as a tool.
I'm as shameless as Ritsuko.
We destroyed the Angel.
So, why can't I be happy about it?
Another unfamiliar ceiling.
Of course. In this whole city, there's
no place that's familiar.
This is your home.
Why am I here?
The brain case has been damaged!
Extent of damage unknown!
We're having problems
maintaining activation!
Status report!
The synchrograph is reversing!
The pulses are flowing backward!
Break the circuit! Block it!
We can't! It's not accepting the
signal! It won't take it!
What about Shinji?
His monitors aren't responding.
His condition's unknown!
Unit 01's gone completely silent!
Misato!
We've got to stop this.
Abort the operation! Rescuing the
pilot is our first priority!
Eject the entry plug!
We can't! It's completely
out of control!
No way!
The Eva's re-activating!
Impossible! How could this happen?!
Impossible!
A berserker?!
It looks like we've won.
An AT field!
No! As long as the Angel
has that AT field up...
He can't get near the Angel!
The left arm has been regenerated!
Incredible!
Unit 01's expanding an
AT field of its own!
It's neutralizing the phase space!
No, not neutralizing, it's eroding it!
Unbelievable! It went through
that AT field so easily.
No! It's going to self-destruct!
Is the Eva...
That must be the Eva's
true form.
Circuits reconnected.
Systems restored. Graphs
back to normal.
Pilot life signs, confirmed.
Send out the recovery team. Hurry!
Preserving the pilot's life
is our first priority.
Shinji, can I come in?
I forgot to tell you something.
You did a very good thing today.
You should be proud of yourself.
Good night, Shinji.
Hang in there.
TO BE CONTINUED
Preview
Shinji starts a new life with the training
of Eva, school, and a roommate.
...but once he's known as the pilot of
Eva, he becomes popular in his class.
Next time: "A Phone That Never Rings."
And of course, I'll give you good service!