Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Hey, have you seen her yet?
Oh, yeah! Yeah!
Seen who?
You dork, you haven't seen
the foreign girl yet?
Foreign girl?
Yeah, she's in 8th grade, Class A.
She just transferred
here last week.
She's hot!
Her name's Asuka Langley Sohryu,
did you know that?
Yeah, she's so cute.
Since she was raised over
there but born here,
do you think she already
has a boyfriend?
Don't be stupid!
I bet she broke up in Germany,
and she's here in a foreign land
with a heart that can't be mended.
To Asuka Soryu
Oh my gosh...
Did you hear all the cat talk?
Asuka! Asuka!
They're just ignorant.
Thank you, come again.
At least the pictures don't
reveal her personality.
Hello!
Shinji!
Guten Morgen!
Guten Morgen.
Hey, why so gloomy? This is the
gorgeous Asuka greeting you!
You should appreciate your
good fortune!
I'm the most popular
girl in school!
Hey, the other one's
here too, isn't she?
Other one?
What are you, stupid? I'm talking
about the First Child, of course!
Oh, Ayanami...
Hello!
You must be Rei Ayanami,
the pilot of the prototype.
I'm Asuka! Asuka Langley Sohryu.
I'm the designated pilot of Eva
Unit 02. Let's be good friends!
Why?
Because it'd be convenient.
You know what I mean?
If I'm ordered to, I will.
Talk about odd.
I'll say. Are only weirdos
chosen to be pilots?
You've lost some weight.
Is that so?
You must be enduring an
unrequited love.
How did you know?
Because...
"A woman with a mole in the
pathway of her tears
is destined to a life full of them."
If you're trying to put a move on
me, I'm afraid you can't.
There's a very ugly face
observing us.
Long time no see, Kaji.
It's been a while.
You're a little less discreet
than I expected.
He hasn't ever been
discreet in his life!
You've handed over Unit 02,
right? You should be leaving now!
I just received orders this morning
that I'll be staying here on loan.
So we can hang around again,
just like we used to.
You've got to be kidding!
Enemy attack?!
We just got this report from
the battle cruiser Haruna.
"Huge submerged object detected
off Kii peninsula. Sending data."
The data has been collated
and examined.
Wavelength pattern Blue.
Confirmed to be an Angel.
All personnel, go to
first stage alert.
Episode 9:
Momentarily Unite the Minds.
The recent battle severely
damaged the intercept system.
Only twenty-six percent of our
defense capability is available.
And our operational capability for
actual combat is virtually nil.
Therefore, we're going to have
to intercept the target
at the water's edge, right
before it makes landfall!
Units 01 and 02 will mount an
attack in a series of waves.
In other words, close in
and take turns.
Roger.
This sucks. My Japanese debut,
and she won't let me solo.
Why do I have to bring you?!
It can't be helped.
Procedures, you know?
Well, let me tell you something,
just don't get in my way!
His selection as a pilot must
have been a joke, right?
Two against one is not what I call
a fair fight. It's not fair.
We don't get a choice.
Survival takes priority.
There!
Commence attack!
I'll handle this Angel!
You cover me!
Cover you?
Ladies first!
Damn it, don't give me orders,
you dumb rookie!
Charge!
That wasn't bad.
What did you think of
that, Third Child?!
A fight should be clean, elegant
and without waste.
What's this crap?
Today, at 10:58:15 AM,
Unit 01 was attacked
by Target Alpha,
which separated from the target
submerged 2 km off Suruga Bay.
At the same time, plus 20 seconds,
Unit 02 was halted by Target Beta.
We have a comment from
E-Project chairperson.
This is pathetic.
This is all your fault! You totally
screwed up my debut battle!
What are you talking about?
You're the one who charged in
there acting like an idiot!
Idiot?! How dare you call me that?
Pathetic excuse for a combat pilot!
You're just a jerk!
Look in the mirror!
In your rush to show off, you
completely ignored procedures!
What was that? You look like a drowned rat!
At 11:03 AM, NERV abandoned the operation
You can't say that kind of thing to me!
And yielded command to the UN Secondary Force.
We've been humiliated.
At 11:05 AM, UN forces attacked with an N2 mine.
We'll have to re-draw
the map again.
They succeeded in burning off 28%
of the target's structural substance.
Did they kill it?
They succeeded in burning off 28%
of the target's structural substance.
Did they kill it?
This is merely temporary relief. A
second attack is a matter of time.
At least we have time to regroup.
You can't ask for more than that.
Listen up, you two.
Do you know what your job is?
Piloting Eva.
No! Your job is to defeat
the Angels.
NERV does not exist to make
grotesque displays like this.
Therefore, you two
must cooperate.
Why should we?!
Enough already.
Why does everyone get
so angry here?
It's because adults are much too
aware of their credibility.
Where's Misato?
Clearing things up. The person in
charge must take responsibility.
Here are the internal protests
and damage reports.
This is a bill from the UN,
and here you have complaints
from the PR department as well.
Read them all.
I can tell what they say
without looking.
"If you're going to fight,
don't do it here," right?
Good guess.
I'll do it as soon as we take
care of this Angel.
I swear I will destroy that Angel.
The Vice Commander
is pretty angry.
You'll almost certainly be demoted
if you embarrass him again.
It was good luck within bad luck
that Commander Ikari wasn't here.
If he'd been here, you'd have been
fired before he ever saw these.
So, have you brought me an
idea to help save my job?
Just one.
I thank you, Dr. Ritsuko Akagi.
It's good to have a friend
one can count on.
However, I'm not the one who'll
be saving my old friend.
This is Kaji's idea.
Kaji?
I'm home! Not that anyone's
here, of course, but...
What is this?!
Don't be so rude!
Those are my personal
belongings!
You! What in the blazes are
you doing in my house?
Why are you still here?
Still here?
You've been dumped for
the new model!
Misato will be living with me.
That's a more logical choice when
you consider my superior abilities.
Although honestly, I'd
rather live with Kaji.
Say, just why are Japanese
houses so small anyway?
Not even half of my stuff fits!
Shinji's Room
And the Japanese sure don't
have any sense of privacy.
How can they live in a room
without locks? Unbelievable!
It's because the Japanese way
is to consider the priorities and
needs of others before one's own.
Misato!
How are you? You two are going
to get along real well, right?
What do you mean?
This is all preparation for
the next operation.
Say what?
There is only one way to destroy
the seventh Angel!
A simultaneous two-point attack
on each target's core
while its components
are separated.
In other words, an attack by two
Evas with synchronized timing.
Cooperation and coordination
between you will be paramount.
Therefore, I want the two
of you to live together.
No way!
A boy and girl should never sleep
together after the age of seven!
The Angel is currently
restoring itself.
It will begin its second assault
in six days, so there's no time.
But it's impossible.
Now, we have a way to
make it possible!
The master attack pattern will be
choreographed using this music.
In six days, as soon as possible.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
I'm worried about Shinji.
He's been gone three days, right?
Hey, there's the class rep.
Two of the three stooges.
Why are you here?
To offer condolences to Miss
Sohryu. What about you two?
To offer condolences to Ikari.
Why did you stop here?
Yes?
You've betrayed us!
You look like two peas in a pod.
I can't believe this!
Neither can we. It's all
Misato's fault!
We have to eat, breathe
and sleep together!
You're living in sin! How awful!
No, it's not like that!
Then, just what is it like?
Hi, welcome everybody!
Why don't you explain
all this to us?
You should have told us that first.
How is the coordination coming?
Well, as you can see.
Well, so much for synchronization!
I could never sink to the pathetic
level this animated turnip lives at!
If you ask me, this whole
idea is impossible!
Then you give up?
But you don't have anyone
else, do you?
Rei?
Yes, Ma'am.
Why don't you try?
Why don'tyou try?
Yes, Ma'am.
Why don't you try?
It looks like I should alter the
operation to pair Shinji and Rei.
No! I can't stand this!
I can't take it anymore!
Asuka!
Even the Devil cries sometimes.
Ikari!
You've got to follow her!
You made her cry! It's your fault!
Well...
Don't say anything.
I know.
I have to pilot the Eva.
I've got no choice.
I'll do it.
No matter what, I'll put Rei
and Misato to shame!
You don't have to squash them.
You're being too simplistic,
even if you are a man!
I must avenge myself.
My pride...
It's a matter of honor
now, you see?
2 days left
Tomorrow: Attack
Where's Misato?
At work. She called earlier.
She'll be there all night.
So that means we're
all alone tonight.
This is the impenetrable "Wall
of Jericho", Third Child.
Take one step over this wall
and you'll be a dead man.
And now, it's time for children
to go to bed!
Why do the Japanese sleep on
the floor? This is so stupid.
Mama...
You're just a child yourself.
No, somebody will see us.
Who's watching?
Someb...
No! There's nothing
between us anymore.
Don't do that again.
But your lips didn't say no.
Which one should I trust?
Your lips or your words?
There you go.
Thanks.
You're unusually sober today.
Yeah, a little.
Work? Or a man?
A lot of things.
Still in love?
Don't be ridiculous!
Who'd want that idiot?!
I was young, and it's still the
biggest blemish on my whole life.
I meant that he may still like you.
Did I scare you?
Why you lousy...
You're only proving
my hypothesis.
Why don't you go with
your feelings?
It's not like it's still
eight years ago.
It hasn't changed. Not a bit.
He's still immature.
Well, I've got to get to work.
Tomorrow is D-day.
Target has broken through the
final defense line at Gora.
Here it comes!
We won't fail this time!
Spread your AT fields as soon
as the music starts.
Then follow the operation
choreography.
Are you two ready?
Roger!
The target has entered
the mountains.
Just remember Shinji, full power,
maximum performance.
I know that. We'll finish in
sixty-two seconds.
Target entering Ground Zero.
Detach external power cables.
Launch.
Confirmation. Both Evas
are operational.
Geez...
This is pathetic.
You jerk! What are you doing
on my Unit 02?!
What are you talking about?
You're the one who fell on me!
You're the one who lost
his timing first!
You're always so slow!
What were you doing, staying
up so late last night?!
Image training for today's battle!
Liar! I know you tried to kiss
me while I was sleeping!
You cheat! You were awake?
Oh, my gosh! I was just kidding!
Did you really kiss me?!
No, I didn't! I stopped!
Pervert! Fiend! Idiot!
I can't believe this!
You caused it by calling for your
mother and sleepwalking!
Those kids are embarrassing
us again.
To be continued...
Preview
In the crater of Mount Asama
lies an unhatched Angel.
NERV personnel attempt the
first capture of an Angel.
An Eva with special equipment
challenges the fires of Hell!
Next episode:
Magma Diver
Next time, service, service.