Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
The fiction has become the reality.
How ironic, that the experiment's
advocate became its victim.
So, you believe that the Contact
Experiment was the direct cause?
Her mental breakdown was
a result of the contact.
Even so, this is too cruel,
committing suicide and leaving
such a young girl behind.
Perhaps, but I believe there may
have been additional causes.
Asuka darling, Mama cooked
your favorite for you.
Oh, no, you have to eat this, or
that girl will laugh at you.
She's like that every day.
She sits there talking to that doll
as if it were her real daughter.
I think it's because of the
guilt she must feel.
She devoted her life to research,
not to taking care of her daughter.
I sympathize with your grief.
But it's like looking at porcelain
figures of a mother and her child.
Perhaps not much is different
between humans and dolls.
Man creates dolls in
his own image.
If God exists, it's possible that
we're all just dolls to him.
That doesn't make you sound like
much of a modern physician.
I may be a doctor, but I'm a human
being and a woman first.
You're a strong girl, Asuka, but
it's all right if you want to cry.
I'm okay. I won't cry.
I can think for myself.
Can you hear me, Asuka?
Your synch ratio has dropped
an entire eight points.
Don't think of anything else, just
concentrate the way you used to.
I'm trying!
Episode 22
Don't be
Asuka's synch ratio is getting
lower and lower.
This is extremely troublesome.
We don't have a spare now.
Maybe we'd better make repairing
Rei's Unit 00 top priority.
We can't afford to repair them
both at the same time.
Mitosis in Unit 02's left arm has
cleared the numerical requirement.
Necrosis development is currently
under point zero five percent.
Apotheosis process is in
nominal status.
Unit 00's regeneration process
is currently stable.
Connecting receptors to the
secondary terminals.
The Eva series was born
from Adam.
Now we're using the force which
caused the Second Impact
to defeat the Angels.
Attempting to harness the engine
of our own destruction.
Only humans are so foolish.
After all, I myself hate the Evas.
Revenge for my father?
Major Katsuragi!
They've started construction on
Evas up through Unit 13?
At seven different locations
around the world?
This is information that came via
Shanghai. The source is reliable.
Why are they speeding up the
construction process now?
Well, we've lost two Evas recently,
and two more Evas are currently
severely damaged.
So I'd assume that they're
accelerating
to create a reserve force for
their contingency plans.
Perhaps...
But we've been receiving spare
parts from Germany
that were originally intended
for Eva Units 05 and 06.
They've been spending
a lot of cash lately.
They just doubled the budget.
I think the brass are being
driven by something.
Yeah, I can feel the
Committee's impatience.
Well, could they be doing
this in anticipation
of intercepting multiple
Angels at once?
Could be.
Except there's no reason for them
to do it outside official channels.
There must be some other reason.
This is the first time we've gotten
together in a while,
so what's with the gloomy
atmosphere?
I'm finished.
Asuka!
I'm not getting it. After all, it's
probably Kaji calling for you.
You should get it.
Never again.
Oh no, I'm sorry that our
mighty invincible Shinji
should have to be bothered
with such a thing.
Yes, hello?
I can't stand the way
he's so aloof!
It's a call from Germany for Asuka.
It's your mother.
For me? My mama?
Give me that!
[Hello Mother! It's been awhile since we talked...]
Hallo Mutter! Wir haben uns lange nicht gehört ...
When she's speaking in a different language,
she seems like a different person.
[Oh, no way. He's a lonely person...]
Ach, niemals. Er ist ein einsamer Mensch ...
[Yeah, really? Ah I see... that's great...]
Ja, ja, wirklich? Ach, so... Das ist aber toll...
Mother...
[I hope it won't be raining. I need to go to bed.]
Hoffentlich gibt's keinen Regen. Ich muß ins Bett.
[Talk to you later. Good night.]
Auf Wiederhören. Gute Nacht.
You were on the phone
quite a while.
Well, it was just a routine
periodic communication.
I wish I could talk with my family.
Well, it's just for show.
She's not my real mother.
But it's not like I hate
her or anything.
I just feel uncomfortable
talking with her.
Why am I telling you this?!
Sorry.
I know I've hit rock bottom when
I get sympathy from you!
Synchrograph, minus 12.8. It's
barely over the starting indicator.
That's pathetic. It's a worse
score than yesterday.
Asuka's not feeling well, it's the
second day of her period.
Synch ratio scores aren't
influenced by physical disorders.
The problem's in her subconscious.
We may have to replace Unit 02's pilot.
Asuka, you're finished now.
Maintenance of Power Grid 8 will
begin this evening at 18:00 hours.
Asuka's pride has been badly damaged.
Maintenance of Power Grid 8 will
begin this evening at 18:00 hours.
It's hard to blame her after she
was defeated so badly.
Primary Command Center team
It's hard to blame her after she
was defeated so badly.
Will meet as scheduled.
Even worse, she feels Shinji beat her.
All General Affairs personnel are
to report to Conference Room 2.
Maybe it's beyond our limits.
All General Affairs personnel are
to report to Conference Room 2.
Maybe it's time for us to
stop living together.
So, you've hit your breaking point?
Are you fed up with your
nice imitation family?
That from someone who uses cats
to fill the holes in her own life.
I'm sorry. I'm just a little upset.
Why do I suffer through this
just because I'm a girl?
I don't want to have
children anyway.
Route 7 Loop is currently closed
due to an accident.
Please use Route 12 as a detour.
If you don't open your mind to her,
your Eva will not move.
Are you saying that I'm
shutting myself out?!
Yes, because your Eva has
her own mind.
The robot does?
You're aware of it, aren't you?
I don't know what happened to
make you start talking to me.
It must be an omen of a
disaster or something!
What?! Are you happy that
I can't pilot my Eva?!
Don't worry! When an
Angel comes,
our invincible Shinji will
destroy it anyway!
We don't have to fight!
They only need Shinji!
When a wind-up doll like you
starts being sympathetic to me,
I've really hit rock bottom.
I am not a doll.
Shut up! You do anything you're
ordered to, don't you?!
You'd kill yourself if Commander
Ikari told you to, wouldn't you?!
Yes, I would.
Then you're a toy, just
like I thought!
You're an unthinking, emotionless
doll, and I hate you!
Everyone! I hate everyone!
Shinji's absent again today.
It's nothing unusual for Ayanami
not to show up, but...
Asuka's missing too.
And Suzuhara can't leave
the hospital yet.
I guess it's gotten so serious they
can't come to school anymore.
Eva Unit 02's signals
all read nominal.
Connection and fusion of VA's
are within normal limits.
The field of proliferation is within
the expected range.
You're my doll, so move like I
tell you to, and don't argue!
Why does a weapon need a mind?
It just gives you trouble.
Anyway, you must obey my orders!
This is stupid.
All personnel, go to first stage
alert! Prepare for aerial assault!
An Angel? They're still coming?
Visual confirmation of Angel.
This is maximum magnification.
It's not moving from its orbit.
It's maintaining a constant
distance from our position.
So, does that mean that it's
looking for a place to land?
Or that it's going to destroy
us from up there?
We can't attack it easily
from this position.
Unless it comes into our range,
there's nothing we can do.
The Evas can't destroy an
enemy that's in orbit.
What's Rei's status?
She and Unit 00 are both
in good condition.
Understood.
Sortie Unit 00. Prepare for
extreme long range firing.
Unit 02, Asuka, be ready to
sortie as her backup.
Backup? Me? For Unit 00?!
That's right, take the rear
guard position.
You can't be serious.
Eva Unit 02 launch!
Asuka!
It's okay. Let her take the point
if that's what she wants.
Major Katsuragi?!
If she fails this time, Asuka won't
be allowed to pilot anymore.
You mean this is her last chance?
Let's start preparing to replace
Unit 02's pilot, just in case.
Yes, Ma'am.
Excuse me, but aren't you
going to sortie Unit 01?
It's to remain frozen. Those are
Commander Ikari's orders.
After what happened,
it's a good idea.
If I fail this time, they're not going
to let me pilot anymore.
You can't make any mistakes
this time, Asuka.
The target is still out of range.
Why in the hell are you so slow?!
Come on down, you lazy Angel!
The Angel has a particle
beam weapon?!
No, there are no thermal emissions
being detected.
We've got abnormal readings
in her psychograph!
Mental contamination
is about to begin!
The Angel's making a
psychic attack?
The Angels can't understand
our minds that well!
God damn it!
Positrons dissipated!
It's not working! It's too
far out of range!
Unit 02's rifle is out
of ammunition.
What's the result of the
beam analysis?
It's an energy oscillation pattern
on a visible wavelength.
It's similar to an AT Field, but
we don't know much more.
How's Asuka?
It's bad! The mental contamination
is crossing her ego borderline!
No!
Don't! Don't come into me!
Get out of my mind!
Please! Don't rape my mind!
Asuka!
Psychograph shows she
can't take anymore!
Yes, her mental circuits
are being destroyed.
This is too dangerous for her.
Asuka! Retreat!
No!
That was an order! Asuka, retreat!
No! Never!
I'd rather die than retreat now!
Asuka!
Accelerator synchronization initiated.
Voltage is increasing. Approaching pressure zone.
Compulsory focus convergence, activated.
Correction for the Earth's rotation
and gravity, point zero three.
Pressure in the chamber is at maximum.
Release the final safety lock. All
personnel, prepare for firing.
No effect! There wasn't enough energy
to penetrate its AT Field from this distance.
We're at maximum power output!
We can't get any more power!
Unit 02's psychograph
is getting weak!
What about the LCL mind barrier?
Negative! We can't even hope
for a buffering effect.
Switch top priority to life support.
Don't allow any feedback.
Yes, Ma'am!
That ray scanned her mental
wavelength, and adapted to it.
Impossible! Is the Angel trying to
analyze a human mind?
Why am I crying? I swore that
I wouldn't cry anymore.
What's wrong, Asuka?
This is a present from your new
mother. Don't you like it?
No!
But why not?
Because I'm not a child!
I'll grow up faster than
other people.
I don't need a stuffed toy.
Please, look at me! Mama! I beg
you, don't stop being my mama!
Come to Heaven with me.
Mama! Mama! Please,
don't kill me!
No! I'm not Mama's doll!
I'll think for myself,
and I'll live for myself!
I don't need a papa or mama,
I'll live on my own.
No! Don't make me remember that!
I want to forget those things!
Don't dig them up from my mind!
I don't want those terrible
memories anymore!
Please, stop this! Stop this!
My mind's being contaminated.
Kaji! My mind's being raped!
What will I do? It's defiling
my mind!
Unit 02 has ceased activation!
The life support system has crashed!
Pilot's mind is entering
danger zone.
Target position is constant.
Relative distance unchanged.
Possibility of the target coming
into Unit 00's range is 0.02%.
Could we airlift Unit 00 and
try shooting from the sky?
No, we can't do that.
If the Angel attacked during the
approach, we couldn't protect it.
I'll go out in Unit 01!
No! This target has the ability
to attack the pilot's mind.
We cannot allow an
invasion of Unit 01.
But that can't happen as long
as I'm not defeated, right?
There is no guarantee that
you will succeed.
But if we don't, Asuka will...
I don't care. Rei, go to Dogma
and get the Lance.
The Lance of Longinus?!
You can't do that, Ikari!
It's the only way to kill a target
beyond the reach of our AT Fields.
Hurry!
But if Adam and the
Eva come into contact,
it might cause the Third Impact!
It's too dangerous! Commander
Ikari, please don't do this!
So, that story was fraudulent too?
The Second Impact wasn't caused
by contact between two Angels.
Opening Central Dogma
barriers 10 through 15.
Unit 00 has passed the
6th Malvoisie.
Now opening barriers
16 through 20.
If something like this won't cause
the Third Impact, then...
What really happened to cause
the Second Impact?
Ikari, I still think it's too
early to use this.
The committee has already started
to mass produce Evas.
This is our chance, Fuyutsuki.
But...
We cannot make time
run backwards,
but we can spur its course forward
with our own hands.
The old men won't allow this.
Therefore, we must finish this
before SEELE has time to act.
It is not acceptable to lose
Unit 02 at this time.
But you can't use the Lance
without SEELE's approval.
The need is the justification.
There are no other factors
to consider.
Justification? No, what you're
looking for is an excuse.
Unit 02's pilot's EKG has dropped
to point zero six.
We're past the limits of the
life support system.
Unit 00 is passing through Vent 2.
She's approaching the surface!
That's the Lance of Longinus?
Unit 00 is in position to throw.
Target sighted. Error corrections
have been made.
Starting countdown.
Going from ten.
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
Zero!
Target annihilated.
Eva Unit 02 is free.
What about the Lance
of Longinus?
It passed escape velocity. It's
moving into a lunar orbit.
It's impossible to recover it now.
Yes, Sir.
We have no method to recover
an object of that much mass.
Unit 02's psychograph is
returning to normal.
Return the Evangelion to
the second cage.
Please use Route 67.
How's Asuka?
We've confirmed that
the pilot is alive,
and we've established quarantine
for the contamination.
I see.
I'm glad you're okay, Asuka.
Shut up! Who the hell is okay?!
How could it get any worse?
That little bitch rescued me.
That little bitch rescued ME.
I'd rather have died!
I hate you! I hate you!
I hate everyone!
I hate you all!
To be continued...
Preview
Unit 00 is possessed and
corroded by an Angel.
In order to protect
Shinji from the Angel,
Rei wishes herself dead.
She becomes light and heat
to disappear with Tokyo-3.
It's the next episode: "Tear"