Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Apotheosis for the three
Evas will be performed
as soon as the MAGI system
is reactivated.
Operation confirmed. Steps 450
through 670 are omitted.
Command has granted approval.
You're fast, Maya, that's
what makes you you!
Of course, I am. You trained me.
Wait a second, A-8 would
be faster there.
Let me do that.
Well, she was my teacher.
How's it going? Are you finished
giving the MAGI their check-up?
Almost done. As promised, it'll be
over before today's test begins.
You're something else, Ritsuko.
You have three impossible tasks,
yet you still beat the schedule.
That one's cold.
All three MAGI systems have
entered self-diagnostic mode.
The 127th routine maintenance
has been completed.
Confirmed. Well done, guys.
Take a break until the test begins.
Everything checked out.
As usual, mother's in
good shape, but...
Is it just me getting older?
Episode 13
Angel Invades
You want me to take off
my clothes again?
The next chamber is an ultra-clean
room environment.
Just taking a shower and changing
your undergarments is insufficient.
Why do I have to go through all
this for a simple autopilot test?
With the advance of time, Eva
technology also needs to advance.
To do so, we need a constant
influx of new data.
All right, I'm here, just
the way you wanted.
Butt-naked and run through the
wash cycle seventeen times.
Now, I want all three of
you to stay that way
as you walk through the room
and board the entry plug.
Don't worry. The video recorders
have been shut off.
We do respect your privacy.
That isn't the point! This is
a very personal thing!
This test's purpose is to remove
interference from your plug suits,
and monitor the harmonics
directly from your bodies.
Asuka, that's an order.
All right! But I don't want
anybody peeking, okay?
All pilots are ready for entry.
Start the test.
Beginning the test.
Initiate autopilot recording.
Inserting simulation plug.
Connecting simulation
bodies to the system.
The simulation plugs are now
under the MAGI's control.
Wow, that was really fast!
The MAGI are magnificent!
It's hard to believe that the first
experiment took a whole week.
According to the schedule, the
test will end in three hours.
How do you feel?
It feels odd.
Yes, it's different from
the other times.
Something's wrong
with my senses.
My right arm is all I can feel
clearly. Everything else is fuzzy.
Rei, imagine moving
your right hand.
Yes, Ma'am.
Data collection is
proceeding nicely.
Everything seems good so far.
Return the MAGI to
their normal state.
A dilemma...
You can sure feel the creator's
personality, can't you?
What are you talking about?
You created them, didn't you?
You don't know anything, do you?
That's because you never talk
about yourself like I do, Ritsuko!
That's true. I just created
the system uplinks.
The one who developed the basic
theorems and the main frame
was my mother.
Are you double checking this?
Yes, I am.
These are the parts that were
brought in three days ago.
These are the parts that are
showing signs of deterioration.
The 87th protein wall.
With magnification, you can
see some of the spots.
Can you tell me what it is?
It's got to be corrosion.
There are slight variations in the
temperature and conduction rates.
Deterioration of sterilized rooms
happens a lot, an awful lot lately.
The construction schedule was
cut by about sixty days.
It's possible that some air bubbles
may have gotten inside.
There are a lot of flaws in the
construction of B Wing.
This building was built after the
Angels appeared, remember?
You can't blame anyone.
Everybody was so exhausted then.
Take care of it by tomorrow.
Otherwise, Ikari will be jumping
all over our asses for it.
Understood.
Another water leak?
No, it's some kind of corrosion in
the protein wall above this floor.
Wonderful.
Could it have any effect
on this test?
No, not at the moment.
Then, let's continue.
We can't abort experiments due to
minor technical problems.
Otherwise, Commander Ikari will
be jumping all over our asses.
Understood.
Synchronization
position is correct.
Connecting the simulation plugs to
the Evas via the simulation bodies.
Contact with Eva Unit 00
has been confirmed.
AT Field will be generated on two.
What's happening?!
We've got a contamination alert
in the Sigma unit on A Floor.
The 87th protein wall is corroding
and releasing heat.
We've detected an abnormality
in the 6th pipe as well.
Corrosion of the protein wall is
increasing at an incredible rate!
Abort the experiment.
Shut off the 6th pipe.
Right!
Numbers 60, 38 and 39
are all closed.
Corrosion has occurred in 6-42.
No effect! Corrosion is spreading
along the walls.
Prepare the polysomes.
Set laser power at maximum.
Shoot the invasive particles.
Corrosion has reached 6-58.
It's here!
Rei!
Rei's simulation body is moving.
Impossible!
The corrosion is still spreading.
It's invading the simulation bodies'
active water system.
How's Rei?!
She's all right.
Eject all plugs immediately.
Hurry up with that laser!
An AT Field?!
Impossible!
What is it?
The pattern analysis is blue.
There's no question. It's an Angel.
An Angel?! You let an
Angel get inside?
I'm sorry, Sir.
This isn't the time for excuses.
I want a physical shut down
of Central Dogma.
Isolate it from Sigma Unit.
Initiating physical shut down
of Central Dogma.
Isolating from Sigma Unit.
Abandon this unit! Evacuate immediately!
What the hell are you
doing? Hurry!
Isolating Sigma Unit from B Floor.
Closing all partitions. All area
personnel must evacuate.
I know. Please take care of it.
Stop the alarm.
Stopping the alarm, Sir.
This is a malfunction, an error
in the alarm system.
Report that to both the Japanese
government and the committee.
Yes, Sir!
The contaminated area
is still descending.
It's spreading all over Sigma
Unit from the Pribnow Box!
That's a critical area.
Yes, it's too close to Adam.
Stop the corrosion within
Sigma Unit!
If necessary, sacrifice the Geo
Front. What's the Evas' status?
Ready in seventh cage.
We can launch them as soon
as the pilots are recovered.
There's no need to wait for the
pilots. Launch them immediately.
Launch Unit 01 first. Sacrifice
the other two if necessary.
Unit 01 has top priority?
But Sir, we can't destroy the
Angel without the Evas.
If the Evas are contaminated first,
we'll be finished. Hurry!
Roger!
All of Central Dogma
under Sigma Unit
will be shut down in sixty seconds.
So that's the Angel.
Thirty seconds until activation of vacuum pump.
Time to take a break.
Central Dogma has been
completely sealed.
Mega-depth facilities are entirely
occupied by the intruder.
Well now, how will we fight off
an Angel without an Eva?
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Look, this is the border between
the normal and heavy water.
There's a higher level
of oxygen here.
Their preference is pretty obvious.
The place where ozone
is vented in
to maintain aseptic conditions
isn't contaminated.
So does that mean that its
weakness is ozone?
It would seem so.
Injecting ozone. Ozone
concentration is increasing.
It's working, all right.
Will this work?
Zero A and Zero B seem
to be recovering.
The area around the pipes is
getting back to normal.
The central portion is proving
a little more difficult.
All right, inject more ozone.
This isn't right.
What? It's increasing?
Something is wrong. Heat
levels are increasing.
The contaminated area
is spreading again.
The ozone is no longer
having any effect.
Now it's absorbing the ozone.
Stop the ozone injection!
Amazing...
It's evolving.
What's wrong?
Something's hacking into
the sub-computer.
The intruder hasn't
been identified.
Not now! Dealing with C-mode.
Unfreeze the barrier.
Open a decoy entry.
Decoy entry has been avoided.
T-minus eighteen seconds
to completion of trace.
Spreading barrier.
Barrier has been penetrated.
Open another false entry.
No human being could do this.
Trace complete. The hacker
is inside this facility!
It's in B-Wing, in the Pribnow Box!
Optical pattern is changing.
Those glowing lines look
like electronic circuits.
This is just like a computer.
Opening decoy entry.
It failed. There's interference.
Cut off the main cable.
Negative, it refuses to
accept the command.
Fire the laser.
It's generating an AT Field.
No effect.
It is accessing the main security
bank. It's cracking the pass code.
Twelfth digit... sixteenth digit...
D word has been cleared!
It's broken into the main banks!
It's reading the main bank.
We can't stop it.
What does it want?
Scanning the main directories.
This code is... my God!
It's going after the MAGI!
Shut down I/O system.
Countdown!
Three... Two...
One!
We can't shut it down!
The Angel is intruding further
into the computers.
It's made contact with Melchior.
It's no good! The Angel is
taking over Melchior.
Melchior is being re-programmed
by the Angel.
Melchior's self-destruct
has been initiated.
Overruled. Overruled.
Melchior is hacking into Balthasar!
Damn, it's too fast!
What calculation speed!
Change the logic mode.
Change synchronization code
to every fifteen seconds.
Roger!
How much time did we buy?
At least two hours, I think.
The MAGI have become
our enemy.
This Angel must be composed of
a group of micro-machines,
each the size of a virus.
These micro-machines group
together to form colonies.
In a very short period of time, they
have exponentially evolved
to form a sophisticated
intelligence circuit.
Evolved...
Yes.
They're continuously
changing themselves
to form the best system to cope
with any environment.
That's their survival mechanism
as a life form.
Against an enemy that evolves to
overcome its weaknesses
the only effective counter measure
is to eliminate the host
and let the parasite die with it.
The only option is to order the
MAGI to commit suicide.
I propose the physical elimination
of the MAGI.
That's impossible.
Destroying the MAGI means
destroying headquarters itself.
Then I officially request it on
behalf of the Operations Division.
I reject it.
This is a matter for the
Technology Department.
Why are you being so
mule-headed?!
This situation is a result of
my carelessness.
Why do you always have
to be like this?
You always take the responsibility
on your own shoulders
and avoiding depending
on anyone.
As long as this Angel keeps
evolving, we have a chance.
Expedite its evolution?
Yes.
The end of evolution is
self-destruction. Death itself.
Thus, we just need to accelerate
its evolution.
If the Angel considers it the only
practical means of survival,
it may choose to co-exist
with the MAGI system.
But how?
If the Angel is a computer itself,
we can counter-hack it by
connecting Casper to the Angel
and uploading a self-destruct
program, but...
At the same time, we'll be turning
off the barrier to the Angel.
So either Casper or the Angel,
whichever is faster, will win.
Yes.
Will the program be ready in time?
If Casper is taken over first,
it'll all be over.
I keep my promises.
Red alert! Red alert!
An emergency has occurred
in NERV Headquarters.
All D-class personnel
must evacuate.
What are those?
These are notes left
by the developer.
My gosh! These are access codes!
MAGI's access codes!
It's like a special map to all of
the MAGI's back doors.
Am I allowed to see these?
I can't believe it! This is INT-C!
With these we can program much
faster than we thought!
Thank you, Mom. We can make it.
Give me the wrench.
Doesn't this remind you
of our college days?
Now, board number twenty-five.
Hey, how about telling me about
the MAGI? Just a little?
It's a long story.
A long, boring story.
Do you know about personality
transplant OS?
Yes, it's for implanting an
individual's personality
into a seventh generation
computer so it can think.
The same technology is used
for operating the Evas.
I've heard MAGI's programming
used one of the first test subjects.
My mother developed
the technology.
So, it was her personality
that was transplanted?
Right!
In a very real sense, these
brains are my mother.
Is that why you wanted
to protect the MAGI?
I don't think so. I didn't
really like my mom.
This was a decision as a scientist.
It's starting!
Balthasar is being taken over!
The self-destruct sequence has
been initiated by the computer.
Has it begun yet?!
Destruct will be triggered twenty
seconds after all three AI consent.
Destruction will encompass Geoid
Depth -280, -140 and Floor 0.
Special Command 582 requires the consent...
Balthasar is now invading Casper!
...of two computers to cancel the action.
It's faster than us!
What speed!
T-minus twenty to self-destruct.
My God!
Casper will be taken over in eighteen seconds.
T-minus fifteen to self-destruct.
Ritsuko, hurry!
Relax. I've got almost one whole second to spare.
T-minus ten to self-destruct.
Only one?!
9...
At least it's not a zero or a minus.
8...
7...
6...
Maya!
We can do it!
5...
4...
3...
2...
Hit it!
1...
Zero.
Self-destruct has been canceled
by the computer.
All right!
Special Command 582 is also canceled.
The MAGI are returning
to normal mode.
The red alert has been canceled.
All hands return to first stage alert.
What's going on outside?
Jeez, I can't get out with
no clothes on!
Somebody, help me fast!
Sigma Unit released. T-minus zero
three to MAGI reactivation.
I'm getting old. Staying up for
these all-nighters is rough.
You kept your promise again.
Good job.
Thank you.
This is the first time I've ever
really appreciated your coffee.
The night before she died,
my mother told me
that the MAGI are three
aspects of herself.
Herself as a scientist.
Herself as a mother.
Herself as a woman.
The three aspects of her struggle
for dominance inside the MAGI.
She intentionally implanted the
dilemmas of human experience.
Actually, each of the three
programs are slightly different.
I don't think I'll ever
be a mother,
and I don't really understand
her as a mother.
I respected her as a scientist.
However, as a woman, I hated her.
You're rather talkative today.
Only sometimes.
Casper contains the program
of her as a woman.
She stayed a woman to the last.
How totally like my mother.
To be continued...
Preview
NERV and Seele manage the Human
Instrumentality Project behind the scenes.
They will revise the present
and the future of NERV.
Are all the incidents simply just a
realization of a given scenario ?
Next time:
"Seele, Throne of the Soul"
And of course, service, service.