Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
It's eating the Angel?
Those bindings were what allowed
us to control the Eva's power.
But now the Eva is removing the
web that binds it to our will.
Unit 01's been awakened
and set free.
SEELE won't stay quiet for this.
The Eva series aren't capable of
generating S2 organs themselves.
But we never imagined it'd be able
to take one into itself this way.
This incident is at extreme odds
with the scenario SEELE created.
It will not be easy to correct this.
It was a mistake to entrust NERV
to Gendo Ikari, wasn't it?
But he was the only one who could
achieve this project's goals.
Ikari, what's going on
in your mind?
It's begun, hasn't it?
Yes, this is the beginning.
Episode 20
Shape of the Heart
Damage on both Evas
is over the Henflick limit, beyond
any normal restoration.
It may be a while before we can
restore everything to normal.
Fortunately, the MAGI system can
be transferred to a new location.
We may be able to start
working tomorrow.
But this place will have
to be scrapped.
It's just a matter of time before the
brass decides to abandon it.
That's true.
For the time being, we'll have to
use the Secondary Control Center.
You mean, without the MAGI?
That's right.
We can clean the dust off, and be
working again by this afternoon.
But those chairs are cramped, and
the sensors don't operate well.
It's difficult to work there.
But at least the layout is the same
as our original control center.
It just feels like we don't
belong there.
At least we have an alternative.
We have no choice when it
comes to using Unit 01.
It may be restrained by the cage,
but are you sure it's safe?
No heat emissions, free electrons,
electromagnetic fields
or chemical reactions
are being detected.
The S2 unit is completely inactive.
Nevertheless, on three
separate occasions,
Unit 01 has moved without power.
You can't judge this situation
just by the things you can
see and measure.
Yeah, we can't take any chances,
that's for sure.
It's as unpredictable as
you are, Katsuragi.
I'm sorry.
However, our concerns are
not limited to Unit 01.
Correct. Serious damage was
sustained by Units 00 and 02.
Headquarters was partially ruined,
exposing Central Dogma.
The destruction was enormous.
We can't even estimate how much
money and time have been lost.
This all is because we didn't put
a bell around Ikari's neck.
A bell was there, but
it didn't ring.
A bell that doesn't ring
serves no purpose.
We'll make sure the bell
works next time.
My, my, what an unexpected
situation!
The committee... I mean, how will
you explain this to SEELE?
Unit 01 wasn't under our control.
This was an accident.
Unit 01 will stay frozen until the
Committee gives us further orders.
That's a very appropriate decision.
However, isn't your son still
trapped inside it?
It's hopeless. It's not accepting
the code to eject the entry plug.
What about the backup codes?
Also refused. Even a direct circuit
isn't getting through.
The plug's video monitor
is active though.
Switching to main screen.
What in the hell is this?
I'd say that's the truth behind
a 400% synch ratio.
I can't believe it.
What happened to Shinji?
Apparently the Eva has
taken him into itself.
What does that mean?!
Just what is an Eva?!
It is something created by man
in Man's own image.
I really can't describe it
any other way.
You didn't create anything!
You just copied something you
found in the Antarctic.
What was the original? That's what
I want to know, Doctor.
This is not just a copy.
A human will is inside it.
Are you saying somebody
willed this to happen?!
No, the Eva did.
Do something, damn you!
You created this, didn't you?!
Take responsibility for it!
I am still alive.
I know that Wonder Girl
is still alive!
Why are you bothering me with
trivial crap like that, Misato?!
I can't believe it. I couldn't
do anything.
I can't believe that stupid Shinji
outperformed me.
Not again!
What do you mean, you're going
to "salvage" Shinji?
Well, theoretically, Shinji's life
force still exists in there.
And you'll be respecting
that life this time?
Losing Shinji is out of
the question now.
I don't know.
What NERV wants is Unit 01
as their tool, not Shinji.
I don't deny it.
Our assumption is that Shinji's
body lost its Ego Border,
and he's floating in the entry
plug in quantum form.
You're saying that Shinji has
shifted into a form we can't see?
Yes, the LCL has
chemically altered
into something very similar to the
sea water of primitive Earth.
You mean, like a primordial soup?
All of the substances which
composed Shinji
are still preserved in the plug,
and his soul exists there as well.
In fact, his Ego Image is giving a
sort of substance to his plug suit.
In other words, this
salvage operation
must both reconstruct his body
and fix his soul in it.
Is that possible?
With the Magi's support, yes.
This is all theoretical, isn't it?
You won't know what will really
happen until you do it.
What is this?
Where am I?
In the entry plug?
That's right. But there's nobody
here. Not even myself.
What is this? What is this?
What is this?
I don't understand.
These people...
Yes, they're people I know,
people who know me.
I understand now.
This is my world.
What is this?
This is supposed to be my world,
but this I don't understand.
An image from outside?
A hostile image?
That's right! The enemy!
Enemy! Enemy! Enemy! Enemy!
Our enemies are called Angels.
They have the names of Angels.
They are the targets of
Eva and NERV.
This is our revenge for the
death of Misato's father!
Why do I fight? Despite all the
pain and suffering?
What are you, stupid?
An unknown enemy is attacking,
of course we have to fight them!
Am I odd to try to find a
reason to fight?
Am I not supposed
to think about it?
Enemy! Enemy! Enemy! Enemy!
All are my enemies!
Us... That which threatens
us is the enemy.
Of course, how can I be faulted
for protecting my own life and
those of others?!
Enemy! Enemy! Enemy! Enemy!
My enemy! My enemy!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
You hurt Toji and killed
my mother! Father!
Why do you hate your father?
Anyone would hate such a father!
You don't understand him, do you?
Of course not. I've hardly
ever seen him.
Is that why you hate him?
Yes, my father doesn't need me!
My father deserted me!
And am I his substitute?
Yes, it must be so!
He abandoned me because
he had Ayanami!
As if you didn't run away
all by yourself.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
It's all his fault!!
That time I was actually going
to tell him I hate him!
Did you tell me to pilot this just
to make me suffer, Father?
Correct.
That can't be true! It can't be!
How can you say that?!
You don't need me, do you?!
I called you because
you had a use.
Why me?
Because there was no
one else who could.
No way, I've never seen this
before. It's impossible!
Yes, I knew it was true.
It's true! I knew Eva.
Then I escaped!
I really escaped! Leaving my
father and mother behind!
Concentration of LCL is currently
stable at 36%.
No problem with oxygen
concentration.
Electromagnetic radiation pulse
is normal. Wave pattern is 0.
Counters are functioning normally.
Salvage Plan Guideline
and Procedures...
It's amazing that you could create
all this in only one month.
Thanks for giving me credit,
but it wasn't my idea.
This was already experimental
ten years ago.
This kind of thing happened
during the development?
It was before I worked here.
My mother was here, though.
I only know the data.
And how did it come out?
I've heard they failed.
Kindness...
Warmth...
Is this the warmth of a human?
I was never aware of it.
What is loneliness?
I was never aware of it, but
now I think I know it.
What is happiness?
I was never aware of it, but
now I think I know it.
Are others kind to you?
Why?
Because I am Eva's pilot.
Because I pilot Eva,
they treat me well.
That is the reason I can exist.
That is the everything to support
my reason to be.
So, I must pilot Eva.
And then?
Enemy! Yes, I must fight what
they all call the enemy!
And then?
And I must win!
Right, I can't lose.
As they tell me to,
I must pilot Eva.
As they tell me to, I must win!
Otherwise...
Nobody...
Do your best.
Get to work, idiot.
Good work, Shinji.
Misato, Ritsuko, Asuka,
Toji, Kensuke
and Father.
They all respect me.
When I pilot Eva, they
all respect me.
They respect this worthless being.
Everyone says to pilot this.
I'll prove to my dad
I'm worthwhile.
Do your best.
Yes, I'm doing my best.
I am doing my best!
Somebody be nice to me.
I fought so hard.
I'm doing my best!
Treat me well! Be nice to me!
I'm nice to you.
Tell me, Shinji, do you want
to become one with me?
To be of one mind and body?
It could be very, very nice.
Ask me anytime. I'm ready.
Hey, Shinji-idiot, don't you
want to be one with me?
To be of one mind and body?
It could be very, very nice.
You ought to appreciate your
good fortune. Come on.
Ikari, do you want to become
one with me?
To be of one mind and body?
It could be very, very nice.
Ikari?
Do you want to become
one with me?
To be of one mind and body?
It could be very, very nice.
Relax and release your soul.
All investigative needles fixed.
Fixed at electromagnetic radius
of zero minus three.
Ego Border pulse connection
is complete.
Roger. Start salvage.
Roger, transmitting first signal.
Eva has received the signal.
No rejection confirmed.
Proceeding to second
and third signals.
Subject cathexis is normal.
Destrudo is not confirmed.
Roger, shift the subject
to stage two.
Shinji!
Hey, Shinji-idiot!
Hey, Shinji!
Yo, Shinji!
Ikari...
Shinji!
Shinji-idiot!
Hey, Shinji!
Yo, Shinji.
Ikari...
Shinji!
Shinji-idiot!
Hey, Shinji!
Yo, Shinji.
Ikari...
Shinji!
Shinji-idiot!
Hey, Shinji!
Yo, Shinji.
Ikari...
It's no good. The Ego Border
is frozen in a loop.
Irradiate the wave patterns
in all directions.
It won't work. The signals are
trapped in Klein space.
What does that mean?
It means we failed.
Abort intervention.
Reverse tangent plug.
Return additions to zero.
Yes, Ma'am.
Destrudo reaction in the old area.
Pattern sepia.
A change is confirmed on the core
pulse too! Plus 0.3 is confirmed!
Maintenance of the status quo is
top priority. Prevent back flow.
Yes, Ma'am.
Plus 0.5... 0.8... This is odd.
I can't stop it!
What is this? Why? Don't you
want to come back, Shinji?
I don't understand.
I... I...
What do you wish?
Eva has rejected the signal.
LCL self-replenishment
is dropping.
Pressure in the plug is increasing!
Abort all operations.
Cut the power.
It's not working. The plug
is being ejected.
Shinji!
Where am I? Inside of Eva?
Inside of Eva?
Did I pilot Eva again? Why?
You won't pilot the Eva anymore?
I've decided I will never
pilot Eva again.
But you have just piloted
Evangelion Unit 01.
Shinji, you are here because
you have piloted the Eva.
Piloting the Eva has created
your present.
You can never deny
your past, Shinji,
nor can you deny that you did
indeed pilot it once more.
That which is, is. It's true.
I just wanted to tell you that
only you can decide.
It's your future.
I... I...
What good is damned science?
It can't even save one small life?!
Give me back my Shinji!
Give him back!
That scent?
A human smell?
Misato?
Ayanami?
No, not them.
That's right.
This is the smell of my mother.
Second Impact has occurred.
Will he live in this hell?
Anywhere can be heaven
if you try to live.
Because he has a life,
as long as he lives, he will have
the chance to attain happiness.
Yes, you're right.
Mom...
Have you decided yet?
If it's a boy, Shinji. If it's a girl,
I'll name the baby Rei.
Shinji... Rei...
Mom...
Shinji!
Let's speak of what psychologists
used to call the Oral Stage.
Unit 01 will be restored in two days.
Let's speak of what psychologists
used to call the Oral Stage.
Even given divine power, humans still...
Let's speak of what psychologists
used to call the Oral Stage.
Even given divine power, humans still...
It's when someone is dependent
on another, like his mother.
...treat it as a matter of fact.
It's when someone is dependent
on another, like his mother.
I can hardly agree.
It's when someone is dependent
on another, like his mother.
I can hardly agree.
I know a lot of guys like that, and
your letter sounds just like them.
Speaking of which, the committee
is considering freezing Eva.
I know a lot of guys like that, and
your letter sounds just like them.
The Evangelion android...
I know a lot of guys like that, and
your letter sounds just like them.
The Evangelion android...
I feel sorry for your girlfriend. She
can't be your mate and mother.
It's man-made, but who knows
what lurks inside that black box?
I feel sorry for your girlfriend. She
can't be your mate and mother.
Well, I'm just glad Shinji was saved.
Maybe your sister, too? Aren't you
just taking advantage of her?
That wasn't me. It was you, probably.
Maybe your sister, too? Aren't you
just taking advantage of her?
That wasn't me. It was you, probably.
Well, maybe that's mean. Girls are
sensitive to how they're loved.
Why don't we go to a bar tonight?
Well, maybe that's mean. Girls are
sensitive to how they're loved.
Why don't we go to a bar tonight?
So she's already been aware that
you want her as your mother.
Sorry, I've got to go somewhere.
So she's already been aware that
you want her as your mother.
I see.
So she's already been aware that
you want her as your mother.
I see.
See you!
Seeing her man as soon
as Shinji is saved?
Well, I can't criticize her.
Ritsuko must be thinking
I'm pretty disgusting.
Appearing to give in to our
desires looks more human.
We might even fool them.
Fool the Intelligence Department?
Or the Commander and Ritsuko?
Or me?
No, I meant myself.
You want to fool the others?
You never show interest in others,
but you want their attention.
You really are just like my dad.
A cigarette? I didn't know
you still smoked.
I only smoke after this
sort of thing.
So nobody knows but you.
I see. I'm honored.
And how's Instrumentality going?
Adam could wipe out mankind.
Why is it being kept there?
Did you come to see me
just to learn that?
Well, that's one of the reasons.
It would be my honor to be used
as my lady's cat's-paw,
but I can't tell you right now.
I just want you to know
what I want.
What are NERV and Commander
Ikari really planning?
I'd like to know that myself.
Hey, you can't dodge my
questions by doing that.
Hey, no!
Don't put strange things in there!
I can't believe this. What is it?
A present for you, the
first in eight years.
And maybe the last as well.
To be continued...
Preview
Vice-Commander Fuyutsuki has
been abducted by SEELE.
The memories form the present
as others delve into NERV.
Could NERV really be a
fortress for all Mankind?
Next time,
"NERV Arises"