Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Are you refusing to allow us to
question the pilot of Unit 01,
the only one directly involved in
the incident, Major Katsuragi?
Yes, Sir. Because he is
emotionally very unstable,
I believe that it would be unwise
to have him here.
Then, as his proxy, let us ask you,
Major Katsuragi.
In this incident,
didn't the Angel attempt to
communicate with a human being?
I find no suggestion of that
in the subject's report.
I believe this was an irregularity,
a coincidence.
If, and only if, his memory
is correct.
There is no evidence that his
memory has been tampered with.
However, the Eva's AC recorder
was not functioning.
There's no way to confirm it.
Was the Angel interested in the
human spirit? In the human mind?
I am unable to answer
that question.
Whether the Angels even have
a concept of what "Mind" is,
or whether they can understand
human thoughts or not
is completely unknown.
A new factor has been added
with this incident,
in that the Angel tried to
take Eva into itself.
Is there any possibility that this
aspect may be linked
to the predicted Thirteenth Angel
and all Angels thereafter?
Based on the previous patterns,
there appears to be no systematic
organization among the Angels.
Correct! It is obvious that they
have worked independently, so far.
What do you mean, Sir?
You are not allowed to
ask questions.
Understood.
That will be all. Dismissed.
Yes, Sir.
What do you think, Ikari?
The Angels appear to be getting
more and more intelligent.
There's not much time left.
Episode 17
The Fourth Child
Left for us, you mean?
Who's the patient in Room 12?
That's the emergency room patient
from the first Eva incident.
She's been here for a long time.
Her injuries are really difficult,
poor girl.
She's still in elementary school.
He's here again today?
Yeah, he comes to see her
at least twice a week.
He's a good brother, thinking
about his sister like that.
Yeah, boys like that
are pretty rare.
He has a good heart.
Rei, are you all right today?
Yes, Sir. I will be with
Dr. Akagi tomorrow,
and the day after
I'll be at school.
How is the school?
No problems, Sir.
I see. That's good.
Stand up! Bow! Sit down!
Let me see, Ayanami is absent
as usual, and Aida too?
What's up with Kensuke?
Professor Koike is absent today,
He went to New Yokosuka to see a battleship.
So the class in modern Japanese will be self-study.
A ship called Myoko or something is in port.
And finally, the student on duty today will be...
Mister Suzuhara.
Yes, Sir!
Will you deliver this document to
Miss Ayanami after school?
Yes, Sir!
Don't worry about it.
First Branch is okay.
The data from the recon plane will
be confirmed by the MAGI.
It disappeared?!
The entire Second Branch
just vanished?!
Yes, Sir, it's been confirmed.
It's gone.
Dear God...
Administration and Investigation
sections are going crazy,
and General Affairs
is in a total panic.
What was the cause?
It's still under investigation.
Our only clues are these
geo-synchronous satellite photos.
There's nothing else left.
10 seconds...
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
Contact.
This is horrible.
Evangelion Unit 04,
its support group and all other
facilities within an 89km radius
were completely destroyed.
Along with thousands of people.
Looking at the time schedule,
It seems they were installing the
experimental S2 engine.
Potential causes range from
a lack of structural integrity to a
preliminary design stage error.
That's 32,768 possibilities
right there.
And that's not mentioning
sabotage.
But it wasn't an explosion, was it?
It was a disappearance.
In all probability, they were
swallowed by a Sea of Dirac,
just like Unit 01 was.
And the restored S2 engine?
Gone, along with our hopes.
It's all because we're being forced
to use things we don't understand.
Things like the Evas.
What'll we do with Unit 03?
We'll receive it here.
The U.S. Government doesn't want
to lose the First Branch as well.
Didn't they insist on the right to
build Units 03 and 04?
And now they're foisting
it off on us?
They're really pushing their luck.
After a disaster like that, anyone
would get nervous.
And how are you going to
do the test activation?
Will you use Rei's dummy plug?
I'll have to make a decision.
This is the dummy plug prototype.
Rei's personal data has
been loaded into it,
but it's not really possible to
digitize a human mind and soul.
A fake, that's all it is.
It copies a pilot's thinking
process.
In the end, it's only a machine.
It transmits a signal
pattern to Eva,
and Eva believes there's a pilot
and synchronizes. That's enough.
Load the data into Unit 01
and Unit 02.
There are still some
problems with it.
That's not important. As long as
the Eva activates, it's sufficient.
Understood.
I've delegated the transportation
of the Unit to the U.N.
It will arrive by the end
of the weekend.
You'll take care of it from there.
Yes, Sir.
We'll perform the modifications
and activation test in Matsushiro.
And the test pilot will be...
Use of the Dummy Plug is not
recommended at this time.
One of our prospective
candidates...
Will be chosen as the
Fourth Child?
Yes, there is one child whose core
can be prepared immediately.
Then, I'll trust you to make it so.
Yes, Sir.
Rei, we're finished now.
Let's eat.
Yes, Sir.
Stand up! Bow!
Lunch time! Lunch time! This is
the single best thing about school.
You didn't make lunches for us?
I didn't have time to cook last
night. I had too much homework.
And that's your excuse for me
having to go without lunch?!
A husband and wife quarrel?
It's not like that!
What is it? You look so serious.
It's the Unit 03 activation test.
We'll be using the Fourth
as the pilot.
The Fourth?
The Fourth Child's been found?
Just yesterday.
But I haven't received a report
from the Marduk Institute yet.
The official documents will be
delivered tomorrow.
Dr. Akagi, are you hiding
something from me again?
No, nothing at all.
Well, okay. So, who's the kid?
Jeez! It's HIM?!
It can't be helped.
All the possible candidates were
gathered together for protection.
It's so hard to tell them.
Asuka will be fine. Her pride
keeps her piloting her Eva.
Rei is exceptional,
with no problems with her
Eva or our work.
Shinji probably knows the most
about the down side.
I don't want him to suffer
any more hardships.
But we need children of this kind,
in order for us all to survive.
Are you saying not to
complicate the issue?
Bye! Later!
Suzuhara, you've got the duty
this week. Get to work!
What do you mean?
The class printout!
Didn't our teacher tell
you to deliver this?
Come on, you can ask the other
person on duty, can't you?
Miss Ayanami is absent today!
Ayanami and me?
Then I guess there's no choice.
But I don't want to go to some
girl's place all by myself.
Well, I can go with you...
Shinji!
Walk home with me, will you?
Ayanami, we're coming in.
You can't enter a girl's room
without her permission.
We've got no choice.
She won't see it if we
leave it there.
Excuse us...
Good grief!
Is this a girl's room?
It's so decrepit.
Hey, you shouldn't touch anything!
She'll get pissed!
I'm just cleaning up.
I won't help you!
That's not a man's job!
Okay, but Misato hates
guys like that.
I don't care! It's my policy!
Come to think of it,
you've changed.
What?
You, Shinji.
The first time I saw you, I really
thought you were a jerk.
You didn't seem like you would do
something for someone else.
I guess you're just
really reserved.
Excuse us!
What?
Those are the school bulletins that have piled up.
I'm sorry.
I took it upon myself
to clean up a little.
But I didn't touch anything
except trash.
Thank you.
Eva pilots are sure
weird all right.
Thank you...
Words of gratitude.
Words I've never used.
Not even to him.
The city, a paradise
made by Mankind.
Driven from Paradise,
Man escaped to this earthly
existence, on the edge of Death.
Created by the weakest of beings,
created by the sapience born
from that weakness,
this paradise is our creation.
To protect ourselves from
the fear Death instills,
to satiate our beings
with pleasure,
we create a paradise by
and of ourselves.
This city's surely such a paradise.
A city armed to protect us.
A city of refugees from the outer
world, the world of our enemies.
But cowards do live longer.
That's to our benefit.
The third New Tokyo, NERV's
hidden intercept base,
the delayed seventh construction
phase will be finished soon.
At long last, it will be completed.
How will you report Unit 04's
"accident" to the committee?
With the facts, the cause
is unknown.
But this is a major,
catastrophic loss.
Unit 04 and the Second Branch
are of no consequence.
The S2 engine prototype
may have been lost,
but the data is still on
record in Germany.
This installation and Unit 01
will be sufficient.
But the committee is in a panic.
Of course, it was an
unscheduled accident.
Seele must be busy changing
the schedule.
Incidents not depicted in the
Dead Sea Scrolls may occur.
This ought to teach those
old men a lesson.
The Third District Transformation
and Direction Weapon experiment
is on schedule.
The intercept system is completed,
Will Dr. Nishizono of the Technical Department,
and they're not going to have a party?
Call Section 2 of the R&D Division immediately.
NERV is a most inflexible organization.
It's because of Commander Ikari.
And are you a prude too?
Are you serious, Mr. Kaji?
I'll tell Ms. Katsuragi
and Dr. Akagi.
Not if your mouth is covered
with mine.
So, how's it going?
Well, it's going, I guess.
Well, I have work to do.
Excuse me.
Far be it from me to make
judgments on your private life,
but should you really be hitting
on girls in this organization?
Who's under whom isn't
your concern.
Or would you prefer I hit
on you, Katsuragi?
It depends on how you
answer my questions.
You know the secrets of the
Marduk Institute and Adam, right?
What secrets?
Don't try to feign ignorance!
Asking for help isn't like you.
You know, right now I don't care.
I'm not feeling very reserved.
The Fourth Child was conveniently
found at just the right time.
What's the truth behind that?
I'll tell you one thing.
The Marduk Institute doesn't exist.
NERV is pulling the strings
all by itself.
NERV itself?
Commander Ikari is?
You need to check Code 707.
Code 707?
Shinji's school?
Misato!
What is it?
Ritsuko's expecting you for a
meeting about tomorrow's trip.
All right. Thank you.
See you.
Yeah, yeah.
Buy you a drink? Cup of tea?
But I'm a boy.
I thought you'd be a more
serious person, Kaji.
You're saying that to someone as
straight arrow and reliable as me?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too. I didn't mean
to sound rude.
Hey, I want to show
you something.
They're watermelons?
Yeah, aren't they cute?
This is my hobby.
Keep it a secret, okay?
Growing... Making something
grow is really great.
One can see and learn so many
things from the process.
It also brings pleasure.
But pain too, right?
Do you hate pain?
I don't like it.
But have you found what
gives you pleasure?
That's not so bad.
If you know pain and hardship,
it's easier to be kind to others.
Being kind isn't a weakness.
Yes? Hello?
It's Katsuragi.
The synch test will
be starting soon.
Fix the depth at 3.2.
I thought so. Shinji's synch ratio is dropping.
LCL thickness is nominal.
Harmonics level is negative 1.1...
What's that mean?
I can't say.
Harmonics level is negative 1.1...
...0.5
I believe something happened during the incident.
...0.9
...0.8
I believe something happened during the incident.
Something in his mind.
...0.9
Current exponent is 0.9.
This makes it even harder to
tell him about Unit 03's pilot.
Current exponent is 0.9.
This makes it even harder to
tell him about Unit 03's pilot.
All results posted to Melchior.
The pilot will be officially informed tomorrow.
Stand up! Attention! Bow!
Lunch time!
Attention student Toji Suzuhara...
Toji Suzuhara, report to the Principal's Office.
What the...
What did you do?
I don't know.
Excuse me, I'm Toji Suzuhara.
You're Toji Suzuhara?
How was your trip to
New Yokosuka?
Way cool!
Speaking of which, I picked up
some disturbing information.
Eva Unit 03?
Yeah, the one they built in
America. It's completed, isn't it?
I don't know.
I know it's classified, but please
tell me something.
I really don't know!
Haven't you heard the rumor
that the activation test
will be held at the second test
facility in Matsushiro?
I haven't.
The pilot hasn't been
chosen yet, right?
How would I know?
Misato could pick me for it.
Shinji, would you ask her for me?
I really want to be an Eva pilot!
Really, I don't know.
What about the story that
Unit 04's been lost?
What was that?
You really don't know?
It disappeared along with the
entire Second Branch.
My dad's section was in a panic.
Really?
I think so.
Misato didn't tell me anything.
Well, I guess it doesn't directly
concern the pilots.
If she didn't tell you, it's likely
because you don't need to know.
I'm sorry about bothering you
with weird questions.
But Toji hasn't come back yet.
Thus, we, mankind,
survived the hell called the
Second Impact and rose again.
The number of children has
been decreasing yearly...
Sorry I'm late.
I know about it. Be seated.
Anyway, it is you, the young who
will lead the way to the future...
Let's go home.
What about Toji?
He'll be late.
He's got class duty.
The school is now closing.
All students must go to their
homes immediately.
Suzuhara!
You're on duty.
Line up the desks and write
up the daily record.
I haven't had lunch yet. I'll do
it as soon as I've eaten.
Suzuhara, you always buy your
lunch from the school shop.
That's because there's no one
who cooks for me.
Suzuhara...
I have two sisters. Their names
are Kodama and Nozomi,
and I always cook lunch for them.
That must be a lot of work.
So, I'm actually a good cook,
though you might not think it.
Really?
And I always end up cooking
too much for our lunches.
That's a waste.
If you need help getting rid of
your leftovers, I'll help.
Yes, help me.
Kaji?
Oh, Asuka? Sorry, I'm busy
right now. Can it wait?
But you have time to see
Misato, don't you?
Damn! Not right now!
These are our synch data reports.
Four of them?
What in the hell is this?
Who made HIM the Fourth Child?
No! I don't understand!
What is this?!
NERV, 1st Branch, USA
To be continued...
Preview
Eva Unit 03 is delivered to
Matsushiro from America.
People gloried in the peaceful day,
unaware of the coming tragedy.
The quiet days that collusion
has camouflaged are gone.
Next Episode:
"The Judgement of Life."