Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Hi! I'm not in right now, so leave
your message after the beep!
This may be my last assignment.
This looks like blood.
Episode 21
He Was Aware That He Was Still A Child
The Vice-Commander
was abducted?
Two hours ago. He was last
seen in the 8th District.
That's inside our installation.
What in the hell were you idiots
in Intelligence doing?
The whole thing was set up by
someone inside our operation.
We were taken by surprise.
Someone who could outwit
Section 2? It couldn't be him?!
Ryoji Kaji is suspected of being
the mastermind behind this plot.
Then, that's why you came for me.
We believe that you can
be of use to us, yes.
As your colleagues,
we regret having to consider the
Director of Operations a suspect,
but that is the nature
of our profession.
Considering our relationship,
it's a natural precaution.
I appreciate your cooperation.
Take her away.
It's been a while, Chairman Keel.
This is a rather rough reception.
I will not apologize for
necessary discourtesies.
This was necessary for us to speak
without the Commander present.
You haven't changed.
You still have no concern for the
circumstances of others.
The subject to be addressed has
become an immediate concern.
Thus, these measures
were unavoidable.
Please understand our situation.
What a surprise. Not the
committee, but SEELE itself!
We have no intention of
creating a new god.
We hope that we will have your
cooperation, Professor Fuyutsuki.
Professor Fuyutsuki, is it?
Professor! Professor Fuyutsuki!
Hello, boys.
Why don't you join us for a beer
by the Kamo River?
What, again?
Ryoko and the other girls said
they'll come if you come.
The professor said that you
shouldn't be so unsociable.
All right, I'll be there.
It's nice to have a drink
outside for a change.
Yeah...
You're very competent,
but you tend to underestimate the
value of relationships with others.
I'm sorry, Sir.
Speaking of which, Fuyutsuki...
There's a student who wrote a very
interesting research paper
for the bio-engineering class.
Her name is Ikari. Do
you know her?
Ikari? No, Sir.
I've told her about you, and she
says she'd like to meet you.
She'll be calling you soon, and
I'd like you to take her on.
And her name is Ikari?
I understand.
Metaphysical Biology
Fuyutsuki
I've read your paper.
There are a few things I disagree
with, but it's very interesting.
Thank you, Sir.
Your name is Yui Ikari, right?
Yes.
What are your career plans?
Corporate research?
Or joining the school
research facility?
I haven't really thought about it.
And there may be a third option.
I'm also thinking about
getting married,
assuming that I meet
the right person.
Again A.D. 2015
By incorporating the
S2 unit into itself,
it has achieved its ultimate form.
Evangelion Unit 01!
A supreme being which we
created. What blasphemy!
The creation of a god
is unacceptable.
Man must not create gods. He
can't possess such power!
Can we trust Gendo Ikari?
Gendo Rokubungi? Well,
I have heard the name.
No, I've never met him.
However, he does seem to be at
the center of many rumors.
He wants to be released
in my custody?
Yes, I'll come visit him.
What time should I come?
I've been hearing some interesting
things about you.
I've been wanting to meet you.
You were drunk and got into a
fight. How pathetic.
I didn't even have a chance to say
anything before they jumped me.
I'm not used to being liked.
Being hated, on the other hand,
is quite familiar.
That's not my concern.
Professor Fuyutsuki,
you are exactly the kind of person
I expected you to be.
My first impression of him was that
he was a total son of a bitch.
Back then, there were still seasons
in this country. It was autumn.
Are you serious?
Yes, I'm dating Mr. Rokubungi.
When she told me that, I
couldn't hide my shock.
It's hard to imagine
you seeing him.
Now, Professor Fuyutsuki...
He's actually a very sweet person.
It's just that nobody
really knows him.
Sometimes ignorance can be bliss.
I'm the one who first mentioned
you to him. Does that bother you?
Well, I'll admit that he's
an interesting fellow,
but I just don't like him.
It was generally believed that the
real object of his overtures to Yui
was her talent and the support of
the organization backing her.
According to the rumors, that
organization was called SEELE.
A.D. 2000, Antarctica
Second Impact...
It was in the last year of the 20th
century that this tragedy occurred.
Then, in the first year of the 21st
century there was nothing but hell.
I can't find any other words to
describe that year.
This used to be a continent of ice?
There's no sign left of it!
Professor Fuyutsuki...
Is that you? You survived?
I'd heard that you were with the
Katsuragi research team.
Fortunately, I returned to Japan
the day before the incident.
You don't say?
Mr. Rokubungi, you...
Excuse me, but I've changed
my surname.
A postcard? Not a business card?
We are married
Gendo and Yui Ikari
Ikari! Gendo Ikari!
My wife's been asking me to send
this to you. She's a fan of yours.
What an honor.
How is Yui doing? She's not
participating in this expedition?
Yui wanted to come too, but
we have a child now.
Your organization, SEELE
or whatever it's called,
is at the base of many
ugly rumors.
I don't like the way it manipulates
the committee by force.
You're still too scrupulous.
No completely chaste organization
can survive in this day and age.
If this official investigation
of the Second Impact
was composed solely
of SEELE personnel,
there would have been trouble.
So, are we just here for
political convenience?
NERV Headquarters
I still hate the darkness.
All it does is bring back the
most horrible memories.
Who is she?
The only survivor of the
research team.
Her name is Misato Katsuragi.
Katsuragi? Is she Doctor
Katsuragi's daughter?
Yes, she hasn't said a
word in two years.
How terrible.
She saw hell firsthand.
Her physical wounds are healed,
but repairing the damage to
her mind will take time.
That's true.
The results of our investigation
aren't easy to analyze.
This Giant of Light's origin is but
one of many unsolved mysteries.
The Second Impact was caused by
a massive meteorite strike,
or so the United Nations
officially declared later.
However, from my point of view,
the announcement was
obviously a fabrication.
The organization known as SEELE
and a man named Keel were
behind this artifice.
It became my goal to find out
the truth about the incident,
even though I discovered that
Yui Ikari was involved.
Why did you conceal the
existence of the Giant?
You knew that the Second Impact
was going to happen, didn't you?
You say it's just luck you returned
the day before it happened,
but explain why you brought back
copies of all the documentation?!
I'm surprised that those
weren't destroyed.
I've checked into your
finances as well.
Bringing up a child and educating
him is expensive,
but isn't this a bit much?
Very impressive,
Professor Fuyutsuki.
Perhaps you should be
teaching economics.
I'm going public with the real truth
about the Second Impact,
about you, SEELE and
the Dead Sea Scrolls.
I can't forgive anyone who would
have caused something like that.
As you wish.
However, before you do, there's
something I'd like to show you.
We're getting rather far
down, aren't we?
Are you worried?
A little.
What is this?
We didn't create it, someone
else excavated this cavity.
Eighty-nine percent of its
total volume is buried.
Was this originally a giant sphere?
This facility has been consuming
all mankind's resources.
Hi, Professor Fuyutsuki!
Doctor Akagi, you're here, too?
Yes, this is the ideal place
for our research
into creating a functioning
bio-computer system.
I'm going to name them the MAGI.
MAGI? The three wise
men of the East?
Is this what you wanted
to show me?
No, it's over this way.
Ritsuko, I'll be back soon.
Is this...
This can't be THE Giant?
No, here in Gehirn, we refer
to that giant as Adam,
but this isn't the original one.
Then, this...
Was created from Adam
by Man, Eva.
Eva?
Our operation to revive Adam
is referred to as Project E.
This is Eva Unit 00,
our system prototype.
This is a prototype of a god!
Fuyutsuki, let us create a new
genesis for Mankind, together.
Hey, boss.
I'm sorry. Let's proceed
with Rei's re-test.
Where is Major Katsuragi today?
I don't know.
Miss Katsuragi?
Yeah, Misato Katsuragi,
pleased to meet you.
Mother, I've just met a girl
named Katsuragi.
People tend to keep their distance
once they find out who I am,
which forces me to remember how
important your name is here.
However, Misato's different. She's
open and honest, even with me.
I've heard she is the only survivor
of the original research team,
and that she was once mute.
She talks quite a lot now, as if
she's making up for lost time.
Dear Ritsuko, I'm always
underground these days,
and I'm getting sick of living on
the box lunches they provide here.
On the surface, they've started
construction of Tokyo-3,
as directed by the Second
Capitol Transfer Directive.
Misato missed classes the last few
days, and I finally found out why.
Talk about stupid!
She'd spent the whole week
in her apartment
having non-stop sex with
her new boyfriend!
I think there's another side to
her I haven't seen before.
She introduced me to him today.
He's handsome, but his unkempt
manner bothers me.
You've always been a little
boy-shy, Ritsuko dear.
I think it's because you
only had a mother.
And I'm afraid I didn't take
care of you properly.
I'm ashamed to admit I acted like a
mother only when it suited me.
Like a mother...
Hakone, 2. Underground Test Site
Why is there a child in here?!
That's Commander Ikari's son.
Ikari, this isn't a daycare center.
This is a very important day!
I'm sorry, Professor.
I brought him here.
Yui, this is your experiment today.
That's why I brought him.
I want to show him how bright
the future will be.
Those words would be Yui's last.
A freak accident wiped her
from this existence.
Just as I had hoped it would.
What a disgusting woman I am.
After that day, Commander Ikari
completely changed.
Where have you been all week?
I understand your grief,
but you must be aware of
your own importance!
I know. Fuyutsuki, as of today we
will begin the new project.
I have already made the proposal
to Chairman Keel.
You're really going to do it?!
Yes, what has never been done,
the path to becoming a god!
The Human Instrumentality
Project.
Mother, congratulations on
completing your MAGI theorems.
I have good news which I think
will please you too.
I have been officially accepted
by Gehirn!
I'll start working on
Project E next month.
Who are you?
Technology Development Section,
Ritsuko Akagi. Here's my ID.
I heard the command center was
complete, so I came to see it.
But it's a real maze down
here, isn't it?
The Commander and Doctor Akagi
will see you in Command.
Are you really all right?
Yes, I have no regrets
about my work.
You're lying! You still can't forget
about Yui, can you?!
But that's acceptable to me.
That's Gehirn Headquarters.
Good Morning, Commander.
Did you bring your child?
Oh, I thought you had a son.
This isn't Shinji.
I've decided to take care of
an acquaintance's child.
Her name is Rei Ayanami.
How are you, Rei?
She resembles someone...
Yui?!
All of the records concerning
Rei Ayanami have been deleted?
They're all blank!
What's going on here?
Magi Casper...
Magi Balthasar...
Magi Melchior...
The MAGI are the three
aspects of me.
Myself as a scientist, myself as a
mother and myself as a woman.
Those three aspects are in
constant conflict with one another.
Three mothers...
The only thing left to do is to
switch the power on.
I'll be taking off early today.
Misato just got back.
Yeah, I heard that she
joined Gehirn.
In Germany, if I
remember correctly?
Yeah, she's stationed
with the 3rd Branch.
So, she's having a long
distance relationship.
They broke up.
But they seemed like such
a perfect couple.
The things that happen between men
and women are hard to comprehend.
They're not logical.
You're always so cold
about these things.
You may lose your chance
at happiness.
The definition of happiness
is even harder to fathom.
Well, I can't wait to see her.
Have a good time.
A good time it is.
What's the matter, Rei?
I'm lost.
Is that so? Do you want to
come with me then?
No.
But how will you get
home by yourself?
That's none of your business,
old hag.
What?
I can get home by myself.
Leave me alone, old hag.
You shouldn't call someone a hag.
But you are an old hag,
aren't you?
I'm getting angry. Commander
Ikari will spank you.
The Commander is the one
who calls you that.
That's...
That old hag is annoying. That
old hag is no use anymore.
...old hag... old hag...
That old hag is annoying. That
old hag is no use anymore.
The Commander said...
...that old hag is annoying.
...no use... no use...
You little bitch! Did you know
you're replaceable too, Rei?
Replaceable just like me!
Keel Lorenz, Chairman of the
Instrumentality Committee,
dissolved the Gehirn Research
Organization immediately.
In order to complete the project,
the special organization
NERV was formed.
We all transferred to NERV,
except for one person.
The one who had rendered such
great service to the MAGI System,
Dr. Akagi.
Oh, it's you.
Yes, it is.
It's been awhile. The guards
are sleeping.
This action could result
in your death.
All I want is to get closer
to the truth.
To have it in my grasp.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Is it over?
Yes, the problem has been solved.
I see.
Where is he?
I have no idea.
Oh, hi! You're a little late.
I'm back.
Katsuragi, it's me.
I'm sure you're listening
to this message,
especially after I caused
you so much trouble.
Sorry.
Please tell Ritsuko I'm sorry too.
Oh, and there's one more thing.
I've been growing watermelons.
I'd appreciate it if you could
water them for me.
Shinji knows where they are.
Katsuragi, the truth is with you.
Don't hesitate, move ahead!
If I ever see you again,
I'll say the words that I couldn't
say eight years ago.
Bye.
This message was recorded
at 12:02 PM.
You fool...
You were always such a fool.
All I could do was run away from
the tragedy Misato was facing.
There was nothing I could say.
I was just a child.
But I understood.
Preview
Surpassed by Shinji again, Asuka
falls into a dark pit of despair,
and damage from the next Angel
attack is even more horrifying.
Shinji can find no words to
soothe her shattered soul.
It's the next episode:
"At Least, Be Humane"