Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Katsuragi, it's me.
I'm sure you're listening to this message,
after I caused you so much trouble.
Sorry.
Please tell Rit-chan "I'm sorry".
And there's one more thing to trouble
you with.  I've been growing flowers.
I'd appreciate it if you
could water them for me.
Shinji-kun knows where they are.
Katsuragi, the truth is with you.
Don't hesitate.  Move ahead.
If I can see you again, I'll say the
words that I couldn't say 8 years ago.
Bye.
A telephone that doesn't ring...
ON BUSINESS
Sorry, but don't
call me
Misato-san's shutting herself
up today, as usual.
Authorized Personnel ONLY
If you enter without my
permission, you shall die!
Entry Forbidden!
Asuka...  she isn't coming back?
She doesn't go to school or home,
she just plays games all day.
Hikari...
Hmm, what?
Let's go to bed.
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I'm causing
you a lot of trouble.
No, you're not.
I lost. I'll never pilot an Eva again.
Now, it's not worth living.
I lost all my values for everything.
I hate this. I hate everyone.
I hate everything.
Though I hate myself the most.
Now I don't care about anything.
I have nothing to do.
I think you can do anything you want to.
I don't blame you.
I really think you've done well.
Well, that child is gone.
Hmm, probably.
Even cats die.
Don't cry, Grandma.
Mm, I'll come home when I have time to.
I haven't been to my mom's
grave in three years.
Next time, I'll call you.
OK, I have to go.
So, that cat died.
Episode 23'
TEARS
It's impossible for us to
retrieve the Lance of Longinus.
Why did you use it?
And about the Eva series, we
don't have all of them scheduled.
The annihilation of the Angel was more
important. There was no other way.
No other way? Your excuses
should be more persuasive.
The things you have done recently are too bold.
Fuyutsuki, I'm in conference.
Understood.
An Angel is approaching right now.
We'll finish this discussion
at the next opportunity.
That is, if your chair remains.
Ikari, are you going to betray us, SEELE?
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
Launch Unit 00 from the 32nd gate.
Set Unit 02 as backup.
No, I don't have the right to cancel
Commander Ikari's freeze on Unit 01. Bye.
Angel confirmed visually...  right?
Unit 00 launched. Deploying
to interception point.
Unit 02, wait at your present position.
No, sortie.
Commander!?
I don't care. At least it
might be useful as a decoy.
Yes, sir.
Eva Unit 02, preparing for launch.
I'm on board again, as usual.
Oh, no. Am I still synched to this?
Send Unit 02 to Gate Eight.
As soon as a location is
designated, we'll launch.
Even if I sortie, all I can do is disturb the others.
Target's approaching and is past
the Gora Final Interception Line.
I don't care about anything, anymore.
Target is rotating in the
air over Owakidani valley.
Target's AT Field is still active.
Where have you been?
I don't have an excuse.
Present status?
Still a stalemate.
Changing cyclically from pattern blue to orange.
What does that mean?
The MAGI are still working
on the answer.
The data is insufficient to find an answer.
But I'm sure that shape isn't fixed.
Our side can't attack first.
Rei, we'll observe its status for a while.
No, it's coming.
Rei, prepare for battle!
No! It's too late!
Target has physically contacted Unit 00.
Unit 00's AT Field?
Active, but being penetrated.
The Angel is trying to achieve
first level contact with Unit 00?
Danger! Unit 00's bioparts are being penetrated.
Eva Unit 02, sortie! Have her
rescue Rei and provide cover.
Target is penetrating Unit 00.
This is dangerous. 5% has
already been bio-fused.
Asuka, advance 300 meters and
spread your AT Field,
then fire the
palette gun at the Target's back.
Alright? Eva Unit 02, lift off!
Move out! Asuka?! What's wrong?
Unit 02's status?
Impossible. Synchro ratio is under 10%.
Asuka!
It doesn't move. It doesn't move.
Like this, she'll be a victim too.
Retrieve her! Hurry!
Who? Me? Me within Eva?
No, I feel someone else other than me.
Who are you? An Angel?
A being that we call an Angel?
Don't you want to be unified with me?
No. I am I. Not you.
Hmm, but you shall be. It's too late.
I give you part of my mind.
I give you this emotion.
Pain... See, your mind has pain.
Pain? No, something different.
Loneliness. Yes,loneliness.
Loneliness?  I don't understand.
Do you hate being alone?
We are many, but you are alone.
You hate it, don't you?
That's called loneliness.
That's your mind. Full of sorrow.
That's your own mind.
These are tears?
It's me who's crying?
Rei!
The freeze on Unit 01 is
canceled, effective immediately.
Sortie as soon as possible.
Sortie!
Yes, sir!
Am I so worthless to you?
You didn't do this for me.
Spread your AT Field.
Rescue Rei immediately.
Yes!
Ikari-kun!
Shinji-kun, use your prog knife!
It hurts, doesn't it Ikari-kun?
Is this my wish? To be one with Ikari-kun?
No!
AT Field has been reversed! It
will be corroded immediately.
To hold the Angel?
Field limit reached! The core
can't hold up much longer!
Rei! Abandon the unit and escape!
No. If I escape, the AT
Field will disappear.
I won't let it.
Rei, do you want to die?
The core is collapsing,
critical pressure exceeded!
The target has disappeared.
This operation is finished.
Move to level one alert.
Roger. Moving to situation yellow immediately.
Unit 00's status?
Entry plug ejection not recognized.
Rescue the pilot as
soon as possible. Hurry!
You mean, if there still is one.
Still unable to find the constituent matter for
section 16. Location efforts proceeding.
...extending in the southwest direction.
Dr. Akagi...
This is top secret. Scavenge the plug.
Dispose of the parts concerned.
Roger.
Do it immediately.
The 3rd Angel
Sachiel
The 4th Angel
At last we have defeated
the Angels, up to the 16th.
Shamshiel
The 5th Angel
Ramiel
The 6th Angel
Gahgiel
The 7th Angel
Israphel
The 8th Angel
Now there is only one Angel left, which is
described in the Dead Sea Scrolls of Seele.
Sandalphon
The 9th Angel
Matriel
The 10th Angel
Sahquiel
The 11th Angel
Ireul
The 12th Angel
Leriel
The 13th Angel
Bardiel
The 14th Angel
The promised time is close.  The road
has been long, with many casualties.
Zeruel
The 15th Angel
Arael
The 16th Angel
Armisael
Aye.  After losing the Lance of
Longinus, we lost Eva Unit 00.
That's sufficient reason to dismiss Ikari.
He must understand why
we returned Fuyutsuki alive.
We have to find another pawn
to use against Ikari.
And this one must know the truth.
Shinji-kun, I'm coming in.
Misato-san, the tears won't come.
I think I'm sad, but tears never come.
Shinji-kun, all I can do for you is this.
Stop it! No, Misato-san.
I'm very sorry.
I'm sure he's feeling lonely.
Is he afraid of women?
No, he's just afraid of
affection in general.
Pen Pen, come here.
Okay, I just want anybody.
I'm the one who's lonely.
It's me who's lonely.
Rei...
The product of my despair,
and yet the object of your hope.
I guess it's impossible to forget her.
Yes, hello. Really?!
Shinji-kun!
Dr. Odani of the First Internal Department...
Dr. Odani, please contact the second
conference room immediately.
Ayanami!
First Neurological Surgery
Third Surgery
2nd Floor
Hospital Ward
Radiation Diagnosis
X-ray Reception
I'm glad, you're alive!
But, my father isn't here?
Thank you. You saved me.
What?
You saved me, by sacrifying Unit 00.
Oh, did I save you?
Yeah. Don't you remember?
No... I mean, I don't know.
I think, probably, I'm the third.
Are these tears?
I'm seeing this for the first time,
but it feels familiar.
Am I crying?
Why am I crying?
That's right. Preserve the present
status for the First Children.
No restrictions are necessary.
This applies to the Second and
Third as well. Just watch them.
If they find out Rei is alive, Chairman
Keel and the others will cause trouble.
I'll present something else to the
old men of SEELE.
There's no problem.
We wish to proceed peacefully.
We don't wish you to suffer from insults anymore.
I don't feel any insult.
A strong tempered woman.
I can see why Ikari wants
to keep her next to him.
However, it was none other than
Ikari who presented you to us.
Rejecting the interrogation
of the pilot of Unit 00,
he presented you as her replacement,
Doctor Akagi.
I'm Rei's substitute, am I?
ON BUSINESS
Sorry, but don't call me
The way to the truth which you wanted,
was sent to you by 36 other methods.
But those won't reach you.
The only one guaranteed is this capsule.
It's completely up to you how to use this.
The pass code is our first memory.
Bye, Take care.
I'm not upset anymore by
the telephone that doesn't ring...
...since I received your heart.
Are you sure about releasing
Doctor Akagi?
She isn't like Fuyutsuki. It will be
beneficial to release her.
She rendered remarkable
service to the Eva series.
She should be useful to us for a while.
Yes, for the future of humanity.
Regarding Evangelions, eight of
them are under construction.
So, there are four more to go.
The disappearance of Tokyo-3
will enhance the project.
Hurry with the completion.
The promised day will be that day.
Yes, hello.
Listen to me. You're free from
the secret service right now.
You can go out now.
Ritsuko-san...
No good, without my pass.
I see. Kaji-kun arranged this?
The secret of this place must
be revealed before my eyes.
Alright. But this one will see it as well.
Very well.
This looks just like Ayanami's room.
Ayanami Rei's room. This is
the place where she was born.
In this room?
Yes, her birth place.
Light and water, which make up Rei's
deep mentality, reflect the image of this place.
Dr. Akagi, I didn't come to see this.
I know, Misato.
Eva?
The first one. A failure.
Disposed of ten years ago.
A graveyard for Evas.
Nothing but a dumping ground.
This is also the place where
your mother disappeared.
You probably don't remember
but you were watching it,
watching the moment
when your mother disappeared.
Ritsuko!
You say this is the core of the dummy plug?
I'll show you the truth.
Ayanami...  Rei.
What? Eva's dummy plug is...
Yes. These are about to be
the core of the dummy system.
This is the factory for manufacturing them.
This is...?
These are dummies.
And nothing but spare parts for Rei.
Humans found a god, and thus tried to obtain it.
As a result, humanity was punished!
That was 15 years ago.
The god that they found vanished.
However, Man tried to resurrect
God with his own hands,
and created Adam. From Adam,
man created what resembles God.
That is Eva.
Human? Is that a human?
Yes, that's a human.
Eva, which originally didn't have
a soul, now has a human soul.
All of these were salvaged.
However the vessel which truly contains
a soul is Rei. Only she has a soul.
None of the other vessels have a soul.
There was nothing within the room of Gauf.
These are empty containers.
They have no souls.
Nothing but vessels.
So I'll destroy them, because I hate them.
Do you know what you're doing?!
Yeah, I know. Destruction.
These are not human, but human-shaped things.
I lost against the THING. I couldn't win.
When he's in my mind, I can bear any insult.
I don't care about my own body.
But...  but he...  he chose...
I knew that.
I'm stupid. I...  I'm as stupid
as my mother. So foolish!
You can kill me, if you wish.
I'd be glad if you did.
You're truly stupid if you wish that.
This is the tragedy of
people possessed by Eva.
I'm also one of them.
To be continued...
Preview
The city that the boy had been
protecting disappears.
The friends that the boy had
been close to leave.
The girls that the boy had been
drawn to turn to fear.
Shinji has lost all his emotional supports,
but a new boy smiles upon him in the dusk.
Shinji gives himself over to the smile
that seems to envelop all the sins
he has ever committed.
But a cruel fate was in store for them.
Next episode: "The Final Messenger"
Next Time
The Final Messenger