Zankoku na tenshi no youni
Like an angel without a sense of mercy...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare
...rise young boy to the heavens as a legend.
Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Aoi kaze ga ima
Cold winds, as blue as the sea...
Mune no door wo tataitemo
Tear open the door to your heart...
Watashidake wo tada mitsumete
But unknowing you seem, just staring at me...
Hohoenderu anata
Standing there smiling serenely.
Sotto fureru mono
Desperate for something to touch...
Motomeru koto ni muchu de
A moment of kindness like that in a dream..
Unmei sae mada shiranai
Your innocent eyes as yet have no idea...
Itaikena hitomi
...of the path your destiny will follow.
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday you'll become aware of...
Sono senaka niwa
...everything that you've got behind you.
Haruka mirai mezasu tameno
Your wings are for seeking out...
Hanega arukoto
...a new future that only you can search for.
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
The cruel angel's thesis bleeds...
Madobe kara yagate tobitatsu
...through a portal like your pulsing blood.
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
If you should betray the chapel of your memories...
Omoide wo uragiru nara
...the cruel angel will enter the window of your soul.
Kono sora wo daite kagayaku.
So boy, stand tall and embrace the fire of legend...
Shonen yo shinwa ni nare.
Embrace the universe like a blazing star!
Unit 01's interlocking
circuit has been cut.
What about the force eject signal?
It's being blocked from the plug
side. It's not being accepted.
But, Shinji, if we hadn't done that
you would have been killed.
That's not the point.
But it is a fact.
Don't push me anymore.
Unit 01 has 185 seconds of
power left in its reserves.
That's enough to destroy at
least half of Headquarters.
The way he is right now,
he'll do it too.
Shinji, listen to us!
If Commander Ikari hadn't
made that decision,
everyone could have been killed!
I said that's not the point!
My father...
My father tried to kill Toji
using my hands!
That bastard!
Episode 19
A Man's Battle
Father, you're there, aren't you?
Say something! Answer me!
Increase the pressure of
the LCL to maximum.
We have no time to waste
on a petulant child.
I've still got a direct
control circuit...
Damn! Damn!
Damn...
The right breast has been
completely dissolved.
We'll begin cleansing the bodily
fluids from Unit 03 on schedule.
Have you recovered?
I can work.
I couldn't just lie in bed during
an emergency like this.
So what happened to Shinji?
I understand that they opened the
escape hatch with a laser cutter,
and removed him forcibly.
This sucks.
This time...
He's really finished.
That idiot won't find a
way out this time.
How is Ikari?
He wasn't injured, so he
ought to be okay.
He's probably dreaming away.
Dreaming?
Yeah. Don't tell me you
don't dream?
Shinji...
Why is he lying here next to me?
Where am I?
In the same hospital where
my sister is, maybe?
Hey, isn't that Shinji and Ayanami?
Ikari, why did you do that?
Because I couldn't
forgive my father.
He betrayed me.
Even though I was finally
able to talk to him,
he doesn't understand me at all!!
Did you try to understand
your father's feelings?
I did.
Why don't you try to
understand him?
I said I did!
You're running away from
unpleasant truths.
Why not?!
What's wrong with running away
from reality if it sucks?!
What are those two arguing about?
This is an exception.
You've got five minutes.
Thank you very much.
If it isn't the Class Rep...
Suzuhara, are you okay?
Well, I'm still alive.
I thought Shinji was here though.
Was that just a dream?
Ikari was let out yesterday.
You've slept for three days,
Suzuhara.
I did? For three whole days?
Class Rep, did you...
No, I came here as the
class representative!
It's an official duty!
Yeah, I know that.
You don't know anything.
I'm sorry that I didn't get to
eat the lunch you made.
Don't worry about it.
But I am sorry that I can't bring
you a lunch here, it's not allowed.
Class rep?
What?
Would you do me a favor?
Would you tell my sister that
there's nothing wrong with me?
Get out, Shinji Ikari. The
Commander wants to see you.
Disobeying orders, personal
occupation of an Eva,
childish intimidation...
These are all criminal offenses.
Do you have anything to say?
Yes, I don't want to pilot
an Eva anymore.
I don't want to stay here anymore.
Well then, leave.
Yes, I'll go back to my
teacher's place.
So you're running away again?
You disappoint me. I assume
that we'll never meet again.
Yes, that's my intent.
It's me.
Erase the Third Child.
Rei will be Unit 01's
designated pilot,
with the dummy plug as back up.
Are you there, Shinji?
Is it true that you're leaving?
It's true, isn't it?
But why? Why are you
running away again?
I admired you.
I envied you. You're
different from us.
Damn! Even Toji became
an Eva pilot, while I...
This line is monitored.
For security reasons we have
terminated this call.
We appreciate your cooperation.
I assume that Asuka is
disgusted with me.
Yes, she didn't even ask me
to say goodbye to you.
That sounds like her. That's good.
It's going to be hard if you keep
hiding your anger like that.
That's your philosophy, Misato.
I can't live like you.
As I'm sure you know,
there will be a lot of restrictions
placed on your activities.
Yes.
But...
What?
Let me ask you one thing.
Why was Toji chosen to
be the Fourth Child?
All your classmates are
Fourth Level candidates.
I just found out myself that it
was yet another set-up.
All of them?
All of my classmates...
Suzuhara was a mistake that can't
be mended with words alone.
But, Shinji, to be honest,
I was projecting all of my dreams,
hopes and purpose onto you.
I know that it's been a huge
burden for you.
But we, everyone at NERV,
had no choice except to entrust
our future to you.
I want you to remember that.
It's a selfish cause, isn't it?
I admit that.
I'll leave your pass code to HQ
and your room as they are.
What's the point? Get
rid of them please.
I won't pilot an Eva again.
That's the real Shinji talking.
I've never heard him
so positive before.
A special state of emergency is
declared for the Tokai region.
All citizens must evacuate to their
designated shelters immediately.
Repeating...
An Angel!
All personnel go to first
stage battle stations.
Prepare for ground-to-air
intercept.
Target status?
It's moving into our perimeter.
The Komagatake Defense Line
has been breached.
The first eighteen layers of armor
have been shattered.
Eighteen layers of special armor
at once! Incredible!
The Eva won't make there in time
for a ground level intercept.
Position Unit 02 for combat
inside the Geo-Front,
directly in front of Headquarters.
Asuka will engage the target as
soon as it breaches the Geo-Front.
What about Unit 00?
It's been placed in the AT Field
Neutralization Zone.
However, the left arm hasn't
been regenerated yet.
Then, it's not ready for combat.
Sortie Rei in Unit 01.
Prepare a dummy plug as
the backup system.
Yes, Sir.
Start entry.
Charge LCL.
Commence A10 nerve connection.
It's not going to work this time.
Pulse flow is reversing!
Unit 01 is refusing the
neural connection!
Is that possible?
Ikari?
Yes, it's refusing me.
Abort activation.
Sortie Rei in Unit 00.
Re-activate Unit 01 with
the dummy plug.
But Unit 00 isn't ready!
It's not a problem. I can go.
Rei?
If I die, I can be replaced.
I decided. I swore I'd
never pilot it again.
Hey, you! What're you doing?
Get into the shelter, quickly.
It's no use.
One more hit, and the armor will
be completely destroyed.
I'm counting on you, Asuka.
Here it comes. Even without
Shinji, I can beat it easily.
You!
Next!
I'm neutralizing its
AT Field, aren't I?
Why doesn't it collapse?
I can't lose again!
No way!
You damn bastard!
Asuka, cut all the nerve
connections now!
Evacuation training?
What are you, stupid?
That stuff's not for us pilots.
Direct hit on the Eighth Block!
Abandon the Sixth Shelter! All
survivors, go to the Third Shelter!
Unit 02 is severely damaged.
It can't continue combat.
How's Asuka?
She's safe. Alive!
Damn...
The Angel has started moving.
What's Unit 01's status?
Dummy plug upload, complete.
Probe insertion, complete.
Start contact.
Roger!
What?
The pulses have vanished.
It's refusing the dummy plug.
It's no use. Eva Unit 01
will not activate.
The dummy, Rei...
Are we being refused?
Fuyutsuki...
I'm leaving you in charge of this.
Take casualties to the Sixth Block.
Uninjured, go to the Third Shelter!
This way!
Hurry!
Quick!
Hey, you! What're you doing?
Do you want to die?!
Asuka...
Is that you, Shinji?
Kaji?
What are you doing here?
That's my line.
What are you doing here, Shinji?
I...
I decided that I'll never
pilot an Eva again.
And since I decided that...
Is that so?
Well, since my other job became
public knowledge,
I'm off the combat roster.
So, here I am, sprinkling.
At a time like this?
What better time?
Although I'd rather be between
Misato's breasts,
I wouldn't mind being
here when I die.
Die?
That's right.
It's said if an Angel makes contact
with Adam, who lies below here,
humanity will be eradicated.
The Third Impact.
The only thing that can stop it
is the one thing with power equal
to an Angel's, the Evangelion.
Ayanami?
With no rifle?!
Is she trying to blow herself up?
Rei!
AT Field, full power.
What happened to Unit 00?
Rei!
What has she done?
Shinji, the only thing I can do
is stand here and water.
But you, you have something that
you can do. That only you can do.
Nobody is forcing you.
Think for yourself, and make
the decision by yourself.
Think about what you
have to do now.
Think about no longer
having any regrets.
Direct hit on the third foundation.
The final armor plate has melted.
Damn! The Main Shaft
is completely open!
Isn't Unit 01 ready yet?
It's refusing the dummy plug.
It failed. No response detected.
Keep trying. Repeat the process
from step 108.
Let me pilot it!
I... I...
Let me pilot Unit 01, please!
Father...
Why are you here?
I... I...
I am the pilot of Evangelion
Unit 01!
I am Shinji Ikari!
The target has entered
the Main Shaft.
It's descending.
Where is it heading?
It's advancing directly towards
Central Dogma.
It's coming here?
All personnel evacuate. Hurry!
All personnel evacuate! Repeat,
all personnel evacuate!
Eva Unit 01?!
Shinji!
Misato!
Launch the fifth catapult! Hurry!
Out of energy?
Unit 01 has drained its reserves.
The backup power supply
isn't working.
Shinji!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Come on, move!
Move now or there's
no point to this!
That's...
Move! Move! Move!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Move! Move!
Move! Move! Come on, move!
You've got to move! Move now!
Or everyone will be killed!
I'm sick of it already! So...
COME ON, MOVE!
Eva has re-activated!
Incredible!
No way, this is unbelievable. Unit
01's synch ratio is over 400%!
Does that means she's
been awakened?
It's eating the Angel?
She's taking the S2 engine
into herself?
Eva Unit 01 is...
The bindings!
Bindings?
That's right. It's not
really armor.
Those are restraints that allow us
to control the Eva's power.
But now the Eva is removing the
web that binds it to our will.
We can no longer control the Eva.
Unit 01's been awakened
and set free.
SEELE won't stay quiet for this.
Did you say this was part of your
scenario, Commander Ikari?
It's begun, hasn't it?
Yes, this is the beginning.
To be continued...
Preview
Mankind has been saved
by the Eva's awakening,
but its pilot has been
physically fused with the Eva.
Shinji's been fused with another
existence. What will he see?
What was it that
the crying Misato saw?
Next time:
"Shape of Heart, Shape of Human"