(THIS IS A BETA VERSION!)
Today this person will conduct.
Chiaki-Sama!
Chiaki....
I'm.....the orchestra's Conductor?
Why Chiaki? He's from the Piano Division, isn't he!
What happened with Stresemann?
What happened...err...
If you kiss me, I will permit Chiaki's transfer of Division
After you graduate, you're going to go to Europe, right?
Europe or kiss?
Nodame-chan!
? @@@german@@@
When I thought you were going to kiss him,
suddenly launching Seiken Zuki
Because suddenly Milch was going to jump on me...
Which means he's an impostor afterall.
Let's go home!
Chiaki, can you really conduct?
He can do it easily at leasure!
What easily at leasure!
What piece is it?
Beethoven's Symphony No 7.
I have just studied it from Vieira Sensei's recording
I can do it
Everybody, did you practice it already?
Yes, because the piece is already decided
Yosh! First, let's do some tuning!
Oboe!
Yosh! Now Ore-Sama will....
Wait!
Why is Mine imitating a Concert Master?
I'm not imitating, I AM the Concert Master of S-Oke!
It's decided properly by competition!
Eh? It can't be!
Errr......
This is the conductor's baton used in our lectures,
you can use it if you like...
No, please use mine...though it's a bit too big...
Chiaki-Sama!
Chiaki-Sama, no....no...look here, I have...
Can he really conduct with only good-look?
He'll just act cool and wave that stick around.
He'll make a good sight!
Please, Chiaki-San.
Get back, you ugly!
Although I'm a substitute for the practice,
I can get to conduct an orchestra.
There's seldom any chance like this!
Yosh! Let's begin!
Milch, please wake up!
Chiaki-Senpai is going to conduct.
Though I've never seen him conduct before
He always studies so hard, he must be amazing!
Milch will certainly come to like him too....
? @@@german@@@?
Noooo!!
Ouch!
Beethoven's Symphony No 7
although it's not major like "Fate" and No 9
(Fate = No 5)
the scale is big...
a wonderful Symphony overflowing with uplifting spirit.
What with this Oke???
EXTREMELY no good!
Even if it's the first try,
can I allow such a pathetic piece of Beethoven's?
That Jiijii!
Didn't he just gather all the no-good and all the weird
throughout the Academy?
Stop! Stop!
Hey everybody!
Let's play it more grandly!
More intensely, more nobly....
OK? Got it?
What grandly?
Are you in a level proper to say that?
Eh?
You made a lot of mistakes, didn't you!
The Concert Master confusing the orchestra,
what are you trying to do?!
What a miserable Concert Master!
Clarinet!
The pitch is not at all in sync!
Trumpet!
Your sound's too loud!
Horn!
Y....yes?
Skip properly!
Viola!
You skipped too much on your own!
Yes, YOU!
Chiaki-Sama is wonderful!
He's like a real Conductor!
The way he waves the baton is also beautiful!
Dammit! Doing it in front of Kaoru-san...
Everybody can easily notice such obvious mistakes!
Eh, shall we play a little trick on him?
Iet's exchange the oboe and the clarinet
Definitely he won't notice it!
So many weird sounds....
I feel sorry for Chiaki-Sama!
It's no use criticizing their individual technique
this is a chance for me to conduct an orchestra
I'll try to materialize this wonderful piece of Beethoven
by my own way
Okay let's begin again from the start!
Oboe, too high!
Clarinet, get in sync!
Horn, your pitch!
Bass and clarinet!
@@?@@
Waaah, amazing!
Chiaki-Senpai can soon recognize whose sound
each sound is...
Milch
Violin! Pianissimo!
Viola, faster!
Second violin, keep fortissimo!
Clarinet, don't lower the sound!
How can I stand doing it!
They didn't pay attention to my conducting
they have no ability to learn
on top of that, playing a stupid trick on me too
Such a terrible Oke like this!
Okay until here's enough.
Chiaki's a failure.
Quick, go down!
Huh?
Everybody, sorry to make you wait!
Here's the appearance of the leading role!
Oi! I'm a failure? Why?
You made a girl cry
That's the lowliest failure.
Eh?
Sorry I am late!
Are you okay?
Wow, now everybody's here!
Let's begin
Chiaki
You... didn't notice an important thing.
An important thing?
Mine-kun, for the time being you
don't have to bother with the written technique
Let out more enjoyable sounds
Just as you usually do...
Hai!
You, Horn!
Yes?
You'd better blow your nose once first
Hai!
You, Clarinet! Perhaps it's better to change that reed.
Then, you, the beautiful twin girls...
It's very OK  to attract the Conductor, but..
but using sexy sounds....
Ha...hai
Kontrabass Kiddy-chan!
Are you ready?
Hai!
Okay....
Let's do it together....
according to what Chiaki said.
Is this...... according to what Chiaki said?
No
I don't mean to make excuses...
but thy are really bad at it
As to the reed and being unwell, they are also
the responsibility of the player
but....
with that person only waving his hands...
the orchestra comes together well...
He must certainly be....
respecting music
and respecting people...
and those things return to himself...
That is....
a real Maestro
Nodame Cantabile
Lesson 3
Please permit my transfer to Conductor Division
That's fine. Until you permit me, I will submit
as many as necessary
Even if you do not transfer,
I will take you as my pupil
Eh?
Because you seem to be interesting
it's a shame to let you be the pupil of the like of Vieira
But, don't transfer Divisions
it's better for you to continue your piano
In return for that, spend your other time
always with me
Sensei!
Yooooooooooosh!!
Since it's decided!
let's go to Shibuya!
Huh?
Together with Chiaki,
we'll get gyaku-nampa!
(=get girls approaching them)
Just a little more...
Just a little more
Look, what's that?
A music instrument is walking!
Ghost Kontrabass...
Look, look, Maki-chan, your lunch box is also walking!
Nodame!!!!
My "Spring Excursion" lunch box...
Err....
That lunch box....
if you don't need it, may I eat it?
But the food fell off and is full of sands...
That's alright
Hunger makes excellent spice.
Oh no!  I'm late for the orchestra's practice...
unconsciously my eyes got stuck on food
Nodame-chan, thank you for the meal!
Are you alright?
Oke?
Eh?
Participating in the periodical performance?
That will be S-Oke's debut!
There are only two weeks left
Such an Oke like this! Are you serious?
In that periodical performance, A-Oke will
also participate, you know!
Yosh! That'll be my Concert Master debut!
Let's not get beaten by A-Oke!
Let's not get beaten!
Let's do it!
Well,
it's not that I'll appear in it anyway.
And one more thing!
From today...
for the role of Vice Conductor of this S-Oke...
I'll have Chiaki to do it!
Huh?
Therefore, Chiaki...
here are the baton and score, the
conducting instruction is written inside it
I'm going to go to "douhan"
("companion")
Please do the rest for me
Club "One More Kiss"
"Companion"
Because I have a very important business to do now...
I leave it to Chiaki to do it
Bye bye!
Wait!
We joined this Oke because we want to
receive guidance from Sensei!
I am not responsible for S-Oke nor Conductor Division!
I can't bother with S-Oke all the time!
And next, until I come here,
all of you have your level up with Chiaki's help!
with no one missing, do your best
Bye bye!
Why am I Vice Conductor?
What's he thinking about, that Jiijii!
Well, don't think it too deeply
Don't you finally get to conduct in an Oke
together with me?
It's good to be shallow like you, people...
Dammit! Ignoring me who am from the Conductor Division!
Wait a minute!!
Who are you?
I'm Number 2 in this Academy....
Are you OK?
Sorry I am late!!
Gehh! Sakura! You're late again because of your
part-time work?
Actually today is off-day
But since I don't have money for the train,
I walked until here from home...
Walked? From where?
From Nakano
NAKANO????
Carrying this???
I wanted to practice but in the end I couldn't,
not having much time...
Hurry, get ready!
Hai!
We begin from the 1st movement!
Eh? Shinichi is Stresemann's pupil?
It seems so, I heard he's also participating in
the orchestra's practice.
Oh My!!
Tagaya-san DID NOT know it???
Bukko!
(Ugly Girl)
Aren't you in "keep" relationship with Chiaki-kun?
Accckkk!!
Ex-"keep" relationship, my mistake!!
Rather than that, Shitanoma-san...
Congratulation for winning the role of the heroine!
Thank you!
Well, because you becomes the heroine in my place
Do your best....
in dieting!
Hey! Don't run in the locker!
is that really true?
That Shinichi is participating in A-Oke?
Not A, but S!
S-Oke?
That Oke with the underachiever members?
Violin!
Are you people really looking at the score?
the 29th....
From the 29st mark, from here, feel more of the ensemble,
so to blend well together....
Hai...
And then you, Horn!
Hai?
At the start of the 89th mark,
you may enter suddenly and directly here
sync with each other, the two of you
Hai!
And next, Kontrabass group!
Hai
You!
Practice before coming here.
Hai!
Err ....excuse me!
May I copy the changed written technique?
About such a thing,
memorize it when we were practising.
I'm sorry....
It's because of you alone that everybody in the Kontrabass
group was reprimanded like that...
You're late and on top of that you lack practice...
You don't really want to do it, do you?
Let's go home!
Chiaki-Senpai!!
She came!
You must be tired!
Here! Towel, and lemon dipped in honey!
And ....
I love you!
Wait..wait...what's this?
Are you the manager of the baseball club?
No, she's the Mascot Girl!
I'm Minami-chan!
Ouch! What Minami?
Today I'll really kill you!
Let me in too!
What's this!
Umm....Chiaki-Sama...
Chiaki-kun....
I can't play this phrase well...
Eh?
I asked Stresemann before, but he
ignored me, so I asked Vice Conductor...
Here it is easy to get confused by the surrounding sounds....
you must get a strong hold of your own.....
Chiaki-kun!
I also have something to consult with you...
Me too!
I have a question!
A question?
What to consult ...wait!
Is it alright if I play it....
Here the second violin and viola....
That Chiaki!! He's overdoing it!!
Who are you?
I'm the second famous in this Academy....
He's gentler than before...
he became closer to us, didn't he?
I'll go ask him a question!
Me too!
Chiaki-Senpai!
What about today's dinner?
The supermarket might close soon!
Here until the other instruments come out...
Nodame's going home, will that be alright with you?
Towards the 116th mark it will come in...
the start of the 116th mark skips it, right...
here modulate it...
Stupid Senpai!
What's wrong with you, kiddy-chan?
I'm not kiddy!
Spice Girl!
Being in orchestra seems to be very tough...
Were you scolded by Chiaki-Senpai?
But I envy you!
Eh?
Because a pianist cannot join an orchestra.
Really...
Actually it's my first time to be selected in an orchestra
therefore I want to practice more
but my family is so poor, if I don't work part-time
I cannot buy food....
I wonder if there's some food ....
is there??
Just this rotten carrot....
Acck! My allowance is the day after tomorrow!
Therefore my parents told me to get a job
but I want to continue studying....
How would I know!
Don't consult with me about such a thing!
Hello?
Chiaki? I'm Tamaki the clarinet player
What do you think about Suzuki Kaoru-chan?
Dammit!
I shouldn't have distributed my phone number!
Am I a children councelor?
At the end, it's Nodame, huh?
I must be really exhausted I'm seeing things...
Senpai, it's Nodame, please open the door...
Nodame?
Please give some food as alms....
Is this also the job of a Vice Conductor?
Waaa....amazing! Pasta, soup and even salads!
But the soup is instant soup! Hmph, you didn't cook
it as you usually do, don't you?
Nodame is not going to drink the soup
Is that something an alms-recipient can say??!!
Nodame-chan, Chiaki-Senpai always cook such
wonderful dishes by himself for you?
Yes, and they contain a lot of love!
They don't contain such thing!!!
Itadakimasu!!
Incredible!
I wonder how many years have passed since I last
had such a luxurious pasta like this....
Luxurious?? I just put in leftover vegetables.
That there are still some vegetables left is LUXURIOUS!
My family don't even have rice for tomorrow
Huh?
My Dad's company is not doing well
He seems to have some debt as well
Debt?
My Mom also works part-timer, but it's still not enough
Because being in a Music Academy needs more money
than in a usual University
Therefore I work part-time so that at least I can
earn some money for the school fee...
That's why I don't have time to practice Kontrabass
and quickly got behind the others
If I keep being in this condition,
how could I remain in S-Oke?
That Oke is not a good thing anyway!
But the others in the Kontrabass group are good at it!
I'm just a stumbling stone...
If so, then you only need to practice more!
I told you I don't have time because I have to work part-timer!
Then what about quitting your part-time job?
I told you if I quit my job I can't continue studying at school!
Then....what about quitting school?
Why did it come to that??
Well, if for the sake of school fee she has no time to practice,
is there any meaning she goes to school?
There is!
For love, for meeting new friends, for joy....
If it were me, I'll go to school and practice
Well, if she doesn't want to improve her skill,
it's also alright to be like this, I think
I want to improve my skill.
Really?
If one has the time to cry here
and not thinking of practicing instead,
isn't she already hopeless?
Chiaki Senpai!
Sorry to have bothered you.
Sakura-chan...
What is it?!
Sakura-chan!
I....
....should perhaps quit school....
Dad, I'm going now!
Going now? What happened with you?
It's unusual you woke up by yourself!
This is a Concert Master's destiny!
Without me, the Oke can't do!
I go!
Take care!
Hai!
Acting such a wonderful kid.....
Yosh!!!
Flute, at the 117th mark, you two...
Hai!
From 238th mark, don't do it separately,
make it more linked to each other
Hai!
Oboe, it gets a little bit heavy than before, so...
That is Concert Master?
Sh...sh...she's not the Conductor?
Hai!
OK, let's have a ten minutes break.
Masumi-chan!
So you didn't return to your hometown?
As usual, you're striving for the best, Kiyora!
What else can I do?
Until Stresemann comes,
it's Concert Master's job to get the Oke going.
Eh? So he doesn't come to A-Oke either?
What is he doing??
At this time, the Concert Master of S-Oke
must be having a tough time too, doesn't he?
With everyone relying on him
Yes....sort of...
Ah, and this person is....?
He's our Concert Master.
Eh?
Aaah, really...
Today let's stop here.
Next time we'll do the 2nd movement,
so practice before coming here
Hai!
Stresemann didn't come again today
I wonder what's the important business he has....
"companion"
Sakura-chan didn't come either today
Did something wrong happen to her?
She must be working at her part-time job.
But usually she always comes even if she's late
So what if she is not here....
She's no-good, I got irritated by just looking at her
That's mean! Could it be because you always bully her?
Didn't you all think the same way?
She's no-good, there are a lot of people who can replace her!
Chiaki-Senpai!
Sakura-chan didn't come, did she?
It's Senpai's fault!
Because last night Senpai said why didn't she quit school
Sakura-chan was shocked!
Shocked? Just because of that?
It must be because she doesn't want to do it,
so she didn't come
That's not my fault.
Senpai's an ogre! DEVIL!
A person like you won't understand...
Always at the center of people
Always being depended upon...
A person like you won't understand!
Katsuragi Madoka, wow, nice body!
98-52-98!
My nosebleed might spurt out! Hahao!!
I'd better look from a distance!
What is it you intend to do, Maestro?
Oh! It's you, Harisen Sensei!
My name's Eto!
Leaving the Oke to mere students....
actually what are you scheming?
Wow, they look so delicious!!
I wonder if I have enough....
(55 yen = half the price of a rice ball)
What are you doing?
Sakura-chan!
So you're working part-time in that konbini
Yes.
Because I can bring home lunch boxes which have expired
Though if they find out, I'll be sacked.
Itadakimasu!
But it's good that it's Nodame-chan who saw me.
Well, there are a lot of students coming
from well-off families in Music Academy, right?
I feel ashamed....
It's good it was Nodame who saw you?
No, forget it, don't think too deeply about it.
Why didn't you come to practice today?
If you're bothered by what Chiaki Senpai said....
Nono....I think what Chiaki-Senpai said is correct
I also realize it myself...
Saying that I had no time is just an excuse...
Actually it's not caused by my being very poor
It's my own fault, because I'm no good...
I think it's better for S-Oke without me in it
Is Sakura-chan alright with it?
The second movement....
There's still no guidance from Stresemann
Maestro...Maestro....
it's time for me to return to work...
About my...performance...which I am going to conduct....
I will give your magazine special interview!
Bring in all the fruits and drinks,
lots of them, don't linger, go!
Let's play scissor game!
Scissor game, scissor game!
The first, the first, the first is GU!
(gu= fist in scissor game)
Jiijii!!
So were you doing this night by night?
Chiaki, you yourself...
why are you here in such a place?
Huh?
At a time they have to level up like now....
One of the members doesn't come to practice, right?
Do you intend to pass it on to me in such a condition?
That is.....
What?
I came just to see that Jiijii...
Well, well...
Handsome young man....
So young!
What would you like to drink?
For me too! Give me osake!
What are these people?
It was always ojiisan, so boring!
Here you are!
Here, this one is big....aaaaaaannngggg....
What business do you have with the ogre and devil Ore-Sama?
Please lend me your bath
Why bath? You have one too in your room.
I can't use it because they stopped the gas!
My allowance arrives tomorrow, so I can't pay either...
Then bear it until tomorrow! You always stink, anyway!
It reached my limit already, so very itchy!!
Wash it with water!
I ran out of shampoo!
Wash it with soap!!
Don't depend on me for every single thing!
A person like Senpai won't understand...
That, again?
This itchiness, and also this feeling of vexation....
With soap?....Most probably my hair will turn
weird after washing it with kitchen detergent
Kitchen detergent???
Chopin and Beethoven flourished to be great after
fully experiencing poverty...
I don't really know why, but....Senpai has absolutely
no idea about poverty!
For such a person, how could you possibly
understand real music and Beethoven?
I have absolutely no idea of poverty?
I know!
Poverty, right?
Don't you need some matches?
Patrasche, I'm exhausted already....
"I won't forget this road...."
"...walking together with Patrasche...."
Stop singing that song!
So the gas being stopped really does exist.....in reality
Kontrabass...
If I stop working, I can't continue studying in the Academy!
What a good warm bath! Thank you!
Sakura-chan left it in Nodame's room...
What's wrong, Senpai?
Until now I have never worried about
living expenses and school fees...
That  someone might
not to be able to play music anymore
have never entered my mind.
Oh yeah!
I will lend you the latest publication
and the latest  issue of these interesting books
Please cheer up!
Kazuo is here too, Kazuo!
What Chopin, what Beethoven!?
You always buy these things, isn't that why you're in poverty?!!
Gyaboooooo!
Ehhhhh....
Dammit!
I only need to talk a bit with her,
why do I have to go as far as to her house?
What else can we do?
Sakura-chan has no cell phone,
and her home phone is also cut off.
So primitive!
But Senpai changed your heart...
and is going to Sakura-chan's house to say sorry!
I'm not going to her house to say sorry!
I just want to tell her not to play truant for the Oke's practice.
Because until now I'm being blamed for it.
So I have no choice.
Stop that face!!
Oiii...hurry up!
Chiaki-Sama, this way please...
Why is Masumi-chan....the two of you...here?
Do you think I'll let you go out with him?
In terms of the feeling of
someone who plays truant from practice,
I understand more than you!
Let's go, let's go!
THIS house???
You...
what business do you have with my house?
Who is he?
"Certificate of Object Confistication"
Really, so you're all Sakura's friends...
Ah..please sit down...
Excuse me..
She went to work since morning, sorry...
but I think she will return soon...
Please help yourself...
Water...
Water?
Water!
It's water from a well, isn't it?
Sshhh!
Sorry for being rude, may I ask your line of work?
I'm operating a company dealing with import furnitures...
However, it's recession lately...
Such luxurious goods like these don't sell well..
Is it really a recession problem?
Umm..
I learned the condition of your family, but
please tell Sakura-san to go to school
Wait a minute!
All of you....
What do you play in the Academy?
I play the piano
I play timpani!
And this gentleman, he conducts,
and also plays the piano and others.
I see...
No violin.....
I play violin, I'm the Concert Master! What is it?
Really! I have something I want you to certainly see!
This way...
Piano?
This way please
Chiaki, you go, go!
Waaa, it's dark!
Come in please
Welcome....to my collection room!
It only contains excellent violins!
Amazing!!!
Guarnerie? Tomaso Eberle? 100.000.000 yen! 60.000.000 yen!
Such famous instruments....so many...
As I thought, you know them!
I'd like to have Stradivari too! The 400.000.000 yen one!
How is it? Beautiful, isn't it?
Violins retain their form since their first appearance
in the 14th century!
They are different from other instruments.
These instruments are like a miracle!
Would you like to hear how it sounds?
Sure!
You'll be surprised!
What's this??
Surprised??
Actually I can't play violin at all!
Would you play it for me please?
Are you an idiot?
You can't play and yet such a collection?
And you're in poverty???
Right! If you have money debt, sell all of these!
These are not things that one can easily obtain, stupid!
Even if you can obtain them,
these instruments won't be happy with it either!
These are collections which I regard as
muuuuuuuuuuch more precious than my life!
Are they more precious than your own daughter?
Your daughter said she wanted to study music...
but why for such things you....
If you love music you should have understood, didn't you?
about your daughter's feeling to continue studying music!
I.....I love VIOLIN!
Kontrabass, huh?!
So simple, and the pitch so unstable!
A parent like you....
She won't want to hear her father insult the pitch...
Well, I....
I want Sakura
to play these violins one day
I was looking forward to it!
Dad!
Sakura-chan!
I love Kontrabass!
Why couldn't it be violin?
Because.....
Because Kontrabass is BIGGER and COOLER!
Eh? Just that??
I want to study more
I want to practice more, and become better and better...
I wish someday I can be a proffesional orchestra performer
If possible I wish to join Vienna Philharmonic Orchestra
Sakura...
So you have such a BIG dream?
TOO big a dream!
Please!
Please let me continue!
Otousan, rather than several-million-yen violins
doesn't your daughter's feeling to study music have
much more value?
without it, even if you have a lot of money...
Wow, amazing! Sakura-chan's lunch box!
My mom said it's a sign of gratitude for everybody
gratitude?
Thanks to my Dad's selling of his violins...
we can go back to normal life...
even the company can be revived...
even the company!
Yes.
It seems that there was a cursed violin among them....
Eh??
therefore my Dad also lives properly now
Eh? Sakura-chan, you're early!
The earliest?
Somehow you play a lot better!
I want to catch up with everyone so I practised a lot
Konnichiwa!
Hello, hello!
Here it is...
Eh?
It's the changed technique made while you weren't here
Do you want to copy it?
Thank you!
You didn't notice something important
with no one missing, do your best
There are various kinds of people in an orchestra
In a professional orchestra, people from various countries
come with various conditions
Was Maestro trying to convey this to me?
No, it couldn't be....
Won't you feel lonely?
Huh?
Because after everyone gets better,
Senpai has to pass this Oke on to Milch, right?
No way I'll feel lonely
Moreover, they are still far from good
Yosh! Let's practice with Chiaki!
Ah!
Milch!
Please
I make a pledge!
As of today, I withdraw from this S-Oke
and swear here, to concentrate on A-Oke!
Ehhh???
A-Oke?? WHY?
In S-Oke, there's someone whom I can't surpass
namely Chiaki, the excellent and wonderful man
and moreover!
you already have a Conductor, haven't you?
Wait a minute!
What do you mean?
Could it be...
because you bear a grudge on me
over the night club last time?
Naturally!
I bear a grudge on you!
Ahhh night club? Why??
Kisama...
(you, derogatory nuance)
with your shoes you trampled on my harem!
(harem = wives, concubines)
Definitely, definitely I can't forgive that!
HAREM??? Tell me, tell me!
You were cheating on me??
Anyway!
I... with A-Oke
kisama...with S-Oke
In the periodical performance next week...
We'll have a DUEL!
That being the case....
everyone in S-Oke...
do your most!
What is this all about?
You....did you do something, haha...
What is this?
We have been discarded, I think...
because we are all no good..
Everybody!
S-Oke won't lose spirit just because of this, right?
Why are you preparing to go home?
The "S" in S-Oke is the "S" from Stresemann's name
If the Chief quit, what else other than disbanding?
Right, disband!
Chiaki too?
Sorry to say it, but...
even if I could take Stresemann's place
it is worse to be ashamed if we fail
but...
but I want to perform in this Oke!
Eh?
This is my first time to be selected...in an orchestra!
Sakura-chan!
We...it's also our first time to be selected...
in these four years...isn't it?
I don't want to graduate in this condition!
Kaoru-san...
Me too!
I also want to do it with S-Oke!
Me too...since we already practiced this far anyway...
Yeah, I don't mind Chiaki's conducting
Right! Chiaki-Sama's orchestra!
There's no reason not to do it, isn't it?
Yes!
Isn't it?
YOSH!
From today, S-Oke's "S" is the "S" from "Special"!
We overthrow A-Oke!
Overthrow Stresemann!!
YES!!!!!
Oi!! I never said even a word that I will do it...
Sieg Zion!
(overthrow/defeat Zion)
Senpai, good for you, isn't it?
I'm......
this Oke's official Conductor?
Long live S-Oke!!
Credits will be there later in the non-beta version