Until the competition is over,
there will be no practice.
Oi, Chiaki
Senpai, please wait!
what was that just now...?
that was the plane at that time...
But..
the first thing I saw...
was that a human being?
Chiaki Senpai, are you ok?
I'm OK
Okay, for a while, everybody please practice
individually
Ha? What are you talking about, Kiyora!!
There's not much time left until the public performance!
Hey, all of you!
Kangaroo...
Deer...
Senpai.. It must be a real shock for you..
that everyone in the orchestra
isn't serious about this Oke..
but I'm returning to Boston in spring.
Me too, sooner or later, I intend to return
to Vienna
but about professional Oke, are you serious??
No.. Not at all!
Nodame don't mind....
even if I have to eat canned foods...
However, I want you to know that in this world
there are such things like food stores,
lunch boxes, and various other foods...
If you have complaints, then don't eat them.
I was not complaining..
Only Senpai too, why don't you try
eating this bear-meat flake by yourself once again...
I have no appetite
Ack, Senpai! The phone!
Let Nodame answer the phone!
Because I am your wife~
Hello
Shinichi?
Mom?
As always, it's dusty....this country.
Aren't you supposed to be in Europe now?
This time in my company's Culture Project,
they started to support Music Academy students
to study abroad.
To help in that project, I will be in Japan for a while
For a while..?
Hajimemashite,
my name is Noda Megumi.
Okaasama..ah no...I didn't like it, I was not looking..
I'll be fine, I plan to stay with
my parents in Yokohama.. or in a hotel.
Rather than that, Shinichi,
I met Maestro Stresemann there
Eh?
Then he told me that you have become his pupil
and he asked me to convey this message to you..
What is it?
"Please certainly send me Nagaoka Mami's Photo Book!"
I wonder what it is..
And then..
"I'm always watching over you."
"Whether in Japan, or anywhere,
we are connected by music."
"I won't forgive
half-heartedness!"
Even if this is an Oke that will disband
tomorrow...
The time spent on it would never
be a waste!
Senpai?
Ummm..
I made these, would you like to eat some..?
You had better take a bath too...
As expected, nobody came.
Yes...
Oboe Concerto aside,
it's too bad, as we've just started Brahms No 1
Being dispersed like this,
I wonder if we'll manage to do it on time
Dec. 3 Tokyo Sympony Hall
First show of Rising Star Orchestra!
Masumi chan
Kuroki-kun!
What are you doing?
I think we won't have any practice today.
I just happened to pass by here...
And that flower?
I happened to see it at a flower shop...
Do you guys know...
Noda Megumi-chan's house?
Could it be that that flower is for Nodame-chan??
KUROKI KUN!
What's good with that girl??
She's cute, and her character is honest,
cheerful, and gentle...
her clothes are clean, her language
is very polite...how pure she is...
Her character is insensitive, and cold!
She wears the same clothes for several days
she's not clean, she's a weird girl, AITSU!
(=that person, rude)
She always wears one-piece dress because
it is easy to change..
And that keigo
(=very polite level of Japanese language)
that's to hide her regional dialect!
She always eats other people's lunch box,
shampoos her hair once every 3 days,
her room is a a pile of garbage,
suddenly she'll turn into a mongoose and starts to dance!
That's her real identity!
It's impossible that Megumi-chan is hentai like that!
She's HENTAI, I told you!
<c:#FF80FF>Somehow it is coming~
<c:#FF80FF>It is coming soon
<c:#FF80FF>so, la, si, do, boo, boo, boo!  Waaaaa
I must not be angry!
<c:#FF80FF>Energetic fart, cute fart,
Her talent, I will bring out with my own hands
<c:#FF80FF>What kind of fart will come out this time?
But..why is she playing so happily?
<c:#FF80FF>Alright, everyone, let's fart together!
<c:#FF80FF>Hey! Hey!
<c:#FF80FF>Booo!!
<c:#FF80FF>(It came out!!)
Fart exercise.... We finished it!
Sensei..
Although it is just for a short time,
I'm indebted to you.
Take care!
WAIT!
What "take care"?
The other written agreement!
After completing one song,
you will start a lesson as I tell you to. - Eto Kozo
You haven't forget it.. have you?
Therefore, these are for you!
Until next lesson, choose 10 pieces from here,
and read the scores.
Read them?
Yes
Wait, Kiyora!
What do you intend to do with the Oke's practice?
Isn't it a Concert Master's job to pull the Oke
when the conductor's not there?
After competition is over, I will do it properly
Competition.. competition...
..as if you were some great musician
I have no choice!
Everybody's future depends on it!
If we win, the road as a soloist, and the chance
to be recognized worldwide will be bigger!
Therefore, I can't tell them to put the first priority
on the Oke's practice!
And moreover, me too,
in Oshiuri Competition's final selection,
my Master will also come...
Master?
A former Concert Master in Berlin Philharmony..
Kai Dun Sensei..
Eh.. K.. Kai Dun, that famous...
That's why I can't fail..
I have to win!
What's that...
then you shouldn't have made any Oke
from the start!
Idiot Kiyora!
Eto Kozo
Hai, Uraken fried rice!
Welcome!
Doumo!
(casual greeting)
Oh, Etu Sensei!
So you have finalled decided, haven't you?
(they call him "Etu", not Eto)
The student candidate for Maradonna Piano Competition!
Student Name : Noda Megumi
Instructor Name : Eto Kozo
Excuse me...
Senpai! You still haven't taken a bath?
Aaaah... You haven't eaten my rice balls either...
They're hard now..
Ohhhh! Don't only drink!
You should eat something that can fill up your stomach
Pudding
Hai, Senpai
Aaaaang...
Slurp!
Yosh!
Senpai, the hot bath is ready..
Let's become clean...
Nodame will shampoo your hair too
Gyabo!
Senpai.. so you were sane after all
By the next lesson, pick 10 pieces from here..
and read the score.
Megumi chan.. Tomorrow's competition...
I want Megumi-chan to come and listen
to m...my oboe
No...
I will play for you
Ack, Megumi chan! Tomorrow's competition..
Konnichiwa!
Megumi chan! Where are you going in such a hurry?
I'm going to "Super Hitoshi-kun"!
"Super Hitoshi-kun"?
It's Time Service from now!
(=time-limited sale)
Eels....
3 eels for only 300 yen!!
Eels for Chiaki Senpai...
He needs eel power!!
What's wrong with Chiaki-kun?
Chiaki Senpai almost drowned
in the bath tub yesterday
Senpai, are you alright?
GET UP!
Had I not peeked in,
I wonder what would have happened!
peeked???
Super Hitoshikun
Time Service!
3 eels for only 300 yen!!
(usually 1200 yen)
WAIT!
Nodame too!
Certainly
(I don't catch this one)
SOLD OUT
Thank you, thank you
I lost...
Megumi chan, are you OK?
Anago 500 yen
(=sea eel, not as good as usual eel)
Does anago also help for adding stamina?
Sorry.. I wish I had helped you earlier...
It's OK. Kuroki kun doesn't have to.
Because you're always doing your
best in the orchestra, already.
Eh?
Because for now Nodame ...
cannot relate to Chiaki-Senpai through music.
At least, if this can help build Senpai's
blood and muscle...
Megumi chan..
You like Chiaki-kun...
Ohh....anago is expensive..
Nodame Cantabile
Lesson 8
Please do not distribute this softsubs.
You can download it at
http://s-projects.org
All Japan Music Competition
Oboe Section
Megumi chan,
while I was looking at you,
your thoughts were full with love for Chiaki-kun..
Concentrate!
Return to my cool self!
It will be fine. For today's sake I've practiced so very hard..
Moreover I have made my reed perfect...
Ah!
Oh no! I put it in the water too long!
I need another reed..
The next person
Kuroki Yasunori-san
Reed...
Kuroki-san, hurry up!
Congratulation!
Congratulation, Miki-san!
How do you feel about
winning the 2nd place in Violin section?
2nd place
Kiyora?
Wait..
What's wrong with your neck?
I slept at a bad angle and got stiff neck
What?
Come...
Since I was born it's the first time I got stiff neck,
why it has to be today?? Why??
Oi! Isn't that Kai Dun?
Yes! The former Concert Master of Berlin Phil !
Sensei..
Congratulations
But I thought that
you would surely win 1st place..
Miki san.. How do you feel about winning 2nd place..
Congratulations, Kikuchi-kun!
How do you feel about winning the 1st place?
I feel as if I were in a dream
I want to thank to my parents and teachers
who have supported me until now
Kikuchi-kun
Congratulations, Kikuchi-kun
Tooru! Congratulations.
Who are you?
Are you Yuuko?
I am Yuuko!
So you're Izumi!
Ah.. Let's have the interview over there.
Kikuchi won first place...
Aizawa and Katayama .. as expected..
Heh? Kiyora only got 2nd place?
and surprisingly..
Kuroki-kun didn't win any place...
Ah, Kuroki kun?
(anago rice bowl)
I met him that time..
What did you do to Kuroki kun?
What did I do to him..?
I just consulted with him about my
love problems...
I didn't cheat on you..
If you are so worried about Nodame,
why don't you tie me up with chains?
Oi, Kiyora
Here, I bought it for you
I..don't have the face to see them
to see my Master.. nor Chiaki kun...
Though I'm a Concert Master, why ...
Though I've practised so hard and take
a break from the Oke's practice...
I don't really know what kind of person
your Master is..
But.. Chiaki..
is not someone who'll abandon a friend
just because of one failure..
Being his best friend, I'm sure I didn't make
a mistake in my judgement.
Oi, Kiyora! Don't cry!
Hush, hush! Here, drink it.
I'm an idiot!
That was not my real performance!
I want to go up on the stage once more!
Next time, certainly...
In Rising Star, certainly....
I will let you hear...
my real performance!
From today our rehearsal will begin again.
Now.. If I..
can make something great... that will be enough..
Violin! Stronger on the eighth bar!
Blend the two measures into one!
Stop!
All of you!
Do you think it will do playing like that?
Listen to the surrounding sounds too!
Just Violas.. From K..
No! It doens't synch! Once more!
What happened witth Chiaki kun?
Devil Chiaki..
is back!
And Violins!
Yes!
On K's 5th bar, don't cut the sound.
It's not Ta-TaTaTa-Ta.
It's Taaa-rarara-ra
Express it with richer emotion!
It's not only a matter of reading the score!..
You are not soloists,
so listen to the other sounds around you well!
Think by yourself about the meaning of
each phrase and play it.
Hai!
OK, once more!
Yep!
But Nodame-chan..
with your condition right now,
you can't be together with Chiaki.
I can't believe this!
5 hours of practice straight without taking any break!
that's Chiaki kun..
Is that Chiaki-kun?
Ahahaha... Japan is big after all...
Somehow, I feel I can understand
what Chiaki-kun wants to do.
It's becoming interesting now...
Just performing as usual is not enough...
We are not up to his expectation at all.
Kuroki kun.. again he's a Samurai..
Kimura-kun!
We sold 100 tickets for the public performance!
Eh! Already that many?
Wow! Sakuma Manabu!
When I told my friends in the same Association,
they were all insterested in it!
Ack, can you give me 50 more tickets?
Hai!
The advance tickets at Uraken-san
are also selling well, right?
That was thanks to this advertisement page!
Conductor - The Young Lord of Music
Chiaki Shinichi
What is that?
What's that? So fast already?
So they're done already!!
Done already????
"Mesmerizing Cellist"?
"The Orient's Bright Red Ruby"?
"The Young Lord of Music"!
It suits him very well!
"Japan's new-style youth perform together"
"An overnight dream for you."
Wh...what is this!!
Although it's an exaggerated copy,
there are some of you who
won in the Oshiuri Competition,
so it has quite an influence on it!
"The Aloof Oboe Kuroki Yasunori"
Okay? I'm counting on you!
Shall we practice now?
Yes, yes.. yes..let's practice..
Yes.. let's practice!
Let's practice! Practice!
Soon, it will be the opening time for the performance..
Here's the score.. and the baton..
before that, I'll smoke a cigarette first.
It's time.. Hurry up!
Ah!
What is it?
Dammit!
Woohh! You startled me!
Ss--ss-senpai, ww...what's wrong with you?
You look so pale.
Dream
That  dream again..
Recently I keep having  strange dreams...
Strange dreams?
Maybe it is related to airplanes...
I think you already knew
that I can't ride on a plane..
Ten years ago, when I returned from Prague,
my plane was forced to make an emergency landing
After that, I became phobic to airplanes
Though I've forgotten that for a while...
But lately.. I started to have nightmares very often
On top of that, they're not understandable at all
What was that I wonder...
Dammit!
Senpai, is airplane phobia incurable?
Since a long time ago, I took various treatments...
such as psychosomatic medicine, hypnotherapy...
But they couldn't hypnotyze me
It seems that my guard is strong
I also went to faith healers and spritualistic medium,
I already tried everything that I thought
I could rely on
Senpai, have you ever tried this?
I've seen it in movies
You're getting sleepy....
Silly!
That's called "fixed-gaze method", I've already
tried it using a pen-light.
So you've experienced it before..
But have you ever done it using a watch?
If such a mere thing works,
up to now...
Senpai? Please wake up!
What should I do
Wake up!
...I wouldn't have been suffering now
Mooshha!!!
You're getting sleepy...getting sleepy...
Green Caterpillar Bookshop
Understand Well
"Hypnotism Book"
What things are there in a phobia?
What is the cause of the phobia?
Experience in childhood
Listen to his story at those days, make his
insecurities and worries lighter.
I..
Am I still confused?
Do I really want to go abroad that much?
I'm quite angry at myself
for my own mental instability
I'll be alright
My confusion will certainly
be resolved in this Oke!
Everybody, please buy this!
They start to be sold now!
Mine-san, more of Chiaki-Sama please!
Sure!
Why do we have to do such a thing like this?!
We can't help it, can we? He said that if we help him
he'll give us free tickets to Rising Star!
Everybody!
Don't forget to buy my son's
Ryuutaroo T-Shirts too!
Okay?
They really did it, didn't they?!
You mean me? Me??
Hey, you...Aren't you the boy here?
Wow! He's the real thing!!
Let's do our best, Concert Master! Umm, no...
My...Bright Red Ruby!
Ah!
Could it be that that is Rising S...!!
Huh? What's wrong, Kiyora?
Eh? Are you going to come too, Mom?
Of course! It's my son's gala stage!
Because Saiko-chan kindly called me
I thought certainly the two of you were still dating...
Shinichi, is it true that you have a new girlfriend?
Huh?
You'll introduce her to me, won't you?
You don't have to come.
Do your best!
Please do your best, Shinichi.
I'm fine now
I have things I can do here too. (in Japan)
Really..
Nodame, wait.
Here, a ticket for tomorrow.
Oh, if ticket, Nodame already bought one.
Look!
As I thought, the cheapest seat
This is the best seat!
First Floor, 13th Row, Seat #24, 5000 yen
Wow!
I'll give it to you for free. Use this one!
Is this "Girlfriend Seat"?
No
Senpai, if your airplane phobia is cured,
what are you going to do?
Ha?
What are you going to do?
As I thought....
Anyway, listen....
to Ore-sama's music!
Laymen must not imitate this kind of thing...
Kikuchi-kun is so cool, isn't he?
The most wonderful is Miki Kiyora, isn't it?
Yes, she's a great newcomer!
By the way...this Chiaki Shinichi...who's he?
How annoying, nobody knows Chiaki-kun!
That's a matter of course
He has never even once taken part in any competition
and the only time he ever conducted was just
at the Academy's Periodical Public Performance.
Even for me, it will be my first time seeing
Chiaki-kun conduct.
That's why it will exciting for you
Oboe Concerto and Brahms No 1?
This Oboe player Kuroki-kun...
didn't he lose very badly at that competition?
Those guys, are they really better than us?
It will be a good sight to watch! Heeheehee....
Ah, Obasama!
Saiko-san
Thank you very much for inviting me in this occasion
Don't mention it. Let's go...
He came!
My Master came too
What should I do...if I fail again this time...I...
You'll be fine
because you're the woman I fell in love with...
Ryuu...
First it's the Oboe Concerto...
Do your best! Kurokin!
Kurokin???
Please warm up the audience for our sake
Kuroki Yasunori! Fight!!
Do your best!
Do your best, Kurokin!!
Chiaki-kun, thank you.
Eh?
Even after I failed tragically in the competition,
the trust you and everybody in the Oke
have put in me did not change even a little.
I will show that I'm worthy of your trust
BRAVO!!!
OK
Time to enjoy music!
Amazing! This Oke is really amazing!!
He's so cool! What's that Oboe??!!
Hashimoto-kun!
Moe-san!
Kaoru-san!
As expected, everybody came!
Their level is really high, isn't it?
I want to get in that Oke!
Me too!
Our A-Oke's Concert Master is cool too, isn't she?
Yes, Miki Kiyora!!
But whatever you said, it is...
Chiaki-Sama!!
Huh! Still too early!
Wait until you listen to their Brahms!!
K...Kai Dun!!
In addition, people from professional orchestras,
famous conductors and critics also came.
To do music, not only talent is needed, but
good luck is also definitely necessary!
Right now...
the highest peak of noble Art which was sleeping
in the golden island
is smiling at you!
Now, can you catch it?
Chiaki Shinichi!!
Sakuma-san!
It's time to return to our seats!
Stop that mouth!
Undoubtedly...
you're overflowing with talent
yet despite having such passion for music..
why are you always carrying despair on your shoulders?
OK
Let's sing!
From despair...
to HOPE!!
SING!!
Sing a song of GREAT JOY!!
BRR...
BRAVO!!!
Saiko!
Please excuse me.
Are you Chiaki-Senpai's mother?
As always, this country is dusty
Moreover, the air is not clean,
and the sky is narrow.
But..
it's not as uncomfortable as before...
Senpai!
What is it!
If you want food, there's pot-au-feu in the fridge!
(=beef in broth with veggies)
I know it, but it's not that.
Today I have a present for you
Ha?
It's as a reward for your sucessful performance
Why do I have to receive any reward from you!
Well, well...
Don'y say that...look at this.
Ah, are you going to give it to me?
Actually I also want it....
Before that, please look carefully!
Look carefully...
Your....
eyelids are so very heavy
you can't bear not closing your eyes anymore
I almost can't bear it anymore..
What was next?
You are now in a plane, from Prague heading to Japan
You are 11 year old
Shinichi said that he did not remember it all
but actually, at the time of that plane accident,
there was someone who died
Who is the person
sitting on your right?
A music-loving....
...elderly man.
He was holding Viera Sensei's
concert pamphlet in his hands.
He said to his wife sitting beside him:
"Let's go again next year."
over and over again..
But...
What's wrong with you?
Medicines, medicines...where is it? Medicines!
I couldn't take it!
Although I was the only one who knew it!
Next year, let's go to Prague again.
The two of us, together...
It's not Senpai's fault.
Senpai was just a kid...
Even so, it was certainly something that
no one could do anything about.
It's enough
Because God is calling me,
I have to go now.
When the timer goes off, please open your eyes.
When you open your eyes, you will forget
all that you have said or experienced
while your eyes were being closed.
It's alright now.
Now Senpai is not afraid of going by plane anymore.
This is again, a BETA version
It has not been thoroughly checked and timed
http://s-projects.org