BETA release of Ep 5
It's done!
Nodame, it's time to go to school!
Hai!
Don't use other people's internet
since morning
But Senpai's connection is using Hikari
(Hikari=fiber-optic)
and at the moment, they disconnected my phone line...
Again?!
Wah, it's pouring, isn't it?
Eh?
Senpai, let's share an umbrella!
No!
Don't say such thing....
No!!
Senpai!
It's been a week since S-Oke's first performance
Stop it!!
As usual Nodame is leeching on me
Then, the season for School Festival came
to Momogaoka Music Academy
Costume Orchestra?
There's still some opening in the Hall
for next week's School Festival,
let's participate!
Then...
Then why must it be Costume Orchestra?
Let me answer!!
I want to wear a dress!
A Princess dress!
I'll make a stuffed animal, stuffed animal...
I'll make a stuffed animal costume!
You may wear anything, you may make anything!!
Umm
I also want to participate
Sakura-chan!
S-Oke members going to do it?
I want to do it too!
Me too!! Me too!!
Alright!! Let's gather the members of S-Oke!
It'll be Costume Orchestra!
So why must it be Costume Orchestra, I asked you!!
Wow! Wow! Wow!!
Everybody, you're all in uplifting spirit, aren't you!!
That being the case,
let's all have a Gokon!
Master deserted S-Oke, didn't you?
Right, right!!
You're a betraying Master!
You'll only do sekuhara again, right?
(sekuhara=sexual harassment)
Who wants to go with you, Ero-JiiJii!!
(dirty old man)
Right,  right!!
Go home! Go home!
I see
I feel very hurt....
okay I'll go home...
Whoever wants to go to Gokon!!
Come here and grab this chest!!
Hah??
I'll GOOOOOOO!!!
Me too..
Eh!
Thinking again about it...
Is he really Stresemann?
Chiaki-Senpai!! Where are you???
He's real! I can tell when I watched him conduct!
Are you sure?
We just saw him conduct once,
and it was only a practice
I know it
otherwise who would have wanted to be his pupil?
That's the real Stresemann
Ok, everyone!
Everybody's here, right?
Let's go to Gokon!!
Go-Go-Gokon! Go-Go-Gokon!
But where's Chiaki-Sama?
Chiaki will come later
No need to worry!
"Elise"
(sounds meaningless to me, LOL)
It looks delicious, what is it?
Pasta in crema di scampi et camberi
(Pasta in cream with shrimps and prawns)
Your prided dish!!!
But Senpai, is it really OK not to go to Gokon?
Disobeying your Master
Hmph! If he's my master then teach me!!
Talking about it, the fact that Stresemann is in Japan...
Won't it be a topic for the news?
Ah, Senpai, your meal will get cold!
You eat first by yourself!
WHAT'S THIS??!!
Suki desu, suki desu, desu desu desu desu!
(I love you)
Senpai, you found it?
With this you can always meet me....
WHAT MEETING YOU?!!
Change it back like before!!
No!
I said change it back!!
No....
Iyaaan...(no)
What "Iyaaan"!!
"Goolegle" Search
Oh, it can't be...
Missing! Maestro Strezemann!!
After his concert in London last month,
the globally famous conductor has suddenly disappeared:
Franz Strezemann
The official says: "He's on vacation as usual".
They denied the rumor that Strezemann is
suffering dementia,
while they asked the Police for searching Strezemann
At the time being, concentrating on Europe,
they are chasing to solve the disappearance case.
What's that??
Wir haben die richtigen hauser
(He's in this school, no mistake, right?)
Dann holen wir mann, Oliver!
(Let's go get the man, Oliver!)
Jawohl!
(Yessir!!)
Chiaki !! Come a moment!
Nodame too!
Sexy Guide...
Shinjuku Club, or Roppongi Club, which is better?
Etchi!!
(lecherous)
What are you doing!!
Do you know what has happened because of you?
Chiaki! What are you mad about?
Let's go together!
Franz!!
Das war ein Zug vom Maestro!
(What a move from you, Maestro!)
Elise...
Back!!
Oliver!!
Jawohl!!
(Yessir!!)
Gut, ich habe gedacht
(Good, just when I thought..)
er ware friedlich geworden in letzter zeit ....
(that he had become more quiet recently....)
Ich habe ihn eingefangen!
(I captured him!)
Ok, bring ihn allein zum Wagen, verstanden ... sofort!
(OK tie him up and put him in the car, I'll go there now!)
Einen Moment mal, bitte!
(Wait a minute, please!)
Erlauben Sie mir die Frage, Wer sind Sie eigentlich?
(Allow me a question, who are you?)
I'm Maestro Stresemann's Secretary, cum Manager!
Manager?
Concerning Maestro,
if there's anything you want to sue him for,
you can contact here.
For example for cases related to women,
or for sexual harassments...
No, it's not that....
Why did he come to Japan?
How do you know that he is in this Academy?
By intuition
Intuition??
This is Streseman's best friend when
he was a University student
Minako Momodaira
wow, what a beautiful person...
She's this Academy's Rijichou
(=Chairwoman of the Board of Directors)
Maestro always looks at this photo
as if it is a treasure
That is the only reason why I
thought he could be here
Good bye, Milch!
Eventhough he's a dirty old man...
I learned a lot from him..
again I ...
lost my Master..
Stresemann Returned Home
Enforced Repatriation
Nodame Cantabile
Lesson 5
Forbidden Love!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi (43)
married a 65 year old lady
Hmm? Matchan got married??
Congratulations!
Thank you.
What attracts you to Chieko-san?
Well, there's no other thing to say
than because she's cute...
You're so cute....
Yes, she's cute
She's not that cute, isn't she?
This is trivial, isn't it?!
Cheer up, Chiaki-Sama!!
Would you like to have Nodame's
Mabo boiled vegetable noodle?
Aaaaaaang!!
But it's something that Jiijii will typically do...
So he came here just in order to
see his ex-girlfriend, right?
But I wonder if Milch had been able to
really meet Rijichou...
Talking about this, recently we have
not seen Rijichou for quite some time, don't you think so?
What a surprise....
That Rijichou and Stresemann-san used to be...
Dad, you know Rijichou?
Of course, because I have the shop here
since many many years ago
Originally she's an excellent pianist,
and moreover,
that beautiful face!
At that time, she was called the Jewel of The Orient!
Where's Rijichou now?
I heard from other teachers that
she's now on a long-term official trip
So they missed each other?
I feel sorry for Milch
Love is very often such a thing
Well, so what's the big deal! For such a
dirty old mentor to go away....
Sensei!!
Milch!
Nodame-chan!!
So you didn't go back to Germany?
I jumped off from...
the plane....
Aren't you hurt somewhere??
Of course it's a lie!!
Why...
does he want to see Rijichou that much?
Sure I got back here!
Chiaki!
This is your new assignment!
Please practice this piano piece
alone by yourself
Piano??
Rachmaninoff Piano Concerto No 2
This piece is for me to....
Oh, no....why do I have to practice
such a piano concerto piece now?
You are...
a student from the Piano Division.
What's wrong with playing the piano??
At the coming School Festival...
...together with A- Oke which I'm going to conduct,
perform this piano together with me!
A-Oke?
But for me I have S-Oke...
Do not each time oppose
what your MASTER told you! NAA!
As to your being S-Oke's Conductor....
Drop it off!!
Chiaki in A-Oke?
Dammit! That Jiijii!!
Chiaki too just the same!!
He simply accepted being in A-Oke!
So what's wrong
Chiaki-Sama playing Rachmaninoff!!
That will be cool!! And romantic!!
Surely he'll be a PRINCE!!
Is that a nosebleed boo?
(means very attractive/sexy one gets nosebleed))
Yes, boo boo!!!
Chiaki-sama is going to perform Rachmaninoff?
I want to see!!
Ahhhh frivolous stupid women!!
Certainly A-Oke can't beat us!!
Are we going to perform S-Oke?
Of course!
Then who'll be the Conductor?
That, ummm...
WAIT A MOMENT!!
Hee, if it is okay, I don't mind doing it for you..?
Who is he?
No idea..
Thank you...
Ah Chiaki-kun!
I heard about it. Yoroshiku ne!
Sure..
However, I wonder what is he thinking....Maestro
All of a sudden he seriously instructs A-Oke like that...
Excuse me...
Chiaki!
Please tell me the reason
Why do I have to play the piano...
Mina..
Huh??
Mina!!
Mina!!!!
Mina!!!!!!
Finally we can meet...
I wonder how many years since we last met?
You have become a big success
it is you, Mina...
you're beautiful as you always were
If it is for Mina's sake,
I can do anything...
You never change, Franz, don't you?
But it's true...
In the next School Festival,
that elite Orchestra....
This Stresemann!
and that pupil!!
for Mina's sake, will perform Rachmaninoff
Piano Concerto
Please definitely come to see it
That's my most beloved piece!!
You remember it!!
oh...I'm about to faint....
So in the end, that Jiijii just want to show off
in front of Rijichou....
and thus make me play the piano...
Wah! Madame de Polignac!!
Who's that?
The Rose of Versailles!
Are you going to make it yourself?
Yes! Because I want to wear a dress that suits me well!
Wow....
What about Nodame?
But  Nodame can't participate in the Oke...
even if I make it...
What about this!
What if Pianoka plays Pianika?
(it's a pun on Pianoka or Piano Division)
Pianika? / Yes!
In that case Nodame can participate too!!
Me too!!
I want to participate too!!
Me too!
Maki-chan!
Let's do it, let's do it!
Everybody, the new score is ready!!
Ooo, so we're going to play this piece!
Everybody!!
Let's practice from today!!
Sieg Zion!
Until very late? What should I do?..
What about dinner...?
Will Senpai be alright?
Dammit! What Master is he? Stop joking!!
Wouber bist du bose? Was ist los, Chiaki?
(Why are you angry? What's up, Chiaki?)
Huh?
It's you, isn't it? Stresemann's pupil..."Chiaki".
Ah! Milch!!
Is A-Oke's practice over yet?
Where's Chiaki-Senpai?
Chiaki?
Yes! Nodame is going to participate in
the School Festival too!
I want to inform Senpai about this....
Well.. I don't know where he is
I see...
Thank you
About Franz..
When he was a student, he played the piano
But at that time he always played truant
He was also involved in affairs of the heart
It seemed that the situation was pretty bad
not that he's changed now
But one day...
Franz..
You really have an amazing talent!
Yes, conducting...
You'd better be a Conductor!
She was the Madonna of the Academy at that time,
Minako Momodaira
Franz instantly fell in love with her
But at that time her talent in playing
the piano was already acknowledged
together with her beauty, she
became famous in society.
Chasing her presense high on the clouds,
Franz began to study conducting very hard
However, she was striked by an illness of the fingers
she quit piano, and returned to Japan
Good bye..
So those two persons' relationship is....
Had she not striked by that illness
had she continued playing the piano...
perhaps the two would have been lovers
but as a result,  now and back then...
they are no more than friends...
But Maestro still loves her until now..
No, it is not true. Now is different...
Then why did he come to Japan now?
It's to see Rijichou, isn't it?
At first I also thought as you did,
but I was wrong
She asked him to come here,
so he came as a mentor
Huh?
Isn't he teaching here? Teaching you!
For Franz to take a pupil, even if people beg him,
he has never agreed up to now, not even once!
If you're not serious learning,
please return Franz back to us!!
it's a big hindrance to our business!
How is it, our Academy?
There's a very interesting kid, right?
Is that why you asked me to come here?
I didn't expect that you would really come.
But I'm glad you came
And you found that kid too, didn't you?
Thanks to you,
though at first I only intended to have a
little fun and then go home,
now I cannot go home...
It seems that that kid cannot
leave Japan
Can't something be done for him?
For Franz to take a pupil, even if people beg him,
he has never agreed up to now, not even once!
There's yet another kid for whom....
something must be done.
Eh?
It's as if I were looking at myself in the past
making me feel very painful...
really a "komatta ko" ...
(a kid who causes someone to worry or to feel anxious about)
Those two.....
if something interesting happens between them
I'll be very happy!
Rachmaninoff Piano Concerto No 2
Rachmaninoff who overcame a deep scar of the heart
composed this first Piano Concerto of his.
This great music, beginning in depressed mood,
then overcoming it,
in the end thoroughly
singing forth the joy of living
There she is!!
Nodame, what are you doing?
S-Oke's parctice is waiting for you!!
Wait a minute...Chiaki Senpai!!
Let's go!
Oh...S-Oke...
I wonder how it is going....
Nodame..
Is she also waiting for dinner today?
I'm starving...
Ha, maybe she's crying...
Chiaki Senpai!
Nodame...
I missed you!!
So you're still at school
Yes!
Oh Senpai...
there's a sad news...
Because from now on Nodame will be busy for a while
preparing for the School Festival with Mine-kun and the others...
I think I have to come home late
Therefore though you'll feel lonely,
please have dinner by yourself for a while.
Hmm....I am sorry!
What sad news!
Oh, it hurts, it hurts...
You're Nodame and yet you
act rejecting me, huh?
That was MY line to say!!
Don't come to my house anymore!!
Senpai....
Stop!!
Everybody
please take a little break.
Impressive....
It's the first time I heard him play,
but as expected, Chiaki is very good!
Chiaki!!
What's that, the way you played!!
Huh?
This is the place where it should be the most
passionate!
Use your whole body more
to express music!!
But I'm not such a type of person.....
Chiaki!
You don't know yourself at all!
To enchant the audience,
is also an important study!!
Enchant?
Play it more beautifully!
More romantically!
More painfully!!
More sexily!
for instance,
as if you were in agony..
Why do I have to twist and turn to play Rachmaninoff?
It's not twist and turn!
I am saying for you to immerse more into the music!!
Immerse?
You studied piano for four years in this Academy
show your accumulative ability all those while!
and the one conducting will be me!
This is a hard-to-obtain
and valuable experience, and also, study.
I won't forgive...
mediocrity
Okay, one more time
No 9, from the beginning
Hai
Yes it is a wonderful experience
As a performer, to perform together with Stresemann...
I also don't like mediocrity
It's finished!!
Now the cloth materials...
What's Nodame-chan making?
She said it's the paper patterns for a stuffed animal
Wow..
But to cling to such a thing to that extent...
But you too, Masumi-chan!
Then what costume will Ryuu-chan be wearing?
Actually...
A fan of the Concert Master of S-Oke, or me,
is going to design for my costume
Ryuu-chan's fan?
Yes!!
Your father?
No! Why my father?
Mine-san!!
Look, that's my fan!!
Seriously?
Really?
Mine-san! The designs are done!
Please choose the one you like!
Thank you!!
Not a human being?
As expected, your fan, right?
Well, whatever will be fine
since it's done already!!
and it is the last anyway,
so let's just do it,
the striking way!
Eh, the last?
Ryuu-chan is a repeat student, so it's OK
but we fourth year students, we must think seriously
about what to do after graduation and stuff
With this Oke, it's a farewell performance!
Really?
Yes..
It's a pity that Chiaki won't be here as well
In use by S-Ok !
Do not take a peek inside!!
As I thought, you are worried....about S-Oke
Nope...not particularly
What about giving them some advice?
Surely they miss you, Chiaki, don't they?
Alright! We can't lose to A-Oke!!
Overthrow A-Oke!! Overthrow Chiaki!!
They're all livening up, aren't they?
School Festival's Special Performance
A Orchestra
World Maestro  Stresemann conducting
Rachmaninoff Piano Concerto No 2
Hello, it's Momogaoka Music Academy
Huh? Chiaki Shinichi?
Yes, yes, he will perform!
At School Festival!
Yes, with Stresemann!
Yes, this time he will really perform!
What's happening, what's this!
Hello, this is Momogaoka Music Academy!
Really!!
He's featured, he's featured! Chiaki-kun!
Yes, it's true! Wow, for a student to be featured
in "Classic Life"! Wonderful!
Yes, wonderful!!!!
Saiko, look, look!
Your ex-"husband"
Eh?
Araaa! Pianist Chiaki Masayuki's son,
and Stresemann's sole pupil...
Tagaya-san, don't you regret it now?
Ne...this reporter of "Classic Life"
must be a woman, don'y you think??
[Classic Life Editor Division ]
AH CHOOOOOOO!!!!
Ah, excuse me...
It's OK
Therefore, I am wondering if Sakuma-san
also has the time
Yes! The 13th of this month
We certainly wish Sakuma-san will
come and see it
"Sakuma Manabu" Music Critic
"Piano Division Beauty Girl Cafe"
Those! They're not the parents, are they?
They're S-Oke!
S-Orchestra at 5:00 PM at Main hall
The Legendary Stage
Certainly don't see us alone!
Haaaaa??? Wait!!
What are those attires!!
What happened with your costumes?
The costumes are not good at all
so I changed my mind!!
Haaaaaî??
My costume was good, Amuro!!
(Amuro from Gundam)
Ours were good too, dressing up as maids....
Just because you don't like your own costume,
why must we change our costumes as well?!
Be quiet!!
My goal with the Costume Oke is
to have a cool-looking Oke!!
Otherwise, how could we possibly
beat that Chiaki??
Well, apart from whether this is cool or not,
isn't it quite good, this attire?
Yes, it stands out too!
Yes, we just borrowed it from our parent, so
it doesn't cost anything
See?? Right?? This is good, right??
Wait a minute!!
Then what about me?
I'll be the only one wearing a dress??
It's fine for Masumi-chan to wear it as it is
Moreover, you have made it yourself!
It really suits you very well!
Really?
Ummm..
May I wear it as it is?
Who are you??
I'm Nodame
What is that costume?
It's a mongoose!
I don't get it! Why a mongoose??
Ah, and this is "Habu"!
"Habu"!! Heee...
Enchant....
sexily..
as if in agony..
I don't understand..
What is it that Maestro wants me to do?
S Orchestra [The Legendary Stage]
at Main Hall 5:00 PM
Program: Not Fixed!
S-Oke without Stresemann nor me...
Those people, what are they planning to perform?
[ Program: Not Fixed!]
Pianika?
Why is a pianika tuning?
So cute!!
Nodame??
Yes it's Nodame!
Rhapsody In Blue
Big Band ala Japonaise?
Oi, Oi!!
You're all cool, aren't you?
The song arrangement is good!
The pianika also divide the parts very well
The arts is played in small details
Ah!! That is...
....to enchant....
I got it, Mine!
Though it looks a little stupid,
that's your feature show-off , guys!
S-Oke
you showed us quite a good thing...
Me too, it's good enough if I have trust in myself,
and perform just as my own self
Sorry, Mine!
But the closing/main performance is by Ore-Sama!!
A-Oke Concert will start soon!
What are they doing, making a big commotion like this
It's because they can see Stresemann live!
and on top of that, they can see Chiaki-kun!
Stresemann's pupil, isn't he?
But he's still a student, right?
Moreover, he has no experience in Piano Contests either.
Is he really good?
Well, I don't know yet about his piano-playing ability
But they'll play Sakuma-san's favorite
Rachmaninoff piece
Well, yes ...
However,
I'm not going to write anything!
for a mere University School Festival.
Pianist:
Chiaki Shinichi
Did Chiaki Senpai come to see us earlier?
Milch?
Although it's quite an unusual Gershwin,
it's very good!
Very entertaining!
Really?
Yes!
Nodame-chan.
Yes?
What do Nodame-chan want to be in the future?
Heeeh?? Suddenly giving me a quiz??
No, it's not a quiz!
It's about your future hope...
My hope is..
...to be a kindergarten teacher.
Ho!
But recently....
because I also hope to be Chiaki Senpai's wife...
that's why it's my # 1 dream to be a kindergarten
teacher while being Chiaki Senpai's wife
Yaaaaa, I said it!!
oh I feel shy, I feel shy!!!
Oh, Chiaki?
However, Nodame-chan,
just like you are now....
you can't be together with Chiaki.
You can't be together with him.
Oh, it's time now.
I'm indebted to you, Nodame-chan
This is...
a present for you
Milch?
That's quite a nice style
What about making your hair stand up a bit?
And perhaps it's better to take off that tie...
I'll say it in advance,
but I'm going to perform the way I am
Such a thing....it's a matter of course!
Huh?
You told me to show sexiness,
to show agony.....
Those things...they don't matter anymore now
What's important is...
how seriously you and the music piece
face each other...
That will be enough.
Now...
me too...
I must show my beloved Mina my good point...
because after this, I will be apart from her
and Japan for quite a while...
Okay, shall we go now?
It's the time for enjoyable music!
Chiaki Shinichi, ne?
Well, I admit he's good-looking.
but if he's bad at it, it'll be very laughable
Sakuma-san, you're still saying it again?
Oh!
Masumi-chan?
Where's Nodame??
Nodame!!
What are you doing???
Chiaki-Sama's Concerto has started!
Oh! But Nodame's still in this stuffed animal ...
It's OK, come quick!!
And your place is on standing row, OK, got it??
I don't like the fact....
that it will be over soon...
More....
I still have things I wanted him to teach me...
I want to listen more..
more, more..
I wanted to feel more...
of this person's...
music.
CHIAKI!!
Chiaki..
please take that cigarette for me
Take it by yourself
I told you it's farewell...
Is that an atittude to show to your Master?
You're already old...
Don't overdo it on alcohol, cigarettes, and women...
Please live long...
Without alcohol, cigarettes, and women...
I will die.
Jiijii...
Pianist:
Chiaki Shinichi
Sakuma-san!!
I understand how you feel,
but we have to leave.
Ne..
Concerning my serial article for this month..
my draft for "Dream Color Classics"....
is it still possible to change it with another one?
Nodame too..
Stresemann is going to go home, isn't he?
I wonder if this time is really the end!
For S-Oke!
Well, from tomorrow we'll have to start
working life, anyway.
What about you, Kiyora?
Are you going to study abroad again?
Umm...I'm still thinking about various things..
Just as you are now...
You can't be together with Chiaki!
Piano...piano...
I must play the piano!!
Dokyaaaa!!!!
The German/Italian in this BETA version by Airhead
DOKYAAA!!!
Bye bye for now!
}}