BETA Version!
Congratulations for being promoted to be
the official conductor of S-Oke!
Alright, let's drink a toast!
Would whiskey and water be fine?
Aren't you happy?
S-Oke belongs to you now.
I'm not happy!
What's he thinking, that Jiijii!
Is he serious in withdrawing himself?
I'm with A-Oke, you're with S-Oke
In next week's periodical public performance.
we'll have a DUEL!
The A-Oke Stresemann is going to conduct
versus that S-Oke?
That is no match at all...
It's not the time to celebrate
Can I really bring that Oke together?
Okay, study...study....
I'll think of it as a good chance
However excellent they are, there are a lot of
conductors who have no chance to conduct
Even if it's such a terrible OK,
I'm Streseman's substitute
I'll show that I can make it perform
Ah, Chiaki!
What are those you're wearing?
We made these!
S-Oke T-shirt!
We have one for Chiaki-Sama too!
For the Conductor, look!
It also has it at the back!
Wear it! Wear it! Wear it! Wear it!
Nodame! What are you doing?
It's something for Chiaki Senpai
But why are you doing it at school?
Beacuse I want to deliver it when it's still warm....
"beloved-wife lunch box"
What "beloved wife"?
He doesn't even pay any attention to you!
But he does!
Like lending me his bath, and cooking for me...
Chiaki Senpai only thinks of you as
a discarded dog he picked up
A dog?
Hey, it's burning....
He does other things to for me!
It's burning!
For example..?
For example....
Don't make a mistake in just two measures!
Gyabo!
Ouch!
Those things....and
Gyabo!
......these things?
Could it be that Nodame is lower than a dog?
Stop! Stop!
What are you all doing? Such a strange pose!
Eh? It's cool, isn't it?
I suggested what about putting a bit of Rock into it,
and we practiced it together already, right?
This way of playing like Jimihen, very cool, right?
(Jimihen=Jimmy Hendrix)
This is it, right?
We should also show the Oke, right?
Stop joking around!
Before doing such performance, play properly first!
Why?
In the world of music,
what's wrong with expressing it using the whole body?
Express it using sounds! Using sounds!
Moreover for Beethoven No 7, different from
"Pastoral"  or "Eroica"
it has no title,
so don't create an imaginary story by your own!
But Number 7 is too grand...or difficult to cling to
If we don't do it this much, it's boring!
Huh? Boring?
Yes, that's true...
Even if we do it the usual way,
we won't be able to beat A-Oke
Right? Everybody, let's have an adventure!
A Rock Orchestra! This is the best!
Everybody, let's do something with the horns too!
Aren't we overdoing it a bit?
We have no time left!
Don't talk back for each single thing!
I'm the one hearing the whole sound!
Play the music as I demand!
Mine!
You stand on my way more than this,
and I'll sack you from the Concert Master!
Eeek!
Cello!
Your fourth measure pitch is bad!
Viola!
Only one bow is different!
Oboe, clarinet!
Are you snake charmers? I'll strangle you to death!
Before grumbling this and that like some big things,
play the sounds well first!
Play it according to the score! Accurately!
Absolutely according to the wish of the composer!
Chiaki-Sama...
Just when I thought he had become agreeable...
Anyway,
by next week, each of you
practice it according to the score before coming here
One more week until the periodical
public performance
I have to do something with it....
It seems that they practiced again today....that S-Oke
With Stresemann quitting from them,
is there any meaning for that Oke to exist, huh?
No meaning!
Shall we just disband them?
Then we'll have more time in the periodical concert too.
But....S-Oke will have Chiaki-kun conducting it, right?
It seems interesting, I'd like to see it
Ahhh...Tanioka Sensei...come on!
They'll just be an embarassment to the school
Let Stresemann's A-Oke overthrow them,
then d-i-s-b-a-n-d them!
Oh let's do so, let's do so!
Uraken fried rice is delicious!
If you like...
we started to have a new menu....
We started to serve "Overthrow A-Oke Noodle"
Dammit!
They're only doing unimportant things...
Why can't they play according to the score accurately?
A simple thing like that?
What is it?
Big operation of love food delivery!
Let's make hotpot, the two of us!
Huh?
My family sent me this nabe ingredients set
I have no free time
I'm studying the music piece right now
Eeek!
Chiaki Senpai, is the practice not going on well?
No such thing!
A conductor also fights with stamina,
so you need to eat properly
Alright, it's perfect!
What's perfect?!
Wasn't it me who did all these things?
Well, well....
Hmm.....
Senpai's room is very nice but I feel something's lacking
Huh?
My philosophy is not to put too many things in my room
That's it!
Uhhh....
This is it! Kotatsu!
For nabe, kotatsu is the best!
Don't bring in such a thing here!
Eh, why shouldn't I?
Of course! I hate this kind of futon-covered dull-looking table!
Oh why?
There is nothing that feels nicer in the world than this thing
Senpai must have used it too before, haven't you?
Actually, since I was born I have never used a kotatsu...
When I was big enough to understand things,
it was already a life in Europe
Returning to Japan, my mother's family
lives in a western house
and there is no tatami room
Hmm, perfect!
May I put the meat in now?
Yes
Put a lot in it....a lot....
So this is kotatsu...
So warm....
Senpai, it is done
OK
I'll serve you...because I'm your wife...
Huh?
Mushroom....and meatball...
...and scallops...
Senpai?
Chiaki Senpai....did you fall asleep?
Did you really fall asleep?
Chance!
Oh no!
I ate too much, so unconsciously I....
I still have to correct the checkmarks on the score...
Oh well, I'll leave it alone for now
Recently I'm lacking of sleep anyway
I'll do the nabe clean up...
and the conducting study...
after I sleep some more first
Kotatsu,
appearing in Muromachi Period,
is a heater appliance for winter which continues
to be loved by the Japanese until now
But....
this thing which seems to be a
calm, non-offensive and peaceful emblem...
later...
is going make me suffer.
Nodame Cantabile
Lesson 4
Senpai, good day!
Good day? Now....
2:35 PM
Already day time!
lusterless spiky hair....how nice, how nice!
Wait a minute!
Why are you wearing pajamas in my house?
Dokii!
And what's that TV? Why is it on the sofa?
Because the TV in your house was put on the floor,
and the kotatsu is tall, so it's hard to watch....
Then watch TV in your own house!
But in Nodame's house there's no kotatsu now!
Then bring it back home,
don't start living here!
Well, well, well, I'll really go home later
Ah nabe! There are still a lot of ingredients left,
let's cook nabe again!
Why nabe again...
Here, beer for you!
Senpai was in the kotatsu for a long time,
you must be thirsty, right?
I bought it at the konbini earlier
Her head works after all
....catches the music the conductor is trying
to express as if a radar...ra...ra....??
....radar, and instantly adopts the performance....
...adapts???....adopts...??? Hmm??
Wow, today's a holiday but unexpectedly you're so
serious at it, aren't you?
A-Oke's Concert Mistress!
"Orchestra For Beginners"
So you're reading "Orchestra For Beginners"
So what?
Are you insulting me?
"A Concert Master....
is the First Violin player who leads the Oke,
decides the bowing,
and plays the solo recital part if any."
"He gives signs using his eyes or body movement
concerning the performance's detailed timing
which cannot be synchronized by just
the baton of the Conductor"
"Furthermore, an excellent Concert Master
catches the music the conductor is trying
to express as if a radar,
and instantly adopts the performance."
Perfect! Not missing even a word!
Because I also seriously read it when I was
selected as the Concert Mistress for the first time
I miss those days
Well, it was a long long time ago.
Well, do your best!
As I thought, you're insulting me!
"radar"
Chiaki's radar?
Kotatsu...it's hard to get out of it...
I shouldn't have.....
What's this???
Exactly like Nodame's room!
NODAME!!!
So she's gone home
Yosh!
First, I must clean up this place
and have some meal
This is no joke!
What is it?
Why are you sleeping in my bed?
I'll have the Police kick you out!
Nodame wants to sleep in a bed,
it's been a long time
Your bed is just buried under a mountain of garbage
Dig it out!
You have a visitor!
WHO IS IT??
It's home express delivery!
Dammit!
Lunch set!
Good evening!
Sorry to make you wait!
Here's your lunch set!
Here, I brought this food for you
This Chiaki-Sama's room!
Wow, wonderful!
Ah, let's invite Nodame too!
Don't do unnecessary thing!
An Mine-kun and Masumi-chan!
Welcome!
Heh?
Why are you here????
Why? Why? And in pajamas too!
Chiaki, are you two living together?
Yosh! I will really kill you today!
You, tatami room ghost!
Wow! Kotatsu! I miss it! Wow! Nice kotatsu!
Oi!
What do you come here for?
What about your practice?
He said he wanted to be near you to support you...
As fas as a Concert master can do,
he seems to think about various things too.
Delicious!
Hauuuuuuunn!
What's that? New menu?
It's Mabo Beancurd
What is it?
Nope
Looking for your radar.....
Huh?
Is there anything I can help?
Chiaki-Sama
aaaaaaaaaaang!
Be quiet!
OK, if there's anything I can help, tell me
Tis...tis....tissue, tissue, tissue tissue, tissue!
There is, there is, there is, there is, there is!
OK, here it is!
Nodame!
Wah, so smelly!
It'll get trapped under here!
Oh I want to use the toilet now!
Please throw away my part of poo too!
Ah, take an orange for me please!
No! Go take it yourself!
It's on your way back here, on your way!
Ah! I'm relieved!
Ha?
You're lying!
I feel good now!
Why does it come to this?
Buy more osake!
Nodame, buy some more snacks!
No, I don't want to! It's cold outside!
Mine-kun, you go to buy them.
I can't go now, because a cat is
sleeping on my feet
Is there a cat here?
Eh? There's no cat here!
It stinks !!!!
That must be it!
Now I finally got it
The root of all these crimes is this kotatsu!
Along with this kotatsu, I allow Nodame
to impose on me
with these warmth and futon
the senses of body and the mind are made blunt
and human being is made corrupt
Oi!
I give you this money
you all go to konbini!
(10.000 yen is big money)
"Dried Squid" Symphony No 1!
Let's eat dried squid!
Let's have calcium intake!
It's now to do it!
It's now that I must remove this disgusting thing
from my house!
"Big-size Garbage"
With this, they certainly will move to Nodame's room
with that kotatsu along!
Huh?
Tadaima!
(we come home)
It's good that we went out bringing the key with us, isn't it?
That's true!
I bought Senpai's favorite snack!
Kotatsu, kotatsu! Let's bring it in!
Say 1, 2, 3...Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho!
"...you stink like squid..."
It's not the kotatsu!
"...I stink like squid..."
The cause is these people!
"Everybody stinks like squid..."
Ah! What's wrong with you, Senpai?
I ask you please...
LET ME STUDY!!!!!
"The 28th Periodical Public Performance"
STRESEMANN conducting A-Orchestra
S-Orchestra
Conductor: Chiaki Shinichi
Music: Beethoven Symphony No 7
Eh?
Stop! Stop!
And now what was it you don't like?
Horn? Oboe?
It's YOU! Concert Master!
Why did you keep looking at me like that?
Wh...why? I'm looking at Chiaki's radar....
Look at the score!
But what about the radar....
I'll sack you from being the Concert Master, Mine!
Oh, please don't do that! Oh!
And then you two, horns!
Hai!
You don't sync at all! Your pitch is too big!
You cellos! the sound's too weak!
Then all of you!
The balance is sloppy!
All of you, did you really come here after practicing?
We practiced...before coming here, right?
Hai, today's practice stops here!
Everybody please practice what I taught you today!
Please wait a moment
We just practiced only for forty minutes....
It's alright, it's alright!
Everybody's is excellent, no need to worry!
But...
we need some more intructions....
there's no time left until the public performance...
I have no time left either!
The time has already been reserved!
Kaaa!
Hai....
If you understand, good!
Sensei!
W--w--wait a minute!
Please let me conduct A-Oke!
Who are you?
I'm Ookouchi, the Number 2
in this Academy's Conducting Division!
Ookouchi?
You let Chiaki conduct S-Oke, didn't you?
Rather than letting a student from the Piano Division
to do it, please give me a chance too.
What about my repayment?
Huh?
When one asks for a favor,
it's the Japanese common sense to give something as a gift!
Under the table!
Un---under the table?
To a person who doesn't even know such a thing,
to be my substitute is too presumptious!
You can just stand in front of the mirror,
and wave a chopstick around, huh?
Wow, wonderful!
But Senpai's photo is too small!
Don't! Stop!
You may not enter!
Wh...why???
Just a little peek from the back should be alright!
No! Chiaki Senpai told me not to let anyone enter!
CHIAKI??
What is he? Acting like a Sensei, what right does he
have to say such a thing?
Are you a spy from A-Oke?
I....I...I'm not a spy!
All spies say so!
I'm not someone from A-Oke!
I'm the Number 2 in this Academy's
Conductiong Division, Ookou...OUCH!
Wait, Shizuka-chan!
I can't stand it anymore!
No, Shizuka-chan, do not run away from this!
Even if you got scolded by Chiaki-Sama....
Stupid Chiaki!
Mine-kun, wait! Don't run away!
What will become of it if the Concert
Master's also running away?
Today's just until here, he said!
Dammit! That Chiaki! He's a devil!
Hey...
let's boycott him, everybody!
Shall we?
That Chiaki!
He's hated by the Oke!
Just whan I thought how amazing he must be,
because Stresemann passed him the Oke
This is a failure as a Conductor!
Failure?
To be a Conductor, first thing is Human Character!
Chiaki Shinichi! He's not worthy of it!
Go ahead! Go ahead!
I'm looking forward to the periodical performance!!
Human Character?
How envious....your Oke seems to be going on well...
is S-Oke that terrible?
Yes, it sounds very terrible, terrible!
Ryuu-chan, everybody's not serious about boycotting, right?
Why should I know!
I'm really mad at him too!
Well, do your very best!
Just that?
Only one short comment?
What a cold woman!
Okay, just one more short comment!
They say that when the conductor is in trouble,
it's the Concert Master's job to support him
That's what I think too
You said you wanted to talk, so what is it, Mine?
Let's practice!
Haaaa?
Weren't you up to your limit earlier?
However hard we practice,
none of us can play the kind of performance
Chiaki-Sama can be satisfied with
Even so, let's do it!
It is our first chance to appear in an Oke!
I understand your feelings of anger
But all of us...S-Oke's Conductor is Chiaki!
Let's practice according to what Chiaki said
Let's try to come closer to the music Chiaki
wishes to express!
Second violin...always from here...
Umm.....
How on earth you did get in here?
You seem to forget your meal, so I made these for you...
If you don't eat, you might fall ill
How many did you make?
Nodame never fails when it comes to making rice balls!
Fails? Normally people don't fail when making rice balls!
Oh! Senpai! Shall we watch video while eating?
I brought a movie which I like a lot with me here!
Huh? A movie?
Senpai seems to be stuffed up, it will be good for a change.
What is it, suddenly...
Could it be.....there'll be a hint for the Oke in the movie?
"Puri Gorota"
Wahhh...it starts! It starts!
Do you know Puri Gorota?
How would I know!
It's a complicated story about Gorota,
an elementary school kid
who's always just lying around lazily,
whenever he's in trouble,
he will depend on the magic power of Puririn,
a fairy from outer space
It's simple! Not complicated!
Then, this time, using Puririn's magic, they are
setting out for a trip into outer space
but as the case goes, it ends up with Kazuo-kun
the Big Bully and his gang tagging along!
"Konnichiwa, Goropi-kun!"
"Hey don't forget us!"
"Wonderful! It's my first time in outer space!"
Gorota, have the previous space candy I gave
you every hour, otherwise you'll die!
In such situation, because of Kazuo-kun,
the space ship got damaged
"It's your fault, how are you going to fix it?"
"But it's Kazuo-kun yourself who caused this!"
"Gorota, you fix it by yourself, OK?"
"While he's fixing it, let's play baseball!"
"I'll be the pitcher!"
"Then I'll be the batter, OK?"
"What shall we do? Kazuo-kun will get blown away!
We must save him!"
"But if we flop, we'll become the
outer space's seaweed ourselves!"
"Mummy gatherers will become mummies themselves?"
"If he's gone, you won't be bullied anymore!"
"But.... Kazuo-kun gave me the space candy earlier!"
"Hadn't Kazuo-kun advised me at that time..."
"I would have died!"
"Gorota!"
"I'm so sorry for what I have done to you until now"
"It's alright, Kazuo-kun!"
"I understand something after going to outer space"
"Human beings cannot live alone"
"Human beings cannot live without love and friendship"
waaaah....I'll cry...it's so touching!!
Senpai, you understand Kazuo's feeling, don't you?
Because you two are similar!
What are similar!
STOP JOKING AROUND!!!
Gyabo!
See? You're being Kazuo....
I'll KILL you!
You're being Kazuo again....
What is it you want to say??!!
GYABOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!
580.000 Yen
(a lot of money!!)
What? The office won't pay the Club's bill?
Connect me with the Editor Chief....
Oh! Look, there's a poster here!
Who has made such a striking poster?
I'm a bit overexposed!
Isn't he the boy who came here previously?
What a good-looking guy, isn't he?
Wonderful!
Chiaki-kun?
He's so cool!
Chiaki!!!
Get away!
Won't you tell me the truth now?
Maestro!
The truth?
A great Conductor like you, why did you
come to a Music Academy in Japan?
Isn't there another reason behind it?
"Elise"
"Calling"
Why am I Kazuo?
Three more days until the periodical performance...
This way it'll be impossible to accomplish it in time
Stop, stop!
I'm sorry for having been in your way until now
Eh?
We all practiced before coming here!
I see.
OK let's begin from the beginning.
Amazing!
They do it well!
The sound that was like garbage.....
Even the cellos too...
...and the horns...
Today everybody plays so well...
According to my instructions,
according to the score...
But...
what's this?
the sound is little by little...
inexplicably shifting off...
All of them....
are not looking at my conducting!
I feel sick!
"It's your fault, how are you going to fix it?"
Chiaki-sama!
Huh? What's wrong?
Chiaki!!
Chiaki-Sama!
Are you alright? What's wrong?
Ah...
it's space candy....
Oh, Chiaki Senpai!
Chiaki-Sama! You woke up?
Oh right...I was.....
I'm fine
I just got a little sick by the sound
Really sorry!
We...decided to play according to the score..
We were looking earneslt at the score....
..that we forgot to look at your conducting.
They..... really want to meet your demand...
Anyway....take a rest today
OK?
We'll practice by our own
About today's practice,
apart from not looking at the conducting,
everybody really played very well...
but something is different...
Was that the No 7 which I demanded them to play?
You.....
You remember No 7 by heart?
Well, because I listened to its performance everyday
This is a good musical piece, isn't it?
Ikazuchi!!
(=lightning)
Dokyun!!
So sloppily!
thunderbolt
heavy rain, dorobou, dorobou, dorobou, doroboooooooou!
(dorobou=thief)
What song is this??
As usual, though she plays it messily...
Amazing!
It's the same with that time!
It gushes up...
frolics about....
presses near....
They have pure....
uncalculating....
personality.
Ah!
I got it!
They are all....
Nodame!
I got it why Maestro chose them!
I got it why Mine was chosen as the Concert Master!
I got it why for S-Oke it's a musical piece without a title!
Haaaa???
You'll change the entire performance?
Sorry, but please forget whatever we did up to now!
Forget everything??
But the public performance is tomorrow!
We'll do it over again within today
How could we possibly do it....
Just when we finally can get it right....
Sorry...
because of me you have to change around...
but it will become better still...
I'm asking you....
please, Concert Master
Chiaki is lowering his head asking me a favor??
No, he's not lowering his head
ALRIGHT!
Well, I don't really get it, but okay let's do it
all over again!!
YESSSSS!
It can't be!
Seriously??
About the piece's interpretation,
previously I told you to express by only using sounds
but now, I think it's also nice to have a theme
or similar thing for the piece
therefore...that idea the Concert Master wanted to do
at the beginning...
Is it okay to do it like Rock?
Although as expected it looks foolish....
As to how all of you can
show your power,
...your uplifting spirit,
your personalities,
I also have thought about it.
Shall we try it?
Okay, let's start from the beginning!
Lift the tension higher!
Bravo!!
Everybody! It's well done!
As expected, Stresemann is amazing!
Kiyora!
Hai
Come!
You brought them very well to this extent
Your hand...
Everybody!
At tomorrow's periodical performance,
let's make that S-Oke
be an old version!
(make it history, disband)
Momogaoka Music Academy
28th Periodical Public Performance
A Orchestra Conductor: Stresemann
S Orchestra Conductor: Chiaki Shinichi
As expected, Stresemann is popular
Oi!
All calm down!
Oh...oh... ohh...
How could we calm down?!
For most of us, this is our FIRST time in an Oke!
If...if....if we end up embarrassing Chiaki-
Samaaaaaaaaaaaaaa...
It's also my first time
Eh?
Don't bother with things like A-Oke..
or having a duel.
Chiaki!
Our S-Oke's Hatsu Butai!
(First Stage/Performance)
Chiaki!
Our S-Oke's Hatsu Butai!
(First Stage/Performance)
Let's enjoy it!!
So Chiaki-kun's S-Oke performs first?
What's that, wearing such clothes?
Although it's the opening before A-Oke's performance,
don't embarrass us too much, alright?
The Conductor's a student?
Chiaki-Sama......soooo cool!!
Hahaha, that Concert Master's so "hade"!
(=conspicuous, garish, striking)
That kid, has he been playing that well?
It's not only the Concert Master
Are they really underachievers?
In that case, the one who changed them is...
Eto Sensei....that conducting kid, who is he?
Hmh....
Oi! Are you going to do that??
OK, OK!
If you're going to do it,
do it HERE NOW!
Incredible!!!!!!
So cooooool!!
With this, a fair evaluation has disappeared...
but....
it's fun!!
BRAVO!
Is it my imagination? Isn't it mixed with laughters?
It's not an imagination!
That Chiaki! Acting so cool, huh?!
Such a vulgar performance!
That's a childish trick!
Chiaki!!
Hey you, you!
Maestro!
Wow! Ookouchi!
You said you wanted to conduct, didn't you?
Yes!
Wow!
For the next live performance, be my substitute, please!
Huh?
Your clothes is very "dasai"
(bad-taste)
I'll give you my jacket!
I got a stomachache
I'm going home! Bye-bye!
CHEERS!
Yaaa.....we easily overthrew A-Oke!
That's just their Conductor doing a
self-destructive act!
Don't overdo it!
Yes, that's true!
It's good that our Conductor is Chiaki-Senpai, isn't it?
We practiced like Spartans, didn't we?
For me to practice as hard as that, perhaps
it was since practicing for the university entrance exam!
Me too! I thought I was very good,
so I became very serious at it.
Yes, because we felt upset
when he said we're not good!
That's true!
As expected, someone who has a high
aspiration is really something!
We should work harder....
Hey...hey...do you think S-Oke will continue to exist?
Let's keep S-Oke to continue to exist, shall we?
No objection!
Yaaa....I was surprised!
Really as expected....Chiaki-kun!
Moreover, he seems to have a good influence
on other students!
Yes, such as on that Concert Master....Mine-kun!
We start to serve:
"S-Oke Continue To Exist" set menu
Senpai!
Chiaki Senpai...
are you sleeping?
Really?
Syuuuuu...
Syukiari!!
(Chance!)
GYABOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!
I did it!
Idiot!
This is just for my gratitude, okay?
Thank you for watching
I have just finished this BETA version
Sorry for any imperfections!
(o_-)/""