Piano!
Piano....
I must play the piano!
Mukyaaaaa!!!
Although it's a very strange Rachmaninoff,
it's very interesting!
However,
it cannot be harmonized in an orchestra.
Why?
Nodame also wants to perform a concerto in an orchestra
Milch, please let me do it too!
Nodame-chan,
just as you are now, it's impossible!
unless you face music face to face more,
you won't be able to enjoy music from your heart
Nodame is enjoying it...
Why did you say such a thing?
Oh, it's time already
I have to go.
Milch....
Wait, Milch!
Nodame-chan...
don't forget to lock your door
A dream?
Good morning, Chiaki!
I.......
Don't you remember?
No mistake, after that School Festival,
I was dragged around by Maestro to...
Ginza,
Kyoto,
and onsen (hot spring)...
for three days and three nights.
Yesterday, again we went drinking in Roppongi,
that way, I ended up in Maestro's Hotel...
Then?
Earlier I took him to Narita
because if he changed his mind and said
he wanted to remain in Japan, it won't be good.
I'm still here to settle the remaining bill,
and to deliver this....
"Dearest Chiaki"
Huh?
From Maestro for Chiaki
Chiaki, I have something to ask you.
Please send to Germany
the photo book of Mami Nagaoka
which will be released in December
Oi!
Good bye
Wait...
Please convey my gratitude to Maestro....for now.
I'll convey it to him
And from me to you too
Eh?
It has been a long time since I saw him
conducting so happily
Thank you
Let's meet again some day!
This way....Stresemann went back to his country
This time....he really...
without mistake.....went home.
"Stresemann really returned home"
Then...the time will soon come,
compelling us who are left behind...
to choose the road
we are supposed to walk on...
Hmmh....I haven't got any job offer yet...
Me neither....
It felt like a blow after playing so much
But it was fun, wasn't it? S-Oke.
Yes, just when I thought we couldn't participate
even once in an Oke after 4 years in the Academy,
yet at the very last we managed to. It's good, isn't it?
Talking about it, S-Oke has not yet held a
closing party, right?
In that case, let's hold a drinking party!
"Disband Party"!
Wait a minute!
Come on, what are you talking, guys?!
Why did you talk as if S-Oke is just a
memory of a long long past?
I have no intention of making it end yet!
OK?
Mine-kun!
I want to do it too!
Sakura!
Yosh, okay shall we continue it?
Yes, let's!
Right??
That is S-Oke! Right?
Oh no! I have an interview in the afternoon!
I have an Introductory Meeting!
See you...
Wait...what are you suddenly up to, everybody?
Oi, all of you, what do you want to be? Oi!
Chiaki-Sama!
Chiaki!
Long time no see!
Yes.
Mine!
Are you still angry that Chiaki was in A-Oke?
I'm not angry!
I am....
Aaahhh...I was impressed....
It's...it's....it's the first time I was impressed,
other than to my own performance!
As expected, you are really my best friend!!
Huh? Since when did I become your best friend?
Um....I have a suggestion, if you don't mind....
What?
Ehhh??
Didn't Chiaki-Senpai come together with Nodame?
Huh?
Since the School Festival, Nodame-chan has
never come to school.
Nodame?
Hello?
Yes
Yes...
Publishing Editor Department
Kawano Keeko
Ehh, so this is the restaurant Chiaki-kun often goes
Somehow it's different from his image
Welcome!!
What would you like to have?
Clubhouse sandwich and expresso coffee, please
Eh?? Sandwich in a Chinese restaurant?
Sure!
Eh?? There's sandwich here??
Now, what is it that a music magazine writer
wants to talk to me about?
Oh! Sorry to say it late...
I'm Sakuma Manabu, a music critic.
Music Critic
Sakuma Manabu
In fact Sakuma-san is writing serial articles
for my magazine Classic Life
but for next month's article, we asked him
to write about Chiaki-kun!
Eh?
Dream Color Classic Serial Article
50th Anniversary
Special bonus:
With Pin-up!!
Sorry for not asking you first!
But earlier we got permission from Stresemann to
take photos, and he also said please take care of my pupil
See, they are good photos, aren't they?
Jiijii!!
Please read my part too.
"Reaching the fathomless bottom of a deep ravine
is the illuminating light of the piano prelude"
"I took a peek into that light...."
Aaahhh, beautiful Rachmaninoff piece...
Sakuma-san became your great fan!
Me too! Since I saw your conducting at school,
I've been always watching you!
Huh?
Me too, next time I certainly want to see your conducting!
Chiaki-kun, after you graduate, you're going
to go abroad, right?
Huh?
Of course as Stresemann's pupil!
Are you going to take part in
Conducting Competition over there?
Please wait a minute!
I have no intention of continuing to Graduate School...
What a stupid idea!
It came!!!
In this vast blue sky far over there,
aspiring for the shining sun,
spread your snowy white big wings
which have been sheltering
the soul of the sublime music in you,
it's time to FLY up for your new journey!!
Haaa???
"Why don't you study abroad?" that's what he's saying.
I.....
CANNOT FLY, YOU KNOW!!
In this vast ocean far over there,
the greatest treasure of Arts
is smiling at you,
why didn't you start rowing your boat?
"You'd have a good record of winning competitions abroad."
that's what he's saying.
I CANNOT ROW A BOAT, YOU KNOW!!
Neee, why won't you go abroad?
When you have such a talent,
and you have an amazing Master too!
Why??
Remaining in Japan, what do you actually intend to do?!!
Wherever I am....whatever I'm doing...
IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS!!
You have no right to worry about me!
Leave me alone!!
Oh Chiaki-san!
Your sandwich....I specially put pickles in it!
Please wrap it up, I'll pick it up later!
Okay!!
Why??
Once, God did not forgive Icarus,
but even God, if He is shown the music you perform,
He'll probably give you Love, Grace, and Blessing....
Maybe your poems made him upset?
Your orders please?
Stop!
Tagaya-san,
Don't break the lines in such small parts
Please express more insecure feeling!
Hai
Earlier you heard how Suganuma-san sang, didn't you?
Sing like that, with rich emotion!
Again, Suganuma?!
You have a very beautiful voice, but...
it's as if you can't get through one thing...
If you plan to continue to Graduate School
and to sing, you have to get through this wall...
Hmph....no timpani....
"Japan Metropolitan Philharmony"
Recruitment: Violin
"Audition for Oboe"
"Looking for Oboe Player"
Masumi-chan!
Ah, Kiyora!
As I expected, you're going to apply
to a Professional Orchestra?
Well, but at the time there's no
recruitment for timpani player at all....
It's really a tough world!
Ne, about Chiaki-kun, what's he going
to do after graduation?
Why on earth did you ask about Chiaki-san?
WHAT IS IN YOUR MIND?!!
No wories! After the outcome is fixed, I'll tell
Masumi-chan too.
Huh?
Eh, Chiaki?
Yes, but he hasn't shown up after saying
that he would pick it up
Is that why you came to the school to deliver it?
Of course!
Chiaki-san is your best friend, isn't he?
Well, yes.....
Let me deliver it....
I'll deliver it!
In the end, I....
am stuck at the same place again.
Even if I have conducted in student orchestra...
even if I have performed a concerto with Stresemann...
Why won't you go abroad??
When you have such a talent!
Saiko
"Noda"
But Nodame-chan, in your condition now,
you can't be together with Chiaki
can't be together
Nodame Cantabile
Lesson 6
http://s-projects.org
I didn't need it, you didn't have to deliver it
What's that attitude?!
Recently you're so cold!
Thank you for delivering it!
Right! They asked me to, that's why I
had no choice but to deliver it!
By the way, I saw it....
Shinichi's Concert
It was extremely good
But....
somehow you seem to have
gone far away, suddenly...
It's not true
You too, in these four years you have progressed
to sing quite well
Really??
Especially the low register can come out well now
But one thing still cannot come through
Though you have technique,
your acting ability is lacking....
whatever you sing, it's always one pattern that
it becomes boring
if you let out your malicious
character more,
perhaps the song you're singing
would also have some breadth?
I'll go to konbini and will be back soon
If you go home, you can leave the door unlocked as it is
I didn't know he's such a jerk!!
"Noda"
"Shubi Gakuen Music High School"
Year 2002 Graduation Album
Rather than worrying about me...always music, music...
He never changes...
If I quit music...
will we be able to stay together?
Saiko!
So she's gone home
Eeek!!!
Be careful, lock your door...
No....Nodame??
Yes, Nodame...
So you're still in Costume playing....
No, I'm not
Senpai!!
Please let Nodame play piano concerto
in an orchestra too!
Huh?
Nodame also wants to practice
the piece Senpai performed!
Nodame also wants to play that piece!
Senpai, I want to play... piano....
You stink!!
Eh?
You....for how many days haven't you taken a bath?
How many days? What day is today?
Go take a bath now!
The gas....
Again??
OK, OK, take a bath in my house!
But what about the clothes to change...
Here! This is the clothes you left here!
That female!!
Who is she?!
That girl...after she listened to my concerto,
she keeps practising after that?
Until she became like that...
Here, eat it!
I have no appetite
OK, eat it!
Gyabo!
Anyway, eat it!!
Concerto first...
It's impossible for you.
Why?
You never see the score, playing it your own way,
composing your own song!
How could the orchestra possibly harmonize with you?
Although Nodame do not see the score,
I have heard Rachmaninoff a few times, I know it
Moreover, Senpai's piano sound...
still remains in my ears...
Nodame also wants to play...
the way you did.
Nodame...
Yosh!
If you want to do it that much,
okay let me hear it.
Eh?
Your Rachmaninoff!
Let's go to the school
It's better to have two pianos!
Senpai!
Let's go home!
One more song, one more song!
Ehhhhh??
If you're just having fun playing,
would you let us have a turn?
Ha--hai!
My pleasure!
Nodame?!
There!
I'll play the part of the Oke,
and you play as usual
Imagine there's an Oke here.
Okay?
Alright.....you can start whenever you like.
The first pianissimo is played as fortessimo?
What piece is this?!!
On top of that, it's fast!
You can play this piece at this tempo??
Rachmaninoff Piano Concerto No 2?
Is it Chiaki-sama who's playing it?
Eh...Chiaki-sama is accompanying it...
It can't be!
So the one playing is.....Nodame??
There are too many sounds....
As expected, you're composing, aren't you?!
Moreover, she's already at it from the start.
She's just playing it on impulse.
It won't be!
This is not a Concerto.
Shall I stop it?
Dammit!
I'll harmonize with you!
Listen to my sound!
Oi!
What are you doing this late?
All of you!
Come on!
Or I'll drop you off.
Amazing!
As I thought, aren't they dating?
Those two.....
Ehhh?
Well, they're always together...if they were not,
how could they possibly play like that....
despite Nodame playing it very sloppily,
perhaps those two have matching minds...
Even so, I didn't know Nodame could play that well
It's enough....
Stop it....
It's enough.....
Oi, Nodame!
It's time to go home!
Oi!
This girl....
what should I do with her?
Here, from today, practice the Concerto.
But I already played the Concerto.
Huh?
Senpai accompanied me, didn't you?
Already played it?
But you said you wanted to play it in an orchestra
Senpai's piano was like a real orchestra!
I felt very good...
Nodame is very satisfied!
Really thank you very much!
I was extremely happy!
You're satisfied with such a performance?
Is that enough?
Nodame
Ara! You're here, Nodame-chan?
Aaaa, Masumi-chan!!
Chiaki! Look at this!
Voila! We got job offer!
"Job Offer Notification"
Congratulations!
Our music company has also been decided.
While working at the company we'll continue
taking lessons, while hoping we can make a professional debut...
That's great!!
As for me, I'm to take over my family's bakery
Me too, I'm going to help my family's Inn
in my hometown. Please come and visit, everyone!
Ne, ne, what are you going to do, Shizuka-chan?
Waaaaahhh!!!
Shizuka-chan is going to get married?
Although I'm glad for them, I will feel lonely...
I envy Shizuka-chan....getting married....
Nodame wants to graduate and get married at
the same time....
Yes do it....with a person from the same planet as yours!
Naturally Chiaki-Senpai will continue to
the Graduate School, right?
That's great! There are so many people either
going to study abroad or return to their home!
Nodame, shut up!
If you're not practicing, get out!
Eh?
Ack! Mine-kun, what's up?
Chiaki...
I have been thinking...
Can we continue S-Oke?
Huh?
That's a good idea!
Right? Moreover third year students Sakura
and me can continue...
If you do it, Masumi-chan will do it too...
and the others will find time in their works to get together...
Stop joking around!
Huh?
I don't have time to entertain such unrealistic talk!!
Where is it unrealistic??
Amateur Oke, whatever Oke, there are so many Oke, right?
If we wish to continue, we can continue, can't we?
With you becoming the Conductor,
all of us can gather more people...
And then?
With you as the Concert Master,
and that fuzzy-fuzzy Sakura,
you expect me to be the Conductor??
What do you intend to do with that
"we-are-all-friends" play-acting?
Like aspiring to become a professional Oke?
Gimme a break!
Then what are Chiaki going to do from now?
Is there a place you can conduct?
Why?
Remaining in Japan, what do you actually intend to do?!!
Didn't you want to be a Conductor?!
Idiot Chiaki!!
This person too, that person too....
Who needs your meddling!
Senpai, what are you doing?
What? Shopping for dinner!
Fish meat....
Deer meat...
Bear meat....
Bullying?
"Kangaroo Meat"
Senpai, today Nodame will treat you!
(this is kaiten/turning-around sushi, cheap)
(3000 yen!)
Okay, please help yourself!
Today I'll treat you to sushi!
Ah, here comes the egg....the egg...
(cheapest)
What Senpai likes hasn't come round yet?
Dammit!!
Why are the sushi turning around?
(which shows he's never been to kaiten sushi,
but only to bar sushi, which is EXPENSIVE)
(sea urchin, gold plate price=400 yen)
Mukyaaa!
Sea urchin?? Suddenly sea urchin??
Senpai, that's gold plate! 400 yen!!
It's decided in the market that a student
should only take the 100-yen white plates....
Humph!! Just so so!
(=which shows he only eats high grade sea urchin!)
Here! Hmh! I'll give them to you!!
These too, I'll give them to you!
Gyabo!!
Why did you leave the rice??
You just eat the sashimi toppings??
Ohhh....again it's gold plate!
(abalone, 400yen)
Nodame also wants to eat sashimi with rice....
Okay, here they are!
"Gari sushi"!
(no such thing! He just put the FREE ginger pickles,
or "gari", on the rice!!)
MUKYAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!!!
Senpai is weird! No common sense!
Surely I'm NOT going to treat you anymore!!
What treat? In the end I was the one paying!
If one has only 3000 yen, will she normally
enter a sushi shop?
Usually that's always enough for a
kaiten sushi!!
Senpai seems strange, so Nodame....
Could it be...
that even Nodame is worried about me?
What's this....everybody's worrying about me...
Senpai?
Someone like Nodame, it's not your place to worry about others
You too, next year you'll be a fourth-year student!
What are you going to do after that?
What am I going to do?
After graduating, Nodame intends to be a
kindergarten teacher
So you were serious....
Yes!
That's why next year I'll be busy with
such things like training in the field of education...
Why?
When I thought you had become a little
bit more serious about piano...
Even though you play sloppily....
you can play that well!
Why didn't you aim higher?
Ah!
Why won't you go abroad?
When you have such a talent!
Just as I think about Nodame....
if everyone also thinks about me...
that's something to be grateful for....
perhaps it's an honor...
Senpai....yes as I thought, you're strange...
It's not a problem of not being able to go
abroad anymore...now
Yes...
Why??
Remaining in Japan, what do you actually intend to do?!!
That is the problem.
Senpai....
Cut it out!!
Iyaaan....
GIMME A BREAK!!
Too near!!
Chiaki!
I'm not going to give up!
Too persistent!!
Chiaki-kun!
Good! I had been looking for you.
Huh?
Eh? You're going to Graduate School too?
Actually I planned to return to Vienna soon
but the teacher who used to guide me over there
will be busy for a while doing his own tour...
Well, it's a good chance....I'm thinking of
participating in competitions here in Japan
Eeh.....
That, and....
there's one more thing I want to do....
I want to make an orchestra....with Chiaki-kun
Huh?
Honestly, until now I had had no interest
in student orchestra...
However....
my performing with Stresemann in A-Oke
was an incentive...
on top of that, Chiaki-kun's conducting in
the periodical public performance was also...
quite an incentive.
Won't you make an orchestra with me,
and perform together?
I will
Immediate answer??
No....though I want to do it...but
If it's about the members of the orchestra,
there's no need to worry
Actually I have talked with some students from
other Academies whom I got to know from a
Music Festival in Vienna
All are excellent students
For example Kikuchi-kun from Toukoku Music Academy,
who won First Prize in Austria International Competition
Kikuchi...who plays cello?
I've heard of him from rumors!
He's also in Japan now
Then, Kuroki-kun from Morimichi Academy
I've heard of him too
As to the others...there are some who are still
studying abroad, or residing in Kansai....
If Chiaki-kun invite them, I think
they'll come to gather here
Huh? Me?
Of course! Chiaki-kun is a Superstar now!
Haaa?
Dream Color Classic, isn't it?
Okay!
See you later.
OK.
Chiaki!
Geh!!
Please let me enter your Oke too!
Huh?
If it's for Chiaki's Oke, I'll do anything!
In that case, show me you can enter A-Oke
in your next exam!
Then I'll let you in!
Alright!!
Alright! Alright!
I did it....alrighttttt....
Senpai is going to make an orchestra, right?
Yes.
"Today is reserved for
Momogaoka Music Academy's
S-Oke Group"
"S-Oke Disband Party"
I, Mine Ryutaro, would like to ask you to drink a toast
for the job offers for the fourth year students,
and for the safe disbanding of S-Oke!
Ah, why is that?
Didn't you say you wanted to continue S-Oke, huh?
KANPAI!!!!
Kanpai!!!
Mascot!! Beer! Beer! Serve it around!
Hai! Masumi-chan, here's more beer
Here's for you!
Oh, it hurts...
You! Don't you dare to overdo it, OK!
What about?
I didn't know Chiaki-Sama's going to
continue to Graduate School!
I thought Chiaki-Sama would certainly go to study abroad
but that he's going to remain in Japan makes me happy....
Could it be because there's Nodame here?
I'll kill you!
Ah! As Masumi-chan's job is not decided yet,
what about repeating for one year at school?
I'll certainly kill you!
Today, I must tell Kaoru-chan about my feeling...
Kaoru-chan....I......
It's my turn to pour Chiaki-Sama's beer now!
Hey, stop it!
It's my turn! It's my turn!
That Chiaki!
Till the very end....
Hey.....I have a good idea....
Huh?
Heheeheee...
What are you doing? Oi!
It's love ......
...vacation
Oi! Kaoruuuuu!!
(heart mark)
"Chijou no Hoshi" (The Stars above The Earth)
Lyrics by Nakajima Miyuki
Who put in this song??
Chiaki!
Chiaki-kun's going to sing this song!
Huh?
Chiaki-Sama singing karaoke??
Incredible!
How is it, the girls won't want to see it, will they?
Chiaki Shinichi crying out Nakajima
Miyuki's song passionately!
It's a punishment for what he did until now!
Let's make him feel totally ashamed!
Heeheeheeee.....
I know this song!
Wait a minute!!!
This is Ore-Sama's theme song!!
(Ore-Sama=I )
OK
"Kaze no...."
Stop it!
Ne, ne, there are a lot of S-Oke members gathering there...
"Farewell always comes right after happiness...."
Saiko-chan....her character changed!
Yes, it's as if she managed to go through the wall...
"Whenever I wake up, I'm...."
...alone!"
toilet....
toilet...
toilet, toilet, toilet...
Aa-ackk! toilet..
toilet...
Whoops!
Ohhh! Tagaya Saiko!
Ahhahaha...sorry!
Because you called my name without "san",
so I did it without thinking....
Hey....are you alright?
Wow....you smell good....
Why is Shinichi going out with such a girl like this?
Mmm..mmm...hoho...hum..mmmff...
That guy,
despite this kind of girl, he must have a
soft spot for this...
But, it's not that I have accepted it!
Don't sleep!!
"Taiko Tetsujin"
(Drum Master)
Heheeeheeehe...
Oi, Chiaki!!
Come here!
There's an interesting game!
Try to play it, it's my treat!
Drum Master?
It'll be easy, isn't it, if you use your
Conductor's sense of rhythm
Here, hold the sticks!
Spread out your legs!
The pose is also important in
determining the scores!
It's a lie....Hehehe...
Everybody! Chiaki's going to beat the drums!!
He'll do it, he'll do it!
Beating the drums strangely,
we'll make him leave a black stain
on the white handkerchief
in the memory of the Academy's infatuated ladies!
"Chijou No Hoshi" (The Stars Above The Earth)
This song again, I know it!
Wait a minute!!
I told you this is Ore-Sama's theme song....
Chiaki-Sama, all percussions in this world are mine!
OK
Alright! Let's begin!!
Amazing, Masumi-chan!
Today, please listen, Chiaki-Sama!
My feeling for these four years!
This....
this....
..sound percussion of love!!
Masumi-chan!
Masumi-chan!!
With this I'm not in S-Oke anymore,
and graduate from Chiaki-Sama as well!
I....
am going to make a new Oke.
Though it's not quite right to ask a person
who's aspiring to be a professional...
it's OK to do it only whenever you can afford the time...
would you be our timpanist,
Masumi?
HAI!!!
Sakura!
Hmm?
From tomorrow, practice as hard as you can!
Eh?
Together with me...
let's get into A-Oke!
Don't forget us...
shine forever....
...the legendary Super Orchestra!!
Legend of S-Oke....
Legend of....
Real bad!
Hick!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Hick!
What had Nodame been doing until now?
Whose shawl is this?
How would I know?!
Oi! Let's go to one more drinking place!
Eeehhhhh???
Before that, let's go to a game center first!
Let's go to a game center!
All game centers must have already been closed!
In that case, let's go to Karaoke!
Ehh? Did you really like games and karaoke that much??
NO, I DON'T LIKE THEM!!
But they always hindered me!!
I must have been a hated person
Senpai, nobody hates you...
...or, they like you with an effort...
I had no choice....
Sorry, sorry, the konbini was quite far...
Kaoru-chan, coffee or oolong tea, which one would you...
Ssss...sss...synchronized crying!
Chiaki-Sama....
didn't invite us to his new Oke...
Today a few people asked me to let them
into the new Oke....
but I rejected them.
I also enjoyed being in S-Oke.
Moreover it's the first orchestra I conducted
Though I feel grateful to them,
but for this new Oke, I don't want it to be
an extension of S-Oke
I want to make the best orchestra I can
But.....
Dammit! That man!
Just wait, you'll see!
Certainly we're not going to give up!
..even so....
if they look back at me...
Our S-Oke's Hatsu Butai!
(=first performance)
Let's enjoy it!
Although it was just a very short time...
it helped to make a big change in me
it was really a Special Orchestra
today it disbanded...
and then...
everybody to his next stage...
So this is Momogaoka Music Academy....
Good, it seems that the level of the girls is also high!
Just don't mess up the Oke by flopping, okay?
Shall we go now?
Alright, to say it again, I'm Miki Kiyora, playing violin.
Kuroki Yasunori-kun, playing oboe.
Kikuchi Tooru-kun, playing cello
Yoroshiku ne!
Kimura Tomohito-kun, playing violin
Hi!
And, the last, as you already knew...
is our Conductor, Chiaki Shinichi-kun
Yoroshiku!
Aaah, I saw that Dream Color Classic,
with the Special pin-up
I saw it too. Later please give us your autograph!
First, let's discuss about the member formation
among ourselves, five members.
For now, this is a simple Member List of the
people I contacted...here...
Excuse me...
I have a timpani player I want to recommend...
Timpani: Okuyama Masumi
What is it? Eye contact between the Concert Master
and the Conductor right away?
Huh?
Ahhh...it looks like it will be enjoyable...
Right?
Yes.
"Lesson Instructor Change"
Piano Division: 3rd Year Noda Megumi
Instructor: Tanioka Hajime --> Eto Kozo
Eto Kozo....
He's Harisen, isn't he?
Yes..
Elite Specialist
Eto Juku!!
Umm...you entered the wrong room!
It's not the wrong room
I'm your Instructor from today
Eto Kozo!
Yoroshiku!
This is just a BETA version
Any mistake will be corrected in the Final Release
Thank you for watching!!
*<<(o_o)>>* bye bye!!