We don't know Eto Sensei, do we?
Right, Nodame's Sensei is Tanioka Sensei, you know.
Hmmmm....could he possibly mistake his student?
Don't joke around!!
Ohhhh....Gorota...
Didn't you hear anything about yourself
from Tanioka Sensei?
Aryaa?
Noda Megumi!
I'll show that I can bring out your piano talent fully
after being buried for these 3 years!
Be thankful!
Alright! Let's begin the lesson!
First, play for me the piece you've played before,
or one that you like, OK?
Come on...
Quick, sit down!
Huh, what's this? Music Score?
Fart Exercise...What's this??
It's the piece I've played before.
Haaaa???
It's to be used for exercise in the kindergarten
Together with Tanioka Sensei, I plan to complete it by the time
of education internship, including the body movements too
What the heck were you doing, up to now??
Oi! Classic!
Play classical piece as normally!
What do you mean by "normally"?
Like Chopin, or Liszt!!
You must know even if only one piece, don't you?
Ah! Okay....Mary-san...
What piece is this!
Here is not a kindergarten or a small music lesson in town!
This is a MUSIC ACADEMY!!
Moreover you're already a student whom I selected!
Do you get it?!
You cannot play around for even a second....
PLAYING AROUND, YOU SAID??!
(she suddenly speaks with an accent like him)
NODAME IS DOING IT SERIOUSLY !
Mary-san's....
WHAT'S WRONG WITH IT?!
NODAME'S STUDYING PROPERLY!
Don't address me with "Omae"
(="you", but rude)
Heeeeeh???
[Tanioka Hajime ]
Tanioka Sensei!!
Sorry...
Noda-kun, you entered the wrong room
Why did the instructor suddenly change?!
Oh, so I haven't told you?
It's Eto Sensei's request, he said he wanted
to be your instructor
So it simply changed just like that?
Yes, because I know once he said it he wouldn't listen,
he has more authority than me,
he also seems to be enthusiastic in doing it.
Furthermore, I thought it would be interesting
the combination of you and Eto-kun
It's NOT interesting at all!!
Well, well, we are also having a lesson right now,
please leave...
Sensei..
Your instructor is not me anymore
I don't like that person!
I can't do anything about it
Do your best...
Okay, shall we begin from here...
When and where are we going to perform, and what
piece shall we play?
Before that, we should decide first where to practice.
Moreover we don't have enough people yet
We still have to contact more people
Yes, if we won't get any assistance from school,
we'll have to gather them by ourselves
So it's a student orchestra and semi-pro too?
Somehow I got excited
We got into A-Oke!
Serve you right!!
Two string people added....
What is it?
From your girlfriend?
A smiling face with a wild imagination
Nope!
Shall we continue this at another place?
Drinking party for the new orchestra
That's a good idea!
[No-name Orchestra]
Kiyora! It's been a long time!
Oh, Masumi-chan!!
Katayama-kun! Long time no see!
We had not met since the Dream Music Festival, had we?
It looks like that they all know each other, don't they?
I wonder if we can get along well...
Yes, even Masumi-chan too!
But the ones who know the Conductor are
only us!
Chiaki-kun, do you like Sibelius?
Yes, I do
Last year I played Sibelius....
Masumi-chan, Chiaki's in danger!!
Go, go!!
Whoahhhh!!
Go away, you!
Chiaki-Sama....
You never changes, Masumi-chan, always in high-tension
I want to see Chaiki-kun's conducting soon
Yes, they said you're the only Stresemann's pupil, right?
Hey!
I think it's good if today we can decide first
the piece we are going to play
Chiaki-kun, do you have a particular piece
you want to do?
I have thought about it, but I have several...
What about you all?
If we're going to do it, I'd like to do an a "hade"
one, gathering more people to join us
(= attention-catching)
In my opinion, with this number of people,
it's also good to do a classic....
What, like playing Mozart and the likes?
In that case, rather than Mozart, Haydn is better for it
Somehow, I feel strange...
It's completely different from S-Oke's drinking party
Everyone is calm and mature...
It's good...I feel relaxed...
Bruckner's Symphony no 9 is impressive, it'll be good, I think
[ 30 minutes later ]
It should be Beethoven!
In a blink of an eye, it turned into
a scene I'm used to...
And within just 30 minutes!
Everyone easily gets drunk!!
Sensei, I have a piece I'd like us to play!
Me too, me too!!
Mahler's "Symphony of A Thousand"!!
(=Symphony no 8)
MARRIAGE!!
Symphony of A Thousand..
Ne, Chiaki-kun, for now, why don't we
do a concerto for one of our pieces?
Ah good, there's someone with the right mind...
Huh?
Nothing....Yes, a concerto will be good
I was thinking of doing it too
There are a lot of good soloists in this Oke
True. Because of that....
let's do a cello concerto
of course, with me as the soloist
Flute!
Flute concerto! I'll be the soloist!
Well, well, don't fight over it!
Let's do a violin concerto!
Right, right! And I'll be the soloist!!
DIVORCE!
Mine put aside,
everybody has the confidence of being the soloist?
What about a contrabass concerto? Contrabass!
Yosh! Coming to this, let's let Chiaki-kun
decide over it!
Everyone, you may not bear a grudge over this!
Haiiiii!
Huh?
Contrabass! Contrabass!
Violin! Violin!! Contrabass!!
OK I decided!
Shall we do an oboe concerto?
With Kuroki-kun as the soloist
Okay
Eh, Chiaki-san?
He didn't come here today
Mine said that tonight they were going to have a
drinking party for the new orchestra
so perhaps Chiaki-san went there too?
A new orchestra?
Eh? Nodame-chan is not the mascot girl anymore?
Nodame-chan...?
Ne, would you like to eat something?
Just the right time!
New menu!
Ne, try this!
Gnocchi simmered in Mabo stew!
(weird! Italian with Chinese flavor)
Today Nodame's going home..
What? Nodame is strange?
That's normal!
She's not as usual, she's really weird
She's always weird, I said!
Ma....ma....ma....ma....ma....mabo
She didn't eat Mabo as usual!!
And she turned to look like a ggghost!!
Ha??
Laterz!!
Oi, Chiaki!
Nodame was acting weird, my Dad said.
Huh?
She came to my house, but without eating anything,
she went staggering home,
Nodame not eating meal, is it THAT weird?
Is my Dad an idiot or something?
It's weird
Yosh! Shall we go to the second
drinking place now?
Yes!!!
Chiaki-kun, you'll go to the second drinking
place too, right?
It's time for me to....
(he meant he'd go home)
Ah, let's go, let's go!!!
Chiaki Senpai....
Nodame Cantabile
Lesson 7
http://s-projects.org
Thanks!
Do your best with your practice!
Smooch!
Don't "uwaki", OK?
(=cheating by having an affair with another)
Silly!
For me, there's only you...
Bye!!
Bye bye!
Kikuchi-kun!
Who's she?
Oh, Hitotsuma Megumi-chan?
Hitotsuma??!! (=someone's legal wife)
Hi Sezan!
(=Suzanne? Susan? LOL)
I'm going to practice now, so...
It's true!
I'm not cheating on you!
AMAZING!!!
Chiaki-Sama's going to make an orchestra?
Right, right...
They are that Oke's members,
they said they were
going to practice in our school
Everybody seems to be excellent students
from other Academies...
Araaa! You didn't know it??
Despite that it's Chiaki-kun's Oke???
I have nothing to do anymore with that kind of guy!
Is that alright with you? To let such people
practice in our school?
Who are you?
Geh!
Kimura??
We were at the same Music High School
He was well-known for being extremely good at violin,
but he was also extremely weak
he was often bullied!
Not him, but you, who are you?
I'm the number two in this Academy..
Ouch!
Oi! Did you see Noda Megumi from Piano Division?
Nodame?
We have not seen her yet today..
NODA MEGUMI!
COME OUT!!
If you play truant you'll have to repeat this year!!
Do you understand??!!
Ah, Chiaki-kun
Yes?
Here we should play it a bit stronger,
then from here we can play it a little softer ...I think
Oh really...
But in that case, the change from the second theme
would be hard to append
Then, shall I make it crispier?
Yes, please.
Alright, let's start from the beginning!
Okay!
Oi, wait a minute!
Why are you two sitting there?
Huh? Why?
I told you so!!
This Oboe Concerto only needs 35 players!
It only needs 18 violin players,
with first and second violins combined.
It needs two Contrabass
That's why for this piece, you don't have
any part to play.
Dammit! He found us out!
Why did you choose such a piece?!!
How silly, you two!
Even the timpani isn't used, so bear with it.
Heh!
Mozart, Oboe Concerto in C Major
The piece is Allegro Aperto
Amazing..
So it must be Kuroki-kun's confidence...
that has chosen this most famous concerto,
which has always be the set-piece for any
oboe player competition.
He has high technique,
doing it in minute details,
and powerful
unshaking spirit.
But..
how can I say it...
Samurai...he's like a samurai, Kuroki...
As expected, all are excellent players
They also have good intuition
This orchestra is good!
Ahhh I'm tired!
From the first day playing the whole piece too
Also because these days we're just practising for
the competition, and always skipped orchestras
As I thought, everybody remains in that final selection
But as expected, Chiaki-kun's really amazing
Chiaki Shinichi...
I wondered how good he was
but his guidance was precise, and his
understanding of the piece is also high
He must be studying a lot.
As expected, he's Stresemann's pupil!
Skillful
Huh?
They're all more skillful than me..
Extremely skillful
Of course!
Those people are frequenters of competitions, you know!
Well, as to myself...
I can't participate in competitions because
my goal is to enter professional Oke...
But I was also chosen as S-Oke's Concert Master
and I also could get into A-Oke!
If you have such a leisure time to complain,
why don't you use it to practice?
You're a man,
but acting like a woman!
Oi, Chiaki!
Please decide the next piece quickly!!
Of course a piece I can participate in!
He said he wanted to prepare it in advance,
and make everybody say "WOW!~"
Right!
Koitsu's preparation in advance doesn't matter,
but if you don't decide it quickly,
there won't be enough time
to make the publicity either!
"Koitsu"?? Hah??
(=that person, but rude)
Wait! Ryuu-chan!!
Publicity? We haven't even decided
on the Hall yet....
Kimura-kun! We seem to be able to reserve
Tokyo Symphony Hall!
Really??
That's good...
Saiko...
I have a bit connection with that Hall, you know...
Concerning this sort of thing, Chiaki-kun is umm..ignorant,
or ummm...not very sensitive...
or "Music-Only Idiot"?
That's why I took over the matters related to accounting
HEY WAIT A MINUTE!!
Tokyo Symphony Hall??
Actually, how many persons does it accomodate??
We'll perform in Tokyo Symphony Hall as a nameless Oke??
However hard we advertise, we can't possibly ....
(the hall is too big!!)
If it's about advertising, leave it to us!
Sakuma Manabu?!
Do you want to make an official public notice in Classic Life?
Of course we'll ask for a payment, though!
I'll buy it! One full page!!!
Why are you two here?
We got a phone call
saying that Chiaki-kun made an orchestra with
wonderful members...
it was an anonymous call.
Anonymous?
Oh! If we're going to make a public notice,
we must think of the Oke's name first!
I have thought about that!
Huh?
Dad!
Yes!
What....what's that?!!
Rising Star Orchestra?
Abbreviated: "R.S Oke"!
It's a good name, isn't it?
It's a name my Dad and I thought of whole night long!
Treat it with care, OK?
But why must it be you and your Dad who thought of it??!
Really embarrassing!
The rising stars..
It came!
Oh, the shining greatest treasures that suddenly
appeared in the black darkness....
Oh, the twinkling stars of hope which we behold
in the sky we gaze up above....
Yes, with the music you play...
even the twilight of the Gods  can also
be changed into Hope
Flap your wings freely in this vast universe!
"The name has quite a deep meaning,"
that's what he was saying
Well, in fact I didn't give it any meaning so
deep to that extent....
I need to go home, as I still have to decide
the piece we're going to play next to Mozart's
Wait a moment, Chiaki-kun!
Eh?
This is Stresemann's latest new release
A friend in Germany sent it to me.
You can have it if you like.
Thank you
Ah, Chiaki-san!!
Here it is! Stamina Food Set!
Please let Nodame-chan eat them
Thank you
Senpai's going to conduct Mozart??
What's so funny?
Because Mozart is pink color!
Huh? What's that?
That's the image color in Nodame's mind
Chiaki Senpai conducting pink?
After you finish eating, go home!
I still have to study!
Aaaaah!
A second!
I want to have a second!
What was that news about Nodame becoming a ghost?
As usual, she talks a lot...
eat a lot...
I was worried about her for completely nothing!
Oh what about you..
How's your study going?
Eh?
Your piano practice!!
In fact Nodame..
For a while I won't be able to accompany you,
therefore practice properly by yourself
Ack! Yes, next time I'll deliver food
to your orchestra!
Will lemons dipped in honey again be good?
Don't come! Certainly!
Eeeh, why???
Don't ask. Anyway, don't come!!
This Oke is not for playing around!
Moreover..
for me...
it's the only thing I can do in Japan.
Huh??
Anyway!
Since such good members already gathered
I don't want cause strange gossips
Rather than pink...
it's dull silver?
It's true that for Mozart's piece
perhaps it would be better to have a little
more cheerfulness and warmth
Okay, let's take a break for ten minutes
Then, Kuroki-kun, wait...
Here on this place..
Senpai!!
I bring you miso soup and rice balls!
Excuse me...please help yourselves with these...
Heh, No---Nodame??
[It's being used by R.S Oke!!]
What's wrong?
Oi! I told you not to come!
But I'm just delivering this, and I'll go home immmediately
Ack! I'll greet everybody in the Oke!
Wait a minute!
Why do you have to greet them?
Because I'm your w...wife?
Today you have a lesson, don't you?
Oh....
Tanioka Sensei caught a cold, so....
Oh, then I'll call him to wish him a speedy recovery
Aaa....ahhh...
Today Tanioka Sensei....
with his family...
went to Mexico...?
Yes, something's strange indeed!
Even if you're always strange, you never skip your lesson
Oi!
What are you hiding?!
Chiaki-kun
Earlier what you said about this place..
Oh...sorry!
If you're in the middle of something, I'll...
Aaaa...not at all, not at all!
We're not in the middle of anything!
Umm, you're someone from Chiaki Senpai's Oke, aren't you?
Yes
I brought some food here. If you like, please
have some....
Rice balls....and miso soup.
Do your best with your practise.
Gomen kudasai! *bows*
(=super polite good bye)
(See how she walks, it's like a Kyoto dancer/geisha
in kimono, LOL, it's NOT normal!)
*bows*
That girl..Later I'll sure make her have it!
*bows"
Chiaki-kun...
Is that girl...
*bows"
Chiaki-kun...
Is that girl...
Chiaki-kun's girlfriend?
Ha? No, she's my Kohai in Piano Division
(Kohai= opposite of Senpai)
What's her name?
N...Noda Megumi
Noda....Megumi.....chan.
So skillful!!
If it makes you feel down, why don't you stop
coming here to watch?
Amazinnnggg~
How to produce such sounds?
Huh?
Please take me as your pupil!
Haa??
Please give me private lessons!
Only whenever you have the time is fine!
I'll treat you with any food you like!
My Dad...
will massage your shoulders!
My Dad!
Why??
You guys have teachers of your own!
No, you're much much more skillful
than my teacher!
No!
Suki da!
(I love you/ I love it)
I love Kiyora's violin!!
Oi!
Can I start the practise?
Hai! You can!
Let's start from the beginning all the way through
Earlier this Oke was dull silver...
but now it became pink Mozart....
That Nodame..
Thank you *bows*
Ack! Gokigen yo! *bows*
(again very very polite greeting)
My husband is always indebted to you....
*bows* *bows* *bows*
Nodame's instructor changed to Harisen??
Why, so suddenly??
Did the two of you play Rachmaninoff some time ago?
Yes..
Because of that Eto Sensei seems to like
Nodame-kun
So he listened to that ...
Gyaboo!!!
WAIT, NODA!!
Today I don't feel well, so....
But aren't you running now?!!
Hahaha, wow, so much excitement...
Those two won't be able to get along well..
If it's in order to do something with her,
I wish Tanioka Sensei would have done it yourself
I am...
not the kind of teacher who has enough initiative
to bring out enough initiative
from a student who hasn't enough intiative.
But since students are important customers,
I want to cooperate and make an effort
to help them achieve their dreams or hopes.
As a result, for these 3 years,
I ended up guiding her, cooperating in her composing
those pieces such as "Mojya-mojya Suite" and "Fart Exercise"
Therefore...
viewed from my policy as an instructor,
if Noda-kun doesn't want it, I don't want to hand her
to Eto-kun either!
However..
I feel that lately something changed in her....Noda-kun...
Although she herself might not realize it,
something has changed....
That's what I wish to see....
as a separate individual...
Mama, look, look!
That ojisan is stuck there
Miaouwww....
[Nodame Sensei's Guide Book]
"Concerning the chorus"
"Study of musical instruments"
"Concerning playing musical instruments"
"Scale Practise"
Practise of strong and weak sounds
Chiaki Senpai!
Just the right time! Let's go home together!
Nodame wants to go to supermarket to buy
materials for tomorrow's food delivery
Nodame
Until when do you intend to skip your lessons?
Tomorrow Tanioka Sensei is going to..
Your instructor is Harisen
But I attend the other classes
like children education...
I told you, you don't suit that job
You don't suit to be a teacher
Why is that?
How could you possibly advise children for education?
You'll be disrespected and bullied by the children!
That way you can't be a teacher!
Nodame will be a kindergarten teacher
If I were a parent....
only to you, I certainly won't entrust my kid!
Today Nodame will go home by myself.
Let's split up!
O-oh, please do that favour for me!
I'll go home by myself too!
Let's live separately too!
It's divorce!
(I noticed this is Roppongi Hills)
Silly girl...
You're definitely suitable to be a music performer....
But the way she is now, it can't be...
How much talent she has...
but as long as she does not wish it to be...
Even if I drag and pull her up...
in the end, the thing which can change her..
will be her own effort to get better....
Oh, the person from Chiaki Senpai's Oke...
Noda...Megumi-chan...
Oh, good evening...
Good evening...
Ahh....
I'm Kuroki Yasunori from Morimitsu Music Academy,
Thank you for the food for lunch...
Don't mention it, don't mention it
That...and this.
When I was taking a walk outside,
I saw it accidentally in a flower shop...
Do you know
Lily of the Valley's flower message?
"Purity". "Pure love"....
This is as my gratitude for the rice balls.
Wow, it's beautiful!
Thank you very much!
Today is there still anymore practice for the orchestra?
Umm, no...the practise is already over.
but since there's no class today and I have
nothing to do, so...
Ah, sorry..
I was thinking of shaving some reeds.
Reeds?
For clarinets and saxophones, they sell reeds which they
can use without having to shave first
but for oboe, we have to shave the reeds by ourselves
Heeeei.....so this is a reed?
It needs a lot of work..
But with that included, I like oboe
It's lovable because it needs some work on it...
but...
people tend to think of it as a plain thing in
the orchestrea
People tend to think of it as a plain thing?
ah...hmm...yes...
But Nodame likes the sound of oboe
How nice it is to be in an orchestra...
Seems to be so enjoyable
Megumi-chan's a piano player?
Yes!
Isn't it enjoyable?
Oh it's enjoyable!
Besides, I like piano
But..
I'll show that I can bring out your piano talent fully
Why didn't you aim higher?
You don't suit to be a teacher
Kuroki-kun, do you aim to be a professional?
Or aim for a higher goal?
Ahh...yes!
For now, to be a professional is my target
Then it's strange, isn't it, if I, who want to be a
kindergarten teacher,
aim for a higher goal like you?
I don't understand what Megumi-chan means
by aiming for a "higher" goal,
but doing music,
simply if we can perform well, we feel happy
and if we can perform even better, won't we perhaps be
able to enjoy it better as well?
Therefore, to aim higher is....
perhaps to enjoy music purely....
Doesn't Megumi-chan think so?
Chiaki!!!
Your girlfriend!! What's wrong with her??
What kind of human is she??
She's naturally hentai, isn't she?
(=abnormal, weird, peverted)
She's not my girlfriend, but yes, she's hentai
Can't she take lessons like a normal person?
Even if she's hentai, she's a Music Academy student!
But you also do not give lessons like a normal person
Haa?
There is no other person giving lessons holding
a harisen like you.
But it's not just a harisen
This is the form of my love
Thinking again about it...
why is Nodame running away from him?
Even if Harisen is strict,
her rejection is way too strong...
but.....
Today I'll part with this harisen
I don't want to repeat similar mistake I
made with you
However hentai she is,
I won't...
let go of the student I picked up by myself anymore!
Wait!
For the time being...
Waaa, Puri Gorota figure with candy,
the one costing 350 yen??
Wahhh, Riona!!
Waaah! Papa! Papa!
Waah! Mama!!
Ahh, ???
Ah...but where's Kazuo?
Kazuoooo!
I got Kazuo!!
[Eto Kozo]
Today it's with lunch-box attached.
Hey, don't run away! Wait!
Look, I already threw away my harisen!
It's true!
You may take a look
Nothing on my waist
I changed!
I also apologize for yelling at you that day
Forgive me!
From now on, please take your lessons normally
Anooo...
What?
There's one thing I'd like to request
Request?
Fart Agreement
1. To cooperate in the body exercise of "Fart Exercise"
until its completion.
2. Never hit me anymore
It's more than one!
Eto Kozo
Let's think of a good exercise
Yes. Here we concluded the "Fart Exercise Agreement"!
Hee...okay, first I'll eat this obento...
(=lunch box)
No....eat it after the lesson is over...
Fart Exercise!! Ooo!!
OK start!
<c:#FF80C0>Let's release it energetically,
<c:#FF80C0>Let's release it with a good sound
I'll do my best!
<c:#FF80C0>Do Re Mi Fa Boo Boo Boo Boo
<c:#FF80C0>Waaaa!!
After this is completed,
<c:#FF80C0>Big fart, small fart
the real lesson...
<c:#FF80C0>...all are the same farts anyway
...will start!
Sing while doing it
<c:#FF80C0>Put your hands on your hip
<c:#FF80C0>Okay let's fart now
<c:#FF80C0>Hey! Hey!
<c:#FF80C0>Boooooooo...
How was it?
Eh, something fell off...
The way to handle Noda Megumi
1. For the time being, Puri Gorota
2.  For the time being, lunch box
3. For the time being, let her do it as she likes?
Aryaa? What's this?
Chiaki Shinichi
Puri Gorota? What's that?
Then, maybe it's also good to bait her
with lunch box
Then...
For the time being, let her play the piano as she likes
Well, despite saying this and that...
he's the one most worried about you!
Chiaki Senpai...
Now, shall we do it from the start of this.....
Hey, where are you going??!!
Hey Wait!!
Hey!!
Haven't I given you the bait?!!
Are you still selecting the piece to play?
There are several candidates to choose from,
but none of them really strikes me as the right one.
Here it is
The pamphlet of Tokyo Symphony Hall
It includes the seating map, so I think it
will make a good reference
Thanks
But, Saiko...
Why do you have to do it until this far?
Finally you found it, didn't you?
What you can do in Japan
I used to think that unless I went abroad,
there would be no meaning,
...that the best place for classic was Europe,
...that however good I would be judged in Japan,
...I wouldn't be able to reach the peak.
But now....
Oi! What about the splitting up?!
The living separately?? The divorce??
Rather than that, Senpai...
Is it true that you can't go abroad?
You...how come did you know that?
I heard it from rumors...
Liar!
You must be eavesdropping, right?!
Why can't you go abroad?
Are you suffering from ecology syndrome?
Or have you done something bad that you can't
make a passport?
Whatever it is, leave it alone!
Or perhaps..
you're afraid of getting on a plane?
So it's true, isn't it...
That's why you didn't go to study abroad,
but continue to the Graduate School, right?
This is fine with me
Now I'm thinking of doing whatever I can here
with that Oke
Senpai...
Okay, study, study!!
Ah..
Aryaa? Milch!
"Brahms Symphony no 1"
Senpai, please read this..
Brahms Symphony no 1
This piece is said to have consume the time
spanning 20 years until its completion:
Brahms' first Symphony.
20 years?!
Nevertheless, if you hear this magnificent Symphony
of Brahms'
perhaps you will understand that in those 20 years he
had not wasted even one second.
Chiaki! I was saying that you should immerse yourself
more into the music!
You didn't notice something important
The important thing is...
how seriously you and this piece are facing each other.
I won't forgive...
half-heartedness.
This is it!
Senpai?
What are you looking for?
I have it!
From here..
violin...
From here...
Yes.
There's no more time to lose
From today,
I have to be engrossed in Brahms' world
It's decided that on December the 3rd,
at Tokyo Symphony Hall,
we...
will perform in Rising Star Orchestra's public performance.
We're going to enter into Brahms right away,
so everyone get ready!
Hai!
Finally our turn came!
OK let's do it!!!
Ah, sorry, sorry, I'm late...
because my lesson took a bit longer...
Sorry, Chiaki!
Oh, it has began already...
Sorry!
Oi! Be more concentrated in doing it!
Ha?? What's that?!!
You...I understand that you have practise
for the competition..
But for the Concert Master to be late???
Even if it's free, but because of the competition,
the Oke's practice time has already diminished
And all of you too!
Somehow...
you don't really put your mind in it...
But for now, we can't help it.
Until the competition is over,
our future depend on it,
But I also depend my future on this Oke!
Eh?
Come on, this is not a professional Oke,
how can you depend your future on it?
Then, everybody, what do you have in mind
participating in this Oke??
What do we have in mind?
well, to be able to perform with
excellent members of the same generation
will make a good experience
it will be an incentive, and furthermore..
Chiaki-kun
Heh?
I feel that with these members,
if we do it together with Chiaki-kun,
we'll be able to do an amazing job...
Right??
I'm thinking of doing something amazing,
something which can match a professional Oke
Everyone thinks the same way, don't you?
Once we become popular, when people will
always come to see us, we can earn money,
and can continue this Oke!
That's the same as a professional Oke!
I think ...
If it's this Oke, then it'll certainly be able to become so!
It's not a legend!
But it's an orchestra that will last forever!
That's my dream!
Although I think that's a very good dream,
but I'm returning to Boston in spring.
Heh?
Me too, sooner or later, I intend to return
to Vienna
Though I want to do something amazing
in this Oke,
my dream for the future is to be based in Vienna,
while performing worldwide.
Chiaki-kun must be thinking the same, right? Naturally!
That's a matter of course! He's Stresemann's pupil!
Why are you still in Japan, by the way?
If Chiaki-kun, he'll sure win in the competitions
abroad!
"Naturally"??
Most of us...
rather than wanting to be in a member of an orchestra,
we wish to be a soloist.
So I thought without doubt that this is just a
one-time performance.
To gather periodically is good....
but about professional Oke, are you serious??
Of course....to go that far...no way...
Right?
Brahms Symphony no 1, First Movement,
first synchronization, let's do our best.
Dammit, you all!!!
Why did you all laugh at Mine??!!
I..
Everybody will go their own ways....
It's enough for today
No..
Let's stop our practice, until the competition is over
Good luck in the competition!
Oi, Chiaki!!
From the beginning
it's something that's clearly understood.
That everyone will leave
is something I should have known.
What was it just now?
That is..
the plane accident at that time.....
But..
the first time I see..
a human being?
This is a Beta version, I made it in a rush,
sorry for any mistakes
For the last 20%, I subbed it while watching another
dorama The Glass Slipper on TV (Korean subbed in Japanese)
Sorry if I messed up
Bye Bye!!!
sd_sd_//>>>