This is a BETA version.
I will go to Europe.
After the Rising Star's Christmas performance is over,
I will go to Europe...
You...
So you don't know the reason why she
participates in the competition?
She wants to catch up with you!
With that determination she arrived at this stage.
What's that? Such a messy playing..
Nodame?
It's over now...
What is she doing now?
I wonder what's wrong with her...
Could it be that she forgets that she still has one
more piece to play?
Chiaki-Senpai
Debussy..
Imagine more enjoyable things!
Like being in love....feeling good
Being in love....feel good??
Yes. Debussy...
went to an island in the south with his lover,
and composed this piece feeling a lot of happiness.
Up to now you were walking on a tightrope, weren't you?
Wonderful!
The sounds are glittering...
It's Debussy being lost in love...
She's expressing it very well!
Auclair Sensei
No, she is not expressing that
perhaps she's still a baby!
Now we are going to announce the result
of the Second Stage
Noda Megumi
No.28
The numbers of the performers who can
proceed to the Final Stage
It's there!
Number eight, number eight!!
Tsuboi-kun, congratulations!
Aaaaaa!!
Yuu-kun, Yuu-kun, Yuu-kun! Congratulations!!
28.....28....
28, be in there...
It's there!!
It's there~
Congratulations!
It's good, it's good, isn't it!!
So she made it...
I thought I wouldn't make it..
I'll go and see the Final Stage too,
so do your best!
I'll be waiting
I have to do our best too
There are still some things in Japan...
which I have to do.
I'll show I can definitely get the 1st place!
Nodame Cantabile
Lesson 10
This softsubs only for home use.
Do not distribute.
http://s-projects.org
Chiaki!
You guys....
We heard that there'll be an audition
Let us take the audition too!
Even if only for a reserve, I don't mind!
We have practiced very hard to be able to get
into Rising Star!
Please!
Please!!
I'll hold an audition when the piece needs many players,
therefore practice as hard as you can.
Hai!!
We did it!
WAIT A MINUTE!
If it's my Oke,
you can enter it right away now!
The second famous in this Academy, Ookouchi Mamoru's
special orchestra,
abbreviated as..
O...
(O.M.S Oke = Ookuchi Mamoru Special Oke)
Chiaki-kun!!
Sorry, but could you please hurry up
wearing this?
Huh? What is it?
Publicity photo for the Christmas performance!
Unless we print and distribute it today,
it won't be on time.
Huh?
Then I had better change my clothes too, right?
Sorry...
For the advertisement, I'm thinking of only
emphasizing the good-looking ones...
Uh!
Don't
mind
Chiaki-kun, there's a music room over there,
change your clothes in that room, please.
I was not informed about this before!
Hurry up, or else it will be too late!
Wait a minute...
Chiaki-kun, as this will be the last,
what about changing your clothes here...
No!
Shall I help you change your clothes?
Wait, OK I'll go to that room!
Eh! New East Philharmony?
Yes!
Suddenly there was a recruitment for
a timpani player, and when I applied to it,
I passed through the document selection!
The next steps will be the exam for practical
skill and the final interview!
Heeeh, that's good!
It was Masumi-chan's dream to join a
professional Oke, right?
But if I pass the exam, it means I will be
playing double with Rising Star?
What should I do?
Even if you're playing double, you can
continue to be in Rising Star, isn't it good?
Hm?
Kiyora
Your concert last time was great!
This spring you will be coming to Vienna, won't you?
I will set aside my time for your sake,
and I'll be waiting for you.
Ka-ka-ka-ka-ka-ka....Kai Dune Sensei
directly praised you?
That's great, that's wonderful!
Yes, but....
Ah, Ryuu-chan!!
Haiiiii...
The sales for our Christmas performance tickets
seem to be very good!
An everlasting orchestra!
This is the second step to my dream!
Ryuutaro, umm.....
Oh right, let's tell Chiaki about it too!
Right! Where is he now?? Where?
Chiaki!
Ryuu!!
Oi, Chiakiiiiii!!
You're Chiaki-kun, aren't you?
Let me join your Oke.
Huh?
I'm violin player Takahashi Noriyuki
What are you doing?
Kiyora, look!
I won 3rd place in last year's
Buffon International Violin Competition
I was studying in Paris, but last month
I returned to Japan
My experience in orchestra is just a little
while in the University over there
I wonder if these aren't enough?
I think I'm NOT below this Oke's
Concert Mistress.
What??!!
No, no, Kiyora...
3rd place in Buffon International?
You did it, didn't you!
Ah...
What did you say your name was?
Never mind that! Hurry up take off your clothes,
I can't barely wait anymore!!
Ha?
MASUMI-CHAN!!!!
CHIAKI-KUN'S IN DANGER!!!
Wohhhhh!!!
Chiaki-Samaaaaa!!
What are you, who are you?!!
For the Finals, play Schumann's Piano Sonata no2 and...
Stravinsky's Petrouchka!
Petrouchka..
You must finish these two pieces by the day after tomorrow!
I didn't expect that you would pass through
until the Final Stage!
up to now it was like walking on a tightrope
that we managed to arrive to this stage
There's no time left for you to master
two pieces perfectly!
That's why on the opposite,
I selected two pieces having high level of difficulties,
so that you can appeal using your technique!
Hai!
Wow, as befitting of him.
Unless one is no 3 in Buffon International Competition.....
Yes
High-level technique, various vibrato, fast passage,
very firm,
thorough, and detailed...
Dynamic and passionate,
a different type of player from Kiyora.
So what's your decision, Chiaki-kun?
This girl, or me,
which one is more suitable to become
the Concert Master?
Eh?
Who do you think you are!
You came here to take an audition, didn't you!
Why do you suddenly want to be the Concert Master!
Shut up, Mojya mojya!
(=afro hair)
I got an invitation from the entertainment biz, you know,
but if I can enter this Oke, I'll reject their offer.
Therefore, I should at least get the Concert Master
position here.
Entertainment biz?
If it's already a sure thing, why would you reject them,
and prefer to enter our Oke?
Because this Oke is great, isn't it!
At that time, my heart beat faster
after not experiencing it for a long while!
Everybody is skillful,
young, confident, and looked to enjoy it!
How can I say it...
It's as if a lot of sounds are making love...
There's this beautiful Conductor giving himself to ecstasy,
and young guys in tuxedos...
Aaaaa....how should I explain it...
Anyway, I love clasical music!
And I love this Oke especially!
And I love Chiaki-kun too!
What was that, the last thing you said!
Go home, you!
We already have....
(throwing salt to drive away evil)
a wonderful Concert Master!
Please!
Haa?
I'm touched by your enthusiasm!
From today, you're a member of the Rising Star!
What are you saying, Ryuu-chan! All of a sudden!
Although Takahashi-kun's performance doesn't
have power as big as as Kiyora's,
but he has detailed technique, beautiful echo,
his level is higher than Kiyora's!
Moreover...
rather than no 2 in National Competition,
no 3 in Buffon International Competition will be...
better for our Oke's advertisement.
Ryuu-chan!
Mine...
That's why, Kiyora,
don't hesitate anymore
you can wholeheartedly return to Vienna
Then someday, if you want to become this Oke's
Concert Master once again,
bring back with you 2 or 3 better titles
than this guy has!!
You can do it!
Ryuu...
Idiot!
Don't worry about me.
I will practice violin so hard,
that I won't have any time left to cheat on you.
Eh? EHHH???
Chiaki-Sama, you're not very keen, aren't you?
What about?
I will certainly keep this Oke going!
regardless how many of you will leave...
I will keep it going!
Yes, like that please.
Hai!
That's right, Mine.
It shouldn't be a stagnant orchestra,
but an orchestra that will progress with time...
See you!
Bye!
Ah!
Venus is rising!
Idiot!!
OK, Chiaki-kun!
Tonight, in order to deepen our friendship,
let's the two of us have a chat until morning!
Where's your house?
Chiaki-Samaaaa!!!
Chiaki-Sama, hurry up!!
Take this chance to escape!
Masumi, you followed me for this?
Yes!! Hurry!
OK
I must do my part too...
Eh, Chiaki-kun! What's up?
I have a favor to ask concerning
the Rising Star
Eh?
And then...
There's another one who's progressing
in a dizzy way
No, it's wrong...
The second finger was wrong...
The rhythm was wrong...
Why is it so, Schumann?
Nodame-chan?
You have to eat lunch properly!
You haven't eaten anything since yesterday!
Nodame-chan, what's that??
You must take a rest!
Or take some fresh air outside!!
Wow. Noda Megumi? She passed the 2nd stage?
The 18th Maradonna Piano Competition
Competitors for the Final Stage:
4th year Tsuboi Ryuuji
3rd year Noda Megumi
Nodame, all of a sudden..?
Ah..
Eto Sensei!
What is it?
How is Nodame?
Can she win?
Ahhh..
It's unknown yet whether Noda will finish
practising it till the Final Stage
Today she'll have to practice until midnight again.
In any case, Schumann...
That one will sure take time to master..
Eh?
Eh??
She already mastered it!
How come so sudden?
What is that?
Nodame-chan was doing it!
I have no idea what it means
I wonder if this one is plus and this one is minus?
Electrical charge?
Did someone come and teach her?
Aaaa, please don't say such a scary thing!
Nobody came!
Nodame-chan kept practising by herself
She kept repeating the same Movement over and over...
and blah blah blah speaking to herself.....
and then...
electrical charge?
What are these, actually!
It's the same as before.
When I thought that she was playing Schubert messily,
the next day suddenly she could play it correctly!
When I thought she could manage to play
a difficult piece perfectly,
on stage, that was....
What kind of kid is she?
The no-good version again??
I don't get it at all...
I don't have the experience of having such
a pupil like her before.
How should I teach her..geeezz!!!
Eh, Noda!!
What are you doing?
Oi!
Oi! Noda!
Oh no!
Hey, Noda!
KAORI!!!!
Oi, what's wrong?
Saiko..
Good evening
So you were studying just now?
Yes
What is it?
Actually I have some business with
your neighbor next door, but she seems to be out.
My neighbor?
I want to give it to her
Christmas Concert
R.S Orchestra
December 25th, 2006 Suntory Hall
It's because that girl seems to be trying hard to do
her best
I tried to do a few things in the past because
I wanted Shinichi to love me
But that girl...
in order to be able to walk side by side with you,
she is trying so very hard to catch up with you, isn't she?
It will be great if she can do well in the
Final Stage
Yes
Bye..
Shinichi too..
It will be your last performance in japan, isn't it?
Please do your best!
First floor, 12th row, Seat no 19
5000 yen
(good seat)
The last..
38.8 Celcius?
What should we do, Kozo-san?
I wonder if we had better take her to hospital?
Today is already very late...
for the time being let her rest.
Yes...
Do we still have antipiretics?
(=medicine to reduce fever)
It's because she's always strange
so when she's really strange like now, I didn't notice it.
She's forcing herself too much
she didn't even eat...
at a time when, because of the competition,
the peak of exhaustion should be coming.
With this, it is completely time-over.
You don't have to do it anymore.
Take a good rest.
Whoever can go through those Petrouchka rings gets
2000.000 yen prize.
Nodame will go through them!
I'll say it in advance
If you miss it, you'll be punished
by swallowing 1000 needles!
You knew it too, didn't you?
In the past, you were in that room,
right? Megumi-chan!
Yuuto-kun...
Petrouchka...
Stravinsky, who was a pianist and conductor,
changed this orchestra piece
into a piano piece for the sake of a ballet
An orchestra piece?
It's a sad story about a puppet,
who after given life by the puppeteer,
eventually wished to be a real human.
So this piece is like a festival in a
lively toyland...
It's impossible!
even if you have good ears,
you won't make it in time!
Give up!
Once more from the beginning!
Nodame-chan!
It's time already!
We have to go to the competition hall!
We have to rush!
Just a bit more....
One complete song...
doesn't make it in time....
She hasn't given up, has she?
Hey, what's that ringtone?
Today's Cooking, Today's Cooking!
(=a TV show, the song is its theme song)
Nice choice!
Oi! We arrived!!
Noda, let's get off!!
Nodame-chan, hurry up!
Come on, Nodame-chan!!
Hurry!
Noda!
You really did it well!
However...
you shouldn't perform the 2nd piece in
such a condition!
Even if you fail....
Oi!
After you finish playing the first piece,
leave the stage!
Okay?
Nodame-chan, hurry up!
Maradonna Piano Competition
Final Stage
First, you have to change your clothes!
As expected of the Final Stage...
the level is high!
Even I started to feel very tense!!
Will Nodame-chan be alright?
28. Noda Megumi
Schumann/Piano Sonata No2
Stravinsky/Petrouchka
Megumi-chan?
That mouth..
Clown face Megumi-chan!
Clown face?
So you were still playing the piano?
I was so surprised to see you in competition!
Today, Hanasakura Sensei also came here to see.
Ehh, Petrouchka...
So you can play such a piece already!
How wonderful!
Megumi-chan!!
But I...won't be defeated by you anymore!
Anyhow,  once a person passes 20 years old,
she's just a usual person...they said!
I heard that he was a candidate to win 1st place.
Looks like it!! What an appearance!!
He's skillful!
The echo of the chord is good
The feeling of the variation part also
comes out well.
But that obasan! What a person!!
Amazing! Not a single miss!
21. Yuuto Segawa
21 years old
I wonder...what is it that he is scared of?
What's wrong?
You must aim higher!
Fly to the world!
This hand is wrong! This hand!!!
Next is Nodame, right?
I wonder what kind of performance is she
going to give?
Schumann and Stravinsky..
The two pieces....
can she really play them?
Nodame-chan!
Haaa?
Scarlett O'Hara?
What a dress!
Your forte is being surpassed, Masumi-chan!
Wanting to catch up with him...
she did her best to arrive at this stage.
Oh God, please bless her!
She, all of a sudden...
playing it as if the urgency of the rhythm is clinging on her...
a complete Schumann...
It is my first time....
to see her performing like this.
Don't lose control, Baby-chan!
What is it which you want so much,
that you came to this place?
There's still one piece left, but the audience
already......
Kozo-san...
Well done, Noda!
However..
Stop here!
Stand up now....and bow to the audience!
Noda?
Nodame?
Not yet, not yet, there is still more you can do, can't you?
She plays it!!
An active piece with a lot of notes...
Her versatile sounds are being drawn out
This is completely..
the sounds of an orchestra!
"Todays' Cooking"
She stops!!
What happened with Nodame?
That's not Petrouchka!
Ah, back again now!
She's composing her own piece!
She recovered in the later part..
BRAVO!
Megumi Noda
No 28
Megumi Noda...
Even if it was a good performance,
changing the piece is not allowed in competition.
After all, it means that she couldn't master
the piece on time.
Even so..
Noda Megumi
No.28
Fourth place: no 8, Tsuboi Ryuuji!
Third place: no 10......Sakake Shouko!
First place: No one!
Second place: No 21, Segawa Yuuto!
Why there is no one for First Place?
Nodame!
Won't you go to Europe together with me?
If you want to continue your piano,
rather than our school,
I think the school abroad will suit you better.
Moreover there are scholarship organizations,
and other competitions,
go abroad,
and see more,
feel more, experience more....
together with me...
Why?
Why do I have to study to the extent of
doing all those things?
Huh?
Why, you said?
You've become serious with piano, right?
That's why you took part in the Competition.
I joined the Competition just to get the prize money.
It's because I wanted money.
Because of the desire to have the money to play around!
Why did all of you...
do or say the way you wanted it to!
always, always, since a long time ago..
You must aim higher!
Fly to the world!
I'm fed up with it!
What's wrong with playing the piano freely
and the way I enjoy it?
Nodame..
You....
in that competition..
playing the piano on the stage...
really, didn't you enjoy it?
No, I didn't enjoy it.
OK, I understand.
Then it's enough.
Today..
it was the first time I saw you facing
music so seriously!
It was a very good performance.
Even so...
I didn't win, did I?
Chinese Food
Uraken
Several days later
What should I do...my grade-up exam!!
Uraken Original Christmas Cake
Receiving order until 12/25!
My head was so full of the Christmas Concert
that I forgot about the exam!
It's you yourself who said you
wanted to do Christmas Concert, isn't it!
Why didn't all of you stop me?
Everybody also has exams, don't you!
You're the only one who haven't studied to the
point that you panicked just before the exams!
Ack, shall I help you?
What's the subject, German?
You think I'll let you think I'm stupid concerning
my study too, huh??
Well, but you're really stupid, aren't you?
Ha?
Oh Chiaki, can you please teach me?
No, I don't want to!
Oh please, even if just my subdivision, the piano..
No!
I'm also busy myself!
Ryuutaro! If it's piano, what about asking Nodame-chan
to teach you?
Oh Dad, that's a good idea you said!
Eh, but how is she doing now?
Why, I wonder if she's feeling down now?
Since that day,
from her room,
even the sounds of piano never come out...
Hello?
Yes, Sakuma here.
About the matter you asked me the other day...
Yes, yes...
Concerning excellent conductors who might be able
to replace Chiaki-kun as the conductor of the Rising Star
I have listed several of them.
I'll bring it with me next time, OK?
Matsuda Yukihisa (28 years old)
Thank you!
I must tell all of them properly
about my going away..
[Today's Practice]
In use by R.S Orchestra
Good morning!
Hi, Chiaki!
Good morning...
Concerning our Chrsitmas performance
at Suntory Hall,
I have decided on the other piece...
I'm thinking of practising it directly
in our next practice day.
The piece is..
Beethoven's No 7, isn't it?
Eh?
This one is good!
It will be lively too.
Me too, I like this piece!
Everybody already practiced it in advance, you know.
Look here!
Look!
Why....why did everybody know it already?
Why?
We already heard it from Mine-kun quite sometime ago.
Huh?
It's the first piece we performed in S-Oke, isn't it?
Yes! It's the first piece Chiaki-Sama conducted!
That is the start of everything!
Let's perform it perfectly,
it will be Chiaki's last conducting in Rising Star!
Mine....
We don't have much time left, let's begin our practice now!
OK!
Never mind.
It has nothing to do with me.
MERRY CHRISTMAS!!!
http://s-projects.org