♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
[narrator]
Ash and his friends are in for a surprise
at this small-town Pokémon Center.
-Is your name Ash?
-Yeah.
I have a message for you.
-For me?
-Pika. Pika.
Greetings, Ash. It's Professor Oak.
Give me a call
when you get a chance!
It's from Professor Oak.
I guess it's been awhile
since you talked him, Ash.
-Why don't you give him a buzz?
-[Ash] Okay, let's see.
Professor. I hope he's around.
[ringtone]
Hi, Professor Oak. It's Ash!
Hello there, Ash!
I suppose my message
finally found its way to you!
-Yeah.
-How is everyone? Say...
-Pikachu sure is looking well.
-Pikachu!
-I'm fine, too.
-I'm glad to hear it!
Well, they say no news is good news,
uh, but I do wish you'd let me know
how things are going now and then.
I know. We've been kind of busy. Uh...
[Muk] Muk. Muk. Muk.
Come on. Cut that out!
[chuckles] My Muk seems to be doing okay.
Taking care of it hasn't been so easy!
Will you behave?
I hope the next Pokémon you send
will be easier to manage!
I hope so, too, Professor,
but I haven't caught any new ones.
That's right.
Well, make sure the next ones
aren't so mucky!
-Muk.
-[groans]
I almost forgot.
Have you heard about
the new Pokédex upgrade?
Pokédex upgrade? No, I haven't!
Well, now you can get details
on all the latest Pokémon discoveries.
Wow! How can I get it?
Just put your Pokédex
into that slot and I'll do it.
Once upgraded, your Pokédex will have
an updated database and even a new voice!
All right! I'm putting it in right now!
[computer bleeps]
Okay. It's all done.
[Ash] Gee, thanks!
Okay, no time to lose.
Go capture more Pokémon
and collect some new badges too!
Professor...
we're on our way right now!
Where to next?
We could head to Cinnabar Island
and the Cinnabar Gym.
The Cinnabar Gym.
-[Brock blows]
-Pika.
Hey, Brock, when do you think
that eggs going to hatch?
[Brock] Who knows?
-Hey, look what I found.
-[both] Huh?
Are you sure it's all right
to just take that?
Maybe I should have given
this Pokémon egg to Joy.
-No way!
-Huh?
I'll raise this one for you.
And I've been keeping it close to me
every night so it'll stay nice and warm.
What?
You mean you sleep with that egg?
It's the only way it'll hatch.
What else can I do?
[groans]
So, Brock, what kind of Pokémon's
going to hatch out of that thing anyway?
To tell you the truth, Ash,
I don't know.
You mean it might even turn out
to be a Tentacruel?
It could be, Misty.
[sighs]
I'd just love a Tentacruel!
Oh!
But it could it even be an Aerodactyl?
[Brock] That's a possibility, too.
[screams]
-Maybe it won't be.
-I'd like it to be a Golem!
Oh, imagine if it were a lovely Lapras.
I can't wait to see what kind of
Pokémon hatches, no matter what it is.
Did you hear that?
They're hatching a new Pokémon!
-I think he said a Dragonair.
-No, no. He said an Aerodactyl!
Whatever it is, we gotta get
our hands on that egg.
This could be the chance
we been waiting for.
Imagine when the boss hears
we've captured a Pokémon!
He'll be shocked.
Don't forget.
We haven't even succeeded in capturing
that one little Pikachu from those kids!
We have a proud tradition
of failure to uphold!
-[Jessie] Then you fail!
-And we'll win!
What? Hey, what's up?
Hey, let me in! Oh, come on!
I can break tradition!
-So, how far to cinnabar island?
-[Brock] Hmm.
-It looks pretty far.
-[all] Huh?
Hello, everybody! Good day! [giggles]
I don't believe my eyes!
[both giggling]
[both] We kick up our legs
so you will buy our eggs!
What kind of Pokémon eggs are they? Ah.
[chuckles]
Wait and find out when they hatch!
Won't you buy some?
Please! Please! Please!
We don't need any Pokémon eggs
'cause we already have one of our own.
-Yeah.
-Ah!
Let me see it. Show me!
Okay, okay.
Here. Like it?
-Oh! It's pretty! Lovely!
-Beautiful!
[both] One, two...
[all yell]
Which one is ours?
They aren't egg sellers!
[Team Rocket laugh]
-Prepare for trouble!
-Make it double!
-To protect the world from devastation!
-To unite all peoples within our nation!
-To denounce the evils of truth and love!
-To extend our reach to the stars above!
-Jessie!
-James!
-[Brock] Is that it?
-[both] Huh?
Hmm. Let's see.
-Hey! You didn't let us finish!
-Yeah, that's right!
And we didn't even get to the best part.
Ah. Is this it? Huh? Ah.
-Ah. Isn't this it?
-Huh?
-[both groan] Huh?
-[Meowth laughs]
Is this what you're looking for?
That's it! Meowths got our egg!
-It was...
-Your egg.
Let's beat it!
Come back, you thieves!
-[Meowth] Eh, we did it!
-[Jessie] A great success!
It was because I made
such a cute egg salesgirl.
Yeah, maybe.
So shall we cook it over easy?
Or maybe we can scramble it? Or I know!
-We can make a little fried rice!
-[Meowth yells]
You're not cooking it
because I'm hatching it.
-But how will you do that?
-Very simple.
I will warm it with my body.
-Ah...
-[Jessie and James] Huh?
[munching]
-Still holding that egg?
-Of course I am.
If I put it down my beautiful egg,
it'll cool off, and it won't hatch!
[Jessie and James] Hmm?
Now, my little eggy-weggy,
while you and I share a nice hot soak,
I'm going to tell you a bath time story.
Hmm. Once upon a time...
Ah, you're boiling it!
I like mine soft boiled.
Huh? Boiled? I told you
I'm going to hatch it not eat it!
Good night, little egg.
Time for us to go sleepy!
-I never realized Meowth could be so...
-Revolting.
Hey! Ah.
Look, it's another one!
If we just follow these eggs, they'll
lead us all the way to Team Rocket!
Wow, they're pretty dumb, aren't they?
Leaving us a trail of broken eggs.
If they're so dumb, how come
they're the ones who have the egg?
I guess you have a point there. [sighs]
Pika! Pika! Pika!
[all gasp]
[Brock] They must be in there!
[Jessie gulps]
Rise and shine, my little eggy-poo!
Meowth's going to make you nice and shiny
because we got a lot of incubating to do.
Here!
-What's that?
-Your scrambled eggs!
-I told you to lay off the e-g-g-s!
-Ah.
How can you be so insensitive,
you numbskull?
-That's definitely the egg.
-Right, now's our chance.
Go, Pidgeotto!
[squawks]
-Go, Geodude!
-Geodude!
Staryu, I choose you!
[gasps]
-Psy-ay-ay!
-No, not you! [grunts]
-What?
-What's going on?
[grunting and groaning]
-[squawks]
-Ah. Huh?
Good work, Pidgeotto!
Hey, give me back my egg!
That's funny. And all along,
I thought this was our egg.
Go get them and my egg!
-Go, Arbok!
-Weezing, go!
-Weezing!
-Charm!
[all coughing]
Careful, Ash, the egg!
-Charm!
-Argh!
Huh?
[grunting and groaning]
-The egg!
-Nyah! Nyah!
Geodude! Tackle attack!
[grunts]
-I got it!
-I've got it!
Hey, Staryu! Airborne tackle! Now!
[laughs] Huh? Oh!
-Got it! [grunts]
-Got it! Ooh!
Yeah! Ah!
[laughs]
Can't see.
Pidgeotto, Gust attack!
Blow this gas away!
[squawking]
[Meowth screams]
[all gasping]
Quick, somebody catch it!
The eggs going to break!
[grunts]
[yells]
[all gasping]
[grunts] I missed it! Huh?
Pika!
-Pikachu.
-Pikachu!
[all sigh]
-You did it, Pikachu!
-Nice catch, Pikachu!
-Kachu!
-Huh?
What's wrong, Ash?
It feels like there's something
moving inside!
-Huh?
-Pika...
[all gasping]
-It's starting to crack!
-Yeah, it's about to hatch!
Pika!
Hey! Oh, let me see!
[squeals]
Ah!
It hatched! It hatched!
Oh, how cute, heh!
[squeals]
Oh, hello to you too!
Oh, we're so lucky!
[Brock and Ash]
We are!
If Pikachu hadn't caught it...
-That precious little Pokémon
might have...
[all gasping]
-We have a battle to finish!
-I almost forgot!
-[Meowth] Let's get them!
-Pikachu, Thunderbolt attack!
Pikachu!
[all screaming]
-See you!
-Later!
Bye!
[trembling] My egg!
Where am I? Hi!
[squealing and chattering]
-It's so cute!
-It sure is, Misty.
-But what kind of Pokémon is it?
-Ah, good question.
Hey, now that Dexter's been upgraded,
he'll know the answer!
[Pokédex] Togepi, an egg Pokémon.
Specific information about this Pokémon
is still unavailable.
So, Togepi is your name.
You even sound cute!
-Pika!
-[squealing and chattering]
You think so too, don't you, Pikachu?
Pikachu!
Of course it's cute.
All newborns are cute.
That's right!
[trilling]
[babbling]
So now which one of us
gets to keep Togepi?
I think I should.
I'm the one who incubated the egg.
But I was the one
who found it in the first place.
I just let you watch it for a while!
I mothered it!
-Well...
-Huh?
I think I should keep Togepi
because it likes me best, right, Togepi?
[squealing and chattering]
It's obvious.
Togepi has made the right choice.
No fair! I found it, so it's mine!
Well, maybe you should have
taken better care of it!
-But you never took care of it!
-That's right! I took care of it!
Oh, yeah? I took care of it
more than all of you put together!
[all gasp]
That's right. You never saw how much
Meowth cared for that egg.
They were together when they ate.
They were together when they slept.
They even bathed together.
It was touching!
Please, James.
Just hearing it brings tears to my eyes.
I never knew you were so sensitive.
Save your pity.
All I want from you is my Togepi!
[Jessie and James] Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Team rocket's acting almost human.
All right! The only way to decide this
is with a Pokémon battle!
A Pokémon battle?
That's right. We'll have a tournament,
and whoever wins gets to keep Togepi.
-Are you in, or are you out?
-[Team Rocket whispering]
Count me in!
-So we'll have a six-way tournament.
-Right!
-Wait a minute!
-[Ash] Huh?
These two have no right to participate!
-Hey!
-What do you mean?
I hereby testify that neither of you
performed a single act to assist Togepi.
I can't believe you're being so selfish!
What about Team Rocket?
Then just the four of us will battle!
Sounds good to me.
Let's make it a sudden death battle
by using just one Pokémon each.
-[Brock] Okay!
-[Misty] Let's do it!
[Meowth] Fine with me!
Now, let's see.
Which Pokémon should I use?
I forgot!
I don't have any Pokémon to battle with!
Hey, guys, could I borrow
one of your Pokémon?
[both] Not a chance.
Agh! What am I going to do now? Huh?
Uh. Oh, yeah, I forgot! I am a Pokémon!
I can battle for myself!
First up is Brock versus Meowth.
[both growling]
-Go, Onyx!
-Go, Meowth!
Argh!
[screaming and grunting]
Meowth! Give them your Scratch attack!
Unh. Okay! Here goes!
-Being your own trainer must be tough.
-Must be.
Meowth!
Meowth isn't doing all that badly.
I didn't know Meowth was so spunky.
Your scratch attack can't do anything
against Onyx's hard stone body.
Onyx! Rock Throw now!
-[growls]
-Ah!
What's wrong, Meowth? Hang in there!
But Meowths scratch and bite attacks
aren't any good against
that giant rock Pokémon!
-[squealing and chattering]
-[Pikachu] Pika, pika, pika!
I'll do it for Togepi!
Meowth refuses to lose!
Huh? That's it!
Onyx is weak against water!
What do you say, Meowth?
Do you surrender?
Meowth never says die!
The absolute victory drench
with water attack!
[Onyx bellows]
[all gasping]
Fury swipes attack!
Onyx! Are you okay?
Hey, throwing water is cheating!
I am merely a parent
fighting for its child!
And I'm going to win this tournament!
-Well, well...
-Meowth won.
[Brock] Next up is Ash and Misty.
-Our first battle since Cerulean Gym!
-This time I'm going to beat you!
Bulbasaur, I choose you!
Bulbasaur!
Ah, yes, just as I expected.
You chose Bulbasaur!
-So I'll choose...
-Psy-ay!
[screams]
Quick! Get back in the ball!
You're not allowed
to call your Pokémon back!
Ugh, he's right.
Okay, aim for Psyducks head,
Bulbasaur!
Its head? Yeah, like I'm that dense!
-Bulbasaur, go lick Psyduck on the head!
-Bulbasaur!
[grunting and groaning]
No, Bulbasaur!
You'll never lick Psyduck if you lick it.
Good! Now, use the Tickle attack!
Psy-ay-ay! Psy-ay-ay! Psy-ay-ay!
The battle's over. Ash and Bulbasaur win!
All right, nice work! We did it!
-We did it!
-Oh, no! No! No! No!
[squealing and chattering]
The winner will get Togepi!
-[Ash] All right! I choose Pikachu!
-[Pikachu] Pika!
In that case, I choose Meowth! Ready!
Pi!
[both gasp]
[growls]
Little Togepi.
I can still remember
when you were just an egg,
and all we went through together.
For your sake, Togepi,
I, Meowth, will win you back!
All right! Victory will be mine!
Use your Fury Swipes attack! Right!
Pika...
-[Meowth grunting]
-[Pikachu] Chu!
I lost so fast, I'm a little shocked!
-The winner!
-We did it!
-I knew Meowth would lose.
-The heroes always get the breaks.
We did it!
[Meowth] Little Togepi...
I hope you'll be very happy
with your new trainer.
Good-bye now.
Togepi, you're mine now!
Uh, what's wrong?
Togepi, hey... It's no good.
I told you, but you didn't
want to believe me.
[squealing and chattering]
Look, it doesn't want to go
to anyone else but me now.
[both] Huh?
[Togepi trilling]
Hey, what's going on here?
[Pokédex] Togepi is imprinted
with the image of the first thing it sees
after it hatches,
thinking this is its mother.
Yeah, that explains it!
When it hatched,
Misty was the first thing it saw!
[squealing and chattering]
I knew it!
Togepi likes me,
because it thinks I'm its mother!
Right, Togepi?
[squealing and chattering]
I'll love you
just like a mother would.
You'll help me take care of Togepi,
won't you, Pikachu?
-Pikachu!
-Uh-huh.
[narrator]
Well, with Misty as its new trainer,
it seems like Togepi
is the real winner, don't you think?
-Whoa! Whoa!
-[squealing and chattering]
Yeah! [laughs]
♪ Pokémon ♪
Get those lips loose.
It's time to Pokérap.
Come on, sing 'em with me
That's the game.
There's 150 Pokémon
How many can you name?
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Sandslash, Hitmonlee, Psyduck
Arcanine, Eevee, Exeggcutor ♪
♪ Kabutops, Zapdos, Dratini
Growlithe, Mr. Mime, Cubone ♪
♪ Graveler, Voltorb, Gloom
We're almost home ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Charmeleon, Wartortle, Mewtwo
Tentacruel, Aerodactyl ♪
♪ Omanyte, Slowpoke, Pidgeot, Arbok ♪
That's all folks!
Can you name all the Pokémon?
Just put today's song together
with the other days of the week.
That's why you can't miss a show.
You gotta catch 'em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
That no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Our hearts so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪