♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Our hearts so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
[narrator]
As our story continues,
we once again find our friends traveling
together on their Pokémon journey
in perfect harmony.
[Misty] I’m not letting you
out of my sight, Ash Ketchum,
until you pay for my broken bike.
"My bike! My bike!"
That’s all I ever hear from you.
Right! And my name may be Misty,
but I’m perfectly clear
about what you owe me
and you’re not going to get away
without paying.
Maybe if you two had spent
less time arguing
and paid more attention
to where we’re going,
we’d already be in Vermilion City by now.
Come on, we’re already late.
We’ve got to start the show.
Chu.
I think we all need a little break.
Why don’t I just throw
a little something together?
Ah! There’s nothing as satisfying
as a cup of 100% Cerulean coffee.
You kids are too young for this stuff
but it’s really quite good.
-[Brock] How about some prune juice?
-I think I’ll pass.
-How about some herbal tea?
-You must be kidding.
Not so fast, Ash.
I brought my official Pokémon tea set.
Now, of course, the key to good tea
and coffee is good water,
and I just happen to have
a generous supply of sparkling,
delicious Mt. Moon pure spring water.
[Brock] And for the special snack,
I have for you some French crepes.
[gasps] I love French things.
They’re so romantic, aren’t they?
All that crunching and slurping
is ruining my romantic daydreams.
-[Brock] Ah, by the way.
-[both] Huh?
I can’t cook crepes and I can’t boil water
if I don’t have a fire!
One of you is going to have to go into
the forest and carry back some firewood.
That’s a very excellent idea, Brock,
and I’m willing to sacrifice the
excitement of searching for firewood
to stay here and keep you company.
-Well, I guess that means that...
-Yeah, I’m going. Uh!
[Ash] Here, firewood.
Here, firewood.
No firewood here, Pikachu.
Why do I have to do all the dirty--?
-Pika pi. Pikachu.
-Hmm?
Hey, looks like a fire.
[man] All right, what’s the name
of this one?
Is it a Zubat?
Listen, just because it’s foggy out here
doesn’t mean your brain
has to be in a fog.
-It’s a Pidgey.
-Nice guess. You just got lucky.
Okay, now tell us
what its special attack is.
Pidgey’s attack is Gust.
At level 5, Sand Attack. At level 12--
Everybody knows that. Now can you just
tell me at which level Pidgey evolves
and what’s the name
of Pidgey’s advanced stage?
Um...
You better come up with answers quick
or you’ll have to run faster.
[grunting]
[groans]
-I’m sorry. I forgot.
-[all sigh]
You forgot. Huh, and you call yourself
a Pokémon Tech student.
Well, we don’t want to study
with the likes of you.
I’m sorry.
Hey, leave that kid alone.
What’s going on here?
There’s nothing going on here.
Mind your own business.
This is a private training session.
There’s no room
in our Pokémon school for losers
who don’t even know
Pidgey’s evolved stage.
We have to maintain standards.
I don’t know anything
about this school of yours,
but if it’s turning out students like you,
I’d have to say the standards
are pretty low.
[Misty] That’s right, Ash. You tell them.
-Misty?
You better stop bullying that kid
or you’ll have to answer to us, right,
Ash?
Misty, you stay out of this.
Leave it to me.
You’re right, Ash. There’s no reason
for both of us to get into a fight.
It’s very brave of you to take
on all five by yourself.
[nervous chuckle]
[Misty] I’ll be here on the sidelines,
cheering you on,
waiting to drag
your carcass away at the end.
-[Misty] Show them you’re a man, Ash.
-We don’t fight.
Fighting is for cavemen.
This isn’t the Stone Age, you know.
And if we wasted our time having
a fight with a little insect like you,
it’d just make Pokémon Tech
look really bad.
-We’ll see you back at the Tech, Joe.
-Okay.
Hey, maybe you cowards are just
afraid to fight someone like me.
The only thing we’re afraid of is
how badly we’d beat
a little punk like you. [chuckles]
Who do those guys think they are?
-So those are the infamous Tech students.
-Tech students?
Pokémon Tech.
I think it’s short for Pokémon Technical,
a school for Pokémon trainers.
I know I had a flier here somewhere.
Yeah, here it is.
A Pokémon school in the middle of nowhere?
Hm, let’s see what it says here
about the place.
"Pokémon Technical Institute.
A boarding school for serious
Pokémon trainer preparation.
All students guaranteed to enter
Pokémon league upon graduation.
Pokémon Technical
is the educational facility
for exceptional students who want
to become Pokémon trainers
in a very short time
without having to travel on
difficult badge-collecting journeys."
[groans]
Oh, so that’s the story.
Getting into the Pokémon League
without badges is too easy.
Wait, there’s more.
"Students entrance fees and tuition
are in keeping with the highest standards
set by Pokémon Technical."
You know what that means, don’t you?
It’s one of those snobby private schools
only millionaires’ kids can go to.
Oh, that really makes me mad.
Where is this place, anyway?
-It’s right over there.
-Huh?
[woman on speakers] Today’s special class,
fog battle techniques, is now ended.
Tomorrow’s lesson
will be snow competition secrets.
[sighs]
Oh, well. I guess tomorrow
they’ll make me into a snowman again.
Do they treat you like that all the time?
-My friends are just trying to help me.
-You call them friends?
With friends like that,
who needs enemies?
But they helped me learn that Pidgey
evolves to Pidgeotto at level 18,
it learns Whirlwind at level 21,
Wing Attack at level 31,
and that as its level rises,
it learns various tricks.
After evolving to Pidgeot, it can fly at
1200 meters and speeds of up to Mach 2.
I don’t get it.
If you know everything about Pidgey,
why didn’t you just answer them before?
Sometimes, I make believe
that I don’t know all the answers,
because if I do, they make
the questions that much harder.
But I have to stay here at Pokémon Tech.
My mother and father worked hard
and saved money,
so they could pay to send me
to school here.
You see that guy over there?
He’s an upperclassman.
The classes are so hard here, some
students are held back for many years.
Everybody’s too ashamed to go home
without getting a diploma.
That guy,
he’s in the beginners’ class with me.
You’re a beginner?
Beginners have the same qualifications
as someone with two badges,
the intermediate class
has the qualifications of four,
and advanced students
have the same as six.
If you graduate,
you can enter the Pokémon League
without traveling around
to collect the badges.
That guy’s a beginner,
but he’s so much older
than everybody in the class,
the kids don’t bother to help him
like they help me.
What do the teachers say
about that kind of help?
They don’t even know about it
or if they do, they pretend not to.
Well, I for one think
this is a violation of students’ rights
that must stop immediately,
if not sooner.
I want to meet the student in charge
of this system and I’ll see that it stops.
-Mm, here’s a picture.
-[all gasp]
-[Misty] It’s a girl?
-Oh, yeah, you’re right about that.
She can violate my rights if--
Hey!
If she’s making your life so miserable,
how come you’re carrying
her picture around?
I hate the way she treats us
but I like the way she looks.
Yeah, not like some other girls who treat
you bad and look even worse.
While you two are slobbering over
that dopey picture,
I’m going to find this little witch
and straighten her out.
Miss top student.
What’s so great about her?
Hey, Misty, wait.
That place brings back memories,
James.
It certainly does, Jessie,
and all of them are awful.
Tell me your tale of failure again.
-We studied for the big test.
-So sure we would beat all the rest.
And here’s the part I like the best.
We frolicked that night,
for our future seemed bright.
But things weren’t right.
[both] We got the lowest scores
in the history of the school.
-You should look on the bright side.
-[both] What’s the bright side?
At least you guys
were the top of the bottom.
You’re the tops, Meowth.
Such a kind little Pokémon. Ooh, ooh.
These two are worse off than I thought.
I liked it better when they were nasty.
Giselle always practices here
by herself.
Even if you beat her in a fight,
it won’t matter to her.
At the Tech, it’s your skill
as a Pokémon trainer...
that counts more
than winning in any one battle.
That’s what I’m hoping
because I’ve got two badges.
But Giselle is the top beginner
here at the tech.
That’s better
than even having three badges.
Even though I’m at the bottom
of my class,
I’m still more powerful
than someone with two badges.
Argh! Hold on a second here.
I learned how to be a Pokémon trainer
at the Cerulean City Gym.
Are you saying you can beat me?
Oh, Cerulean City. Water Pokémon.
-How’d you know?
-I always beat them on the simulator. See?
What is this?
A simulation’s one thing
but this is real life. Let’s battle.
You’ll be sorry.
[both grunt]
-[Ash] What do you two have to battle for?
-Butt out, Ash.
I have the Cerulean City Gym’s
reputation to defend
and I’m going to defend it.
Misty calls Starmie!
Too bad your water Pokémon
won’t be able to beat my plant.
All right, Weepinbell, let’s go.
Bell.
I’ll teach him about Pokémon.
Starmie, go!
-[groans]
-Huh?
Oh, but Weepinbell is strong
against water Pokémon.
True, but there’s one thing
you didn’t know.
Your opponent’s from
the Cerulean City Gym.
Her Pokémon has much
more experience battling.
You should’ve known that.
You’ve an embarrassment
to the whole school.
-But, Giselle--
-She’s really pretty, isn’t she?
-Yeah, just like a movie star.
-They like stars, do they?
I’ll be glad to show them some stars.
I’m the top student in the beginning class
of the most exclusive prep school
in the world, Pokémon Tech.
It’s sad that others aren’t blessed
with my beauty,
my talent, my humble attitude.
People call me a star
but I’m just Giselle.
I think she’s even more conceited
than we are.
-Yes, but she’s awfully cute, isn’t she?
-Not as cute as Meowth.
-[Jessie] Oh, you’re in the way.
-[James] Stop bothering us.
Meowth!
I want to continue to help my classmates
be the very best they can be.
To teach each other, respect each other,
and insure the Pokémon of tomorrow.
-But you’re a weakling.
-Uh.
You’d better get stronger fast
or before you know it,
your fellow students will turn
their backs on you for good.
Hmm.
Not so fast. A true friend wouldn’t walk
away from someone who needs their help.
You may look beautiful
but you remind me of an old saying
about how beauty’s only skin deep.
Heh, jealousy’s not very
pretty either, is it?
I better do something.
Wise Pokémon trainers
never get involved in a cat fight.
Huh?
Against your water Pokémon,
I’ll choose...
Graveler. Go!
Graveler? But rock Pokémon
are weak against water Pokémon.
But my Pokémon are at such an advanced
level, they can beat water Pokémon.
[grunting and groaning]
I can’t believe it.
Now we’re by the pool,
your Pokémon's specialty.
You can use a different water Pokémon
if you want.
Oh, and I’m sure you’ll choose another
Pokémon that’s weak against water.
Pokémon are only as strong
as the trainer who raises them.
A Pokémon that’s weaker
but better-trained can still win.
It depends on the trainer. I hope you’re
learning something from this, Joe.
A Pokémon's level of training
is just as important a factor
as a Pokémon's type in deciding a match.
A first-class Pokémon trainer
can calculate that.
Wait a minute. There’s more to Pokémon
training than calculating levels.
-Who are you?
-I’m Ash Ketchum from Pallet,
and I’ve already got two badges.
Heh, in other words, you’re a beginner.
And how long have you been trying
to become a Pokémon trainer?
Um, about two months, I guess.
[gasps] Two whole months
and you let your Pikachu walk free?
You haven’t even been able to tame it yet?
-Maybe your Pokémon are training you.
-Chu!
I don’t want to train Pikachu.
Pikachu’s my friend,
and so are Butterfree and Pidgeotto.
-Is that all you have?
-Huh?
That’s funny because even new
Pokémon trainers
usually have at least six Pokémon
and you got two badges with only three.
He sure was lucky, wasn’t he?
Every one of mine has the power of two.
I wonder, with two months
of Pokémon experience,
your Pikachu should be
at least at level 25,
but it’s probably not there yet, is it?
I suppose you didn’t know very much
about Pokémon
if you picked a Pikachu as your first
one. Pikachu tend to be hard to handle.
It says so in any beginning
Pokémon manual.
[gasps] You really didn’t know?
And you still got two badges? How funny.
A Pikachu evolves into an
electric Pokémon called Raichu.
It gets to be about 2 feet 7 inches tall.
Pikachu can shock you, but otherwise,
it’s pretty cute, don’t you think?
So if you don’t let them evolve,
they make great pets,
especially for little girls
but I’m sure you knew that, didn’t you?
Really? You didn’t?
And you have two badges?
[chuckles]
-Knock it off!
-Pikachu.
Let’s battle.
For your Pikachu,
this should be more than a match.
Cubone, go!
Cubone, bone, bone, bone.
Cubone. Cubone.
This Pikachu is my friend
and it’s different from any other Pikachu.
-Shock Attack!
-Pow!
Cubone, bone, bone, bone,
bone, bone, bone. Cubone.
-What?
-Pika?
Pikachu can’t shock it.
Cubone, start things off
with your Leer Attack.
-Cu-bone!
-Pika. Chu.
Pikachu, stare it down. Like this.
[grunting and groaning]
Cubone, Cubone...
Cubone, Bone Club now!
Hey, that’s not fair.
I’m not playing around.
This isn’t a staring contest.
This is a contest of power
and skill between two Pokémon.
Cubone, it’s time for the Bonemerang now.
Cubone, Cubone.
Oh! Pikachu!
Throwing that bone is a cheap way to win.
Well, that’s Cubone’s special attack.
It’s authorized by the Pokémon League
and it’s perfectly legal.
-It’s still a cheap trick.
-[sighs]
-Pikachu?
-Cubone! Cubone!
[groans]
-Oh, Pikachu!
-Cubone.
Calling it a cheap trick
simply proves your own ignorance.
Ugh, hang in there, Pikachu.
If your opponent’s attack is authorized,
then fighting back is too.
Give it your best shot.
Come on, Pikachu.
Bonemerang, now!
[grunting and groaning]
-Huh?
-Go on, Pikachu.
-Give it everything you’ve got.
-Pika!
-Cubone!
-We did it!
[both cheering]
Cubone!
I lost. Cubone, good try.
-Come on back. Don’t cry.
-Cubone.
You’ll be okay now.
None of the textbooks
ever mention a Pikachu winning
by anything other than electricity.
That was a once-in-a-lifetime battle.
And don’t try to copy it.
It was just kind of a fluke.
It was a cool fluke, wasn’t it?
There’s another way to win that’s not
in the textbooks too, isn’t there, James?
-Let’s show them.
-I can’t believe I lost a match. Huh?
Oh, no, it’s not--
[both] Allow us to reintroduce ourselves.
-To protect the world from devastation.
-To unite all peoples within our nation.
-To denounce the evils of truth and love.
-To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James.
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
-Surrender now or prepare to fight.
-Meowth!
I love a splashy entrance.
[Giselle] I’ve heard of Team Rocket.
You’re the ones who got the worst grades
ever on the entrance exam.
-How about your team versus our team?
-[all] Yeah. Yeah.
-The two of us against all of them?
-But the rules say one on one.
Bad guys don’t play by the rules.
Get them!
-[Team Rocket groaning]
-[Jessie] Too many poke balls!
[James] From now on,
we play by the rules!
[Meowth] At least for a little while.
[Jessie and James] Looks like
Team Rocket’s blasting off again.
There are some things you just can’t
learn in school and that’s a good lesson.
I’m going back home to start
from scratch with my first Pokémon,
just like Ash did.
Hey, Giselle, maybe we’ll meet someday
in the Pokémon League.
I hope so.
I’ll try my hardest
to be a worthy opponent if we do.
All right, if I keep your picture with me?
Sure.
I have pictures of my friends too.
-Huh? Do you have mine?
-We’re friends now, aren’t we?
-Good luck, Joe.
-You too, Giselle.
See, why can’t you and I be like that,
Misty?
Huh? I’ll tell you exactly why.
Because he doesn’t owe her a bike.
Ah! [laughs]
So maybe we’ll battle each other
again someday.
-I sure hope so.
-Me too.
[narrator]
So as Ash and his friends journey on,
they take one last look at the school
where they learned so much.
-♪ Pokémon ♪
-Attention all Pokémon Trainers
Do you got what it takes
to be the best?
Today, we'll do 30 Pokémon.
It's the ultimate test.
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Articuno, Jynx, Nidorina, Beedrill
Haunter, Squirtle, Chansey, Pokémon ♪
♪ Parasect, Exeggcute, Muk Dewgong
Pidgeotto, Lapras, Vulpix, Rhydon ♪
♪ And there's 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master
Is my destiny ♪
♪ Charizard, Machamp, Pinsir Koffing
Dugtrio, Golbat, Staru, Magikarp ♪
♪ Ninetales, Ekans, Omastar ♪
♪ Scyther Tentacool
Dragonair, Magmar ♪
Not bad, not bad.
Hey, don't get cocky.
Tomorrow's the hardest part.
We're on our way up to
150 Pokémon.
There's no stopping us.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪