♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
[all] Let’s eat!
[all chomp and grunt]
Pika-um. Pika.
[narrator] It all began with
an innocent question from Misty.
You know, you haven’t gotten
a badge in a long time, Ash.
You think you’ll ever get another one?
[gasps and gags]
I guess you could make another
gym leader feel sorry for you
and get another badge that way.
Take it easy, Ash. Drink this.
[grunts and sighs]
Skill! I win matches with skill!
How much skill does it take to win
a match against Team Rocket?
[all] Huh?
Okay! I’ll show you some skill.
I challenge you to a match right now!
-Pika, pika.
-Huh?
-No, I will not change my mind!
-[Todd] Hold it!
[camera shutter clicks]
-Why should I hold it?
-Not you, Pikachu!
That’s a perfect expression!
-Pika?
-Hey, cut it out!
Okay, okay. It looks like you want
to prove you have skills somehow, right?
That’s exactly what I want to prove!
Well, why don’t you
just get yourself admitted?
-Admitted?
-Take the Pokémon League admissions exam!
-The Pokémon League...
-Admissions exam?
-Pika?
-Togepi!
[Narrator]
To get into the Pokémon League,
a trainer has to travel from
one Pokémon gym to another
and collect badges to prove that
he’s defeated each Gym Master.
However...
Here at the Pokémon League
Admissions Center,
we evaluate applicants based on a combined
written and practical skills exam.
And all those who pass receive this badge
qualifying them for the Pokémon League!
[all gasp]
Take this. It’s your testing number.
[Ash] Lucky seven!
See, Misty, I have skill and luck!
-A little modesty wouldn’t hurt.
-Pika.
Oh, no. I wanted number seven.
[gasps]
[grunts]
Uh, age, 17. Profession, diva.
Hmm, that girl looks familiar.
Wow, look at all the different kinds
of people showing up for the exam!
[Ash]
Yeah. Nobody I’m not better than.
-Oh, Nurse Joy!
-Yeah, but which one?
-[Man] Just a minute!
-[both] Huh?
You’ll have to leave your Poké Balls
here with me.
[Ash] Why?
You’re not permitted to use
you own Pokémon in the exam.
-What? Hmm, here.
-[man] Thank you.
Can I take care of his Pikachu
during the exam?
Of course. Good luck, Mr. Ketchum!
I’d wish you luck, too
but you’re just so skilled.
-You got that right.
-Pika.
[Ash] Uh, so you want to become
a Pokémon Master, too, huh, Nurse Joy?
Well, it always has been
a dream of mine.
-So, uh, where are you from, Nurse Joy?
-I’m Nurse Joy of the Fuchsia City Joys.
Sister to the Vermilion City Joys.
Aha, you’re the most beautiful one yet!
-That’s what you always say, Brock.
-Togepi!
I came here for the exam because my work
keeps me too busy to travel very much.
This exam is really a great idea.
Yes, it’s perfect for people whose age or
health keeps them from traveling around.
And it’s also nice for people like me
who can’t ever seem to get away from work.
I can feel it.
I’m sure you’re going to pass the test!
I hope you’re right.
That’d make a nice human interest shot.
-Hey, save your film for Pokémon!
-[all] Huh?
[gasps and gibbers]
That’s weird.
That guy looked really familiar, too.
-Here’s the exam form.
-Fine. Let’s see. Your name is James.
-Urgh. Will you please keep it down!
-Huh?
-Is that...
-Huh, hey, get lost, old bat!
Huh? Old bat?
[both grunt angrily]
What are you, unhand me, you...
Please let me go! Come on! Ow!
So I’m an old bat, am I?
You’re Jessie? That outfit is atrocious.
-And what are you doing here?
-What am I doing here?
Well, truth to tell, I,
not unlike many other people,
dream of becoming a Pokémon Master.
Make fun if you must! [laughs]
No, you’re doing just fine on your own.
I want to live my dream,
instead of my... my reality.
Hm. I can see why.
What’s your reason for being here?
I simply wanted to add another talent to
my very impressive and extensive resume.
As you know I’m already an accomplished
hostess, florist, costume designer,
wine expert, beautician, style consultant.
-In fact one of the only things I’m not--
-Is a Pokémon Master!
[both] Meowth!
-What are you doing here?
-Looking for you.
The one who suddenly remembered
an important engagement.
This seems suspiciously unlike a visit
to your sick uncle’s bedside.
And I thought you
had a dental appointment!
Well, I...
-It was just such a beautiful day.
-We decided to have a picnic!
-Don’t try to fool me!
-[Jessie and James grunting]
[Meowth] Come clean.
What are you doing here?
-Mind your own business!
-Take this and leave us alone!
[grunting]
-[Jessie] Hurry up!
-[James] The exam’s about to start.
Pika, pika! Pika, Pikachu.
[man] The first test will measure
your overall knowledge of Pokémon.
-Ready. Begin!
-I can’t wait. This’ll be easy!
[Pokédex] Lickitung’s tongue
is twice the length of its body.
-True or false?
-I’m pretty sure it was longer than that.
[Pokédex] Ninetales evolves
from Vulpix only by use of the fire stone.
-True or false?
-Oh man, that’s too easy. True, true!
[Pokédex] Hitmonlee is also
known as the punching demon.
Let’s see. It’s either Hitmonlee
or Hitmonchan that’s the puncher.
Oh, I think it’s true!
[Pokédex] The only attack
Magikarp originally knows is splash.
True or false?
Argh, Magikarp!
Just hearing that name
makes my blood boil!
-[Jessie] True.
-That’s true, too.
[Pokédex] Caterpie
is the world’s smallest Pokémon.
-True or false?
-Yeah, that’s true.
Look at her. She’s so good.
[Pokédex] Koffing was first
discovered in a public bath house.
-True or false?
-[Jessie] True, true, true.
All I have to do is guess
and I’ll get half of them right.
Pika, pika. Pikachu.
Now we will measure your ability
to recognize Pokémon.
Please name the Pokémon
by identifying its silhouette
or any part of its body
as it’s displayed here.
All right!
This is going to be a piece of cake!
Here’s the first question.
Identify this Pokémon.
This is going to be a breeze for me.
It’s a Voltorb!
Ah, how simple.
It’s a Poké Ball, without a doubt.
Obviously, it’s an Electrode!
And the answer is Jigglypuff,
seen from above.
[all gasp]
Next question.
What Pokémon displays this pattern?
I’ve never seen that!
-It must be an Omanyte’s shell!
-It’s an Arbok when it’s all coiled up.
Hmm, hey! It’s a Poliwhirl!
The correct answer, Poliwag!
[all grunt]
As any Master would know,
when Poliwag evolves into Poliwhirl,
the swirl on its stomach
reverses direction.
Hey, this is hard.
-And it’s getting harder by the minute.
-Pika.
Question 15.
What Pokémon does this tail belong to?
Hmm. It’s either Charmander, Charmeleon,
or Charizard?
Yeah, it’s got to be Charmander!
The answer is Ponyta.
No, it can’t be!
Argh, can’t you ask one question
that I know the answer to?
-[all] Huh?
-[man] Please, take your seat!
This is a joke! These stupid questions
won’t make you a Pokémon Master!
For your information, young lady,
a Pokémon Master must understand
all aspects of their Pokémon's life
in order to achieve oneness
with their Pokémon.
Argh, you’re not making any sense at all!
I’m through with this!
-Get out!
-I can’t wait to go, huh!
But, Jessie, uh...
-Dear. What a shame.
-That girl’s attitude seems familiar, too.
Meowth, Meowth.
-Hey, let’s go!
-Unh!
Where am I going?
You’re going with me to help me
get my revenge!
Huh?
[woman]
Here comes the scoreboard!
[all chattering]
The ones on the right got the low scores,
and the ones on the left got the highest.
[Brock]
Look! Nurse Joy is near the top!
Hey, where’s your picture, Ash?
Uh, it must be
where they put the highest scorer.
-[Misty] Ash!
-[all] Huh?
-Uh, down here. Here’s your picture.
-Huh?
[Ash] That’s impossible.
[camera shutter clicks]
-Quit it!
-Ah, just a little souvenir, Ash!
Well, Ash, it looks like you didn’t have
enough luck or skill to pass the test.
Huh? Pokémon isn’t about tests.
It’s about battles!
-[laughs]
-Uh...
[James] Jessie’s been expelled!
Now I’ll have to do my best for her!
Pika, pika! Pika!
[bell rings and cheering]
All right, Squirtle! Water gun attack!
-Squirtle!
-Char!
Squirtle, give it the skull bash now!
Nurse Joy, you’re doing great, yeah!
All right, shoot away. I want 8x10
glossies and wallet sizes, too.
Yeah, sure.
-Now, select whichever one you like.
-[James] Hmm?
[Ash] Uh, I don’t know which one to pick.
You can’t tell us what kind of Pokémon
are inside them, huh?
[man] That’s what makes it a test.
All of these Pokémon are trained
for battle, so they’ll obey your commands.
This test determines
whether a trainer can adapt
regardless of what Pokémon
comes out.
-With whom do we have to battle?
-[man] With me.
-Right! Then I’ll take these!
-I’ll take these.
[bell dings]
[grunts]
[cheering and applause]
Come on, James! Beat that ignoramus!
Right, really beat the guy.
This one’s for you, Jessie!
Pikachu.
[all] Huh?
-Pika, pika?
-Pikachu.
Heh, with this, I can’t lose!
Thundershock! Thunderbolt!
I’ve been destroyed by Pikachu’s attacks
so many times, I know them all by heart!
[laughing]
That’s kind of pathetic
when you think about it.
Yeah.
Now, we begin! Go!
-Graveler!
-It’s a Graveler.
-Pikachu, thunderbolt!
-Pika!
Oh, that feels great to say!
[both grunting]
[grunts]
I don’t get it. How come the thunderbolt
attack didn’t work?
You should’ve known that electricity
doesn’t work on rock Pokémon!
-Minus one point!
-Well then. How about this?
-Char!
-Ivysaur!
[gasp]
With these I can win!
Now what do you say?
[laughing]
-Goodbye!
-Argh!
It’s against the rules
to use two Pokémon at once.
I never play by the... Huh?
-Ugh.
-You’re expelled. Now get out!
He failed again.
Don’t think of it as failing,
think of it as not succeeding.
Now we’ll see if Ash can win one!
-Go get them, Ash!
-Pika!
Thanks. Just leave it to me!
Hey, Todd, make sure
you get lots of great shots!
Don’t worry. Just make sure you win!
[James] I’m such a loser!
-[Jessie] James.
-Huh?
I have a plan that will make us
all winners.
Yeah.
-Are you ready, Ash?
-Ready!
Poké Ball, go!
Flareon!
Okay, now I need something
to beat a Flareon.
First Poké Ball, go!
-Weezing!
-Argh, I got a Weezing?
[all] That’s bad!
[Todd] I got to get this.
His face looks just like Weezing’s!
-Not now!
-It’s time to start the battle!
Flareon, go. Flamethrower now!
[both grunting]
Argh. Oh, I know.
Weezing, give him your smog attack now!
[all gasp]
Now, Flareon, the leer!
Come on, Weezing,
fight back with smokescreen!
-Hey, not too shabby.
-Go, Weezing! Tackle attack!
[grunting continues]
All right! My first victory!
I guess Ash is a pretty good battler
after all!
Even Team Rocket could win
if they fought like that!
Hurry, take notes! Take notes!
-Now round two!
-Jolteon!
Okay, a Jolteon? Next Poké Ball, go!
-Arbok!
-Ugh.
-Ash got the Pokémon Jessie has!
-Chu.
Let’s see. What are Arbok’s attacks?
Jolteon! Agility attack!
[grunting]
I remember. Arbok, glare!
Now squeeze it with your wrap attack now!
[both grunting]
Ugh, that was no good!
I forgot about all of Jolteon’s spikes!
Quick, Jolteon, use the thunder attack!
-Arbok, no!
-Too bad you overloaded Jolteon’s spikes.
Sizing up your opponent
before an attack is a fundamental rule.
Argh! Arbok, return!
Okay, third Poké Ball. Go!
-Meowth!
-Heh, Meowth?
-Pika?
-This ought to be interesting.
Toge! Toge!
Hey, Meowth, good luck!
-Meowth.
-Let’s see. Meowth’s attacks are...
-Use the fury swipes!
-Huh?
Poké Ball, go!
-Vaporeon!
-A Vaporeon!
-Okay, Meowth! Use the fury swipes!
-Meowth!
Vaporeon, use your ice beam now!
Vaporeon!
Ah!
Oh, Meowth.
Looks like another victory for me.
-That was fast.
-[Meowth] Look what you did!
How could you treat a fellow
Meowth that way!
Ugh, sorry you had to go through that!
Say, now, I’d love to catch that
talking Meowth there!
Poké Ball, go!
[all gasp]
[man]
Return those Pokémon immediately!
We’re not taking orders from you anymore,
Mr. Exam Man!
Now we’re the ones
who’re going to test you!
-What?
-Prepare yourself for trouble.
I strongly suggest
you make that double.
Oh, it’s Team Rocket!
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation.
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the stars above.
Heh, Jessie!
James!
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth! That’s right!
Don’t interfere with my test.
Just go home and study harder
and you can try again next time.
Unfortunately for you,
there won’t be a next time!
But now that we’ve rounded up
all these Pokémon, it’s payback time!
Pikachu, Ivysaur, Charizard, go!
Are you ready?
And I’m going to teach you a lesson
for picking on a Meowth!
-Huh?
-We’re not going to let you do it!
-Go, Pikachu!
-Pika!
-Ivysaur! The vine whip now!
-Charizard! Flamethrower now!
Pikachu, thunder now!
Listen up, Ivysaur, Charizard, Pikachu!
About face, now!
[Team Rocket gasp and grunt]
How did you...
Oh, they obeyed you because
you’re the one who raised all of them!
Very good, Ash!
Meowth, Weezing, Arbok,
stop Team Rocket!
-Stop it, Arbok, that hurts!
-[all grunt]
Weezing, please! I can’t breathe!
-Okay, Weezing! Explosion now!
-Weezing!
[all] Looks like Team Rocket’s
blasting off again!
[man] I am terribly sorry, everyone.
But Team Rocket’s intrusion has interfered
with the entire examination.
We have to start over
from the very beginning.
You mean, after all that hard work,
we did?
Well, young man, you did a fine job
of getting rid of Team Rocket!
What do you say?
Do you want to give the test another try?
-Ah, no thanks, sir. I don’t think so.
-I’m sure you’ll pass this time.
Oh, it’s not that. I just think I’m better
off getting badges my own way for now.
-Right, Pikachu?
-Pika!
You proved you’re a great battler
after all.
Thanks, Misty. I guess so.
Well then, if you learned that lesson,
I’d say the test really was worth taking.
Yeah, that’s true, Misty!
Anyway, it sure was awesome to battle
with all those different Pokémon!
[narrator]
Many roads lead to the Pokémon League.
Ash’s chosen path is to win
all eight Gym badges.
Only then can he continue to fulfill
his dream of reaching the ultimate goal,
becoming a Pokémon Master!
-Hey, where’s Ash?
-They already left.
They’re on their way to the next Gym.
-Huh? What’s wrong with that Meowth?
-It got hurt in the explosion.
-Where am I?
-This must be...
Huh? Meowth!
What going on? Where’s Jessie?
Where’s James? Huh?
I finally got my talking Meowth!
Uh! Wait a minute!
Wait a minute. Argh!
[narrator]
There seems to be a little mix-up!
[grunts in frustration]
We’ll show those twerps next time!
Next time, Team Rocket triumphs!
Meowth, don’t you have anything to say?
Meowth-eowth!
[both] Huh?
Meowth! Meowth! Meowth! Meowth!
Meowth! Meowth! Meowth...
Okay, guys!
We gotta rap some Pokémon,
You just do the singing.
I'll take care of the hard part.
Let's get it on.
♪ I want to be the best there ever was ♪
♪ To beat all the rest
Yeah, that's my cause ♪
♪ Electrode, Diglett, Nidoran, Mankey
Venusaur, Rattata, Fearow, Pidgey ♪
♪ Seaking, Jolteon
Dragonite, Gastly ♪
♪ Ponyta, Vaporeon
Poliwrath, Butterfree ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ I'll search across the land
Look far and wide ♪
♪ Release from my hand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Venemoth, Poliwag
Nidorino, Golduck, Ivysaur ♪
♪ Grimer, Victreebel, Moltres, Nidoking ♪
♪ Farfetch'd, Abra, Jigglypuff, Kingler
Rhyhorn, Clefable, Wigglytuff ♪
Thirty-two down
That's it for now.
Tune in tomorrow.
We'll rap at you some more.
There's 150,
so watch Monday through Friday.
You'll catch 'em all!
♪ Catch 'em catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch them all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪