♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon! Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, gotta catch 'em all
[narrator] Holy Titanic!
Just as a Pokémon pirating plan
is prevented by Ash and his friends,
catastrophe strikes the St. Anne.
The cruise ship capsizes
with them trapped on board.
Team Rocket also faces
the same horrible fate,
as the once proud St. Anne plunges deeper
and deeper into the depths of the sea.
Could this be how it ends?
[Ash] Pokémon Shipwreck
[Jenny] At first, we thought all the
passengers had gotten safely off the ship,
but we have just discovered
that five people are missing,
Ash, Misty, Brock, Jessie and James.
It makes all of us sad to think
that these young Pokémon trainers
have had their promising careers
cut tragically short.
May these flowers honor your memory.
A salute.
[taps bugle call]
[Brock] Hey, Ash. Answer me.
[Misty] Wake up, Ash. Wake up.
[Pikachu] Pika-pi!
[moans] What?
Hey, are you feeling okay, Ash?
-Pikachu?
-What?
Oh, brother. What are you
talking about, am I feeling okay?
You guys are the ones who are upside down.
You're definitely the one upside down.
Huh? [groans]
-Whoa!
-Look out!
-Pika. Pikachu.
-[Ash groans]
Will someone tell me
what in the world happened?
Just take a look out the window.
Huh? Huh? Fish swimming?
This can't be.
But that must mean
that this ship has sunk.
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation.
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation.
[both]
To denounce the evils of truth and love,
to extend our reach to the stars above.
-Ah, Jessie.
-James with a perfect tan.
There's nothing like a tropical vacation.
-The blue sea.
-The white sand.
-And the blazing sun above.
-Ah! The sun.
Yes, that blazing sun,
fiery and burning,
and burning, burning.
Burning.
Something's really burning!
-You picked a bad place for a nap!
-Huh?
[both screaming]
[both sighing]
Why is everything upside down?
The ship capsized and sank
while you two were sleeping.
-What?
-Aah!
We've got to abandon ship immediately!
I'm afraid it won't be so easy
to get off while the ship's underwater.
The ship's sunk! We're doomed!
Calm down, James!
I've already thought of a way
to get us out of here.
Ekans!
[rattling]
Ekans, acid.
Open a hole in the floor.
We'll use it to escape.
Wait! Don't do that!
[distant rumbling]
[both scream]
Didn't I tell you numskulls we're sinking?
You think we need another hole
on this ship?
[both yelp]
[both gurgling]
What are we supposed to do?
The ship's leaking everywhere.
We've got to keep calm.
As long as there's air in here,
it'll take time to fill up with water.
Sure, but we better not waste any time
escaping.
Well, we can either go up or down.
Well, if we're sinking,
then up would definitely be better
-and if the ship is flipped upside down...
-The deck is below us
and the ship's bottom is
up above our heads.
Then we have to dive down to the deck.
Pika, pika.
But if we dive down to the deck
and come across a dead end,
-then we're done for.
-[gasps]
[grunts]
[muffled whimpering]
So how are we supposed to know?
Water's my specialty.
Go, Goldeen!
Goldeen, Goldeen. Goldeen.
Goldeen, dive down to the deck.
If you find a way off the ship,
bring something back from outside.
Goldeen.
Goldeen. Goldeen?
What's taking Goldeen so long?
I guess it can't find a way out.
[all gasp]
[all scream]
Team Rocket?
They look terrible!
Prepare. Prepare for trouble.
Yes, make it double.
[both] Huh? You!
We've got you brats cornered.
So you followed us
all the way to the bottom of the sea.
-Ekans!
-Koffing!
-Koffing.
-Ekans.
[both] Here we go!
-Bulbasaur!
-Char! Char!
-Squirtle! Squirt!
-Geodude!
All right, a match.
[all moaning and screaming]
[creaking and rumbling]
[all screaming]
The ship will roll
if we don't do something quick.
Charmander, Squirtle, Bulbasaur, Geodude,
Koffing, Ekans,
to the other side of the ship!
[all mutter]
[all screaming]
To the other side! The other side!
[all mutter]
Dude! Geodude!
Geodude, come back to this side!
[all screaming]
You guys, call back your Pokémon.
But Team Rocket will beat us
if we call our Pokémon back.
He's right.
We can't worry about that right now.
We've got worse troubles.
[both] Yeah.
Call your Pokémon back too.
What's more important,
a Pokémon battle or your life?
She's right. Good point.
[all sigh]
Okay, then, we all agree
there won't be any battles for now.
Let's work together.
[all grumbling]
Come on, now. Shake hands!
[all] Huh?
This is just a temporary truce
until we get out of this mess.
Better believe it.
[both grunt]
-[grumbles]
-Pikachu!
[yelps]
Pikachu!
[groans]
It's agreed we work together.
Now we gotta think of some way to escape.
Leave it to me. I forgot to mention
I built my own St. Anne once.
-[Ash] Huh?
-Really?
It was a model.
-[all] Ah.
-Oh, great.
That's how I learned
all about the structure of the St. Anne.
Since the way to the deck is blocked,
we'll have to climb
to the bottom of the ship.
We can cut a hole in the hull.
That's how we'll escape.
[all] What?
Well, at least it's a plan anyway.
[Brock] Over there.
Onix! Make a staircase!
[growling]
-[Brock] Let's hurry!
-[Ash] Right.
[Pikachu] Pika.
Let's move it or lose it.
[both] Yes, ma'am.
[Brock]
The lights are out. I can't see anything.
[Ash] Let me handle it.
Charmander, I choose you.
Char! Char!
So where does this hall lead to?
This corridor leads
straight to the engine room.
And that's where the hull is the thinnest.
With a little luck,
we should be able to cut our way through.
[all gasp]
This is no good.
It's impossible to cross
to the engine room.
-Jessica?
-Yes, James?
Whoever said beauty doesn't last
must have been thinking of us.
I'll always remember
what a wonderful dresser you were.
So will I.
Will you two knock it off?
There's gotta be some way
to get off this ship!
There must be some angle
we haven't thought of yet.
Think, Ash.
Pikachu, give my brain a jump start.
Pika.
[Ash groans]
Thanks. That's just what I needed.
Bulbasaur, I choose you!
Bulbasaur.
All right, Bulbasaur, vine whip.
Extend your whips to the other side.
Bulba.
Bulbasaur.
-Good job.
-That was a great idea, Ash.
Yeah, we can cross the vines
to the other side.
Let's get out of here.
[whimpers]
I can't cross that inferno.
Jessie and Meowth, you go ahead.
I'm staying here.
James, James, James!
Snap out of it!
How long do you think you'd last
on this side?
Now let's go. We'll cross together.
Oh, Jessie.
Please, don't abandon me.
Don't worry. I won't leave you.
-Hey, Team Rocket!
-[all] Huh?
Bulbasaur!
[all] Wait! Don't leave us!
Send back the vine!
[creaking]
[Team Rocket pant]
Now I know what
a toasted marshmallow feels like.
Hey, no time to take a break.
-We've got to get off this ship quick.
-Right.
Charmander, I choose you.
Char!
Charmander, we need you to weld
through the metal hull of the ship
-with your flame.
-Char! Char!
Mander!
[Misty] Okay, listen up.
Grab hold of a water Pokémon
and swim to the surface.
-Yeah, right. Got it, Ash?
-I'll be okay with my Squirtle.
Hey, don't forget about us.
What are we supposed to do?
Just grab a water Pokémon.
Water Pokémon?
It's almost burned through.
-[all scream]
-Are you crazy? What have you done?
Return, Charmander!
Now, let's go, Squirtle.
Squirtle! Squirt!
[Ash] Follow us, Team Rocket!
Hold on!
We haven't got the right Pokémon!
I hate water. Especially wet water.
We're in big trouble!
We can't escape without water Pokémon!
[James laughs]
You're laughing?
[laughs]
I don't see what's so funny, James.
The poor guy must be cracking up
just like the ship.
You really made fun of me.
But who's got the last laugh now?
Well, a true genius is never appreciated
until there's trouble.
I knew we'd need this in a tight spot.
Look.
-Hey.
-Could it be?
[both] Magikarp! We're not worthy.
Feast your eyes on the king of carp.
-Magikarp.
-You're the best, James.
I take back the jokes.
From now on, I'll treat you
with the respect you deserve.
Hmm. Better late than never.
It's time, Magikarp.
Magikarp.
Lucky for us I bought this,
even if it cost next month's salary.
Enough bragging. Just tie yourself on.
We got to escape.
All right, Magikarp, let's escape.
Magikarp. Magikarp. Magikarp.
Magikarp. Magikarp. Magikarp...
[all] Huh?
Don't tell me this fish can't swim.
Forget swim. It can barely splash.
We're doomed!
[all whimpering]
[all] Looks like Team Rocket's
blasting off again!
I wonder why Team Rocket
still hasn't surfaced.
Do you think they're still trapped inside?
Pikachu?
There's nothing more we can do
except try to find some dry land.
[Ash] Let's see.
Nothing but ocean in every direction,
and no way to tell which direction to go.
I remember the story of Noah,
who, when he had to find dry land,
sent a bird to find it
and return with a branch.
What a great idea.
We're going to do the same thing as Noah.
Pidgeotto, I choose you!
[Pidgeotto screeching]
Pidgeotto,
bring us back whatever you find!
Pidgeotto!
-We're counting on you, Pidgeotto.
-Pikachu.
Huh?
Magikarp. Karp, Magikarp.
Karp, Magikarp. Karp, Magikarp. Karp...
Pidgeotto.
[Misty] They weren't able to make it.
[Ash]
Not even Team Rocket deserved this.
[Brock] Yeah.
I guess the only decent thing to do
is to give them
a traditional burial at sea.
That's right. It's our duty,
even if they were our enemies.
[grunting]
[all] Argh! Zombies!
-Who are you calling zombies?
-We are not zombies.
Somebody help! My fur's getting wet!
[groans]
Chu.
Karp, karp, karp. Karp, karp.
[stomachs rumbling]
I'm so hungry.
It seems like forever since we last ate.
If I'd known I was going to be starving,
I would've stuffed my face full
when I was on the St. Anne.
Oh, I want some food.
Stop it.
Yeah, that whining only makes you feel
even hungrier.
Karp, karp, karp. Magikarp...
Got to eat something,
like filleted carp.
Or fried carp.
Karp, karp, karp. Magikarp, karp.
-Fresh, marinated carp.
-Carp flambé.
Karp, Magikarp.
[all groan]
That's it! Dinner is now served!
[grunts]
[screaming]
I wouldn't try that again if I was you.
Check your Pokédex
'cause Magikarp is just scales and bones.
I wish you'd told me that sooner.
Ugh! Not only can this fish not swim,
it's not even good for eating.
See, I told you buying it was stupid.
You good-for-nothing fish!
I don't want to be your master!
[grunting]
Karp, karp, karp...
Good riddance, Magikarp.
-I feel sorry for it.
-[all] Huh?
Karp, karp, karp!
[roaring]
[all scream]
-What is that?
-Now you've done it.
Magikarp has evolved into Gyarados.
Gyarados? I miss Magikarp.
[Pokédex] Gyarados.
This Pokémon has a vicious temperament,
so use extreme caution.
Its fangs can crush stones
and its scales are harder than steel.
I'm James, your master. Obey me.
[roars]
[whimpers]
Dimwit! If you're the master,
don't act like you're scared of it.
But I am scared.
Goldeen! Starmie! Staryu!
Goldeen.
-How will you battle it?
-My strategy is... run away!
[all] Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
[both pant]
[roars]
[all panting]
[all] Faster! Faster!
[roars]
[all] Huh?
[Ash] What's it doing?
[Brock] It just evolved.
Maybe it's tired out.
[both] We made it!
Unless the stories are true.
[all] Huh?
What are you talking about, Misty?
Sailors tell terrible stories
about the Gyarados.
I think this might be...
It may be dragon rage.
[all]
Dragon rage?
[roaring]
[all screaming]
[all roaring]
Help! We're Gyarados bait!
-We're doomed.
-Pikachu.
[all roaring]
Hey, what are they doing?
Dragon rage.
Gyarados' ultimate attack.
[all] Here it comes!
Let's go!
No one's ever gotten away
from dragon rage!
Whoa! This is it!
[all scream]
Hey, Brock! Misty! Pikachu!
Whatever happens, don't let go!
[grunting]
Pika!
[all scream]
[narrator]
Their underwater escape ends
with our heroes trapped
in a water cyclone.
Talk about a fiendish twist of fate.
With things spiraling out of control,
will Ash and his friends
ever make it to dry land again?
Okay, guys,
we got to rap some Pokémon.
You just do the singing.
I'll take care of the hard part.
Let's get it on!
♪ I want to be the best there ever was ♪
♪ To beat all the rest
Yeah that's my cause ♪
♪ Electrode, Diglett, Nidoran, Mankey
Venusaur, Rattata, Fearow, Pidgey ♪
♪ Seaking, Jolteon, Dragonite, Gastly
Ponyta, Vaporeon, Poliwrath, Butterfree ♪
♪ Catch G'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I'll search across the land
Look far and wide ♪
♪ Release from my hand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Venomoth, Poliwag, Nidorino, Golduck
Ivysaur, Grimer, Victreebel, Moltres ♪
♪ Nidoking, Farfetch'd, Abra, Jigglypuff
Kingler, Rhyhorn, Clefable, Wigglytuff ♪
Thirty-two down, that's it for now.
Tune in tomorrow.
We'll rap you some more.
There's 150 so watch Monday to Friday.
You'll catch them all.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all Pokémon! ♪