♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
[narrator] Ash marches onward
toward Cinnabar Gym,
hoping to win his seventh badge,
but along the way,
other challenges will play
an important part in his training.
-Rhyhorn, I choose you.
-Bulbasaur! I choose you!
-Bulbasaur!
-Rhyhorn, Takedown now.
Pikachu.
-It feels like an earthquake.
-Get out of its way.
Rhyhorn's Takedown move
is like getting hit by a tank.
Bulbasaur, go! Leech Seed now!
Bulbasaur!
-Oh, no.
-That Rhyhorn must be at a high level.
-Bulba bulba. Bulbasaur.
-[growls]
Bulbasaur bulba.
Aw, Bulbasaur, return.
Bulba! Bulbasaur saur.
What are you doing, Bulbasaur?
Return.
Bulbasaur is determined
not to give up the battle till it wins.
Ha-ha-ha!
You must be a lousy trainer, kid.
It won't even listen to you.
Saur.
Pika!
You can do it, Bulbasaur! Razor Leaf!
Bulbasaur!
-Oh, Rhyhorn!
-All right!
You sure chopped me down to size, kid.
Your Bulbasaur's great.
Thanks.
Your Rhyhorn isn't so bad either.
Bulbasaur can never settle
for being second best, can it, Ash?
All of Ash's Pokémon are really stubborn
just like Ash is.
Chu?
That's the way to win, Bulbasaur.
Huh?
Bulbasaur bulba.
Is something the matter, Bulbasaur?
Are you feeling sick?
-Pikachu?
-Oh!
[groaning]
-[Ash] Bulbasaur!
-[Pikachu] Pika ka pika.
Something is really wrong
with my Bulbasaur.
-I think it must be sick.
-Hmm.
Bulba bulba.
I wonder if this Bulbasaur is...
Please, you got save it no matter what.
Please, Nurse Joy.
I can't make any promises
until I examine it,
but I'll do whatever I can.
It's got to be okay.
[gibbers]
What's the matter, Togepi?
Is something wrong? Huh?
It's happening. Now I'm positive.
Joy, is my Bulbasaur going to be okay?
You don't have to worry
about your Bulbasaur, Ash.
It isn't sick at all.
It's just getting ready to evolve.
Evolve? I can't believe it.
Bulbasaur's going to evolve.
You shouldn't be surprised.
That mountain man said
Bulbasaur was strong
and that's because you've done
such a great job training it.
[chuckles]
When Bulbasaur evolves,
it'll turn into Ivysaur, right?
Right. So how long is it going to be
till the big evolve-o-rama?
Let me see.
-Wow, just like last time.
-What do you mean?
When they brought Bulbasaur
into the center before,
I saw a vase of flowers
burst into bloom.
[all gasp]
-Hey, look. The flowers are sparkling.
-Chu.
[Joy] They say that
at a certain time of the year,
Bulbasaur gather together
from all over the world
for the festival where they evolve.
No one knows
why they choose that time.
It's different every year,
but it seems to have something to do
with the alignment of the planets
and the phases of the moon.
[Misty] It sure is beautiful.
It looks like we got here
at just the right time for the festival.
Where do the Bulbasaur go
to evolve?
Have you ever heard
of the Mysterious Garden?
The Mysterious Garden?
Cool name.
Yes, but since no human being
has ever seen the garden clearly.
Most people think
it's nothing but an illusion.
[Misty] Look at those flowers sparkle.
That's not an illusion.
The Mysterious Garden
must be someplace out there.
The Mysterious Garden,
I want to see that.
-How about you, Pikachu? Want to see it?
-[Pikachu] Pika, pika.
Bulba.
Pika?
Pikachu.
Bulbasaur.
-Pika.
-Bulba.
Pika Pika. Pikachu.
Pika Pika.
Bulbasaur. Bulba.
Bulbasaur-saur. Bulba Bulbasaur-saur.
-Pika, Pika.
-Bulba, Bulbasaur.
Pikachu.
Bulba...
-Bulba! Ugh!
-Pika, pika?
-Bulbasaur!
-[Pikachu] Pika, Pika.
[all] Bulbasaur. Bulba. Bulbasaur. Bulba.
Bulbasaur. Bulba. Bulba.
Pika! Pika!
[Bulbasaur] Bulba!
[all] Bulba! Bulba! Bulba!
Bulba! Bulba!
-[Pikachu] Pika. Pika!
-Bulba!
[sighs contentedly]
-That makes a thousand badges.
-Pika Pi! Pikachu!
[groans]
[all sigh]
-Hey, we're trying to sleep, Ash.
-What's the matter, Pikachu?
Pika Pika! Pika.
You mean something happened
to Bulbasaur?
Pika!
Um! Hey! Bulbasaur isn't in the room.
[all gasp]
Pikachu, what happened?
Do you know where it went?
Pikachu.
[Jessie chuckles]
Oh, this place is dreamy.
It makes me feel
just like a princess in a fairy tale.
I feel another sneeze coming.
I hate this sparkly stuff.
-I have allergies.
-And I'm allergic to your whining.
You both give me a rash.
Quit your jabbering. We got a job to do.
Yes! We're going to get you, Pikachu.
And there ain't nothing to it
but to do it.
[all gibbering]
-Woo, it's a Bulbasaur bonanza.
-A Bulbasaur blow-out.
A breathtaking
Bulbasaur bargain bazaar.
[all] And they're all ours.
Bulbasaur!
Our Bulbasaur bonanza went bust.
Looks like Team Rocket's...
[both] Blasting off again.
Which way, Pikachu?
-Pika.
-Hurry!
Ouch. Those Bulbasaur
are going to pay for this.
We won't take this lying down.
[Brock] This way.
Follow that stream of pollen.
[Ash]
It should lead us straight to Bulbasaur.
[Misty]
We must be near the mysterious garden.
Ah! What's that?
This whole forest is going crazy. Huh?
Look, those vines are trying
to block our way.
There's no way a bunch of stupid vines are
going to stop me from rescuing Bulbasaur.
Dive through!
[all grunt]
Oh, that was a close one.
Ugh. Now I'm beginning to understand
why nobody's seen
the Mysterious Garden before.
There's only one way to go now,
into the garden.
-[Pikachu] Pika!
-What is it, Pikachu?
[all gasp]
Wow, this must be the Mysterious Garden.
[all sing] Bulba! Bulba! Bulbasaur!
Bulba! Bulba! Bulbasaur!
Bulba...
-Wow! That's neat.
-Oh, it's so pretty.
[thumping]
What's that banging sound?
Saur!
-Look, you guys, it's a Venusaur.
-It's giant.
[Pokédex] Venusaur, the final form
of the Bulbasaur evolution.
This seed Pokémon soaks up
the sun's rays as a source of energy.
Hmm, but that kind of behavior
makes it sound like a plant.
I don't see my Bulbasaur
anyplace around here.
Hey, Ash, your Bulbasaur still
has that bandage on its head.
-Hmm.
-Ka!
Hey, there it is.
Over here, Bulba... Urgh.
Hey, don't forget human beings
aren't supposed to be here.
-Oh, right.
-Let's watch the festival.
-Saur!
-[all] Saur
Bulbasaur.
-Saur!
-[all] Saur
[all gasp]
[all groan]
How do we get in there?
Why doesn't Meowth just scratch
his way through with his claws?
I just filed them.
-All right, garden wall, you axed for it.
-We're the toughest team you ever saw.
Let's cut to the chase.
[all groaning]
A timber-tantrum, eh?
Let's get to the root of its problem.
[grunting and groaning]
I think its bite is as bad as its bark.
-Ivysaur.
-All right.
[Pokédex]
The seed Pokémon Ivysaur.
Bulbasaur's evolved form.
The bulb on its back absorbs nourishment
and blooms into a large flower.
-Saur!
-[all] Saur
This must be their evolution festival.
For a long time,
people have disagreed
whether Bulbasaur is an animal type
Pokémon or a plant type.
If either plants or animals disappeared
from the planet, life wouldn't go on.
[Misty]
They need each other to live and grow.
Pika.
Maybe the Bulbasaur are a sign
that all life on earth is connected.
Maybe you're right.
I wonder if my Bulbasaur's
going to evolve too.
-Ah!
-Huh?
Hmm, it's not evolving.
-[grunting]
-[Ash] Why not?
it looks like it's trying not to evolve.
Pika.
Venus... Venusaur.
-Venusaur.
-Bulba.
-Venus. Venusaur.
-Bulba. Bulbasaur.
Venusaur. Venusaur. Venusaur.
Bulbasaur. Bulba. Bulba.
Bulbasaur. Saur.
Venusaur. Venusaur!
Venusaur.
Bulbasaur.
[Misty] The others are getting
really angry at Bulbasaur.
I wonder why.
Bulbasaur's even more stubborn
than you.
-Venusaur!
-Bulba!
-Hey!
-Pika!
-Leave it alone.
-Pika.
[groans]
-Pika Pik!
-Bulbasaur!
[sighs and then chuckles]
-Ash.
-Are you okay?
-Ven...
-Asaur.
-Are they mad at us too?
-I don't think they're too thrilled.
Venusaur.
Sorry we broke in on your festival
but the Bulbasaur
you're angry at is my friend.
The reason you're so mad is
because it doesn't want to evolve, right?
[all] Venusaur!
You probably feel like it ruined your
festival and I'm very sorry about that.
But if Bulbasaur doesn't
want to evolve yet,
I don't think you should
have right to force it to.
Venusaur!
[Brock]
Whoa, they're manipulating nature.
If Bulbasaur evolves,
it could do that too.
Don't you want to have
that kind of power, Bulbasaur?
Bulba.
Sorry I got so excited about you evolving
without even thinking about
whether you wanted to do it or not.
Bulbasaur.
Now, look, you can't just force
Bulbasaur to do what you want.
Bulbasaur has a right to decide
when it's ready to evolve.
-[James] The pest is right.
-Saur?
[Jessie]
You've got to choose your own path.
[James] And when our path to
the Mysterious Garden was blocked...
[Jessie]
We decided to rise above it all.
[Meowth]
And we provide our own hot air.
Now we'll have to prepare for trouble.
-[Jessie] Prepare for trouble.
-[James] Make it double.
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation.
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James.
[Jessie] Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
[James]
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Stop wasting time.
Start the machine up.
-We need the motto.
-Our fans have come to expect it.
[Jessie] Let's get started.
Here we go... again.
[chuckles]
-Hit it.
-Suction on.
[all groaning] Bulbasaur!
-It's a vacuum!
-No kidding!
-It's really working.
-It's a suck-cess.
[all yell] Saur! Bulbasaur!
[chuckles] It's trying to save them.
-Turn up the suction full-power.
-Roger.
Venusaur!
Pikachu, use your thunder
to bring down their balloon.
-Pika.
-No, wait!
A thunder attack might hurt
the Ivysaur that Team Rocket captured.
-We got to do something.
-Pika!
-Ah! Pikachu!
-Saur!
-Pika Pi! Pi, pika, ka.
-[chuckles] Pikachu!
-Pika pi.
Thanks, Bulbasaur.
Try to let the air out of their balloon
with your Razor Leaf attack.
Bulbasaur!
-Oh!
-Bulba.
Venus.
All that's left is a puny, little
Bulbasaur. Should we get it?
[both] A Bulbasaur? Ha, ha.
Who needs a Bulbasaur?
Bulba!
-What a wimp.
-[James] You can keep that runt.
[Team Rocket chuckling]
Hey, stop making fun of my Bulbasaur.
Bulba! Bulba!
What's that?
[Pokédex]
Solarbeam, Bulbasaur's strongest attack.
Light is collected and formed
into a powerful beam with intensive force.
Like a super strong sunbeam.
I didn't know you could do that.
Bulba.
Okay, Bulbasaur,
get ready to use your Solarbeam.
-Pika!
-Bulbasaur! Bulbasaur! Bulbasaur!
[gibbers]
Fire the Solarbeam!
Bulba!
[all groan]
[all gasp]
Smoking.
Bulba!
[all] Bulbasaur! Bulbasaur! Bulbasaur!
Bulbasaur! Bulbasaur! Bulbasaur...
[grunting]
[groaning]
Venusaur.
Bulbasaur.
[groaning]
-Things look bad.
-Oh, they're about to get worse.
Saur!
-Saur!
[all]
Team Rocket's blasting off again.
-Great job, Bulbasaur.
-Bulbasaur.
-That was amazing.
-You're the greatest.
[all gasp]
[grunts]
Uh-oh.
[all gasp]
Venusaur.
Bulba.
Bulbasaur.
-I guess Venusaur finally understands.
-I think you're right.
Pikachu.
Hey. The Mysterious Garden.
After the evolution festival,
it must disappear.
Yeah, I'm sure glad
we were here to see it.
Goodbye, Venusaur and Ivysaur.
-[Misty] I hope we see you again.
-[Brock] See you later.
-Bulbasaur.
-Pikachu.
[narrator] And so Ash and his friends
leave the incredible Mysterious Garden.
No one knows if or when Bulbasaur
will finally decide to evolve.
No one, that is, except Bulbasaur.
Bulbasaur.
Okay, guys,
we gotta rap some Pokémon.
You just do the singing.
I'll take care of the hard part.
Let's get it on!
♪ I want to be the best
There ever was ♪
♪ To beat all the rest
Yeah, that's my cause ♪
♪ Electrode, Diglett, Nidoran, Mankey
Venusaur, Rattata, Fearow, Pidgey ♪
♪ Seaking, Jolteon, Dragonite, Gastly
Ponyta, Vaporeon, Poliwrath, Butterfree ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I'll search across the land
Look far and wide ♪
♪ Release from my hand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Venomoth, Poliwag, Nidorino, Golduck
Ivysaur, Grimer, Victreebel, Moltres ♪
♪ Nidoking, Farfetch'd, Abra, Jigglypuff
Kingler, Rhyhorn, Clefable, Wigglytuff ♪
Thirty-two down, that’s it for now.
Tune in tomorrow,
we'll rap at you some more.
There's 150,
so watch Monday through Friday.
You'll catch 'em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪