♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon! Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, gotta catch 'em all
[narrator] Ash and his friends
arrive in Celadon City,
the great metropolis
renowned for both its tall buildings
and for its good scents.
Mm. Pika!
[sniffs]
-Something smells heavenly.
-Perfume.
Hey, what's going on?
[sniffs] Eeh!
Wait, Brock! Where are you going?
[Ash] Pokémon Scent-Sation!
[chuckles]
Who are you making faces at, Brock?
My nose tells me
that this is my kind of town.
Huh?
So, then he says
maybe we can both go together.
I think we should stay here a while.
Well, if you want to waste your time.
Misty, Pikachu, let's get moving.
Misty? Pikachu?
Hm?
This scent is one of our most popular.
It's called Daffodil Dreams.
-[sniffs] It smells just like a garden.
-Pika!
We're having a fragrance sale.
-How much does this one cost?
-Pikachu.
Don't buy it, Misty.
Perfume's just a waste of money,
and it stinks.
Go away.
[woman] I resent that remark.
[all] Huh?
[saleswoman] The manager.
Young man, are you accusing me
of overcharging my customers
for inferior perfume?
Uh, no, ma'am.
I meant all perfumes are a rip-off
because all they do is turn guys
into zombies, like this.
[chuckling]
Hi, what's your name?
Hmm. Mm!
P for pretty, E for elegant,
R for radiant,
F for fun, U for urbane,
M for mysterious, E for energy,
-and that spells?
-Perfume.
-Right!
-Pika!
I don't need that smelly junk to give me
energy. I'm full of it.
I got tons more energy
than I know what to do with.
Why don't you use some of it
to keep your mouth shut?
If you object to our products so much,
perhaps you should leave,
since we all sell perfume here,
you must find us offensive.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
You insensitive little worm.
What did I say?
Get out and don't come back!
I don't want to come back!
I'm on my way to the Celadon City Gym.
What do you mean I can't I come in?
I'm trying to become a Pokémon master.
I wouldn't let you in if you were the last
Pokémon trainer on earth.
-Huh?
-This Gym doesn't allow anyone inside
who says that perfume is a stinky rip-off.
Why not?
We manufacture that stinky perfume
right here in this Gym.
Uh-oh.
So you see, young man...
-[Ash] Ah!
-You're the stinker!
[groans]
But don't you understand?
I got to challenge your Gym Master
so I can win a badge.
You've got to let me in!
Huh? [blows raspberry]
[groans]
Pretty please, with a cherry on top?
Huh. Looks like the coast is clear.
Once we break inside, we'll steal
the secret formula for their perfume.
Then I'll be as irresistible as Cleopatra.
I'll sell the formula
and make myself zillions of bucks.
That's enough money
to buy my own country,
or my own planet even.
Or nine lifetime supplies of cat grub.
That secret formula's got to be hidden
around here somewhere. Hmm.
Now, where could it be?
Hmm.
Huh.
Ah! [groaning]
What is it?
Hey, look.
[snores and grunts]
What's a Gloom doing here?
Taking a nap, I think.
[grunts]
Gloom.
[all gasp]
James, you've woken it up.
Go, Koffing.
Poison gas attack, now!
Koffing!
[trills]
That Gloom just sucked up
all of Koffing's gas.
I can't believe it.
Gloom?
[all yell]
Gloom, Gloom! Gloom!
[Team Rocket gagging]
It smells terrible!
It smells like old sneakers
mixed with some rotten eggs and dead fish
with just a hint of skunk fumes.
[both groan]
-[both whimper]
-My nose feels like it's on fire.
-Meowth, you don't have a nose.
-Huh?
My nose! What happened?
The stink dissolved it off my face.
Hm? Oh.
Oh, yeah, I almost forgot.
The cartoonist never gave me a nose.
Hey, why are you sleeping?
[Meowth groans]
That stopped them.
Gym rules, no thieves allowed.
Hey, get me down! Get me out of here!
You two clowns
better get me out of this tree!
Don't tell me what to do,
you little hairball!
I know what I'm doing.
-Are you three hanging out again?
-Huh? The pest.
Please, could you help us
get out of this tree?
-Traitor!
-Ugh!
-How dare you collaborate with the enemy?
-Whose side are you on?
[grunting]
Huh? Hmm.
Hey, kid.
Bet they wouldn't let you
in that Gym today.
That's none of your business.
They kicked you out.
Even though you're a pest,
I'll make a deal.
Untie us and we'll show you
how to get in that Gym.
Why should I trust you?
Face the facts, boy.
You can't get into the Pokémon League
without winning more badges.
[groaning]
-Bing...
-Bong...
Bing!
[all] Ta-da!
[all] Oh!
Great wig.
Not even your own mother
would recognize you in this outfit.
Think so?
Talk about dressing for success,
that getup will get you into the Gym easy.
Great! Then I'll show that Gym Leader
who's the boss around here.
Uh, that doesn't sound very ladylike.
-Huh?
-You'll give away your secret.
-Go on, try it.
-Try it.
Ahem!
[high-pitched] I'll show those meanies.
[both laugh]
Good evening.
We would like to enroll our daughter,
Ashley,
in your Pokémon training classes.
Nothing but the best
for our little princess.
[Meowth] That's right.
-[Meowth] Ow!
-Hm?
Do you like perfume?
[high-pitched] Oh, yes.
Well, then, I'm sure you'll be accepted.
Your parents should apply at the desk.
Way to scam them, Goldilocks!
[grunting]
[woman]
Are you applying to the Gym, little girl?
[deep voice] Uh, yeah. [gasps]
[thinks] The girl in the perfume shop.
[high-pitched] I mean, yes, ma'am.
We're so proud to have our little muffin
in your Gym.
-Yes, we sure are.
-Cut it out.
Ma'am, where is Erika, the Gym Master?
Oh, you'll meet her soon.
[thinks] All right. Now all I got to do
is beat Erika, and I'll get another badge.
-[Jessie] Bye-bye.
-Hmm?
Hugs and kisses, Ashley.
Mommy and Daddy are leaving you
to battle those cute little Pokémon.
-Bye, sweetie.
-See you soon.
Hmm. While that clueless little twerp
creates a distraction,
-we'll steal the secret perfume formula.
-Let's go.
Just one question,
what am I supposed to do
with this blaster ball?
Stick it someplace
where it'll make a nice, big kaboom.
[cackles] They'll get a bang out of this.
Jessie, what's the blaster ball for?
Sweet revenge for stamping an
on the most beautiful face in the world.
Talk about delusions.
What?
Uh, I mean, that'll teach those slobs.
[both laugh]
One, two, one, two, one, two...
[woman] Remember, a pretty Pokémon
is a strong Pokémon.
And so Omanyte bid farewell
and promised to one day return
to visit the friends who changed his life
on that faraway beach.
The end.
-Great story.
-Pika.
Uh-oh.
How'd Misty and Brock get here?
-[woman] Trainer Erika.
-Hm?
Erika.
[woman]
I'd like to introduce our new student.
Oh, welcome.
Ah!
[thinks] The store manager.
Oh...
Nice to meet you.
[high-pitched]
Thank you, ma'am.
You sure are a shy young lady,
but don't worry.
All the girls want to make you feel
at home here at the Gym.
Let's all give her a warm welcome.
-Pikachu!
-Oh!
[thinks]
Oh, great. Pikachu's here too.
[Misty] May I ask you a question?
Of course you may, Misty.
I was wondering
why we can all sit with Gloom.
I always thought
that because of its terrible smell,
it was almost impossible
to get anywhere near Gloom.
So how come this Gloom
doesn't smell bad to me at all?
That's a very smart question, Misty.
Gloom doesn't have a bad smell
all the time.
Whenever Gloom is in danger,
it lets out the bad smell.
It's a natural defense mechanism.
But as long as Gloom doesn't feel
threatened, it smells just fine.
Just make sure Gloom feels safe
and show you want to be its friend.
-How do you know all that?
-I met Gloom a long time ago.
[sobs]
Grimer!
[Erika] When I was a little girl,
I got lost one day and ran into a Grimer.
I'd never been so scared.
I couldn't even move.
[whimpering]
Please, can you help me?
Please, help me.
[Erika] Somehow that Gloom
understood how scared I felt
and decided to come to my rescue.
Gloom!
Grimer!
[giggles] I love you!
Gloom!
This is the same Gloom
that rescued me from Grimer that day.
We've been friends ever since.
It's all because of her friendship
with Gloom
that Erika decided to become
a grass Pokémon trainer.
I wish Ash could've heard that story.
-[Ash in normal voice] I heard it.
-[all gasp]
Ah! Uh...
[high voice] Please don't stare at me
like that. I'm a very shy little girl.
You look awfully familiar.
Haven't we met someplace before?
[high-pitched]
Maybe you met my sister.
-Pi?
-Ah!
Pika-pi!
[normal voice]
Hey, knock it off.
Pika!
-[all] Oh!
-[Ash screams]
[both] It's Ash!
Yeah, it's me.
You're that boy.
Erika, you wouldn't let me in,
so I wore this stupid disguise.
I had to sneak into your Gym
so I could battle you for a badge.
And now I want to challenge you.
[laughs]
At last we've found the perfume.
Now we'll unlock its secret formula.
I accept your challenge.
It's my duty under the league rules.
We'll each use three Pokémon.
Right. I'll use my own grass Pokémon
against yours.
Bulbasaur, I choose you!
Bulbasaur!
This ought to be easy.
Tangela, I choose you!
[squealing]
What's that?
[Pokédex]
Tangela, a vine Pokémon.
Its body is wrapped in vines.
The rest of its form
is hidden beneath these vines.
That doesn't tell me much.
All right, we'll attack from a distance.
Bulbasaur, vine whip!
Tangela, constrict!
Resist it from pulling you in.
Bulbasaur!
-Ah!
-Bulbasaur!
Tangela, now is the time to hit it
with your stun spore.
[grunts]
Return, Bulbasaur!
[squealing]
Poor Bulbasaur!
Later I'll give you some Paralyze Heal
to make your Pokémon better.
Thanks, but no thanks.
I don't need your help.
I choose Primeape.
Uh, maybe I better not.
Charmander, go!
Charman.
This should be easy.
Weepinbell, go!
-Bell.
-Weepinbell, razor leaf now!
[gibbers]
Charmander, flamethrower, full blast!
Char!
[gasps]
Yes, way to go.
Now let's just finish it up.
Skull bash, now!
Uh! Weepinbell, return now!
-Ash is doing well.
-He might actually win.
Yeah, he's a lot more impressive
than he looks.
Your battle skills are impressive, Ash.
But there's one thing you don't have:
empathy with your Pokémon.
Without it, you'll never become
a great Pokémon trainer like me.
Now I'm going to give you a lesson
in empathy.
Gloom, go!
Gloom.
[both gasp]
Gloom!
Char! Char!
[groans]
Oh! Charmander, return!
[laughs] Poor Ash.
Your Pokémon could use
some more training.
[thinks] If Gloom beats Charmander,
what Pokémon can I use next?
Squirtle, Pidgeotto and Pikachu
couldn't take that terrible smell.
Chu!
-Pikachu?
-Pika.
You're saying you want to battle?
Pikachu.
You know you're probably going to lose,
but you're still willing to battle Gloom
to help me out?
-Pika, pika!
-What? You say you're sure you'll win?
-Pikachu! Pika-pi.
-Oh, Pikachu.
Heartwarming, but what's that smell?
What?
Your Pokémon skills are stinking up
this Gym even worse than Gloom.
[Misty] It's Team Rocket!
To protect the world from devastation...
To unite all peoples within our nation...
To denounce the evils of truth and love...
To extend our reach to the stars above...
And last, but not least,
to blast this dump sky-high!
-Jessie!
-James!
[all screaming]
Where did you put that blast ball?
Near us so I wouldn't lose it. Ah!
At least we get this lovely parting gift,
their secret perfume formula.
What?
[both] Team Rocket's blasting off again!
Quick, girls, we've got to rescue
all the Pokémon fast!
Quick, now! Get into the Poké Ball
and I'll carry you to safety.
Hurry! Now!
-Hurry.
-[woman 1] There's some over here!
-[woman 2] There's a Pokémon!
-[woman 3] We've got to get them all.
-[woman 4] Keep looking. Look everywhere.
-[woman 5] Call the fire department!
[woman 6] They're on their way.
Pika, pika.
Cha.
[groans]
[thinks] I should never have listened
to Team Rocket.
-Don't just stand around, Ash!
-Huh?
Help us to put out the fire before
this whole Gym is burnt to the ground.
Yeah, all right.
Squirtle, water gun!
Staryu, Starmie, help us out now!
Squirtle!
[gibbers]
Geodude! Throw as much dirt
as you can on the flames!
Dude.
Geodude, Geodude, Geodude.
-Keep on spraying!
-We've almost got it!
[pants]
Erika, what's the matter?
I've looked and looked,
but I can't find Gloom anywhere.
-Did Gloom get out?
-Huh?
What if Gloom...?
What if Gloom's still inside?
-Ah!
-[Misty] You can't go in there, Erika!
[Erika]
But Gloom may be trapped inside.
-I'll go in and find Gloom!
-Don't, Ash!
Gloom?
Gloom!
Huh? Ah!
Gloom, Gloom!
Don't worry, Gloom.
I promise I'll get you out of here!
Argh! [grunts]
I can't get closer to that smell.
Gloom!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[groans]
It's okay, Gloom.
It's going to be okay.
[grunting]
[mumbles] It's too much!
I can't hold my breath any longer.
[exhales]
Huh? There's no smell.
[gasps]
As long as Gloom doesn't feel threatened,
it smells just fine.
Just make sure Gloom feels safe
and show you want to be its friend.
Hm.
Come on. Let's go, Gloom.
Gloom, Gloom!
-Pikachu.
-[gasping]
All right, hey!
-Ash!
-[Misty] That was great!
[Erika] Thank you, Ash.
With deep gratitude,
I present you with this rainbow badge.
-What's that for?
-I think you earned it.
-Don't you, Gloom?
-Gloom, Gloom.
Thanks a lot.
Take a look, Pikachu. A rainbow badge.
-Pi, Pikachu!
-Gloom, Gloom.
-Congratulations, Ash.
-Thanks.
Uh, but what about Team Rocket?
They got away
with your secret perfume formula.
[giggles] No, they didn't.
The bottle they stole has only one
of our perfume's secret ingredients:
essence of Gloom.
-Hm?
-[all yell]
It stinks!
Just like your plan.
You said it!
[narrator] And so, in the race for
a rainbow badge, it's Ash by a nose.
But most valuable of all,
Ash has learned an important lesson,
you can't judge a Pokémon by its smell.
Okay, guys,
we gotta rap some Pokémon.
You just do the singing
I'll take care of the hard part.
Let's get it on!
♪ I want to be the best
There ever was ♪
♪ To beat all the rest, yeah
That's my cause ♪
♪ Electrode, Diglett, Nidoran, Mankey
Venusaur, Rattata, Fearow, Pidgey ♪
♪ Seaking, Jolteon, Dragonite, Gastly
Ponyta, Vaporeon, Poliwrath, Butterfree ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I'll search across the land
Look far and wide ♪
♪ Release from my hand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Venomoth, Poliwag, Nidorino, Golduck
Ivysaur, Grimer, Victreebel, Moltres ♪
♪ Nidoking, Farfetch'd, Abra, Jigglypuff
Kingler, Rhyhorn, Clefable, Wigglytuff ♪
Thirty-two down,
that's it for now.
Tune in tomorrow,
we’ll rap at you some more.
There’s 150,
so watch Monday Through Friday.
You’ll catch ‘em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all, ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪