♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
[groans]
All right. Where's this famous
Fuchsia Gym we're looking for anyway?
I can't believe there's a gym
out in the middle of nowhere like this.
-Pikachu.
-Hmm.
[narrator] As our heroes travel
toward their next adventure
at the Fuchsia Gym,
they pass through a deep forest
where they find themselves...
[both] I think it's that way!
[narrator] Completely lost.
[Psyduck] Psy...
Well, let's get going.
I got to get to that Fuchsia Gym
and win another badge.
Wait a minute. Let's wait for Psyduck.
Psy.
Psyduck, cold water
can make a headache even worse.
Psy?
Sometimes I just look at that Psyduck face
and I get a headache.
-What beautiful hair.
-Huh?
Suzie's such a great breeder.
Hey, Brock. How about a trade?
That Vulpix for my Psyduck?
No way.
It wouldn't take much time to brush
'cause Psyduck only has three hairs.
Psy.
Come on, guys. We better get going.
Hold on.
If we fall, our Pokémon journey's over.
-Pikachu.
-Ah!
Are you sure Fuchsia Gym
is somewhere around here?
-Pika!
-[both] Huh?
[Ash] Huh? What's that?
[Misty] That's weird. A huge mansion
right in the middle of nowhere.
[Brock] I didn't know
any old houses like this still existed.
Well, at least we can ask somebody here
the way to the Fuchsia Gym.
Hello? Is anybody here?
Is anyone home?
[Brock] Seems deserted.
[Ash] Hello.
Hm. Ah!
Huh? Misty?
-Kachu.
-What's wrong? Where's Misty?
-Chu!
-She's gone.
-Ash, this is a secret door.
-Secret door?
When you touch this wall, it opens.
Ow.
Brock, what kind of crazy place is this?
It sure isn't
your run-of-the-mill mansion.
-Pikachu.
-[both] Huh?
-[squeaking] Venonat!
-What's that?
[Pokédex]
Venonat. A bug Pokémon.
It's eyes function as radar,
allowing it to see in the dark.
Venonat.
Hey, that's not a run-of-the-mill Pokémon.
Hey, wait up!
Where is the owner of this place?
Venonat!
-Say what?
-Maybe it wants us to follow it, Ash.
-Chu.
-Let's go see.
Yeah!
Ah!
Pikachu. Why did you do that to me?
-Chu-chu.
-Well, if you didn't do it, then...
Ash, look there!
[zapping]
Doesn't look friendly. Wonder what it is.
[Pokédex] Voltorb.
The identity of this creature is unknown.
It has an extreme personality,
uses electric attacks,
and at times, self-destructs.
Voltorb.
This place gets weirder and weirder.
Where'd Venonat go?
-[Misty] Look. Over there.
-Hey! Wait up.
Whoa! [groaning]
-Ah.
-Ash, what is it? What happened?
-It's an invisible wall.
-An invisible wall?
[groans]
Brock, this place is really giving me
the creeps.
Right. We better get out of here
while we still have the chance.
Yeah, come on, Ash. Let's go.
[groans]
-It's another invisible wall.
-[shouts]
I think we've fallen into somebody's trap.
-A trap?
I hope they're not trying to trap us
so they can steal our Pokémon.
Huh?
'cause I don't want them
to take away my Vulpix.
Come on, Brock.
We gotta get out of this place.
Maybe there's an exit. Ah!
[both] Ah!
-[both] Ash!
-Pika, pi!
-Oh, no, he's gone.
-Oh, Ash.
Pikachu.
-[Ash] Hey, guys! I'm still alive.
-[both] Huh?
Here! Down here.
Come on. Help me up!
Oh, that was close.
This is a dangerous place
if you're not careful.
-[door creaks]
-[both] Huh?
[Ash] Venonat?
It's you. I'm going to teach you a lesson.
Come back! Ah!
Whoa! [screams]
-[both] Ash!
-Kachu!
Huh? Where is he?
[Brock]
There must be another way out.
Maybe it's just another trick.
-Someone help me.
-Huh?
-[laughing maniacally]
Born in darkness, living in darkness,
such is the fate of the ninja.
I am Aya, ninja warrior.
But don't you think that color
is a little bright for a ninja?
I don't need your fashion report.
But tell me, didn't you enjoy
my little star treatment?
You can't just chuck
throwing stars around.
-It's dangerous.
-That's right. Tell her, Brock.
-Huh?
-[moans]
I think that electric pink
suits you perfectly,
and you certainly look lovely.
-Ah! [chuckles]
-Whoa.
[grunts] This is a training camp.
It was your fault you let your guard down.
My guard down?
I won't let you leave this mansion
without first having a Pokémon battle
with me first.
-Huh?
-Venonat.
[Ash] Oh, that thing.
[Aya]
This Venonat informed me
that three stupid-looking people
had entered the mansion.
Venonat. [squeals]
For your information
we're not the stupid ones around here.
I accept your challenge!
Uh, but first
could you let me down from here?
Ah!
One Pokémon for each of us.
Choose yours now.
Bulbasaur, I choose you!
Bulbasaur.
-I select Venonat.
-Venonat.
-Bulbasaur! Tackle now!
-[grunting]
-Venonat!
-Sar!
-Venonat, stun spore.
-[shrieking]
Bulbasaur, whirlwind.
Now! Vine whip!
Venonat! Venonat!
Psybeam now.
-Bulbasaur!
-[groaning]
Hang in there, Bulbasaur!
Now it's time to give it your leech seed!
-Bulbasaur!
-Venonat!
[shrieking]
Venonat?
[chuckles] Leech seed is sucking away
your Venonat's power.
-It's helpless.
-Bulbasaur. Bulbasaur.
Return, Venonat.
Good work, Bulbasaur. A victory for me.
-[grumbles]
-Voltorb.
It's that Voltorb!
[all coughing]
You've still got a lot to learn, Aya.
Honored brother, I have failed.
And you're Aya's older brother?
My name is Brock.
You sure have a very nice sister.
It's a pleasure to meet... Ah!
This is no time to kiss up, Brock.
None of you will be permitted
to leave this venerable mansion
unless you do battle with me.
Who are you?
I am Koga,
the Pokémon master of the Fuchsia Gym.
-Oh, so this is the Fuchsia Gym?
-That is correct, miss.
-Well, at least we're in the right place.
-[beeping]
[Meowth]
So that's the famous ninja mansion.
Well, I for one am not impressed.
It looks like a Japanese restaurant.
There are lots of precious
poisonous Pokémon in that mansion.
Then let's figure a way
to bust into this ninja joint,
snatch the poison Pokémon
and hit the road.
Poisonous Pokémon are positively perfect
for perfidious people like us.
-What does that mean?
-It means beautiful things can be painful.
Ow. That hurt.
-Let's go.
-Ooh!
Well, that's fine with me.
We were looking for Fuchsia Gym,
and now I'll win one of your badges.
[Koga] This soul badge will be yours
if you defeat me, of course.
All right, let's battle.
We shall have two-on-two Pokémon battle,
young man.
That's fine with me.
I'll start with Pidgeotto!
Then I shall lead with Venonat.
[squawks]
[laughs] Guess I'll just have to beat
this Venonat, too.
[laughs] This Venonat
has a great deal more experience.
-[Ash gasps]
-Venomoth! Venomoth! Venomoth!
-A metamorphosis attack?
-No, it just evolved.
[Pokédex]
Venomoth. An evolved form of Venonat.
Tiny scales on its wings
disperse various spores
-when they are flapped.
-Uh-oh.
-Venomoth, stun spore.
-Venomoth!
-Pidgeotto, whirlwind!
-[screams]
-Pidgeotto!
-Venomoth, release your sleep powder.
[shrieking]
Oh. Pidgeotto, return.
Charmander, go!
Venomoth, stun spore.
-Charmander! Flamethrower!
-Char!
Great job, Charmander.
Huh? What's that?
[both]
Welcome to the show.
What's going on here?
[Jessie]
Now let our ancient performance begin.
Prepare for trouble.
[James grunting rapidly]
Make it double.
[rapid grunting]
To protect the world from devastation.
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James.
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare.
Prepare to fight.
Meowth. That's right.
Now step aside while we pick up
all your pretty little poisonous Pokémon.
-Forget it, Meowth.
-[groaning]
Jessie, it's too hard to move
in these costumes.
A ninja mansion calls for a kabuki star.
-We have to wear these outfits.
-Yes, but--
If you can't move, we'll lose the Pokémon.
You're right. Let's change.
[grumbling]
We'll have to join forces
-to vanquish them.
-Right.
-Charmander, go!
-Char!
-Go, Venomoth.
-Go, Venonat.
Step right up. Ha!
[all screaming]
-Huh?
-Oh.
-Ah, Pikachu.
-Pika!
-You're in the way.
-[screaming]
-Pika.
-Pikachu!
-Pika, pi!-
We need you now, Starmie!
Psyduck.
-Psyduck! You're not Starmie!
-Psy?
[groans] This time I'll choose Staryu.
Psy?
You're Psyduck, not Staryu.
Don't you understand?
[grumbles] Fine, then.
Go if you want to.
-Psyduck. Psy.
-[groaning]
-Psy!
-Psyduck, you're driving me crazy!
Psy-i-i-i.
-Psyduck. Psyduck.
-What attacks can Psyduck do?
Here, ask Dexter.
Psyduck's attacks are, one, tail whip.
Psyduck. Tail whip attack now!
-Psyduck. Psyduck. Psy...
-[all groan]
How can you call that lame tail wag
an attack?
It must have other attacks.
Psyduck attacks. Number two: scratch.
-All right, Psyduck. Scratch attack now!
-Psyduck.
Psy. [grunting]
Psy.
Psy!
Psyduck! Psyduck! Psyduck!
What a totally pathetic Pokémon.
-Now it's giving me a headache.
-I think I have a way out of this.
-[both] Huh?
-What are they?
I don't know what they are,
but they're in the way.
[grunts]
[squeaking]
This is a nice little catch.
I don't know what these things are,
but I can use them
to practice my bowling game.
[whimpering] That's a Voltorb!
A Voltorb?
-Voltorb.
-Ah!
[all coughing]
-Hey, Brock.
Do you notice anything weird
about this room?
The walls, the beams, the ceiling,
they're all on a slant.
This is a slanted room
to confuse our enemies.
[groaning]
-No good. I can't get it off.
-Char.
How about your electric attack, Pikachu?
-Kachu!
-Char.
Pikachu.
This gunk isn't affected by electricity.
-[low rumbling]
-Huh?
There you are.
For some reason
I seem to be losing my liqui-ebrium.
[both]
Whoa!
They built this place like a fun house.
The floor is slanted.
Maybe they'll have some fun
with this Voltorb.
Voltorb.
[all scream]
[grunts] Pikachu! Electric attack now.
Pika, pika.
Oh, I forgot.
What's with this loser Pokémon?
Psyduck, you're just
going to get hurt out there. Return!
[groans]
Psy-i-i-i!
[grunts]
You're in the way!
[gibbers angrily]
-Let's snatch this Pokémon, too.
-We don't need Pokémon like that.
[gibbers angrily]
Even rejected by Team Rocket.
It looks like its headache's
getting worse.
-Uh, look. You come here right now.
-Huh?
[screams]
-Ah! What's...? What's happening?
-I... I'm frozen. I can't move!
Hey, this must be one Psyduck's attacks.
[Pokédex]
Psyduck's attacks. Number three: disable.
[whimpering]
[Pokédex]
Psyduck's attacks. Number four: confusion.
[all screaming]
-Psyduck's attacks are pretty good.
-Yeah.
-You're right.
-[all screaming]
This place looks a lot nicer from the air.
And what else it looks like--
[all] Team Rocket's blasting off again!
Psy.
[whimpering]
-Pika.
-Char!
[groans and Brock sighs]
And you had that kind of power all along?
[Pokédex] When Psyduck's headache
becomes severe, it uses amazing power.
Psy-i-i-duck.
-That kind of talent's a real pain.
-Oh, yeah.
Magnificent.
That was quite an impressive display.
I was very impressed by your performance.
Young lady, would you consider
trading your Psyduck for my Venomoth?
I'd gladly trade for my Venonat.
Well, I wouldn't trade Psyduck
for any Pokémon in the world.
Misty, you couldn't wait
to get rid of Psyduck.
A woman's heart
can be a very fickle thing, Ash.
A Pokémon like that would certainly merit
one of our soul badges.
Uh, that's right.
We still haven't finished our match.
The Pokémon I choose for this battle
is Charmander.
And I will choose, Golbat!
-Golbat.
-[sighs] What's that?
[Pokédex]
Golbat. Attacking with its sharp fangs,
this Pokémon can drain
300 cubic centimeters of blood per bite.
-Be careful, Charmander.
-Golbat. Wing attack.
Golbat. Golbat. Golbat. Golbat.
Charmander. Ember attack.
Charmander!
Golbat. Golbat.
[gibbering]
-All right. Good job, Charmander.
-Golbat. Golbat.
Golbat, use your screech attack.
Golbat. Golbat.
[grunting]
-Ooh, I can't stand that noise.
-Ah! I'm getting goose bumps.
Charmander, flamethrower.
Char! Char! Char!
Ouch.
Golbat. Golbat. Golbat.
Okay. Finish it off with fire spin.
[yelling]
Golbat. Golbat.
[all gasp]
Golbat.
-We did it.
-Char, char.
You have beaten me.
And Psyduck saved my Voltorb
from being stolen by those thieves.
This soul badge rightfully belongs to you.
A soul badge! All right!
We both have got a lot to learn
about battle.
-We will now train even harder, Aya.
-Yes, brother.
Yes! I got a soul badge!
All right! Woo-hoo!
[narrator]
So after earning a soul badge,
our heroes continue along
on their Pokémon journey.
You know, you did a really great job
back there, Psyduck.
I hope success doesn't go to your head.
Psyduck.
You guys up for the Pokérap?
There's 150 Pokémon
you gotta name 'em all.
I'm doing 32 today so try to keep up.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon♪
♪ Zubat, Primeape, Meowth, Onix ♪
♪ Geodude, Rapidash, Magneton, Snorlax ♪
♪ Gengar, Tangela, Goldeen, Spearow ♪
♪ Weezing, Seel, Gyarados, Slowbro ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Kabuto, Persian
Paras, Horsea. ♪
♪ Raticate, Magnemite
Kadabra, Weepinbell ♪
♪ Ditto, Cloyster, Caterpie, Sandshrew ♪
♪ Bulbasaur, Charmander, Golem, Pikachu ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon master it's my destiny ♪
All right, how'd you do?
Loosen those lips.
Shake out that tongue!
Give it a rest. Today’s song is sung.
We'll be back tomorrow!
♪ Catch 'em catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪