♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
[narrator]
As our heroes continue their journey,
the future looks sunny and bright.
Uh-oh.
[thunder rumbling]
Pika?
-[both] Huh?
-A storm?
[all grunting]
[Ash] Let's get out of this.
[Misty] Where can we go?
We're in the middle of nowhere.
-Huh?
-What's that?
[Misty] I don't like the looks of it.
[Ash] Well, this is no time to be picky.
Pika.
-[all groan and gasp]
-Pi.
Hello! Sorry for barging in!
Is anybody here?
-It looks like some kind of theater.
-Yeah.
Hey, since nobody's around,
we might as well stay till the rain stops.
-Uh-huh.
-Pikachu.
[both] Huh?
Where'd that other Pikachu come from?
[both] Pika. Pi, pi.
How cute. [chuckles]
[giggling] Hi, there.
[giggles] Ooh.
What is this? What's wrong with it?
-What's your problem?
-That Pikachu doesn't look right.
-[both] Huh?
-Pikachu.
-Could be a new kind of Pikachu.
-A new kind?
All right.
Then I'll just have to capture it.
Pikachu, thunder shock!
Pikachu!
Go, Poké Ball!
Hey! Huh?
Hey, Ash,
that guy is dressed just like you.
Hmm. Except it's a girl.
-How can you tell?
-Men's intuition.
-Huh?
-Who are you?
-Tell me who you are.
-I'm Ash Ketchum from Pallet Town.
Duplica, from the House of Imitay.
Imitay? Like imitate?
Is that why you look just like me?
[chuckles] That's right.
You're right, Brock. She is a girl.
Hmm, but she may be a little young for me.
You're sad.
Aw. It still hasn't gotten over
that old habit.
Ditto.
[all exclaim]
[Pokédex]
Ditto. A transform Pokémon.
It is able to rearrange the cells
of its body and assume any form.
Its only attack is transform.
-[giggles]
-Squishy.
And Ditto can make itself look
just like anything.
Hmm.
Yeah, but it's face stayed the same.
When it transforms,
shouldn't it be able to change completely?
Yeah, it still can't change its face.
But it's the only Pokémon
that can transform like that, right?
Or are there others?
Nope. Ditto's one of a kind.
A transforming Pokémon.
It's only attack is to copy other Pokémon.
That's all it does.
Isn't that enough?
Yeah, but you can't have the fun
of teaching it different attacks.
That is kind of boring.
You think that's boring? Ha!
Well, that's what everyone says
who doesn't understand Ditto's real power.
-Its real power?
-Let's have a little match.
Then you'll understand, Ashy-boy.
Ashy-boy?
Ditto's power. Let's just see.
Mm-hm.
I chose to use my Ditto, of course.
You choose what you want.
Bulbasaur, I choose you!
Bulbasaur.
Go, little Ditto. Transform!
Ditto!
-Bulbasaur.
-Bulba.
You'll have to be better than that.
Uh-uh-uh.
You haven't seen the best part yet.
I'll show her.
Bulbasaur. Razor leaf.
Bulbasaur. Bulbasaur.
Ditto. Vine whip.
Bulbasaur.
-[Ash and Misty gasp]
-It can imitate attacks, too?
All right. Ditto, restrain Bulbasaur.
-Ah!
-No!
Have you had enough yet, Ashy-boy?
-Bulbasaur.
-Oh!
All right, I understand. I give up.
Ah!
-Ditto.
-[both] Ah!
But how...
How could the real thing lose?
Wow. What are all these clothes for?
Don't worry. I'll take good care of it.
My name is Jenny.
You're under arrest for Pokémon poaching.
[both giggling]
Great imitations.
Very good, but she doesn't capture
the more adult charm
of the real Joy and Jenny.
[groans]
With all these costumes,
I can imitate just about anybody.
Watch.
-[giggles]
-She's me.
Don't be so down, Ash.
That Ditto's powers are unbeatable.
Pika, pika!
Better than the real Pokémon.
I just can't believe I lost the match
to a great big fake.
Oh, Ash, don't think of it as a fake.
Ditto was battling you as real Bulbasaur.
I'm even more impressed
by how much knowledge Duplica has.
-Knowledge?
-Well, think about it.
Bulbasaur!
Why do you think Duplica had Ditto
use vine whip
instead of razor leaf
against your Bulbasaur?
Duplica must know all Bulbasaur's
potential attacks.
She can order Ditto
to use the strongest attack possible,
according to whatever Pokémon form
it takes.
That's right.
I guess that means Duplica must know
every attack of every Pokémon there is.
You must have studied a lot, Duplica,
to be able to battle in any situation
like that.
Oh, stop it, Brock.
You're making me blush.
-Pika.
-[giggles] Ditto.
I get it. It's more than just imitation.
It looks like you've got another rival,
Ash.
Duplica would make
a great Pokémon master.
-No way.
-Huh?
I just want to become
the greatest Ditto master.
[both] A Ditto master?
You got it.
And I want to be a big star.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'm the amazing Duplica,
-and this is my assistant, Ditto.
-Ditto!
[cheering and applause]
And now for my first imitation,
my impression of...
A Gloom.
[all laughing]
Now that we have your attention,
I'd like to do some of my favorites.
[all laughing]
You see, I started this Imitay House
because I like to imitate Pokémon.
This place is so flat and boring,
but people pass by here all the time.
I thought maybe when they stop here
for a rest, I could entertain them.
Now it's time for my assistant Ditto.
Will the Machoke in the front row
please come up onto the stage?
Machoke.
-Okay, Ditto, transform.
-Ditto.
-Machoke.
-Hey.
-That face.
-It's all wrong.
-[woman] What's going on?
-[man] It shouldn't look like that.
The only trouble is Ditto hasn't been able
to fix this weird problem
that keeps its face
from transforming the right way.
Thank you very much, Machoke,
for being a good sport.
Now how about this Voltorb?
Would you mind coming up to the stage?
-Voltorb.
-Okay, Ditto.
Transform!
Voltorb.
It's still got that dumb face.
That's so...
You can tell them apart!
[laughs nervously]
[man]
What a fake! It can't transform at all.
Ditto!
[coughing]
And that's what happens.
When people watch Ditto,
they don't want to see
an imperfect transformation.
This little one is trying its hardest
to master transform perfectly,
but its face stays the same.
Ditto.
-I guess being a Ditto trainer's tough.
-[all] Huh?
That was a touching story.
What? Who are you?
Prepare for trouble.
Make it double.
To protect the world from devastation...
To unite all peoples within our nation...
To denounce the evils of truth and love...
To extend our reach to the stars above...
-Jessie.
-James.
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth. That's right.
Let's give them a hand.
Okay. Show's over. Time to go back home.
Quiet, young twerp.
You'll be happy to know
we're not interested
in your Pikachu today.
We're here for...
The Ditto.
-Ditto!
-Stop!
Time for action, Weezing.
Weezing.
[grunting and coughing]
Oh, no, my Ditto's gone!
Team Rocket.
What are they up to this time?
[chuckling]
[Jessie]
Cute little Ditto. Our little Ditto.
Why didn't we think of this before?
Now we're unstoppable.
Right. Now we can take our names
off the loser list
and put them in the winning column.
And the boss will make me top cat again.
All right, little Ditto,
we have a little favor to ask you.
Ditto?
[Jessie] Transform into this.
Won't you, please?
Please? Pretty please?
Become Dratini, the Pokémon
we've never been able to capture.
It would make a handsome gift
for the boss.
Sir, we've finally captured Dratini,
that legendary Pokémon.
Yes. Well done.
I will reward you lavishly
for your hard work.
From now on, you will take my place
as the head of Team Rocket.
[chuckles] Your wish is my command.
Let's do it. Let's make it change
right this second, Jessie.
-What's the hurry?
-Hmm?
Since Ditto is ours for the moment,
let's have some fun
before we hand it over to the boss.
-Some fun?
-Ditto.
What would the person in this picture
look like if he were an adult?
-Ditto?
-Transform and show me.
Whose picture is that? Let me see.
-No way. This is personal. James, stop it.
-Let me see.
Let's see.
Ha! It's a little boy.
Ooh! Jessie has a boyfriend?
He was my first true love.
-First love?
-Show me?
Ditto.
-Huh?
-[both laughing]
Your first love
sure has an interesting face.
Especially if you're interested in Ditto.
[both grunting and groaning]
That wasn't funny.
Is that your idea of a transformation?
-Ditto.
-Huh?
[both laughing]
[grunting and groaning]
Now do as I say!
Transform into this.
-Ditto.
-[all groan]
I'm beginning to see a flaw in this plan.
How dare you insult us like this!
I'm warning you,
you'd better transform perfectly this time
or I'll transform you into jelly.
[whimpering] Ditto.
[Misty]
Don't worry, Duplica. Cheer up.
We'll all help you find Ditto.
We've already sent Pidgeotto and Zubat
out on surveillance.
There you go. See?
Yeah. Thanks, you guys.
Hey, Ash. What's on your mind?
Well, it's just Ditto's transform.
You can't forget how important
the trainer's ability is too.
It's not the Pokémon
but the trainer who decides
which attack to use in a battle, right?
And that means that if you raise a Ditto,
its progress and power
are connected directly to your own.
Yeah. I think you're definitely right
about that, Ash.
Sounds like you've been studying, Ash.
[squawks]
-Pika, pika?
-[squawks]
-Pikachu, did they see Ditto anywhere?
-Pika!
-Let's go save Ditto.
-Yeah.
-[Duplica] Wait.
-[all] Huh?
I think I have an idea.
What's wrong with you?
Why can't you get it right?
I don't have a goofy face like that.
Get it right this time, Ditto,
or you'll regret it.
-That's right.
-[whimpering] Ditto. Ditto.
-Oh!
-Success.
You really can do it if you try.
Great job, Ditto.
Now how about a Dratini?
-Sorry, Meowth.
-[both] Huh?
-Hey!
[dramatic music playing over speaker]
Prepare for trouble.
And make it "double" double.
[groans] Quit imitating us.
To protect the world from devastation...
To ignite all peoples within our nation...
[growls] This is insulting.
To denounce the evils of truth and love...
To extend our reach to the stars above...
-Ash.
-Misty.
And Brock.
Duplica. That's right.
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now
or prepare to fight all of us.
Pika, pika.
[Misty]
That was great to do the whole thing.
[Ash] Now I know why they like saying
all that dumb stuff so much. It's fun.
Hey, I know,
maybe we should all become actors.
-Pika, pika.
-[all laughing]
Team Rocket is not something
to be made fun of,
but if you're going to imitate us,
at least do it right.
To unite all peoples within our nation.
Not ignite.
We'll be taking Ditto back now.
No way.
[both chuckling]
Hey, I can't tell which one is which.
But I thought
that Ditto couldn't imitate faces.
That's true,
but Ditto was finally perfected
under the expert care and training
of Team Rocket.
[both laughing]
-[Duplica] Oh, thank you.
-[both] Huh?
I've tried everything I could think of
to get Ditto to imitate faces.
Now Ditto can finally become
the kind of Pokémon
I always knew it could be.
Duplica.
-That's beautiful.
-Yeah.
-That's so beautiful I can't stand it.
-[James] Neither can I.
Hey, you guys, why don't we just
solve this without a big battle?
All right. We'll do it your way this time.
We'll just give you Ditto.
Hey. What are you doing?
We'll be on our way now.
-Goodbye, everyone.
-Good luck with Ditto.
-Hold it right there!
-[screaming]
Hey, Duplica, what are you doing?
-This isn't Ditto.
-Huh?
Hey, let me go, will you? Ah!
[screams and groans]
Impossible. How could you tell?
It was a perfect transformation.
[sneezes]
[Jessie squealing]
[squealing]
[giggles]
I wouldn't be much of a trainer
if I couldn't see through
that transformation, would I, Ditto?
Dimwits!
How'd you manage to mess this one up?
You are in no position to complain.
It's time for plan B.
[all gasp]
Stop! You can't do this!
Quiet, all of you!
We're going to win after all.
Ditto, transform now!
Ditto!
That's great.
I didn't know Ditto could transform
into things like that.
-Pikachu.
-Pikachu!
Pikachu, aim!
Ditto, fire!
Fire!
Chu!
[screaming]
Ah!
Jessie, we lose everything.
Even all our hot air.
[together] Looks like Team Rocket's
blasting off again!
-Ditto.
-That was great.
You've learned
how to completely transform.
Ditto, would you please transform
into a Pikachu?
Ditto.
-Pikachu.
-Pi?
-Pika.
That's amazing.
Ditto transforms perfectly.
Ha. I can hardly believe it.
Team Rocket was actually good
for something.
Yeah, and the way Ditto transforms
into objects is great.
You're just as real as the real thing.
Hey, Ditto, great job.
-Pika?
-Pika.
But now I can't tell
which one's my Pikachu.
Then I guess you need to keep training,
Ashy-boy.
[Ash groans]
-Right, Ditto?
-Ditto.
Ah. [chuckles]
Pikachu.
Ditto. Ditto. [giggles]
There. The Imitay House is reopened.
[Ash laughs] Congratulations.
-[Misty] You did it, Duplica.
-Thanks for everything.
Come back and see us anytime, okay?
Good luck!
And take of yourself, Ditto master!
Imagine, the strength of all the Pokémon
in one.
Maybe I'll capture a Ditto
for myself someday.
[narrator]
Our heroes helped bring the sunshine
back into a fellow trainer's Life.
Who knows what rewards and adventures
await them beyond the rainbow?
[distant trills and squawks]
-[Meowth] Hey! What are you doing?
-[Jessie] Hold still.
[Meowth] Stop it. Let me go!
Cut it out, will you? Ow! Quit it!
Will you stop it, Meowth?
The only way we can get out of this mess
is to dress you up like a Dratini
and present you to the boss.
Pea brains. This won't work.
Take that! And that!
[both whimper and growl]
-[Jessie] How dare you touch my face!
-[Meowth] Let go of me!
[all shout]
You guys up for the Pokérap?
There’s 150 Pokémon.
You gotta name 'em all!
I’m doing 32 today,
so try to keep up.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Zubat, Primeape, Meowth, Onix
Geodude, Rapidash, Magneton, Snorlax ♪
♪ Gengar, Tangela, Goldeen, Spearow
Weezing, Seel, Gyarados, Slowbro ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, yeah! ♪
Gotta catch 'em all! ♪
♪ Kabuto, Persian, Paras, Horsea
Raticate, Magnemite, Kadabra, Weepinbell ♪
♪ Ditto, Cloyster, Caterpie, Sandshrew
Bulbasaur, Charmander, Golem, Pikachu ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
All right, how’d you do?
Loosen those lips.
Shake out that tongue!
Give it a rest, today’s song is sung.
We’ll be back tomorrow!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪