♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon! Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, gotta catch 'em all
[woman] So now, time for us to play.
[narrator] Ash and his friends
continue their journey.
As they pass
through a dark and mysterious forest,
it seems that danger
lurks behind every shadow.
And once again,
they've lost their way.
So this is the way to Saffron City,
huh, Misty?
I knew we shouldn't have listened to you.
Now we'll never get out of here.
As if. Your sense of direction's so bad,
you can't find yourself in a mirror.
-You crack mirrors.
-You big baby.
That's enough, guys.
You two don't want to stand here
and insult each other like this.
[both] Yes, we do.
Bad enough we're lost.
If I've got to listen to your arguing...
[Pikachu screaming]
[giggles]
Uh, hello? Do you live around here?
Hey, please don't run away.
Wait! We need directions.
Wait, ah!
Bulbasaur!
[grunts then sighs]
-[Brock] Ash, are you okay?
-Yeah!
Phew, that was close.
Hey, what about that weird little girl?
Where'd she run off to?
Beats me,
but take a look over there.
-Oh.
-[Misty] Oh, wow, it's beautiful.
Saffron City.
[Brock] Sabrina's the Gym Leader
of the Saffron City gym.
You defeat her, you win a marsh badge.
Yes! Look out, Sabrina. Here I come.
[Ash]
Abra and the Psychic Showdown
-[Ash] Now this is what I call a city.
-[Brock] Yeah.
[firecrackers crackle]
[all yell]
This must be some kind of ambush.
Huh?
[both laugh]
[both] Congratulations, winners.
Winners?
There's something real fishy about this.
Why should we win something
just for walking into town?
There's a simple explanation.
It just so happens
that you're the millionth,
millionth and first,
millionth and second
and millionth and third visitors
to Saffron City.
♪ Saffron City
The city you love to visit ♪
Oh, boy! It looks like our luck
is starting to turn good.
Right this way to the grand prize room.
Please step lively.
[both chuckle]
Thank you for your, Pikachu.
[all] Huh?
-Hey, you can't take Pi--
-You've won a trip through the warp tile.
[all yell]
-[chuckles]
-That was easy.
[all gasp]
[all groan]
What's going on here?
If this is the grand prize room,
then where are all the prizes?
Can't you put two and two together?
The only thing we've won is this trap.
Oh.
There aren't any doors or windows
in this room.
[Jessie] Bingo. The warp tile
is the only way in or out of this room.
There's no way to escape.
What are you talking about?
[both] Good evening.
You're watching the premiere
Prepare for Trouble,
Make it Double show.
[both panting]
It's Team Rocket!
Ew, gross, they both kissed me! Blah!
Blah! Blah! Blah!
-To protect the world from devastation.
-To unite all peoples within our nation.
-To denounce the evils of truth and love.
-To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James.
[both]
Hey, don't sit there ignoring us.
-Their show is pretty boring.
-It'll get canceled pretty soon.
We're boring?
Just you wait. We have something
that'll grab their attention.
[laughs] Because now it's time
for our special guest's...
Farewell performance.
You better give Pikachu back
right now.
Hey! Where you going?
Turn it back on.
-James, something's wrong.
-Turn it on!
We can't. Nothing's working.
That's what happens
when you work with amateurs. Huh?
Hey, you guys!
Can't you see
we're a little busy right now?
-Yeah, but who's the kid?
-Huh?
How did you get into this room,
little girl? You don't belong in here.
You can't just come barging in here.
-Oh! I can't move! I'm frozen.
-Ah! So am I.
You want me to turn down
the air conditioning?
-[Jessie] James, I can't move.
-[James] Me neither.
Team Rocket, give me back Pikachu.
-[girl giggles]
-[all] Huh?
Pikachu!
So, it's you again.
-Are you the one who saved Pikachu?
-Uh-huh.
Thank you. I owe you one.
[giggles]
[all gasp]
We better watch out.
That's no ordinary little girl.
So, what is she then?
[giggling]
Hey, what's going on?
[all groan]
How'd we wind up back outside again?
That little girl must have done something
to get us out of there.
We should be okay as long
as we don't have to win anymore prizes.
Huh? [gasps]
What's that?
[man panting]
You've come to Saffron City
and you don't even know Sabrina's Gym?
So that's Sabrina's Gym.
If you're trying to enter
the Pokémon league, young man,
this is one gym
I suggest you stay away from.
Huh? But why? Ah!
Where's he going?
[all sigh]
I've got to compete here.
Without a Marsh Badge,
I can't get into the Pokémon league.
Anyone here?
That's weird. Everyone's gone.
Hello?
There's something creepy
about this place.
Hmm?
[all gasp]
-A circle.
-A star.
[groans]
[grunting]
Oh!
Whoa, what kind of place is this?
What are you kids doing here?
We've come to ask for a Pokémon match
to earn a Marsh Badge.
-You want to challenge the great Sabrina?
-Sure do.
Uh, excuse me, but what are all
those people doing in that room?
Hmm, you know so little, yet you wish
to challenge the great Sabrina?
-Heh.
-[all] Huh?
[grunting]
Is something wrong?
You look like you've got a headache.
[panting]
Fool. It's Telekinesis.
You can't control a psychic-type Pokémon
without using Telekinetic powers.
Hmm, that's what you think.
Telekinesis is okay, but I have my own
secret method for bending spoons.
[grunting]
Ah!
[laughs]
Muscle over mind.
-Embarrassing.
-Just pretend we never met him before.
Pika. Pi.
Now hurry up and take us to Sabrina
so we can start the match.
Heh, as you wish.
Here we are.
[All] Huh?
This is more like some kind of temple
than a Pokémon gym.
Whatever it's like, I don't like it.
Oh, great Sabrina,
these strangers have come
who wish to challenge you.
Though I don't know why you'd waste
your time on this group of losers.
[laughs]
[all] Whoa!
It's the little girl
who brought back Pikachu.
[grunts]
Forgive me, great one. It's not my place
to decide whom you battle.
[yelling]
[all scream]
I told you there was something
really strange about her.
-Right, but who is she?
-Are you really Sabrina?
[giggling]
Sabrina, I demand an official match
to compete for a Marsh Badge.
Mm-hmm.
I'd like to have a match.
Well, that was easy.
-[Sabrina] But if you lose...
-[all] Huh?
...you have to be my friends
and let me play with you.
Uh, be your friends? Uh, okay, you bet.
You both got to have
a little more faith in me.
Even if she does have
some Telekinetic powers,
she's still only a little girl.
Ah, just don't let your guard down, Ash.
[Ash] Huh?
So now, time for us to play.
[all gasp]
So you are really Sabrina, The Gym Leader.
One-on-one. An all-out match.
Agreed?
Agreed.
Come now, Abra.
Go get him, Pikachu.
Pikachu!
[snores]
Pi?
Pi. Pi. Pi. Pi. Pi. Pi. Pi. Pi. Pi.
Pika. Pi. Pikachu.
I don't get it. Nobody sends
a sleeping Pokémon into a match.
Maybe she's making fun of me.
[Pokédex]
Abra, a psychic power Pokémon.
It sleeps 18 hours a day but employs
telekinesis even while sleeping.
-Telekinesis?
-Be careful.
No problem. Pikachu, Thunder Shock!
Pi!
Pikaaaaaaa-chu!
Pi? Pika?
Pika!
[all] Whoa!
It teleported itself.
Childish fools.
-Kadabra.
-Cha!
What's that?
[Pokédex]
Kadabra, a psychic Pokémon.
The evolved form of Abra.
Employs powerful telekinetic attacks.
That isn't fair.
I thought this was one-on-one.
But evolving during a match
isn't against any rules.
Be careful.
Kadabra is really powerful.
This time,
you won't get away from Pikachu.
It's against the rules to leave a stadium,
even by teleportation.
Pikachu, fill up
this whole stadium with lightning.
Hit them with your best shock.
Pika... chu!
-Kadabra.
-Pi?
-Now what?
-Confusion.
[groaning and screaming]
-Pikachu!
-Psychic attack.
-[groans]
-Kadabra.
That's right, Pikachu, don't give up.
Pika. Pikachu. Pika.
Heh, look at that.
Pikachu feels like dancing.
That's no dance. Kadabra's using its
psychic powers to control Pikachu's body.
-Huh?
-Pika, Pikachu.
-Kadabra.
-[groans]
Pikachu!
[groaning]
-Oh, Pikachu!
-Cha! [groans]
[angry grunt] That's it. Stop the match!
[gasps]
Pikachu. Are you all right?
[whimpers]
-I forfeit.
-Be my friends.
You promised I could play with you.
[all] Huh?
[all grunt]
Now where are we?
Ah, looks like
we've been teleported again.
Sabrina must've teleported us
from the Pokémon Gym.
This place is empty.
-I'll take a look around.
-We'll come with you, Ash.
[grunts]
Is anybody home?
Please, can somebody help us?
Hey.
-That cake looks delicious.
-Ah!
Sabrina wanted to play with us but I guess
we're going to have lunch first.
I wonder where she is.
Guess it's rude not to wait for her
but I can't resist.
-Ah! This stupid cake is fake!
-Huh?
Now what's in here? Oh!
Oh, I'm very sorry. I really didn't think
that anybody was home. I just...
-Huh?
-Pika, Pikachu.
Hmm?
Huh? Something's not right here.
That thing is a doll.
Ash, you're not going to believe this,
but we're inside a doll house.
This is a doll house?
Everything in here is made out
of plastic, including the food.
How can that be?
[rattling]
[clamoring]
[giggling]
Now I can play with you all.
Wow, she's pretty tall for a little girl.
Actually, I think we're the ones
who got a lot smaller.
[giggling]
Run for it.
How can we get away from her?
The houses, the streets,
they're all her toys.
-That means we're...
-That means we're trapped!
Trapped inside her toy box.
Must have shrunk us with telekinesis.
So when she said she wanted
to play with us, she really meant it.
[giggling]
[all panting]
-[all] Huh?
-It's a dead end.
What's that?
[all gasp]
[girl giggles]
-She's coming this way.
-Uh-oh.
We're going to have a ball.
I want to play catch.
We're going to get squashed.
[giggles]
[all scream]
Listen. Let your minds rely on mine.
Teleportation.
That was fun.
Let's play again sometime.
[giggling]
[all groan]
-Now what?
-This is a real place.
Ha, we made it.
-[Misty] There's that guy.
-Thanks for the help.
But why did you decide to rescue us?
Sabrina is a dangerous Pokémon trainer.
I got the chance to help you this time,
but next time, you won't be so lucky.
You'll all be trapped in her toy box
for eternity.
[all] Huh?
Give up your crazy idea
of challenging Sabrina.
Leave Saffron City
and never come back here.
I can't do that. I have to win
Sabrina's Marsh Badge
so I'll be able to get into
the Pokémon League.
You will never be able to defeat
Sabrina and her psychic Pokémon.
Yes, I will. We just need to make
a quicker attack
before she can kick in
with her psychic powers.
Hmm?
[all yell]
-Ash what do you think you're doing?
-It's not me. My body's moving by itself.
Heh, if you can't beat me,
you haven't got a chance against Sabrina.
What do you mean?
Can you use telekinesis too?
Please teach me how to use
psychic powers.
Argh! Ugh.
[both] Whoa!
You usually have to be born
with telekinetic powers.
-You can't just learn them.
-Please wait.
Just forget about it, Ash.
You haven't got a chance
against telekinesis.
I may not have telekinesis
but I've still got the guts
to take on Sabrina again.
Whoa!
Wise up, kid. Not even I have
the powers to defeat Sabrina.
Guts don't count in this contest.
I'm telling you this for your own good.
-Don't, Ash.
-Better call it quits, Ash.
[grunting]
[groaning]
-Ash, give it up.
-Please.
I need your help.
I've got to defeat Sabrina
for the Marsh Badge. I have to.
You've got to help me beat her.
Please show me how. Ugh.
Well, that's one determined kid. Hmm.
[panting]
There just may be one way
you can defeat her.
Huh?
Only one other type of Pokémon
can battle the psychic type.
If you capture a ghost Pokémon
from Lavender Town,
you might have a chance.
A ghost Pokémon from Lavender Town.
Thank you.
Hm. [groans]
-Ash. Hey, Ash.
-Ash!
Uh, are you okay?
You haven't got a chance
against a psychic Pokémon.
Ha. Let's go. On to Lavender Town.
With some luck, that kid may be
the one who can rescue Sabrina.
[narrator]
Who is this mysterious bearded man?
And what's the secret
of the Pokémon trainer Sabrina?
Will Ash have what it takes to capture
a ghost Pokémon in Lavender Town?
Only the future will tell us and that's
exactly where our heroes are headed.
[grunts] Still can't move a muscle, huh?
-We're paralyzed.
-Now I know how a statue feels.
Meowth.
This is getting to be a real drag.
[Jessie]
Maybe we should call the psychic hotline.
You guys up for the Pokérap?
There's 150 Pokémon.
You gotta name 'em all!
I'm doing 32 today, so try to keep up.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Zubat, Primeape, Meowth, Onix
Geodude, Rapidash, Magneton, Snorlax ♪
♪ Gengar, Tangela, Goldeen, Spearow
Weezing, Seel, Gyarados, Slowbro ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, yeah! ♪
Gotta catch 'em all! ♪
♪ Kabuto, Persian, Paras, Horsea
Raticate, Magnemite, Kadabra, Weepinbell ♪
♪ Ditto, Cloyster, Caterpie, Sandshrew
Bulbasaur, Charmander, Golem, Pikachu ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
All right, how'd you do?
Loosen those lips, shake out that tongue!
Give it a rest, today's song is sung.
We'll be back tomorrow!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪