♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon!
Oh, you're my best friend ♪
♪ In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
I'm waiting for you. Come back to me.
Return to your beloved.
I'm waiting for you.
[cackles]
[narrator] Since last time, Ash
and his friends have been on a ferry,
sailing from the resort of Porta Vista
to continue their Pokémon journey.
Suddenly, Misty spots a landmark.
-Hey. Look over there.
-Pika!
Great. That must be Maiden's Peak,
that's where we get off.
We'll be landing soon.
Ah, it wouldn't matter to me
if I never saw land again.
I just wasted another summer.
But we had a whole summer
of adventures.
For kids, summer means
playing on the beach,
splashing around and having fun,
but for me...
summer means bathing suits
and girls to wear them.
Ah! Now bikini season's over and I'll have
to wait another year to meet a girl.
[groans]
[ship's klaxon]
-We're really at the end of our rope.
-No room. No room service.
Stop whining. We don't have a cent
and at least this beats swimming.
[man over speakers]
Maiden's Peak welcomes the passengers
arriving from Porta Vista!
We invite you all to attend
our annual summer's end festival,
-now in progress.
-Cool! A festival!
It looks like fun. Let's check it out.
I'll ride the Ferris wheel all alone.
Huh?
Who's that?
Whoa. What a knockout.
Ah!
Pikachu.
-Hey, she's gone.
-Pikachu.
-Cheer up, Brock. We're at a festival.
-Yeah. Let's have some fun.
It's a festival.
Heh, people spend a lot of money
at these festivals,
but they never pay attention, so they
drop their change all over the place.
-Meowth want a cotton candy.
-Money is sweeter.
Ooh! Sweet!
-Snap out of it! Stop day-dreaming!
-[groans]
That festival is waiting,
and I can smell money.
-I can smell corn dogs.
-Ooh.
[all cheering]
-[boy] Let's go on the Ferris wheel.
-[woman] Yeah! Woo!
-[girl] Let's go on the Ferris wheel.
-[both chuckle]
She was the most beautiful girl
I've ever seen.
[all gasp]
[woman] Hey, you, there.
Are you the--?
Ah, you're not that beautiful.
Who's not beautiful?
[groans]
Beware.
Not of an old beauty like me
but of a beautiful young woman
or you'll meet a cruel fate.
Ah! That girl on the rock.
I have to meet her.
Ah, I must be the beautiful girl
she's talking about
but I'd never hurt Brock.
I was talking about
an elegant young woman,
not some scrawny
little blabbermouth like you.
Scrawny?
Real scrawny. Ow!
That's it. I don't have to stand
around here and be insulted.
-Let's get out of here!
-[both groan]
The beautiful woman. A cruel fate.
The cruelest fate
would be never to see her again.
[Team Rocket] Hm. Huh.
Nothing! There's no money anywhere
at this festival!
Not a quarter, nickel or dime.
Not even a penny.
What kind of cheap festival is this?
We got to keep looking
till we find something.
-Ah! A penny!
-[woman] Hold it right there.
Hmm? I dropped this.
I've been watching you.
You're up to no good.
And there's no good in your future.
Who? The police?
The sheriff' the FBI?
I see a young and beautiful woman
who will lead you to a cruel fate.
I don't need a fortune teller
to know that.
Some woman is always causing me trouble.
It's a curse. Ah.
Who do you mean?
-[Jenny] Good afternoon.
-Huh?
I'm with the local police department
and I know exactly what you're all doing.
[all scream]
I see you found some change
that someone dropped.
Whenever money's lost, even a penny,
it must be reported to the authorities.
Thanks for being such
and observant citizen.
Now, if you'll just follow me,
we'll file a report at the station.
-The station?
-We don't want to get in your way,
so why don't you go ahead and file it
without us and keep the change?
Bye-bye!
[old man] Welcome.
To celebrate the summer's end festival,
we will now display the shrine
of the Maiden's greatest treasure.
For 2,000 years, this painting has hung
within the shrine of the Maiden.
Once each year,
it is removed from the shrine
and displayed to the public
during this festival.
As I unveil the painting,
please gaze upon it with reverence.
[all gasp]
-Who's that's?
-She's cute.
Ah, it's her.
But it can't be.
[both sigh]
[sigh]
She's so incredibly beautiful.
She's the girl of my dreams.
Don't wake me up.
Stay back! The woman in this painting
perished over 2,000 years ago.
2,000 years.
She was in love with a brave
and handsome young man
but he left her and sailed away
to fight in a war.
I'll wait for you forever.
Come back to me. Farewell.
[old man]
And she did wait for a very long time,
hoping to see his ship on the horizon.
But her true love never returned
to that place again.
Still, she waited and waited,
never moving from that spot,
until finally her body
was turned into stone,
just like the cliff
upon which she stood.
To this day,
she waits for her love to return.
Just tell me. Where's this rock?
Maiden's rock is not far
from this shrine.
So that's Maiden rock.
It's the most beautiful rock
I've ever seen.
I don't care if she is made of stone.
I'm still in love with her.
If she were my girlfriend,
I'd make sure
she was never out of my sight.
No one would ever steal her from me,
not even Team Rocket.
I'll fight them to keep her safe.
James, you're insane.
Why would we steal a thing like that?
-We could steal that other thing.
-What thing?
Pokémon are valuable
but so are works of art.
Let's swipe that painting.
If we grab that painting,
we could make a bundle.
Oh, Jessie! Jessie!
Before you grab it, grab hold of me.
Whoa!
Team Rocket is really slipping.
No matter how long you wait here,
a rock is a rock, Brock.
Yeah, let's go back to the festival.
This is boring.
Why don't you two go back.
I want to stay a little bit longer.
You remember
where we're staying tonight, right?
The Pokémon Center near the port.
I'll make it back by curfew.
[sighs]
Don't worry about me. I'll be okay.
11 o'clock. Curfew time.
Curfew time. Curfew time.
I'm really getting worried.
Brock still isn't back yet.
Hmm. Huh?
[rattling]
-Wait. I'll go out and look for him.
-[Joy] Hold it.
-Oh!
-Don't you realize it's your bedtime?
-Yes, but--
-Staying up late is bad for your skin
and it makes you irritable
and it ruins your appetite.
I won't allow it.
Now get to bed this instant.
[alarm beeping]
What time is it? Wake up.
Time to steal the painting.
-Wake up, you two.
-Beauty sleep.
Hmm, beautiful, I must meet you.
I'm coming to you.
[wind whistling]
Ah!
What's that?
[screams]
[sighs]
Must be dreaming.
Back to sleep. Meowth.
-My love, I'm waiting for you.
-Ah, who said that? Who are you?
It's you. So it really was you.
2,000 years. Huh?
I've been waiting for you
for such a long time.
It's you. It's really you.
-Brock!
-Brock, where are you
Pikachu.
James? James?
If you're not here,
at least come out and tell us.
-That's right!
-Hey, Brock!
[all] Hm? Huh?
-Oh!
-You again.
-Yuck.
-Double yuck.
I've finally found you.
Oh, wait a minute,
you're not the one I was looking for.
Hey, are you looking for somebody, too?
Ahem. Prepare for trouble
and make it double.
Doing this by myself is a real drag.
To protect the world from devastation.
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
[James]
To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie?
-[James] James.
Ah, Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
-Surrender now or prepare to fight. Ooh!
-Ah!
-He looks awful.
-Worse than usual.
[Brock groans]
Brock, what happened?
[both groan]
-Pull yourself together.
-What do you think you're doing?
So everything turned out
just as I predicted.
-[all] Huh?
-[Ash] It's the old woman.
Obviously, these two have both
seen the Ghost of the Maiden.
[all] Ghost of the Maiden?
-I love her. I love her. I love her.
-Me too. Me too. Me too.
[all sigh]
-They're possessed. Pikachu.
-Pikachu!
[Brock and Jessie groan]
-Uh, who am I? I am Brock.
-Brock's back.
I'm James from Team Rocket. Eeh!
-He's back.
-But not to normal.
All men who pass this way
fall under her spell.
It's always the same story,
over and over.
We find them here acting like zombies
with the life sucked out of them,
babbling like idiots.
It's the work of that Maiden's ghost,
still waiting
for her young soldier to return.
It's just as I warned you.
So what? who cares as long
as I can be with her?
Ah, he isn't cured.
I'm scared.
You've got to do something!
-There is only one thing we can do.
-[all] What?
We have stickers.
These are anti-ghost stickers.
-Ah, however...
-What's the catch?
I can't just give these stickers
away for free.
Uh, ah! Oh, well.
If it's the only thing that'll help.
We'll stick stickers all over the place.
-This'll really work, right?
-Chu.
-Shut your mouth.
-[groans]
-Will she come?
-Oh, she'll come.
-This better work.
-Let's hope.
She's here!
[all screaming]
-It's you.
-I've been waiting for you.
-Yes, and I've been waiting too.
-I'm scared. Really, really scared.
-I wanted to meet you.
-And I, you.
-Brock!
-But why?
-Why aren't the stickers working?
-Maybe because...
-We got them...
-[both] For free.
-Free? What do you mean, free?
-A two for one deal.
We got one set free
for every set they bought.
It was a real bargain.
-You used freebies?
-Oops.
I can't believe you're letting
that ghost get me,
just because you're both so cheap.
-You don't want to go?
-Of course I don't want to go.
I don't want to go. I don't want to go.
I don't want to go.
-Grab him!
-Wait, Brock!
Hey, let me go!
I don't want to go!
[screams]
Whoa!
Hey, girl. You can't take him.
-You haven't got a ghost of a chance.
-[splashing]
[all gasp]
[groans]
-Ah!
-You really do care.
It's not because of you.
Girls like her disgust me.
Always waiting around for her man,
as if she were his faithful pet.
She can't stand the thought of losing him.
She cries.
But I'd say, see you later.
-There are plenty more fish in the sea.
-I could sure go for some fish.
I've been waiting.
You cannot not interfere.
[cackling]
[both scream]
-What is that?
-Not any Pokémon I know.
-[Pokédex] No Pokémon entry found.
-They're not Pokémon?
[all groaning]
[Pokédex] Still searching.
[both] Oh!
[Pokédex] Pokémon entry found.
Gastly. A ghost Pokémon.
It is usually invisible.
It's specialty is hypnosis.
Gastly? You're really a Pokémon?
So you finally figured it out.
Sometimes I'm the ghost
of the 2,000-year-old maiden...
And sometimes,
I'm the mysterious old woman.
But no matter what the disguise,
I'll always be...
Awfully Gastly.
Well, Gastly, time for a battle.
Pikachu?
My hypnotic powers
can work on other Pokémon too
including little rodents.
-Pika.
-Stop a rodent...
...with a mousetrap.
[screams]
Mousetraps won't hurt Meowth.
So, Meowth,
you want to play games with me?
[roars]
[Gastly] Here's a cat toy
I think you'll enjoy.
Meowth. Meowth. Meowth.
-Go, Ekans!
-Ekans.
A snake's natural enemy is a mongoose.
Dinner time.
[screams]
-Your turn.
-Um, uh, Koffing, Poison Gas Attack.
Koffing! Huh?
[Gastly] Smoking is prohibited.
My turn now.
Charmander, I choose you.
Char! Char!
Well, now.
Here's something for you, squirt.
Cha!
Now who shall I defeat?
[groans]
Squirtle, Bulbasaur, attack together.
-Bulba!
-Squirtle.
Ha! What a nuisance.
This is too easy.
Here are Bulbasaur's and Squirtle's
evolved forms,
Venusaur and Blastoise.
And just for fun, I'll combine them
into one super-Pokémon
to make Venustoise.
Try that on for size.
[both scream]
We lose. It's just too strong.
Then how about this?
-What's that?
-It's a cross.
I've also got garlic, a stake
and a hammer.
Uh, what do I look like,
a vampire or something?
[bell tolling]
Huh?
-[all gasp]
-What's happening?
I may not be a vampire
but I hate sunlight.
It's time for me to go
until the next festival.
Don't forget the Ghost of the Maiden.
She and the old lady
will return next year too.
That was ghastly.
-I'll say.
-Pikachu.
Hey, look! The sun.
At the end of every summer,
the visitors send out these tiny boats,
each one with a candle
to help light the way
for any wandering spirits
who can't find their way back home.
[Gastly] This summer is over
but your legend will continue to live on.
-Thank you, Gastly.
-My pleasure.
I enjoy keeping alive all the old legends
that people have forgotten over the years,
and if I do a good job of it,
I make a few bucks as well.
I'll see you again next festival.
I'll be waiting until that day
when my true love returns to me at last.
Well, I am a ghost Pokémon.
Perhaps one day I'll meet
the young man you love,
and if I do, I'll remind him
that his maiden
still longs for him to return.
Thank you and goodbye.
[sighs]
If only you were 2,000 years younger.
Maybe next year.
[upbeat drumming]
I think I'm doing a bang-up job.
Let's drum up some fun.
♪ Doo-dee-doo-dee-doo-dee-doo ♪
-A ghost Pokémon. Ghastly.
-Pikachu.
-[Misty] Sorry I'm late.
-[Ash gasps]
-Come on, Ash. Let's dance.
-Uh, sure.
-You, too, Pikachu. [giggles]
-Pika!
[narrator] And so the summer festival
draws to a close.
There's autumn in the air,
which means that poor Brock won't
get back to the beach until next year.
But cheer up, Brock.
A lot can happen in a year's time.
Who knows what new adventures
and romances are waiting
just over the horizon.
♪ Pokémon! ♪
Get those lips loose!
It's time to Pokérap!
Come on, sing 'em with me!
That's the game!
There's 150 Pokémon.
How many can you name?
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, yeah! ♪
Gotta catch 'em all, ow! ♪
♪ Sandslash, Hitmonlee
Psyduck, Arcanine ♪
♪ Eevee, Exeggutor
Kabutops, Zapdos ♪
♪ Dratini, Growlithe
Mr. Mime, Cubone ♪
♪ Graveler, Voltorb, Gloom
We're almost home! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, yeah! ♪
Gotta catch 'em all! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Charmeleon, Wartortle ♪
♪ Mewtwo, Tentacruel, Aerodactyl ♪
♪ Omanyte, Slowpoke, Pidgeot, Arbok ♪
That's all, folks!
Can you name all the Pokémon?
Just put today's song
together with the other days of the week.
That's why you can't miss a show.
You gotta catch 'em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all... Pokémon! ♪