♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
[narrator] Once again,
we join our hero, Ash
on his continuing quest
to become a Pokémon Master.
With his friends Brock,
Misty and Pikachu,
Ash's next adventure
is on the horizon.
-[Ash] Wow. look at those rocks.
-Pi.
That's a long drop.
Fall from here
and the ball game's over.
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
[Brock] The map says that this ridge
leads right to Saffron City.
[Ash] And to our next challenge
at the Saffron Gym.
Yeah. huh?
-What are those?
-[Misty] They look like Butterfree.
The Butterfree are celebrating
their season of love.
-Love?
-[Brock] Yeah.
The season of love
is when Butterfree lay their eggs.
The Butterfree find mates
and then lay their eggs across the sea.
-[Ash] Across the sea?
-[Brock] That's right.
[Misty] How cute.
You mean my Butterfree would go too?
If you don't let it cross the sea,
it will never have babies.
Hm. Babies?
[Misty] I'm surprised there was
a hot air balloon for rent out here.
We'll probably see lots of other balloons
once we get up into the air.
Hold on, guys.
[Ash] Heh, what a view.
-[Pikachu chuckles]
-[all] Huh?
-[Misty] Look, there they are.
-[Brock] Let's go.
[all trill] Butterfree!
Wow, all the Butterfree
are pairing off into couples.
-Okay, Ash.
-Oh, right.
Butterfree, go!
-Go out there and find your mate.
-Good luck, Butterfree.
Huh?
Maybe none of those Butterfree
is its type.
What do you mean
by its type, Brock?
The Butterfree
all look exactly the same to me.
Some must fly better than others
or maybe they have
slightly different patterns, I guess.
-Huh?
-[all] Huh?
[Misty] Look at all the balloons.
[trilling]
[Brock] They're all Butterfree trainers.
They come at this time every year
to release their Butterfree.
[Ash] Oh.
You just go find yourself
a nice mate, Butterfree, go!
[laughs]
[gibbering]
Oh, no, not this again.
[all gasp]
-Butterfree.
-Listen up, Butterfree.
See the Butterfree
that girl just released?
Ha! that one. That one right there
pick that one.
Don't you get it?
If two Butterfree fall in love
their trainers will meet
and they can fall in love too.
-Oh.
-Don't butt into Pokémon love affairs.
But, Misty,
if Butterfree doesn't find a mate
it won't ever have babies.
Go ahead, then.
[trills] Free! Free!
Go get them, Butterfree.
The perfect mate for you
is got to be out there somewhere.
Free! Free!
Free! Free! Free! Free! Free! Free!
It looks like Butterfree
really found someone it likes.
Yeah, love at first sight
with that pink one.
Butterfree's acting kind of weird.
[Brock]
That's Butterfree's courtship dance.
[Ash] Courtship dance?
It's Butterfree's way of saying:
"I want to be your Butterfree."
Oh, that's so romantic.
If it's successful,
the other Butterfree does a dance too.
[Misty] It's doing something.
What's going on?
Free! Free! Free! Free! Free...
[groans] Free...
[all gasp]
-Butterfree got shot down.
-What? That's so mean. That isn't fair.
[sobs]
[gasps] Butterfree.
Where are you going?
Butterfree!
Shot down in its prime.
[Ash] Butterfree! Hey, Butterfree!
-[Misty] Butterfree.
-Pikachu.
-Butterfree. Come out.
-Butterfree. Where are you?
It's Butterfree.
Hey, there, Butterfree,
are you okay?
[groans] Free...
-Hey, how come you look so sad, buddy?
-It was rejected by someone it loved.
That's a terrible shock.
Believe me, it's a terrible feeling.
I could write a book
about the secrets of love and heartache.
I guess that book
would be your autobiography.
[groans]
Pikachu. Pika, Pikachu.
Pika. Pikachu.
Do you think maybe Dexter
might be able to tell us
how Butterfree can get that
other Butterfree to be its mate?
Dexter's never been in love.
I just don't understand it.
My Butterfree's great.
Why would any other Butterfree
reject it?
Butterfree, maybe you just have
to show off your strengths
and let the others see
how great you are.
Show how powerful your Tackle is
or how you can use Stun Spore.
That's right, Butterfree.
You've got to be assertive.
Love is all about attacking
your opponent first.
Get in a quick punch and surprise them,
then while they're still weak
take the lead
and you'll beat them hands down.
Trust me,
I know that's the best way to win.
-You mean it?
-Sure do. That's love.
-Ah! I wish I'd known that sooner.
-Let's give it another try.
-Hold it.
-Huh?
A new look might help.
[coos]
-Heh.
-Yeah, that looks great.
[coos]
[flames whooshing]
Free! Free!
We got to find it. Where did
that pink Butterfree go?
-This is important to you, isn't it?
-I raised that Butterfree myself
and I'll show them all
how good it is.
Heh, it looks like the trainer
is just as passionate as the Butterfree.
All right, there it is.
Now, Butterfree, this time
just have confidence in yourself.
-Go.
-Pika.
Free!
Butterfree! Show it your Whirlwind attack!
[trills]
Hm. Now use your Tackle.
That should do the trick.
Free! Free! Free! Free!
-[whimpers]
-Free...
-[sighs] Shot down again.
-Pikachu.
-Huh?
-What's that?
-[Jessie] Prepare for trouble.
-[James] Make it double.
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation.
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation.
-To renounce the evils of truth and love.
-To extend our reach to the stars above.
-[Jessie] Jessie.
-[James] James.
[Jessie] Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
[James]
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth. That's right.
[Jessie]
Ha-ha! Look at all the Butterfree.
[James] All ours for the taking.
[Meowth] Let's do some networking, ha-ha!
Look! They're stealing the Butterfree.
It's those little twerps again.
No matter where we go,
those kids are always in our way.
But this time
they can't do a thing to stop us.
[cackles]
[all whimpering]
[Ash] Hey, knock it off.
[Brock] Stop or you're going to disrupt
their whole egg-laying season.
[Misty] Can't you see
these Butterfree are in love?
Heh, we're in love too, little girl,
with all the pretty little Pokémon.
Those Butterfree are free no more.
Argh! We've got to stop them.
[Team Rocket laugh]
[all yell angrily] Quit it!
Leave 'em alone!
[laughs] We're having quiet a spree.
-We're swiping all of the Butterfree.
-There's never been a happier me.
Can't we speed this thing up
and catch them?
I'm trying, Ash,
but their chopper's a lot faster.
Huh.
Ha-ha, nothing but net.
Free!
Free! Free!
Yeah. That's it, Butterfree!
Use your Tackle Attack.
Huh, that pathetic little insect thinks
it can stop us.
Butterfree, Stun Spore now!
Ha-ha-ha! That was a stunning failure.
[sighs] I guess I'm going to
have to use Pidgeotto then.
Wait a minute. You can't do that.
Just think how Butterfree would feel.
It's trying its hardest out there.
All right.
All right. What a catch.
Now let's hit the skyway.
[Jessie] Our thanks to all of you who came
to see Team Rocket's latest triumph.
-We hope to see you again.
-[James] Next time we steal the show.
Hey, come back!
Free! Free!
-Butterfree! After it.
-Here goes.
-I don't see Butterfree or Team Rocket.
-[sighs]
Butterfree was flying
as fast as it could.
I bet it's going to follow that pink
Butterfree no matter where they take it.
Butterfree, where are you?
Pika!
-[Ash] Butterfree!
-Pika!
-Please, Butterfree!
-Hey, Butterfree!
Free! Free!
-Ah, Butterfree.
-Free! Free!
[gibbers] Free! Free!
What happened?
-[Butterfree gibbers]
-Chu, chu?
-Is the pink Butterfree over there?
-Free! Free!
Don't worry.
Show us the way, Butterfree.
[Meowth] 98 Meowth, 99 Meowth,
100 Meowth, hee-hee-hee!
-[Jessie] A very nice catch.
-[James] Just between us, isn't it nice
to have one of our nefarious schemes
actually work for once?
Feels great.
We're at our best
when we're at our worst.
We've finally got it back.
Yeah, when the boss hears about this,
I'll be top cat again.
[purrs]
Na-na-na!
[laughs]
-Hey, somebody's busting in.
-Who is it? who's there?
-Prepare for trouble.
-And you can make that triple.
To protect the world from devastation.
-To unite all peoples within our nation.
-This was just--
-Too good.
-To last.
-You got that right.
Pika!
We're defending the beauty
of truth and love.
-Let's do it.
-We got to stop them!
-Today is the one day.
-You won't win.
Butterfree, go.
[all shouting]
Go, Starmie!
Starmie, Tackle attack.
[all yelling]
Free! Free!
[grunting]
[all] Free! Free!
The Butterfree are getting away!
Do something!
Take this.
Hang in there, Starmie.
Hurry up, fly away.
Wait. Stop them.
They're getting away. hurry.
[panting]
Are you all right, Butterfree?
Free! Free! Free!
I'll get you.
[grunts and screams]
Free!
We won't let them get away, argh!
-[Brock] Stop! Come back!
-[Misty] Wait!
We're going to get every one of them back.
Hurry. Faster.
[Ash] There's team rocket. Over there.
[Misty] The flock of Butterfree.
No, they're doing it again.
Pikachu!
Pikachu, what are you two going to do?
Pika!
[whimpering]
What's that?
[all] Huh?
Pika!
Ka!
[all] It's going to shock us. It's going
to shock us. It's going to shock us.
It's going to shock us. It's going to...
[all screaming]
[all scream]
-We were so close this time.
-[screaming]
[Jessie] Looks like Team Rocket's
blasting off again!
We did it.
That'll teach 'em not to play around
with a Pokémon romance.
-Free!
-Pika.
-You did it, Pikachu. Great work.
-Pi. Pikachu.
Free!
[sings and coos] Free! Free!
Hey, look.
[coos and sings] Free! Free! Free!
[Brock] Heh, now the pink Butterfree
is doing the courtship dance
for your Butterfree.
-All right, good for you, Butterfree.
-Chu.
[both] Free! Free! Free! Free!
Well, I guess you have
to leave us now, don't you?
They have to cross the ocean
and start their new family.
-I'll miss you, Butterfree.
-It's time.
I'll say goodbye, then.
This is a great Butterfree,
so take care of it for me.
Free! Free!
-Your babies are going to be beautiful.
-I guess you better get going.
Free!
Don't worry. I'll just tell all
the other Pokémon that you're on a trip
and you'll come back someday maybe.
[sobs] Free! Free! Free!
Goodbye, Butterfree.
-Bye-bye, Butterfree.
-Good luck to both of you.
Pikachu.
Butterfree.
Hey, Ash,
Butterfree's almost out of sight.
Huh?
[grunts]
Take care, Butterfree!
Good luck, buddy!
Free!
Goodbye, Butterfree.
I'll always remember you.
Thank you for everything.
Goodbye, Butterfree!
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
Have a good trip, Butterfree.
Take care of yourself!
Goodbye, Butterfree.
♪ Pokémon ♪
[sighs]
Be happy, old friend.
You know, Ash, you raised Butterfree
to have a lot of courage
and I think you just proved
you have a lot of courage, too.
Thank you, Brock.
-Pikachu.
-[Ash laughs]
-Isn't that beautiful?
-It sure is.
♪ Pokémon ♪
[narrator] Good friendships last forever
even though friends
don't always stay together.
Helping Butterfree to grow, Ash just
might have grown a little himself.
[Butterfree] Free! Free! Free! Free!
Okay, guys,
we gotta rap some Pokémon.
You just do the singing.
I'll take care of the hard part.
Let's get it on!
♪ I want to be the best there ever was ♪
♪ To beat all the rest, yeah
That's my cause ♪
♪ Electrode, Diglett, Nidoran, Mankey ♪
♪ Venusaur, Rattata, Fearow, Pidgey ♪
♪ Seaking, Jolteon, Dragonite, Gastly ♪
♪ Ponyta, Vaporeon
Poliwrath, Butterfree ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I'll search across the land
Look far and wide ♪
♪ Release from my hand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Venomoth, Poliwag
Nidorino, Golduck ♪
♪ Ivysaur, Grimer
Victreebel, Moltres ♪
♪ Nidoking, Farfetch'd
Abra, Jigglypuff ♪
♪ Kingler, Rhyhorn, Clefable, Wigglytuff ♪
Thirty-two down, that’s it for now.
Tune in tomorrow.
We’ll rap at you some more.
There’s 150,
so watch Monday Through Friday.
You’ll catch ‘em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all, ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪