♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon!
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪
[birds chirping]
[narrator]
With Bulbasaur as his newest Pokémon,
Ash and friends are making their way
triumphantly to Vermilion City,
aren’t they?
There's nothing
but Spearow around here.
Well, that's the least of our worries,
isn't it?
Just because we're a little lost
doesn't mean I have to stop catching
all the Pokémon I can, does it?
-Chu.
-Of course not. Enjoy yourself.
[narrator] Our friends have gotten
off track just a bit.
I just can't go one step further.
We've been looking for Vermilion City
for ten whole days!
Uh, there's a bug right on your--
[screams]
-Get it away!
-[grunts].
Heh, it was just a piece of grass.
[grunts angrily]
[laughs]
Huh? Oh!
[groans]
I'm going crazy! Where are we?
According to this,
we're right in the middle of nowhere.
But it looks like route 24
leads right to Vermilion City.
-Does this trail take us to route 24?
-According to my calculations, it does.
All right! Then let's get this show
on the road.
Huh?
Hey, Ash, take a look at this thing.
It looks like some kind of giant Pokémon.
-Pikachu.
-Chu!
Pikachu!
A Charmander.
Char.
[all grunt]
[Pokédex] Charmander, a flame
burns on the tip of its tail from birth.
It is said that a Charmander dies
if its flame ever goes out.
When I went to get my first Pokémon
from Professor Oak,
I was disappointed
because I couldn't get a Charmander.
Now I can catch my own.
I don't know.
It looks like it's in bad shape.
[Brock] Yeah, catch it and we'll take it
to Pokémon Center for help.
Poké Ball, go!
[gasps]
It looks pretty healthy to me.
You think I should have Pikachu
battle it first to weaken it
-and make it easier to catch?
-Why don't you let me catch it?
My water Pokémon would be stronger
against Charmander.
Hold on a minute.
Take a look at the flame on its tail.
Char! Char!
There's no way it could still have
the strength to battle.
-Ash, try the Poké Ball one more time.
-All right, I will.
Poké Ball, go!
All right!
[grunts]
-It sure has a lot of spunk.
-A little too much if you ask me.
I think this Charmander
has an attitude problem.
Pikachu.
Charmander.
What's the story, Pikachu?
Pik, Pikachu.
[Misty] A necktie?
Hm. A man maybe.
Pika!
I don't get it.
Hey, Ash, why don't you try to figure out
what Pikachu's saying?
Pikachu, Pika, Pika, Pika.
Pikachu. Chu! Chu!
-Pikachu!
-Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Okay, I think I've got it.
Pikachu says that Charmander's
waiting on that rock
for somebody to come and get it.
-[Misty] You mean it belongs to somebody?
-[Ash] Well, I'm not exactly sure.
If it's waiting for someone,
I think we better leave it.
It's probably best
if its own trainer takes care of it.
I hope its trainer comes back soon.
[whimpers]
Hey, you guys, look over there.
It's the Pokémon Center.
The one on the map.
Route 24 can't be too far.
[rain splashes]
-Pi. Pikachu.
-[Ash] Hurry!
-[Misty] Here's some nice hot soup.
-[Ash] Thanks, Misty.
Have some soup, Brock. Huh?
What's wrong?
I wonder, do you think anybody picked up
that Charmander yet?
What if its trainer left it there?
I don't think the Charmander
would wait around this long, do you?
I don't either, Ash.
Its trainer must have gotten it by now.
[men laughing]
-Sure got a lot of them.
-For sure.
Just look at them.
It's a pretty cool collection.
Heh, way cool.
You're the man, Damian.
Yo, I thought
you had a Charmander too.
Yeah, I had one
but that puny thing was so weak,
it couldn't even beat
the weakest opponents.
I don't like his attitude.
Charmander may be weak
against water Pokémon,
but if their trainers work hard,
they can be strong.
So what did you do
with the Charmander?
Eh, I left it on some rock in the woods.
[all gasp]
That thing is so stupid.
No matter I do to it,
it keeps on following me.
I finally got rid of it by promising
I'd come back for it. It fell for it.
It's probably still there waiting for me.
[all laughing]
[growls]
He's the one who abandoned
that Charmander.
Yeah, and it's still waiting for him
on that rock.
Brock, what are you doing?
I bet it's still up there
wagging its tail.
It'll probably wag it so long,
it'll put the flame out.
Yeah, for sure.
[laughs]
-Hey, what--
-[Brock] Go and get it!
[gasps]
[Brock] That Charmander is still
waiting for you. Go and get it now.
Why should I?
You lied to your Pokémon
and said you'd be back.
Now its waiting out there
in the rain for you.
And if its tail flame goes out, it'll die.
Oy, what I do is none of your business.
-[Ash] Do what he says!
-What'd you say, nerd?
You heard what I said.
And you want to be a Pokémon trainer.
-You're disgusting.
-Pika, pika!
-You want to fight with me?
-You better not mess with Damian.
Let's go!
Let's break it up. You know the rules.
[all gasp]
Pokémon are never to be used
in personal fights.
It's disrespectful to the Pokémon
and their trainers.
Yeah, well, tell them.
They were the ones what started it.
I think you'd be better off
not to get mixed up with them.
They have a very bad reputation.
Uh, thanks for the advice.
[giggles]
She sure is pretty.
I've never seen anyone as pretty as her.
What are you talking about?
She looks just like all the other Joys.
Yeah, it's a joyful world.
-All right, snap out of it.
-Ugh, huh?
Oh, quit spacing out.
What about Charmander?
Ah, that's right! We've got to help it.
This is dangerous, going out
in a storm like this to help a Pokémon.
-What if we all catch pneumonia?
-Well, nobody asked you to follow along.
Got to help a Pokémon in need.
[Spearow screeching]
[whimpering]
[Ash] Knock it off!
[all grunting]
-Thunder shock, Pikachu!
-Chu!
Pikachu!
[squawking]
Pika.
Next time, make sure
you don't shock us too, Pikachu.
Pikachu.
[Ash gasps] Oh, no!
The flame on its tail is almost out.
Let's get it to the Pokémon Center.
I'll make sure its tail flame stays lit!
[wind whooshing]
[all panting and grunting]
[Brock] Hold on!
You can make it, Charmander.
[door opens]
Joy, please help us.
[Joy] What is it? What's wrong?
-This Charmander is in bad shape.
-The flame on its tail...
[gasps There's not much time.
[wind whooshing]
[machine bleeping]
-[Brock] Will it survive?
-[Joy] Charmander is very weak.
How could you let it get
into this condition?
It's not our fault.
Damian's the one who abandoned it.
What?
Well, Damian promised Charmander
to come back for it.
Charmander's loyal to Damian,
so it believed him.
Poor Charmander.
And Damian just left
with the rest of them.
Joy, I'm begging you.
Please, save it.
Charmander has got to get better.
I'll do whatever I can.
[wind whooshing]
[in mind]
Charmander, you've got to hold on.
Please, keep your flame burning.
[dings]
[all] Huh?
Mm.
[all sigh]
Charmander's recovering.
It should be fine by morning.
[in mind]
That's the spirit, Charmander.
[all snoring]
[grunts]
-[Brock] Wake up, everybody!
-Ah! [grunts]
-What's up, Brock?
-Yeah, what's the matter?
Pikachu?
It's Charmander.
Charmander has disappeared from the ER!
[Ash] But how?
I bet it went back to
that rock to wait for Damian.
-We got to go back.
-But that's no use.
We can't force Charmander
to come with us
if it wants to wait for Damian,
even if he is a lying creep.
She's right. There's nothing you can do
until Charmander realizes the truth.
Oh, I thought Charmander understood
that we cared about it.
Brock, Charmander knew that we cared
but don't you see?
It couldn't forget about Damian.
It's still loyal to him.
-Chu.
-That's why it went back.
Hmm. Unh!
Come on!
Route 24 is just ahead.
Once we get to Vermilion City,
there will be plenty of Pokémon.
[Brock sighs]
To protect the world from devastation...
To unite all peoples within our nation...
[both] To denounce the evils
of truth and love,
to extend our reach
to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James.
Mm, mind if I cut in?
Huddle up!
They're going to be here soon.
Finally, a foolproof plan
to capture Pikachu.
I'm so excited.
I can't wait to test our new automatic,
high-speed, super-duper, whatchamacallit!
[Jessie and James] Start it up.
So, what does this thing do, anyway?
[clanking and whirring]
Not another hole driller!
We tried that already!
If at first you don't succeed...
This time, we'll remember
where the hole is.
Are you sure you're going to remember
where the trap is?
Meowth, don't you think
we're smarter than that?
[sighs]
-Our trap is set.
-Huh?
Hey, here they come now!
[bleeping]
Hm, they're getting warm.
-[chuckles] Warmer...
-They're burning up.
It's too strong.
You used too many tree branches.
Me? You're the one
who covered it with too much dirt.
[growls]
Meowth!
Quiet.
-Whoa, you feel something?
-I did.
Huh? Feel what?
[rumbling]
[all yell]
Pikachu.
[all groaning]
Pika, pika?
[squeaks]
[Meowth] I can't believe they fell for it.
[Jessie] Our invention worked.
We're geniuses!
-Pi.
-Come with us, Pikachu.
-You belong to us now.
-[Pikachu] Chu!
[James]
Rubber won't conduct electricity.
[Jessie] Just another example
of our incredible genius at work.
You have to be a rocket scientist to
outsmart us, the team rocket scientists.
We call these our anti-Pikachu suits.
We made them ourselves.
I must admit, I don't think
this is really my color at all.
Enough talk! Let's just grab
the Pikachu and get out of here!
[gasps]
[James] We'll use our anti-Pikachu
rubber balloon bazooka.
Ready. Aim. Fire!
[whimpers]
[pants]
Chu!
[all] Pikachu, Pikachu!
Pikachu!
[grunts]
Come on, you guys, get up!
We got to do something!
We'd love to get up Ash.
Unfortunately, you're standing on us.
[Jessie cackles]
Hello down there.
Thank you so much for dropping in.
Don't worry. Pikachu is safe with us.
We won't lose it like you did.
Chu.
-Pikachu.
-Let's get out of here.
[Charmander] Charmander!
[Jessie] What is that thing?
Charmander.
It's saying you better give Pikachu
back to those guys right now.
It's got to be kidding.
Now, step aside,
you insolent little firebug.
We haven't got time to play with you.
Team rocket plays rough
so get moving.
[all] Huh?
Char!
[all groan]
[all scream]
You see, didn't I tell you
we needed fireproof uniforms?
Shut up and keep running!
Some geniuses. Meowth!
[Team Rocket] Looks like
Team Rocket's blasting off again!
Charmander beat them?
Unh! Wow!
Thanks for the help, Charmander.
You see, Brock?
Charmander knew we cared.
-That's why it's here.
-Way to go.
Charmander, how'd you like
to join up with us?
I'm afraid your trainer
isn't going to be coming back.
Hi, Charmander. Been looking
all over for you.
-Damian, it's you!
-What do you want, Damian?
I came back for Charmander
just like I promised.
[all gasp]
So let's go.
[whimpering]
Careful. This trainer's already
abandoned you once before.
Charmander is mine.
I'm the one who caught it, remember?
Damian, you bragged about
how you abandoned it.
Good thing I did.
That toughened it up.
Besides, what's wrong with dumping
off a weak Pokémon'
[gasps]
I wasn't going to come back for it,
but now that I've seen what it can do,
I'm real glad I ran into you guys.
The best thing is, I didn't have to
raise it myself!
That's terrible.
Raising a Pokémon
is the best part of being a trainer.
You wish!
It's the most boring part of the job.
How dare you call yourself
a Pokémon trainer!
You see?
He doesn't care about you.
He just wants to use you
to win matches.
-Charmander.
Charmander, return!
[squeaks]
Ah! [groans]
[all gasp]
That does it! I'll crush you
with every Pokémon I've got!
Char!
Chu!
[yelling]
[sobs] Mommy!
-[Brock] Way to go, Charmander!
-[Ash] Yeah, good work.
Go ahead, Ash. You get Charmander.
It'll be a great Pokémon.
But, Brock, you saved it,
so you deserve it, I guess.
Right, but don't forget, you're the one
who kept the flame on its tail lit.
I'm sure you'll raise Charmander
to become a great Pokémon.
Thank you, Brock.
Come on, Charmander.
Welcome to the group!
Char! Char!
You got a Pokémon and a new friend.
Yeah.
[narrator] And so Charmander joins
Ash and his friends on their journey.
Maybe getting lost
isn't so bad after all,
especially when you're lost
with your friends.
Of course, finding your way
with your friends is even better.
Okay, guys,
we got to rap some Pokémon.
You just do the singing.
I'll take care of the hard part.
Let's get it on.
♪ I want to be the best there ever was ♪
♪ To beat all the rest, yeah
That's my cause ♪
♪ Electrode, Diglett, Nidoran, Mankey
Venusaur, Rattata, Fearow, Pidgey ♪
♪ Seaking, Jolteon, Dragonite, Gastly
Ponyta, Vaporeon, Poliwrath, Butterfree ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I'll search across the land
Look far and wide ♪
♪ Release from my hand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Venomoth, Poliwag, Nidorino, Golduck
Ivysaur, Grimer, Victreebel, Moltres ♪
♪ Nidoking, Farfetch'd, Abra, Jigglypuff
Kingler, Rhyhorn, Clefable, Wigglytuff ♪
Thirty-two down!
That's it for now!
Tune in tomorrow.
We'll rap at you some more .
There's 150,
so watch Monday through Friday.
♪ You'll catch 'em all! ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪