♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon!
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪
[Narrator] Once again we find Ash, Misty
and Brock continuing their journey.
And once again the ever-vigilant Pikachu
keeps a careful watch for trouble.
Sort of.
-Huh?
-Groovy.
Greetings, children of the universe.
-Hello. Are you all by yourself?
-I have my music.
[plays Poké flute]
[all chuckle happily]
Pik? Pika.
-Wow.
-That was nice.
Now that you heard my music,
you have to give me some food.
-[all] Huh?
-We thought it was free.
Isn't my flute playing
at least worth a sandwich?
Uh, we'd like to give you
something to eat,
but we don't even have anything
to eat ourselves.
-Not even a cookie?
-Cookie? We don't even have crumbs.
Another free concert.
Well, guess you should hit the road, then.
Ah.
[groans] I'm so hungry.
I'm about to collapse.
We haven't had anything
to eat since yesterday.
[sighs]
-Pika, pika.
-Huh?
[Poké flute playing]
Pennies for the piper?
Food'd be nice too.
-You stop people, play some weird song.
-Then you beg for food?
-You should be begging for music lessons.
-[all chuckling]
Bad vibes.
Those dudes should at least
respect their elders.
[Ash] We finally made it.
[Misty]
At last we can get something to eat.
-Pikachu.
-[Ash] Yeah.
There's no bread left!
[crying]
Excuse me.
We'd like to buy some bread, please.
-What's that? A customer?
-We'd like to buy some bread, please.
-I'm sorry. We don't have any bread left.
-No bread at a bakery.
[Brock]
There aren't any vegetables either.
-Where'd all the food go?
-I'll eat anything.
I'm sorry, but we are closed.
I'd like to cook,
but I have no ingredients.
Okay.
[Chef] Come back some other time.
This is great.
An entire town
with absolutely no food anywhere.
[sighs] Pikachu?
Children, what's the matter?
We've been looking all over for food
in this town, but there's nothing to eat.
We're so hungry we can hardly move.
[all munching loudly]
So you are trying to become
a Pokémon Master?
That's very difficult.
What's wrong with this town?
There's no bread in the bakery.
And there aren't any vegetables
at the market.
The water in the river has completely
dried up, killing all our produce.
So, food in our town has become
very, very hard to come by.
It's hard enough
to keep food for ourselves to eat.
Huh? Oh, please don't worry.
My family can live off our food stores
for quite a while yet.
But I don't remember the weather being
any drier this year than it usually is.
-It rained just like it always does.
-It's not the rain.
This is the river that used to flow
through our town.
For some reason,
it suddenly stopped running two weeks ago.
-The plants... they're all dried up.
-Pika, pika?
We can't produce wheat or vegetables.
Our town's in real trouble.
And you can't grow anything
without water, can you?
No. This is a serious problem.
Could the source of the problem
be somewhere upstream?
Let's go check it out.
We have to pay you back
for that delicious meal.
We'll find out what the problem is.
Mr. Mayor,
we'll be back as soon as we can.
I should warn you
that no one dares go upstream anymore.
-There's no telling what you might find.
-That's okay.
-We're always ready for anything.
-Pika!
[Ash]
Why would the river just dry up like this?
-[Misty] It's weird.
-[Ash] Mm-hm.
-Hey, what's that?
-[Ash] The river leads to a dead end.
[Brock]
The whole thing's covered with thorns.
-Oh!
-Be careful. Those things are sharp.
How am I supposed to be careful?
Everywhere you look, there's more thorns.
-Pika, ka, ka, ka.
-Hey, Pikachu, are you okay?
Say, Ash, let's get our Pokémon
to help us out here.
-Good idea.
-Bulbasaur!
-Bulbasaur, razor leaf attack!
-Saur.
Okay, Starmie, your turn!
-Uh--
-Psy!
Just when you think
things can't get worse.
-Ugh, we're finally through those thorns.
-Pikachu.
Ah, it's a spring.
It looks like the spring
is starting to dry up too.
-What's that?
-[snoring]
[snoring]
-Pika, pika.
-Whoa, it's huge.
[Brock] It's a Snorlax!
-That's a Snorlax?
-All right.
[Pokédex]
Snorlax, a sleeping Pokémon.
Snorlax wakes only to eat.
[Ash] It doesn't sound too hungry.
[Misty] Ash, look. Snorlax is blocking
the water from the spring.
That's why the water in the stream
stopped flowing.
So we just have to get Snorlax
out of the way.
Well, let's wake it up.
-[Ash] Wake up, Snorlax.
-[Misty] Hey, Snorlax, wake up.
-Wow, he's really big.
-Pika, pika.
Hey, Snorlax! Wake up!
[all groaning]
[snoring]
[Misty] It just won't wake up.
-Well, then, we'll have to move it.
-[grunting]
[all groaning]
Snorlax. Snorlax.
Why is it so hard to move?
Snorlax is the heaviest species
of all known Pokémon,
with some weighing more than 1,000 pounds.
[Ash] A thousand pounds?
Well, then, there's no way
we'll be able to move it.
There must be some way.
Well, what if we tried to capture it
in a Poké Ball?
Ah! That's it!
Poké Ball, go! Oh, great.
We've got to move it
or the town will run out of water.
[Ash] Argh! Snorlax, wake up!
Come on!
-Yay. It's a Snorlax.
-Right.
-We'll go after it in a formation Z.
-Okay.
[Brock]
Well, then, how should we wake it up?
Good morning, everyone.
Oh, well,
it's not really morning anymore.
Who cares anyway?
I'm here to report on the eagerly awaited
awakening of the Snorlax.
Zoom in, cameraperson.
Ah, it's sleeping. Still sleeping.
Watch closely, everyone.
This is how Snorlax looks
when it's sleeping.
Ooh, doesn't it look cute?
Now watch carefully
as we wake up the Snorlax.
What do you think you're doing?
-Prepare for trouble.
-And make it double.
-To protect the world from devastation.
-To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils
of truth and love.
To extend our reach
to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James.
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Your routine's so boring,
Snorlax'll go into a deeper sleep.
Ha! That's what you think.
-This is R2 calling R1, over.
-This is R1. All systems are go.
It's Meowth!
The ultra-deluxe balloon bang-bang
is about to begin.
-What are those things?
-[laughs]
Soon you'll be seeing Snorlax on cable.
I hate to let them steal Snorlax,
but if they get it
out of the way for us...
The spring water will flow like before.
Pika. Pika, pika.
Well I never thought
I'd live to see this day,
even with nine lives.
Team Rocket and Team Twerp
working together.
Pika. Pika, pika.
-Pika, pika.
-[James] Okay, hoist away!
Steady. Keep it up. Keep it up.
We've got it now.
[creaking]
Just a bit further.
-Ah!
-Whoa!
-[all groan]
-The cables were too weak to lift Snorlax.
I knew this wouldn't work.
Yeah, we should have known
Team Rocket would mess things up.
-What did you say?
-Well, it's the truth.
Nothing makes me angrier
than being told the truth.
[Meowth groans]
It looks like we're going to have
to wake up Snorlax after all.
[alarm rings]
-Pika. Pika.
-An alarm clock doesn't work.
Let's see it sleep through this. Ha!
-That's sure to do it.
-Nothing could sleep through that.
[snoring]
[both sob]
-It's not waking up.
-But why not?
Ah! I've got it.
In the story of Sleeping Beauty,
the beautiful princess,
with whom I identify,
was awakened by the kiss
of a noble prince.
[James] Jessie, that's it.
Snorlax might just wake
with a kiss from a noble Pokémon.
Hey, that might just work.
All right, everyone.
Pick your noblest Pokémon,
-and we'll try it.
-Okay!
It's supposed to be
a noble Pokémon, right?
-Yeah, whatever that means.
-What about Misty's Horsea?
Yeah, that's right.
It's like a prince's horse.
What? You want Horsea to kiss that?
-It has to. Horsea's our best bet.
-No fair.
Horsea, Horsea. I think this is--
Psyduck? Psy!
-[both] Ah!
-Oh, no!
-Duck!
-Ah! You dimwit duck!
-There's nothing noble about you!
-Psy, psy, psy.
Psy? Psy?
Brock, which Pokémon
do you think they'll try?
The same ones they always do.
-Snorlax will have nightmares.
-Those lips would give me nightmares too.
-Our noble Pokémon...
-[both] Ta-da!
Meowth is the only one with a kiss
powerful enough to wake Snorlax.
[James]
Give it a big wet one, fella.
Why do I have to be the one to kiss
that big lummox?
[chuckles] So we can bring that Snorlax
back to the boss.
Hey, you don't look half bad, Meowth.
-[Meowth] Keep your eyes to yourself.
-Pikachu.
Pucker up.
-Give it a smack attack right on the lips.
-Disgusting. I quit. No way!
The hygiene! Mwah!
-[groans]
-Lax.
-Is it?
-That kiss may've done it!
[snoring]
It looks like it's been poisoned.
How'd you look
if you got kissed by Meowth?
I'd look for a new mouth.
Hey! Wake up, you big lump!
Hiyah!
[screaming]
-[groans]
-[Ash] Huh?
[grunting]
-What'd you find, Ash?
-It says, "Do not disturb."
It's like those signs
you hang on hotel doors.
-Turn it over, Ash.
-Huh?
"In case of emergency,
please use a Poké flute to wake."
-[Misty] A Poké flute?
-That's right. Now I remember.
I heard once that you play a Poké flute
to wake up a Snorlax.
A Poké flute?
The Poké flute is used
to wake sleeping Pokémon.
Snorlax will only awaken to this flute.
-Huh?
-Oh!
It looks just like the one
that old hippie had.
-Come on. Let's go find him.
-Pika!
-Poké flute?
-Hippie? Huh?
[Poké flute playing]
-[both] The music man!
-[grunting]
-Oh, no. We've let them get ahead of us.
-Let's hurry.
Wait for me!
-Hmm?
-[all yelling]
Pika!
-What's the rush, dudes?
-Ah, thank goodness you're still here.
Please, sir.
We have a favor to ask of you.
-Ask away.
-Just come with us.
-Hey, hey. Chill out, my friend.
-[all] Wait, wait, wait!
-Hi, again. Please come with us.
-We really need your help.
Hey, let go of him right now.
We got here first.
-The first are the worst.
-[all grunting]
If you don't stop,
you'll both get half of me.
Enough of this. Arbok, go!
Pidgeotto, I choose you!
[screeching]
Pidgeotto, gust attack now!
[all grunting and screaming]
[all] Team Rocket's gusting off again!
Great. Now's our chance.
[snores]
Please play your Poké flute
to wake this Snorlax.
Hey, you've gotten a lot bigger
since I saw you last, Snorlax.
Your girth is blowing my mind.
You mean you know this Snorlax?
I don't just know it.
This Snorlax is mine.
This little dude loves to snooze.
I can't even take it for a walk.
I just come to wake it up once a month.
Huh?
I'm running a little late this month,
though.
Your Snorlax is stopping the water
from flowing into town.
-We've got to move it out of the way.
-No problem. I can do it.
[Poké flute playing]
Snorlax.
Snore, snore, snore, lax, lax, lax.
[all gasp]
-Pikachu.
-Lax, lax, lax.
-Snorlax.
-[Brock] I guess that did it.
[footsteps pounding]
[Hippie] Later, Snorlax.
[Misty]
Look, the water still isn't coming out.
[Brock] Ah, look at that.
[Misty] Oh, not more thorns.
That means we'll have to clear out
all of these thorns
before the river can start flowing
into town again.
What a job.
-[bushes rustling]
-[all] Huh?
[munching loudly]
Chow down, Snorlax.
Looks like you got a case of the munchies.
-Look, it's eating the thorns.
-Thorns are Snorlax's favorite snack item.
Snorlax's hunger isn't satisfied
until it consumes 900 pounds of food.
Then it goes back to sleep.
Back to sleep?
Look, guys.
The river's back to normal again.
Pika!
Thank goodness.
The river's flowing just like before.
How can we thank you?
-It wasn't just us.
-The Snorlax helped out too.
This calls for a celebration.
We'll hold a special banquet.
-[Misty and Ash] All right!
-Okay!
-[all laughing]
-Pika. Pika!
[groans]
I'm getting tired of always being beaten.
I'm as tired as Snorlax.
Hey there. What happened to Snorlax?
Mi amigo, Snorlax ate all those thorns,
and it's copping some Z's.
It went back to sleep?
Mm-hm.
It'll be a while before it wakes up.
-About how long?
-Well, let's see.
This one wakes up about once a moon.
[both groan]
[device bleeps]
Well, I got to split,
wake up another Snorlax.
Keep on trucking, dudes. [laughs]
[all groan]
[Jessie] Should we try
to capture the Snorlax?
-I ain't kissing it.
-We'd better kiss it goodbye.
[Narrator]
Our heroes have awakened the Snorlax,
unstopped the river and saved the town.
And the Snorlax? Well, do not disturb,
until feeding time, that is.
[all yell and scream]
[Snorlax] Lax. [snores]
Okay guys,
we gotta rap some Pokemon.
You just do the singing.
I'll take care of the hard part.
Let's get it on.
♪ I want to be the best
That ever was ♪
♪ To beat all the rest
Yeah, that's my cause ♪
♪ Electrode, Diglett, Nidoran, Mankey
Venusaur, Rattata, Fearow, Pidgey ♪
♪ Seaking, Jolteon, Dragonite, Gastly
Ponyta, Vaporeon, Poliwrath, Butterfree ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Pokemon ♪
♪ I'll search across the land
Look far and wide ♪
♪ Release from my hand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Venomoth, Poliwag, Nidorino, Golduck
Ivysaur, Grimer, Victreebel, Moltres ♪
♪ Nidoking, Farfetch'd, Abra, Jigglypuff
Kingler, Rhyhorn, Clefable, Wigglytuff ♪
Thirty two down. That's it for now.
Tune in tomorrow.
We'll rap at you some more.
There's 150, so watch Monday
through Friday You catch them all
♪ Catch them, catch them
Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪