♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch them all
Pokémon ♪
Hey! We're here!
[narrator] After earning a soul badge
at the Fuchsia Gym,
our friends arrive at the Safari Zone,
where they're sure to discover
some new and unusual Pokémon.
-Hey, it feels like an earthquake!
-Look out! Over there!
[rumbling]
Uh, what is it?
[grunting and mooing]
-Pika! Pi!
-Oh, man.
-What are those things?
-Pika!
[Pokédex] Tauros. A wild bull Pokémon.
When whipping itself with its three tails,
its tackle is
a powerful destructive force.
Yes. Okay, Pikachu. Hmm? Huh?
Hey, Pikachu!
Nice time for a nap.
Don't you think
Pikachu's outnumbered here?
I know that.
Charmander, I choose you!
-Char!
-Ember attack now!
Char!
[Growlithe howls]
[Charmander grunts]
What's that thing?
[Pokédex] Growlithe. A puppy Pokémon
of pleasant demeanor and great diligence.
It drives enemies away
with barks and bites.
Growlithe?
All right, Charmander,
flamethrower attack!
Char! Char!
[growls]
So it's a fire type too.
Charmander, return!
Maybe Squirtle.
-Hold it!
-[Ponyta neighing]
Whoa!
-Hey, what are you doing?
-You little sidewinder,
don't tell me you don't know
this whole area is a Pokémon reserve.
-A Pokémon preserve?
-Yes.
What's that?
It's a place where it's against the law
to capture Pokémon
so they can grow up here naturally.
That's amazing.
[chuckles]
You grew up right pretty yourself, miss.
What's the name of this here place?
Have you ever heard
of the Big P. Pokémon Ranch
that's owned by the Laramie family?
Isn't that the place where they raise
lots of Pokémon in the wild?
Hey! This must be that place.
This is the Laramie Big P. Ranch,
and I'm Lara Laramie.
Growlithe!
And this Growlithe makes sure
nobody tries to capture our Pokémon.
-[both] Oh.
-Pikachu.
[Pokédex]
Ponyta. A fire horse Pokémon.
Its mane is made of intense flames.
-Whoa.
-Pika.
-Isn't it real hot?
-I don't need to worry
because Ponyta will never,
ever burn anybody it really trusts.
[grunts] Hmm.
Nice Ponyta.
[screams]
[Ash groaning]
[giggles] It took a while for Ponyta
to trust me too.
Just training one Pokémon's a big job,
but a whole herd must be really tough.
[Brock] Breeders love Pokémon
from the Laramie ranch.
Because they're raised in the wild,
and they're a little stronger
than other Pokémon.
You're lucky if you get a Big P. Pokémon.
[chuckles] I'm real glad some folks know
about all the hard work we do.
We're real proud of the way
we raise our Pokémon here.
I'd love to see more of this place.
Well, we're having our big party here
tonight.
-Why don't you all come as my guests?
-A party? That sounds great!
Pika! Pika!
And if you stay here at the ranch tonight,
you'll be able to see
the big Pokémon race tomorrow.
A Pokémon race?
We race one another
to find out who's got the best Pokémon.
Anybody who wins the Big P. Pokémon race
becomes an honorary member
of the Laramie clan.
-[rumbling]
-Huh?
The Tauros again?
[Lara]
No. That sound could only be...
-Oh, man. They move fast!
-Howdy, Lara.
[Pokédex]
Dodrio. A three-headed bird Pokémon
that can run faster than it can fly.
Its three heads represent
joy, sorrow and anger.
We're going to win
the Pokémon race tomorrow.
Don't be too sure, pardner.
It takes more than just speed
to win the race.
Just get ready to lose, Lara.
Yee-hee!
What a jerk! Who is that guy?
He's Dario, a Dodrio trainer.
And we'll see what kind of guy he is.
Hey, Lara, good luck in the race tomorrow.
-We're all going to be rooting for you.
-Thank you kindly.
-[woman] Your Ponyta's great.
-Thank you, ma'am.
-[man 1] Good luck, Lara!
-Appreciate it.
[man 2] Go for it, girl!
She must be a real contender in that race.
Well, she sure has done a great job
training that Ponyta of hers.
We're really lucky to have run into such
an incredible Pokémon breeder, aren't we?
[man] Hey, Lara!
All of your Tauros are going crazy
back at the ranch.
[both] Huh?
[whistles]
Hyah!
-Let's go!
-[panting]
[chuckles maniacally]
Hey. What...?
[zapping]
Growlithe,
get in there and settle them down.
Growlithe.
Growlithe. Growlithe. Growlithe.
Hmm. What's that?
[Ponyta neighs]
[Lara screams]
[groaning]
Lara! Ponyta!
-Lara.
-I think I'm okay. [groans]
Don't move that arm!
Whoa, Ponyta! Settle down! [grunts]
[groans]
Come on. Settle down.
Calm down, Ponyta!
[neighs]
[sighs] I wonder what happened
to spook all the Pokémon.
He's good.
-Pretty nice work.
-Even better than we planned it.
I have got a very good feeling
about this one.
-[man] Good work.
-Huh?
I wouldn't expect anything less
from Team Rocket.
-Meowth.
-We're just here
to do the best job possible
so we can all get just what we want.
Once Team Rocket gets in
with the Laramie clan,
we'll make big bucks.
We're going to get rich
and rule the world!
We're going to make sure
that you win that race, Dario.
Uh-huh. If I get what I want,
you get what you want.
Right, pardner.
[all laughing]
[sighs]
With my arm like this,
I can't grip Ponyta's reins,
so I won't be able to race tomorrow.
Too bad for the Laramie clan.
Hold on.
Ash, you could ride Ponyta for me.
[both] Huh?
I can't do it.
Ponyta will burn any rider except you.
[chuckles] I'm sure you could do it.
When I saw you trying so hard
to pet Ponyta,
I knew you could, Ash.
Please give it a try.
Yeah, but...
[whinnies]
Give it a try.
-We'll help you in every way we can.
-Pika. Pikachu.
Well, in that case I'll do it.
Looks like we're partners, Ponyta.
[screams]
-I guess Ponyta's not too cool with this.
-Pika.
-Ponyta!
-[neighs]
Ponyta,
if you win the race with a new rider,
it'll prove how great you really are.
Everybody'll know
that you're the best of all.
And that is the best praise for me.
Won't you please let Ash
ride you tomorrow?
[grunts]
Remember, Ponyta.
[groans] Hey, it's not hot.
I did it. Yeah!
Oh! [yelling]
[Brock sighs]
-At least he's hanging in there.
-Pika.
[yelling]
[cheering]
[announcer] Welcome, ladies and gentlemen,
to this year's Pokémon challenge,
sponsored by the Laramie clan.
Our course takes our challengers
over rugged terrain
to test their speed and ability.
Whoever clears all the obstacles
and crosses the finish line first
is our winner.
Will the Pokémon and trainers
please come to the starting line now?
-Good luck, guys!
-Huh?
Ready to race, Ponyta?
-Hey!
-They're going to burn up the track!
Ready...
Go!
[announcer] And they're off
on this exciting Pokémon challenge race.
When the dust settles,
we'll be able to see
who's in the early lead.
-Squirtle!
-Pika!
Now the contestants have left the stadium
and are on the first part
of the obstacle course.
-Yee-ha!
-Pika, pika! Pi.
[announcer] And Dario riding Dodrio
has pulled away from the pack.
If he keeps up this blistering pace,
he'll be unstoppable.
You can beat him, Ash.
[moos]
[announcer]
And something has happened to the Tauros.
It's acting like this is a rodeo.
Whoa! And now Nidorina is fighting mad
after getting bumped by Tauros.
They're ignoring their trainers
and starting to battle.
These Pokémon could use
some strict training.
They look like they're out of this race.
-I got a bull's-eye!
-Or close to it.
[announcer] The next obstacle
is a 45-degree uphill climb,
a test of endurance
for the Pokémon and their trainers,
and Dario still holds the lead.
[grunts] Come on, Ponyta!
Squirtle. Squirtle.
[announcer] Bringing up the rear
are Pikachu and Squirtle,
but slow and steady may not be enough
to win this race.
Whoa! Who is that
barreling down the steep slope?
-What?
-He's fast!
That's Electrode
using its perfectly round body
to gain speed
and take the lead on the downhill.
[both laughing]
[announcer]
Oh, and it's another accident!
Electrode has fallen into a hole,
and Dodrio once again takes over the lead.
Oh, no!
Electrode's voltage level is too high!
-Ah!
-Ash!
[announcer] What a shock!
Electrode's most powerful attack:
explosion.
It's destroyed everything around.
Electrode's living up
to its bomb ball nickname.
[both laughing]
Another one bites the dust.
-Pikachu.
-[Squirtle grunting]
-Pikachu!
-[screaming]
-[sighs]
-Oh, no!
[announcer] They're back up!
Ponyta and Lara's replacement, Ash,
are showing that they've really got guts.
All right.
[announcer] Now one of the most difficult
sections of the course.
The Pokémon have to jump
from one stone to the next
to cross the river.
Go! Go, Dodrio!
[growling]
Ah!
That's okay. We tried.
Ah! Too bad, folks.
Rock Pokémon can't deal with water,
so Onyx is out of here.
Pika!
[announcer]
And looks like surf's up for Pikachu.
Squirtle and Starmie are performing
like true-blue water Pokémon.
-I'll keep on going, Brock!
-Pikachu.
[announcer] Ponyta's a great jumper
and crossing beautifully,
with no fear of the water.
It could make a comeback!
Faster! Faster! Faster!
That's it. You can do it, Ash.
[announcer] Now to boost their energy,
each Pokémon can resume the race
only after eating an entire bowl of food.
The Pokémon decide which bowl to eat.
Ah! Oh, quit fighting!
You'll all get your fair share.
[announcer] It looks like each one
of Dodrio's three heads
wants to eat first,
and a fight's broken out!
The fastest runner
is losing valuable time here
as Starmie, Squirtle and Ponyta
appear on the scene.
Okay, Ponyta, time for some fast food.
[grumbles]
All right, Team Rocket,
time to go to work!
Ah!
[announcer]
We've got a major problem here, folks.
Black smoke is blowing over the course.
I hope our camera crew
can get our picture back soon
and show us if there's been
another accident out there.
Ponyta.
[Jessie] Prepare for trouble.
[James] Make it double.
It's Team Rocket.
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation.
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love
To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James.
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth! That's right!
We don't have time
to play around with you three stooges!
How dare compare us to the...
I mean, come on up.
I'd like to have a word with you.
Yes, come on up
and bring your Ponyta with you.
Then I can mess you up again.
"Mess you up again?"
So it was Team Rocket!
It was you who broke Lara's arm.
-It was such a sad accident.
-We couldn't sleep after it happened.
Save your tears!
Pikachu, Squirtle, get ready to rumble!
Squirtle!
This race is over for you, losers.
Arbok, glare attack!
-Squirtle!
-Pika!
Let's go, Starmie!
Weezing, sludge attack now!
[grunts]
You okay, Starmie?
-I think we're winning.
-I think you're right.
Whoa! Settle down, Ponyta.
Hey, calm down!
Dario. Now's your chance.
Thanks, Jessie! Go, Dodrio.
Team Rocket's working for Dario.
Ash! Forget about them.
You have to win this race
for Lara Laramie.
Go catch up with Dario,
and we'll take care of Team Rocket.
-But... But I...
-Pika!
Stop Ponyta with your poison sting.
-Ar!
-Ah!
[neighs]
Arbok!
[grunts]
Oh, no! Don't use the gas.
[all screaming]
Things seemed to be going so well for us
this time.
Maybe we'll have better luck next time.
Now we're blasting off again!
[announcer] Yes. Now we've got our picture
back and Dodrio is still in the lead!
Now let's take a look at what happened to
the other Pokémon and I can't see any...
Wait. Who's that?
It's a giant burning flame!
Faster, Ponyta. We're way behind!
[announcer] It's Ponyta!
I don't know how it happened,
but it looks like this has become
a two Pokémon race
between Dodrio and Ponyta,
with nothing left but a flat-out run
to the finish line.
And Dodrio has entered the stadium,
still in the lead!
[cackles]
I'm going to win this one! [cackles]
[cheers and applause]
Huh? How'd he get so close?
[announcer]
Now Ponyta's closing in on Dodrio.
Okay, Ponyta, let's beat him.
[announcer]
Now, these two powerful Pokémon
are trading the lead.
Do it, Dodrio.
Ah! [moaning]
[announcer] Something's happened.
Ponyta is falling behind.
That was a cheap shot, Dario!
I do what I have to to win.
[announcer]
Dodrio is closing in on the finish line!
[groaning and gasping]
[screaming]
-Ponyta just--
-Evolved into Rapidash.
[announcer]
Fans, this is incredible!
Ponyta has evolved into Rapidash,
the fastest sprinter
in the world of Pokémon.
I can't believe it.
[announcer]
Here comes Rapidash,
who has a top speed
of over 100 mile an hour!
And Rapidash has caught up!
They're neck and neck
heading for the finish line.
Come on, Dodrio!
Rapidash!
[announcer]
It's down to the wire!
[cheers and applause]
[announcer] An incredible upset!
Rapidash makes an amazing comeback
to win this Pokémon challenge!
-Way to go, Rapidash!
-You cheater!
You interfered with me!
-You're the one who attacked me.
-I'll show you.
Go get them!
Huh? Oh!
[announcer] Congratulations, Ponyta...
I mean, Rapidash!
You are this year's
Pokémon challenge champion.
Let's give a big hand for its trainer,
Lara Laramie,
and for the winning rider, Ash Ketchum!
-[barks]
-Yeah!
Squirtle.
-Hey, congratulations, Lara. [chuckles]
-Thank you, Ash.
You proved yourself
to be a fantastic Pokémon trainer.
Isn't that right, Rapidash?
[giggles] Aw, shucks, Rapidash!
[all laugh]
If you're looking to capture Pokémon,
the Safari Zone just ahead
should be perfect.
The Safari Zone? That's the place for me.
Thanks again, Ash. You did a great job.
I'm sure you'll be a Pokémon master.
Thanks, Lara, I'm much obliged.
[narrator] As our heroes say goodbye
to their new friend
at the Laramie Pokémon ranch,
they're headed for new adventures
in the Safari Zone.
[groans]
You're the reason I didn't win
the Pokémon challenge.
Team Rocket's the worst.
We'll just have to plan better next year.
And maybe you can get yourself
some nicer riding clothes.
And give that smelly bird a bath.
[all mutter]
-[Team Rocket grunt]
-[Meowth] James! Stop this crazy thing!
♪ Pokémon! ♪
It's that time again.
A hundred and fifty Pokémon
five days a week.
That's about 30 or so each day.
It's not too hard,
just listen real good.
♪ Alakazam, Doduo, Venonat, Machoke ♪
♪ Kangaskhan, Hypno
Electabuzz, Flareon ♪
♪ Blastoise, Poliwhirl, Oddish, Drowzee ♪
♪ Raichu, Nidoqueen
Bellsprout, Starmie ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Metapod, Marowak, Kakuna, Clefairy ♪
♪ Dodrio, Seadra, Vileplume, Krabby ♪
♪ Lickitung, Tauros, Weedle, Nidoran ♪
♪ Machop, Shellder, Porygon, Hitmonchan ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
Okay, so today was pretty easy.
But you gotta put
All five days together.
It's the only way to name all 150.
Catch you here tomorrow .
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Oh gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Ooh, gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Its you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪