♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon! Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, gotta catch 'em all
[narrator] Last time, Ash and his friends
traveled to the Pokémon Tower
in Lavender Town.
His mission,
to capture the ghost Pokémon he needs
to defeat the psychic Pokémon of Sabrina.
Ash had a high-flying adventure
and made some new friends.
The ghost Pokémon hated to see Ash go,
so Haunter decided to follow Ash
to Saffron City.
Now Ash is ready to face Sabrina
in the biggest Pokémon showdown
of his life.
-[Ash] We made it, Pikachu.
-[Pikachu] Pikachu.
And this time, I know we're going to win.
Right, Brock?
-Uh, if you say so.
-Huh?
-What's the matter?
-Pika?
I think maybe I'm allergic to ghosts.
Kind of feel sort of dizzy.
You're not scared are you?
Please. He couldn't be afraid
of such a cute little thing. [giggles]
[Haunter growls]
[Misty giggles]
Cute. Right.
[giggles]
-Ah!
-It just crossed the cute line. [grunts]
-Haunter! You paralyzed her.
-[groans]
[sobs]
[Ash gasps]
[Misty groans]
Hey, Haunter,
it's really not that big a deal.
[chortling]
Haunter, in Saffron City,
there's a trainer named Sabrina
who uses psychic Pokémon.
Ghost Pokémon are strong
against psychic Pokémon, right?
Will you help me defeat her?
[chortling]
Yes!
That marsh badge is as good as mine.
[Ash] Haunter versus Kadabra
[electronic bleeping]
[thinks]
That Sabrina sure showed us up last time.
She made Pikachu and me look like a joke.
This time, the joke's on her.
Hey, Brock? Misty?
Go give it your best shot, Ash.
-Yeah, let us know how it turns out.
-Pika, pika, pi!
Stop goofing around!
Aren't you even coming in with me?
Last time, she wanted to play with us
and pretended we were her bowling pins.
Remember?
And she almost bowled a strike.
Now that I've got Haunter,
that won't happen again.
I wouldn't be too sure, Ash.
What if Haunter's the one
who's controlling you?
Huh?
[chuckles] Me and Haunter are pals.
[chortling]
[laughs]
Haunter isn't worried at all.
-It's pretty confident.
-Pika, pika.
You've got nothing to worry about.
With Haunter on my side,
I'm guaranteed to win that badge.
-Now, wish me luck.
-[both] Good luck.
[Ash] Charmander!
Char!
[Ash] Squirtle!
Squirtle!
[Ash] Bulbasaur!
Bulbasaur!
Are you all ready to face Sabrina?
[all cheering]
[Haunter chortles]
Sabrina, I've come back here to your gym
to demand a rematch.
Another battle?
Even after my Kadabra beat up your Pikachu
during the last match?
You don't have a chance.
This time, you won't have it so easy.
If you lose,
you'll have to play with me again.
Go, Kadabra.
Kadabra.
And I choose as my Pokémon Haunter!
Go, Haunter!
So, you captured a ghost Pokémon, did you?
-Where is it?
-Kadabra, Kadabra.
Uh, Haunter?
Hey, Haunter, where'd you go?
Will Haunter please report to the floor?
Looks like the ghost Pokémon got spooked.
Haunter's not the most dependable Pokémon
in the world.
Pika.
Haunter!
[groans]
Enough stalling.
Send out your Pokémon at once
or you'll all go back to the toy box.
[all grunt]
Great, back where we started.
Forget Haunter. Send out another one.
Right.
-Pikachu, you...
-Pi?
Pika!
Pikachu.
Charmander, Bulbasaur, Squirtle.
-Squirtle. Squirtle, Squirtle.
-Mander.
You won't help me?
Ah! [groans]
Well, are you ready yet?
Uh, yeah, just a sec.
The battle will begin now.
Uh...
I quit.
-Whoa!
-Quit?
Run for it!
-Hey, wait for us!
-Hurry!
It's fun to catch them.
The exit!
Ah! Ugh.
We're trapped!
[giggling]
[both yelling]
Hey, Brock! Misty!
Ah! They're dolls!
[giggling]
Now I'm going to turn all of you
into dolls.
[all shouting]
Hey, take it easy. Please wait!
Hey, where'd you come from?
Sometimes, you've got to retreat to win.
Teleportation.
He's back.
[all screaming]
Pika, pika.
Hey, Pikachu, I'm glad you're safe,
but would you please get off my back?
Will you all please get off mine?
-Charmander!
-Squirtle, Squirtle, Squirtle.
[sighs]
Sabrina's the meanest trainer I ever met.
She wasn't always such a mischievous girl.
You mean, you knew Sabrina
before she changed?
Huh?
Well, I've heard stories.
Please stop, Sabrina. That's enough.
That's not a toy.
Humph.
[both grunting]
[man]
Though she was very young,
Sabrina became completely obsessed
with her psychic training.
She didn't want to make friends.
All she wanted was to be left alone
to develop her powers.
Her parents tried to help,
but Sabrina used her psychic powers
to drive them away.
The conflict caused Sabrina
to split into two girls.
The strong Pokémon trainer
who is always causing trouble
and the lonely little girl
who desperately desires to make friends.
That doll that Sabrina always holds
represents her true self
before her training,
before she rejected her own heart.
Sabrina had this picture of her family
in her room.
If you have the same picture,
then that must mean you're...
[thinks] Huh? Does he know?
He must have figured it out by now.
After everything I've said,
he must have figured out the truth
about Sabrina and me.
He must realize that I'm Sabrina's father.
Then that must mean you're a photographer.
-Ah!
-Pika!
Don't you see? Don't you get it?
-Get what?
-Never mind.
Sabrina turned Brock and Misty into dolls.
-There's nothing we can do about that.
-Huh?
The only way to rescue your friends
is to defeat Sabrina.
Isn't that why you traveled
to Lavender Town to get a ghost Pokémon?
But Haunter's disappeared someplace.
Then you must find Haunter first.
Without it, you'll never be able
to defeat Sabrina and her psychic Pokémon.
I guess not.
[sighs]
Pikachu,
where do you think Haunter could be?
Pika, pika.
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation...
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation...
To denounce the evils of truth and love...
To extend our reach to the stars above...
-Jessie.
-James.
Yeah, yeah, that's very dramatic.
Now, let's cut to the chase
and catch that Pikachu.
Just leave that to us.
By the way, what's the secret weapon
you got cooked up this time?
A deadly weapon that's been perfected
over thousands of years.
Now we have learned to use
its awesome powers.
With a flick of this fishing net,
we'll round up Pikachu.
You mean that's your secret weapon?
It takes a genius to realize
a fishing net is the perfect weapon.
Oh, James, it's the greatest discovery
since Einstein invented the light bulb.
[both] Even greater than the chicken
who invented the egg.
[both groan]
All of us true geniuses know, of course,
that it was actually the egg
that preceded the chicken.
Of course. I knew that.
I had just forgotten.
Now you got my brain scrambled.
Let's cut the eggs-planations
and capture Pikachu!
[grunts]
[growls]
[all scream]
[all yell]
[chortles]
[all whimper]
Jessie, pull us up!
You're too heavy.
I can't even pull myself up
until you both let go of my legs.
B... B.. But, Jessie, you have to.
Be brave.
If I let go, we're all goners,
but if you let go, at least I'll survive.
I'm the designated survivor,
so both of you better hold on tight.
[sobs] I thought we'd finally gotten away
from all those horrible ghost Pokémon,
but they followed us all the way here.
[howls]
[grunts]
Don't laugh, Jessie.
Otherwise, you're going to let go.
[gibbers]
[grunts]
Don't laugh. Don't smile.
I won't crack. The members of Team Rocket
have been trained to resist all silliness
and to be totally serious.
[chortles]
[screaming and laughing]
I really don't see what's so funny.
She's going to die laughing.
[screaming and laughing]
Huh? What was that?
-It's Team Rocket.
-Pikachu.
[chortling]
Haunter, you stopped them
from capturing Pikachu.
[guffawing] Haunter!
Way to go.
Now let's get back to Sabrina's gym.
[grunts]
But you promised
you'd help me battle Sabrina.
I can't beat her psychic Pokémon
without you.
[growling]
Please,
you can't let her make a fool out of me.
Haunter! [chortling]
Oh, gee, thanks, Haunter. Thank you.
Just help me save my friends,
and you'll never
have to help me out again.
Haunter, Haunter, Haunter.
[Brock thinks] Misty,
what do you think's going to happen to us?
[Misty thinks] I don't know.
I've never been a doll before.
[Brock] I don't even like dolls.
Are we going to be stuck this way forever?
[thinks]
That depends. It's up to Sabrina.
-[Brock] Ah!
-[Misty] That other doll just spoke.
[thinks] It's nice to have company.
I'm Sabrina's mother.
[Brock] Her mother?
[Misty]
She turned you into a doll too?
[mother]
Please don't think badly of Sabrina.
She's really a good daughter.
[Kadabra giggling]
-My new dolls are so cute.
-[both] Huh?
What game should I play first
with my brand-new Brock and Misty dolls?
Maybe we can have tea.
[Brock] Sabrina.
Turn us back into humans right now.
[Misty] I challenge you to a match.
If I win, you've got to change us back.
If I change you back,
you'll just run away from me.
You have to stay as dolls.
We'll play together all the time,
and we'll all be friends forever.
[Ash] Sabrina!
I knew he'd be back.
Have you returned for more humiliation?
Haven't you realized
that you'll never defeat me?
Brock and Misty are my friends,
and I can't leave them behind,
not even if you're going to turn me
and all my Pokémon into dolls!
-Pika!
-[both] Ash!
If you want to be a doll too,
I'll be glad to play with you.
It'll be a one-on-one battle.
Sabrina's Pokémon will be...
Kadabra.
-And for my Pokémon, I choose Haunter!
-Haunter?
Well, where is your Pokémon?
Oh, no, not again. Ah!
-[Pikachu] Pikachu!
-Why don't you forfeit?
That way,
I'll have new dolls to play with.
Ah!
Haunter! Haunter!
You promised me!
Where'd you go? Please stop hiding!
-Haunter! Haunter!
-Pika.
This time, you won't escape.
[giggling] My new dolly.
Dolly?
[groans]
-Pika!
-Pikachu!
You don't stand a chance against Kadabra.
You'll get beat up again.
-Come back!
-Pi. Pika!
-You don't want Sabrina to make me a doll?
-Pikachu.
-You want to fight for me?
-Pika!
Thank you, Pikachu. You're a real pal.
Pikachu, thunder shock!
Pikachu!
Kadabra, teleport.
[grunts]
Kadabra, psybeam.
Kadabra.
[whimpering]
Pikachu.
Try to hang on, Pikachu.
Come back at Kadabra with a thunderbolt.
Pikachu. Pika... chu!
Kadab... [whimpers]
-That's it.
-Recover.
Kadabra.
-[Ash gasps]
-Pika!
It's impossible to win.
[giggles]
Haunter?
Haunter!
[chortling]
Two against one's not fair.
It is just playing around on its own.
Haunter is not battling against you,
so it isn't against the rules.
Ah!
[grunts]
[growls]
[all] Huh?
[both gasp]
[Haunter cackles]
-Ah, she smiled.
-Huh?
-[chuckles]
-Haunter, Haunter.
[both laugh]
Is that Sabrina laughing?
Ever since she started
her telekinetic training as a little girl,
I've never seen Sabrina laugh like this.
I've never seen her so happy
in her entire life.
But if you've known Sabrina
ever since she was a little girl,
-does that mean...?
-Hmm. So you figured it out, eh?
You must have taken her baby pictures too.
[man screams]
Just how dense can a person be?
[clears throat]
But I'm glad you came back.
That Haunter has helped Sabrina
rediscover the human part of her heart.
What do you mean?
Haunter was supposed to beat
the psychic Pokémon,
and instead,
it's making friends with Sabrina.
I'm going to be a doll.
-Hmm, look over there.
-Huh?
[laughing] Kadabra.
I don't get it.
It looks like Kadabra's in pain.
It's not in any pain.
Kadabra and Sabrina
are joined telepathically.
Kadabra is rolling with laughter,
just like Sabrina.
[groaning]
[laughing]
[both gasping]
[both] Ah!
-Misty! Brock!
-Pika!
Since Kadabra is no longer able to battle,
I officially declare Pikachu the winner.
[both laughing]
[Ash] Goodbye!
-Thank you for everything!
-Have a good journey!
-Take care of yourselves!
-See you later!
[Ash] I've finally got a marsh badge.
And that marsh badge
puts you one step further along the road
to the Pokémon League.
Yeah, but do you really think
I deserved to get this marsh badge?
[Misty] Sure.
Making Sabrina laugh herself
into a defeat is great strategy.
Pika, pika!
Keep it up, and you'll become known
as the funniest Pokémon master
of all time.
Hello up there, anyone!
We're trapped down here!
-Stop pouring cement! Ah!
-Get me out of here quick!
-Huh?
-What's wrong?
I could've sworn I just heard
Team Rocket's voices.
No way.
We've got more important stuff
to think of, like where we're going.
Okay. So where's the next closest Gym?
In Celadon City.
Look out, Celadon City!
Ash Ketchum is coming to town!
-Pika!
-Hey, wait up, Ash!
[narrator]
With a little help from Haunter,
Ash was able to defeat Sabrina
and win a marsh badge.
Will he get another badge in Celadon City?
And what adventures will our friends
find along the way?
Those answers aren't yet written in stone.
And speaking of things in stone...
or cement,
how will Team Rocket
get out of this mess?
-A little cement...
-Will never stop Team Rocket.
A little cement?
[all gasping]
[all] We're blasting off again!
-♪ Pokémon! ♪
-Attention, all Pokémon trainers!
Do you got what it takes to be the best?
Today, we'll do 30 Pokémon!
It's the ultimate test!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, yeah! ♪
♪ Articuno, Jynx, Nidorina, Beedrill
-♪ Haunter, Squirtle, Chansey ♪
-♪ Pokémon! ♪
♪ Parasect, Exeggcute, Muk, Dewgong
Pidgeotto, Lapras, Vulpix, Rhydon ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
♪ Charizard, Machamp, Pinsir, Koffing
Dugtrio, Golbat, Staryu, Magikarp ♪
♪ Ninetales, Ekans, Omastar
Scyther, Tentacool, Dragonair, Magmar ♪
Not bad, not bad!
Hey, don't get cocky.
Tomorrow's the hardest part.
We're on our way up to 150 Pokémon!
There's no stopping us!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪