♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon!
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon!
Oh, you're my best friend ♪
♪ In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon!
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪
-[Ash] Scissor Street? Why'd we come here?
-[Brock] You'll see.
[Misty] Sure are a lot of Pokémon
beauty parlors.
[narrator] Ash and his friends
take a walk along Scissor Street.
Why have they come here?
Only Brock knows the answer.
-Hm.
-Is there any place special
you want to visit, Brock?
-Hm.
-Wait a minute. I just remembered
that Scissor Street
is also called Breeder's Lane.
-Where is it?
-So that's why we're here.
Brock's always got to see
the latest breeder gear.
[narrator] Brock dreams
of becoming a Pokémon breeder,
a person who devotes his time and energy,
learning how to raise the best Pokémon.
[Ash]
Pokémon Fashion Flash
Some of the best breeders
have shops here.
There are lots of terrific makeup places
and fashion salons, too, just for Pokémon.
Hey! Oh, look. This must be
the newest fashion.
-How cute!
-You think that's cute, huh?
Come on. We've got to go in.
-Whoa! I don't want to go in there.
-Hm.
[James] You won't believe how beautiful
a Pokémon can be.
Step in and see for yourself.
Let us dazzle you with the latest fashions
by the expert artists of Salon Rocket.
-Did he just say Salon Rocket?
-Why does that name sound so familiar?
[Brock] Whoa, is that supposed to be
a Pokémon or a Christmas tree?
[both scatting]
Bring your drab old Pokémon
to Salon Rocket
for our complete Pokémon makeover,
including jewelry.
And hairstyling.
[both] We'll make your Pokémon
a pretty-mon. Ta-da!
We've done it again,
another Pokémon fashion masterpiece.
[James]
I can't believe how talented we are.
Your Pokémon have gone from frumpy
to flashy, thanks to Salon Rocket.
-Oh! How precious.
-What?
[all gasp]
120, 130, 140, 150, 160
-[both] Please come back again soon.
-200.
You two are spending way too much
on advertising.
TV commercials are a big waste of money.
Remember, we're in this to make a profit.
We know what we're doing.
The more we spend to hype this place,
the more customers we'll get.
Customers who will spend thousands
for a fashionable Pokémon.
[panting]
-I think I'm going to get in line.
-Huh?
-It's there!
-[both] Huh?
[panting] I found it!
I've been looking all over for this place.
This is the store you've been looking for?
[trembling]
-What are you so nervous about?
-[woman] Hi. Can I help you?
[screams]
Just relax. Release all your tensions.
[trembling]
Now you'll have more energy.
Chansey. Chansey. Chansey!
Chansey! I've come for you, darling.
Ah! Don't you look precious.
Thank you for bringing Chansey
to my salon.
-See you soon, Suzie.
-Chansey.
-May I help the next customer?
-Pika.
We're just kind of sort
of browsing around.
-Uh, no, uh.
-Look! Isn't that Vulpix the cutest thing?
-Oh, don't you want to hug it?
-[Ash] Ah!
-Pikachu.
-What is it?
[Pokédex] Vulpix, a fox Pokémon.
Its six tails are extremely beautiful.
As it evolves, it grows even more tails.
I love its hair.
I wish I had hair like Vulpix
that looked so shiny and soft.
-Don't touch it!
-You're just about the cutest
-little Pokémon I've ever seen--
-Ah!
[yawns]
-Very cute. [groans]
-Hm.
[Pokédex]
Vulpix uses powerful flame attacks.
Duh.
Please pardon Vulpix.
It doesn't like to be picked up
or hugged by strangers.
-Wish I'd known that sooner.
-Uh, Suzie?
Yes.
Uh, my name's Brock.
Nice to meet you, Suzie.
Uh, I want to breed like you. I mean,
I want to be a breeder like you.
It's very nice to meet you, Brock.
I'm flattered
you want to make me your model.
Yes, I want to model you. I mean,
I'm flattered that you're flattered.
I mean, your Vulpix is nice.
-Uh.
-Huh?
What I'm really trying to say is,
Suzie, I'm begging you to accept me
as your pupil.
-[all gasp]
-Pika.
You got to be kidding, Brock.
Mind your own business, Ash.
I know what I'm doing.
Please say yes, Suzie. [groans]
I don't have pupils, Brock.
Breeding takes up all my time.
What makes her
such a great breeder anyway?
How dare you!
The sensational Suzie of Scissor Street
has been awarded the trophy for excellence
at the World Pokémon Breeder's Contest
for three consecutive years.
Wait. There's more.
Lights. In addition to that,
the readers of Pokémon Friends magazine
named her the most popular breeder
four years running.
And her hugely popular website
records over 10,000 hits per day.
Now, that's what I call a great breeder.
You better believe it.
Okay, Brock, we heard you clear and loud.
I wonder if this Vulpix has ever won
any awards in competition?
That's a fabulous question, Misty.
Vulpix is the hottest supermodel
of the Pokémon world.
Notice the gorgeous, flowing tails
that have made Vulpix a champ.
-Plus there's--
-We get the idea, Brock!
-Vulpix is terrific too.
-[yawns]
So all three of you are traveling
on a Pokémon journey together.
Pikachu! Pi!
[Suzie]
Your Pikachu has a beautiful shiny coat.
Are you the one who prepares
all of Pikachu's food, Brock?
-Yes! I do.
-And it's Brock's own recipe too.
My career as a breeder also began
when I first became interested
in Pokémon nutrition.
[mutters]
[all gasp]
Pi!
Mm. Mm.
Whoa.
-Vulpix.
-[Brock] Ah!
I can't believe Vulpix is eating
the food I made.
Brock, this is really impressive.
Vulpix never eats food
that I haven't made myself.
Looks like Vulpix is a fan
of Brock's cooking.
[trembling] Uh, thank you, Vulpix.
-[grunts] I'm not worthy.
-[Suzie gasps]
[Misty] Suzie.
We saw some super-fancy-looking Pokémon
when we were walking down the street.
Is that really the latest trend?
By any chance, did you pass
a very large salon on the way?
Mm-hm, you mean
that really tacky-looking place.
Ever since it opened,
some trainers are trying to make
their Pokémon as flashy as possible.
So that salon started the trend.
A good breeder is always trying
to bring out a Pokémon's
inner strength and personality.
But this new fad is about standing out,
not what's inside.
I don't like it either.
It's pretty stupid
to waste your time showing off.
But sometimes even Pokémon
like to get dressed up
and show off a little
just like the rest of us.
Right, Pikachu? I see it now.
Pika, pika?
I think Pikachu's perfect the way it is.
We don't need any goofy fashions.
It's what's going on inside
that really counts.
I never said the inside wasn't important,
but the outside counts too.
The inside is what matters.
-Outside too.
-Inside!
-Inside matters the most.
The outside matters too.
-Inside.
-Outside too.
-Shouldn't you stop them?
-That's like trying to stop the tide.
If you think fashion's so great,
how about taking your Psyduck
to that salon?
Hey, what a great idea.
Let's go, Psyduck.
Psy-ay-ay.
[laughs]
Now we'll see who gets the last quack.
Ha! Anyway Psyduck and I are so cute,
we'll look good whatever fashion we wear.
I'm sure Psyduck will.
What do you know about fashion?
-Right, Psyduck?
-Psy-ay-ay. Duck?
This may be more of a challenge
than I thought it would be.
Better get going.
Ha! You'll be jealous
when we get back from the salon
and Psyduck turns out to be even cuter
than Pikachu.
-Come on, Psyduck.
-Psy.
Psyduck. Psyduck. Psyduck.
I wonder if it's what's on the outside
or what's inside
that really counts in the end.
Ever since that new salon opened,
I've been wondering about my methods.
-Don't say things like that.
-[gasps]
Suzie. You've got to keep following
the path you believe in.
We have to stick up
for what's inside together.
-Right, Pikachu?
-Pikachu.
That's very kind. But how can we?
If they want to put style over substance,
we'll give customers substance with style.
Uh, there are still a few seats left
in the back of the room
for our lecture on Pokémon care.
Each Pokémon needs your special care
and attention.
Whenever a Pokémon's been injured
in a battle,
it should be given a therapeutic massage.
Pika.
Hey! Wait! Where did everybody go?
-Say, weren't you over at Suzie's?
-Yeah, I saw you there.
Suzie's lecture just started.
It's a series about Pokémon care.
Today she's talking about massage.
A lecture on Pokémon massage?
This volunteer and his Pikachu
will now demonstrate the techniques
we learned in today's lecture. Mm-hm.
As you may already know,
a Pikachu's electric sacks
are located in its cheeks
and they become very tense
after a difficult battle.
Pika, Pikachu.
Ash, would you please massage Pikachu's
cheeks just like I showed you earlier?
Uh, sure.
Pikachu.
-Ah, let's see.
-Ha!
-Maybe...
-[Pikachu giggles]
-[chuckles] How's that feel, Pikachu?
-Pika.
-[woman] That's amazing.
-Wow.
Good communication between Pokémon
and their trainers is essential.
These techniques build trust
and bring out a Pokémon's personality.
I think Suzie will agree with me
that any technique is only as good
as the trainer or breeder who uses it.
-[woman] I never thought of that.
-[all sigh]
-[James] The perfect touch.
-[Jessie] One last rose.
Voila. This Squirtle shell
has become the perfect advertisement
for our latest line of Pokémon fashions.
Oh, yet another masterpiece
from Salon Rocket.
Roses are the flowers of love and romance.
[sighs]
We also paint daffodils.
Squirtle.
Meowth,
send in the next customer, tout de suite.
Can't you see I'm counting money here?
Hmm? Only one customer?
One or one million, it doesn't matter
as long as we have customers
who appreciate true beauty.
We only want to offer our services
to the most refined customers.
We're not going to make
any money that way.
Hello there, everybody.
-[all gasp]
-Huh?
-Welcome, young lady.
-Hmm.
-[both] Oh.
-[Misty] Hey, what are you doing?
-[James] Step in. Don't be shy.
-No, not me. Psyduck.
[Jessie] Don't be so hard on yourself.
You're just as lovely as any Psyduck.
[Misty] Hey. Hold on a second.
-Psy.
-[James] It's another masterpiece.
You like it?
Oh, I love it!
You've really captured the real me.
You're totally amazing artists.
I look so cute.
I'm thrilled.
There's nothing that pleases us more
than a satisfied customer.
Oh, why don't we try out
even more new styles?
[both] Time for a makeover!
-A dab of rouge.
-[James] A bit of blush.
-[Jessie] A smidgen of lipstick.
-[James] A modicum of mascara.
-[Jessie] A pinch of powder.
-[growls] Forget about that makeover.
She hangs around with that Pikachu.
We got to grill the kid
to figure out how to steal it.
Hey, wait. You're Meowth.
We were trying to find out
until you blew our cover!
First you get the opponent to relax,
then you pump them for info!
So stop pumping me and get that Pikachu!
[both yelling]
I'll never tell you phonies anything! Ah!
So you figured out the truth.
Well, you'd better tell us
where Pikachu is
if you don't want your face
painted just like Frankenstein.
Heh. Do I want a face like Frankenstein's?
No, I don't.
-Hey, Psyduck!
-Psyduck?
-Where'd Psyduck go?
-I don't see it.
-It's gone!
-Psyduck.
Psy, psy, psy.
Psy, psy. Psyduck. Psy, psy, psy.
Psy, psy, psy. Psyduck!
[all] Huh?
-Pika?
-Psyduck! Psyduck!
Psy, psy, psy.
Psy-ay-ay-ay!
Pika! Pika! Pika!
What's the matter?
Has something bad happened to Misty?
Pika! Pika!
[Ash grunts] Pikachu!
[Ash grunts]
-Misty!
-Pika!
-[all] Huh?
-[both] It's Team Rocket again!
What took you guys so long?
[both] What happened to her face?
[grunting]
-Dumb boys.
-[grunting]
-Let Misty go right now!
-Sorry, you'll have to wait your turn.
We won't be finished with her makeover
until she looks like this.
We're conducting
some important beauty research.
Beauty research?
Can't you understand
it's the beauty inside that counts?
Every Pokémon is beautiful.
We just have to help
the Pokémon discover it.
What's she talking about?
What does she know
about breeding Pokémon?
Who cares about the inside?
Outside counts.
What do you two numbskulls know
about Pokémon breeding?
This whole Salon Rocket idea's
supposed to be a scam remember?
-[gasps]
-It was a brilliant plan.
Part one, think up some stupid
Pokémon fashions
and take piles of money from the trainers.
Money? What?
And part two, whenever a trainer brings
in a rare Pokémon,
first get the trainer distracted,
then steal the Pokémon on the spot.
-What?
-[laughs]
And our greatest masterpiece of all
will be that Pikachu of yours.
How about a trade?
This twerpy girl for your Pikachu?
[gasps]
If you're trying to steal Pikachu,
we're going to battle.
-Count me in too. Tag team.
-Pika!
[laughs] Salon Rocket is ready
with our own fashion-battle platform!
-Here goes.
-[all yell]
[Jessie]
And now Salon Rocket presents
a fashion extravaganza
and Pokémon battlethon.
[Jessie] To protect the world
from boring fashion
[James] To dress all people
with flash and passion
[Jessie]
To give all Pokémon pretty faces.
[James] To extend our art to outer spaces.
-Jessie.
-James.
Salon Rocket.
When it comes to chic,
we know what's right.
Surrender your taste or prepare to fight.
Oh, we're supposed to battle on that?
-Dazzle them, Ekans.
-Knock them dead, Koffing.
-Ekans.
-Koffing.
We don't need costumes.
Pikachu's super-energized
from that massage.
-Go!
-Pika!
Geodude, go! Ugh.
-Geodude.
-Geodude, give them the seismic toss.
-[both grunting]
-Ekans.
Ekans!
-[grunts]
-Thunder shock, now!
-Pikachu!
-Koffing!
Pika!
Koffing, cutie.
Sludge makeover!
-Koffing! Koff!
-Pi!
-Ah, Pikachu!
-Geodude!
Now the finale. Go!
Koffing!
Oh, no! It's a fashion disaster.
Get up, you guys! We've still got a battle
to finish. Let's go!
Koffing!
[screaming]
-Now what?
-Vulpix and I will take care of them.
We'll give your Vulpix a makeover
when we get rid of its tails.
Time to give you a lesson in breeding.
If all you worry about
is your Pokémon's outer beauty,
-its inner strength will be lost.
-Vul.
A Pokémon is like a fashion model.
All that counts is a pretty face.
-Like mine!
-Ekans!
Vulpix! Wrap them up with fire spin!
[grunting]
[all yelling]
[all screaming]
[both] Save the gowns!
Hey! Don't fire spin me!
Help, help, help!
[all] We're blasting off again!
Now, that's an attack.
[Pokédex]
Vulpix's greatest attack, fire spin.
Using powerful flames
to block its opponent from moving,
it then inflicts great damage.
Did you see that?
A cute exterior hides inner strength,
that's the Pokémon's true personality.
[crowd murmuring]
-[Misty] Psyduck!
-Psy?
Just when I really needed you,
you ducked out on me.
Get up here quick and untie me.
Untie me now! [coughs]
Psy-ay-ay!
Nice work, Vulpix.
Thanks to all of you,
I believe in what I'm doing again.
You helped me regain confidence
in my beliefs.
Heh. It's not hard when the person
you're helping's as great as you are.
-And, Brock?
-Uh, yes?
I was very impressed
by the way you handled your Pokémon
in a crisis like that.
Suzie.
I have a lot more to learn
about breeding Pokémon.
Even if I do have a championship,
I'm still a student, not a teacher.
Looks like you and I
both have journeys ahead of us.
You leaving, Suzie?
What about your Pokémon salon?
There are things I can only learn
if I leave here.
I want you to continue
your journey too, Brock.
-From now on, we're rivals.
-Uh, sure.
-Vulpix.
-Ah!
I'd be grateful if you took care
of Vulpix for me.
-Huh?
-You're the first person other than me
that Vulpix has been friendly with.
Right now I believe
you could do a better job
-of raising Vulpix than I could.
-Vulpix.
-Mm, thanks. I don't know what to say.
-[Ash gasps]
Pika.
You don't have to worry, Vulpix.
I promise I'll take good care of you.
All right! I got Vulpix!
[chuckles]
Hm. [laughs]
Hey, what are you laughing for?
This makeup is very fashionable.
[narrator] And so Brock must continue
down his own path
to becoming a Pokémon breeder.
With Vulpix, he has a new friend on
his journey and he has a new determination
to be the greatest Pokémon breeder
of all time.
[all screaming]
Now, we need a total makeover
so nobody we ripped off can recognize us.
They're all just jealous because they're
not attractive enough to wear our designs.
[all] Back to the drawing board!
[narrator] So long, Salon Rocket!
♪ Pokémon! ♪
It's that time again.
A hundred and fifty Pokémon
five days a week.
That's about thirty or so each day.
It's not too hard.
just listen real good.
♪ Alakazam, Duduo, Venomat, Machoke
Kangaskan, Hypno, Electabuzz, Flareon ♪
♪ Blastoise, Polywhirl, Oddish, Drowzee
Raichu, Nidoqueen, Bellsprout, Starmie ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Metapod, Marowak, Kakuna, Clefairy
Dodrio, Seadra, Vileplume, Krabby ♪
♪ Lickitung, Tauros, Weedle, Nidoran
Nachop, Shellder, Porygon, Hitmonchan ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon master is my destiny ♪
Okay, so today was pretty easy.
But you gotta put all five days together.
It's the only way to name all 150.
Catch you here tomorrow.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪