♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Our hearts so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
[narrator] Ash's quest
to become a Pokémon Master
brings our heroes to a vast desert.
So, where's that town
you were talking about, Brock?
It's dark already.
You don't think we're going to camp out
in a place like this, do you?
[Brock] Chill out.
It's got to be around here somewhere.
Wow! That must be it!
[Ash] Look at all the lights.
[Misty] Wow, it sure is bright.
Pikachu.
[Brock] I knew it. This is Neon Town.
Doh. What rotten luck.
People love to come here
'cause it's open all day and all night.
It never closes?
-There's action 24 hours a day.
-Wow.
[both grunt]
Hey, watch where you're going, you jerk.
You watch it.
You're the one who bumped into me.
-Oh, yeah?
-[both snarl]
Hey, ash. Just apologize.
He should apologize.
He's the one who bumped into me.
Why you little--
[siren wailing]
All right. Break it up, you two!
There's no fighting here.
Eh, that little runt's not worth it.
You kids shouldn't be walking the streets
at night.
I'm sorry, Officer,
but we just got into town.
Then you go find yourselves a hotel
or something.
People around here
are pretty short-tempered!
-Short-tempered?
-Pi?
They're on edge because they stay out
all night and don't get enough sleep.
You kids should find a hotel,
get a good night's rest,
and mind your own business.
[woman] What do you think you're doing?
-[man] Shut up!
-There's another one.
This jenny seems a little edgy too.
I just love all these bright lights.
[both grunt]
Watch where you're going.
Oh, yeah? You walk into me,
and then you start complaining?
You walked into him. Huh? Huh?
That hurt.
I'll make you pay for that.
[all grunting and screaming]
Oh, I think we should prepare for trouble.
-[man 1] Hey, who do you think you are?
-[man 2] Watch it.
[yawns]
I don't believe it.
Everyone in town is already awake.
-Look at them.
-[Brock] I wonder when they sleep.
Break it up. Calm down. Move along.
Let's just keep moving.
Yeah, this place makes me nervous.
Ah, it's much nicer here in the woods
where it's quiet.
Yeah, it was so loud in Neon Town,
I couldn't get any sleep.
Hey, what's that?
-[Brock] Isn't that a Jigglypuff?
-Jiggly.
You're right, Brock, it's a Jigglypuff.
I've always wanted one of those.
I though you only liked water Pokémon.
I do, but I like this one, too.
I'll capture it. Staryu, go!
Psy.
Psyduck, I didn't want you. Return.
Staryu. Double edge.
[squeals]
[groans]
[cries]
-What's wrong?
-It looks like it's crying.
[Brock]
There's something strange about it.
I wonder what its problem is.
[Pokédex]
Jigglypuff, a balloon Pokémon.
It has large, friendly eyes,
and it sings a pleasant song.
A Pokémon that sings?
Oh, that's so cute.
-Sing for us.
-Puff.
What's the matter?
Please sing us a song.
[sighs]
Is something wrong?
Jigglypuff.
[sighs]
I think it's saying that it can't sing.
Hmm-hmm.
I see, a Jigglypuff that can't sing.
So that's why it didn't attack.
Oh, I'm sorry I bothered you,
little Jigglypuff.
Jigglypuff. Jiggly-jiggly.
I still think it's cute, but who wants
a Jigglypuff that can't sing?
[Jigglypuff gasps]
Jigglypuff.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Hey, I know.
Why don't we see if we can help
this little Jigglypuff to sing?
Good idea.
We can't just leave it here alone.
Jiggly.
[both laugh]
It looks like those kids found
a Jigglypuff.
A Jigglypuff?
A Jigglypuff's songs have the power
to put people to sleep.
Then I got a great idea.
We get that jiggly-thing to sing
to everybody in Neon Town.
And when it does...
It's naptime for Neon Town.
And then we grab anything
and everything we want.
That'll teach them not to mess with us.
Finally, Team Rocket is about to enjoy
the success we so richly deserve.
Let's get on with it.
[all] Right.
-Greetings, you Pokémon pipsqueaks.
-Huh? What are those guys doing here?
[James] Pump it up to the max.
[rock music]
♪ You know us as Team Rocket
And we fight for what is wrong ♪
♪ We're tired of our motto
So we thought we'd try a song ♪
-Jessie.
-James.
[both]
The speed of light, prepare to fight.
♪ Meowth, that's right ♪
♪ I am the handsome one ♪
♪ I'm the gorgeous one ♪
[both]
♪ Looking good is lots of fun ♪
♪ We get some things wrong
But we keep rolling along ♪
♪ We want to capture Pikachu
We hope to do it soon ♪
♪ And when we do
We'll be the new stars of this ♪
♪ Cartoon ♪
You need to work on your timing.
You were late on the last verse.
[Meowth] But my pitch was perfect.
So, what's your crummy plan this time?
We need Jigglypuff to sing
one of its little lullabies for us.
Its lullabies?
Jigglypuff's going to sing Team Rocket
right to the top.
Hey, Ash, this looks bad.
I choose you, Bulbasaur!
-Bulbasaur.
-Take care of them!
-Get them, Weezing.
-Weezing.
-Weezing, poison gas attack.
-Bulbasaur, vine whip.
Bulbasaur.
[groaning]
[all gasp]
Weezing.
[all coughing]
Okay, Staryu.
[all grunting]
[Misty]
♪ Do, re, mi, fa, sol, la, ti, do ♪
♪ Do, ti, la, sol, fa, mi, re, do ♪
Like that.
See how I control my breathing
as I sing the notes?
You're a great voice teacher, Misty.
Okay. Now it's your turn.
-[whimpers]
-Huh?
It doesn't look like
it really wants to sing.
♪ Pika, pika, pika, pik... ♪
-[laughs] Very good, Pikachu.
-Pika.
[grumbles]
Hey, Ash,
you're hurting Jigglypuff's feelings.
[grunts]
-[chirps]
-Pika? Pika?
-What is it, Pikachu ?
-Kachu.
Now you try it.
Fill up the balloon like this.
It'll help make your lungs bigger
and stronger.
-[sighs]
-[all groan]
I told you. It doesn't want to.
-Take it. Here you go.
-Hmm?
-[squealing]
-Forget it. This isn't working.
Let's see.
There it is. Here, look at this.
What's that, Brock?
The juice of this fruit
has very special properties.
It has the power to heal your throat
if it's sore or tired.
If Jigglypuff eats it,
it might start singing.
Would you like to try some?
-Give it a try, Jigglypuff.
-Jiggly.
Wow, this just might be the answer.
[munching]
-[Jigglypuff] Puff.
-[chuckles]
♪ Jigglypuff ♪
-Hooray!
-Jiggly, jiggly!
[laughter]
Pika. Pika. Pikachu.
-Jigglypuff.
-[groans]
-[giggles] Ah!
-[gasps]
Now, sing your song for us, Jigglypuff.
Jiggly.
[confused grunts]
-Hmm?
-What's the matter, Pikachu ?
Pikachu.
-Please sing for us, Jigglypuff.
-Jiggly.
Hmm?
[sighs]
♪ Jigglypuff ♪
♪ Jiggly ♪
♪ Jigglypuff, jiggly ♪
Good thinking, Jessie. Why go through
the trouble of capturing Jigglypuff...
When all we want is its voice?
We'll just record it and use it ourselves.
We got it made.
It's over there.
Time to record.
♪ Jigglypuff ♪
♪ Jigglypuff, Jiggly... ♪
Puff?
Jiggly? Jiggly?
Puff.
Jigglypuff.
Jiggly. [chuckles]
-[snoring]
-Puff?
[snoring]
[all snoring]
Jiggly. Jiggly.
Jigglypuff.
Jigglypuff. Jigglypuff.
[all snoring]
Puff!
[all yawning]
What a nice nap.
What happened to your face?
[both] Huh?
-[both scream]
-Huh?
Hmm.
-What's wrong, Jigglypuff?
-Jiggly.
-What's it mad at?
-I don't know.
Maybe it's mad 'cause we fell asleep
while it was singing.
Uh, no way.
Why would it be mad
about something like that?
I wouldn't be too happy
if people fell asleep
while I was performing for them.
[Ash and Brock]
Neither would I.
We're sorry, little Jigglypuff.
-Puff.
-[sighs]
I've got it. Maybe there are some Pokémon
that wouldn't fall asleep.
♪ Jigglypuff ♪
♪ Jiggly ♪
♪ Jiggly... ♪
[gasps] Puff.
Oh, they all fell asleep.
Jigglypuff's song is strong.
-I know.
-[Ash and Brock] Hmm?
We should let it sing to Psyduck.
Psyduck's too doofy to know
whether it's awake or asleep anyway.
Great.
♪ Jigglypuff ♪
♪ Jiggly... ♪
Hmm?
Mm. Hey.
Psyduck stayed awake and heard you sing.
Good old Psyduck,
you finally did something right.
[gasps] Puff.
What are you angry about now, Jigglypuff?
Psyduck listened to the whole thing.
-Puff.
-What's wrong?
Hmm?
You stupid Pokémon,
you're just sleeping with your eyes open!
Psy!
[all scream]
-Who did this?
-How dare they?
Wait a sec. We got to check to see
if we got the Jigglypuff on tape.
[both] Oh, good idea.
[all snoring]
-What is that awful sound?
-It's all of us snoring.
What are we supposed to do with that?
What else can we do for it?
It must be frustrating
to have such a beautiful voice,
and have no one listen to the whole song.
I know.
Neon town's the perfect place for it.
Hey, that's right.
Since those people never seem
to have to sleep...
They'll be able to listen
to Jigglypuff sing.
Now, you'll get to sing for all the people
in Neon Town, Jigglypuff.
Jiggly!
Did you hear that?
Those fools are going to do exactly
what we'd planned to do with Jigglypuff.
With enemies like that, who needs friends?
[chuckles]
Now, where can it sing
so that everyone will be able to hear it?
It would be great if we could find
an outdoor stage someplace.
Let's ask somebody.
[man] An outdoor stage?
Yes, do you know
where we can find a place like that?
Hey, there's nothing like that
anywhere in town.
Now, get lost. I'm busy.
[Misty] Oh, what a big jerk.
[Ash] Worse than a jerk.
He was out-and-out mean.
Hey, we heard you're the ones
who are looking for an outdoor stage.
-Huh?
-Yeah, that's right. We are.
You can go ahead
and use ours if you want to.
[all] Huh?
-[Brock] Hey, all right.
-[Ash laughs] Cool.
Uh, we can really use it?
Sure, we love to showcase new talent.
Crank the speakers up to 11.
-Thank you very much. This is great.
-Pikachu.
We finally met someone
in Neon Town who's nice.
[both giggling]
This will be perfect.
Isn't this great, Jigglypuff?
You can sing from the stage.
Jigglypuff. Jigglypuff.
[Jessie] How sweet.
Now, everyone in town will hear.
And afterwards,
the town is ours for the taking.
Hey. Don't forget these things.
Oh, our earplugs, of course.
-[man] Huh, what's that?
-Hmm?
♪ Jigglypuff ♪
♪ Jigglypuff, Jiggly ♪
-Song.
-What's that song?
♪ Jigglypuff, Jigglypuff ♪
-Hmm?
-Huh?
♪ Jigglypuff, Jiggly ♪
-[woman] Where's that coming from?
-What is that?
♪ Jigglypuff ♪
♪ Jigglypuff, Jiggly ♪
♪ Jigglypuff, Jigglypuff, Jigglypuff ♪
-I don't think my ears are plugged enough.
♪ Jigglypuff ♪
♪ Jiggly ♪
♪ Jiggly... ♪
Hmm? Puff!
[yawns] What a great nap that was.
[all yawning]
-Uh-oh. Everybody in town fell asleep.
-It sure seems so.
[all yawning]
-I wonder where Jigglypuff went to.
-Oh, I bet it's pretty mad.
I wanted to tell you,
I'm really sorry about starting that fight
with you yesterday.
Oh, no, no. It was my fault.
Huh?
Jigglypuff's song
not only puts people to sleep,
but maybe it has the power
to make people nicer, too.
-[man] Hey, it's you.
-Huh?
I just wanted to apologize
for bumping into you like that last night.
-Uh, you're that guy.
-Yeah, I'm sorry.
That's okay. Thanks for the apology.
So, where's Jigglypuff gone?
-Did it get mad and run off somewhere?
-Jigglypuff!
[Jessie] We've failed again.
The earplugs didn't even work.
But the skies are blue
and the air is so fresh.
[Meowth] Isn't life great?
[all laugh]
[James] Tra-la-la-la-la!
[Ash] This is great.
Everyone in town is so happy now.
Yeah, everyone needs a good rest now
and then to recharge.
But where could Jigglypuff
have run off to?
I wanted to capture it.
Maybe it started its own quest
to find someone
who can hear its song
all the way through.
I hope we meet Jigglypuff again.
[narrator] After hearing Jigglypuff's song
and resting up,
our heroes continue their journey
refreshed in mind, body, and spirit.
-Puff.
-[narrator] Huh?
Jigglypuff. [chuckles]
Jigglypuff, Jigglypuff,
Jiggly, jiggly, jig!
[narrator] Wait for Jigglypuff.
♪ Pokémon ♪
Get those lips loose.
It's time to Pokérap.
Come on! Sing 'em with me
That's the game.
There's 150 Pokémon.
How many can you name?
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Sandslash, Hitmonlee, Psyduck
Arcanine, Eevee, Exeggcutor ♪
♪ Kabutops, Zapdos, Dratini
Growlithe, Mr. Mime, Cubone ♪
♪ Graveler, Voltorb, Gloom
We're almost home ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Charmeleon, Wartortle, Mewtwo
Tentacruel, Aerodactyl ♪
♪ Omanyte, Slowpoke, Pidgeot, Arbok ♪
That's all folks!
Can you name all the Pokémon?
Just put today's song together
with the other days of the week.
That's why you can't miss a show.
You gotta catch 'em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
It's just you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Our hearts so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪