♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon! Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, gotta catch 'em all
[narrator] Our hero Ash,
along with his friends Misty and Brock,
continues on his quest
to become a Pokémon Master.
Tired from their adventures,
they decided to take a break
in a quiet forest.
Pi, pi... Pika.
Cha!
The air's so fresh,
and the water's beautiful.
What a great place this is for a rest.
Yeah, it sure is nice
to kick back and relax a little.
-[Ash] Kanga, Kangaskhan!
-[both] Huh?
[laughs] This is fun!
Ash, look out, that tree!
Huh? [screams]
[groans]
Wah!
-Jungle boy.
-He'll never learn.
Pika, pi. Pikachu.
- [Ash groan]
- Pika?
Pi?
Pika!
Pi!
Pi? Pikachu?
Huh? Pikachu? Huh?
Pikachu.
Pikachu?
[Ash]
Hey! Where you going, Pikachu?
-Where's Pikachu running to?
-I don't know, Misty.
Maybe it saw something out there
in the woods.
Pi?
[chittering]
-[all] Huh?
-Pika!
[Ash] What's that?
[Misty] It's amazing.
Look at all the Pikachu.
[all chittering]
Pika.
[trilling and chattering]
Those must be wild Pikachu.
I've never seen so many Pikachu
in one place.
Pika, pika!
Pi. Pika!
[all] Pika?
Pi? Pika?
Pika.
Pika! Pika.
=Pikachu!
-[all chittering]
[all] Huh?
Pi? Pika?
Pikachu.
Pika. Pika!
-Pikachu!
-Pika!
Pika!
-Pi?
[all gasping]
[sniffs]
Pika? Pi?
Pika?
Pi.
Pika!
-Pikachu!
-Pikachu.
[all] Pika.
[all chittering]
[all] Pikachu!
Pikachu!
[chittering]
Aw.
It looks like they've finally
accepted Pikachu as part of their group.
-All right!
-[both] Huh?
[Ash] Hey!
I want to be part of your group too.
Pika, pi!
[all chittering]
Hey, wait up! Huh?
[whimpers]
Hey, don't run away.
[Misty] Quit it, Ash.
But why?
Don't you understand?
Those Pikachu are scared of you, Ash.
Huh?
Pika.
-I'm sorry, Pikachu.
-Pi.
But why would those Pikachu
be afraid of me?
I wouldn't do anything to hurt them.
They probably haven't had much contact
with humans before.
Yeah, I don't think too many people
come this far into the forest, Ash.
This place must be perfect
for those Pikachu.
You mean like a Pikachu paradise?
I'd sure hate to do anything
that would disturb all those Pikachu here.
[Misty] Yeah, me neither.
[Ash] Yeah.
-Pi! Pi!
-Pika?
Pi! Pika! Pika!
-What's that?
-It's one of those Pikachu!
-Pika!
-[all grunt]
-Pika! Pika! Pika!
-[all pant]
Pika! Pikachu!
Ash, we have to try to save it!
[Misty]
Quick. It's headed for the waterfall!
Pika! Pika! Pika!
Pi.
Pikachu!
-[both gasp]
-Pikachu!
Pika!
Pika! Pika!
Pikachu! Pikachu! Pikachu!
[screaming]
Pi!
Pikachu!
Pika!
[all] Pika!
[all] Pikachu! Pikachu! Pikachu!
-[panting]
-Pikachu!
Kachu!
Ah!
Pika, pi.
[grunting]
Pika.
Pika!
[all] Pika! Pika! Pika!
Pika! Pika! Pika...
Pika! Pika! Pika!
[all chitter sadly]
Oh! Huh?
[groans]
[electricity crackling]
Pi.
Pi...
Pika?
-Pi! Pi!
-Pi?
Pika? Pikachu!
-Pika.
-Pikachu.
[all] Pika!
[chittering]
-Pika!
-[all] Pika! Pika! Pika!
[all] Pika! Pika! Pika!
[Jessie chuckles]
[Jessie] Just look at all of them.
[James]
Pikachu to the left. Pikachu to the right.
[Meowth] Piles of Pikachu everywhere.
If we turn over this many Pikachu
to the boss...
We'll be promoted for sure.
I'm so proud to be part of this team.
Everything in this forest
is public property.
And we're all members of the public.
So that means all these Pikachu
are really our property.
[both] Right!
[all screaming]
[all] Shh!
[all groaning]
[all singing]
-Those Pikachu sure are having fun.
-Looks like it.
Misty, Ash.
Dinner'll be ready in just a few minutes.
Oh, it looks like Pikachu
sure is fitting in well.
Yeah.
I think it's the best thing in the world
for Pikachu to be here with its own kind.
Huh? [sighs]
[all singing]
-Pika, pika.
-Pika!
[Ash sighs]
Thanks, Brock.
That was a delicious dinner.
[chuckles]
What can I say? I'm a great cook.
[Misty] Maybe it's because the vegetables
around here are so tasty.
Don't you think so, Ash?
Ash?
-[Misty] Hey, Ash.
-Huh?
Ash, what's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
You don't look so good. Do you feel okay?
Never felt better. Everything's fine.
[chomping]
[groans]
[both] Hm?
[Misty] This place must be perfect
for those Pikachu.
[Brock] I think it's the best thing
in the world for Pikachu
to be here with its own kind.
Here with its own kind.
Oh! Aw. Hmm.
-[shrieking]
-Huh?
[both gasp]
Wha..? What is that sound?
-Pika.
-Pi.
[all squeaking]
-They're trapped.
-Who could have done this to them?
Pikachu! Pikachu!
Pika, pi! Pikachu!
[Groans] Who's there?
[Jessie] Prepare for trouble.
[James] Make it double.
Those voices.
[Jessie and James laugh]
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation...
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation...
[Jessie]
To denounce the evils of truth and love...
[James]
To extend our reach to the stars above...
Jessie.
James.
[Jessie] Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth.
[all] Team Rocket!
[all] That's right!
We'd like to thank all of our fans
for their loyalty and support.
This victory is for them.
And now you're about to witness
Team Rocket's finest performance.
Cut the speeches,
and let's swipe these Pikachu. Ha!
You're not swiping anything.
Pikachu, break the ropes
with an electric shock.
Pi. Pikachu!
[gasps] Pika, pika.
[Meowth laughing]
They're no match for our new
Pikachu-insulated seizure net.
You might as well just give up.
It's made
from environmentally-safe material
that absorbs electricity.
-That's very thoughtful of you.
-Let those Pikachu go now.
[all] Nyah-nyah.
[groans] We've got to save the Pikachu.
-Yeah!
-Right!
Why don't you check out our website?
[all yelling]
Hey, let us out of this stupid thing!
You're not going to get away with this!
[laughs]
Time to make our exit.
-[both] Roger!
-[Ash] Wait!
[all Pikachu screaming]
Oh! Pikachu!
Pika, pi!
It's a Pika-palooza.
We're at the "pika" our powers.
"Chu" can say that again, Jess.
[all laughing]
[all gnawing]
Ah. It's good to be on top.
Wha... We got a pika problem down below.
[both] What?
[Jessie] Huh?
-[James] Quit it!
-[Jessie] Hey! Stop that!
-[James] Pikachus, cut it out. Stop.
-[Meowth] What are you doing? Hold it.
[Jessie] Quit it! Stop!
Pika!
Ah! It's coming.
-Ooh. Huh? Ooh!
Catch it, James!
There, grab it.
[grunting]
All right, we're free!
Watch out, Team Rocket.
Hey, Pikachu, jump onto this!
Hurry up!
Pika!
Chu!
All right, that's the way.
Come on, keep on jumping!
Pika! Chu!
Pika!
Chu!
Pika! Chu!
-Pikachu.
-Chu!
Pika!
Pika.
Pikachu.
[grunting] This rodent's bugging me.
Huh? [yells]
All the Pikachu have gotten away!
[both] Huh?
[all] Not again.
But wait.
There's one Pikachu left.
Let's grab it.
[all groan]
Pika.
[grunts]
[James gasps]
[all] Oh. We're blasting off again.
Pikachu!
Pika, pi!
[laughs] You did it, Pikachu!
[laughing]
Pika, pika!
Pika, pika! Pi?
Pi! Pikachu!
Ah! Pikachu!
-Pika, pika.
-Pika!
[all] Pika!
[all] Pikachu! Pikachu! Pikachu!
[gasping]
[all] Pikachu! Pikachu!
Pikachu! Pikachu! Pikachu!
Hmm.
-They all made it back safely.
-Yeah. Ash really trained Pikachu well.
You did a great job, Ash.
[both] Huh?
-[Brock] Ash?
-[Misty] Where are you going, Ash?
[Brock] What? You're leaving Pikachu?
[Ash] That's right.
But, Ash, what are you doing?
This is crazy.
[Ash] My mind's made up.
[grunts]
[all] Huh?
Pikachu.
Pika, pi. Pikachu?
-Pikachu, you stay here. I'm leaving.
-Pi.
I know you'll be much happier here
in the forest with the other Pikachu.
Pika, pi.
[whimpers]
Goodbye, Pikachu.
Pika, pi!
Please don't.
Pika.
All of these Pikachu here
in the forest need you.
So just... Goodbye. [grunts]
-[both] Huh?
-Pika, pi!
Goodbye! [pants]
Pikachu.
[panting]
[thinking]
Pikachu was my very first Pokémon.
♪ I close my eyes ♪
♪ And I can see the day we met ♪
♪ Just one moment and I knew ♪
♪ You're my best friend ♪
♪ Do anything for you ♪
♪ We've gone so far and done so much ♪
♪ And I feel
Like we've always Been together ♪
♪ Right by my side
Through thick and thin ♪
♪ You're the part of my life ♪
♪ I'll always remember ♪
♪ The time has come ♪
♪ It's for the best, I know it ♪
♪ Who could have guessed that you and I ♪
♪ Somehow, someday ♪
♪ We'd have to say goodbye ♪
♪ The time has come ♪
♪ It's for the best ♪
♪ I know it ♪
♪ Who could have guessed that you and I ♪
♪ Somehow, someday ♪
♪ We'd have to say ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
This is for the best. I guess.
[panting]
-[Brock] Ash!
-[Misty] Why are you doing this?
I'm sure Pikachu will be better-off
staying here
than traveling around with me.
Pikachu will be happier this way.
[both] Huh?
Huh? Huh?
[squeaks]
Ah! Pi... Pikachu!
Pi.
Pi, Pikachu.
Pikachu.
[both] Pika, pika.
[all] Pika!
Pi?
[all] Pikachu! Pikachu! Pikachu!
-What do you think they're doing?
-Well, I think they might be cheering.
[both] Huh?
For Ash and for Pikachu.
[all] Pikachu! Pikachu! Pikachu!
Pikachu!
Pika, pi!
Ah!
[Ash laughing]
[squeaks happily]
[all] Pikachu! Pikachu! Pikachu!
[Ash sobs]
[narrator] Another adventure
has brought Ash and Pikachu even closer.
In their hearts, they know they'll go on
to face every challenge together.
-♪ Pokémon! ♪
-Attention, all Pokémon trainers!
Do you got what it takes to be
the best?
Today, we’ll do 30 Pokémon!
It’s the ultimate test!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, yeah! ♪
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Articuno, Jynx, Nidorina, Beedrill
Haunter, Squirtle, Chansey, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Parasect, Exeggcute, Muk, Dewgong
Pidgeotto, Lapras, Vulpix, Rhydon ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
♪ Charizard, Machamp, Pinsir, Koffing
Dugtrio, Golbat, Staryu, Magikarp ♪
♪ Ninetales, Ekans, Omastar
Scyther, Tentacool, Dragonair, Magmar ♪
Not bad, not bad!
Hey, don’t get cocky.
Tomorrow’s the hardest part.
We’re on our way up to 150 Pokémon!
There’s no stopping us!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪