♪ I want be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all!
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny,
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon!
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you,
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
[narrator] After forfeiting to Sabrina's
psychic Pokémon in Saffron City,
our friends learn from a mysterious
bearded man how they might defeat her.
Now they're on their way to try
and capture one of the ghost Pokémon
that haunts the dreaded
Pokémon Tower in Lavender Town.
[Ash] The fog's coming in.
And that's not good.
We'd better be super careful.
We've got to make sure
we don't get separated.
Maybe this is an omen.
Maybe we should forget
about catching a ghost Pokémon.
We've come too far.
Everybody, let's hold hands
and stay together.
-[Misty] Okay.
-[Ash] Right.
Hey, Ash, where are you?
-Up here.
-What do you mean here?
Right here.
Ah, there.
Pi... Pikachu!
[screaming]
[Brock grunts]
Huh?
[groans]
Brock? Oh, don't you know how scared
it makes me when you yell like that?
-[Ash] Well, Misty, you sure scared me.
-Huh?
[Ash laughs]
Ah! Say what?
I'm feeling like a ghost myself.
[growls]
[screaming]
[laugh]
Sorry, guys. I was just testing you.
If we're going to try to catch
a ghost Pokémon,
we got to learn to deal with fear.
That's the only way we're going to become
great Pokémon trainers.
You must be crazy!
Don't ever do that!
Chu!
Argh!
[groans]
We've got enough things to scare us
without your boneheaded jokes.
Pika, pika.
I'll just save the masks
till next year's Halloween.
[Ash] The Tower of Terror
[birds cawing]
[Ash] There's Lavender Town.
I'm glad we got here before it got dark.
[Misty] Looks like it's always dark
around this place.
[Brock] This is the Pokémon Tower
where ghost Pokémon hang out.
I like what they've done with the place.
Okay, Ash. It's time for you to show us
what a great trainer you are.
Huh?
We'll let you handle this one alone.
Hey, wait a minute.
You guys promised me
you'd help me capture a ghost Pokémon
when we got to Lavender Town.
[Misty] I don't remember promising that.
You know how to deal with fear, Ash.
Ha, run away if you want to.
I'm not scared,
and I'm not going to let
some stupid ghost Pokémon
prevent me from becoming
a great Pokémon master.
Right, Pikachu?
Pikachu.
All right, good idea.
Let's do this in the morning. Hey!
Make sure you don't wake me up too early,
okay?
Night, guys.
Time to wake up!
-Chu!
-Wah! Wah! Wah!
Maybe I'll be a little braver
tomorrow morning.
[sighs]
[laughs]
There they are.
I'm so glad they could make it.
I'm no psychic,
but I see success in our future.
This time, Pikachu's in the bag.
-Let's get started.
-Mm.
-Whoa!
-Hey!
James? Are you all right?
[Meowth] The floor broke his fall.
[Jessie]
These old places can be so dangerous.
[Meowth] Huh?
What's that there?
[yawns]
[screams]
Meowth, where are your manners?
It's impolite to leave your mouth
hanging open like that.
Look behind you.
-What are you jabbering?
-Behind you. Look there!
Right there.
Behind me.
There's nothing there.
Wha...? Huh?
You must be seeing things.
It was there.
[Meowth] Huh?
Don't tell me you're seeing things again.
Get away!
[screams]
It slipped.
You mangy alley cat. You numbskull.
You've ruined my beautiful face!
Ah!
[grunting]
[thudding]
It was only a scratch.
[whimpers]
A tragedy.
My face.
Perfection has been ruined.
[screaming]
[James groans]
You're right. This place is dangerous.
Thanks for breaking my fall.
[all] Huh?
[all screaming]
Horrible.
It sounds really horrible in there.
You're right.
They must have
some kind of torture chamber in there.
Torture chamber?
[James whimpering]
[Meowth]
Ah!
This has got to be a nightmare.
[groans]
[all]
Huh?
Gastly.
[screaming]
Oh, those screams again.
[Brock]
But I heard a different voice that time.
Those voices are familiar.
I feel like I've heard them all before.
Why don't we go inside
and find out who they are?
You go in first.
[both]
Go. Go.
[door creaking]
Hello, there.
Anybody home?
Uh, it's kind of dark in here.
[door creaks, then slams]
[Misty]
Oh, now it's pitch-black. Do something.
Charmander, I choose you.
Char, char.
Char!
This place is creepy.
Maybe we should come back tomorrow
when it's daylight.
Have you ever heard of a ghost
that comes out during the day?
Look, I found a candle.
All right, Charmander,
light up that candle for us.
Char!
[whimpering]
Light the candle, not me!
Pika, pika, pi.
[Misty] Watch where you walk.
There's a hole in the floor.
[devious laughter]
Where are those voices coming from?
[grunting]
Gengar, Gengar, Gengar.
[whistling]
Ah! [laughing]
[guffawing]
Gengar, Gengar, Gengar.
Ga-ga... Gastly!
[all laughing]
Gastly.
Gengar.
Might as well check in this room first.
[Misty]
Maybe we should just get out of here.
Nah, there's no way we can turn back now.
We've got to go in.
Uh, hey, ghost Pokémon,
if you're in here, say hello.
I'm going to capture you.
Don't say that. If they know
you're trying to capture them,
they won't come out of hiding.
You're right.
[laughs]
-Char, char.
-Pika...
-What's this?
-It looks like...
Huh?
It looks like some kind
of fancy restaurant.
Maybe it's a party
or some kind of reception.
But who's it for?
[Ash]
What's that string?
[Brock]
There's something written on the card.
[Misty]
It says "pull this."
[Ash]
Well, why not?
[Misty]
Wait!
-[Ash] Are we...?
-[Misty] Being welcomed?
[Brock] By who?
[Misty] Look!
[all] Huh?
[all screaming]
Whoa! Help me!
-Ah!
-Hold on!
Ah!
[both screaming]
Come on!
Jump!
-Pika.
-Char.
[screams]
-Pika, pika, pika.
-Char!
[all laughing]
Gastly. [laughing]
[Misty panting]
There is no way
I'm going back in that tower.
It's just too scary in there.
Me neither.
What are you saying?
There's no way we can capture a ghost
Pokémon if we don't go back in there.
Right, Pikachu? Charmander?
Pi... Pi...
Char!
[all groan]
Hold on! Are you two really cowards?
How do you expect to beat
Sabrina's psychic Pokémon
if you don't go back in?
-Do you want to lose again?
-Pi...
Cha! Cha!
Cha.
Listen, if you're ever going to beat
psychic Pokémon,
you got to learn to overcome your fear,
understand?
-Pi...
-Mander.
I say it's time to give it another try.
Pikachu, Charmander, are you with me?
-Pi.
-Char.
Great. Let's do it!
Come on, guys. What about you?
-We'll both be waiting for you right here.
-Have a nice time.
[all] Wah!
[Ash] Hello, everybody.
We're back.
We'd love to meet you.
Feel free to introduce yourselves
whenever you like.
Huh?
What was that?
[Pokédex]
Ghost Pokémon are in a vapor form.
Their true nature is shrouded in mystery.
Oh, well.
Guess I'll try to solve the mystery.
-[Meowth] Cut it out.
-[James] Could you please knock that off?
-[Jessie] What's this?
-[James] Stop it.
They're down there.
Time for us to go get them.
Pikachu, electric attack.
Pika.
Pikachu!
[screaming]
Charmander, flamethrower, now.
Char!
[screaming]
[Ash] Hey, it's working.
Go, Poké Ball!
Huh?
Ouch.
[sobbing]
Huh, I wonder if I captured it.
Oh, it's that stuck-up little brat again.
I'll get him
if it's the last thing I ever do.
Someday, I'm going to make him pay dearly
for what's he's done.
She's got fire in her eyes.
Yeah, and in her hair too.
Huh?
[squealing]
[Ash] Hey, a fireball.
He's going to pay for this.
Aw, the fireball's gone.
Guess we'll get it next time.
Pi. Pika, pi!
Huh? What's what?
You must be seeing things.
Huh?
Uh...
[all] Argh!
[laughing]
Is this a ghost Pokémon?
[bleeping]
[Ash grunts
[Pokédex]
Haunter, a gaseous Pokémon.
No further information.
Huh? Is that all?
Well, we're not going to lose
to some stupid ghost Pokémon.
Go, Charmander.
Huh?
Don't bother me now, Pikachu. Quit it.
Cut it out.
Uh...
[Ash screams]
[Haunter laughs]
I'm not afraid of you.
You just surprised me a little bit.
-Charmander, you're on.
-Char!
Charmander, time to use your leer attack.
[growling]
[groaning]
Bah!
Huh?
[laughing]
What are you doing, Charmander?
You're not supposed to make it laugh.
Mander?
[whimpers]
Oh, this isn't working.
Charmander, return.
Bah!
Do you really think I'm afraid of you?
Gengar...
Pika-pi!
Gengar. Gengar.
There are more of these?
Gengar!
[Ash groans]
[laughing]
[groaning]
I better find out about this one.
Gengar. No information available.
Not again.
Pikachu.
[laughing]
I don't get it. They're weird.
Huh?
[squeaking and grunting]
Are you guys trying to be funny?
Your routine really isn't working for me.
Pikachu?
[wailing]
I'm sorry to say it,
but their humor really leaves me cold.
Pikachu.
They're pretty sad.
-[Pikachu] Pika-pi!
-[Ash] Hey! Don't go!
Wait a second!
-[Ash grunts]
-[Pikachu] Ah!
Ah!
[groaning]
[crackling]
[laughing and cheering]
Huh?
[Gengar] Gen... gar?
Gengar.
[laughing]
[Ash whimpers]
-Huh?
-Pi.
[Ash] We're down there!
[Pikachu] Pika, pika?
-What's going on?
-Pikachu?
Haunter, Haunter.
-You're saying we're alike now?
-Pika?
Oh, no! We've been totally separated
from our bodies!
Haunter, Haunter.
No way. I don't want to be a ghost yet.
[Ash screams]
Ah, no! Wherever you're taking us,
we don't want to go.
Ah!
[Ash] Ah! Oh, what a view.
-Ah!
-Pikachu.
Huh? [chuckles]
Now's our chance to have some fun.
Pika.
Ash is taking too long.
I think we'd better go in
and see how he's doing.
That's a good idea.
So, Misty, you're really worried about me.
Huh?
What's wrong, Misty?
I just thought I heard a voice.
-Come for a ride with me, Misty.
-[screams]
-[Brock] Ah! Misty!
-Help!
[Ash laughs]
The ghost has got me!
Okay, ride's over. Catch her, Brock!
[Brock grunts]
[both groan]
Wait a minute. That voice...
I think something terrible's happened
to Ash.
Yeah!
[all laughing]
[Ash] I'm flying!
Ah, cool.
[all sigh]
Ah!
[screams]
You fooled me.
[all laughing]
[laughing]
Pikachu.
Whoa.
Wow, look at all these toys.
Pikachu!
Haunt, haunt, haunt.
Gengar, Gengar, Gengar.
Gastly, Gastly.
Huh?
Do you mean you only wanted somebody
to play with?
-Gengar, Gengar.
-Haunt, haunt, haunt, haunt.
Really? Was that all?
You just wanted to have some fun,
not scare people?
-[Pikachu] Chu.
-Huh?
-Gastly, Gastly.
-Pikachu. Pika, pika.
I understand how you must have been bored
for such a long time.
That's tough.
[groaning]
I'm sorry, but I can't stay with you
and play with all these great toys.
There are still lots and lots of opponents
out there for me to battle.
I have to fulfill my dream
of becoming a Pokémon master.
[both] Hmm.
Sorry, but I really have to go.
[moaning]
I'll miss you all.
[sobbing] Uh...
[sighs]
Ash? Pikachu?
Come on, wake up.
-Oh, Ash, can't you hear me?
-Please say something.
Ash, open your eyes. Please, Ash.
Huh,
I guess it's time to go back, Pikachu.
[all sigh]
Whoa.
Hi, Misty.
Huh?
You're alive.
Pika.
Pikachu.
Hey, guys. Sorry to worry you.
No sweat. Glad to have you back.
[sobs softly and chuckles]
[laughing]
[laughs]
But, Ash, what about the ghost Pokémon?
Ah, it's impossible to catch them.
What? Then how are you ever going to beat
the psychic Pokémon?
Hmm, maybe I'll have to use
my sense of humor.
[both] Huh?
Pika!
Huh?
Blah!
[screaming]
[laughs]
Pika. Pi, pika, pi.
Pikachu!
[narrator] Well, it seems
it was so much fun playing with Ash
that Haunter decided to follow along
on his Pokémon journey.
Maybe together, their comedy act
will knock out Sabrina's psychic Pokémon.
[screaming]
I can't take any more!
Let me off! I'm dizzy!
Stop the ride! I want to get off!
[all laugh]
[all] Looks like Team Rocket's
throwing up again!
Pokémon! It’s that time again!
A hundred and fifty Pokémon,
five days a week.
That’s about 30 or so each day.
It’s not too hard, just listen real good!
♪ Alakazam, Doduo, Venonat
Machoke, Kangaskhan, Hypno ♪
♪ Electabuzz, Flareon, Blastoise
Poliwhirl, Oddish, Drowzee ♪
♪ Raichu, Nidoqueen
Bellsprout, Starmie ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Metapod, Marowak, Kakuna
Clefairy, Dodrio, Seadra ♪
♪ Vileplume, Krabby, Lickitung
Tauros, Weedle, Nidoran ♪
♪ Machop, Shellder
Porygon, Hitmonchan ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny. ♪
Okay, so today was pretty easy.
But you gotta put all five days together.
That’s the only way to name all 150.
Catch you here tomorrow!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Oh, gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach pokemon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokemon! Gotta catch 'em all!
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny,
Pokemon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokemon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you,
Pokemon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokemon! ♪