♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that’s inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you’re my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
[narrator] Ash and his friends find
themselves in beautiful Grandpa Canyon.
Our heroes will soon discover that this
natural wonder holds an ancient secret.
[all gasp]
What’s going on down there?
[people chattering]
I wonder what everybody’s doing
with those picks and shovels.
-[Gary] Don’t you know anything?
-Huh?
Ash, not only late as usual,
but clueless too.
Hey, it’s Gary.
Uh, why are you dressed like that?
Huh. Don’t tell me you never heard
about the Pokémon discovery.
Even a nerd like you should have heard
about the great fossil rush.
[all] The great fossil rush?
[all] Gary, Gary he’s our man!
If he can’t find them, no one can!
Thank you. Thank you to all my loyal fans.
I got to go. I got to find all the fossils
quick before anyone else does.
Can’t waste my precious time
hanging around with a loser like you.
-Loser?
-Easy.
-Ash?
-That know-it-all. Ah!
I’m going to find a Pokémon fossil
before Gary even starts digging.
That’ll show him who the real loser is.
I don’t feel right about digging up
old Pokémon fossils,
especially after they’ve been resting
in the earth for such a long time.
If they’ve been lying underground
for thousands of years,
maybe they’d like a little fresh air, heh.
I think it’s your brain
that needs fresh air.
-Who asked you?
-Jigglypuff.
[gibbering]
Puff, puff, Jigglypuff.
Puff, puff.
[sighs] Puff!
[all grunting]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[Gary laughs]
Success. My first Pokémon fossil.
[all] Yay. Gary, Gary, he’s the best.
Found a fossil before the rest.
Go, Gary.
Hmm.
Impressive, isn’t it?
Found it on my first try.
Looks like a brain
from an extinct Pokémon.
-[man] This is--
-A brain?
-It’s fossilized Pokémon manure.
-Huh?
[groans]
[all] Ew, yuck. Gross.
[Ash] Wow. Look at all the people digging.
Pika.
[Misty] We'd better hurry
before all the fossils are dug up.
All these people digging
but nobody’s found any fossils yet.
I wonder if this great fossil rush
is really for real.
Sure it is.
-[Meowth] What’s taking those two so long?
-[all] Huh?
Humans. The only thing you can depend on
is that they’re always undependable.
[both] Ta-da.
-Prepare for trouble.
-Yes, and make it double.
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation.
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James.
Team Rocket.
Blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to...
-Oh!
-[all grunting]
Cut the poetry. I bet you two clowns
didn’t even plant the dynamite
-like you were supposed to.
-Wrong again, fur ball.
[groaning]
Of course we planted the dynamite.
Once we blast Grandpa Canyon
to smithereens,
we’ll be able to scoop up
all those Poké fossils.
[yells]
Next time, I’ll make fossils out of you.
Did you hear that? They’re going
to blow up this whole canyon.
All the people who are digging here
are going to get caught in the blast.
Pikachu and I will stop them.
You two, spread the word to run for it.
-There’s no time to lose.
-Let’s go.
[laughs]
Pretty soon, we’ll have
all the Pokémon fossils to ourselves.
[pants]
-Hold it right there.
-Oh, it’s that pest again.
-Always messing up our plans.
-But this time, you’re too late.
The fuse is already lit.
Whoa. I got to stop 'em!
Squirtle, I choose you.
Squirtle, squirt.
There’s no time to lose.
Squirtle, squirt out that fuse.
Squirtle!
Squirtle, after it.
-[all grunting]
-Pika!
-Arbok, go.
-Go, Weezing. Keep that fuse lit.
Weezing!
-You can do it, Squirtle.
-Ah, stop that twerp.
Keep squirting.
-[James] Quickly.
-[Meowth] Don’t let it hit the fuse.
-[James] Come on. They’re getting away.
-[Jessie] Hurry, you slowpokes.
-[Ash] We got to put it out somehow.
-[Meowth] You’re running like slugs.
-Faster, Arbok. There’s not much time.
-Hurry up, Weezing.
Weezing, sludge attack now.
[all yelling]
[grunting]
We’re not going to get it.
[panting] Oh!
[all yelling]
-Oh, look out.
-Pika.
[all yelling]
[all groaning]
No. The dynamite.
[all screaming]
Pikachu!
[all gasp]
[all screaming]
Squirtle. [gasps]
-Ash.
-Pikachu.
-Squirtle. Squirtle.
-What a disaster.
-[sighs] We’ve got to get them out.
-Hmm, let’s go.
Jigglypuff?
[all grunting]
[people cheering and applauding]
Jigglypuff.
[all grunting and groaning]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[all groaning]
Where are we?
Looks like we got blown
all the way to the moon.
Or down to the center of the earth.
[all gasp]
This is a cave. The dynamite must have
blown a hole in the roof and we fell in.
We must be buried deep
under the earth’s crust.
[both] Buried?
This is all your fault, you twerp.
If you hadn’t tried to put out that fuse,
we never would have fallen down here.
Hey, you’re the crooks who planted all
that dynamite up there in the first place.
Pikachu.
What difference does it make
who got us down here?
All that matters is getting out of here
in one piece. Look up there.
[all gasp]
[all yell]
[Ash]
The roof of the cave is blocked.
Hmm, heh.
James, it sounds like
you have an answer to our problem.
-Hmm? We’re all doomed.
-Huh?
-That’s not the answer I wanted to hear.
-Ugh.
-There must be some way out.
-Chu.
-Pi?
-What’s up, Pikachu?
-Pika, pika.
-Huh?
-[both scream]
-I don’t think we’re in here alone.
What are they?
[all quivering]
Let’s see.
[Pokédex] Omanyte and Omastar.
Kabuto and Kabutops.
It is believed that these Pokémon became
extinct tens of thousands of years ago.
The details of their behavior
is shrouded in mystery.
Though some have speculated
that they may still exist,
none of these Pokémon
have ever been seen alive.
We’re going to be rich.
We’ll open a prehistoric Pokémon park
that’ll be bigger than Pokéworld.
Even the boss will be impressed with us.
Ah, I could get my own talk show
or even my own cartoon.
Those Pokémon don’t seem as happy
about this as you guys do.
Chu.
[Ash] Just look at those eyes.
These Pokémon seem really angry.
They look like they just woke up.
Maybe these Pokémon weren’t fossilized
but were just sleeping.
That’s it. The dynamite must have woken
them up after thousands of years.
Some alarm clock.
Ugh. Never mind.
Let’s just capture them.
[both] Poké Ball, go.
-Kabutops!
-[grunts]
[all yelling]
-They have us trapped.
-There’s no place to run.
We have to battle.
Charmeleon, I choose you.
Char.
Charmeleon, use your flame
to stop them.
[grunts]
Ah, it still won’t obey me.
Kabutops!
[all screaming]
[Pokémon growling]
[all yelling]
[all grunting]
[Misty] Team Rocket blew the canyon up
with dynamite.
Ash must be trapped down under these
boulders. You’ve got to help us.
The bulldozers can’t make it down here.
We’ll have to dig by hand.
I’ll go and get some help.
[both groan]
[sighs]
Go, Geodude.
Geo.
Geodude, help us move
this pile of rocks.
[grunting]
[all grunting]
Listen, Ash, you better hold on.
Don’t forget you still owe me a new bike.
[all yelling and growling]
Arbok. Weezing. What are you doing?
Why are you running away from them?
-You have to chase them.
-[both gasp]
[growling]
Go on, Pikachu.
Give them your electric shock.
Pikachu!
Pika, pika!
Ah, electricity isn’t going to work.
Charmeleon.
[grunting]
Aw, it’s useless.
[screams]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[Pokémon murmuring]
I don’t understand what happened.
-A miracle. This is a miracle.
-We’re alive.
[distant whooshing]
Oh, no, I hear something else.
[whooshing]
[all screaming]
[grunts]
[screeches]
[all quivering]
[Pokédex]
Aerodactyl, an extinct flying Pokémon.
Its hard fangs suggest that
it was a carnivore.
Its sharp claws were probably
used to capture prey.
-What’s a carnivore?
-That means it thinks we’re dinner.
-That must be why the others ran away.
-I hope it don’t like cat food.
[screeches]
[all screaming]
Charmeleon.
[gasps] Looks like Charmeleon’s
finally ready to fight.
-Good luck.
-Char.
[groans]
A first-round knockout.
[all groan and gasp]
-[Brock] Ash.
-[Misty] Hey, Ash.
Get us out of here.
And hurry up.
[all gasp and scream]
[screeches]
[yells]
-[Jenny] Over here.
-[Brock] Hurry up.
[Misty] Let’s go.
[yells]
-Charmeleon.
-Pikachu.
-Pikachu, where did Ash go?
-Pika.
[all gasp]
[screeching]
[groaning]
[screams]
-Watch out.
Jigglypuff. Huh?
Jigglypuff. Jiggly, jiggly, jigglypuff.
-Hey, there’s Jigglypuff.
-I wonder what it’s doing here.
-Oh, I get it.
-What?
Jigglypuff.
It wants to sing.
I’ll get Jigglypuff to sing to Aerodactyl.
Great idea.
Jigglypuff, if you help us out now,
later, we’ll listen to your song
as much as you want.
Jigglypuff, heh.
Somebody get me down.
[both gibbering]
[all gasp]
Pika!
[roars]
Whoa. Charizard.
-Amazing.
-It evolved into Charizard.
[grunting]
[squawks] Aero!
[yells]
Huh?
[Ash] Charizard.
[roars]
[all grunting]
Charizard, you evolved because you wanted
to rescue me when I got into trouble.
I thought you didn’t want me
as your trainer but now I see I was wrong.
[grunting]
[yells]
I was right.
Looks like the only reason Charizard
evolved was to battle Aerodactyl.
Pika, pi.
Careful, Ash.
Pretty soon, Ash is going to be too
overcooked for Aerodactyl to eat.
[gasps] Please, Jigglypuff,
sing us your slumber song.
Jiggly.
♪ Jigglypuff ♪
♪ Jigglypuff, Jiggly... ♪
Hey, stay awake, Aerodactyl.
If you fall asleep, we’ll both...
-[Jigglypuff sings]
-[snores]
[grunting]
[both yawn]
[all yawning]
♪ Jigglypuff ♪
-[growling]
-[Jigglypuff singing]
[screeches]
[snores]
[Jifflypuff singing]
[Jigglypuff singing]
Jigglypuff , puff! Puff!
Jigglypuff.
[snoring]
Some of you are claiming that you saw
a prehistoric Pokémon here in the canyon.
That is ridiculous.
Let me assure you, it was only a dream
caused by Jigglypuff’s song.
I must also announce that due to
the danger of further cave collapses,
no more digging will be permitted.
[all chattering]
Hmm. That Aerodactyl sure didn’t seem
like a dream.
[all] Gary dreams the best.
Better than the rest.
He’s the best from east to west.
I guess they’re right.
[all laughing]
-Where’d Jigglypuff go?
-Were you hoping for an encore?
Well, at least it deserved to take a bow.
Jigglypuff and Charizard
really saved the day this time.
That Aerodactyl is one of a kind.
It’s too bad you couldn’t capture it, Ash.
But I think Aerodactyl and the others
would be happier just going back to sleep.
-Maybe you’re right.
-[Ash] Hey, I almost forgot.
-[both] Huh?
-I found this when I woke up.
[both] Huh?
Are you sure it’s all right for you
to just take that?
What do you mean? Do you think
I should have left it with Joy?
-Ugh, okay, Ash, I’ll raise it for you.
-But I could raise it myself.
You would have dropped it
and broken it anyway.
I would not.
Don’t worry, Ash.
I’ll take good care of it.
Hey, wait up! Give it back.
Finders keepers!
[narrator] And so our heroes
leave Grandpa Canyon,
resting place of the ancient Pokémon,
with a souvenir.
Hm. Maybe they should have
just bought the T-shirts.
Meanwhile, another group of tourists
is still enjoying the sights.
[Pokémon snoring]
-Hey, up there, somebody help us.
-We don’t want to be extinct too.
[yawns]
-[both] Ah.
-Shh. You’re going to wake it up.
[all shiver]
[Team Rocket sing]
Rockaby, dactyl please don’t eat us
[James sneezes]
[Aerodactyl screeches]
Okay, guys, we gotta rap some Pokémon.
You just do the singing.
I'll take care of the hard part.
Let's get it on!
♪ I want to be the best
there ever was ♪
♪ To beat all the rest
Yeah, that's my cause ♪
♪ Electrode, Diglett, Nidoran, Mankey
Venusaur, Rattata, Fearow, Pidgey ♪
♪ Seaking, Jolteon, Dragonite, Gastly
Ponyta, Vaporeon, Poliwrath, Butterfree ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
♪ I'll search across the land
Look far and wide ♪
♪ Release from my hand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Venomoth, Poliwag, Nidorino, Golduck
Ivysaur, Grimer, Victreebel, Moltres ♪
♪ Nidoking, Farfetch'd, Abra, Jigglypuff
Kingler, Rhyhorn, Clefable, Wigglytuff ♪
Thirty-two down, that's it for now!
Tune in tomorrow.
We'll wrapped at you some more.
There's 150,
so watch Monday through Friday.
You'll catch 'em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪