♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
[Ash] Wow, look at that.
It's a wild Hitmonchan.
So that's one of those fighting Pokémon
I've heard about.
That one's a real fighter.
[Pokédex]
Hitmonchan, a skilled fighting Pokémon
that packs an incredibly fast punch.
All right, let's capture it.
-Ready, Pikachu?
-Pikachu.
If you defeat Hitmonchan,
you'll become the world champion Pokémon.
Pikachu.
[cheering and applause]
Chan!
-Pika.
-You don't have to be afraid.
I'll teach you my secret punch,
and nobody'll be able to beat you.
Pikachu.
You got to learn the basics first.
Keep your left up and jab with your right.
Pika, pika.
Since when did Ash become a boxing expert?
Beats me.
[narrator]
Well, everything's been going pretty well.
Misty caught Psyduck,
and Brock got Vulpix,
but Ash hasn't captured
any Pokémon lately.
He might be getting a little worried,
but now Ash'll try his luck
with Hitmonchan.
[Ash] The Punchy Pokémon
-[Pikachu] Pi.
-Chan.
Okay, Hitmonchan, ready for a match?
Chan.
[grunting]
Monchan.
Hitmonchan,
Pikachu's going to teach you a lesson.
-Pikachu, attack.
-Pika.
[bell dings]
Pika, pika, pika, chu!
That's it, Pikachu. Now jab, jab.
Now give it the big uppercut.
Pika, pika, pika, Pikachu.
-Chan!
-[groaning]
Chu!
Make Pikachu stop, Ash.
This isn't even a fight.
Pikachu, give me that special punch
I just taught you.
-Pika, pika!
-Chan.
Give it the rocket punch.
Pikachu!
-[both] Huh?
-Pika.
We did it.
-They did?
-No way.
Pikachu.
-Pi.
-Chan.
[screeches]
So much for the great rocket punch.
How many times do I have to tell you,
don't drop your guard.
-Chan.
-Keep your gloves up, Hitmonchan,
because fighting smart
hurts less than fighting stupid.
-Chan.
-Now go knock that pipsqueak out.
-Hitmon.
-[all gasp]
-Hitmonchan, hit.
-Ah!
-Hitmon, hitmon, hitmon.
-[all gasp]
-Cha!
-Pikachu.
Hitmonchan.
[gasps]
Chu.
-Pikachu, are you okay?
-Pika, pika.
I declare Hitmonchan the winner.
Congratulations.
One, two, three.
-Hooray!
-Chan!
-I wonder who this guys is?
-He's a pretty serious trainer.
-I guess it wasn't wild.
-[girl] Daddy.
-Daddy, please come home.
-Rebecca?
Daddy, please quit Pokémon training
and come home with me.
I won't come home until I become
champion in the P1 Grand Prix.
Daddy.
I'll be in the Gym taking on challengers.
The Gym's that way.
I'll be waiting for you.
Uh...
[sighs]
-Oh, well.
-Aha.
Can I be of help to you, young lady?
-I'm really sorry my father bothered you.
-No problem.
Can I ask a favor of you,
Pokémon trainers,
a really, really big favor?
Please feel free to ask.
We'll be glad to help in any way possible.
Thank you.
Please, I want you to defeat
my father's Hitmonchan.
[both] Huh?
-We'll do it for you.
-Ah!
[Ash chuckles]
The Fighting Spirit Gym.
[Ash] This sure doesn't look like
an ordinary Pokémon Gym.
What's the P1 Grand Prix?
P1 is short
for the Pokémon number one Grand Prix.
It's a tournament for fighting Pokémon.
Because my father wants to win the P1,
he's training all the time
and ignoring his family.
So if we defeat that Hitmonchan,
your dad will come to his senses
and go back home.
Right.
Ha, don't worry. Just leave it to us.
-Huh?
-Leave it...
-To us?
-Pika.
We'll take care of it.
Ash, don't you have a fighting Pokémon
we can use?
What are you talking about?
[chuckles]
You don't mean Primeape, do you?
Primeape!
[growls and mutters]
Ape-prime!
Yeah, Primeape should be able
to do the job.
And I've got Geodude.
We'll both enter the tournament
and defeat that Hitmonchan.
[James] A big Pokémon match.
[Meowth]
And feast your eyes on that prize.
[Jessie] I'd love to get my hands
on that championship belt.
And if we sold the belt,
we could go and stuff ourselves
at the all-you-can-eat buffet.
Unlimited food.
Honey-glazed ham, roast leg of lamb,
strawberry jam.
Sirloin steaks, chocolate cakes.
Can't you numbskulls think of anything
but food?
[both yell]
What would you do with the money, Jessie?
-Who me?
-Yes, Jessie.
What would you do
if you had some extra cash?
First, I'd go to the salon
and get a complete facial.
Then I'd get my hair and makeup done.
Then I'd go on a major shopping spree.
Dresses, then handbags, then shoes.
Then I'd do a bit of jewelry shopping.
And after all that,
I'd invite some close friends over
for a nice quiet dinner at home.
[laughs]
I hate to interrupt
your internal dream sequence,
but shouldn't we figure out
how to get into this competition?
Only fighting Pokémon are allowed.
Of which we currently have none.
Well, then, we'll just have to borrow one,
won't we?
All we have to do is find one. Hmm.
-Like that one there.
-[Meowth] What is it?
[James]
Hitmonlee, the kicking fiend.
Ah.
[announcer] Ladies and gentlemen,
our fighting Pokémon Festival,
the P1 Grand Prix,
is about to begin.
Now we've got our fighting Pokémon.
Thank you. Please remain seated.
[mumbling]
[announcer]
The contestants in the P1 Grand Prix
are about to enter the ring.
Introducing the number one contender,
the fighting machine Hitmonchan
and its trainer Anthony.
Hitmon.
[announcer] And now the challenger,
the kicking fiend,
Hitmonlee, along with its trainer Giant.
[groans] Stand up straight.
You're making me dizzy.
I'm tired. Let's trade places.
-Ah!
-Quit complaining.
[announcer]
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
two new Pokémon trainers
competing here in their P1 debut.
Please welcome Ash and Brock.
-Oh, no, not you again.
-Huh?
Hmm...
-Hey, Ash, what's the matter?
-Uh, nothing, I guess.
[announcer] And now for our first match,
Machop is ready to battle.
What Pokémon will Ash use to challenge it?
I choose you, Primeape.
Primeape.
[growls] Primeape.
-Machop.
-Primeape.
[both growling]
[bell dings]
[yelling]
[grunting]
Primeape!
-Get up, Primeape.
-It looks beat.
[announcer]
And it looks like Machop has the advantage
in the battle with Primeape.
Machop may be small,
but it sure packs plenty of power.
[growling]
-[both gasp]
-This looks bad.
[announcer] Machop's mega-muscle power
stops Primeape's kick cold.
It looks like Machop's getting ready
for its special attack.
Special attack?
[Pokédex]
Machop. Its body is pure muscle.
Its special attack is the seismic toss.
Oh, no. It's going to toss Primeape.
-Machop.
-Primeape.
Ah!
Primeape. [grunts]
[groans]
[both gasp]
[Ash groans]
[Primape grunts]
Primeape, are you okay?
[groans]
-Primeape.
-All right, good.
-Now, we're not going to quit.
-Primeape!
Watch out for that seismic toss
and give it everything you've got.
Primeape.
-That's amazing.
-What's amazing?
Primeape used to do just what it wanted
and never listened to anybody.
-But now it's taking orders from Ash.
-Pika.
Primeape, scratch attack.
Primeape. Primeape.
Jump, Primeape!
[growls] Prime... Attack.
Mega kick right now.
-Machop.
-Primeape. Primeape.
-We did it.
-[announcer] And this match is over.
Machop is down and out.
Ash's Primeape wins the battle.
-That Primeape, it's really tough.
-Monchan.
It seems like everything changed
when Ash dove to save Primeape.
That's when Primeape started
to trust Ash.
Pika, pika.
Primeape. Primeape. Primeape. [growls]
[announcer] Our next match
is between Hitmonlee and Geodude.
Fans, Geodude is hard as a rock.
Will Hitmonlee be able to crack Geodude?
[bell dings]
Rebecca, don't worry.
Everything's under control.
-Brock, watch out behind you.
-Huh?
[Brock groans]
[groaning]
Monlee.
This won't take very long.
Ah! Geodude, this time, hit Hitmonlee.
Dude.
Don't show any mercy.
Kick, kick, kick.
Hitmonlee. Lee, lee, lee...
Geodude's going to get turned
into gravel. [groans]
-Brock.
-[groans]
Huh?
If you're a real man,
you know when you have to admit defeat.
Time to face facts.
You can lose today and win tomorrow.
Right.
[announcer]
Fans, Brock has thrown in the towel.
[bell dings]
[Brock] Geodude.
-I'm sorry. Are you okay?
-Geo.
You don't have to apologize.
You gave it your best shot.
Dude.
Don't worry,
you'll be as solid as a rock again soon.
Primeape and I
will take care of things now, Brock.
-I'm counting on you, Ash.
-Right.
[announcer] Machop wins.
-Monchan.
-Hitmonlee.
Primeape.
Yay!
[announcer] Now Ash's Primeape
will advance to the final match,
while the Fighting Spirit Gym's
very own Hitmonchan,
the number one contender
at this tournament,
takes on the legendary kicking fiend
Hitmonlee
for a chance at the championship.
This is a tough opponent.
If we play fair, we may lose.
Not with the plan I cooked up with Meowth.
And speaking of cooking,
I'm broiling in here.
-Get back in.
-Hmm.
Keep on moving. Keep on fighting.
-Remember, you're a champion.
-Monchan.
[bell dings]
Hitmonchan. Hit. Hitmon. Hit.
-Monlee.
-Chan.
Got to be smart. Got to be strong.
Got to keep moving.
Lee, lee, lee...
Hitmonchan. Hitmonchan.
Hitmonlee is not landing any kicks.
We've got to slow Hitmonchan down.
And a little gloppy glue should do it.
[chuckles]
Hitmonchan. Chan.
Hitmonlee.
[announcer]
Hitmonchan's in trouble.
Hitmonlee's mega kick
is getting the best of Hitmonchan.
Hitmonchan.
This is dangerous.
You should forfeit the match right now.
Lee, lee, lee...
Finish it, Hitmonlee.
Hitmonlee.
Stop it!
Don't hurt my father's Pokémon.
-Rebecca.
-[all gasp]
[both gasp]
[groans]
-Aw. Are you all right?
-I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
Oh, Daddy.
[grunts] Are you hurt, Rebecca?
-No, I'm fine.
-I'm glad.
[Rebecca chuckles]
I give up.
[bell dings]
[announcer]
Anthony throws in the towel.
Hitmonlee is the winner.
Eh, good work, Hitmonchan.
Are you okay?
Monchan.
I'm sorry I worried you
and your mother so much.
-Oh, Daddy.
-That's my girl.
-Isn't that great?
-The family's back together.
-That means we're up against Hitmonlee.
-That's right.
Your battling brought them back together.
And now all Ash needs to do
is win one more time to be champion.
-Pikachu.
-[Jessie] Don't bet on it.
-[all gasp]
Huh?
I can't wait for the chance
to show you three little goody-goodies
what losers you are.
You don't stand a chance against us.
We're going to win that championship belt.
And after we do, you can find us
at the all-you-can-eat buffet table.
-Oh!
-Will you be quiet?
-It's them again.
-Team Rocket.
How did you ever guess?
[both] Ha!
To protect the world from devastation.
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the st...
Oh, I can't take it.
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
-Surrender now.
-Ah!
[James] Surrender now or prepare to...
Prepare to... [sobs]
-Uh, we're not finished.
-Hmm.
As I was saying, we are going to be
the winners around here.
-And you can bet your buffet on that.
-[bell dings]
[announcer]
And now for the final confrontation.
Primeape, a newcomer
who's battled to this last round
with tremendous attacks,
faces the ferocious footwork of Hitmonlee,
the kicking fiend.
Get ready, fans,
for a match you'll never forget.
You can't just defend yourself, Primeape.
Attack.
If you can't get inside Hitmonlee's kicks,
you'll never win the battle, Primeape.
Primeape, get in there
and show Hitmonlee that you're not afraid.
Primeape.
[growling]
-You did it.
-All right.
[growling]
-What are you doing?
-Kick it. Kick it.
[chuckling]
Pikachu.
-The secret weapon is ready.
-Aha.
All you got to do now
is use this remote control.
Have Hitmonlee jump up,
and then flip the switch.
A hundred thousand volts
will run through the ring
followed by an explosion.
Primeape will get a charge out of that.
[cackles]
Pika. Pika, pi.
-What is it, Pikachu?
-Pikachu. Pikachu. Pikachu.
Look, I don't have time for this now,
okay?
-Hang in there, Primeape.
-Pika.
Pika.
[whimpers]
Monlee.
-Hit it.
-You got it.
-Nothing's happening.
-Something's wrong?
-Hitmonlee.
-Primeape.
Primeape. [growling]
All right.
Use the seismic toss now, Primeape.
-[both] Oh, no.
-This is bad.
Primeape.
We did it.
Hitmonlee.
[announcer]
And it's all over.
Primeape defeats Hitmonlee
with a seismic toss.
Ash's Primeape wins by a knockout.
Primeape is the new
P1 Pokémon Grand Prix champion.
-We did it!
-All right!
-It's prime time for Primeape.
-Primeape. Primeape.
I'm proud of you, Primeape.
Congratulations.
Primeape.
Ash, this Primeape has got a lot
of natural fighting talent.
-You think so?
-Mm-hm.
Why don't you let me train it for a while?
I promise to turn it
into a real P1 champion.
A true P1 champion.
-What went wrong, Meowth?
-What happened to our secret weapon?
Pika.
Pikachu.
Here it is. It looks like it works.
Pika.
Really appreciate it.
[beeping]
[all] Ah!
[all] Oh!
Team Rocket's blasting off again.
Prime. Prime.
Please take care of Primeape.
I'm counting on you.
[chuckles] There's no need to worry.
You can depend on me.
And I'll make sure my father spends
-lots of time with our family.
-Mm-hm.
You keep on training and winning,
Primeape,
and I'll always be grateful and proud
that I knew a real P1 champion.
-Prime. Primeape.
-Mm.
-Bye.
-Goodbye and thank you.
[chuckles] Nice kid.
[narrator] Just when they were beginning
to understand each other,
Ash and Primeape go their separate ways.
Maybe they'll meet again someday
somewhere.
But for now, new Pokémon
and new challenges are waiting just ahead.
-♪ Pokémon! ♪
-Attention, all Pokémon trainers ♪
Do you got what it takes
to be the best?
Today will do 30 Pokémon
It's the ultimate test!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Articuno, Jynx, Nidorina, Beedrill, ♪
♪ Haunter, Squirtle, Chansey
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Parasect, Exeggcute, Muk, Dewgong ♪
♪ Pidgeotto, Lapras, Vulpix, Rhydon ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master
Is my destiny ♪
♪ Charizard, Machamp, Pinsir, Koffing ♪
♪ Dugtrio, Golbat, Staryu, Magikarp ♪
♪ Ninetales, Ekans, Omaster, Scyther ♪
♪ Tentacool, Dragonair, Magmar ♪
Not bad, not bad!
Hey, don’t get cocky.
Tomorrow’s the hardest part.
We’re on our way to 150 Pokémon!
There’s no stopping us!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Each Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Its you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪