♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test ♪
♪ To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon! Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, gotta catch 'em all
Pikachu, go!
Pika!
[narrator] You’ll remember in
an earlier Pokémon adventure,
our hero Ash achieved his dream
of catching a Bulbasaur.
It was a shocking victory!
[Pikachu grunts]
Go, Poké Ball!
[narrator]
And so Bulbasaur joined the ranks!
Soon Misty, Brock and Ash lost their way,
but found a Charmander.
Braving a fierce storm,
Ash and his friends came to its rescue.
Abandoned by its trainer,
the fire Pokémon recovered its strength
and gained some new friends!
Come on, Charmander.
Welcome to the group!
[narrator] Charmander became
Ash’s newest Pokémon.
[laughs]
[narrator] And that’s how Ash caught
Charmander and Bulbasaur.
He’s pretty pleased with himself
as he skips down the road,
singing our favorite theme.
Becoming a Pokémon trainer
looks like it’ll be a snap. Or will it?
Can things continue to go so smoothly?
Maybe Ash is too confident.
He’d better keep his eyes
glued to the road ahead.
Who knows what pitfalls are waiting
to swallow up our young hero?
[thuds and then Ash gasps]
[all yell]
[narrator]
Ah, what did I tell you? A pitfall.
[Ash]
Here Comes The Squirtle Squad.
[Misty]
No, not another hole!
-[Brock] Ow! I landed on my head!
-[Pikachu] Pikachu!
[groaning]
-It must be a prank.
-Someone has a bad sense of humor.
[Ash]
Who would play such a rotten trick?
Squirtle, Squirtle, Squirtle...
Who are you?
What’s so funny?
We could have been hurt!
Squirtle, Squirtle, Squirtle...
Ah, dangerous practical jokes
are nothing to laugh about.
Pikachu!
Squirtle, Squirtle, Squirtle...
[Pokédex]
Squirtle, this tiny turtle Pokémon
draws its long neck into its shell
to launch incredible water attacks
with amazing range and accuracy.
The blasts can be quite powerful.
With my very own Squirtle,
Gary will never beat me!
Go, Pikachu!
[Squirtle and Pikachu grunting]
Squirtle!
Squirtle, Squirtle. Squirtle.
-Pika.
-Squirtle.
[growls]
[both growl]
-Pik!
-[growls]
-Squirtle. Squirtle. Squirtle...
-[police siren]
[all] Squirtle.
That was sure weird.
[tires screeches]
Are you guys all right?
Has anyone been hurt here?
-Officer Jenny!
-Huh? Have we met before?
Your face doesn’t look familiar.
We met you back in Viridian City,
remember?
Oh, you mean one of the other Jennys,
my cousins.
- Cousin?
- My cousins are all police officers.
All of us look identical,
plus we’re all named Jenny.
[camera shutter clicks]
Talk about family resemblance.
At least they remember all their names!
[Jenny] That Pokémon gang calls itself
the Squirtle Squad.
-Squirtle Squad?
-I’ve never heard of a Pokémon gang.
They’re all Squirtles who were deserted
by their Pokémon trainers.
Deserted?
They don’t have a trainer,
so they just run wild
and play tricks on the whole town.
[all laughing and gibbering]
It’s really kind of sad because if they’d
had somebody to care about them,
they wouldn’t have turned out to be
as bad as they are.
It’s a real shame.
[Jessie] There! I see them!
The little brats. And Pikachu’s with them.
Do you see a restaurant?
I’m really starving here.
But no more pizza!
[Meowth and James grunt]
I’m sick of pizza every meal!
You’ll never eat again
if you mess up this mission!
-Can we order Chinese food?
-Or maybe some tacos?
[growling and smacking]
-[groaning]
-Am I the only member of this team
who thinks world domination is more
important than what’s for lunch?
Now, let’s focus ourselves
on what really matters
and that’s how we’re going
to capture Pikachu!
[stomach growls]
[both gasp]
Heh, now my stomach says
it’s time to eat.
-Huh, yes!
-Yay, yeah!
We’re going to have a picnic!
[all gasp]
You guys got a problem?
Squirtle. Squirtle. Squirtle. Squirtle.
Meowth, what’s it saying?
I think it said,
"give us your food or else!"
You’re threatening us?
We’re Team Rocket. We threaten!
Squirtle. Squirtle. Squirtle.
-Let’s show these little creeps.
-I’m game.
[all yelling]
[all groaning]
[grunts] Squirtle. Squirtle.
Squirtle. Squirtle.
Squirtle. Squirtle. Squirtle.
Oh, no. They’re eating
all the jelly donuts and eclairs!
They’re drinking all the lemonade!
This is cruel and unusual!
Squirtle. Squirtle. Squirtle. Squirtle...
-Those aren’t Squirtles. They’re piggles!
-They’re starting on the sandwiches.
We’ve got to do something!
Oh, wait! You Squirtles, how’d you like
to do a little job for us?
There are these three kids
with a Pikachu.
Our boss would be most appreciative
if you helped us capture them.
He’d make it worth your while.
Squirtle. Squirtle.
What did Squirtle answer?
The Squirtle said, "Forget it.
We know humans can’t be trusted."
So make them trust us!
Hmm, that won’t be easy
but I’ll see what I can do.
Squirtle, both of these humans
belong to Meowth!
-Huh, "belong to"?
-They’ll never trust you two.
You’ve got "liar" written all over you.
Just let me handle this!
Ugh, oh, you little...
These humans are my pets.
I trained them but they’re pretty stupid.
Squirtle.
Don’t ever raise your voice to me again,
you bad human!
-Bad human! Bad, bad human!
-[grunts]
Squirtle. Squirtle. Squirtle.
Squirtle...
Squirtle.
Ha! [laughs]
See, you guys can trust me!
Squirtle. Squirtle.
[munches]
Meowth, what about us?
Untie us too!
-I want a donut!
-Be quiet.
We got to keep up this act
till the Squirtles trust me
and that’s going to a little time!
[gasps]
-I caught something!
-Huh?
[all yelling]
Squirtle.
-I’m soaked.
-Me too.
Pik! Pikachu!
[all yelling]
Knock it off, Pikachu!
[all groaning]
Wet clothes conduct electricity!
Squirtle. Squirtle.
I’ve had enough of your pranks, Squirtle!
Pikachu, it’s out of the water now!
[both grunting]
Huh?
Oh! Pikachu!
Oh, it’s a Goldeen!
Watch out for its horn!
Pika? Pik!
Goldeen. Goldeen. Goldeen.
Goldeen. Goldeen....
Swim to shore, Pikachu. Hurry up!
Faster! Faster!
[screams]
[all gasping]
[groans]
Pikachu!
[yells]
Ugh, they got us!
Squirtle.
-Squirtle.
-[Meowth laughs]
You’re not going to Squirtle out
of this one!
-It’s Meowth!
-Meowth?
I’m the Pokémon in charge here.
Just wait till my human pets get back!
Na-na-na-na-na!
[grunts]
[screams]
Don’t believe him, Squirtles.
Meowth’s a big liar.
Those humans aren’t Meowth’s pets.
Team Rocket’s trying to trick you all
into doing their dirty work.
Squirtle.
Quiet, human!
Who are you going to believe,
this human or a fellow Pokémon?
[all] Squirtle. Squirtle...
-Ash, Pikachu’s in bad shape!
-Huh?
[Misty]
We’ve got to do something!
[Brock] We’ve got to heal Pikachu
with super potion before it’s too late.
But we don’t have any super potion.
What can we do?
-A shop in town sells it.
-In town?
Squirtle Squad, please,
you’ve got to let me go into town.
If I don’t get the medicine,
Pikachu’s in a lot of trouble!
Squirtle. Squirtle.
Squirtle. Squirtle...
They know you humans
are just trying to get away!
Trust me. I won’t run away!
As soon as I buy the medicine,
I’ll come back. I promise!
Squirtle.
Squirtle says promises are cheap!
I’m begging you. Please trust me.
[sobs]
[whimpers and wheezes]
Squirtle. Squirtle. Squirtle. Squirtle...
The Squirtle says
if you’re not back here by noon tomorrow,
the red-headed girl
gets her hair dyed purple!
-Purple! Why you mangy little flea trap!
-Huh?
When I get out of this,
I’m going to wrap your tail--
Misty, don’t worry. I’ll be back, okay?
[grunts]
So long! Be back in a flash!
Good luck.
Even if that kid does make it back,
we’ll all be long gone.
[chuckles]
[in mind] Just hold on a little longer,
Pikachu. I’ll get you that super potion!
[screams and grunts]
I got to keep going.
Pikachu needs me to get that medicine.
Just don’t look down.
[grunting and yelling]
[sighs]
[gasps]
Man, that was close!
[gasps and screams]
[screams and grunts]
That’s it. That’s the place!
[yelps]
I beg your pardon.
[groans]
[wheezing]
Pikachu, don’t give up.
Ash will be back here
with the medicine soon. Just hold on!
[in mind]
Where are Jessie and James already?
-[Jessie] All right, freeze!
-[all] Huh?
These are ice packs we’re gunning,
I mean ice guns we’re packing!
It’s Team Rocket!
Cool! We’re just like those supervillains
in the comic books, except better looking.
And even meaner!
[Jessie] Listen up!
We want all the flash powder you’ve got!
-[James] And a large roll of dental floss.
-[Man] What do you need them for?
[Jessie] You want to get rid
of the Squirtle Squad, don’t you?
The flash powder will scare them
out of town!
-The floss is for our teeth.
-The Squirtle Squad!
-Ciao for now.
-Farewell!
[all gasping and grunting]
Look! It’s snowing!
It’s Team Rocket! I’ve got to get back
before they get Pikachu!
[grunts]
Super potion, please!
Oh, no, I don’t need a new gun!
-Don’t shoot me, please. I’m not--
-[Jenny] Stop!
Drop those! He’s not with Team Rocket!
Step on it, Jenny.
I got to get there by noon!
Just hang on, Ash! Huh?
[tires screech]
A dead end.
These flash blasts will scare
the shells off the Squirtle Squad.
[Jessie] And in the confusion,
we’ll snatch Pikachu!
[Jenny]
Here’s a secret entrance to the cave.
[Ash]
Gee, there’s not much room.
[Jenny]
The passageway’s too narrow for an adult
-but maybe you can squeeze through.
-I can do it!
Be careful, Ash!
It’s too dark to see in here.
Hey, I know!
-Charmander, I choose you!
-Char! Char!
-Charmander, lead the way!
-Charmander!
[Ash grunts]
They’re gone! Pikachu!
[screams]
Misty! [gasps and grunts]
What’ve you done?
I told you I’d be back by noon and I am!
What did you do with my friends!
-We’re right here.
-Huh?
-Squirtle...
-Where’s the super potion for Pikachu?
Oh, uh, here!
Hurry! Let’s spray it on Pikachu!
-So, Misty, your hair isn’t purple.
-Nope! I’m still a redhead!
[Brock]
The Squirtle Squad was bluffing!
They play tricks but they’d never change
a girl’s natural hair color!
-Hm?
-Squirtle. Squirtle. Squirtle...
That blast! It’s Team Rocket!
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation.
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation.
[both]
To denounce the evils of truth and love,
to extend our reach to the stars above...
-Jessie.
-James.
Squirtle Squad, it’s payback time
for insulting Team Rocket.
[both] Bombs away!
[Jessie]
Meowth, carry Pikachu up the ladder!
And the rest of you are in
for a real blast. Get it?
Meowth!
Pikachu!
[all yelling]
Quick, run for cover!
Head for the cave!
[Misty] Hurry!
Squirtle.
-Squirtle!
-Squirtle.
Here I come!
[Ash grunts]
Oh, Ash!
[Ash groans]
Hey, Squirtle, are you okay?
[feeble] Squirtle...
Here come two more!
Save yourself, Squirtle.
Run for it!
- Whoa, Squirtle!
- Squirtle!
[both grunting]
Look out!
[all yelling]
No more Squirtle Squad!
The town’s going to give us medals
and we’ll be heroes!
[Ash] Not so fast!
-Who said that?
-Huh?
-[Jessie] Weren’t they...
-[James] Didn’t they...
[Meowth] How did they...
- Squirtle! Water Gun attack now!
Squirtle!
[all yelling]
-[James] Come back here!
-Pikachu!
[grunting]
[Team Rocket] Looks like
Team Rocket’s blasting off again!
A fire! The blasts must have set it off!
If it keeps burning,
the whole town could go up in smoke!
-Don’t worry, Jenny. I’ve got an idea.
-Oh.
Listen, if you Squirtles work together,
you can combine your water guns
to put out the fire!
And so we gratefully award
this certificate to the Squirtle Squad.
Thank you for saving our town
from the fire.
Because of your skill and bravery,
we proudly appoint you
the town firefighters!
Squirtle!
Pi, Pi, Pika, Pikachu.
Hey, Ash, that Squirtle is following us!
Squirtle. Squirtle.
Would you like to come along with us,
Squirtle?
Squirtle!
[Ash laughs]
-Welcome to the team, Squirtle!
-Squirtle!
-Guess I’ve caught a new Pokémon!
-Pikachu!
-Caught? What do you mean caught?
-Oh, what’s the difference?
It’s on our side now!
[narrator] One more adventure,
one more new friend,
but there’s much more excitement
waiting just around the bend!
You guys up for the Pokérap?
There's 150 Pokémon.
You got to name them all.
I'm doing 32 today,
so try to keep up.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Zubat, Primeape, Meowth, Onix
Geodude, Rapidash, Magneton, Snorlax ♪
♪ Gengar, Tangela, Goldeen, Spearow
Weezing, Seel, Gyarados, Slowbro ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em, gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Kabuto, Persian, Paras, Horsea
Raticate, Magnemite, Kadabra, Weepinbell ♪
♪ Ditto, Cloyster, Caterpie, Sandshrew
Bulbasaur, Charmander, Golem, Pikachu ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
All right, how’d you do?
Loosen those lips.
Shake out that tongue!
Give it a rest. Today’s song is sung.
We’ll be back tomorrow!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em,
gotta catch 'em all, ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪