♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon! Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, gotta catch 'em all
[narrator] As our heroes travel onward,
a new challenge awaits them,
and so do many new and unusual Pokémon.
-Pi?
-Huh? What's the matter, Pikachu?
-Pika-pi!
-Hey! Pikachu!
-Pikachu.
-[all] Huh?
[squealing]
-Why's it tied up like that?
-It's been abandoned.
-What?
-No way.
You mean that someone
just left it here alone?
That's cruel.
[Pokédex]
Eevee. The evolution Pokémon.
It has the potential to evolve
into any one of three different Pokémon.
Whoa! Then I want one.
I don't think you should.
-Why not?
-Take a look at this.
[Ash] A tag? Hmm.
Stone Town?
[Brock] Stone town? That's the place
at the foot of Evolution Mountain.
[Pokédex] Eevee evolves
into one of three Pokémon,
depending on what stone is used on it.
Using a fire stone will yield Flareon,
the flame Pokémon.
A water stone yields Vaporeon,
the bubble jet Pokémon.
A thunder stone yields Jolteon,
the lighting Pokémon.
Huh, I'd love a Vaporeon.
Oh, big surprise, Misty.
All you ever think about is water Pokémon.
It sounds to me like you want to keep
that Eevee all to yourself.
Ha! So that's why she won't let go of it.
Well, if you really want something,
you have to go for it.
[squeals]
Hmm. That's it.
Third block, number 14.
[both gasp]
-[Misty] Wow.
-[Ash] It's gigantic.
[indistinct chatter]
-It's a garden party.
-Looks like fun.
-Hey, guys. Look there.
-[both] Huh?
Congratulations.
Poliwhirl evolved into Poliwrath.
Thank you so much.
Wow. That's so amazing.
Poliwrath.
-Cloyster.
-Vileplume.
Exeggutor.
Raichu.
Ninetales.
[all gasp]
They've all been evolved
using those stones.
Amazing.
[James]
Ooh! Look at all those evolved Pokémon.
We've got to have them.
They're ripe and just ready for picking.
It says here
Stone Town has these special stones
that help Pokémon evolve.
Baloney.
That's why we came to Evolution Mountain,
to get some of those special stones,
and I couldn't find a single stone
anywhere.
You dug in the wrong place,
Team Rocket scientist.
Well, we'll worry
about those stones later.
-I want some of that food.
-Stones can wait.
Let's grab some grub, shall we?
[slashing]
Stop thinking about food!
Good work.
Now that we've seen a round of evolution,
how about comparing attacks, eh?
-Eevee?
-[both] Huh?
-Ha-ha-ha.
-[both] Eevee.
-Where did you go to?
-We were worried about you, Eevee.
Yeah, thank you for finding Eevee for us.
This is great. We've got our star,
now we can go on with the show.
-Eevee's a star?
-Uh, then why was it tied up?
Mikey. Hey, Mikey! Eevee's come back.
Oh.
[squealing]
How could you lose him?
You've got to be careful.
You'll lose your trainer qualification.
Did Eevee really escape?
But it was tied to a tree, right?
Why did you bring it back?
[all] Huh?
[squealing]
Listen, Mikey.
One day you'll be a Pokémon trainer
just like us.
Do you really think
you can win your first battle
with an unevolved Eevee?
All of us won our first battles
because we've evolved our Eevees.
There's no other way to win.
The key to a first victory is evolution.
But I don't care about battles.
[all] Don't care?
-Vaporeon!
-Jolteon!
[Misty shudders]
-They're scary.
-Pika.
Everyone is waiting to see
what you make Eevee evolve into, Mikey.
You've got three choices.
Which do you think is the strongest
of all the evolved Eevees?
We want to know what you think
of our Pokémon.
Mikey, which Pokémon
do you want Eevee to become?
A thunder stone will make it a Jolteon.
When a Jolteon gets mad,
the hairs on its body turn to needles.
Then it fires at its opponent.
A water stone will make it a Vaporeon.
It can melt into water
and make itself disappear.
A fire stone will make it a Flareon.
With a blazing flame attack
released from its internal fire sack,
Flareon is the strongest
evolutionary choice of all.
Flare!
What, are you crazy?
My Jolteon is the strongest of all.
Too bad you're the only one who thinks so.
Heh, Mikey,
I'm sure you'll make the right choice
and make it a Vaporeon.
This family sure is competitive, Ash.
That's a lot of pressure
to put on the little guy.
Hey, give the kid a break, will you?
Isn't he a little young to battle?
We're throwing this party
just for him and his Eevee.
You should know you have to start training
early if you want to become a master.
Yeah, one of these days, you'll turn
that Pikachu into a Raichu won't you?
Huh? Well, I, uh...
Pika, pika?
Do you need a stone?
[Ash] Aw.
Wow, water stones, and thunder and fire.
[Brock]
You really have collected a lot of them.
That's what our town's known for.
But you can't mine them all the time.
[device beeping]
-Ha! Look at those beautiful stones.
-It's like a rock concert.
That's a special edition
of the Pokémon Friend.
Yeah, we used it to plan
today's special evolution party.
We wanted to bring together
all the trainers
that specialize
in stone-induced evolution.
Why don't you join our club, Ash?
Here, take this thunder stone.
What have you got, Brock?
I've got a Vulpix
that will become a Ninetales.
Vulpix.
Then why don't you just make it evolve?
Here, take this fire stone.
But I...
I can't just force Vulpix to evolve.
Vulpix is really important to me.
[all] Don't be dumb!
Hey, take it easy. You don't have to yell.
Evolution is what Pokémon are all about.
[both shuddering]
Horsea. Horsea.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Have a good swim, Horsea.
Horsea.
[laughs]
Huh?
-Huh?
-Hungry?
-[Psyduck] Psy?
-Huh?
Psy.
[Psyduck munching and Misty growling]
Stop that!
[laughs] Want some?
Uh-huh.
[squeals]
-Is it good?
-Mm-hm.
Pika?
[squeals]
It doesn't seem like you really want
to make Eevee evolve, do you, Mikey?
My brothers don't care about anything
but battling Pokémon.
And what about you, Mikey?
I was trying to hide Eevee from them,
just for today.
Then nobody could force me
to make it evolve at the party.
But Eevee looked very, very lonely
out there.
Chu.
I was going to go get it later.
[squeals]
I don't care if Eevee evolves or not.
I just want it to be my best friend.
That's great.
Huh? You think that's great?
-There's only one thing wrong.
-What's that?
You shouldn't have hidden Eevee.
You were just running away
from your problems.
Running away?
If you don't want Eevee to evolve,
tell your brothers how you feel.
That's your responsibility as a trainer.
But, hey, I'm not your mother or anything.
No. You're right.
Ha! I really should apologize to you.
If you hadn't claimed Eevee,
I was going to keep it
and change it into Vaporeon myself.
You were, Misty?
Pi, pika. Pikachu.
[squealing]
-Pika. Pikachu.
I wonder what they're saying.
A while ago,
Pikachu decided not to evolve.
Really?
Pika. Pikachu.
-You just don't get it, do you?
-We get it, all right.
We just don't evolve our Pokémon that way.
You like your way of evolving,
and we like ours.
That's the way to tell them, Brock.
Come on. Let's move on to the main event
so they can see evolution our way.
Good idea.
Mikey!
Have you decided on Eevee's evolution yet?
Uh... Uh... I'll, mm...
-Come right out and tell him, Mike.
-Uh... Uh...
Hmm...
Come on, Mikey.
Tell us what you decided.
Go ahead. Tell him, Mikey.
You can do it.
Pikachu.
[squeals]
Hmm.
-A Jolteon, right?
-A Flareon, right?
A Vaporeon.
Aw, you guys, I, uh...
[popping]
[all screaming]
[Jessie] It's show time, everybody.
[brother] Who invited you?
-Prepare for trouble.
-And make it double.
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation...
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation...
To denounce the evils of truth and love...
To extend our reach to the stars above...
-Jessie.
-James.
[munches] Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
That's delicious.
Keep your eyes open, guys.
Team Rocket will steal your Pokémon
if you're not careful.
[munches]
Weezing, spread a smokescreen.
Weezing.
[all coughing]
[brother] I can't see anything!
Pidgeotto, blow the smokescreen away.
Gust attack!
[screeching]
[all coughing]
-My Jolteon!
-Vaporeon!
Flareon!
-Where's Eevee?
-Pikachu!
Oh, no! My Horsea is gone!
Help! Help! My Poliwrath's gone!
The stones are gone!
All the food is gone too!
Those creeps took everything.
Team Rocket took the stones,
and they took the food too.
-Psy!
-Why couldn't they take you too?
The balloon! They're getting away!
Pidgeotto, attack that balloon!
[screeching]
You did it! Good work, Pidgeotto.
[all] Huh?
-It's empty.
-No.
Pidgeotto, go find Team Rocket.
[screeches]
[laughs] A piece of cake.
That was easier
than taking candy from a baby.
Candy and cold cuts and Pokémon too.
-We've outdone ourselves, James.
-Outdone ourselves, outsmarted them.
[laughs]
[squeaking]
[screeches]
Pika, pika. Pikachu!
[belches]
Ah, nothing tastes better
than a victory meal.
We've gotten beaten so many times,
I'd forgotten what victory tasted like.
Ooh!
I don't ever want you
to call us losers again.
From now on, we'll be known
as Team Rocket, champions of the world.
Champions of the entire world!
Why don't you two dry up?
It's time make that little one evolve.
[squeaking]
All right. Evolution time.
What we need
is a really evil-looking Pokémon.
That's why we need it to be a Jolteon.
Argh!
-Who said you get to decide?
-Yeah, who said?
I'll turn it into Flareon.
What? Wait a minute.
Vaporeon is so much more villainous.
Jolteon's the best of the worst!
Flareon and its passionate flames.
Cool Vaporeon!
-[Meowth] Jolteon is the best!
-[James] Vaporeon is much stronger!
[blows whistle]
Time out, Team Rocket. I've got an idea.
-Huh?
-What is it?
We'll use all three stones on Eevee
at the same time.
It's bound to evolve
into something really evil.
-All right. Sounds bad.
-Count me in!
[squeals]
Go!
-Squirtle, water gun attack now!
-[all] Huh?
Squirtle. Squirtle.
-Squirt!
-Psy!
[gargling]
Embarrassing.
[babbling]
-Psy!
-[Misty] Embarrassing is right.
Squirtle, it looks like it's up to you.
Squirt, Squirtle, squirt! Squirt!
[all gasp]
-Now let's go rescue the Pokémon.
-Yeah!
[Jessie] Not so fast.
Huh! Eevee!
How did you ever find us
all the way out here?
Yeah, it's the first time
we didn't mess up.
Well, you see, Horsea spit out
a trail of ink to show us the way.
-Pretty smart, huh?
-Horsea.
Unbelievable! That little squirt
screwed up our perfect plan.
I guess we'll just have to settle
for little Eevee.
Forget it, you old hag!
We won't let you do that!
What? What? What did you just call me?
[growling, then screaming]
Wow, Jessie just evolved into a Flareon!
-Ready for battle?
-[both] Okay.
[James] Weezing!
Weezing.
[Jessie] Arbok!
Arbok!
Attack, Arbok.
Show that puny little punk who's boss.
I'm not puny!
-Ready, Pikachu?
-Pika.
Wait. That's our brother's Eevee.
It's our job to save it.
-Let's go, Rainer, Pyro.
-[both] Yeah!
Brothers!
Watch the power of an evolved Pokémon!
-Jolteon, attack!
-Jolt!
-Vaporeon, attack!
-Por!
-Flareon, attack!
-Flare! Flare! Flare!
-Arbok, poison sting attack!
-Cha!
Jolteon, pin missile, fire!
[growls]
Ar!
-Weezing.
-Weezing, hit it with a sludge attack!
Vaporeon,
use your acid armor and fight back!
Weez, weezing.
[brother] Vaporeon, attack!
-Weez!
-Poreon!
[both screaming]
[Jessie] Run for it!
Don't let them get away!
Flareon, fire spin!
Flare! [growls]
[all gasp]
-[all] Yeah!
-All right!
We beat you. Now, hand over the Eevee.
We're not finished.
Cha!
-Jolteon!
[both shouting]
-Vaporeon!
-Flareon!
[laughs]
So you thought you had us beat, did you?
We're the champion Team Rocket.
Champions?
[gasps]
-Ash, quick!
-Let's go, Pikachu.
Pika, pika, Pikachu!
[all gasping]
-We can't lose this battle to them.
-Especially on our first day as champions.
Let's get them!
-What?
-They still want to fight?
There's something different
about Team Rocket.
-Pika.
-[Eevee squeals]
Oh, Eevee. [laughs]
[brother] Hang in there.
-Jolteon.
-Vaporeon.
Flareon.
Uh-oh.
-It's time to finish them off.
-Victory.
[growling]
All right, Eevee! Get ready!
It's time for our first real battle!
[squeals]
-That little guy sure is brave.
-Go get them!
Pikachu!
Eevee, take down attack.
[squealing]
What's this, a stuffed animal?
Rage tackle attack!
[both] What?
[all grunting]
[screaming]
Victory?
It looks like champion Team Rocket...
[all] Is blasting off again!
[squeals]
Yeah!
-Eevee!
-Wow! You're the greatest, Eevee!
[laughs]
-You did it, Mikey.
-That was really cool.
-Beautiful.
-Pika, pika.
[brother] Mikey.
Winning your first battle by yourself,
that's incredible.
And you won without making Eevee evolve.
I was wrong.
You always said you didn't want to battle,
but you did great.
I just wanted to help everybody out.
Hey, you guys.
I've decided to become an Eevee trainer.
[all] Hmm?
-An Eevee trainer?
Well, Mikey, if that's what
you want to do, then do it.
If you felt that way about it,
you should have told us sooner.
Now we really are the four Eevee brothers.
My brothers are the best.
[squeals]
-Congratulations, Mikey.
-Thanks!
Hey, guys, let's make this party
a celebration of Eevee's first victory.
[both] Mm-hm.
[all] Congratulations.
-You did it, Mikey.
-Yeah.
-Uh, Miss Misty?
-What is it?
I wanted to thank you for helping me.
-For you.
-Oh, it's beautiful, Mikey.
I'm sure you'll become
a great Eevee trainer.
-Friends forever?
-Friends forever.
[Misty giggling]
[Mikey laughs]
[all] Mikey! Mikey! Mikey!
That's so sweet.
It must be nice to have big brothers.
You could pass for my brother.
[growls]
[shouting]
Grasshopper have little sense,
but big mouth.
Pika, pika.
Psy-ay-ay-ay!
Psyduck, Psyduck, psy!
[narrator]
Team Rocket has been defeated once again,
and all the Pokémon have been reunited
with their rightful trainers.
And Mikey and his brothers
have learned an important lesson.
All of us must have the courage
to follow our own true path.
[all chomping]
Well, it's back to eating
the lunch of losers.
Victory tasted a lot better.
I don't think this stuff
is really too bad. Ow!
Hey, is that the attitude
of a future champ?
No.
Just you wait.
Team Rocket will be champions
of the world.
[both] Mm-hm.
[all] Someday.
[crow cawing]
♪ Pokémon! ♪
Get those lips loose.
It's time to Pokérap!
Come on, sing 'em with me!
That's the game!
There's 150 Pokémon.
How many can you name?
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
Gotta catch 'em all, ow! ♪
♪ Sandslash, Hitmonlee, Psyduck, Arcanine
Eevee, Exeggutor, Kabutops, Zapdos ♪
♪ Dratini, Growlithe, Mr. Mime, Cubone
Graveler, Voltorb, Gloom ♪
We're almost home!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
Gotta catch 'em all! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Charmeleon, Wartortle
Mewtwo, Tentacruel, Aerodactyl ♪
♪ Omanyte, Slowpoke, Pidgeot, Arbok ♪
That's all, folks!
Can you name all the Pokémon?
Just put today's song
together with the other days of the week.
That's why you can't miss a show.
You gotta catch 'em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪