♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that’s inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you’re my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
-Okay, Togepi. Open wide.
-[trills]
-Now, make sure to chew every bite.
-These rice balls are pretty good.
-Cha!
Ha, ha. Of course they are.
Argh!
When you got lemons,
you make lemonade
and when you’ve got rice,
you make rice balls.
Eat up, everybody. There’s plenty more
where that came from.
[narrator]
As our heroes enjoy a delicious meal,
they are completely unaware they are being
closely watched by a mysterious stranger.
What could he possibly be plotting?
Okay, I have the Pikachu in my sights.
Now, don’t move.
[gasps]
[all groan]
-Look out, everyone!
-Argh!
-Run for cover!
-What’s go... Oh!
[both groan]
[sighs]
-What’s your problem?
-Pika-pi! Pikachu!
-Oh, it’s okay. I’m right here for you.
-[Topegi groans]
Are you crazy, Ash?
You just made Togepi cry.
Oh, well, I thought someone
there was trying to shoot us.
-Where?
-There.
There’s nobody here.
-[trills]
-Oh, it’s okay. It’s okay.
There was somebody there.
You were probably just seeing things.
If you don’t believe me, see for
yourself. Squirtle! I choose you!
Squirtle!
Fire Water Gun at 1:00, now.
-[groaning]
-[all gasp]
-Quit it. Stop spraying me.
-[gasps]
Squirtle, return.
-Is everything okay?
-Uh.
It’s okay. It’s working just fine.
I wasn’t asking about your camera.
I was worried about you.
But, you see, this camera is my life.
Get yourself a new life.
Why were you spying on us?
I wasn’t spying on you.
My name’s Todd
and I love taking pictures.
You didn’t have to sic your Squirtle on me
and flip out like that.
Come on.
You should consider it an honor that I
want to take a picture of your Pikachu.
-Pika?
-Oh, really?
If you wanted to take a picture,
why didn’t you just ask us first?
I didn’t want Pikachu to know
I was taking pictures of it.
I never like them to look posed.
You see, I am the number one
Pokémon photo master!
[both] Did he say...
-Masker?
-That’s right. I’m the...
-Oh, not masker. I said master.
-Uh-huh.
Pika.
You may not recognize my name
but I’m sure you heard of the photographer
who took the only known photo
of the legendary Pokémon Aerodactyl.
-Uh...
-Have you?
-Uh, not me.
-[Todd groans]
How is it possible
that they never heard of me?
Pika, pika.
Here!
Look at this issue of Pokémon Times.
-That’s my picture of an Aerodactyl.
-There’s his name.
Hey, yeah. I guess you are famous.
Wah! Hey! That’s me!
What are you talking about?
This is Aerodactyl, the ancient Pokémon.
Right, but see here? This is me.
-[roaring]
-Argh!
See? I told you. That’s me getting
carried away by that Aerodactyl.
I guess you’re right.
That puny little thing really is you.
Puny?
Hmm, it’s incredible how two people can be
brought together by a single photograph.
It’s funny when you think about it.
You’re in the picture
and nobody knows who you are
and I take your picture,
and I’m world famous.
Yeah, that’s real hysterical.
Uh, I’m sorry I scared you.
Let me make some breakfast for you.
You like pancakes?
-Uh, pancakes?
-That’s right.
-You bet. I love pancakes.
-I haven’t had pancakes in a long time.
-That sounds great, Todd.
-Okay.
And I’m sure you won’t mind
if I take Pikachu’s picture.
-Uh...
-Pika?
Don’t worry.
I’ll be sure to capture your best side.
Pi?
-Let’s chow down.
-Pika Pikachu!
[Brock] Mmm!
You have to give me your recipe.
-[Misty] These are delicious.
-Pika, pika.
Pika, pika?
Okay, Pikachu, uh, keep eating.
Just pretend I’m not in the room,
all right? Relax. Just act natural.
That’s fabulous.
Now smile. Smile!
-This is going to be great!
-Pika?
[Todd and Pikachu groaning]
-Pi! Pikachu!
-[Ash chuckles]
The camera’s shutter
must have scared Pikachu.
-We don’t get our picture taken too much.
-Pika.
There’s nothing to be afraid of, Pikachu.
Let’s try again.
-Okay, smile.
-[whimpering]
Pika?
I’m sorry. I can’t work like this.
What do you mean, Todd?
Pokémon should be photographed naturally,
not posing.
That’s the only way
I want my pictures of Pokémon.
Why is it such a big deal
whether the Pokémon pose or don’t pose?
Take a look at those photographs
over there.
They’re all Pokémon
living in their own natural habitats.
Those aren’t poses.
Look how peaceful they are.
Don’t those shots show Pokémon
the way they ought to be?
Wow. I’ve never seen Pokémon
pictures like that before.
-They all look so cute and carefree.
-Yeah, they’re happy.
With my pictures,
I can show the whole world
how happy and beautiful Pokémon
are in the wild.
-Yeah.
-That’s great.
You have a real talent for showing Pokémon
the way they should be seen.
That’s why I never want to shoot
a Pokémon that’s posed.
-And looks sad and scared.
-Pika.
Well, Pikachu may
not like being photographed,
but Pikachu is not my only
Pokémon, you know?
I’ve got others in these Poké Balls.
How about a shot of Pidgeotto?
Pidgeo!
-Or Bulbasaur?
-Bulbasaur!
[Misty]
I have Pokémon you can shoot too.
[Brock] Hey, how about taking
some shots of my Pokémon?
See, Todd? I have plenty of Pokémon
you can take great pictures of.
-Me too.
-Don’t forget me!
Uh, that’s very nice, but no thanks.
What’s the matter, Todd?
Is there something wrong with our Pokémon?
No, they’re fine, but I only want
to take pictures of Pikachu.
What’s so important
about taking Pikachu's picture?
-Well, you see...
-No, we don’t see. Tell us.
I can’t tell you why.
What do you mean,
"I can’t tell you why"?
That’s all I can say.
I have to take Pikachu
and that’s all there is to it!
Mm. Then go ahead.
But you won’t have much luck.
Ha, ha. You just watch.
I’ll capture you, Pikachu,
like no other photographer
could capture you.
Pi, pika.
You must help us. We really need you
to capture this Pikachu.
Oh, please.
This Pikachu is so important to us.
Pikachu?
Hmm, these pictures rot.
Please. Grant this old woman
one last wish before she passes on.
[all sobbing]
[in mind] It’s so sad. They must have
raised a Pikachu just like this one.
I’ll do it. I’ll use my camera to capture
Pikachu on film for them.
-Don’t worry! I’ll take the job!
-You mean you’ll do it?
I’ll capture the Pikachu perfectly.
[all sobbing]
Thank goodness we found you
before it was too late.
We’re very grateful.
But we’d appreciate it if you’d not tell
anyone that we’ve been here.
No problem! I would never reveal
my clients’ identities.
[in mind]
I have to grant the old woman’s wish.
I have to capture
the perfect picture of Pikachu.
[Jessie] Um, all right, Meowth,
where did you find this Todd kid?
Can he... [gulps] get Pikachu?
It says in the Pokémon Times
that this kid’s the best
at capturing Pokémon.
And he did show us that huge photo album
with all the Pokémon he said he’d taken.
He even said he wanted to take a shot
at Pikachu or something like that.
[both grunt]
-[Jessie] Let me have it!
-[James] I need protein! Uh!
[chomping]
You’re not acting like a nice old lady.
Ha, that’s because I’m not nice or old.
Ah, time to lose this guy’s disguise.
[all] Surprise! Surprise!
Yeah, right.
-Pika Pikachu!
-[crashing]
-[Ash] Hold it right there!
-Pika!
-[Todd] Hey, what?
-[chuckles]
-You got to be quicker.
-Chu!
[sighs]
[Todd]
Ready? Ah, not again.
-Wah! Missed again, Todd!
-Chu!
Argh, I’ll get that picture
if it’s the last thing I do.
Remember the last time
we made a trap like this, Meowth?
Yeah, I really dug it.
Why don’t you try more digging
and less talking?
Those twerps are on their way
and they will be here any minute... Ooh!
Uh, I think I just discovered something.
What are you stopping for?
Keep digging.
[both] Roger!
Patty-cake, patty-cake, it’s a trap.
Huh? It’s that Todd kid!
Hurry up! Disguises on!
[both] Huh?
Look at yourselves.
You got them mixed up!
[both] Huh?
I’m sorry. I haven’t taken that Pikachu
for you yet.
We’re sure you’ll get it sooner or later.
And just as a little insurance policy,
we even dug this trap--
[Jessie chuckling]
Hmm. This dirt is soft.
May be a good place to wait for Pikachu.
All right. Tripod, check.
Camera, check. Lens, check.
Okay, now I’m ready.
Right on time.
Pika. Pi, pi.
Pikachu must really hate cameras.
I’ve never seen it act
so nervous before.
Oh, it’s too bad Todd won’t get
the kind of picture he’s so great at.
I don’t see what’s so great
about that Todd.
He doesn’t even understand the feelings
of the Pokémon he takes pictures of.
[in mind]
I don’t understand the Pokémon's feelings?
-I say we just forget about Todd...
-[all] Argh!
[gasps]
-They’re gone!
-Ow! My arm!
Whose idea was it to put
a hole in the road?
[Brock]
Who else would have an idea like that?
Just Team Rocket.
-We finally caught them.
-They fell for our trap.
Usually we’re the ones to fall in.
Oh, I can’t wait.
Soon we’ll have our Pikachu.
Let’s watch and learn from the expert.
It’s capture time!
-How did you get down there?
-Easy. We fell.
-You’ve got to get us out of here.
-Uh, I think I have a rope.
Pi...
-Are you okay, Pikachu?
-Pikachu!
Huh? Ah, that’s the Pikachu
I want to capture.
-Great. Now throw us that rope, Todd.
-What is that boy doing?
He’s taking a picture of Pikachu.
[all sigh]
-Meowth!
-Huh?
The magazine says he’s, uh... Aw.
"The best at capturing Pokémon on film."
Ah, now I get it.
The article said
that he’s good at capturing them on film.
I thought he actually captures them.
An amusing mistake.
[both] You’re the mistake!
Ah! Meowth!
All right, hold it.
I did it! Okay, now, just a few more.
Huh?
-Oh, no. Grab the rope!
-Huh?
The bottom of the pit is crumbling.
You’ve got to get out
before it falls through.
Huh? [shouting]
-Ash! Oh!
-Pikachu! Huh?
[grunts]
Pikachu, don’t let go.
-Pika!
-[Todd] Ash, Pikachu!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, we’re okay.
Grab on to something quick.
There’s not much time.
Huh? Uh...
Ah! There’s nothing to grab on to!
-I’ve got to think of something fast.
-Oh, come on, Pikachu!
-[gasps]
-Agh! We’re going to fall!
I know!
-[screaming]
-Ash, grab ahold!
[groans]
Ash, Pikachu, just hang on.
You saved us.
-Pika.
- Ah!
-I’ll pull you up now.
-But your camera is ruined!
You sacrificed your camera to save us?
Don’t you worry about my camera, Ash.
-You just worry about holding on.
-Okay!
[grunts]
[Jessie]
You did a great job for us, Todd.
-Huh?
-Prepare for trouble.
[James] Make it double.
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation.
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie!
-James!
-Huh?
-Team Rocket!
Team Rocket blast off
at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth! That’s right!
-And we just netted ourselves a Pikachu!
-Pika!
-Pikachu!
-Why did you trick me?
You tricked us first, little shutterbug.
We wanted you to take Pikachu,
not take its picture.
But thanks for helping us snap up
the real Pikachu.
And just to show our gratitude,
why don’t you have one of these?
[both screaming]
[grunting]
Looks like I need a little work on my aim.
Ugh.
[groaning]
[panting]
-Todd!
-Pikachu!
Ha, ha. Squirm all you want.
You’ll never get out of this rubber bag.
-Could we wind this up now, please?
-Will do.
[groans]
Huh?
-Ha-ha.
-And the final pitch...
-[Ash] Hold it!
-Huh?
Okay, everybody,
just smile for the camera.
You’re going to love this shot.
-[giggling]
-What’s the magic word?
[all] Cheese!
-Oh, let me just take the shine off.
-[Ash] Now look to the right.
[all gasp]
Oh, look at my face.
-You ruined the shot.
-Oh!
[grunts]
Oh. Okay, Todd,
let’s give Team Rocket our best shot.
-[all gasp]
-[Ash] Bulbasaur, go!
-Bulbasaur!
-Bulbasaur, Razor Leaf, now!
Bulba!
-[all shrieking]
-Cut it out!
-Run for it, Pikachu!
-Pi! Pikachu!
Bulbasaur, give them your Vine Whip!
-Bulbasaur!
-[all groaning]
Quick! Get to the water!
[all gasp]
-[Jessie] A waterfall!
-[all yelp]
But first, a poem.
Team rocket drifted down the stream
and now we scream!
[all screaming]
-Nice work, Ash!
-Thanks.
-Bulbasaur, return!
-Bulba!
-Hey, Ash! Todd! Over here!
-Are you okay?
You guys missed all the excitement.
You should have brought a camera.
-[both] Huh?
-Pika-pi! Chu!
Huh? Whoa!
[both groan]
[all chuckle]
I don’t get it. How come you guys
are acting like friends?
We are friends, Misty,
because we have something in common.
We both like Pokémon.
-Imagine, those two friends.
-I never pictured it.
[all chuckling]
I don’t usually photograph humans,
but this time, I’ll make an exception.
I want to remember
my new friends forever.
-Get my good side.
-Okay, get ready.
[grunts]
Wah-wah-wah!
[all scream]
Whoa!
[narrator] One picture is worth 1,000
words but a new friend is priceless.
♪ Pokémon ♪
Get those lips loose.
It's time to Pokérap.
Come on, sing 'em with me.
That's the game.
There's 150 Pokémon.
How many can you name?
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Sandslash, Hitmonlee, Psyduck
Arcanine, Eevee, Exeggcutor ♪
♪ Kabutops, Zapdos, Dratini
Growlithe, Mr. Mime, Cubone ♪
-♪ Graveler, Voltorb, Gloom ♪
-We're almost home!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Charmeleon, Wartortle, Mewtwo
Tentacruel, Aerodactyl, Omanyte ♪
♪ Slowpoke, Pidgeot, Arbok ♪
That's all folks!
Can you name all the Pokémon?
Just put today's song together
With the other days of the week.
That's why you can't miss a show
You gotta catch 'em all!
♪ Catch ' em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Oh, gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ I want be the very best
That no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's just you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Our hearts so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪