♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that’s inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you’re my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
[narrator] Ash continues his journey
with Misty, Brock, Pikachu
and their Egg-Cellent new companion.
But our heroes are about to
be caught in a treacherous web.
Hey, look. A poster! "Missing."
- Is that...?
- It looks like.
It can’t be.
[all] James?
Wow! It sure looks like James.
Have you seen the boy in that photo?
We have if he’s James from Team Rocket.
Jolly good. Eureka.
Quick, to the estate.
[all] Hey!
Hmm, this kid looks a lot like you.
You think so? He looks pathetic.
- That’s what she means, James.
- Right! We'd better go investigate.
-Yeah.
-[sighs]
- James.
- What you waiting for?
-Oh, I’ll stay here.
-[both] No, you won’t.
[James groans]
[Ash] Hey, mister,
how much farther is this place?
We’re almost at the end of the driveway.
Seems like we drove past the main gate
about half an hour ago.
- Whoa!
-[Brock] Huh?
-Look at that.
-It’s huge.
Mm-hm. I’ve seen shopping malls
smaller than this place.
-[all] wow!
-[Misty] It must have 100 rooms.
It’s the biggest mansion I’ve ever seen.
-[man] That is not the mansion!
-[all groan]
This little dog house is for Growlie,
the favorite Pokémon of Master James.
[all] Huh?
[man] Behind you there, that building
is the master’s mansion.
[all] Whoa.
Please, follow me.
[all gasp]
-Oh, wow.
-Yeah.
We’re in the lap of luxury.
[both] Yay! We hit the jackpot.
[all] Oh. Huh?
Coffins? Was there a funeral here?
My master and mistress had only one child,
a boy named James.
This morning, his parents passed away
and this estate is now his.
[all gasp]
[Ash] You mean that this whole estate
is going to belong to James.
-Ah! James!
-Is this place really yours?
I suppose.
It’s so frightfully tragic.
After Master James ran away,
his parents no longer
had the strength to go on.
Their hearts were broken.
That’s so sad.
And now they’re... I hope you find
James to tell him real soon.
-Real soon won’t do.
-[all scream]
His parents’ will clearly states
that Master James must marry his fiancé
within 24 hours of their passing away.
If not, this entire estate will
no longer belong to him
but will be donated to charity.
I must find him at once.
[Ash] We should help look for James.
What? why should we help him
after all the trouble he’s caused us?
He may want to come
to his parents’ funeral.
I mean, it’s his last chance
to say good bye to them.
Gee, I didn’t think of that.
But we’ll never find him in just one day.
-[James] No. Never!
-[Jessie] Careful, James!
[all] Whoa!
[all groan]
[shouting and arguing]
Stop that.
James’s parents just passed away.
-He’s got to come to their funeral.
-Never!
Uh, uh.
Look, James, we’re becoming
very annoyed with you.
Don’t you want to become
the richest guy in the world?
I don’t know.
Oh! I feel like my head is splitting!
I can’t remember anything
that’s happened!
-What’s wrong?
-Maybe James has amnesia.
It’s all a blur to me.
I remember flunking out of Pokémon Tech
and joining a bicycle gang.
I only remember one scene before that.
It was a dark and stormy night.
A boy was wandering far from home
with his loyal Growlithe, Growlie.
They were both freezing
and they hadn’t eaten in days.
Ah. Growlie. I’m not going make it.
Leave me alone and save yourself. Oh.
The angels have come for me.
Farewell. I leave this cruel world
for a better place.
-Remember me, Grow... [grunts]
-Growlie.
[howls]
Then the boy departed this world.
Little Growlie howled all night.
-The boy was found frozen solid.
-Oh, that’s such a sad ending.
-That poor kid.
-I can’t believe James is gone.
-I miss him.
-Pika.
Hmm. James is standing right here!
Ah, that’s right. Huh? Hmm?
I’m all mixed up!
Who cares? It doesn’t matter
what you remember. Just take the cash.
But James can’t get his inheritance unless
he marries some girl in the next 24 hours.
We’ll fake a wedding
and scram with the money.
-That’s ridiculous.
-Ridiculous?
Ah. This entire estate will be all yours.
-Yeah! Yeah!
-I won’t do it!
-He’s weakening.
-He’ll see it our way.
Ugh! Let me go. I don’t want to.
You can’t make him get married.
He should be free to decide
who he does or doesn’t want to marry.
-Put a sock in it.
-Keep your dumb opinions to yourselves.
[all sigh]
-Pikachu!
-This is great.
These invisible costumes are perfect.
[man] Yes? Coming.
They won’t fool that butler.
-May I help you, sir?
-It’s me, James. I’ve come back.
-Welcome home, sir!
-all] Whoa.
Your parents shall be most pleased
to see that you have returned.
-Please come in.
-[Jessie] Thank you.
[all] Huh?
-They wouldn’t have fooled me.
-[man] Everything is fine now, masters.
Your little boy James has finally
returned home just as you wished.
Oh, Mommy, Daddy. It’s true. I’m back
home at long last to get my money.
-Huh?
-Uh, I mean....
You’re blowing it.
I’m going to get married,
just like it says in your will.
-And I want cash, not a check.
-What’s that?
-I mean, I’m only joking. Of course.
-[all gasp]
Oh, Mom and Dad.
I wish I’d come back sooner.
-[ghosts chuckle]
-Huh?
-Hey, who’s that?
-Prepare for trouble.
-Yes, dear, and make it double.
-But they’re...
They’re ghosts!
[all groan]
Oh, James dear, we’re so happy
you’ve come back home.
And you’re wearing a suit.
-They’re either alive...
-Or they’re real solid ghosts.
They aren’t ghosts, you furry imbecile.
It’s just like them to pull a stunt
like this to get me to come back home.
-Does that mean...
-You really don’t have amnesia?
Huh? Who am I? Where am I?
Why, you’re James
and you’re about to be married.
-Hopkins, begin the preparations.
-Yes.
-I’ve got to escape.
-Oh, no, James.
You’re tying the knot.
[Meowth]
Ha, Jessie means you’re tying the noose.
[both chuckle]
So this whole thing was a trap
so James would get married.
-[all groan]
-I’m proud of you.
You realized you must uphold
the family tradition.
As our son and heir,
you have certain obligations.
The most important of these is to marry
and to continue the family line.
-Right.
-Do I have a duty to be manipulated?
[Dad]
I don’t know what you’re talking about.
[Mom] We only want what’s best for us.
I mean, best for you.
A man who can’t settle down is like
a bumblebee without a nose.
He’ll never sniff the daffodils of life.
You’ll learn to be a real gentleman
once you marry the right girl.
-And here she is.
-[both] Huh?
As James’s wife, it will be your duty
to change him from a worthless do
nothing into a respectable gentleman,
-my dear Jessebelle.
-As you wish, mother.
Meowth! Her voice is catnip to my ears.
Now, that’s what I call a real lady,
not a tough, mean, nasty girl
like Jessie. Ow!
I’ll show you tough, mean and nasty.
My name’s Jessebelle.
My only wish is to be your devoted
and loving wife
and companion and also
to educate you in your duties
as a gentleman of property.
[all] Whoa!
-She looks like Jessie!
-[groans]
Amazing. That girl looks just like Jessie.
-How dare you compare me to that wimp?
-Are you kidding?
-You both have exactly the same face.
-We do not.
Will you stop arguing?
We’ve got to get out of here right now.
Don’t be ridiculous.
How can we get your inheritance
if you don’t get married?
You’ve got to go through with it.
If you won’t get married for yourself,
then do it for the team.
We’re counting on you
to make us all filthy stinking rich.
Forget the team! I’m not doing it!
-I’m not.
-Is something wrong?
Why ever do you keep talking
to yourself like that, James?
Talking to yourself?
Meowth and Jessie are right in front
of their eyes and nobody notices.
Say, here’s an idea.
Let’s go down to the vault
and count all the money you’ll inherit.
[Jessie and Meowth chuckle]
After you disappeared, your mother
and father were so worried about you,
as I was, of course.
But I knew one day
you’d come back to me.
I’m sorry for running away,
but everything is going to be just fine
now that I’m back here
with my money.
-What?
-I mean back here with you. [chuckles]
Here we are at the vault.
Let’s go inside.
Your inheritance is in here.
-Ah.
Cha-ching!
-Huh?
-Bah uh? What’s all this junk?
What kind of inheritance is this?
It’s looks like
a lot of weird gym equipment.
Don’t you fools get it?
Jessebelle tricked you two
into coming down here.
-Huh?
-How did she spot us?
Imbeciles!
Your mother and I are tired
of waiting for you to grow up.
[all] Huh? [gasping]
James, it’s time to face the music.
You can’t just do whatever
you feel like anymore.
Now you’ll obey Jessebelle.
-Let the taming begin.
-[all] Oh.
I’m starting to like you more
than her, Jess.
Thanks for the compliment.
Hey, get off my head.
[both gasp]
They see us.
Everything was fine until you opened
that big Meowth of yours.
Do you take us for fools?
We just ignored you until you brought
James down here to the dungeon.
-Now you see us...
-And now you don’t.
[all cough]
Jessie, Meowth. Don’t leave me.
Ooh! Ooh!
-At last we’re together. I’m so happy.
-Eee! Ah!
-You won’t escape from me again, James.
-[groans]
[grunting and groaning]
Those two were made for one another,
just like you and I, my precious.
It’s a perfect match.
If you two weren’t such lousy parents,
you’d stop this mad woman.
Shouldn’t we try to help him?
I don’t like to get involved
in these little family squabbles.
Oh, James,
I just knew you’d fall for me.
-I choose you, Vileplume!
-Vileplume.
Hey, what’s that?
[Pokédex]
Vileplume, the flower Pokémon.
Using the largest flower petals
in the world,
it spreads large clouds of pollen
that cause allergic reactions.
Now Vileplume! Use your Stun Spore to slow
James down and keep him from escaping.
Vileplume.
Ah! This is just like this is just
like last time. Oh.
[all] Oh!
Heh. Sleeping like a baby.
James, my sweet, I’ll make a gentleman
out of you yet, even if it destroys us.
-Oh, Hopkins?
-Yes?
Would you please get a large broom
and sweep up this mess?
-Yes.
-[all] Whoa.
Ugh. Well, like they say,
even a rose has its thorns.
She’s more like a cactus.
If he marries her,
James gets his inheritance.
[grunting and groaning]
-If he survives being married to her.
-[growling]
[all gasp]
[growling]
Hey, what’s that?
-Pika, pi! Pikakaka pikaka pi!
-Huh? What’s it want?
It wants somebody to open
the door of that dog house.
Okay. Ugh. Oh, it’s locked.
-Come on. Give me a hand here.
-Sure, Ash!
[all grunting]
-Pika?
-What’s that?
[groaning]
James, it’s time for the wedding.
-Growlie!
-Oh, no!
Now, who let you in here?
-Vileplume, get rid of this horrid thing.
-Vileplume.
Run, Growlie!
-[grunts]
-Where are you going? Don’t leave.
-Ruff! Ruff!
Growlie says to go inside.
I’ll follow you to the ends of the earth
and the bottom of the sea, James dearest.
Ugh. You saved me, Growlie.
Thank you.
-[pants] Growl! Growl!
-[laughs]
Oh! That tickles, Growlie.
Well, James, that fiancée
of yours is truly despicable.
Told you she’s just like Jessie.
I’ll make your mouth even bigger.
[sighs]
She’s the reason
I ran away from this estate.
What a rotten day.
As soon as my engagement to Jessebelle
was announced,
she began to follow me everywhere,
trying to change me.
Nothing I did was refined enough for her.
Please, leave me alone.
I can’t stand it.
Growlie?
Where are you going, James?
I haven’t finished teaching you
the correct way to eat spaghetti yet.
-I want to do things my way, Jessebelle!
-You’re not running properly.
Let me show you the right way.
Ever since I was a kid,
I hated how upper class society
had rules for absolutely everything.
Jessebelle is so rigid, marrying her would
be the worst mistake of my life.
Growlie is my only real friend
on this stuffy estate.
Mm hmm.
I always wondered what it would
be like to grow up in a place like this.
Who would’ve thought being rich
could be such a bummer?
-What’s that?
-[all groan]
Now what?
My sweet James,
you can’t escape me.
Leave me alone.
Vileplume!
Stun them to sleep just like before.
-Vileplume.
-[all] Oh!
-Now, Pikachu! Electric Shock!
-Pikachu!
[grunting and groaning]
Keep away from me, you horrid beast!
-You’re the best. Thank you.
-Rowr! [barks]
It’s lunchtime in the pond.
Are you hungry, my friends?
-Oh, look! Jessebelle.
-Jessebelle.
Oh, what a refined daughter
in law she’ll be.
-[all] Ah!
-I’m leaving!
-I can’t stand that Growlie!
-She’s as delicate as a flower.
She’s much too good
for our delinquent son.
Well, Growlie, please take
good care of my parents.
They need you here. This upper
crush high life doesn’t suit me.
I’m better living the low life
with Team Rocket.
-Plus I like my freedom.
-Growl.
Please don’t cry, Growlie.
It’s hard enough to leave you.
-So long, Growlie.
-Rowl.
Oh, well, guess James chose to hang up
his Team Rocket costume.
Eh, I guess all that money and luxury was
just too tempting for James to give up.
I guess you’re right.
-[James] Prepared for trouble?
-Hey, it’s him!
James?
Make it double.
[chuckles]
[both grunt]
I guess we’re not going
to get rich this time either.
Guess not.
They wouldn’t give me the inheritance.
Oh, there’s always next time.
We may not make a lot of money,
but we sure have got our freedom!
Yeah. Double trouble time, right?
Sounds great to me, James.
Hey, wait!
You forgot Meowth again!
[all groaning]
Oh, please, won’t y’all help me
find my beloved James?
Believe me, miss,
-he’s the one who finds us.
-Pikachu!
[narrator] And so, Ash dashes away
from the magnificent estate,
eager to get on
with his Pokémon journey.
But has our hero learned anything
valuable during his visit?
Well, maybe.
[Jessebelle] You’re not running properly!
♪ Pokémon! ♪
It’s that time again!
A hundred and fifty Pokémon,
five days a week.
That’s about 30 or so each day.
It’s not too hard.
Just listen real good!
♪ Alakazam, Doduo, Venonat
Machoke Kangaskhan, Hypno ♪
♪ Electabuzz, Flareon, Blastoise
Poliwhirl, Oddish, Drowzee ♪
♪ Raichu, Nidoqueen, Bellsprout, Starmie ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪Gotta catch 'em all
♪ Metapod, Marowak, Kakuna
Clefairy, Dodrio, Seadra ♪
♪ Vileplume, Krabby, Lickitung
Tauros, Weedle, Nidoran ♪
♪ Machop, Shellder
Porygon, Hitmonchan ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
Okay, so today was pretty easy.
But you gotta put all five days together.
That’s the only way to name all 150.
Catch you here tomorrow!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all!
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪