♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
[Narrator] Last time, Magikarp evolved
into Gyarados
and our heroes were swallowed up
in the deadly power of its dragon rage.
[all screaming]
Hey, Brock! Misty! Pikachu!
Whatever happens, don't let go!
[grunting]
Pika!
[screaming]
[Narrator] Talk about twists of fate.
Round and round they go.
Where they'll stop, even I don't know.
[heavy breathing and groaning]
Huh? How did I get on a beach?
[grunts]
Oh, Misty! Misty, get up!
-Hey, Brock!
-[Brock groans]
-How did we get here?
-How did we survive that cyclone?
Hey, we were lucky.
But where did Pikachu go?
[screams]
I only have two of my Pokémon.
[chittering]
[both yell]
-Could it be...?
-Does this mean...?
[both] We survived again!
We're the completely invincible...
-Unbeatable...
-[both] Team Rocket!
[both] Huh?
-But I don't hear any annoying...
-Complaining.
[both] Meowth is missing.
Oh! I've lost the Poké Ball with the Ekans
I got for my birthday last year!
Oh! The Poké Ball with the Koffing
I got for Christmas is gone, too.
And we're totally broke.
We're penniless and Poké-less. [sighs]
How will we survive?
Time is running out for the both of us.
-[James] We could always call for help.
-Huh?
-[James] Look over there.
-A phone booth.
Aren't we lucky? [chuckles]
Now we can call someone for help.
-But we don't have any change.
-And without any change...
[both] Our luck sure has changed.
Char.
Squirtle.
Pika.
-Pika pi?
-Char.
-Pi.
[chuckles] Squirt, squirt, squirt.
So, Pikachu and his friends survived?
Ha! That means
I can finally get my revenge.
All right, Pokémon, surrender.
-Squirt?
-Char?
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight!
[all groan then Meowth sighs]
I guess the Team Rocket motto
is starting to lose its impact.
Never mind!
Okay, guys, go get them!
Huh?
Hey!
I said go get them.
What?
Mm-hmm.
Right.
Masters?
I'm twice as smart as those
two-watt light bulbs
you're calling masters.
Come on, we're all bad guys here.
We don't need masters
to tell us to go out and do bad stuff.
There's no such thing as a bad Pokémon?
It can't be!
My master's not around,
and I always seem to act like a rat.
This ain't fair.
You got me outnumbered.
Hey, I could use a little help over here!
[slurping]
[groans]
It's no use.
Oh, well,
I guess I'll let you guys off easy
and call it a draw.
[all chomping]
-[Meowth] Hey, guys!
-Char?
Ain't you ever going to stop
stuffing your faces
and give Meowth something to eat?
I don't apologize!
Stop making fun of me!
Untie me and give me something
to eat! Huh?
Squirtle?
[ground rumbles and all whimper]
[roars]
[all screaming]
-Squirtle!
-Pika!
That's one big Pokémon.
Wait! Somebody come and untie me!
Huh?
[grunts] I could've gotten out myself.
[growling]
[all panting]
[squawking]
[screaming]
[all groaning]
[squawking]
[all sigh]
I've never seen a flying Pokémon
like that before.
Ah, me neither.
It's one of the most incredible Pokémon
I've ever seen.
Ash, this place is really dangerous.
We really ought to try to find a safe spot
to crash for the night.
[sighs] Right.
[thinks]
Be careful, Pikachu. All of you.
Just stick together.
[both screaming]
[screaming continues]
-What is that thing?
-I don't want to stop to find out!
-[both grunt]
-[screeches]
Good thing we hid behind this sign.
Yeah, maybe our luck is changing.
-[both groan]
-[both] It's a good sign.
-Koffing. Koffing.
-[Pokémon sob and groan]
-Pika, pika, pika. Pika, pika.
-Koffing...
Pika, pika. Pika pi.
-Bulba. Bulba. Bulbasaur.
-Squirtle, Squirtle, Squirtle.
-Ekans.
-Pika, pika.
-Bulbasaur.
-Koffing. Koffing.
Koffing.
Char. Charmander.
Pika, pika. Pika, pika, pika.
Squirtle, Squirtle.
Squirtle, Squirtle, Squirtle.
-[Pokémon sob]
-Char.
[sobs] Koffing.
-Pi.
-[all snore]
Let's go.
We got to find Pikachu and the others.
-[both groan]
-Sun's up.
-It's morning.
-[both] That means...
we'd better run for cover.
Uh, pardon me,
but where are we running?
-To make a phone call.
-Huh?
But, Jessie, we don't have any money.
There's one number
we can always call for free.
Huh?
Hello, operator, I'd like to put this call
through collect, please.
Who'd accept the charges?
-Hello, boss?
-[gasps] The boss?
[man] You fools had better have
a very good reason
for calling me this early in the morning.
Yes, but first,
we must do the introduction.
-What?
-Prepare for trouble.
Yes, and make it double.
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation.
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James.
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light!
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Nitwits! How dare you
annoy me with your nonsense.
Don't ever bother me like this again.
[line clicks]
Well, I suppose we'll have
to get off this island ourselves.
-The phone didn't help.
-But it will.
But where will this telephone cable
lead us?
It must lead to the phone company.
The people there
-can help us get off the island.
-Good point.
And if we stay inside this booth
the whole way, we'll be safe.
-Pikachu!
-Squirtle!
Charmander! Bulbasaur!
Oh, where could they all have gone?
[both panting]
Jessie,
hauling this phone booth is exhausting.
Well, you could use a good workout.
-[both] Huh?
-[James] Is that a mirage?
Pikachu doesn't even see us.
So we'll have no trouble catching it.
[both] Come to us, Pikachu. [both gasp]
It is a mirage.
A really big mirage.
[both] It's Big-achu!
[both scream]
[all gasp]
[all] Let's get out of here!
[roaring]
[all screaming]
It looks like a Charizard.
An evolved Charmander?
But much bigger.
This is Squirtle's evolved form,
a Blastoise.
[growling]
[all grunts]
Squirtle.
[all screaming]
That's a Venusaur,
evolved from a Bulbasaur.
[Squirtle grunts]
[both screaming]
-This is a nightmare.
-Well, I hope we wake up soon.
[JESSIE] There's a railcar.
Let's hop in and make a run for it.
-Hurry! Let's go!
-[both grunts]
[wheel grates]
-Huh?
-Don't tell me we're...
[both] Going back the way we came!
[both scream]
Jessie, we've got to do something.
-Let's hit the brake and run for it.
-Right.
-One.
-Two.
[both] Three! Pull!
Huh?
[both] Runaway train!
[all panting]
-[all gasp]
-Pikachu!
[screaming]
Pikachu?
-Jumbo-sized.
-[rumbling]
[grunts]
I wonder what that is.
[all screaming]
[gasping and screaming]
[screaming]
Now we've got you
just where we want you.
Hand over Pikachu. Huh?
-[both scream]
-[James] But not that big one.
- Ash, look. Back there.
- [gasps]
[all screaming]
-Pikachu!
-[Pokémon yelling]
Pika pi!
Squirtle! Charmander! Bulbasaur!
They'll all be trampled
if you don't do something.
Stop the car right now!
-[James whimpers]
-We can't do that.
We can't stop. The brake's broken.
Give me a break.
[all scream]
-We've just got to help them.
-Huh?
-Ash, up ahead.
What is it?
-Prepare for big trouble.
-Make it double.
And I can't stand roller coasters!
-What do we do?
-Hold on tight! [grunts]
[screams]
Stop the ride! Stop the ride!
I want to get off!
-Whoa!
-[all scream]
We're going to crash!
[all grunting]
-Come on, jump in!
-Pika!
[all yelling]
[laughter]
[groaning and hissing]
-Pika!
-[laughs]
-Are you okay?
-Pikachu.
Wow, we made it.
Is everybody here?
-Aren't we missing someone?
-The furriest member of our team.
-You mean Meowth?
-[both grunts]
-You're safe.
-How did you make it?
[laughs] I catapulted.
[screeches]
[all screaming]
[Misty] They're after us!
[Ash] Maybe our luck will hold out!
Well, based on our recent run of luck,
I would say the cable should snap.
That should happen about now.
-[Misty moans]
-Next, we'll be hurled into the air.
[all yelling]
Then we'll probably crash into something.
[all screaming]
That's weird.
Looks like that was a mechanical Pokémon.
-And then, finally...
-We hit the water.
After a very, very long drop!
[tour guide] Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Pokémon land.
Here, you'll see various Pokémon
at over ten times their natural size.
Of course, the Pokémon are all mechanical,
So don't worry, it's very safe.
Now, if you'll look to your left...
[gasps]
[cheesy music]
We apologize, ladies and gentlemen,
but our giant Pokémon
are temporarily out of order.
[telephone rings]
[boss] Yes. What?
Pokémon land has been totally
destroyed? [growls]
I spent millions on that place.
[narrator] Finally, our tired heroes
resume their long journey.
[all] Huh? Ah!
[narrator] And arrive
at the beautiful town of Porta Vista.
-All right!
-[all] The beach!
-[Ash] I can't wait!
-[Misty giggles]
[narrator]
Ah, yes, blue skies and white sands.
Time to hit the surf
and soak up some rays.
Don't forget to use
lots of sunscreen, Ash.
[sighs]
Slowpoke. [sighs]
Slowpoke slow.
[sighs]
Ah, Slowbro.
You guys up for the Pokérap?
There’s 150 Pokémon.
You got to name 'em all!
I’m doing 32 today,
so try to keep up.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Zubat, Primeape
Meowth, Onix ♪
♪ Geodude, Rapidash
Magneton, Snorlax ♪
♪ Gengar, Tangela
Goldeen, Spearow ♪
♪ Weezing, Seel
Gyarados, Slowbro! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
Gotta catch 'em all! ♪
♪ Kabuto, Persian
Paras, Horsea ♪
♪ Raticate, Magnemite
Kadabra, Weepinbell ♪
♪ Ditto, Cloyster
Caterpie, Sandshrew ♪
♪ Bulbasaur, Charmander
Golem, Pikachu ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
All right, how’d you do?
Loosen those lips.
Shake out that tongue!
Give it a rest!
Today’s song is sung.
We’ll be back tomorrow!
♪ Catch 'em catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪