♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that’s inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you’re my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
[Pikachu] Pikachu!
-Uh...
-[Misty] Ash? Ash?
-Ash. Come on, wake up, Ash.
-[grunts]
-What is it, Misty?
-Something’s wrong with Pikachu.
-Huh?
-Ash.
-Pikachu.
-[Pikachu squawks]
[Brock] There’s something wrong
with Pikachu’s voice.
What’s the matter, Pikachu?
Are you in pain?
[Pikachu squeaks]
Maybe there’s something stuck
in Pikachu’s throat.
Ah! Hold on.
I'll get it out for you, Pikachu.
[groans]
Cut it out, Ash.
You’re making it worse.
-We should get Pikachu to a doctor.
-You’re right.
We've got to get Pikachu to the nearest
Pokémon Center right away.
[Ash sighs]
[narrator] What our heroes don’t know is
there’s no Pokémon Center
around for miles.
So they’ll have to try
the next best thing.
[Ash grunts]
[Ash] Hello? Ah.
Open the door. We have an emergency.
[groans]
Just getting to sleep.
This is an emergency.
Please help us.
Hmm? Ah.
Please help us, doctor.
Well, how could I turn down
such a pretty face?
All right, what seems to be
your problem, little lady?
-Oh, I’m not the one who’s sick.
-Huh?
Here’s your patient, doctor.
[whimpers]
This is a hospital for people.
Why don’t you take your Pokémon
to Joy at the Pokémon Center?
It's too far to the Pokémon Center.
We might not make it.
Please, you have to look at Pikachu.
I'm sorry, but I’m a specialist
in human medicine.
Please just take a look.
[sighs]
I’ve just never been able to refuse
requests from young girls.
Okay. It's not my specialty,
but Dr. Proctor will do his best to help.
[heartbeat thumping]
There’s something stuck
in its throat.
-Oh, no.
-Hang in there, Pikachu.
Please, Pikachu is one of my best friends.
Please do whatever you can to save it.
Right. I'll do my best.
The electric pressure
in its body is rather low.
We'll have to give it an electric charge.
Wheel that defibrillator over here.
[both gasp]
[Brock] This thing?
Good.
A Pikachu would need about 10 000 volts.
All right, clear.
[squawks]
Pikachu, are you okay?
Good, it's regained consciousness.
-All right, Pikachu, say, ah.
-Ah.
I see it.
You’ll have to hold Pikachu still.
-Right.
-Okay.
This may hurt a bit but just relax.
[Pikachu squawks]
[all yelling]
[all groan]
Hooray.
-Pika.
-Pikachu!
-Pika?
-Pikachu, you’re all right.
-Pikachu.
-If you had waited any longer,
serious respiratory complications
would have arisen.
You were just in time.
But I have to say it was very
irresponsible of you as a trainer
to let your Pikachu eat this thing whole.
-I didn’t let Pikachu do it.
-[Proctor] Huh.
In any case, the treatment's over,
so go on home.
Well, he may have had
a soft spot for Misty,
but he sure seemed
pretty hard on you, Ash.
Well, he's not the only one who has
a soft spot for pretty girls, is he?
Uh, well, I, uh...
I knew I should have been a lawyer.
[computer] Ring, ring, ring.
Phone call, phone call.
-Uh.
-Um, your phone is ringing.
I'm not going to answer it. I'm off duty.
Off duty?
Oh, but what if it's an emergency,
like with Pikachu?
[computer] Ring, ring, ring.
Phone call, phone call.
Hello. Hello.
-Ah, hello, Nurse Joy.
-Who's that?
This is supposed to be
an emergency hospital.
-Ah.
-It is.
Give me a break. I'm off duty.
Doctor, this is a critical situation.
A truck that was carrying Pokémon
was involved in a traffic accident.
Many Pokémon were injured
and my Pokémon Center
can't handle all the victims.
The Pokémon Center's full. We better
get these Pokémon to the hospital.
This was all your fault.
Why weren’t you watching the road?
-I thought Meowth was.
-[Meowth sobs]
I lost the gold charm on my forehead.
[all groaning]
[Meowth sobs]
[Chansey] Chansey. Chansey. Chansey.
This is terrible.
It's awful.
We need your hospital to help care
for some of these patients temporarily.
-You have to help them.
-Okay.
Bring them down this way.
By the way, Nurse Joy,
would you be interested in going out
for pizza Saturday night?
You can talk to me about pizza
after our work is done.
Well, can't blame a guy for trying.
I don’t like this guy.
He sounds like me.
-That is disturbing.
-Pika.
All right, kids,
you better get into these.
[all] Huh?
We don’t have enough
doctors and nurses,
so it looks like you’ll
have to be my assistants.
We're going to help treat Pokémon?
[chuckles] You’ll do fine as long
as you do exactly as I tell you.
-I'm ready if you are, Brock.
-I'm ready.
-Let's help those hurt Pokémon.
-Pika, pika.
[siren wailing]
They never told us
about this in med school.
-Cubone, Cubone!
-Chansey.
What’s the condition of the patient?
[both] Chansey!
Hmm. Okay.
Take it to external injuries room one
and prepare for a Cubone scan.
-Cubone.
-Chansey.
Move Cubone to the treatment table stat.
Ready? We'll do it on three.
-One, two, three.
-Cubone!
-Ah.
You’ve got to keep the patient
under control.
Okay, Bulbasaur, hold Cubone
down with Vine Whip now.
-[Cubone] Cubone! Cubone!
- Bulbasaur!
-Under control.
-Cubone! Cubone!
You can't be so violent with patients.
This ones just a youngster.
Please, be a little gentler.
Sorry.
-Chansey.
-Cubone. Cubone.
-Thanks, Chansey.
Its head is okay,
thanks to that thick skull.
Repair the fractures with superglue
and apply a bandage.
-I can do that for you, Doctor.
-Okay, Misty.
Take it easy.
You’re going to be okay.
Watch out. They can be pretty nasty.
Heh. You were scared, weren’t you?
Everything’s going to be fine now.
-[chuckles]
-Cubone.
You’re a brave little one,
aren’t you, Cubone?
Chansey!
Misty, you’ve got a knack for this.
Thank you, doctor.
-Cubone.
-Humph, knack.
-Arbok!
-Raticate!
Can someone please remove this raticate?
It insists on trying to take
a bite out of our Arbok.
Arbok, beat it. Amscray.
This Raticate's teeth are broken.
It couldn’t bite anything if it tried.
Just glue its teeth back
in with superglue.
-Chansey.
-Thanks.
-Who are you?
-I'm Dr. Proctor.
How about a pizza with me
after I finish treating these Pokémon?
I'll bet you’re quite a doctor.
Well, yes, I am.
We'll talk more over the pepperoni,
but right now,
you’ve just got to help my Arbok.
Okay, let's see.
Its own poison
is circulating through its body.
I'll have to remove it in a hurry.
-[grunts] You!
-Ah. It's the twerp.
The twerp's an MD?
What dumb plan are you two
working on this time?
Later.
Doctor, I'll be so grateful
if you help my Arbok.
Don’t trust them, doctor.
Those two are from Team Rocket.
-So what? Arbok is injured.
-We're bad, not insensitive.
Chansey, bring me
a hypodermic of anesthetic.
-Chansey.
-Doctor!
[yells]
I wanted you to cure it, not kill it.
It's just sleeping.
-Now I can perform the procedure.
-Huh?
Why help them?
They’re from Team Rocket.
To a doctor, a patient is a patient.
There’s no such thing
as good guys or bad guys.
-Uh...
-A doctor's job is to heal, not to judge.
Sorry.
Chansey. Chansey.
Looks like more are on the way.
I’ve still got to work on Arbok,
but maybe I could convince this beautiful
young woman to lend us a hand.
Huh?
I presume you are referring to me?
-Why, yes.
-I'll do my best.
And me, too.
What happened to my charm?
Somebody help me find my charm.
I'll pay any price.
[Chansey] Chansey?
Oh, thanks. I said price, not rice.
-Chansey.
-I don’t want to play.
-Find my charm, please!
-Chansey!
Did someone call the police?
My charm. My charm. My charm.
Venonat.
-Will you get off of me?
-Chansey!
-[Meowth] Ah!
-Chansey! Chansey! Chansey!
-[Meowth groans]
Squirtle!
Bulbasaur.
[monitors bleeping]
[Brock] Keep it from moving around.
I'm trying.
All right, this one looks okay.
Uh, try not to move around too much
until the glue hardens, okay?
[grunting]
Hey, there, take it easy.
[laughs]
It's just trying to say thank you, James.
We have to do this carefully.
I don’t need you to tell me
how to do things, thank you.
Easy. Easy does it.
-Voltorb, Voltorb.
-[both yelling]
I told you.
Watch what you’re doing
over there, ladies.
Voltorb can self-destruct, you know.
This thing can self-destruct?
-Uh, I forgot, I have to find Meowth.
-But, Jessie.
-Chansey, take over.
-Chansey!
-Voltorb, Voltorb.
-Chansey.
-Don’t you self-destruct, Voltorb.
-Chansey. Chansey.
Chansey. Chansey.
Hang in there, Weepinbell.
-[grunts]
-Nice work.
Chansey.
How you feeling, Weepinbell?
Weepinbell.
[squawking]
Hey, settle down.
We can’t get near it.
-That’s a knotty problem.
-Chansey.
Dr. Proctor, what do we do?
Dodrio, a triple bird Pokémon.
Its three heads represent
joy, sorrow and anger.
[Ash] Uh, all three heads
look pretty angry to me.
If we don’t get it untangled,
it could suffocate.
Chansey, prepare the anesthetic.
Chansey.
Okay. Now, don’t move.
[squawks]
[Proctor yells]
[Brock and Ash gasp]
Chansey.
Oh, boy, that's not good.
-Ah.
-Are you okay, doc?
-Does this look okay?
-Huh?
I'd say this’ll put me out
for at least six hours.
Doctor, you can't go to sleep.
You guys take over. Good night.
-Doc!
-Doctor!
Pika.
Uh, wake up, doc. Come on, wake up.
Uh, he's out.
Chansey.
-So, what now?
-Beats me.
[squawking]
-Pika, pika.
-Chansey!
Hmm. All right, then.
Let's give it a try.
We'll just do our best
to help these Pokémon.
I’m going to be the world's
best Pokémon master someday.
I can't let this scare me.
-Go, Squirtle.
-Squirtle!
-Weaken Dodrio with Water Gun.
Dodrio should be weak
against electric attacks.
-Pikachu, Thunder Bolt now.
-Pikachu!
Yeah! I knew that would do it.
-Now I'll just capture it and--
-Ash!
Oh, yeah.
I'm not supposed to capture it.
Just take it easy.
We'll have you better in no time.
[Proctor snoring]
Bulbasaur.
[Misty] You'll be fine.
-[Ash] It's okay.
-Huh?
Weezing.
Mm.
Where’s my charm? I want my charm.
Parasect. Parasect.
Well, James, so much for charity work.
Now it's time for Team Rocket
to take over.
Exactly.
Now that they’re weak, we should be
able to capture those Pokémon
with no trouble at all.
Ah!
To protect the world from devastation.
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James. Come on.
Team Rocket
blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
-I want my charm! [sobs]
-[Jessie and James jibber]
[all groaning]
Quit it. We need help around here.
We're through with the goody-goody act.
From now on,
we're bad old Team Rocket.
All of the Pokémon
in this hospital are ours.
-You can't have them.
-The doctor treated your Pokémon too.
Is that how you act
when somebody does you a favor?
-Exactly how.
-And that’s because...
[both] We're Team Rotten.
They got that right.
Our first attack
will be the stretcher catcher.
[both grunt]
The stretcher catcher?
[Ash grunts and groans]
[mumbles]
-I can't move.
-We're all trapped.
-Pikachu.
-Excellent.
We concocted these while you were busy
tending to all those poor little Pokémon.
Comfortable?
Let us go!
There are still lots of Pokémon
waiting for us to treat them.
Don’t worry.
We'll treat them just as soon as
we capture every single one of them.
Right. We're finally going to win.
So get ready.
It's payback time for Team Rocket.
Oh, no, wait. Don’t do it!
Chansey!
-What’s with this one?
-Get out of the way.
Chansey!
So, you won’t move?
Arbok, deal with this.
Arbok!
Eliminate this Chansey immediately.
-Chansey!
-Arbok.
Chansey!
What are you waiting for?
Attack it, Arbok.
-Arbok.
-You won’t do it?
-All right, Weezing, Gas attack!
-Weezing.
Don’t just float there.
I said Gas attack.
Weezing.
-What’s going on around here?
-My charm.
[Proctor laughs and all gasp]
You shouldn’t be surprised.
-Good morning, everyone.
-[all] Huh?
You see, Team Rockets
Pokémon haven’t forgotten
that Chansey cared for them when
they were injured and needed treatment.
This isn’t any of your business.
[grunting]
-[Brock] Nice slice.
-He's fast.
You see, miss Team Rocket
before you start playing rough,
you better take a look at my ammunition.
-Ooh, quite an arsenal.
-We shouldn’t mess with him.
-No way.
-Now, who wants to be my next patient?
-Yeah!
-Chansey!
Chansey!
We're free again.
-Thanks a lot, Chansey.
-[Chansey] Chansey.
Oh, and thanks for the break,
Team Rocket.
You can have these back.
[all yelling and gasping]
-Ha-ha.
-See you again soon.
[all panting]
We came away empty-handed again,
James.
Well, I did manage to get this one.
-Ah. But that’s a--
-It's a Voltorb!
Voltorb! Voltorb! Voltorb!
[all yell]
[all]
Team Rocket's blasting off again.
[all screaming]
I got my charm back.
[James and Jessie] That’s charming.
All of you could become
outstanding doctors.
Why don’t you stay here and train
in my hospital with me?
Now, thanks anyway.
I have to follow my dream
of becoming a Pokémon Master.
Yeah and my dream of becoming
a Pokémon breeder.
I really think I might like
being a doctor someday,
but first I have a lot more to learn
about Water Pokémon.
Hm, I’m sure you’ll become
whatever you want.
-See you.
-Goodbye.
-And thanks again.
-Pikachu.
-Good luck to you.
-Chansey!
[narrator] Ash and his friends know
that helping others is its own reward.
The Pokémon
are on the road to recovery
and our heroes are back
on the road to adventure.
You guys up for the Pokérap?
There’s 150 Pokémon.
You gotta name 'em all!
I’m doing 32 today,
so try to keep up.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Zubat, Primeape, Meowth, Onix ♪
♪ Geodude, Rapidash, Magneton, Snorlax ♪
♪ Gengar, Tangela, Goldeen, Spearow ♪
♪ Weezing, Seel, Gyarados, Slowbro ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Kabuto, Persian, Paras, Horsea ♪
♪ Raticate, Magnemite
Kadabra, Weepinbell ♪
♪ Ditto, Cloyster, Caterpie, Sandshrew ♪
♪ Bulbasaur, Charmander
Golem, Pikachu ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
All right, how’d you do?
Loosen those lips.
Shake out that tongue!
Give it a rest. Today’s song is sung.
We’ll be back tomorrow!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all, ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪