♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
[narrator] With two Pokémon badges
pinned to his jacket,
our hero, Ash, marches boldly
along the path to, uh...
-the path to...
-Where are we going?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Vermillion City.
It's got a luxury cruise ship
and I'm dying to see it.
We won't have time for sightseeing.
I've heard that there's
a really great Gym in Vermillion.
A Gym? All right!
I'm going to win my third badge.
-Let's go!
-Don't get your hopes up.
There are a lot of tough trainers
around here.
Ah, bring them on!
I bet none of them has even
one Pokémon badge.
[Pidgeotto cawing]
Pidgeotto, finish it!
[Pidgeotto screeches]
Oh, Rattata!
And I win!
That's number ten!
[boy] You're a really
great Pokémon trainer.
Well, I guess I was pretty good there.
Wow! You've got badges.
-Oh, you mean these?
-[boy] You got two?
I think getting him those badges
was a mistake.
Uh-huh.
-Pika, pika.
-I bet you could even beat A.J.
-A.J.?
-Yeah, he lives over there.
A.J. trains savage Pokémon.
He built his own Gym.
He's never lost a single match.
Until now.
He hasn't come against somebody like me.
He's getting a big head.
Yeah, but his brain's still the same size.
Pika, pika.
Look at that! This Gym isn't even licensed
by the Pokémon League.
Undefeated? Big deal!
I can beat him.
98 wins in a row.
You may have won ten battles,
but he's won almost ten times
more matches than you have.
I go for quality, not quantity!
[A.J.]
Are you my next victim?
You must be the wild Pokémon trainer.
Huh! That's my job.
But beating chumps like you is my hobby.
Ready to lose?
[gate creaking]
-Wow.
-Now, this is not too shabby at all.
Free! Free!
[all gasp]
-What's in the backpack?
-The wild Pokémon that I just caught.
There's a whole bunch more
in the tent and then some.
-Hey, can I see them after the match?
-If you want.
So which Pokémon are you gonna choose
for my 99th win?
99th? Hmm.
I'm afraid you're going to have to change
your sign after this match.
You'll be formerly undefeated.
You may think that you're hot stuff, kid,
but you're not playing in the Pokémon
little League anymore.
After I win 100 matches in a row,
I'll start competing for badges.
That means he's only two wins away.
And he'll be extra psyched to win.
98 wins and you still don't have a badge?
That's tough luck, A.J.
I have ten wins
and I've won two Pokémon badges.
Did you buy those badges
or steal them?
Either that or you competed
in some loser Gyms.
Where were they,
Failure City or Wimpsville?
[both seething]
What do you mean, loser Gyms?
Hey, Ash! Pulverize this guy.
[chuckles]
Let's get started, then.
Sandshrew, go!
A Sandshrew, huh?
This should be interesting.
Let's be careful now, Ash.
Remember,
Sandshrew is a Ground type,
so Pikachu's electricity
is no good against it.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
I don't need your help.
Pidgeotto, I choose you!
[Pidgeotto caws]
-Sandshrew, go.
-Pidgeotto, dive at it!
[Pidgeotto caws]
Ash is lucky. The flying Pokémon
should have the advantage here.
Too bad Sandshrew can't fly.
[Pidgeotto caws]
[gasps]
-Pidgeotto!
-Finish it!
Uh-oh!
Pidgeotto, return!
[Pidgeotto moans]
Butterfree, I choose you!
[Butterfree coos]
You can do it!
Flying versus ground should be no problem.
That's what you think, kid.
Now watch and weep.
[Ash]
Go! Stun Spore!
Free?
That Sandshrew is well-trained.
He controls it with a crack of his whip
like a lion tamer.
-Shrew!
-Free!
[gasps]
[Butterfree groaning]
-Butterfree!
-It's not so free anymore.
Chu!
Come on, Pikachu.
You've got to help your friends.
Pikachu!
[screams]
[groans]
Nice work.
[sighs]
-That Sandshrew is very tempting.
-We should grab it.
[Meowth] Hmm. Looks fat.
You two got to carry it.
The outfit that trainer
is wearing is positively hideous.
That shirt looks like
it's from a century or two ago.
He'd fit right in perfectly at a museum.
At least he doesn't look like
he's trick-or-treating like you do.
-Unh!
-Meowth! Unh.
And that makes victory number 99.
It's not fair.
I'm the one with the badges.
How about two out of three?
Stop whining, kid.
Nobody wants to compete against a crybaby.
Hey, there's something fishy here.
I didn't have any problems winning
until I battled in your ring.
How do I know this whole match
wasn't rigged?
That's it. You cheated!
How else could Sandshrew
defeat Butterfree?
Flying Pokémon always have
the advantage over Ground Pokémon.
Chill out.
What do you say we go replay
the match someplace else, huh?
Ash doesn't know when to quit, does he?
That A.J. sure is strong. I don't get it.
How is he so good?
One more chance.
[A.J.]
Come back when you grow up.
Hmm. It's not fair.
[groans]
Looks like you'll have
to rethink the way you train.
-What do you mean?
-[A.J.] You call that last match a fight?
[all gasp]
[A.J.] It's time
for some serious training.
[gasps]
[Butterfree squeaks]
Rattata!
[Sandshrew coos]
Get back in the water!
Knock it off!
[both grunt]
[gasps]
Now what do you want,
a swimming match?
-You're hurting Sandshrew.
-Mind your own business.
I don't need any amateurs teaching me
how to train Pokémon.
You call that training?
What's that?
-It looks like a straitjacket.
-[A.J.] That's no straitjacket.
It's a strength intensifier.
-Who invented that thing?
-I did.
It's my own secret weapon
for unleashing a Pokémon's powers.
Sandshrew, back in the pool!
[Sandshrew titters]
But Sandshrews are weakened by water.
-I know that.
-You'll hurt it!
Sandshrew, dive!
Nice dive.
-Good work.
-The water doesn't weaken your Sandshrew?
You're looking at the only Sandshrew
in the world
that's strong enough
to withstand water.
Sandshrew, pick up your pacing!
[Sandshrew titters]
[Rattatas grunting]
Hey, wait.
I thought you said pacing, not passing.
[both gasp]
-Pikachu!
-Huh, I said padding.
I mean, I said pacing!
[squeaks]
Why are you so tough on Sandshrew?
I have to be tough,
but I ask no more of Sandshrew
than I do of myself,
the very best.
But you aren't nearly as tough
on any of your other Pokémon.
That's because Sandshrew
is the first Pokémon I ever caught.
I will never forget that moment.
We promised to do
whatever it took to become
the greatest Pokémon
and trainer of all time.
Nothing would stop us
from reaching our dream,
no matter how difficult our path.
Enduring fierce storms
and raging winds,
we're sacrificed everything
to achieve our dream.
And it was worth it.
We're an unbeatable team.
What you're doing is wrong.
A great trainer should make
friends with his Pokémon.
Why should I listen to you?
Hey, Brock, don't you have
anything to say about this?
I do.
Your Pokémon are all in great shape.
What kind of Pokémon food
do you give them?
-Ah.
-My own recipe.
Come on, I'll show you.
To get the results I want, I have to
carefully monitor the Pokémon diets.
-Of course, the recipe is secret.
-[Brock] Oh, yeah, of course.
You know, I mix my own food too.
[grunts]
[Pikachu] Pikachu!
-Insulated gloves?
-Check.
-Big rubber ball?
-Check, check, check-a-rooni.
Team Rocket will do what it has to do...
To snatch that little Pikachu.
Maybe we should go back
to our old motto.
This one doesn't feel right.
Hey, how about
a theme-Meowth song?
And I can even do a little dance solo.
Everyone loves me-ooh-thic.
A song's no good.
[hums]
A dance won't work.
-Here's a line you'll like.
-And what's that?
How about, choreography killed the cat?
Okay, you wimps get a 15-minute break.
[Rattatas panting]
[Butterfree cooing]
[Sandshrew panting]
[Pokémon panting]
-Hey!
-Now what do you want?
Your Pokémon are totally wiped out.
You better believe it.
In this Gym, we live by the rule
no pain, no gain,
but judging by your little stuffed Pikachu
over there, you don't follow any rules.
It's not a stuffed Pikachu.
Take it back!
Hey, did you hear me?
I said take it back!
-[both grunting]
-Don't, Ash!
You don't win badges for being buddy,
buddy with a Pokémon!
[Brock]
Knock it off, you two!
[Misty] Isn't there a rule against
splashing in the pool?
Pika, pika, chu...
[Sandshrew laughs]
I'm getting dizzy.
Stop complaining.
Look for Pikachu.
-[Jessie] Roll over there.
-[James] What's that?
-[Jessie] Could it be Pikachu?
-[Meowth] Yeah, that's it. Now hurry!
All that rolling made me nauseous.
[James] Got it.
-[Jessie] Lets go.
-[Meowth] Hurry! I feel sick!
-[James] Watch where you're going!
-[Jessie] This way!
[Meowth] Hey, take it easy.
Ah, my leg fell asleep.
I wish your mouth would.
[both panting]
Why do you keep hanging around here?
There must be other trainers
you can bother.
Yeah, right.
Time's up.
Back to work, all of you!
Hey, where's Sandshrew?
Well, that's weird.
What's your Pikachu doing?
Oh. Ohh!
Pikachu.
[grunts]
-It's no use.
-Here, give it to me.
-Huh?
-Pikachu!
Pikachu, you're okay.
Pikachu, have you seen Sandshrew?
-Pika.
-You haven't.
Sandshrew!
Where are you?
Maybe it ran away.
What are you talking about?
The way you treat your Pokémon,
I'm surprised they all haven't run away.
Sandshrew and I have been together
for a long time.
Yeah, I know, but when Sandshrew saw
how well Pikachu and I get along,
it thought, I deserve better.
I'll find a trainer who treats me
like Ash treats Pikachu?
Sandshrew would not
break the promise we made,
not after all we've been through,
not just before our 100th victory!
Chu.
Now move it.
Go find Sandshrew.
-Free!
-Rattata!
[all panting]
Those clowns
will never catch up with us.
I'm exhausted.
You take the bag now.
But a real gentleman
always carries the bag.
Is that so?
Well, as you know, I'm no gentleman.
[all gasp]
[yelling]
You've all had enough of A.J.
and the way he pushes you around,
haven't you?
Well, you don't have to put up
with it anymore,
because now you can come with me.
Anyone who's coming with me,
raise your hand!
[Ash] Just raise your hand.
Get them up there.
-Ash is making a fool of himself again.
-Mm.
You see what happens when you try
to start a mutiny in my Gym?
My Pokémon are all loyal.
So then where's Sandshrew?
-Meowth!
-[A.J. grunts]
[both groaning]
Sandshrew.
[Pokémons tittering happily]
A.J. and all his Pokémon sure are happy
that Sandshrew is back.
[groans]
[laughs]
How could they possibly pick him over me?
A.J. is tough, but as you can see,
he cares deeply for his Pokémon.
[laughs]
[Ash]
Wow, A.J. does care about them.
[grunting]
-Pika, pi, chu!
-What is it?
Meowth!
So then it must've been Team Rocket
that kidnapped Sandshrew.
-Wake up.
-Meowth?
[yells]
Hey, where am I?
What's going on here?
[whimpering]
How am I gonna get out of this mess?
-[Jessie] Prepare for trouble.
-[James] Make that double.
-Meowth?
-Ugh, Team Rocket.
Use the old motto.
[Jessie] To protect the world
from devastation...
To unite all peoples
within our nation...
[both] To denounce the evils
of truth and love,
to extend our reach
to the stars above...
-Jessie.
-James.
Team Rocket, blast off
at the speed of light!
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth! That's right!
That felt great.
We don't need a theme song.
It's a classic.
So these are the creeps
who kidnapped my Sandshrew?
Mm, that was an unfortunate mix-up.
We have no interest
in your second-rate Sandshrew.
Second-rate?
The only Pokémon we want is Pikachu.
You can keep all those other wimps.
Wimps, are they?
That's it! Huh?
I'll take care of this.
No one insults my Pokémon
and gets away with it.
Let's step outside.
Uh-oh.
Team Rocket has insulted our Gym!
We'll answer them with our 100th win.
100th.
That's right.
As Sandshrew and I vowed.
Good luck!
Your small talk will cost you big-time!
-Ekans, go!
-Your turn, Koffing!
Ekans!
Koffing!
Sandshrew, go!
-Koffing!
-Ekans!
Ekans, bind it now!
Ekans!
[Ekans groans]
-It's so strong.
-Good work!
Excellent!
Koffing, Sludge attack!
Koffing!
Meowth, don't just stand there.
[humming]
Stop pussyfooting around!
Just biting my time.
Ah! The moment of tooth!
Finish it!
Sandshrew, Fissure Strike!
[Sandshrew yelling]
[thunder rumbles and all gasp]
Go, Sandshrew!
Drill into the ground till it splits!
[all yelling]
[groans]
That's it! I forfeit the match!
-Koffing!
-Ekans!
-Come back here!
-Meowth, where are you going?
[Meowth]
To write us a theme song!
[Jessie]
Not that again! Ugh!
We did it, Sandshrew!
We finally reached victory number 100!
Today, all our sacrifices and hard work
have finally paid off!
Now we can start winning our badges.
When I return here, I'm gonna be
the number one Pokémon Master.
Why don't you come along with us?
Thanks, but Sandshrew and I
have our own path that we must follow.
Someday we'll meet again
at the big Pokémon League competition.
Okay, but next time,
you better be in shape,
because I only want to beat
expert trainers.
That's a deal.
So long!
He's tough, but pretty cool.
Yeah, looks like
you've found another rival.
[Ash]
A.J., I'm not going to lose next time!
I'll train hard to become the greatest
Pokémon Master in the world,
following my own path.
[narrator] There are many paths
that lead to the Pokémon League
and Ash is just beginning
to discover his own.
What lies on that path is unknown,
but one thing's for sure,
he'll never forget the name of that place
with the great Gym again.
-♪ Pokémon! ♪
-It’s that time again!
A hundred and fifty Pokémon,
five days a week.
That’s about 30 or so each day.
It’s not too hard, just listen real good!
♪ Alakazam, Doduo, Venonat, Machoke
Kangaskhan, Hypno, Electabuzz, Flareon ♪
♪ Blastoise, Poliwhirl, Oddish, Drowzee
Raichu, Nidoqueen, Bellsprout, Starmie ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, yeah! ♪
Gotta catch 'em all, ow! ♪
♪ Metapod, Marowak, Kakuna, Clefairy
Dodrio, Seadra, Vileplume, Krabby ♪
♪ Lickitung, Tauros, Weedle, Nidoran
Machop, Shellder, Porygon, Hitmonchan ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
Okay, so today was pretty easy,
But you gotta put all five days together.
It’s the only way to name all 150.
Catch you here tomorrow!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Yeah! Pokémon! ♪