♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon!
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon!
Oh, you're my best friend ♪
♪ In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon!
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon!
Gotta catch 'em all! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all!
Pokémon! ♪
[sighs]
[narrator]
After two weeks of being lost,
[sighs]
Our heroes reach Vermilion City.
Congratulations! You've finally made it.
[All] Hip, hip, hooray! Hip, hip, hooray!
Hip, hip, hooray!
I can't wait to take a bubble bath.
I have to hit the Laundromat.
I'm going to find the Vermillion City Gym
right now.
-[Brock] Hold it.
-Huh?
-What's the matter?
-[Pikachu's stomach growls]
-Pikachu.
-It must be hungry.
We haven't eaten anything decent
for three days now.
Hey, Pikachu,
you feeling hungry, little buddy?
[stomach growls]
Oh!
[laughs]
I guess we're all a little hungry,
right, Pikachu?
Pika.
[Ash] I think it's hungry.
We'll fix Pikachu up.
[All] Huh?
I know why you're surprised.
I look like all the other nurses, don't I?
My first cousin works in
Pewter City,
and my second cousin works
in Viridian City.
I think I'm the prettiest one, don't you?
[giggles]
-Yeah--
-[boy] Hurry!
-Huh?
-You'll be okay, Rattata.
Hurry!
That Ratatta's in rough shape.
I wonder what happened.
Oh, it's the 15th one
brought in this month.
What?
[Brock] This is terrible.
[nurse] They all lost to Lieutenant Surge,
the Vermilion Gym Leader.
Whoa, he must be a great trainer.
So, Ash, you scared already?
-No way.
-Well, you talk big.
But when you see how tough it is
to get badges, you turn chicken.
Maybe you should just quit now.
Besides, the only badges you do have
you got out of pity.
A badge is a badge!
[gasps and groans]
Why don't you try prove how tough you are
at the Vermilion Gym?
From the looks of things here,
you'll have to be tough
to battle with this Lieutenant Surge.
You think he's that tough?
We gave you badges, you know.
How do you think we'll look
if you get crushed by Surge?
You have nothing to worry about,
except maybe seeing
my own incredible strength.
[nurse]
All right, that's enough.
She started it.
-Remember, this is a hospital.
-[both moan]
They say if two people fight,
they really care about each other.
-Me care about her?
-Me care about him?
[both sigh]
-[giggles]
-[musical bleep]
That signal means
your Pokémon has recovered.
[munches] Mm! Yum!
-[Ash] Pikachu!
-Pik.
I hope you're full because
we got to win big at that Gym today.
-Pi!
-Come on, let's go win a badge.
[boy] Please hurry!
Just hold on, Pidgey.
I guess they must've come from that Gym.
-Pi!
-Huh?
-Pikachu! Pikachu!
-What?
Don't be a coward.
-Pika. Pikachu.
-Huh?
Don't I care if you end up
like that Pidgey in there?
-Is that it?
-Pika, pika!
Yeah. I guess you're right.
[sighs]
No problem.
You won't end up that way
because you'll win.
[grunting]
Don't be a scaredy-cat, Pikachu.
Pika. Pikachu!
[grunting and groaning]
The way they fight,
must mean they care a lot.
[Ash]
So this is the Vermilion City Gym.
It's not too late to back out.
Why should I back out
when I'm going to win?
Just stick around and watch me.
I'll stick around to see your face
when you get creamed.
If you think We're going to get creamed,
you're going to be disappointed.
Are we ever going to go inside?
[creaking]
Hello. I've come for a Pokémon battle
to earn a thunder badge.
Hey, boss, another victim
for the emergency room.
-Which one?
-[Ash stutters]
Whoa, he's huge.
Is he the Gym Leader you have to beat?
-Welcome to Vermilion Gym.
-[Misty] Ah!
Oh, my next challenger is a cute one.
Don't think I'll go easy on you.
[stammers] Excuse me,
-I'm not the challenger. [chuckles]
-Then who?
Me, that's who.
Hm? Oh, you.
Okay, baby.
[grunts angrily] I'm no baby.
My name's Ash Ketchum.
[chuckles] I call everybody
who loses to me baby. Huh?
-Pi?
-[chuckles] A Pikachu.
Hey, look at this.
Baby brought along a baby Pokémon.
-[all laugh]
-Quit it.
Why are you making fun of my Pikachu?
Pika, pika!
Well, I'll show you why.
Go, Poké Ball!
Rai!
It's a Raichu.
[Pokédex] Raichu. A mouse Pokémon
of the electric element.
Raichu is the evolved form
of Pikachu.
It can shock
with more than 100,000 volts,
enough to render
a Dragonite unconscious.
Chu.
[grunting] Okay, baby.
If you want to quit,
-now's your chance.
-Raichu.
There's no way we're going to quit now.
[Surge chuckles]
What could a baby like that do?
If you just want to become
a Pokémon Master,
you should make your Pokémon evolve
as soon as you catch it.
There's more to raising a Pokémon
than forcing it to evolve.
And I like this Pikachu
just the way it is.
[both laughing]
Wrong, baby.
Electric Pokémon are only useful
once they've learned
all their different electric attacks.
You keep it puny like that,
it's no more than a little pet.
Pika!
-Can Pikachu beat Raichu?
-I seriously doubt it.
Especially if Raichu knows
all the electric attacks.
Okay, baby,
did you just come here
to show us your little pet?
We came here to earn a thunder badge.
-Pika, pika.
-Pikachu?
[growls]
That's unusual.
Pikachu really wants to go into battle.
I'm not surprised.
Pikachu, I'm counting on you.
Pikachu.
Oh, well.
I guess you'll learn
that playing with the big boys
can be a shocking experience.
[announcer]
The Pokémon battle will now begin.
Only one Pokémon may be used.
The Gym Leader, Lieutenant Surge,
has chosen Raichu.
The challenger, Ash,
has chosen Pikachu.
No time limit.
Let the battle begin.
[bell dings]
-Go, Raichu!
-Rai!
-Go, Pikachu!
-Pika!
Pikachu, thunder shock!
Pikachu!
-Pi!
-What's that?
Raichu, show them a real thunder shock.
-Raichu!
-[screams]
[all gasp]
[moans]
-Raichu.
-It's over, baby.
You didn't really think that Pikachu
could beat my Raichu, did you? [chuckles]
Pikachu.
-Call it back, Ash.
-But--
Raichu's shocks are too powerful.
This is a mismatch.
[grunts] Pikachu, return.
[gasps] Pika.
-Pikachu?
-Pikachu still wants to fight?
Pi... Pikachu.
[chuckles]
It's pretty gutsy for a toy.
-Pika!
-Pikachu!
I enjoy playing with toys,
but playtime's over.
-Raichu, mega punch!
-Rai!
-Now a mega kick!
-Chu!
Pikachu!
[grunts]
[moans]
[Jessie chuckles]
Pikachu's really getting pounded.
That Raichu really must be strong.
Hey, I just thought of something.
If Pikachu loses this battle...
You're right.
Then it's not worth stealing after all.
We've wasted all this time.
-Maybe you can steal Raichu.
-[Jessie grunts]
-[thudding]
-[whimpers]
Come on, Pikachu.
Can't you zap it like you always do?
-Surge is getting ready to finish it off.
-[gasps]
Now, give us the big finale, Raichu.
Raichu!
[all screaming]
-[Ash] Pikachu!
-[cries]
-Pi...
-Pikachu. I'm glad you're okay.
-Pikachu.
-[Ash sighs]
-Pikachu got hurt pretty badly.
-I can see that.
-No, no. I mean its spirit.
-What do you mean?
Pikachu was totally overpowered
by that Raichu.
-Brock's right, Ash.
-We'll try harder.
We'll win next time
if Pikachu tries harder.
I think Pikachu was trying its best
the last time.
Hm.
-[nurse] There is one way you might win.
-[all] Huh?
I'm sorry. I overheard your conversation,
and I just thought that maybe--
How can we win?
A while ago, I just happened
to come across this.
-Wow, it's a Thunderstone.
-A Thunderstone?
Yes. You can use it to make Pikachu
evolve into a Raichu.
I could evolve Pikachu
into a Raichu?
Then Pikachu might be strong enough
to win.
You've got to think hard
before using the Thunderstone.
Huh?
If you make Pikachu evolve, Ash,
you can't change it back.
Pikachu will never be the same.
If Pikachu becomes a Raichu,
I might be able to win that badge.
On the other hand,
to make it evolve just to fight,
I would be just like Surge.
Pikachu, what do you want to do?
-Pika.
-I really want to beat that Surge,
but I also don't want
to force you to evolve
if you'd he happier
staying the way you are now.
-He's letting Pikachu decide.
-If it becomes Raichu, it'll be stronger.
What's it going to do?
-Pi--
-Pikachu.
Save your strength.
-Chu!
-[Ash moans]
-Pikachu.
-Pika, Pikachu! Pika.
Pi, pi, pi, Pikachu!
Chu! Pika, Pikachu!
It's so brave.
-So tell us what Pikachu's saying.
-Pikachu won't change.
If it's going to pick a Raichu,
it wants to do it just as it is.
You mean, it's going to battle again
as a Pikachu?
It's going to fight
in the name of all Pikachu.
-[both crying]
-Really?
That's so beautiful.
Pikachu, together, you and I will beat
Lieutenant Surge and his Raichu.
Pika, pika!
-You're both crazy.
-You should change your strategy, Ash.
Maybe use your other Pokémon.
It's hard, but it's not impossible.
Pikachu and I will find a way to win.
Pika, Pikachu! Pika!
Huh? Pikachu will prove it
can beat Raichu.
It will defend its honor and Ash's.
Oh, dear, that's magnificent.
All right, are we all charged up?
Pi... Pika. [sighs]
-Huh?
-It hasn't fully recovered its stamina.
You should let it rest
a little while longer.
[sighs] Pikachu.
Oh, this whole thing has me so nervous.
Really? Since when did you
decide to worry about me?
Not you. I'm concerned
about Pikachu. I hope it'll be okay.
-Hey, Ash.
-Yeah?
During the fight, Surge said
that he made his Raichu evolve
-as soon as he got it, didn't he?
-Yeah.
-Then perhaps there is a way.
-Huh?
Pikachu, our lucky star is shining today.
Pi? Pika?
Where? I don't see it.
How can you see a star
in the middle of the day?
Oh! I don't mean it's actually shining.
-Let's go, Pikachu.
-Pika.
Seems like they're ready to win,
doesn't it?
[Ash] Huh?
Uh, who are you guys?
[both]
To protect the world from devastation.
[both] We forgot.
We are the challenger's cheerleaders,
and we're here to show our support
for the brave Pikachu and Ash.
[both] Rah!
In honor of the great Pikachu's bravery,
we wish to offer a cheer.
We want you, Pikachu!
Give me a pi Give me a ka!
Give me a chu! What've you got?
Pikachu! Fight, fight, Pikachu
You're our Pokémon, yeah
-Hip, hip, hooray!
-Yay, Pikachu!
Okay, let's split.
-That was really disturbing.
-Thanks for your support!
-Bye, Team Rocket!
-[all grunt]
-[Meowth] How did they know it was us?
-[Jessie] Lucky guess.
[chuckles]
Hey, baby,
you ready to take another beating?
You didn't even make your
Pikachu evolve.
You haven't learned anything yet.
Don't you be so sure, Surge.
Okay, well, let's see.
[announcer]
The challenger, Ash, using a Pikachu.
The Gym Leader, Lieutenant Surge,
using a Raichu.
The Pokémon will battle one-on-one
with no time limit.
-Let the battle begin!
-[bell dings]
Use the strategy we planned,
Pikachu!
-You can do it!
-Pika!
A strategy?
So they've been planning a new way
to lose.
-Go, Raichu!
-Raichu!
-[screams]
-[chuckles]
[groaning]
Pika... [grunts]
-[whipping]
-Raichu.
-Pikachu!
-Hang in there, Pikachu.
Roll to the side and break away.
-It can't lose.
-Not after the cheer we did.
Maybe we did the wrong kind
of cheer.
Do it, Raichu.
Give it the body slam.
-Raichu!
-[cries]
[all gasp]
Finish it off, Raichu.
Another body slam!
-Raichu!
-[Misty and Brock] Oh!
-[all gasp]
-[all] Pikachu!
Watch out!
-Hey, what?
-Chu!
-[all] All right!
-Do it, Pikachu! Agility now!
-Chu!
-Raichu, use your body slam!
Raichu! [grunting]
[groaning]
Uh, Raichu?
It's working. Just like brock said.
Right. Raichu evolved too fast,
and it never learned the speed attacks
it could only learn in the Pikachu stage.
-Okay, use all the agility you've got.
-[grunting]
Your Raichu's way too slow, Surge.
That's its weakness.
Okay, Raichu.
Give it a thunder bolt.
Shut it down.
Raichu!
[all gasp]
[all scream]
[grunting]
The end of the match.
Huh? What?
-Pikachu.
-All right, way to go.
It used its tail as a ground
and dodged the electric shock.
-What a shocking story.
-That was quite a tale.
-Meow!
-[James whimpers]
[Meowth] And now you've both
been punished. [chuckles]
-[James] Caught me.
-[Meowth chuckles]
[panting]
Raichu, give it another thunder bolt!
Rai...
-Oh.
-Rai!
-[Raichu gasps]
-Do something!
It's over.
Raichu ran out of electricity.
All right. Quick attack.
Chu!
Raichu, take down now!
-Rai!
-Pikachu!
-[groans]
-Pika, Pikachu!
Raichu!
Unbelievable!
[whimpers]
We did it, Pikachu.
-Way to go.
-Fantastic.
-[all] Hooray!
-Victory!
Pikachu.
Congratulations. Nice job, Ash, Pikachu.
As proof of your victory,
a thunder badge.
Thank you.
Would you look at that?
It's really a thunder badge.
You should be proud.
You and your Pikachu
really fought good together.
Thanks. [grunts]
A thunder badge!
And it's all mine!
Pi, Pikachu.
Nice victory, Ash.
You're no baby.
-Congratulations, Ash, Pikachu.
-You finally got your own badge.
Rai, rai, rai.
-Pika.
-Rai.
Thank you, Pikachu.
This was your victory.
-Pika.
-[grunting]
Wow! Now I can really can see
lots of lucky stars.
Pika, pika.
-Those two really are quite a team.
-Yes, indeed.
[both laugh]
[all laugh]
That Pikachu really is special.
That's why it's worth snatching.
Hey, once we steal it,
maybe we can earn our own badges.
[narrator] Ash and Pikachu won a thunder
badge in an impressive performance.
But they still have a long way to go
to reach their goal, as does Team Rocket.
And so the adventure continues on and on.
Drat! We wasted this episode
cheering the good guys.
[both grunt]
[narrator]
Right, James. Better luck next time.
-♪ Pokémon! ♪
-Attention, all Pokémon trainers!
Do you got what it takes to be the best?
Today, we’ll do 30 Pokémon!
It’s the ultimate test!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
♪ gotta catch 'em all ♪
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Articuno, Jynx, Nidorina
Beedrill, Haunter, Squirtle ♪
-♪ Chansey ♪
-♪ Pokémon ♪
♪ Parasect, Exeggcute
Muk, Dewgong ♪
♪ Pidgeotto, Lapras
Vulpix, Rhydon ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master
is my destiny ♪
♪ Charizard, Machamp
Pinsir, Koffing ♪
♪ Dugtrio, Golbat
Staryu, Magikarp ♪
♪ Ninetales, Ekans, Omastar ♪
♪ Scyther, Tentacool
Dragonair, Magmar ♪
Not bad, not bad!
Hey, don’t get cocky.
Tomorrow’s the hardest part.
We’re on our way to 150 Pokémon!
There’s no stopping us!
♪ Catch 'em catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Oh, gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Oh, gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all yeah! ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪