♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon! Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
[narrator] Today our heroes find
themselves traveling through the forest,
heading towards Cinnabar Island,
the site of the next Pokémon Gym.
There Ash hopes to win
his seventh Pokémon badge.
However this forest
isn’t as peaceful as it seems.
- Puff!
-[boy] Stop, thief!
-Jigglypuff!
-A thief? Where?
-I bet it’s that Team Rocket.
-Maybe.
[gasps]
-Look, that must be him.
-He looks like a thief to me.
-Go, Pikachu.
-Pika! Pi!
-Pika pi!
-What’s wrong, Pikachu?
-[boy] Attack!
-Huh?
[all] Whoa!
[growls and barks]
-[boy] Sic him, Growlithe.
-Oh!
[growls and barks]
[yelling and growling]
-All right, Pikachu, Thunder Shock!
-Pika pika!
Pikachu!
[groans]
All right, Pikachu.
Show that thief who’s boss.
-[growling and barking]
-[all] Huh?
[growling and barking]
-Pika.
-Uh, what’s going on?
-Easy. We’re not going to hurt you.
-[pants] How awful. Are you okay?
-Uh, yeah. I think so.
Just what do you think you’re doing,
interfering with us?
-Huh?
-Interfering?
But we were just trying to help you
capture that dangerous thief
before he got way.
He’s not a thief. He’s a police officer
training our canine police unit.
-Canine police?
-These are police Pokémon.
[all gasp]
[Pokédex]
Growlithe, the puppy Pokémon.
While loyal to its master,
the Growlithe will drive away enemies
by barking and biting.
I guess that must make Growlithe
a perfect Pokémon for the police to use.
-You’re right.
-The canine unit.
These Growlithe pups are so well-trained.
And so cute too.
-[growls]
-Look out!
Oh, no. They’re not going to bite us,
are they?
Don’t worry. The Growlithe won’t bite
unless I order them to attack.
-Growlithe, line up.
-[all growling]
These people are our new friends.
Say hello, canine squad.
-[all gibber]
-Oh, they’re so cute.
That’s so cool.
Look, a whole pack
of police-trained Pokémon.
The boss would certainly love that.
Yeah, but who knows if their bark
is worse than their bite?
I believe I have the perfect plan
for capturing those puppies.
-That sounds great.
-It sound familiar.
You kids must be exhausted.
I hope you’ll be able to eat something.
[all gulping]
Ha, ha. I guess that’s not a problem.
Did you see the way that Growlithe
tackled that guy, Brock?
-it was braver than Pikachu.
-Pi?
But the officer playing
the thief was holding a gun.
You can’t expect Pikachu
to attack somebody like that.
Brock’s right.
I bet you never even thought about
how badly Pikachu could have been hurt.
Of course I did.
Having a Pokémon take
on an armed opponent
is very, very dangerous
unless it has special training.
I guess that’s true.
Hm. So far I’ve only been using
my Pokémon to battle
and help capture other Pokémon.
You’re thinking of something, Ash.
[Brock] Wait a minute. I hope you’re
not thinking of having Pikachu train
with the police like Growlithe.
[Ash] What’s wrong with that idea?
It’ll make Pikachu even stronger.
Officer Jenny, will you train my Pikachu
the way you train the Growlithe?
Pikachu!
[Jenny] Well, this school
is for training Growlithe.
We can’t admit just any Pokémon.
Ah!
Maybe Pikachu just isn’t cut out
for that kind of training.
You keep saying you want to become
the world’s best Pokémon breeder,
don’t you, Brock?
Hm. Well, sure, of course I do.
Well, I want to be
the world’s best Pokémon trainer
and I also want my Pikachu to be
the best Pokémon it can possibly be.
Well, if you really want
your Pikachu to be the best,
why don’t you bring your Pikachu down
to our training class tomorrow?
Do you mean it?
You hear that, Pikachu?
-Uh, Pikachu?
-[groans]
Pika!
[chirping]
[snoring]
Uh, ah. What?
-What’s going on, Office Jenny?
-Pika, Pi!
Well, it’s time for our class.
What time is it?
-It’s only four o'clock. Uh, good night.
-Pika pika.
Huh?
[inhales and blows whistle]
[both scream]
[both sigh]
Come on. Rise and shine. It’s time
for you to start your training class.
[both groan]
Pi!
Okay, first we’ll test you out
on the obstacle course.
Here’s your chance, Pikachu.
Let’s show ‘em what you can do.
-Don’t let that Growlithe beat you.
-Pikachu.
Don’t worry. I know you can win.
Actually, Pikachu won’t be
the only one running this race
-because you have to run too, Ash.
-Me? How come?
Ash, a master will never be respected
if he won’t do something
he asks his own Pokémon to do.
Really?
I’ll be running too,
so let’s get started, shall we, Ash?
Uh, okay.
Heh, looks like Ash is having
some second thoughts.
I wonder if this police training
will be too tough.
Don’t worry. Pikachu will be fine.
-I mean too tough for Ash.
-Huh? Right.
Ready, set, go!
Go for it, Pikachu. We can beat them!
[grunting]
-This is too easy.
-Pika!
Huh?
[both groan]
Hey, what’s this thing?
-How are we going to get past it?
-Pikachu.
Crawl, growlithe.
if they can do it, we can do it too.
[grunting and groaning]
-This training is tougher than I thought.
-Pika!
-What’s wrong, Pikachu?
-Pika pika!
Cut it out, Pikachu!
-Climb, Growlithe!
-[both grunt]
-Now we have to climb this thing?
-Pika pika.
Okay! Ugh, ah.
Follow me, Pikachu.
Ah. All right!
[grunting and groaning]
Pika!
Pika! Pika! Pikachu!
[Ash] Ah! Pikachu!
[sighs]
This police canine training sure is tough.
Are you still going to go through with it?
Of course I’m going through with it
‘cause I want Pikachu to be the best.
But don’t you think Pikachu’s
a great Pokémon just the way it is?
Yeah, Pikachu's great but I want it to
be just as tough as Growlithe.
That’s what you want too,
isn’t it, Pikachu?
-Pika.
-Huh?
Hey, what’s going on here?
[Jessie chuckles]
-[Jessie] Prepare for trouble.
-[James] Make it double.
Huh?
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation.
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James.
Team rocket blasts off
at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth! That’s right.
[all growling]
[all growl and bark]
Team Rocket.
They wouldn’t try to steal these Pokémon.
They must be crazy, breaking
into a school for police canine.
Isn’t that kind of like saying:
"Please arrest me"?
These police Pokémon
really give me the creeps.
Can’t we steal some Pokémon
that are more cat-friendly?
You coward!
We can do anything once we get
that pack of obedient Growlithe.
They’ll do whatever we command.
[James] They’ll rob banks
whenever we see them.
[Jessie]
They’ll steal artworks from every museum.
We’ll be the richest criminals
of all time!
The queen, the king, the cat of crime!
Luckily your dream won’t come true.
These police Growlithe would never
do anything to break the law.
-Don’t bet on it.
-[chuckles].
-[gasps]
-Wait till they try...
-Team Rocket’s esopho-gas.
-[all gasp]
[all coughing and groaning]
Now those Growlithe
won’t be able to use their noses.
Right!
-Time for our next move.
-Ready when you are.
Take a sniff of this.
Just a whiff of this.
[both]
And hear the metamorphosis.
[both chuckle]
[all gasp]
What kind of gas is this? Yeow!
What happened to my voice?
I sound like one of the chipmunks.
Something’s wrong with my voice.
That gas they just sprayed makes
your voice get high and squeaky.
Pika pi! Pika! Pikachu.
[chuckles] Our plan is working.
Yes, we’re certainly hitting
a career high note.
I don’t know what you’re planning,
but I’m placing you under arrest
for trespassing.
All right, Growlithe.
Round them up!
-Huh?
-[all groan]
[Jenny] What’s the matter, Growlithe?
Arrest them!
The Growlithe can’t understand Jenny’s
order now that her voice is changed.
If these Growlithe can’t use
their sense of smell
and they can’t understand Jenny’s orders,
they’re useless as police Pokémon.
Uh.
Heh. Their plan’s working!
[Jessie chuckles]
-Shall we move on to phase two?
-Sounds good to me.
All right then.
A little changing music.
Hmm. Pass me that, will you?
No, that’s mine.
-[Jessie] Almost ready.
-Oh, hand me those pumps.
[both] Ta-da!
And now for one more change.
This synthesizer will make
me sound just like Officer Jenny.
Sit, Growlithe!
Huh?
Beg, Growlithe! Lie down!
What’s wrong with all of you?
That’s not me, that’s Team Rocket.
Don’t listen to them.
All right, Growlithe, listen to me.
I want you to place
that woman under house arrest.
No, please.
[grunts]
No, stop it, Growlithe!
-Well, that about wraps things up.
-Mm-hmm.
-Line up, Growlithe.
-[all growl]
No, please don’t go!
[all growl]
-Attention, Growlithe.
-Now, Meowth, open the hatch.
Roger.
- Everybody, in the van. Huh?
-[Ash] Hold it!
You can’t take those Growlithe.
And just how are you going to stop us,
squeaky?
Why don’t we teach them all
a lesson before we go?
Why not? Growlithe, about face.
Surround them.
[all growling]
Uh-oh. I know!
We’ll use our Pokémon to battle them.
Oh.
[screams]
-What’s wrong now, Ash?
-I left my Poké Balls behind.
-I didn’t bring mine either.
-I left mine in my backpack.
-We’re in trouble.
-You said it.
Don’t let the bad criminals get away
from Growlithe.
[all gasp]
[groans]
Pika pika!
Uh, Pikachu?
This is perfect.
We’ll catch a Pikachu too.
-Aren’t we lucky?
-I should say.
This should be interesting. Let’s see.
Pikachu!
-Pikachu!
-Huh.
I want you to get in the car with
these Growlithe. Come on, hurry up.
Don’t go. That may sound like me
but it’s Team Rocket.
Pika, Pi?
He’s lying. My voice doesn’t sound
that messed up. Get in the van.
-Hurry!
-Pikachu, don’t! Huh?
Pika!
-Why didn’t it work?
-Pika pi!
-Pikachu.
-Pikachu knew?
Ash and Pikachu recognize
what’s in each other’s hearts,
so Pikachu can’t be fooled
by somebody using a fake voice.
Oh, who cares?
Growlithe, get that Pikachu
and its trainer now.
[grunting and groaning]
Pikachu!
[groaning]
Quit fooling around and get them.
-[all growling]
-Pikachu
-Pikachu!
-[groaning]
-Pikachu! Pikachu!
-[groans]
- Oh, Pikachu!
-Please, tell me what’s wrong, Pikachu.
-Pikachu.
You’re dizzy
from using too much electricity.
-Pika.
-[all growling]
This looks bad.
[all growling]
-Huh?
-Jigglypuff.
♪ Jigglypuff ♪
Huh?
Nice song, Jigglypuff.
Listen to me, Growlithe.
Team Rocket are the bad guys.
[both] This looks bad.
-Take care of them quickly.
-[growls]
-Oh!
-[growling]
[growling]
[whimpers]
[growls]
Ha, ha. Good Growlithe.
Nice Growlithe.
Hey, wait for me.
Growlithe, are you okay?
Growl.
Growlithe, you remember me.
What are you doing, Growlithe?
Don’t lick her, attack her.
[all growling]
Attack them. Attack them!
They’re the enemy!
Do what we tell you, you dimwit dogs.
[all growling]
-[both groan]
-Not us, get them!
Hey, that’s my voice.
I told you don’t get us, get them!
Uh, wrong voice.
I knew this wouldn’t work.
[both] Huh?
-What are you doing, Meowth?
-You come back here!
They should have known.
I’m just a scaredy-cat.
[grunting and growling]
Let me in!
-Meowth, wait!
-Slow down!
-Let us in!
-Yeah!
I sure made a big mistake.
Pikachu doesn’t have to train with a
canine squad to be the perfect Pokémon.
-Pikachu!
-I like Pikachu just the way it is.
You two recognize what’s in each
other’s hearts and that’s what counts.
Heh, I’ll try to keep that in mind.
Ha, ha. So will we.
Well, keep up the good work, both of you.
[Brock]
I’d like Brock to know what’s in my heart.
Huh?
Brock’s so good-looking
and he’s so talented.
I just love him so much.
Brock is the coolest.
You are pathetic.
-Oh!
-[chuckles]
[narrator] A strong thread joins
Ash and Pikachu’s hearts together.
It is a bond of friendship
that will keep them safe
no matter what lies on the road ahead.
With their courage renewed,
our heroes continue their journey
to Cinnabar Island
and their next exciting Pokémon
adventure... Uh-oh.
Jiggypuff.
-♪ Pokémon! ♪
-Attention, all Pokémon trainers!
Do you got what it takes to be
the best?
Today, we’ll do 30 Pokémon!
It’s the ultimate test!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Articuno, Jynx, Nidorina, Beedrill
Haunter, Squirtle, Chansey, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Parasect, Exeggcute, Muk, Dewgong,
Pidgeotto, Lapras, Vulpix, Rhydon ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
♪ Charizard, Machamp, Pinsir, Koffing,
Dugtrio, Golbat, Staryu, Magikarp ♪
♪ Ninetales, Ekans, Omastar Scyther,
Tentacool, Dragonair, Magmar ♪
Not bad, not bad!
Hey, don’t get cocky.
Tomorrow’s the hardest part.
We’re on our way up to 150 Pokémon!
There’s no stopping us!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪