♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land ♪
♪ Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all!
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny,
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
[narrator]
As his Pokémon journey continues,
Ash is one step closer
to achieving his dream
of becoming a Pokémon master.
Last time, Ash defeated
the Vermilion City Gym Leader
and earned a thunder badge.
[laughs] Hm?
-[Ash] Hey.
-[Pikachu] Pikachu.
[narrator]
Has Ash's ship finally come in,
or will our heroes be cruisin'
for a bruisin'?
[Ash]
Battle Aboard The St. Anne
-[Pikachu] Pika!
-[Ash] Wow!
[Misty] Beautiful.
[Ash] Oh, man, I'd love to cross the ocean
on a ship like this.
Yeah, just think of all the Pokémon
we'd be able to see along the way.
Oh, for sure.
Just imagine, sunbathing on deck all day.
Just a nice, long, relaxing cruise.
-We could never afford a cruise like that.
-Oh.
Reality can really bum you out.
Congratulations! You guys are way lucky.
You can go on a super deluxe sea cruise!
[laughter]
[all] A sea cruise?
Well, it's, like, you know,
we have these incredible,
-super cool tickets for you.
-Cool.
-Cool, huh?
-[Misty] What?
These are tickets for the biggest party
ever, on board the St. Anne cruise liner.
The famous St. Anne?
-Cool.
-The coolest ship on the sea.
Everyone's going to be together
and, like, have the coolest party.
Cool.
And the party's for Pokémon trainers only.
-Step this way.
-[giggles]
It'll be a radical party. All the most
radical Pokémon trainers will be there.
Do you know anybody
who says "radical" anymore?
Uh-uh.
Okay, dudes, here are your tickets.
We'd love to go
on the Pokémon trainer cruise,
but we really don't have the money
to pay for it.
Oh, whoa, like, you don't understand.
-Cool.
-They're totally free.
-Huh?
-Totally free.
Totally free.
For free? Why are you giving them away?
Well, like, we have to go out
with our boyfriends,
but we wanted to give our tickets
to cool Pokémon fans.
Cool.
We saw you and thought
you looked really cool.
Just take these
and have a really cool time.
-Thanks a lot.
-No sweat.
-Cool.
-Have a nice day, for sure.
All right. This really is cool, Isn't it?
Pikachu.
[ship's klaxon blows]
[Brock] The St. Anne. Wow!
[Ash] Yeah and that Pokémon party.
I wonder which one of these ships
is the St. Anne.
-I think that's it.
-Huh?
[Brock] Wow. That's incredible.
[Misty] It's huge.
[Pikachu] Pika.
[Jessie] We did it. We got them.
Like, wow, don't I make,
like, the coolest girl?
-[Jessie growls and James whimpers]
-Stop acting like an ignoramus.
Ow.
[Meowth]
We got a call from the boss.
Greetings, sir.
So the team is all there.
[all] Sir.
[purrs]
Meow! What's with the Persian?
Hey, boss, what about Meowth?
Ain't I your favorite anymore?
I'm totally disgusted watching you fail me
when I expect total perfection.
-Purr-fection like this beautiful Persian.
-[meows]
But... Meowth.
If you want to make me happy,
you can make sure
our latest plan succeeds.
Meow!
Have you handed out all of the tickets
to the St. Anne cruise?
[Jessie] Yes.
All of the Pokémon trainers
were delighted to take them.
Was it really all right for us
to give out all those tickets for free?
A small price to pay
for what I'll get in return.
[both] Oh.
My men have already secretly boarded
the St. Anne.
When I give them the signal,
they will take the Pokémon
from all of the trainers we tricked
into boarding the ship.
That's the boss for you, a real genius.
This time, failure is out of the question.
[both] Aye-aye, sir.
We can do it.
[evil chuckle]
[Ash] What an awesome ship.
[Misty] I'd like to travel around
the whole world in this.
Welcome aboard the St. Anne.
This way.
Wow! Look at this!
[indistinct chatter]
Come one, come all.
Oh. It's so cute.
It's like a giant Pokémon convention.
Everyone's a Pokémon trainer.
Take a look at the smooth skin
on my Charmander.
That shows how healthy it is.
Look at the flame on my Charmander.
There's orange mixed in with the red.
Cool, huh?
Check it out.
[chuckles] Wait, look how hard
the shell is on my Squirtle.
Tough, huh? [chuckles]
My Squirtle and my charmander
are much better than theirs are.
-[man] All right, bring them on.
-Hm?
Raticate, a jump kick.
Raticate!
All right, Starmie, spinning tackle.
[grunting]
Raticate!
-All right, they're having a battle.
-Pikachu.
Raticate, super fang attack, now.
Raticate!
[grunting]
[gasps]
Are you okay, Starmie?
[whimpers]
Ah, don't feel too badly, young man.
It was only a practice match anyhow,
and I just happened to be lucky.
My, how gracious.
Heh, not at all, miss.
Keep working on building
your Starmie's strength there.
Well, now, is anybody else brave enough
to challenge my Raticate?
[grunting] I can't wait.
How about battling my Butterfree?
As you wish.
Boy, I hope he knows what he's doing.
Say, Jessie, this place is packed.
Yes, and packed with Pokémon.
And soon all these Pokémon will be ours.
[maniacal laughter]
All for us.
Shut up. They're not for us.
They're for the boss.
I forgot.
Raticate, a jump kick.
Raticate.
Butterfree, tackle!
[screeching]
[both grunting]
Does Ash's Butterfree even stand a chance
against that Raticate?
Sure. It's a good match, really.
Finish it, Raticate.
Hyper fang attack.
Raticate!
[grunts]
-Whoopee!
-Raticate!
Butterfree, stun spore.
[chattering]
[grunting]
All right. Now the whirlwind.
Well, that's enough.
Huh?
Why don't we just call it a draw?
But I was winning.
[salesman]
Boy, boy. Hey, you boy. Come here.
Are you addressing me?
I want you to have a look at this Pokémon.
Huh?
What is this thing?
The king of all carp. A Magikarp.
What do I do, eat it?
[chuckles] See how healthy it is.
Oh! It certainly is lively.
Just between you and me, this Magikarp
is like a Pokémon gold mine.
Gold mine?
Right.
A Magikarp lays 1,000 eggs at a time.
Each of those 1,000 baby Magikarp
lay 1,000 more.
One thousand times 1,000 makes
one million.
Every one of those one million
lays another 1,000.
That's a billion Pokémon.
A billion?
You can sell one Magikarp for $100.
In three generations,
you have tons of money.
Billions and billions.
Billions?
[laughing]
[salesman] You'll be so rich,
you can go on a Pokémon shopping spree.
Rich. Rich!
I normally charge $100, but for you,
I'll throw in an egg-laying set,
childcare set
and an education set for only $300.
-How about it? [chuckles]
-I'll take it.
I can tell. [chuckles]
You're going to be a very rich man.
A very rich man.
[crazed laughter]
[chomping and grunting]
So, are you having yourself a good time?
Yes, sir, We're having a great time.
You know, that Butterfree of yours
is quite extraordinary.
It's incredible.
She's beautiful.
Hello in there.
Beautiful.
Here we go again.
Well, I put a lot of work
into raising it.
What did you think of my Raticate?
It looked great,
and it really put up a tough fight.
In that case, I'll be direct.
Why don't we trade?
Trade Pokémon?
When two people find that they each like
the other's Pokémon, they trade.
-It's quite a common practice everywhere.
-Everywhere?
You see, friends who trade
then trade with their other friends
and so friendships grow deeper
and continue to spread wider and wider.
Trading and making new friends
is one of the best things
about having Pokémon.
That's how Pokémon friendships
get to spread all around the world.
Wow.
Friendship is wonderful, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah. Why don't you and I
start a friendship right now?
-Should I trade, Brock?
-Oh, yeah. You got to trade.
Everybody should trade.
Let's start trading.
Well, okay.
Here we go.
Hm.
Well, that's all there is to it.
Raticate is your new Pokémon.
You idiot!
Can't you see you were tricked?
What a dope.
But you don't understand.
Magikarp is a goldmine.
Even its Poké Ball is solid gold.
It's just gold-plated.
[screams]
Magikarp is a no-talent Pokémon
that can't do anything but flop around.
How could you possibly expect to sell it?
I was tricked.
How did you get the money for it?
Well, the advance on my salary
didn't quite cover it, so I--
So you did what?
I used the advance on your salary.
You go return that fish
and get my money back right now.
[ship's klaxon blares]
What's the matter, Ash?
You look so serious.
Uh, I was just thinking.
I wonder if that guy is going
to take good care of my Butterfree.
-Oh.
-I traded my Butterfree to some guy
I don't even know just because
he seemed to like trading so much.
I really don't even know
if he'll take care of it the way I did.
Look on the bright side,
you got a Raticate.
[sighs]
It's just when I was trading it away,
I remembered the time
when it evolved into Butterfree.
Pika.
[ship's klaxon blares]
[growls happily]
[man chuckles] It won't be long now.
[screeches]
-Hey!
-Pikachu?
[confused chatter]
[man] Who are they?
Hey, hombre, I want my... my money back!
[screams]
Are you crazy?
-But I--
-We've got work to do!
To protect the world from devastation...
To unite all peoples within our nation...
To denounce the evils of truth and love...
To extend our reach to the stars above...
-Jessie.
-James.
Team Rocket.
Blast off at the speed of light.
[sighs]
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth. That's right.
Team Rocket will now take possession
of your Pokémon.
-[man] My Pokémon?
-[boy] They can't do that.
[woman] What are they talking about?
Our Pokémon.
[all screaming]
-Give me your Pokémon.
-No way.
Don't make me take them.
Pikachu!
Chu!
[screaming]
If they're going
to try to rob our Pokémon,
we might as well make it a battle.
-Yeah, we can't just surrender.
-Let's fight back.
[all cheering]
[all] Go!
Suck them up. Suck them up.
Suck them all up!
Attaway to go, guys.
Keep sucking them up.
Make sure you get every last one.
Squirtle, go!
Squirtle.
We got to fight them together.
-Pikachu, go.
-Pika.
[all] Kachu! Kachu! Kachu...
Kachu! Kachu! Kachu!
Pikachu!
[screaming]
Charmander, I choose you.
Char!
[all] Char! Char! Char!
[all screaming]
Geodude, go!
Geodude.
[all] Geodude. Geodude. Geodude.
[screaming]
[all chattering]
[all screaming]
[trilling]
Now it's my turn. Go, Butterfree!
Raticate!
Huh?
-Ash, you traded it, remember?
-Oh, yeah.
[trilling]
Butterfree.
Oh!
[trills] Butterfree!
Yeah! All right!
I raised that Butterfree all by myself.
I have to get Butterfree back.
Hand over the Poké Balls.
Pidgeotto, I choose you.
[all] Pidgeo!
Pidgeotto, group gust!
[squawking]
Pikachu, all together, thunderbolt!
[all] Kachu! Kachu! Kachu!
Pikachu!
[all scream]
-[Ash] We did it! Great job!
-[all cheering]
I think we should all be very proud
of our Pokémon.
And we taught Team Rocket
a lesson they'll never forget.
I can't wait to get off this lousy bucket.
[all screaming]
Wait, there goes my salary advance!
-There goes my money too.
-Meowth.
[all gasping]
Oh, no, it's a big storm.
It'll be tough to get back
with waves like this.
What?
Hey, where's Ash?
So you want to go back on our trade?
Butterfree was the first Pokémon
I ever captured.
I worked very hard
training and raising it.
Please, can I have it back?
You leave me no choice.
I'm sorry.
Now, calm down.
These high seas have just pushed us
a little off course.
[man] A little off course?
There's nothing to worry about.
We're heading for port now,
and besides, this ship is unsinkable.
There's absolutely no need for alarm.
[all gasping]
Now, there's no reason to panic. I just
thought I'd test out one of the lifeboats.
[nervous chuckling]
[all clamoring]
[woman] Hey! Got to get off the ship!
Come on, Ash, we got to go.
The ship is sinking.
Hold on.
Butterfree, please forgive me.
[groans]
Butterfree!
Ash!
[James]
Wait, there goes my next paycheck!
Who cares about your paycheck?
What about mine?
[Meowth]
We got to get out of here.
-[man] Oh, what are we going to do?
-[nervous chatter]
[man] Oh, no.
[all panting]
I got you!
[all screaming]
[grunts]
Got it!
[all sigh]
[all screaming]
[man]
Look, there goes the ship! It's sinking!
May I have your attention.
Anyone who didn't leave the ship safely,
please say aye.
Good. Well done. Everyone's safe, then.
[narrator] Not everyone, Captain.
And as the St. Anne heads to
the bottom of the sea,
our heroes are trapped unconscious inside.
And so is Team Rocket.
Could this be the end?
How will they escape their watery fate?
I don't know,
but I have a terrible sinking feeling.
♪ Pokémon! ♪
Get those lips loose!
It’s time to Pokérap!
Come on, sing ‘em with me!
That’s the game!
There’s 150 Pokémon.
How many can you name?
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Sandslash, Hitmonlee, Psyduck
Arcanine, Eevee, Exeggutor ♪
♪ Kabutops, Zapdos, Dratini
Growlithe, Mr. Mime, Cubone ♪
-♪ Graveler, Voltorb, Gloom ♪
-We're almost home!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Charmeleon, Wartortle, Mewtwo
Tentacruel, Aerodactyl, Omanyte ♪
♪ Slowpoke, Pidgeot, Arbok ♪
That's all, folks!
Can you name all the Pokémon?
Just put today’s song together
with the other days of the week.
That’s why you can’t miss a show.
You gotta catch ‘em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em,
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all!
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny,
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪