♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all!
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
[narrator] It's hard work
trying to become a Pokémon Master
and our heroes haven't had much rest
or relaxation.
But now they're in luck.
They've come to town
on the same day the carnival has arrived.
Huh-uh-uh.
Look at all of those beautiful girls.
And check out
all of the rides and shows.
All right. Let's show these people
how to really party.
Yeah.
-[Ash] Let's boogie.
-[Brock] Yahoo!
What's wrong, Misty?
Don't you want to party with us?
-Uh, we'll just party over here, okay?
-Pika-pi!
See you guys later.
Woo-hoo!
-Whoa!
-Pika.
Well, that one was great, wasn't it?
Which one do you want to ride next?
[woman] I've had it. I quit!
Please don't leave me.
I promise to pay you as soon as I can.
Then pay me right now.
I can't just now,
but I promise, as soon as I get
some paying customers, I'll pay you.
[all] Exeggcute...
And just who do you think
is going to come watch your lousy show?
They'll come, I promise.
[woman]
I've heard your promises before.
Ow!
Huh! Goodbye.
Don't leave. I need you.
Excuse me. Are you all right, sir?
You're a kind person, aren't you?
Well, no, not especially.
And such a beautiful girl.
You'd help me out, wouldn't you?
I need your help so badly,
and you'd be so perfect.
Oh, pull yourself together.
You're the only one who can help me now.
-Uh...
-Please, just listen.
Uh, okay.
Keep an open mind.
Uh-huh.
I'd like you to become the assistant
in my act.
-What?
-[all shouting]
I'm a magician. Melvin's the name.
Hi.
For you.
Oh. Ha.
I'm not very famous yet, but I'm working
really hard on my magic act.
My dream is to have
my own Las Vegas showroom
and perform my magic act
before thousands of cheering fans.
Won't you help me make my dream come true?
I'll help you. But just for today.
Thank you so much.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for coming.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Melvin the Magician Magnificent.
At least the crowd's small,
so nobody will see me.
[Ash] Misty?
What are you doing up there?
Are you part of the show?
Pika-pi.
What are you two doing here?
That's a real cute outfit, Misty.
Come on. Hurry it up.
-[man] Start the show.
-Yes, yes, of course.
Thank you for your patience.
Please allow me to present
my magical Pokémon, Exeggcute.
[all] Exeggcute!
[laughs] Exeggcute.
[Pokédex]
Exeggcute, an egg Pokémon.
Although it resembles an egg,
it is known to be more closely related
to the seed of a plant.
Now it's time for some Exeggcute juggling.
This is magic?
[man] We don't want juggling!
Boring.
-[man 2] We want to see some magic!
-[man 3] Yeah, do a trick, will you?
Hold on. The best part is coming up.
My Pokémon and I are going to do
some great magic tricks now,
which will "summaze"
and "apprise" you.
Uh, don't you mean surprise
and amaze?
That's right.
See, that's why we make such a great team.
Yeah, right.
[all] Exeggcute! Exeggcute! Exeggcute...
Raging fire.
[man screams]
-[man 1] That was pathetic.
-[man 2] You're the worst!
Just one more try.
[shrieks]
-[both] Oh!
-Fire! Fire! And fire!
Ah!
[both] Ah!
Hey! Be careful, Melvin!
I can't believe it.
It never worked before.
Fire!
[fire alarm rings]
-[man 1] Hey, what is this?
-[man 2] What's going on?
Pika, pika?
[groans]
-I want my money back!
-You're the worst!
-Rip-off.
-Yeah.
Wait. Don't go.
The best part is just about to start.
Ow!
-That hurts.
-Exeggcute! Exeggcute
-Oh.
-Pika.
Get out! You're fired!
Give me another chance.
Are you kidding?
No one comes to see you and you almost
burned my carnival to the ground.
Get out of here.
[sighs]
I feel sorry for the guy.
He just doesn't know what he's doing.
You can relate to that.
What's that mean?
Don't worry, Melvin. Cheer up.
Fired again.
I'll never make it to Las Vegas.
[Exeggcute] Exeggcute...
I guess we'll have to give up
all our dreams.
Give up?
You're not going to give up your dream
that easy, are you?
-But--
-If your show's no good,
then learn some new tricks
and make it good.
That's a good idea.
Ash does say something right
once in a while.
Say what?
[all] Exeggcute!
New tricks?
We'll even help you out.
You can do it. What do you say?
Don't quit now. Come on, Melvin.
Okay, I'll give it a try.
What are those twerps up to now?
It looks like
they're talking to a magician.
Talking to a magician, huh?
Wait till they see our bag of tricks.
Okay, well, here I go.
Abracadabra.
Ta-da.
-Hey, all right.
-[Misty] Oh, all right.
That was great.
Uh, thanks.
Uh. Huh?
The flowers are dead.
So is his act.
Pika-pika.
All my life,
I've dreamed of becoming a magician,
entertaining people,
seeing their faces light up.
But now the dream is all over.
[all] Exeggcute.
[sighs] Now they're depressed.
Hey. I'll show you
how to put on a real magic show.
-Huh?
-Pika.
What kind of a magic show?
I'll do a Pokémon magic show.
Welcome!
I am the swami,
and I can make water, fire,
anything appear out of this box.
Yay.
What would you like to see first?
-Uh, fire.
-Okay.
Fire appear!
Wow, that was great.
Now water appear!
How does he do it?
[laughing]
Water vanish!
[sizzles]
Squirtle.
-Char?
-[grumbling] Squirtle. Squirtle.
Squirtle. Squirtle.
-Bulbasaur.
-Squirtle!
-Char.
Cut it out!
What's happening?
Stop it. Quit fighting!
Ah!
[screams]
[all whimper]
Squirtle
I guess I need a bigger box.
-Squirtle
-Char.
[all] Exeggcute.
So the only Pokémon you have
are Exeggcute?
That's right.
They don't really do very much, do they?
[all]
Exeggcute! Exeggcute! Exeggcute!
Why are you staring at me?
[all]
Exeggcute! Exeggcute! Exeggcute!
[all] Exeggcute!
Stop it, Ash.
A staring contest
isn't going to get you anywhere.
-I'd like all of you to stop now.
-Exeggcute.
-Okay.
-[all] Huh?
Turn around three times
and act like a Bulbasaur.
-Exeggcute.
-Bulbasaur. Bulbasaur. Bulbasaur.
-Pika-pi--
-What's with Ash?
He's acting kind of weird.
Hmm.
Aha.
Keep going straight into the leaf forest.
-Exegg--
-Yes, master.
I hate to do this to you,
but I hate exercise.
It looks like that magician
has the little brat under his spell.
They're just where we want them.
What's our plan?
We follow them and see what they're up to,
then we make our move.
With Melvin?
Yeah, someone saw them
headed for the leaf forest.
Pika-pika pika.
Ash and Melvin must have just
come through here.
But why would Ash have gone with Melvin?
-Wait a minute.
-Huh?
[all]
Exeggcute. Exeggcute. Exeggcute.
What if Ash was put under hypnosis attack
by those Exeggcute
and now they're controlling him?
They belong to Melvin,
so he's making Ash do whatever he wants.
-Mm-hm. Keep looking, Pikachu.
-Pika.
Stop.
[Exeggcute] Exegg!
Now, Ash, you say
that you want to become a Pokémon master.
-Yes.
-Then use your Pokédex
-and tell me what those are.
-Yes.
[Pokédex]
Exeggutor. A coconut Pokémon.
Also known
as the walking tropical rainforest.
Each coconut has a distinct face
and its own character.
Its special attack is hypnosis.
I'd like you to battle these Exeggutor
for me.
Yes, master.
Charmander, Squirtle, Bulbasaur, attack.
-Squirtle.
-Bulbasaur.
-Char. Char!
-[Exeggutor roaring]
Now I'll capture all the ones you weaken.
One Exeggutor.
Squirtle!
Now I've got two Exeggutor.
-Char!
-Exeggutor.
Squirtle!
Bulbasaur!
I've got another one and another one
and another one and another one.
Char!
[roaring]
Bulbasaur!
[laughing]
[all panting]
Look at all the Exeggutor I've caught.
-That's all for now.
-Yes.
Return, everyone.
Now that I've captured these Exeggutor,
I can put everyone at the carnival
under hypnosis
and command all of them
to come see my magic show.
At last, I'm finally on my way
to Las Vegas.
[all] Exeggcute! Exeggcute!
In your dreams.
Who's that?
Prepare for trouble.
Make it double.
-To protect the world from devastation.
-To unite all peoples within our nation.
They look more like magicians than I do.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the stars above.
Jessie.
-James.
-Alakazam kalamazoo!
Pesto!
That was great. You guys are wonderful.
[Jessie] It's not over yet.
Team Rocket.
Blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth. That's right.
[laughs]
If you were a real magician,
you'd be able to do tricks like that.
That's right.
They're right. My magic stinks.
You obviously have no talent
as a magician,
but you're good
at catching Exeggutor for us.
Now we'll make them disappear.
And we'll use their hypnotic power
to capture all of the Pokémon
in the world.
No, you can't.
-You have...
-...no choice.
Stop it. Let me go.
-Hey.
-Huh?
Be quiet,
or I'll knock the cholesterol out of you.
[all] Exeggcute.
That's better.
Now, there's something
we need you to do for us.
[all] Exeggcute. Exeggcute.
-Huh?
-It's looking at us strangely.
Yeah.
-Could it be...
-...some sort of magic?
-No, it's...
-...evolving.
Exeggutor.
[all] It's an Exeggutor.
-Uh, I'm feeling...
-A bit sleepy.
Hypnosis waves are coming out of its eyes.
Well, then just don't make eye contact.
[all] Exeggutor.
Too late.
-I'm going...
-...under.
-Good work, Exeggutor.
-Exeggutor.
Exeggutor, no more hypnosis.
[all] Exeggutor.
Exeggutor. Exeggutor. Exeggutor.
What happened?
Hey, where are all of you going?
Whoa.
I don't get the respect I think I deserve.
Ah. Look, over there.
The forest is moving.
That's no forest.
That's a herd of Exeggutor.
[both scream]
What...? What's going on? Ah!
-Team Rocket.
-Exeggutor. Exeggutor.
Ash. Ash.
-Are you okay, Ash?
-Melvin.
Pikachu, you've got to do something
to help Ash, quick.
-Pikachu!
-Ah!
What's going on?
I don't remember anything.
You were under deep hypnosis.
Hypnosis? Oh, yeah. Where's Melvin?
Ash.
What's going on here?
What have you done, Melvin?
The Exeggutor used hypnosis on each other
and got all confused.
The Exeggutor are heading into town
right now, Ash.
Oh, we got to stop them.
Now they're beyond my control.
[grunts]
[lively music playing]
[creaking]
-Hey, what's that noise?
-[woman] The forest is moving.
No. Those are Exeggutor.
-[crowd screaming]
-Exeggutor. Exeggutor. Exeggutor.
Looks bad.
They must have stampeded
right through the carnival.
-Hey! You better get out of here!
-Huh?
[all] Hm?
Those Exeggutor are coming back this way.
I've planted a time bomb in this clearing.
It'll blow up
just as they make it to this field.
[explosion]
You can't.
Those Exeggutor are under hypnosis.
They don't realize what they're doing.
It's not their fault.
Who cares? We can't let them cause
any more damage to the town.
Now, get out of here and fast!
Wait. Come back.
Oh, why are people so stubborn?
-What are we supposed to do now?
-Now I'll have to stop them myself.
You're coming with us, Melvin.
[all] Exeggutor. Exeggutor. Exeggutor.
Squirtle. Bulbasaur. Charmander. Attack!
Squirtle, water gun.
Squirt!
That should wake 'em up.
Ash, it looks like
they're liking the water.
Bulbasaur, razor leaf attack now.
Don't prune them. Stop them.
Squirtle and Bulbasaur, return.
Charmander, flamethrower.
Char!
The Exeggutor are waking up.
Stop, Exeggutor!
Exeggutor are weak against fire.
All right. Charmander,
rapid fire flamethrower attack.
Char!
-Char!
Exeggutor! Exeggutor!
Hurry, Ash. Don't forget, that time bomb's
going to go off any second.
I know. I know, but--
Char!
-Oh, Charmander.
-Pika.
We've got to stop those Exeggutor
before they reach the time bomb.
Wait. I've got it.
Melvin, you can wake all of the Exeggutor
at the same time
with your fire magic trick.
Huh? But all I ever do
is make a mess of things.
I can't do it.
But, Melvin, you have to try.
You said it was your dream
to be a magician.
You've got to wake these Exeggutor
for their sake and for yours.
[sighs]
I know I can't do it.
You can do it.
Just look at Ash's Charmander.
If that little Pokémon worked that hard,
then you have to at least try.
[sighs]
Then I'll give it my best shot.
Melvin.
Melvin, Charmander, it's up to you.
-Char.
-Uh-huh.
-Raging fire!
-Char!
[all] Exeggutor. Exeggutor.
-Who?
-What?
Where?
[all scream]
[Exeggutor]
Exeggutor. Exeggutor. Exeggutor.
-I did it.
-[Exeggutor] Exeggutor. Exeggutor.
I did it.
I really did it.
-Yeah. A great job, Melvin.
-[all] Huh?
Exeggutor, your hypnosis spell is broken.
This is so wonderful.
Wow. That was a close call.
You're right.
Thank goodness no one was hurt.
Char. Char?
What's the matter, Charmander?
Pika?
Charmander looks funny.
It's evolving.
[Pokédex]
Charmeleon, the flame Pokémon.
It has razor-sharp claws
and its tail is exceptionally strong.
Congratulations, Charmander.
I mean, Charmeleon.
Char.
Hey, watch where you're breathing.
[laughter]
[Misty] Never forget your dream.
[Ash] Practice makes perfect.
[Brock] See you in Las Vegas.
Thank you, all of you.
[all] Goodbye.
[narrator] A big day,
our heroes enjoyed a carnival,
helped Melvin The Magician stop
a herd of rampaging Exeggutor
and Charmander evolved into Charmeleon.
But what about Team Rocket?
-[grunts] Watch who you're shoving.
-Get me out of here.
[all] Looks like
Team Rocket's marching off again!
♪ Pokémon! ♪
It's that time again!
A hundred and fifty Pokémon,
five days a week.
That's about 30 or so each day.
It's not too hard.
Just listen real good.
♪ Alakazam, Goldeen, Venonat
Machoke, Kangaskhan, Hypno ♪
♪ Electabuzz, Flareon, Blastoise
Poliwhirl, Oddish, Drowzee ♪
♪ Raichu, Nidoqueen
Bellsprout, Starmie ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Metapod, Marowak, Kakuna
Clefairy, Dodrio, Seadra ♪
♪ Vileplume, Krabby, Lickitung
Tauros, Weedle, Nidoran ♪
♪ Machop, Shellder, Porygon, Hitmonchan ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon master is
My destiny ♪
Okay, so today was pretty easy.
But you gotta put all five days together.
It's only way the name all 150.
Catch you here tomorrow.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Ooh, Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Ooh, gotta catch them all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all!
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪