♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
[narrator] Ash and his friends have been
on the road for quite a while now,
so they've decided to take a little break
in a beautiful meadow.
[grunts] Psy-ay-ay.
-Uh, is this the one, Brock?
-Yeah. It's called Farfetch'd.
-Wow.
-Pika?
Hey, what are you looking at,
a new kind of Pokémon?
Uh, there was a rumor that one's been
spotted right near here.
It looks like it's holding a leek
in its wing.
Yeah.
[Pokédex] Farfetch'd,
a wild duck Pokémon.
Farfetch'd makes a delicious meal,
especially when cooked with leek.
Because of this,
Farfetch'd is nearly extinct.
[all gasp]
Hey, if it's that valuable,
I'll capture it.
There's supposed to be a spring nearby
and we need to get some water.
-You want to come?
-Yeah, I'll go with you.
-Great.
-Will you get some for me?
-Pretty please, Brock?
-Sure, Misty.
-Let's go, Pikachu.
-Pika.
Thanks, you guys.
Ah, my legs are tired from walking.
-Psy?
-Huh?
Psy-i-i!
Hey, I don't have the energy
to deal with you.
If I have to look at that face,
I'm going to get a headache.
-Psy.
-[sighs]
-Time for you to go back in your ball.
-[Farfetch'd] Farfetch'd!
-Psyduck, was that you?
-Psy?
-[Farfetch'd] Farfetch'd!
-Huh? [gasps] Who's that? Who's there?
[Farfetch'd] Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd.
Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd...
[gasp]
Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd.
Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd...
Wow, I don't believe it.
That's Farfetch'd, the rare Pokémon.
Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd.
Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd...
Look at that.
Ha, that's the coolest Pokémon ever.
Oh! While Ash and Brock are gone,
I'm going to capture it myself.
-[Farfetch'd gibbers]
-Huh?
-Hey, wait!
-Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd...
Wait. Come back, Farfetch'd!
Little Farfetch'd!
[panting]
Where are you hiding?
Come out, Farfetch'd!
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
[gibbering]
There it is. Uh.
Hey, wait! Come back, little Farfetch'd!
Hold on! Please wait for me!
-I won't hurt you, Farfetch'd.
-[Farfetch'd] Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd...
I'm in no mood for a marathon, Farfetch'd.
[groans]
-You won't get away from me!
-[Misty and man groan]
Ow, that hurt.
-I'm sorry. Are you okay?
-Yeah.
It's my fault.
I wasn't looking where I was going.
Well, I wasn't paying attention either.
I was chasing a Pokémon.
-Oh. Here you go.
-Thanks.
-See you.
-[Misty] Bye.
Oh, now I've lost track of Farfetch'd.
[groans]
[both] Huh? Hey, there she is.
Oh, how could I let it get away?
-[Ash] Misty!
-Huh?
Where'd you run off to?
Oh, I found a Farfetch'd
and tried to capture it but it got away.
[both] You tried to capture it?
Have you been sneaking around
behind our backs?
Huh? Of course not.
If I caught it,
it would have been all of ours.
Yeah, right.
Anyway, Farfetch'd is
an incredible Pokémon.
Oh, it's so cute
and it twirls it's leek like a baton.
-Huh?
-No lie?
I'm telling the truth this time.
-This time?
-Oops.
-Here, I brought you your water.
-Thanks, Brock.
[hums]
-Huh?
-What's wrong?
-Pikachu?
-I must have picked up the wrong backpack.
-[all gasp]
-Look.
[all gasping]
[laughs]
Just like taking candy from a baby,
eh, Farfetch'd?
Fetch. Far Farfetch'd...
Now, let's see what's inside.
Five Poké Balls?
This must be all of her Pokémon.
[laughs]
-And now they're mine.
-[both laugh]
You bumped into him?
That must have been
when the backpacks were switched.
How could this happen?
I had all the Pokémon
I ever caught in that backpack!
-[sobs]
-Pikachu.
[chuckles] That was too easy.
-[footsteps approaching]
-Huh?
-Farfetch'd. Far. Far. Farfetch'd.
What is it, Farfetch'd?
-Farfetch'd.
-Hm? Ah.
Are you sure there are Farfetch'd
out here in the middle of nowhere?
Trust me, we'll find some.
I hear people are spotting Farfetch'd
in this forest all the time.
-[Farfetch'd] Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd...
-[both] Huh?
-What's that?
-Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd...
Far. Far. Farfetch'd.
What amazing luck. We come to
look for it and it comes to us.
It tastes good and has good taste.
And it looks so happy to see us.
This Farfetch'd is mine.
Hi. Sounds like you guys
like my Farfetch'd.
-It's your Farfetch'd?
-It already has a master.
[all groan]
-But this is just perfect.
-[all] Huh?
I was just planning on getting rid
of my Farfetch'd anyway.
You guys want
to make a deal with me?
-[Meowth] For that Farfetch'd?
-Yeah.
I have a Starmie and a Staryu
in here too.
I guess I'm sort of getting tired
of raising Pokémon.
I'd be happy to find somebody
who'd take them off my hands.
Far. Farfetched'd!
[all] Huh?
[all laugh]
Aw, I'm sorry.
I forgot something back in the forest.
Would you mind watching my Poké Balls
and my Farfetch'd while I run and get it?
[all] Huh?
-Sure, we'd be glad to.
-Leave it to us.
We'll take care of them.
Thank you so much.
And I'll be right back.
-Be careful.
-Take your time.
-[man] Thanks!
-No problem.
-[chuckling]
-That sucker just lost one Farfetch'd.
This is easier than taking candy
from a baby.
Letting Team Rocket guard
your Pokémon is like
letting your cat guard your canary.
[laughs] I can't believe how stupid he is.
And look, he even left a boat for us
to make our getaway.
He's done all the work for us.
Too bad he didn't leave his recipe
for Farfetch'd flambé.
[laughing]
-[Jessie] Let's get going.
-[James] Right.
-And he left a Starmie and Staryu.
-Now they belong to us.
[laughs]
Heh, this was the simplest Pokémon
capture in Team Rocket history.
Maybe that's the key to success.
Maybe we should just let good things
happen to bad people.
-And Pokémon.
-We've found our winning formula.
[laughing]
[screams]
[all grunt]
-Quick, plug that hole before we sink.
-That kid rigged the boat.
[both gasp and grunt]
[laughs]
[both groaning]
Plug it up tighter!
The water's getting in. We're going to--
[all gurgling]
[all gasping]
-My Weezing!
-Arbok and Lickitung are floating away.
We can use his Starmie and Staryu
to bring them back.
Right. Good idea.
-Huh? What's this?
-What's what?
-Ah. Oh, no.
-That little twerp tricked us!
-But why would he do it?
-Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd.
Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd.
Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd...
Back off, birdbrain!
Those are my Pokémon!
-And that's my Weezing.
-[groans]
Come back here.
[both] Give us back our Pokémon.
[grunts]
[all screaming]
Far-far-far-far-far-far!
-Farfetch'd.
-Hey, that's nice work, Farfetch'd.
[laughs] Now they're mine. All mine.
[Misty] And then he ran off.
I think he might have taken
my backpack by accident.
-The Farfetch'd came and then did a trick.
-Yeah.
-I'm sorry but that was no accident.
-What do you mean by that?
This has happened before?
You're the fifth victim of
the backpack-switching thief this week.
[gasping]
You were tricked by that boy
and his Farfetch'd.
Jenny, you have to help me.
That thief and Farfetch'd stole
every Pokémon I had.
I've been trying to track him down for
a while but never he stays in one place.
-He's a slippery one, that kid.
-[sighs]
We've been together for a long time,
Farfetch'd.
Right after I found you injured on
the road and nursed you back to health,
-we started stealing.
-Farfetch'd.
I wish there was some other way
for us to get by,
but... how else are we
ever going to survive?
-We're just too weak to battle.
-Farfetch'd.
Psyduck. Psyduck.
[man] Well, I think our stew is ready.
We're going to find that no-good,
rotten crook and show him
what good rotten crooks are like.
I can't wait. And I can't believe
he tricked us so easily.
-It's because you were so stupid.
-Ah!
But Meowth was the one
who fell for his trick in the first place.
Let's not fight. Let's save all
our nastiness for that lousy kid.
This is it.
This is the place I ran into him.
-Maybe he lives somewhere nearby.
-Hmm.
Oh, I can't believe
he stole all my Pokémon.
Staryu, Starmie, Goldeen and Horsea.
-Misty, you forgot Psyduck.
-Oh, I wish I could forget Psyduck.
Psy. Psy. Psyduck.
-Look, it's Psyduck.
-[all] Huh?
Ah, I'm so happy to see you.
I missed you so much.
-But how did you get back here?
-Psyduck.
-Where's my backpack now?
-What about the other Pokémon?
-Psyduck.
-Where did he take you?
-Well, then how did you get away?
-Psyduck.
-[Misty] Where's the guy who stole you?
-And where's that Farfetch'd?
-Psyduck.
Come on, you dumb duck!
Start thinking straight!
-Ah, now you're giving me a headache!
-Psyduck.
Okay, Psyduck, tell us which way to go.
Left or right?
-Psyduck.
-[grunts angrily]
What's wrong with you?
Can't you remember anything?
-Hey, Misty, chill out.
-Yeah, Misty, you've got to relax.
Psyduck's trying as hard as he can
to remember where the others are.
-Psy-ay.
-Huh? To the left?
-Are you sure about this?
-Psy-ay.
-You better be!
-Following directions from a Psyduck
-doesn't sound like a good idea.
-Pikachu.
-We keep getting more Pokémon.
-Farfetch'd.
Well, if we meet someone on the road,
we'll just have to take their Pokémon too.
-Farfetch'd. Far.
-[Meowth] There he is!
Huh?
-Hold it, buster.
-You won't get away now.
-What are you doing here?
-Fetch'd far.
You thought you were going
to get away with it, didn't you?
Sinking that boat
and grabbing our Pokémon.
Now we're going to make you pay
for making fools of us.
Hey, come on, can't you guys take a joke?
I meant what I said.
I really am sick of raising Pokémon.
I've got so many.
Look, I'll give you Arbok and Weezing
and Lickitung and we'll call it even.
Nice try.
You can't make it up
by just giving them back.
-[man] No, you're right.
-[all] Huh?
So I'll give you all of these
and my apologies.
What? You mean all of these?
Don't worry about it.
Go ahead and take them.
-Well, since he's being so generous.
-We'll have to forgive him.
I'm glad I ran into you guys.
I was planning on moving anyway
but I just had too much stuff to carry.
-Oh, lucky you.
-Yeah.
So please forgive me
and good luck.
-[all] What a haul.
-There's so many of them.
Well, it looks like the kid
wasn't so bad after all.
[both] Mm-hmm.
-Psy.
-That's the kid.
[all] Huh?
-Good work, Psyduck. You found him.
You act like a quack most of the time
but you're pretty smart, Psyduck.
Psy?
-Well, I guess we better get going.
-Fetch'd far, far.
-[Misty] Stop right there.
-Ah!
Give me back my Pokémon right now,
you thief.
-Pika, Pika.
-Oh, no.
You're under arrest
for grand theft Pokémon.
-You're crime spree is over.
-Farfetch'd far.
What makes you think it was okay
to lie and cheat people
so you could steal their Pokémon?
It takes a lot of love and care
to raise Pokémon.
We worked real hard to train them all
to win their Pokémon battles.
-That's right.
-Maybe we should start off
by showing this kid just how
difficult a Pokémon match is.
-Good idea.
-Huh?
-That's right, a battle.
-Wait a minute.
Farfetch'd is too weak.
We had no other choice.
That's not true at all.
Pokémon will become stronger
with trainers who work with them.
-But Farfetch'd isn't--
-Fetch'd far, far.
-Huh? You mean you want to battle?
-Far Farfetch'd.
-But Farfetch'd--
-Good. Let's start our Pokémon battle.
-Bulbasaur.
-Fetch'd. Far. Far.
-Wait, Farfetch'd.
-Go for it, Bulbasaur! Tackle attack!
[grunting]
-Farfetch'd!
-Farfetch'd, stop.
-Bulbasaur, vine whip attack.
-Bulba.
Farfetch'd, no!
At least now you can see the right way
to capture Pokémon in the wild.
-Farfetch'd
-Please stop, Farfetch'd!
-You can't win this!
-Farfetch'd! Farfetch'd! Farfetch'd!
-Farfetch'd!
-Bulbasaur!
Farfetch'd! Farfetch'd!
-Huh?
-What's that?
-It's Farfetch'd's agility.
-Pika.
I didn't know Farfetch'd could do that.
[grunting]
[singing]
-Bulbasaur, are you okay?
-Pika?
[groans]
I never thought Farfetch'd
had attacks like that.
Huh? You really didn't know
about its powers?
No. If I had known it was this strong,
I wouldn't have used it to steal.
[sighs]
You can't judge a Pokémon
by the way it looks.
[groans]
-All right, Pikachu, your turn.
-Pika.
-Pika, pika.
-Hold it.
He robbed me,
so it's my job to battle him.
I choose you, Staryu!
Oh, I forgot.
I didn't get my Poké Balls back yet.
[both grunt]
-Psyduch-si.
-Far.
-Psyduck?
-Psy?
[laughs]
[grunting]
[Misty in mind] Here's my chance.
Come on, Farfetch'd!
Give Psyduck your best shot!
Hit. Hit. Hit. Hit. Hit. Hit...
Psy!
It's working.
Psyduck's headache is getting worse.
-Just a little more.
-Pikachu.
-Hit. Hit. Hit. Hit. Hit. Hit. Hit. Hit...
-Psy!
-Hit... [squawks]
-Farfetch'd, no!
That's it! Psyduck's absolute
migraine attack, disable.
[both screaming]
[both groaning]
-You did it, Psyduck!
-Psyduck!
I'm embarrassed
for ever doubting that kid.
Let's open up these Poké Balls
and find out what kind
of great Pokémon he gave us.
-Voltorb.
-All of them are Voltorb.
-That two timer.
-He tricked us two times in one episode.
[all] We'll get him for this.
[screaming]
I'm sorry!
I won't do anything bad anymore!
Farfetch'd!
Forgive me.
I'll give back all the Pokémon I stole.
None the victims are going
to press charges
since they all got their Pokémon back.
-[man] That's good.
-It's great to have my old backpack back.
It was wrong to steal and it was wrong
not to believe in Farfetch'd.
Fetch'd far, far.
Now I'm going to train Farfetch'd
to become even stronger.
Great. That's the way it should be.
Now you see that Pokémon can be
anything a good trainer wants it to be.
-Yeah. Thanks a lot.
-Far Farfetch'd.
-See you. Let's go, Farfetch'd.
-Farfetch'd.
-Good luck, you two.
-Take care.
[gibbers]
[narrator] Misty might have lost her
Pokémon for good,
but thanks to a little help
from Psyduck.
Psy-ay.
Or rather, thanks to a lot
of help from Psyduck.
Psy.
Her Pokémon were returned safely
and everyone learned an important lesson
about honesty, bravery and trust.
[Meowth] Are you sure you want
to tell the boss about this?
[James] Team Rocket can't allow anyone
to steal Pokémon. That's our job.
[Jessie] Right, James.
-[Meowth] Wrong.
-[both] Huh?
If we tell the boss
how the kid outsmarted us,
he'll want to make him part
of Team Rocket.
-Ah, and then...
-He'll be in and we'll be out.
-[Meowth] Exactly.
-[both] Oh, no!
Then we'll just have to tell him...
Absolutely nothing about that kid
or Farfetch'd.
-[both] Okay?
-Precisely. That's what we'll do.
-Voltorb. Voltorb.
-Oh, no, there's one left.
Voltorb.
[all] Looks like Team Rocket's
blasting off again!
-♪ Pokémon! ♪
-Attention all Pokémon trainers
Do you got what it takes
To be the best?
Today we'll do 30 Pokémon.
It's the ultimate test!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Articuno, Jynx, Nidorina, Beedrill
Haunter, Squirtle, Chansey, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Parasect, Exeggcute, Muk, Dewgong
Pegeotto, Lapras, Vulpix, Rhydon ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon master
Is my destiny ♪
♪ Charizard, Machamp, Pinsir, Koffing
Dugtrio, Golbat, Staryu, Magikarp ♪
♪ Ninetales, Ekans, Omastar
Scyther, Tentacool, Dragonair, Magmar ♪
Not bad, not bad.
Hey, don't get cocky.
Tomorrow's the hardest part.
We're on our way up to 150 Pokémon.
There's no stopping us!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Gotta catch them all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪