♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that’s inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Its you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you’re my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪
[narrator]
After winning a rainbow badge from Erika,
Ash and his friends find themselves
in a new city.
Gee, it sort of feels like
all these buildings are closing in on us.
Yeah and they're all so tall,
you can hardly see any sky.
-Where are we, Brock?
-Uh, Hophophop Town?
[both] Hop, hop, hop?
Chu. Pikachu?
-[woman] Arnold!
-Huh?
Arnold!
[Ash grunts]
Where have you been, Arnold?
Mother's been so worried.
-Huh?
-Pika?
Excuse me, but my name is Ash.
And my name is Misty, ma'am.
She wasn't talking to you, Misty.
I guess not. Ah!
Oh! I'm so sorry.
But you look just like my Arnold.
-Huh?
-What happened to him?
[Ash] Hypnos Naptime
I'm so upset
because my son Arnold just disappeared.
He's been gone for three days.
I can't find him anywhere.
-And you haven't heard from him?
-Not a word.
Could he have gone off
to become a Pokémon trainer?
He did like Pokémon of course,
but he never mentioned anything
about becoming a trainer.
Don't you think
he'll probably just come home soon?
Mm-mm. My son isn't the only child
who's disappeared recently.
-[Brock] He's not?
-[Ash] Huh?
[woman] See those posters?
[Ash] Posters?
Those are pictures of all the children
that have disappeared.
[Misty] That many?
This must be a pretty dangerous town.
My picture's going to be on posters
when I'm a big, famous star.
[both sigh]
-Huh?
-Excuse me.
-Well, maybe in horror movies.
-Pikachu.
[woman] They certainly were nice children,
all of them.
Disappearing one by one like that?
I just can't understands it.
Hmm, let's see.
Where should I hang this one?
Excuse me.
Are you the cousin or second cousin
of the Jenny in Maiden's Peak?
Actually, I'm here cousin's cousin.
It figures.
This one's the most beautiful one yet.
They're all exactly alike.
It must be terrible
searching for all these lost children.
I would be very happy
to help you in your search.
-What?
-We can both work together hand in hand.
Hmm. Just don't get in the way.
[Brock chuckles]
[Ash]
Gee, she reminds me of...
My mom.
-She must be worried.
-Pikachu.
-You think so too, huh?
-Pika.
Well, in that case, Detective Ash Ketchum
will solve this mystery.
-Pika!
-[Misty sighs]
All of the missing children
disappeared exactly three days ago.
Three days ago?
Besides that, do the missing children
have anything else in common?
That's a brilliant deduction.
The missing children
must have something in common.
-They don't have a thing in common.
-Hmm.
But I think other kids may know
something about it.
[Brock] I see. So we'll ask the kids
in the Pokémon Center
if they know anything.
That's it, Brock. Brilliant deduction.
-Have you seen this little boy before?
-I haven't.
Yeah, I play with them all the time.
-When was the last time you saw him?
-I don't know.
You two had better answer
all these questions truthfully.
-Okay.
-Now, tell this beautiful young lady
everything you know.
[whimpers]
You do think she's beautiful, don't you?
Come on, what do you say?
Now you're getting in the way.
Ah, I bet you're related to the Joy
from Maiden's Peak, aren't you?
Well, you'd win that bet.
We're here about the missing children.
Oh, those kids who disappeared
all of a sudden.
I saw it on the news.
Please, is there anything you can tell us
about these children?
I'd like to help you, but right now,
I'm afraid I've got my hands full
with our own mystery.
[Misty] What do you mean?
What's the matter?
All the Pokémon here at the center
are behaving very strangely.
[both] Huh?
Just look at Cubone... and Oddish.
Even Magikarp is affected
and it's usually full of life.
The magic's disappeared.
Looks like it's ready
for the deli counter.
The flame on this Charmander
could go out any minute.
Oh.
And this one's
been in just terrible shape.
-Psy-yi-yi.
-What is it?
[Pokédex] Psyduck, a water Pokémon.
Uses mysterious power
to perform various attacks.
-Mysterious powers?
-That's hard to believe.
-So, what's causing all this?
-I have no idea.
How long have they been acting like this?
-Since three days ago.
-Three days ago?
And that's exactly when all those children
disappeared, isn't it?
I wonder if maybe
there's some kind of connection
between the children's disappearance
and the Pokémon's lack of energy.
Hm, one mystery leads to another.
One more puzzle for the mind
of Ash Ketchum, master detective.
Hm...
-Did you think of anything yet?
-Not a thing.
[all sigh]
Something's very strange.
[buzzing]
Huh?
-Is that your radio?
-Hm-mm.
[buzzing]
It's picking up something.
I bet I know what that is.
A handsome guy detector.
Don't kid yourself. [grunts]
-This is a sleep wave detector.
-A sleep wave detector?
Lately, I've been picking up sleep waves.
-What are they?
-Wavelengths that induce sleep.
But I'm sure there aren't any Pokémon
that emit that wavelength in this center.
They're from outside.
Pikachu.
Oh, no.
Look, even Pikachu's losing energy.
I wonder if those sleep waves
and the Pokémons' condition are--
Yeah, they may be connected.
Hey, Pikachu, wake up, pal.
[groans]
I think we'd better find the source
of these sleep waves.
[all] Mm-hm.
[bleeping]
I knew it.
The sleep waves are coming from this town.
Now we can get our wish.
We'll find the source of the waves.
And we'll use them to knock out the boss.
Then while he's fast asleep,
we can take a break.
While the boss is conked out,
I'll take a fishing expedition.
[all sobbing]
[Jessie] We've all been working
so hard at being bad.
[James] Even if we always fail.
Maybe we're not so good,
but we need a vacation bad.
[all wailing]
[buzzing]
[gasps]
They're coming from this building.
[Ash] Whoa, it's so tall.
-They seem to be coming from the roof.
-Let's go.
As we go up,
the signal's getting stronger.
[dinging]
[buzzing faster]
[Ash] Wha... What's that?
[Brock]
A mansion on top of the skyscraper?
-It's coming from inside there.
-All right.
Wait, Ash.
-What now?
-There's someone inside.
I'm going in.
[both] Ready, set...
[grunting]
Unh. Huh?
-Huh?
-Oh.
[both] Huh? Huh?
-What is this place?
-What's going on here?
Are you new members?
Uh, members?
-Uh...
-We've been monitoring
some sleep waves coming from up here.
Sleep waves? Oh, I know.
-This Hypno must have been emitting them.
-Hypno?
[Pokédex]
Hypno, a hypnosis Pokémon.
It carries a pendulum-like device
and performs hypnotic attacks.
[Ash] Huh.
[Misty] And what's that next to it?
Drowzee, said to be a descendent
of the dream-eating tapir.
It was the first Pokémon
to use a combination attack
like hypnosis and dream eater.
I think a Hypno is the evolved form
of a Drowzee, isn't it?
Yes, that's correct.
And our Drowzee finally evolved
into a Hypno.
Three days ago.
-Three days ago?
-I knew it.
That's just when those children vanished
and the Pokémon started to lose
-all their energy.
-[all] Mm-hm.
We've been using the Pokémon
instead of using sleeping medicine.
What do you mean we?
The members of the Pokémon Lover's Club.
-The Pokémon Lover's Club?
-Precisely.
You see, all of our members
absolutely adore Pokémon,
and well, Hypno has become
our favorite Pokémon.
Everyone's hard work paid off
when Drowzee finally evolved.
Oh?
Living our lives in the city
can be very stressful
and all the members suffer from insomnia,
so we've come to rely on Hypno's powers
to help us get to sleep at night.
Hypno. Hypno. Hypno.
Hypno's sleep waves
must have affected all those Pokémon
by zapping their energy.
[gasps]
Take a look at my Pikachu.
Pika.
The same thing happened to all
of the Pokémon at the Pokémon Center.
It must be a--
-A side effect?
-Side effect?
Mm, Hypno's hypnotic powers
are usually just used
only on other Pokémon.
Since the wavelength was changed
to affect humans,
it's creating a side effect
for the Pokémon.
-Yeah.
-Hm.
Somehow, we've accidentally caused
a terrible situation.
[Brock] You know what?
I'll bet that new wavelength
can even affect some kids
that are sensitive to it too.
-[Ash] Kids?
-Yeah.
[Pikachu mumbles]
Let's see.
Hypno. Hypno. Hypno.
Seel, Seel. Seel, Seel. Seel, Seel.
Misty, what's the matter?
Misty's being controlled
by the sleep wave.
We've gotta do something. Aah!
Aah! Hey, Misty!
Where are you going?
Misty, come back! Ugh!
[clapping]
Seel, Seel, Seel.
I can't believe there's a park this big
in the middle of the city.
Seel, Seel, Seel.
[panting]
[all gasp]
Seel, Seel. Seel, Seel. Seel, Seel.
[girl chittering]
Coo, coo.
Bulbasaur. Bulbasaur. Bulbasaur.
These are all the missing children.
Whee!
[chittering]
Gloom, Gloom, Gloom. Gloom.
What's happening?
Why are they acting that way?
-Pokémonitis.
-Pokémonitis?
With that new wavelength,
the children who were exposed
to Hypno's sleep waves
think that they're Pokémon now.
-And it got Misty too?
-Yeah.
Seel, Seel. Seel, Seel.
How on earth could a thing like this
have happened?
Magikarp, Magikarp, Magikarp.
-Bulbasaur!
-Magikarp, Magikarp, Magikarp.
All right, wake up, everyone.
It's time to go home.
Come on. Stop this.
Wake up now, kids.
All of your mothers are worried sick.
Ugh! Magikarp, Magikarp.
-It's just no use.
-What can we do?
Hmm.
Say, I know.
What if we use Drowzee
to cure the children?
Drowzee?
Sleep emits dream wavelengths,
which, in this case, may counteract
Hypno's wavelengths.
Hmm, yeah, that might just work.
Let's give it a try.
Seel, Seel. Seel, Seel. Seel, Seel.
Drowzee, emit your dream waves
and focus them toward this girl.
Drowzee. Drowzee. Drowzee.
-Seel, Seel. Seel, Seel. Seel, Seel.
-Drowzee. Drowzee. Drowzee.
-Whoa, Misty.
-She must be in a pretty deep trance.
Drowzee. Drowzee. Drowzee.
Drowzee!
Huh? Hey, where am I?
Gee, Misty, you're looking kind of beat.
When I want your opinion, I'll ask for it.
-She's back to normal.
-Huh?
Now we've got use Drowzee's sleep waves
on all those kids in the park.
Okay, now we've gotta get those kids
back to normal.
You mean I thought I was a Pokémon?
Yeah, you turned completely into a Seel.
-What's what?
-Whatever it is, it's coming this way.
Oh, no. Not them.
[Jessie] Prepare for trouble.
[James] Make it double.
To protect the world from devastation.
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Ha, Jessie.
-James.
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth. That's flight.
Now to swoop down
and swipe those hypnosis Pokémon.
[all] Ah!
[grunting]
Nice three-point landing.
Team Rocket is here to take possession
of Drowzee and Hypno.
You're dreaming.
Well, we'll just have to see
who's dreaming after this.
If Hypno can put anything to sleep,
try this.
Now, wait.
If you have any pride
as a hypnosis Pokémon, you'll do it.
This is known as the Team Rocket
"mirror, mirror on the wall
who's the sleepiest of them all"
dirty trick strategy.
Just don't hypnotize me.
Okay, do it.
Hypno. Hypno. Hypno.
-You've got to do something, Ash.
-There's not much time.
[Ash grunts]
-Huh?
-[grunts]
And we thought so hard
to come up with that strategy.
-Hyah!
-Ha!
We got 'em!
-Now we'll just fly away with our catch.
-I don't get it.
Why didn't we do this from the beginning?
We have to fill a half hour.
[grunts]
Hang on, Ash.
Go, Staryu!
[grunts]
[both scream]
Pidgeotto, go!
Pidgeo!
Okay, Pidgeotto, powerful gust.
[shrieks]
[all screaming]
Give them your best blast.
Pidgeo!
[all screaming]
I suppose this means
that we blew it again.
We blew it again. We blew it sky-high.
And what goes up must always come down.
[all] Looks like Team Rocket's
blasting off again!
-Come on, guys. Let's go.
-Right.
Drowzee. Drowzee.
[Brock]
They're all dreaming.
Pikachu too.
Drowzee.
Hey, how did I get
into the middle of the park?
Me too. And I should be working
on becoming a Pokémon trainer.
I want to be a fireman.
And I'm going to be a doctor.
-[boy] Let's go home.
-[girl] See you later.
-Pika.
-Huh?
Whoa!
[sputtering]
[Ash chuckles]
Pikachu.
Pikachu! It sounds like you're back
to your old self.
-[woman] Arnold!
-Huh?
[panting]
It's that mother we met.
Mommy.
-That's great.
-Yeah.
Ash, we've gotta cure the Pokémon
at the Pokémon Center too.
Right.
Drowzee. Drowzee.
-Cubone, bone.
-Oddish, Oddish.
Charmander!
Magikarp, karp, karp. Magi.
Heh. The Pokémon are all back to normal.
Sometimes I wonder
what the Pokémon dream about.
I'd love to know that too.
They must have been dreaming
of getting stronger and evolving.
I dream about that sometimes too.
[giggles]
Well, that's just one more case
solved by Ash Ketchum, master detective.
Excuse me, but you didn't solve anything.
Are you joking?
[laughs]
Pika.
[sighs]
What's the matter?
A beautiful woman shouldn't have
too much to be sad about.
All of the Pokémon are better,
but this one's still holding its head.
Leave it to me.
Caring for Pokémon is the sole purpose
of my life, the reason I exist.
Then maybe you can help it.
-Oh.
-Psyduck. Psy.
Well, you were the one who said,
"Leave it to me," Brock.
But Psyduck is a water Pokémon.
You better take it, Misty.
Why would I want
such a boring Pokémon?
[Pokédex] Psyduck,
constantly suffers from a headache.
You mean this thing always has a headache?
[screams]
My Poké Ball.
Psy? Duck?
Psy!
Oh, no. Now it's in my Poké Ball?
Good work, Misty. You captured Psyduck.
Oh, now I've got the headache.
[narrator] And so Misty effortlessly
captures Psyduck
and the mysteries were all solved.
-Congratulations.
-Don't congratulate me!
Psy-yi-yi.
You guys up for the Pokérap?
There’s 150 Pokémon.
You gotta name 'em all!
I’m doing 32 today,
so try to keep up.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Zubat, Primeape, Meowth, Onix ♪
♪ Geodude, Rapidash, Magneton, Snorlax ♪
♪ Gengar, Tangela, Goldeen, Spearow ♪
♪ Weezing, Seel, Gyarados, Slowbro ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Kabuto, Persian, Paras, Horsea ♪
♪ Raticate, Magnemite
Kadabra, Weepinbell ♪
♪ Ditto, Cloyster, Caterpie, Sandshrew ♪
♪ Bulbasaur, Charmander, Golem, Pikachu ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
All right, how’d you do?
Loosen those lips.
Shake out that tongue!
Give it a rest, today’s song is sung.
We’ll be back tomorrow!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that’s inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Its you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you’re my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon ♪