♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all!
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny,
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
Pokémon!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
[narrator] With fond memories
of the Safari Zone fresh in their minds,
our heroes continue on their journey.
Feels weird to be back in a city,
huh, Misty?
Sure does.
Being out in the jungle was great,
but it's kind of nice
to come back to civilization.
Hey, Pikachu, let's have a humongous meal
when we get to the Pokémon Center.
Pi, pika! Pika!
[Misty] I want a hot dog.
[Brock] I want a deep-dish,
extra-cheese pizza. Mm!
-Hey, what's that thing?
-What thing?
-Let's go see!
-Wait for us, Ash!
[all gasp]
Wow! Look at that!
Pika!
That's an amazing bridge.
-So it's been completed already.
-Huh?
Hey. The map says
it's still under construction.
But if it's completed, we can go straight
to Sunny Town on the opposite shore
without going all the way around.
Great! We'll cross the bridge
and get to the next town.
Come on. Let's go! [laughs]
Pika!
Well, I'm afraid the bridge
isn't completely finished.
See there?
[all] Huh?
That means we can't take the shortcut.
Even if it were finished,
this bridge is only for cars anyway.
The bridge is only for cars?
Couldn't we just walk across it?
Well, this bridge is over ten miles long.
It'd be dark
before you reached the other side.
Ten miles long?
Of course you might be able to cross
if you had bicycles.
Bicycles!
[bell rings]
-[man] Hey, Norman!
-Ride safely.
I thought you said
the bridge isn't finished.
The road isn't finished,
but the bicycle path is.
-[woman] Hi!
-Hi, girls!
If you had bikes, you could cross too.
Wish we did.
- [Misty] Well...
-Oh!
If a certain someone here
hadn't totally destroyed my bike,
we could be just zipping
right across this bridge now, couldn't we?
Well, yeah. Maybe.
[laughs]
Hmm...
It's no use. We can't afford these.
Pika.
[all groan]
Let's go to the Pokémon Center
and figure out a plan.
Sounds good to me.
I'll probably come up
with a brilliant idea.
Well, what's your brilliant plan?
Will you be quiet?
I'm still thinking of it.
[groans]
[gasps]
[all] Hm...
Excuse me, if you could spare some time,
would you mind helping me out?
[all] Huh?
[trembling]
Please let me help.
I just love caring for Pokémon.
It's my life. Please.
Please, miss. Miss.
Uh, by the way, are you by any chance
related to the Joy in Gringy City?
I'm her cousin.
Ah, but you're much, much prettier
than she is.
That's just fine, but...
I'm worried about the Pokémon
in Sunny Town,
just over the bridge, that's very sick.
-Oh. [gasps]
-Huh?
I need someone to deliver this medicine
to the Pokémon Center in Sunny Town.
Normally I'd go myself,
but I'm too busy with sick Pokémon
to leave the center right now.
-It's just over the bridge, right?
-That's right.
But we don't have any bicycles.
No problem.
I'll let you use some of our bicycles.
Huh?
-Huh?
-Hey...
[both laugh]
We'll do anything we can
if it's to help a sick Pokémon.
Even if that means we'll have to zip
across the bridge on bikes.
That's great.
The bikes are in the parking lot.
And thank you.
Bye!
[both laugh]
[groans]
I'd be happy to stay here
and help you if you need me.
Come on, Brock!
[screams]
[laughs] Hurry up, guys!
Brock, I'm doing all the pedaling.
Hmm.
Pika! Pika!
[both laughing]
You see, we're getting to cross the bridge
after all.
Right, Ash. We sure got lucky.
Pikachu!
They're riding on the bike path
across the bridge.
Ha! We've got them
right where we want them.
You think we got a chance this time?
Well, it's not like this place
is new to us, you know.
You could almost call it our hometown.
Isn't that right, James?
So we'll have the home team advantage.
James, prepare to attack.
I'm a little busy here.
[ship's klaxon blows]
Ah!
This is a great workout.
Yeah,
and since we lucked into those bikes,
it won't be long till we're in Sunny Town.
Right, Brock.
Ah!
Okay. Time to hit the road.
Huh?
[menacing laughter]
[boy] Yeah!
[all laughing]
[whooping and laughing]
Uh-oh. Who are they?
It's a bicycle gang.
[chuckling] Uh, a bicycle gang?
I think we better get out of here.
[menacing laughter]
[boy] Yeah!
[chuckles]
I don't think I've seen you before.
Uh, we're not really from around here,
so see you.
Hold it!
[all groan]
You're ain't going to cross this bridge
without a proper introduction.
-[boy 1] That's right.
-[boy 2] Get them, boss.
Uh, hello.
It's a pleasure.
Very nice to meet you.
[all]
See you again sometime!
That's no introduction!
When we say introduction,
we mean Pokémon battle.
A Pokémon battle?
All right. I accept.
I'd do anything for an introduction
to a girl like you.
Would you go out with me?
[Ash and Misty yell]
Ooh!
Get lost, loser.
I only care about my bike and my gang.
Is that a no?
All right.
Let's get started.
Then we'll see who's the master.
Huh.
You think you can play with the big boys?
I'll send you home crying.
Golem, go!
Golem!
What's that?
[Pokédex]
Golem. A megaton Pokémon.
Once a year, it sheds its bedrock shell
and grows larger.
Okay, then. I choose...
Bulbasaur!
Bulbasaur.
Bulbasaur. Vine whip.
Bulbasaur!
Your Pokémon needs more practice.
That wimpy vine whip attack is never
going to get through Golem's shell.
[groans]
All right, Golem. Tackle attack!
Golem!
Bulbasaur!
[screams]
Are you okay, Bulbasaur?
Bulbasaur.
[sighs]
Return, Bulbasaur.
Charmander, I choose you.
Char! Char!
Charmander. Ember!
Heh! Trying to heat things up?
It ain't going to happen.
Go, Golem! Rock throw now!
Golem! Go!
Char!
Charmander, flamethrower!
Charmander, fire spin now.
Char!
Golem!
Ha! I wonder how long it can take this.
[grunts] Golem. Tackle attack now.
Golem!
-Char!
-Charmander, run!
[screams]
[all laughing]
Golem, return.
Huh?
[yells]
Now it's my turn to show you.
I choose you, Cloyster.
Crush this wimp!
Cloys!
Huh? What's a Cloyster?
[Pokédex]
Cloyster. A bivalve Pokémon.
Its shell is incredibly strong
and resistant to a bomb.
Its shell only opens when it attacks.
-Okay, no sweat.
-It's a water Pokémon.
-Just leave it to me.
-Huh?
You battle?
[laughs] This should be quick.
[thinking] Which one would be best
against Cloyster's hard shell?
I know.
Starmie, go!
Psy?
Huh? Psyduck, what are you doing here?
I wanted Starmie, not you.
Psy?
Well, now that you're out, give it a try.
Psy-i-i-i!
Psyduck. Psyduck. Psyduck...
[laughing]
Psyduck. Psyduck. Psyduck.
[all laughing]
Psy? Psy?
I have never seen such a pathetic Pokémon.
[whimpers]
[laughing]
Psy?
My gut hurts!
Psyduck, use your tail whip attack.
Psy.
Psy. Psy. Psy...
[all laughing]
[snickering]
Huh?
Pika-pi.
Pikachu.
Psy. Psy. Psy.
Psy! [grunts]
[screams]
[all laughing]
And we were supposed to be attacking.
Psyduck, scratch it now!
Psy!
[grunting]
[grunting frantically]
[all laughing]
[thinking] Um, let 'em laugh. Just wait
till they see Psyduck's real power.
Psy... [screams]
Psyduck, use your disable attack.
Psy? Psy? Psy?
Oh, just attack, you dumb duck!
Go on and use your confusion attack.
Psy. psy...
Psy!
Ah. Can't you remember your own attacks?
Misty it's because its headache
isn't bad enough yet.
Come on, Cloyster! Score a knockout!
Go for the head! Go for the head!
They're even starting to cheer
for our side. [laughing]
Cloyster, clamp it with your shell.
Cha?
[screams]
[grunting]
Looks like this battle's over.
Psyduck needs help.
I'll have to give it a headache myself!
Don't do it, Misty!
-[sirens blaring]
-[all] Huh?
Looks like the next town wants to rumble.
Who is that?
[Jessie] Prepare for trouble.
[James] Make it double.
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation...
To unite all peoples within our nation...
To denounce the evils of truth and love...
To extend our reach to the stars above...
-Jessie.
-James.
Team Rocket.
Blast off at the speed of light.
Surrender now or prepare to fight.
Meowth. That's right.
Tyra, it's been awhile.
Big Jess!
You're looking good, Chopper.
Little Jim.
Big Jess and Little Jim?
What's that about?
Huh! Well, nerd, we had a pretty bad
reputation here back in the old days.
You were Chainer Jessie.
[laughs]
[Tyra] Big Jess was really cool,
swinging her chain around
while she rode her bicycle.
And then there was Trainer James.?
Little Jim was the only one
in the bike gang
who had to use training wheels.
[laughing]
I suppose we really were crazy back then.
Well, I guess our secret past
isn't secret anymore.
I kind of wish it still was a secret.
Pika.
But I see you're still into kid stuff,
riding around on bicycles.
Real gangs ride unicycles.
I guess your cycle gang
must save a ton of money on handlebars.
Tyra, we're not in a gang.
We are members of the famous Team Rocket!
[both] Team Rocket!
And I'd like to have all of you help us
to take care of these little pests
that are always ruining our plans.
I'll do anything for Jess and Jim.
Then capture all of their Pokémon.
[all yelling]
-Let's go!
-Come on!
[sirens blaring]
[groans]
Hey, who's causing all the trouble
on this bike path?
The cops. Let's split!
I thought you were going to help us.
They're all a bunch of scaredy-cats.
I'm getting kind of scared myself.
[both] Uh-huh.
So you're just trying to deliver
Pokémon medicine to Sunny Town?
Right, Joy, the beautiful
Pokémon Center nurse sent us.
Of course, she can't compare with you,
Officer Jenny.
You need to get there,
so I'll give you an escort.
Huh?
[cell phone rings]
This is 303.
Roger. Over and out.
There's been an accident. I'll have to go.
That's okay. We'll be fine.
Be careful.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
We should get moving, Ash.
A sick Pokémon's counting on us.
Let's go.
[thunder rumbling]
-[Ash] Ah!
-Pika!
Pikachu! We better hurry!
Pikachu.
[grunts]
[James]
They're riding right through the storm.
-No kidding.
-I knew those kids were all wet.
That wind could blow 'em
right off of the bridge.
They must be insane.
I'm glad we're inside.
-[Tyra] Big Jess.
-[Chopper] Little Jim.
Hm?
We know you want to be out there.
You could ride a storm twice this intense.
I could?
Big Jess,
lead us into the eye of the storm
and show us how to ride Big Jess style.
I... I...
[both]
Show the whole gang how to really ride.
[both trembling]
[Chopper]
You're not scared of this storm, are you?
I'm not. I just wish
I had my training wheels with me.
What about you, Big Jess?
[whimpering]
[thinking]
I guess I have no choice.
All right, now I'll show you kids
what riding's all about.
I wish I could go with you.
Meowth, we'd never leave you behind.
[groans]
The medicine still hasn't arrived.
But they should be there by this time.
Maybe they won't get through the storm.
[both] Ah!
[Misty] What's that?
[Brock] A drawbridge. That ship's
trying to take shelter in the bay.
-What do we do?
-We'll have to wait till it gets through.
We can't wait. They need that medicine.
Oh, I wish we were out of this rain.
Hey, look there.
How you going to get past that?
Hang in there, Little Jim.
Show us all what you can do, Big Jess.
-Do we really have to do this?
-I guess so.
-Ash, don't!
-There's a sick Pokémon waiting.
I can't let it down. [grunts]
Ash, wait up!
[panting]
[grunting]
Just have to keep going
for that sick Pokémon.
I have to make it. I just have to.
Ah!
[all yell]
Oh, no. They're not going to make it.
Ah!
[both] We'll drown!
-We'll bounce!
-[whimpers]
[Jessie grunts]
[grunts]
[all yelling]
We made it!
They did it! They're awesome!
[all]
Team Rocket's splashing down again!
[klaxon blows]
All right. Now you have to battle us.
I'm delivering medicine
for a sick Pokémon.
-Out of my way.
-What?
You mean
that's why you're out in this storm?
That's right.
Unbelievable. That's a real biker for you.
Listen up, guys!
We're going to take them there in style.
[all cheering]
Don't worry, Ash.
We'll clear the way for you.
Huh?
[Ash] Here, Nurse Joy.
You made it through in a storm like this.
Now this little one will be just fine.
[both] All right!
Sorry for making you worry about us.
We made it just in time.
That's great. Thank you.
[all chatter]
From now on,
we're calling you Awesome Ash.
Mighty Misty.
Well, gosh, I'm not really that awesome.
You could call me honey.
Argh!
[narrator] And so our brave friends
finally saved the sick Pokémon
and made it through the storm
to Sunny Town.
The bike gang has some new heroes
and everyone is happy.
Well, not everyone.
[all groaning]
[all] This is a vicious cycle.
Okay, guys we going to rap
some Pokémon.
You just do the singing,
I'll take care of the hard part.
Let get it on.
♪ I want to be the best ♪
♪ There ever was ♪
♪ To beat all the rest ♪
♪ Yeah, that's my cause ♪
♪ Electrode, Diglett, Nidoran
Mankey, Venusaur, Rattata ♪
♪ Fearow, Pidgey, Seaking
Jolteon, Dragonite, Gastly ♪
♪ Ponyta, Vaporeon
Poliwrath, Butterfree ♪
♪ Catch 'em, Catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I'll search across the land
Look far and wide ♪
♪ Release from my hand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Venomonth, Poliwag, Nidorino
Golduck, Ivysaur, Grimer ♪
♪ Victreebel, Moltres, Nidoking
Farfetch'd, Abra, Jigglypuff ♪
♪ Kingler, Rhyhorn
Clefable, Wigglytuff ♪
Thirty two down.
That's it for now.
Tune in tomorrow.
We'll rap at you some more.
There's 150,
so watch Monday through Friday.
You'll catch 'em all.
♪ Catch 'em, Catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all!
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪