♪ I want to be the very best ♪
♪ Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Each Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
[both grunting]
[crowd cheering]
[commentator] And Nidorino begins
the battle with a Horn Attack.
Oh, but Gengar bounces right back
and there it is,
the Hypnosis Power of Gengar!
This could be the end of Nidorino.
Wait! The trainer recalls Nidorino.
Which Pokémon will he use now?
-Oh, it's Onix!
-[roars]
Now this giant Pokémon is on the attack.
Ho-ho! But Gengar jumps aside.
Gengar is moving beautifully today....
[Ash] Yes, I am Ash.
[Narrator]
Ash Ketchum is a boy from Pallet Town.
[Ash] And now that I'm ten,
I can finally get my Pokémon license.
[Narrator] Ten-year-olds can get
a beginner Pokémon from Professor Oak,
the town's Pokémon expert.
I will journey to gain the wisdom
of Pokémon training,
and I hereby declare
to the Pokémon of the world,
I will be a Pokémon Master.
-Pokémon Master! That's what I'll--
[Mom] Ash, get to bed!
[grunts]
It's 11 o'clock and you should be asleep.
But tomorrow I begin my Pokémon journey.
I can't sleep.
Well, if you can't sleep, you
should at least get ready for tomorrow.
-Here. Watch this.
-Good evening, Pallet.
Tomorrow's the big day for the newest
class of Pokémon students.
I'd like to introduce you
to Bulbasaur, Charmander and Squirtle.
Each one is available for new trainees.
Which one shall you choose?
-Go to bed when this is done.
-All right, I'm going.
-And change into your pajamas, okay?
-I'm going.
POKÉMON
I CHOOSE YOU!
Raising Bulbasaur.
That'd be really simple.
It's perfect for beginners.
I choose you, Bulbasaur!
Then there's Squirtle.
I choose you, Squirtle!
Choose it or lose it. [sighs]
[Dodrio crowing]
Oh, hold on.
Charmander. Those in the know
say that's the best way to go.
I choose you, Charmander!
[clattering]
Ah!
[gasps]
Oh, no! What time is it?
[panting]
Squirtle, Bulbasaur, Charmander.
Anyone's fine.
Just, please, save one for me.
[All] Gary, Gary, he's our man.
If he can't do it, no one can!
Oh, sorry. Excuse me!
[yells and groans]
Hey, watch where you're going!
Well, you must be Ash.
Better late than never, I guess.
At least you get the chance to meet me.
Gary?
-Mr. Gary to you. Show some respect.
-Huh?
Well, Ash, you snooze, you lose and
you're way behind right from the start.
I've got a Pokémon and you don't.
You got your first Pokémon?
That's right, loser.
And it's right inside this Poké Ball.
[All]
Let's go, Gary. Let's go! Yeah, yeah!
Thank you, fans.
Thank you all for this great honor.
I promise you
that I will become a Pokémon Master
and make the town of Pallet
known all around the world!
[cheering and applause]
-Excuse me.
-Yeah?
I was just wondering if you could tell me
what kind of Pokémon you got.
None of your business.
If you showed up on time,
you would have seen that
I got the best Pokémon
from Professor Oak.
It's good to have a grandfather
in the Pokémon business, isn't it?
Thank you for coming out
to see history in the making!
Now I, Gary Oak, am off to learn
the ways of the Pokémon trainer!
I'll show you.
So you decided to show up after all.
Oh, Professor Oak.
Where's my Pokémon?
-Your Pokémon?
-Yes, I'm ready.
You look like you're ready for bed,
not for Pokémon training.
I hope you don't think you're going
to train in your pajamas.
Oh, no, Professor.
I got messed up this morning,
and I was a little late,
but believe me, I'm ready for a Pokémon.
I thought about it a lot
and it took me a long time
but I finally decided to choose Squirtle.
Oh!
Already taken by someone who was on time.
Oh, I wish I hadn't overslept.
But now I will choose as my Pokémon
Bulbasaur! What?
That one was also taken by a kid
who wasn't late.
Oh. Well, that's no problem
because my Pokémon will be Charmander!
-Ah!
-The early bird gets the worm
or in this case, the Pokémon.
Does that mean all the Pokémon are gone?
-Well, there is still one left--
-[gasps] Professor, I'll take it!
[bleeping]
I think I should warn you.
There is a problem with this last one.
-I have to have a Pokémon.
-Well, in that case.
[Ash groans]
-Pikachu.
-[Professor] Its name is Pikachu.
-Oh, it's so cute. It's the best of all.
-You'll see.
-Oh, hi, Pikachu.
-Pika.
It's also known
as electric mouse.
It's usually shy but can sometimes
have an electrifying personality.
-I see what you mean.
-Shocking, isn't it?
Now, take these,
your Pokédex and Poké Balls.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome!
[yelling]
[horns toot, drums clatter]
-Mom.
-Oh, Ash, I'm so proud of you.
You're finally going to fulfill your dream
and start your Pokémon training.
But I'm going to miss you so much.
[sobs] Oh, my little boy.
Pikachu.
I packed your sneakers and jeans,
nice clean shirts and underwear,
and your favorite snacks and some hot
chocolate in case you want something hot
but be careful not to burn yourself and
a pair of rubber gloves to do your laundry
and a new clothesline to hang it
out to dry--
Mom, you're embarrassing me
in front of all these people.
Don't you know I'm a big kid now?
Pokémon trainers can take care
of themselves.
I understand. Hmm?
-That's your Pokémon?
-Pikachu.
[Ash] Yeah, that's my Pokémon!
-Pi.
Ugh. With Pikachu at my side,
I'll get all the Pokémon in the world!
I thought all Pokémon stayed inside
their Poké Ball. Why doesn't this one?
Uh, oh, yeah, right.
Pikachu, get in the ball now.
[gasps]
-Pi.
-Huh?
-Ka.
-Chu.
-Huh?
Pikachu.
Oh, you're playing catch.
You're friends already.
Uh, sure.
Pikachu and I are real pals. Right?
- But it's a little weird.
- Weird?
[groans]
[zapping]
[people yelling]
Those rubber gloves your mom packed
will come in handy!
-Why?
-Rubber blocks electricity.
Hooray!
[people screaming]
Don't forget to change your underwear
every single day.
-Okay.
-Pikachu.
[Pikachu grunting]
[sighs]
Pikachu, are you going to be like this
the whole way?
Pi.
- Is it because you don't like me?
- Pika, pika.
Well, I like you a lot.
And since you're the Pokémon
I'm training,
don't you think
you could be a little nicer
and just open your mouth
and tell me what's wrong?
[squeaks]
That's not exactly what I meant.
- Is your name all you can say?
- Pika.
Well, then, you're just like all Pokémon
and you should act like one
and get inside the Poké Ball
just like it says in the Pokédex.
[Pokédex] While being trained, a Pokémon
usually stays inside its Poké Ball
-You see?
-Pika!
[Pokédex]
However, there are many exceptions.
Some Pokémon hate being confined.
Okay, then.
This ought to make things better.
-And I'll get rid of these. How's that?
-Pi.
-Still not good enough?
-Pika.
[sighs]
-Pika?
-Huh?
-A Pidgey.
-Pidgey is a flying Pokémon.
Among all the flying Pokémon,
it is the gentlest and easiest to capture,
a perfect target for the beginning Pokémon
trainer to test his Pokémon's skills.
This is great. It's our lucky day!
-Pikachu, go get it.
-Chu.
-Aren't you ever going to listen to me?
-But why not?
-Pika. Pika, pika, pika.
Cha!
Okay, I get the message.
I don't want your help or need it.
I can get that thing all by myself.
All right, I've pledged to get all
the Pokémon in the world.
Now I'm ready to take the next step
to be the number one Pokémon Master.
Enjoy your last moments of freedom,
Pidgey, 'cause you're mine!
Poké Ball , go!
I did it! Huh?
[coos]
I blew it.
[giggles]
[Pokédex]
To capture a Pokémon,
you usually have your own Pokémon battle
with the other.
Now he tells me.
[laughs]
But I have to do everything myself!
Wait. I've got an idea.
Okay. Just be quiet.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
[chuckles]
Hi, little friend.
Sorry, buddy!
[grunting]
[groans]
[exhales] What happened? Hmm?
[Pokédex]
Pidgey's gust power creates tornadoes.
-It also has a sand attack.
-Sand?
[Ash coughing]
Guess it's not my lucky day.
[giggling]
[groans]
Hey! Get out of there! Ah.
[Pokédex]
A forest Pokémon. Rattata.
It likes cheese, nuts, fruits,
and berries.
Yeah, but this isn't a forest.
It's an open field.
[Pokédex]
It also comes out into open fields
to steal food from stupid travelers.
That means I'm stupid?
[laughing]
[Pidgey coos]
Hmm?
[grunts]
Ah. Hmm?
I'll get you this time.
[grunts]
I got it!
I wonder what that is.
[Pokédex] Unlike Pidgey,
Spearow has a terrible attitude.
It is very wild and will sometimes
attack other Pokémon and humans.
Ah!
[panting]
[grunting]
[screeches]
Pikachu. Pika!
Hey, leave Pikachu alone!
It didn't throw the rock.
[Pokédex] Wild Pokémon tend to be
jealous of human-trained Pokémon.
-Oh.
-Pikachu!
Pikachu!
[crackling and zapping]
[squawking]
Ah, you got it!
Spearow!
[all grunting]
Uh-oh.
-Uh, should we run?
-Pikachu.
[gasping]
Aah!
Don't worry, Pikachu.
No matter what, I'll save you!
Pikachu.
Don't run ahead! I said I'd protect--
Ow.
[all grunting and groaning]
-Leave it alone, Spearows!
-Pika!
Pikachu!
[panting]
Well, here we go. Ah!
[burbles]
Huh? Ugh.
Hey, I got a bite! Oh, wow, I really think
this could be a big one!
[grunting]
Nah, it's just a kid.
Oh, and a Pokémon!
Oh, are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm okay.
[Woman] Not you!
Look what you've done
to that poor little thing.
-Is it breathing?
-Uh, I think so.
Well, just don't sit there.
It needs a doctor right away!
There's a medical center not too far
from here. You've gotta get moving now!
-You mean a hospital?
-Yes, for Pokémon.
-Um, can you tell me, which way do I go?
-That way.
[wings fluttering, Spearows screeching]
They're coming back! Run!
[Woman] Hey, what are you doing?
-I'm borrowing this.
[Woman] But, hey, that's my bike!
-I'll give it back someday!
Oh, you!
[thunder rumbling]
[lightning crackles]
- Pikachu.
- Just hang on now, Pikachu.
We're almost there.
[Spearows screeching]
[groaning]
[lighting crackles]
[groans]
Huh? Pikachu!
[panting]
- Chu.
- Pikachu, this can't happen.
[lightning crackles]
-Pikachu, get inside.
-Chu.
I know you're afraid of going in there but
if you're inside, maybe I can save you.
Please, Pikachu.
Please listen to me and go inside.
After that, then.
After that, just trust me!
Pika.
Spearows, do you know who I am?
I'm Ash from the town of Pallet.
I am destined to be the world's
number one Pokémon Master.
I can't be defeated by the likes of you.
I'm going to capture and defeat you all!
You hear me?
Pikachu, go inside the Poké Ball.
It's the only way.
Come and get me!
Whoa!
-Pikachu!
[Ash] Whoa!
[both groaning]
Pikachu.
[gasps]
-Well, we beat them.
-Chu.
Chu.
[gasps]
-What's that?
-[Pokédex] There is no data.
There are still Pokémon
yet to be identified.
[Narrator] This is just the beginning of
the amazing adventures of Ash and Pikachu.
Their journey is destined to be packed
with nonstop action, millions of laughs,
heart-pounding perils
and endless excitement.
Together they'll encounter
fantastic friends, evil enemies
and meet creatures
beyond their wildest imagination.
And as their story unfolds,
we'll unlock the magic and mystery
of a most wondrous place,
the incredible world of Pokémon.
♪ Okay guys, we gotta rap some Pokémon ♪
♪ You just do the singing
I'll take care of the hard part ♪
♪ Let's get it on ♪
♪ I want to be the best
There ever was ♪
♪ To beat all the rest
Yeah, that's my cause ♪
♪ Electrode, Diglett, Nidoran, Mankey
Venusaur, Rattata, Fearow, Pidgey ♪
♪ Seaking, Jolteon, Dragonite, Gastly
Ponyta, Vaporeon, Poliwrath, Butterfree ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch them all Pokémon ♪
♪ I'll search across the land
Look far and wide ♪
♪ Release from my hand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Venomoth, Poliwag, Nidorino, Golduck
Ivysaur, Grimer, Victreebel, Moltres ♪
♪ Nidoking, Farfetch'd, Abra, Jigglypuff
Kingler, Rhyhorn, Clefable, Wigglytuff ♪
♪ Thirty two down
That's it for now ♪
♪ Tune in tomorrow
We'll rap at you some more ♪
♪ There's 150 so watch Monday to Friday
You catch them all ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch them all
Pokémon ♪