♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
[narrator] Our friends journey
leads them to a desolate factory town,
known as Gringey City.
It's a depressing place
where few people live
and even the ocean winds
smell like sludge.
Here, their next adventure begins.
This is a really weird city.
Lots of factories but no people.
-This place is called Gringey City.
-Gringey?
Never heard of it.
It used to be a lively, busy place
with all these factories here.
[Brock] Yeah, they kind of went overboard
with factories.
Pollution ruined the air
and the water here.
I guess we won't find any Pokémon here.
Pika.
Pikachu, what's wrong?
Pikachu!
[yelling]
[Ash]
Sparks Fly for Magnemite
[all panting]
Hold on, Pikachu.
We'll get you to the Pokémon Center
as soon as we can.
Pika.
That's them, and they're on their way
to the Pokémon Center.
To protect the world from devastation...
To unite all peoples within our nation...
[retching]
I can't take it anymore!
-This is disgusting!
-This place stinks!
Just chill out
and put on the suits I brought you.
This thing pumps in a mixture of oxygen
and air freshener.
[contented sighing]
[both] That smells good.
Why didn't you tell us
about these suits before, Meowth?
We could have choked.
Quit complaining.
I did come up with this ingenious scheme.
Now get in the pipe
and swim to the Pokémon Center.
We're wasting time here.
Your plan's stupid.
I'm not going in that sewer.
I'm 100 percent with Jessie on this one.
I want to get Pikachu
just as much as you do,
but this is humiliating.
-It's degrading.
-We won't go through with this, Meowth,
so you'll have to go on this mission
alone. I'm sorry if this shocks you.
So am I.
[screaming]
I knew you'd see things my way.
You'll pay for this, Meowth.
[James]
Why do we always get the dirty work?
[dings]
Hey, nurse!
[yawning]
Do you kids have any idea
just what time it is?
Don't you know
that you should be sleeping now?
I'm sorry, but there's something
really wrong with my Pikachu.
[yawning] A cold.
[groans] This is no cold.
Your sisters and cousins
were a lot more helpful!
[yawning]
There's no need to get excited.
Look, sparks are coming
from its cheeks, right?
That's an early symptom of a cold
in electric rodent Pokémon.
If you leave it here overnight,
I'm sure it'll be fine in the morning.
-Miss.
-Hmm?
Excuse me, but are you, by any chance,
the oddball in your family?
Oh, no.
It's all my other relatives that are odd.
Huh?
[all] Grimer, Grimer, Grimer...
[man] Huh? What's that?
Our generator's completely shut down.
-The water intake valve is totally jammed.
-It can't be!
[whirring powers down]
Hey, what's going on?
The power supply just went dead.
If the pump stops working, there's no air.
They won't like that. [chuckles]
[gasps] What do I do? What do I do?
What do I do?
[grunts]
My air supply.
[gags]
-Oh.
-[Ash groans]
-What happened to these Pokémon?
-[Joy] They're in intensive care.
If we don't get the power back soon,
well, I just don't want to think
about what would happen.
Don't just stand there.
We have to save them.
-Joy, please do something.
-I don't know what to do.
Hey, stop giving Joy a hard time.
There's nothing that she can do.
-Let's go.
-[Joy gasps]
Pikachu!
Pikachu, we'll be back
when the power's back on.
Good luck, everybody.
Chu.
I'm trying to find out,
but there's no answer at the power plant.
-We don't have much time.
-What does the power plant look like?
You can't miss it.
It's the big building
with the smokestacks there.
[Ash] All right, let's go.
-[rustling]
-Huh?
Pi... Pikachu.
Pikachu. [groans]
Ah, Pikachu, you should be back
at the Pokémon Center.
Chu.
-I don't get it.
-Just think about it, Ash.
Pikachu's afraid we'll leave,
and we won't come back.
Pika.
-See?
-Hmm...
Okay, you can come along.
But remember, you've got to take it easy.
Pikachu!
[yelling]
[both gasping]
We could have suffocated.
The city has been plunged into darkness
by a power failure.
A power failure is it?
I can identify with failure.
[Meowth]
Huh? There they go. Now we're in luck.
We got another chance.
For what?
For finally once and for
all capturing that pesky Pikachu.
Come on now!
Jessie, James, let's move it!
Give us time to rest, Meowth.
We nearly drowned in the stinking sewer
thanks to your ridiculous plan.
Meowth, you nearly killed us, you dimwit.
Guys, don't worry.
This time we've got a secret weapon
that's Meowth-proof. [chuckles]
-There's the power plant.
-Let's check inside.
Hello? Is anybody in here?
If no one's here,
we might as well look around, huh?
Pikachu.
Something's really weird.
Why isn't anybody working here?
It looks like the central control room's
down that way.
[shivering]
[Misty] Something's following us.
-[whimpering]
-Huh?
The place is deserted. Nobody's here.
Oh, I know I heard something back there.
Listen, Misty,
it's okay if you're a total chicken.
Brock and I are brave enough
to handle things here.
I'm not a chicken, you little twerp!
There was something back there
whether you believe me or not.
Okay, okay, let's just...
[both] Huh?
[stammering]
Chill out?
[both whimpering]
There's something...
Right behind you.
[whimpering]
All right, if anybody's there,
you can come on out.
And if you're a ghost or a monster,
you can stay where you are,
and we won't bother you.
And you called me chicken!
You're a total coward!
Maybe not a total coward.
-[Misty] You're just a--
-[Brock] Come on, guys, quit it.
Pika!
Be quiet, Pikachu.
Be quiet.
Pika, pi-pika!
-Pikachu, I told you.
-Pika! Pika!
-[all scream]
-Pika! Pika.
[all screaming]
What is that thing?
[all whimpering]
What is that thing? What is it?
Magnemite.
Magnemite? Is that a Pokémon?
[Pokédex]
Magnemite, a magnet Pokémon.
Its means of floating through the air
are not understood.
This very mysterious Pokémon
is of the electric type.
What's a Pokémon like that doing here?
It caused the blackout.
Magnemite shut down the power plant.
This one, by itself? No way.
Well, Dexter said it's mysterious.
Great.
I'll capture it, then we can check it out.
Wait a minute. That Magnemite
doesn't look like it wants to battle.
Cha.
What's with this thing?
Why is it circling Pikachu?
It seems to like Pikachu.
-Pika.
-Magnemite.
This Magnemite is blushing,
like it's in love or something.
Love?
If it were an animal Pokémon,
I could understand,
but how can an inorganic Pokémon,
like Magnemite,
fall in love with an electric rodent?
Magnemite's following Pikachu
all over the place,
almost like it's a streaker or something.
Ash, you mean a stalker.
Like I said,
this Magnemite really likes Pikachu.
Yeah, but Pikachu doesn't like it.
Hey you, Magnemite, cut it out.
Pika.
-[whimpers]
-[chuckles] Guess Magnemite gave up.
[sniffs] Mm, do you smell that?
-I do.
-So do I.
-Grimer!
-It's those things.
-They stinks.
What are they?
[Pokédex] Grimer, a sludge Pokémon.
Born from sludge, these Pokémon
specialize in sludge attacks.
Magnemite must have disappeared
because of these things.
Is this what sludge smells like?
It really stinks.
-Grimer!
-[Ash grunts]
Ash, don't say anything that might insult
their Pokémon pride or make them mad.
I'm sorry.
You have such a unique scent.
I should have known
it was the aroma of sludge.
You can call it whatever you want,
but it sinks.
[both] Shut up, Misty!
[mumbling]
-Ah, it's huge!
-Grimer's grandpa?
[Pokédex]
Muk, Grimer's evolved form.
Use extreme caution
as its slimy form contains poison.
[groans]
-That's not good news.
-The smell is getting worse.
-Pika.
-Muk.
[all screaming]
Why'd you have to open your mouth
and make the Grimer mad, Misty?
I had to open my mouth.
I couldn't use my nose.
Cha!
[panting]
[groaning]
What are you doing here?
I'm Brock, this is Misty,
and we're here to help fix--
Uh, skip the introductions.
We've got to get out of here.
-Grimer. Grimer. Grimer.
-Pika!
Aah, the Grimer are here too!
-Back to the control room!
-[panting]
Hey, wait for us!
[screaming and grunting]
Tell us what's going on.
This blackout is a disaster for the city.
Lots of Pokémon are going to die
at the Pokémon Center
if the power doesn't come back soon.
Hang in there.
Those kids are going to get the power
back on real soon, I'm sure.
At least, I hope so.
-They need that power.
-But we can't.
[all] Grimer, Grimer...
[man] There are so many Grimer that
they're clogging the sea water intake.
We've got to bring the water to a boil,
so it will turn the turbines
or the generator won't work at all.
So do something.
I'm afraid that's easy to say.
We've been trying to do--
-[Brock] Ash!
-[both] Huh?
The Grimer are ramming the door.
I can't hold it!
[grunting]
I hate to say it,
but if we don't act fast,
we'll be on the Muk menu.
But what can we do?
[grunting, shouting]
[all whimpering]
[all] Grimer! Grimer! Grimer!
You three are all Pokémon trainers,
aren't you?
You've got to use your Pokémon
to help us out.
That's right. If you can get rid
of the Grimer, the generator will work.
What do you expect us to do?
Pikachu is sick.
It won't be able take on
all of those Grimer at once.
Pika.
Pikachu,
you're the only one who can help.
Kachu!
You-- You're our last chance.
[groans] Give them your thunder shock!
Kachu!
[all] Grimer! Grimer! Grimer!
It's no good. There are too many of them.
Muk!
[gasping]
What are they?
Magnemite and their evolved form,
Magneton.
They're friends of our stalker.
[all screaming]
[all] Grimer! Grimer! Grimer!
-Yeah!
-Yay!
The lights are on.
The turbine's moving again.
The Grimer have all cleared away
from the sea water intake valve.
Yes!
Hold on. There's still one left.
Muk!
[Ash] An adult Muk and its child.
Pikachu, thunder shock.
Pikachu!
Oh, man, that's some pretty strong sludge.
Magnemite.
Muk!
Chu!
All right! Poké Ball, go!
I did it! I captured a Muk!
Ash Ketchum saves the day once again!
-[all groan]
-Hmm? What's wrong?
[both groaning]
The smell comes through the Poké Ball!
[all laughing]
That's the bad news.
But the good news
is Pikachu's 100% better.
That's right. Pikachu was sick
until just a little while ago.
Ah, if an electric mouse
builds up too much electricity,
its body becomes magnetized
nd it seems like it has a cold.
Pikachu.
Well, we all sure owe a big thank you
to Magnemite here, don't we?
[whirring]
Pi! Pikachu!
Pi? Pika?
Hey, until just a minute ago,
that Magnemite was obsessed with Pikachu.
What's going on?
Now it's completely ignoring Pikachu.
Maybe Magnemite fall in and out of love
just like humans do.
Hmm. Could Magnemite have fallen in love
at first sight
because Pikachu's body was magnetized?
That must be the reason.
Animals are attracted to other animals
by scent,
so Magnemite are attracted
to other Pokémon by their magnetic force.
Because Pikachu had built up
so much magnetic force,
it must have been very attractive
to that Magnemite.
-Oh.
-I get it.
After Pikachu ran out of electricity,
it was no longer magnetized,
that's why Magnemite isn't interested
in Pikachu anymore.
It's a good thing, huh, Pikachu?
It won't follow you around anymore.
Chu!
-[all laughing]
-Yeah.
[Meowth] We got them now.
Now the fun begins
with our new secret weapon.
Tell them, James.
Now that Pikachu is magnetized,
our plan is to take
this high-powered electromagnet and...
[both] Finally capture Pikachu!
Hey, who are you talking to?
Let's just catch Pikachu.
Why don't you keep your snide remarks
to yourself?
That's right.
[whirring]
[metallic slamming]
-That sounds strange.
-Certainly does.
Yeah.
[all whimpering]
[all] Team Rocket's splashing off again!
All those Grimer here just prove
that the ocean's totally polluted.
You guys got to clean up the sea
around here.
-I know you can do it.
-You're right, Misty.
We'll do everything we can to make sure
that the ocean is really clean again.
If you clean up the air and the water,
you may just bring this place
back to life.
Thanks, Ash.
You worked so hard to make sure
all these Pokémon survived,
you've inspired me
to become a better nurse.
We salute your fine work.
Oh, please, ladies.
That's very nice of you.
Anyway, try to make your city clean.
We will and please come back and visit us.
Bye.
[narrator] Our heroes leave Gringey City
with big smiles
and even bigger hopes for a future
that's cleaner and greener than before.
Meanwhile...
[laughs] It's been quite a while
since Ash sent me a new Pokémon.
I wonder what he's captured this time?
Ugh! What is this smell?
-M-m-m-muk!
-[groans]
What's the idea of sending me a Muk?
Yuck!
Muk!
♪ Pokémon! ♪
Get those lips loose,
it’s time to Pokérap!
Come on, sing ‘em with me!
That’s the game!
There’s 150 Pokémon.
How many can you name?
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, yeah! ♪
Gotta catch 'em all, ow! ♪
♪ Sandslash, Hitmonlee, Psyduck, Arcanine
Eevee, Exeggutor, Kabutops, Zapdos ♪
♪ Dratini, Growlithe, Mr. Mime, Cubone ♪
♪ Graveler, Voltorb, Gloom
We're almost home! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
Gotta catch 'em all! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Charmeleon, Wartortle
Mewtwo, Tentacruel, Aerodactyl ♪
♪ Omanyte, Slowpoke Pidgeot, Arbok ♪
That's all, folks!
Can you name all the Pokémon?
Just put today’s song together
with the other days of the week.
That’s why you can’t miss a show.
You gotta catch ‘em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪