♪ I want to be the very best ♪
♪ Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch them all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
[narrator] Determined to become
a Pokémon Master,
Ash continues on his quest,
gaining skill and knowledge
and catching new Pokémon
along the way.
His fierce Pokémon battle
with Gym Leader Brock earned
Ash a boulder badge
and a brand-new friend.
Brock, hoping to be
a Pokémon breeder,
decided to join
Ash and Misty on their journey.
[Gary]
"Gary was here, Ash is a loser."
[narrator] But with his rival Gary
way ahead of him,
Ash Ketchum
is still playing catch-up.
We can only wonder
what adventures lie ahead.
[birds chirping]
Ah, it's a great day
to just enjoy the sunshine.
And while you're enjoying
the sunshine,
-Gary's catching more Pokémon.
-Ah!
But I guess a Pokémon trainer can capture
Pokémon and enjoy the sun.
Pika.
Hey! Wait a minute!
Cha.
-Where do you think you're going?
-Oh, I know where we're going.
-We're going to Cerulean City.
-Ah! Cerulean City?
What are you going there for?
Well, it's none of your business,
but I'm going for more badges.
Uh, Ash, you don't want Pokémon
from there. Trust me.
-Why not?
-Because they're all...
All what?
...very scary ghost Pokémon
that look like this.
Like monsters.
[laughs]
Nice face, Misty. Come on, Brock.
Let's go, Pikachu.
Hey, hey! Wait a second!
Hey, what about Vermilion City?
It's right on the water
and there are lots of neat Pokémon
and you can watch all the giant yachts
pulling into the harbor.
And there's a little park way up
on a hill
where you can sit and watch the sunset.
That's so romantic.
Uh-huh.
It's much nicer than that old
Cerulean City, so let's get going!
-Okay. Let's go.
-Really?
-To Cerulean City.
- Ah. Unh!
[Ash] I've got to get
more trainer badges, Brock.
And since there's a Gym
in Cerulean City
[Brock] Yeah, makes sense to me.
Ah, I never wanted to wander back here.
Oh.
-The coast is clear.
-Nothing to fear.
Nobody here. Meowth.
Well, looks like we found it.
[Jessie] Just what we need
to get just what we want.
Pokémon.
-So this is Cerulean City, eh, Brock?
-Pretty nice place, isn't it?
Yeah, pretty cool.
Hey, look. That's weird.
-Misty's not following us anymore.
-Chu.
She really didn't want to come
to Cerulean City, did she?
I wonder why she hates
this place so much.
-Hmm.
-Ah, we'll never figure out girls.
[sirens wailing]
-The police. Wonder what happened.
-Yeah.
Excuse me.
Do you know what happened here?
Some burglars broke
into that store last night.
Burglars, huh?
[girl] What do you know about burglars?
-Huh?
You two look very suspicious
to me.
Hey, you're that motorcycle officer
from Viridian.
Huh? Ah, you must have met
my sister-in-law.
If you know my sister-in-law,
that means you probably had some
dealings with the police in Viridian.
Well, I...
Now, maybe you just stopped
to ask her for directions,
or maybe you found a wallet
on the street and turned it in to her,
or maybe you're a burglar
who broke out of jail!
-I've never been to jail!
-Neither have I, ma'am.
That's what they all say.
We just got into town
and saw the crowd
so we came over to see
what was going on.
The criminal always returns
to the scene of the crime.
-We're not, uh...
-Maybe this'll help clear things up.
I'm Dexter, A Pokédex
program by professor Oak
for Pokémon trainer Ash Ketchum.
Yeah and I was the Leader
of the Pewter City Gym.
-Well, that's evidence enough for me.
-I'm sorry I was suspicious.
Now I'm suspicious of my sister-in-law.
She sure has weird taste in friends.
-[Brock] Um, miss?
- Hm?
I was wondering,
since I'm new in town,
maybe we could get together tonight
and you could show me around.
Well, I'm not off duty
till past your bedtime
and I may even have to work
round the clock to catch these burglars.
-Well, what exactly did they steal?
-That's the strange thing about it.
They didn't take any money,
just a massive vacuum and a giant hose.
But what would anybody
want that stuff for?
I'm sure I don't know, young man,
but I do know I don't have time
to play guessing games with you
because I've got a job to do,
and it's time for you two to move along.
Come on, let's go.
All right, everybody.
The show's over.
Nothing to see here.
Break it up. Break it up.
Good thing I had Dexter
and you had your badge.
Yeah. Shouldn't you head
for Cerulean City Gym?
Yeah. Hey, Brock.
You got any inside info
on the Gym Trainer there?
-Huh?
-Ha-ha.
I just want to find out
as much as I can about him
before we have our match.
Know yourself, know your adversary
and you hold the key to victory.
You sure know
some pretty deep stuff.
Heh, I learned that one from Dexter.
Well, I never actually met
the trainer here but I know
his Pokémon special move.
Yeah? What is it?
I'm sorry, Ash, but I can't
give you that information.
-Why not?
-I'm a Gym Leader, too, after all.
I can't tell you out of respect.
-You understand.
-That's cool.
Well, I have some stuff
I need to check out.
-What stuff?
-Just stuff. See you later.
-Bye. Well, let's get going, Pikachu.
-Pika.
Cerulean City Gym.
Should be right around here someplace.
Huh? There it is.
[man] Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome the star of our show,
the sensational Cerulean City
synchronized swimming sisters!
[gasps]
[cheers and applause]
[All]
Lily! Violet! Daisy!
[cheering]
[music playing over speakers]
But I thought this was
the Pokémon Gym, Pikachu.
Pika.
I can't understand it.
Huh? It's like an aquarium.
How can this be a Pokémon Gym?
-[girl 1] The crowd was totally awesome.
-[girl 2] I know. That was so great.
-Daisy, the dive you did was super.
-The practice really paid off.
Totally.
[all giggling]
-[Ash] Uh, excuse me.
-I'm sorry
but if you want an interview,
you have to, like, call our manager.
-No, it's not that.
-We don't do autographs.
I don't want one.
I really just wanted to know
if this is a Pokémon Gym.
[Girl]
It sure is.
- Well, I'm looking for the Gym Trainer.
-[Girl] You're looking at them.
Huh?
The three of us
are the Gym Trainers here.
-We're The Sensational Sisters.
-We're world famous.
Huh? But what's with
all that swimming?
It's, like, our hobby,
and our fans love to watch us perform.
We pool our talents
to make a big splash.
[giggling]
Come on.
-I challenge all of you.
-Pika.
-Um.
-What?
We don't feel much like
battling anymore.
-What do you mean?
-We just got beaten three times in a row
by kids from this nowhere place
called Pallet Town.
-Not again.
-It was just one defeat after another.
My eyes were spinning from all the losses.
We had to, like,
practically rush all our Pokémon
-to the Pokémon center.
-This is the only one left.
Goldeen. Goldeen. Goldeen.
You mean all you have
is a Goldeen?
If it would evolve into Seaking,
we could use it.
But all it can do now
is its horn attack.
So, like, there's no point in battling.
Now, Instead of having matches
we have time to make ourselves
look more beautiful than ever.
-Ah.
-I know what you want.
Seel?
Seel.
A cascade Badge.
This is what you want, right?
-You can have it.
-Thanks. Uh, I'd rather earn my badges.
Take it. A badge is a badge.
[sighs] Here.
Hold it right there!
-[Ash] Misty?
-Cha!
Hi-yah!
All right, Daisy. If you don't want
to battle him, I will.
[gasps]
If you don't want to battle him,
I will.
What do you mean?
-I'm a Cerulean City trainer too.
-[Pikachu and Ash gasp]
-I'm the fourth Sensational Sister.
-There are only three Sensational Sisters
and one runt.
[grunts angrily]
So, little sister, it's a surprise
to see you back so soon.
That little girl with a big mouth
who said she wouldn't come back
till she was a great Pokémon trainer.
Wasn't that you?
Huh? I guess I did say something
like that when I left.
So that's why Misty was so dead set
against coming here.
Misty, you left here pretending you wanted
to become a Pokémon trainer
because you couldn't compare with us.
Because we're obviously much more
talented and beautiful than you are.
-Uh-oh.
-That wasn't the reason!
Well, then, I guess,
like, you came back
because you couldn't make it
as a Pokémon trainer.
It wasn't my idea to come back here.
The only reason I'm here
is because he wanted to come.
Well, he's totally not someone
I'd choose for a boyfriend.
-Ah!
-But you're no prize yourself.
My boyfriend? If I battle him,
that'll prove I'm not a quitter
and I'm just as good a trainer
as you three.
Well, you are the only one of us
with a Pokémon that can actually battle.
All right, Ash.
Are you ready to rumble?
Uh.
I wasn't planning
on challenging you
till you paid me back for my bike,
but this is as good a time as any.
If you want that cascade badge,
you're going to have to beat me.
It'll be my pleasure.
Pikachu, this one's
going to be a piece of cake.
-So how many Pokémon?
-Two against two works for me.
You got it.
All right, then, Pikachu, I choose you!
-Huh?
-Chu.
-Pikachu, what are you doing?
-Chu. Chu.
Uh, what? Are you saying you
don't want to battle with Misty?
-Pikachu.
-Well, I guess it's okay
If you don't want to battle a friend.
Pikachu, you're a Pika pal!
-Pikachu!
-Thanks a lot, Pikachu.
Butterfree, I choose you!
[chitters]
Well, in that case, Misty calls Staryu!
-[grunts]
-Huh? Hmm.
[Pokédex]
Staryu, the core of this water Pokémon
shines in a rainbow of seven colors.
A core that is valued
by some as a type of jewelry.
Oh. Wow.
Leave it to a girl
to show off her jewelry.
Quit stalling and let's get
this show on the road.
-Do you think Misty could really win?
-Like, in her dreams, maybe.
Butterfree, you can blow that thing
away with one blast. Tackle it!
[squeals]
[grunting and groaning]
-Staryu, counter attack!
-Butterfree, dodge!
[chitters]
[groans]
-Ha-ha! I'm going to win this.
-Staryu, water gun.
In that case, Stun Spore now.
Oh, no.
Staryu looks like it's in real pain.
It doesn't even have a face.
How can you tell?
Because I'm sensitive
to others' feelings, that's how.
-Oh, yeah? Like, I'm not?
-Which side are you clapping for?
Staryu, wash it off.
Yay! Too bad you didn't know
that Stun Spore doesn't work
if you wash it off in water.
She thinks she knows everything.
Butterfree, Sleep Powder.
Tackle it from underwater.
If Staryu can get butterfree underwater,
I win.
Water Pokémon
always have the edge in the water.
[laughs]
[grunts]
Pikachu, you're supposed
to be on my side.
Misty's totally awesome.
Well, we three
got the good looks in the family
so I guess she had to get
some talent.
Butterfree, return.
Pidgeotto, I choose you!
[grunting]
Oh, yeah? Staryu, return!
Misty calls Starmie!
Pidgeotto, Whirlwind it away!
Dive under, then up.
-[squawks]
-Strike back with wing attack.
-Give it a gust to blow it away.
[squawks]
-[sighs]
-Starmie!
[Starmie dings]
Oh, no. Starmie's energy
is just about to run out.
All right, Pidgeotto.
Let's get that trainer badge.
[rumbling]
Huh?
[screaming]
-Check out that hair.
-Like, who invited the party crashers?
[Jessie] Sorry to break in on you, ladies.
[James] Allow us to introduce ourselves.
-To protect the world from devastation.
-To unite all peoples within our nation.
-To denounce the evils of truth and love.
-To extend our reach to the stars above.
-Jessie.
-James.
Team rocket.
Blast off at the speed of light.
-Surrender now, or prepare to fight.
-Meowth, that's right.
-The water Pokémon have the advantage.
-But if we steal that water away.
-The Pokémon are ours for the taking.
-And Meowth knows just how to do it.
What are they trying to prove?
[gasp]
[engine rumbling]
A massive vacuum and a giant hose.
Ah! Team rocket were the robbers
who broke into that store back there.
-I should have known it was them.
-Our swimming pool.
-They're sucking it dry.
-That's our water.
Right. I should give it back.
[screaming]
-We've got to protect the Pokémon.
-Like, what about my hair?
All right, now's the time to suck them up.
[groaning]
Come back, Seel.
[Ash]
Oh, Pikachu.
[Pikachu screams]
Pikachu!
Hey, wait a second.
Water conducts electricity.
-Pikachu, Thunderbolt!
-Pikachu!
[screaming]
It's times like these
that make me want to go straight.
[groan]
Now I know how it feels
to be all washed up.
We'll never come clean.
[screaming]
[Seel cheering]
[All] Looks like Team Rocket's
blasting off again!
[screaming]
-Oh, no.
-Pikachu!
[panting]
Pikachu!
Pikachu.
-Hey, we never got to finish our match.
-Yeah.
-And I was just about to win it too.
-What?
You could say your match had
to be postponed, like, due to drain.
-At least nobody lost.
-I wanted to win.
I guess I'm not going to get
that Cascade Badge.
-Wrong. We're giving this badge to you.
-Huh?
How come he gets the badge?
He didn't win.
Pikachu was the one that,
like, totally saved us all.
And if he'd used Pikachu from the start
there was no way your
water Pokémon could have won.
-Oh, man.
-Take the badge, Ash.
-You deserve it.
-Gee, thanks.
-Heh, I'll take it!
-Cha!
[narrator] And so Ash earns
his second Pokémon trainer badge.
Misty, you just go right on
trying to be a Pokémon trainer.
You might as well be good at something
'cause you'll never be stars like us.
You keep that up,
and you'll be seeing stars.
-Chill out.
-Misty, be careful.
-You know we love you.
-Yeah.
-Ash. Hey, man.
-Yo, Brocko.
-How'd it go?
-See for yourself.
-Cool. Let's go.
-Right.
You're not leaving without me.
Misty, you're not going be
a sore loser, are you?
I didn't lose anything. It was a draw.
[Ash] Well, I'm the one who got the badge.
[Misty] What?
You know you lost with Butterfree.
[Ash] That was just round one.
I made a great comeback.
[Misty] If team rocket hadn't busted in,
I would have destroyed you.
[Ash] You're lucky they showed up.
You were about to lose.
[Misty] Lose? I was just getting started.
-[Ash] Oh, yeah?
-[Misty] Oh, yeah.
[Brock] Oh, brother.
You guys up for the Pokérap?
There's 150 Pokémon.
You got to name them all.
I'm doing 32 today, so try to keep up.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪
♪ Zubat, Primeape, Meowth, Onix
Geodude, Rapidash, Magneton, Snorlax ♪
♪ Gengar, Tangela, Goldeen, Spearow,
Weezing, Seel, Gyarados, Slowbro ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Kabuto, Persian, Paras, Horsea,
Raticate, Magnemite, Kadabra, Weepinbell ♪
♪ Ditto, Cloyster, Caterpie, Sandshrew,
Bulbasaur, Charmander, Golem, Pikachu ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
All right, how'd you do?
Loosen those lips!
Shake up that tongue!
Give it a rest. Today's song is sung.
We'll be back tomorrow.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon ♪