♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
[narrator] Several months have passed
since Ash left his home town of Pallet
on his Pokémon journey.
After lots of adventures and discoveries,
the gang finds themselves
somewhere in the mountains.
-We sure have traveled a long way.
-Yeah, we've seen tons of places.
-I wonder where we should go now?
-Pi.
That's easy. We have to go to the next gym
so we can get another badge.
-Well, Fuchsia Gym isn't far from here.
-Where is it?
Uh, over the mountain.
-[Misty] Uh...
-[Ash] Mm...
-Uh, Brock, over which mountain?
-[Brock] The map says the Fuchsia Gym's
on the other side of one
of those mountains right over there.
Is it this way or that way?
Or maybe it's that way?
Oh, great.
We're surrounded by mountains
on every side.
[groans]
Don't tell me. We're lost again.
-Okay, I won't tell you.
-Kachu?
Wait a minute.
It looks like there's a road here.
Well, let's hit it.
[sighs]
[Ash] Dig Those Diglett!
-I'm having some lovely Chinese food.
-It's tea and crumpets for me.
Nothing for Meowth. I'm getting a gut.
-[both] Work that body.
-Cheers!
[rumbling]
[all yelling]
[grunting]
I wonder what that was.
-I didn't get a taste.
-I didn't get a sip.
That's the breaks.
But I wonder
where that big blast came from.
[rumbling]
It's over there.
[Jessie] My lunch break is ruined.
[James] No tea party for me.
[both grunting]
[both] Someone's going to pay for this!
[Meowth] Hey, wait for me!
[all panting]
[gasping]
This place looks like a battle zone.
Maybe we're being attacked
by aliens from another planet.
What planet are you from?
[all gasp]
-What a wreck!
-This is terrible!
-Oh, the destruction.
-And we didn't cause it.
Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig,
Diglett, dig...
Chu!
[all]
Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
Diglett.
Pika.
Pikachu.
Diglett.
So that's it.
I just can't take it anymore.
Are you all right?
It's the Diglett.
They're destroying everything.
-The Diglett?
-See, they're right over there.
[all] Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig,
Diglett, dig...
Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
Oh, look how cute.
You think they're cute, do you?
Thanks to them
we can't finish building that dam.
[groaning] I hate Diglett! I hate them!
Hmm. Diglett.
[Pokédex] Diglett. The movement
of these ground Pokémon
can be easily detected
by their tracks of upturned earth.
[Ash]
Hmm. I don't see any upturned earth.
That's because the ground here
is covered by concrete,
but if you look closely...
-They're underneath.
-It looks like a mini-earthquake.
And it looks like we'll never be able
to accomplish our dream
of building the great Giva Dam
here in these mountains.
-Giva Dam?
-Over there.
All right! Let her rip!
That blasting is part of building a dam?
Yes, the blasting
is part of building a dam!
But we can't get supplies through
because of Diglett!
Hmm. That is a problem.
We even created a special division
for developing strategies
to fight off the Diglett.
We're calling for any able Pokémon trainer
who's traveling through the area,
somebody with real Pokémon know-how
who can help us get rid of these Diglett.
The reward's a six-night, seven-day stay
at the famous Giva Hot Springs Resort.
If you know any Pok--
We're three able Pokémon trainers
at your service.
Oh, so you're the first squad
of the trainers we called in!
[chuckles]
Uh, well, we weren't exactly called in.
The first Pokémon trainers have arrived.
The rest are in these buses.
-It's Gary.
-Huh? Who are...
Well, if it isn't little Ash from Pallet.
What are you doing here?
It must just be an unlucky coincidence.
Only the best were invited,
like me, Gary from the town of Pallet,
the number one trainer.
-Ash is fourth.
-I'm fourth? I'm better than that.
You're the fourth to leave home,
but as a trainer, you're dead last.
Aw!
Now watch as I step up to the plate
and hit a Pokémon grand slam!
Hooray, hooray!
-He's very...
-Detestable.
[Gary] So, Ash, have you picked up
any good Pokémon?
-Of course I have. Do you want to see?
-No, thanks, Ash.
Only amateurs show off their Pokémon.
If I were going to show something off,
it'd be my personal fan club.
Gary Oak, Gary Oak
He comes through when others choke
Are they Pokémon?
[Ash groans]
Don't be dumb.
-So who are the girls?
-Oh, they're just my friends of mine.
They're nice friends.
How would you lovely young ladies
like to get together with me sometime?
[all] Yes, sir. That would be fine.
[Brock] Yes, sir?
Brock's over-the-hill already.
Okay, so they think I'm an old man,
but I don't care, I'm desperate.
Could I have somebody's phone number,
please?
Maybe an address? E-mail?
Can we please get back
to the business at hand?
Somebody's got to get rid
of these Diglett.
Don't forget: a resort vacation.
Don't give it another thought, sir.
Those Diglett are as good as gone
now that Gary Oak is on the case.
So long, losers!
[cackles]
What about those phone numbers?
We're losers?
[groans] I can't let him beat me. I can't.
We're Pokémon trainers, aren't we?
Why don't we try to win that reward?
That's a brilliant idea, Jessie.
If we get rid of the Diglett,
we spend a week at that hot spring resort.
I could use a rest.
I could use a little relaxation myself,
Jessie.
I'll get rid of those Digglet.
Don't forget, James, we're a team.
You're right. I almost forgot that.
[both] And our team is Team Rocket!
Hello. Uh, I wonder if it's possible
to get traded to a less embarrassing team.
-It sounds like those...
-Aliens are back.
[both groan]
[rumbling]
We greatly appreciate all of you
talented Pokémon trainers
interrupting your training to come here
and help us get rid of the Diglett.
Mm, there sure are a lot of people here.
You, with the Pikachu on your head,
listen with your ears,
not with your mouth!
You'd think the least he could do
is yell at me by name.
Don't be mad.
He doesn't know what your name is.
My name is Ash Ketchum,
the loser from Pallet.
[groans]
Don't listen to Gary.
You can still catch up.
My name's Jessie. Look at all those punks.
Each outfit is more dreadful
than the last.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Jessie, there's no need to be catty.
-What's wrong with catty?
-I just thought of something.
With this many trainers,
imagine how many Pokémon they must have.
Let's see. If each of them has six,
there'd be six times that many Pokémon.
You can do the math,
I just want to grab all those Pokémon.
It's a Pokémon bonanza.
All we have to do is...
[sighs]
Forget it. Let's just give up now.
James, what's the matter? What's wrong?
How can we possibly defeat
all those Pokémon
-when all we've got are...
-Ekans.
And Koffing.
-Koffing.
[both groaning]
Another sneak attack.
They've never worked in the past,
have they?
-No.
-How about plan B?
You know what this would mean?
-Let's try it.
-It's the...
[all]
Principle of induced evolution.
-Ekans.
-Koffing.
Pokémon trainers, here you see Diglett,
the greatest parasitic bug Pokémon
of the century.
Just a minute.
Technically Diglett is not a bug Pokémon.
As a matter of fact, the term mole Pokémon
would be more appropriate.
With a height of eight inches
and a weight of two pounds,
they're hardly candidates to be called
the greatest anything of this century.
That showoff thinks he knows everything.
They may seem to be weak,
but together, they can destroy. [gasps]
It's the Diglett! It's the Diglett!
[all] Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig,
Diglett, dig...
-Diglett. Diglett.
-I'll take care of this.
♪ Gary doesn't dig the Digletts
Oh, no... ♪
Now everyone will be able to see
the top Pokémon trainer in action.
This should do the trick.
[chuckles and buzzing]
Hey, what?
-It won't come out. What's wrong?
-Pikachu.
[all]
Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
-Diglett!
-Oh, thanks.
Wait! This can't happen!
Okay, I can take care of this.
I'll just bring out my best Pokémon.
-You can handle it.
-♪ Let's go ♪
Go get 'em!
What's going on here?
All right. I'll show them.
I'll use every Pokémon I have.
Please, somebody stop them!
Stop the Diglett!
-All right, go!
-Go, Zubat!
-[all speak at once]
-[trainer 2] Haunter, go!
-[trainer 3] Magikarp, go!
-[trainer 4] Vileplume, go!
[all] Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig,
Diglett, dig...
-Uh, thanks.
-Thank you.
[all]
Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
[trainer] Thank you.
-At least they're polite.
-Yeah and unstoppable.
[Ash] Ha! All right. Now it's my turn.
As long as they're underground,
I'm going to use Squirtle.
-I choose you!
-Pika!
I can't stop now!
It almost came out.
-They won't come out.
-Huh?
For some reason, the Pokémon
don't want to battle the Diglett.
-Why wouldn't they battle?
-I just can't figure it out.
-Is that right, Pikachu?
-Pikachu.
You won't get away with this! Go away!
[Gary] That won't work.
Diglett can pull their heads in
at 186 282 miles per second.
-What's that?
-The speed of light.
Diglett aren't very strong,
but they can move super-fast.
Wow. You've been studying, huh?
Yeah, I've been studying, unlike you.
Well, that's it. I'm gone.
Look, since no one's Pokémon
will come out and battle,
there's no reason
for any trainers to be here
unless they want
to watch this arcade game.
I, on the other hand,
must continue my journey
to become a Pokémon master.
-Hasta la vista, Poké people.
-[all] Bye-bye!
Come on, fans, get in the car,
and let's hit the road, shall we?
Good luck!
Aah! I don't like him.
Girls, those numbers?
Ah, there's nothing like a hot bath.
-But something doesn't feel quite right.
-Don't complain.
We got into this place for free,
didn't we?
-No, it's not that.
-Then what's wrong?
I can't understand why the Pokémon
wouldn't come out of their Poké Balls.
-Oh, yeah. Why was that, Pikachu?
-Pika. Pika.
[all] Diglett!
Diglett.
Ash,
shouldn't we put some clothes on first?
Hey, Pikachu.
Pika, pika, pika.
I'll get you! I'll get you!
[panting]
Koffing!
[James]
Some principle of induced evolution.
It says here, "Pokémon need to have
a certain degree of experience points
before they can successfully evolve."
[James]
Our experience is nothing but losing.
But here's something to think about.
When they finally do evolve,
Pokémon become entirely different Pokémon.
-Ekans.
-We've known Ekans for so long.
-[James] Koffing too.
-Koffing.
How could we ever...
[both] Evolve them?
[both sobbing]
-Look!
-Was it...
[both] Something we said?
It could be.
[both] They're evolving for us.
Their time to evolve
just happens to be now.
[all] Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig,
Diglett, dig...
Oh.
[all] Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig,
Diglett, dig...
[all] Trio, trio, trio.
Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
Trio, trio, trio.
-Trio, trio, trio.
-Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
Pikachu.
-Trio, trio, trio.
-Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
[Pokédex]
Dugtrio. The evolved form of Diglett.
No specific information available.
Oh, now I get it.
This must be Diglett and Dugtrio's home.
-Their home?
-Yeah, they work and live here together.
Diglett plows the ground
and Dugtrio plants the trees.
And not just here.
This whole mountain range
is their backyard.
-Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
-Trio, trio, trio.
Diglett, dig, Diglett...
-[Ash] All of these mountains?
-[Brock] Yeah. Maybe.
[Brock] Probably all the forests
in the whole entire world are--
[Misty] Beautiful gardens
made by these little guys.
And if we complete the dam,
this whole mountain forest
would be completely covered with water.
[squawks] Pidgey!
Rattata!
Then nothing could live here.
[Brock] All of our Pokémon
realized that before we did.
[Misty] That's why none of them
would leave their Poké Balls,
even when their masters ordered them to.
I guess we humans
still have a lot to learn
from the ways of the Pokémon, right, Ash?
-I guess so, huh, Pikachu?
-Pikachu.
This project's canceled.
I won't build the dam.
-Trio, trio, trio.
-Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
Trio, trio, trio.
Well, I think I learned my lesson,
Pikachu.
[Jessie] Your lesson is just beginning.
-Aah!
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation...
To unite all peoples within our nation...
To denounce the evils of truth and love...
To extend our reach to the stars above...
-Hah!
-Jessie.
James.
-They know the rest.
-[both groan]
Oh, Team Rocket. I forgot about them.
Sorry, guys, but we're not in the mood
for you right now, okay?
[tuts]
But we're in a good enough mood
for everyone.
Yes, and we never even had lunch.
But now we have a special treat
for all of you.
A treat with a sensational
and exciting new flavor.
For the first time on TV.
-[Jessie] We're proud to present...
-[James] Our new Pokémon.
Our Ekans has evolved into Arbok!
Arbok!
And Koffing is now Weezing!
Weezing!
Arbok! Maximum power!
Arbok!
-Ah, we can handle this, right?
-Pi.
-Charmander!
-[Ash] Squirtle!
-Squirtle!
-[Ash] Bulbasaur!
-Bulbasaur!
-Everyone, go!
-Weezing, smog!
Weezing!
Pikachu, use your thunderbolt!
Pikachu!
Arbok! Dive underground!
-Ar!
-[James] Weezing, follow it!
[groans]
-[all Diglett] Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
-[all Dugtrio] Trio, trio, trio.
-Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
-Trio, trio, trio.
Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
[both] Trio, trio, trio. Huh?
[smacking]
What happened?
-I know what's coming.
-Me too.
-Diglett, dig, Diglett, dig.
-Trio, trio, trio.
[both groan]
[both yell]
-We're surfing.
-Yes, we're curling the shoot.
Cat-a-bunga!
[all] Hang ten, baby, yeah!
-Hey, what's that thing up ahead?
-[both] Huh?
-The dam!
-Maybe it won't hold!
[all] It looks like Team Rocket's
busted up again!
Gee, those guys never seem
to catch a break, do they?
And they never learn their lesson.
Not like me.
I definitely learned my lesson.
So our stay wasn't a waste after all.
That's right. And we're in luck.
-Fuchsia Gym's just over those mountains.
-Mm-hm.
[groans]
Ooh!
"Construction of the Giva dam canceled."
[groaning]
[narrator] And so the Diglett and Dugtrio
were left in peace,
and everybody learned
that when you do a little digging,
you can find something good
wherever you look.
And now it's on
to the next Pokémon adventure.
Okay, guys, we gotta rap some Pokémon.
You just do the singing.
I'll take care of the hard part.
Let's get it on!
♪ I want to be the best
There ever was ♪
♪ To beat all the rest, yeah
That's my cause ♪
♪ Electrode, Diglett, Nidoran, Mankey
Venusaur, Rattata, Fearow, Pidgey ♪
♪ Seaking, Jolteon, Dragonite, Gastly
Ponyta, Vaporeon, Poliwrath, Butterfree ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all! Pokémon! ♪
♪ I'll search across the land
Look far and wide ♪
♪ Release from my hand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Venomoth, Poliwag, Nidorino, Golduck
Ivysaur, Grimer, Victreebel, Moltres ♪
♪ Nidoking, Farfetch'd, Abra, Jigglypuff
Kingler, Rhyhorn, Clefable, Wigglytuff ♪
Thirty-two down, that’s it for now.
Tune in tomorrow.
We’ll rap at you some more.
There’s 150,
so watch Monday through Friday.
You’ll catch ‘em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪