♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test ♪
♪ To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all!
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Got to catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all! Pokémon! ♪
[narrator] Our young hero Ash leads
his friends deep into the forest.
Since he doesn't have a compass,
Ash must rely purely on his instincts.
And that means trouble.
Don't worry. I'm positive this way
will take us back to the path.
-Pika.
-Positive, huh?
That's what you said an hour ago.
I'm tired.
Phew! I told you
to stick to the main road,
but you had to take a shortcut.
[Ash] I took a shortcut?
It was you who said to go this way.
Ha! If I was leading,
we wouldn't have gotten lost like this.
Who says we're lost?
Listen, genius, if you don't know
where you are or where you're going,
-that means you're lost!
-Chill. Chill!
All right, but remind me
to yell at you some more
if we ever get to Vermillion City.
[squawking of forest creatures]
Time for a break.
Hmm?
[slurps]
Oh, wow, a Pokémon!
[Pokédex] Oddish. This Pokémon
is typically found roaming the forest,
scattering pollen as it walks around.
-I'll catch it.
-Hold it!
-What for?
-Because I'm going to catch that Pokémon.
Aw, no way, Misty. I saw it first.
But we found it around the water
and water is my specialty.
[grunting]
Go, Starmie!
[both grunting]
Water gun now!
Now, that's the way to spray.
Tackle it, Starmie!
That weakened it. Got to catch it now.
-Poké Ball, go! Uh-oh.
-Whoa.
Whoa! What's that?
[growling]
Wow! I can't believe it! A Bulbasaur!
[Pokédex] Bulbasaur. It bears the seed
of a plant on its back from birth.
The seed slowly develops.
Researchers are unsure whether to classify
Bulbasaur as a plant or animal.
Bulbasaur are extremely tough
and very difficult to capture in the wild.
Bulbasaur!
-Oh! Oh, Starmie, are you okay?
-Now it's my turn to try.
Bulbasaur is mine!
Butterfree, I choose you!
Butterfree, Sleep Powder!
[both grunting]
Ah! Come on.
Hang in there, Butterfree!
Oh, no.
Oh, the Bulbasaur.
-It's not fair! I want it!
-Pika.
[Ash] Heh, I'll bet there are Bulbasaur
all over this place.
-But where is "this place"?
-I can't find this bridge on my map.
[wind whistling]
[all yelling]
[all grunting]
-Brock's falling.
-Ah!
[groans]
Ash, you have to pull us back up!
It's our only chance!
-Pika!
-[Ash] I can't.
[Misty] Yes, you will!
Just pull as hard as you can!
[all pant]
-[all pant]
-Phew. I'm totally wiped out.
We can't rest now.
-We've got to find Brock.
-Right.
-Hurry up!
-Pika!
-Argh!
-Huh?
-Whoa. How'd you get down there?
-I fell in! How else?
-What's a trap doing here?
-It seems pretty strange.
[Misty]
Just help me out, quick!
-This is just not our day.
-Pikachu.
[Ash] Brock? Hey, Brock!
Think he washed this far downstream?
[all] Whoa!
[Ash] Hey, how'd we get up in a tree?
[Misty] It's another trap!
Do something!
-What can I do?
-Try wiggling. See if the net will open.
-Oh!
-Oh, this is dumb!
You got any better ideas,
let's hear 'em!
-Pi! Pika, pi!
-Bulbasaur!
-Huh?
-Huh? Bulbasaur.
Saur... Saur.
[Ash] Hold it there, Bulbasaur!
I want a match!
[Misty] Now you're wiggling too much!
Ouch, you kicked me!
[Ash] Oh, Bulbasaur!
The village we're looking for should be
on the other side of that bridge.
Let's just hope the rumors are true.
[laughs] Just wait and see what
Team Rocket's got planned for you,
you delicious little village.
[Ash]
Gee, I wonder what happened to Brock.
[Misty]
I wonder too.
[Ash] Maybe the river carried him far
away, all the way to the ocean.
Then some pirates spotted him
and brought him aboard their ship.
And one of the pirates has a wooden leg.
-You have a crazy imagination.
-Pikachu!
Then came the storm.
-[Brock] Ahoy!
-[Ash and Misty] Huh?
[Ash] Hey, Brock!
Why are you hanging around
up in that tree?
[all scream]
[all groaning]
Thanks, but maybe next time, you could
let us down a little more gently.
Yeah, sure. Sorry.
We've been looking all over for you.
We saw you fall into the river.
Then what happened?
[Brock] Well, I was being washed away
in the rapids.
[grunting]
I've got you. Just hold on.
[panting]
[Brock] The girl who saved my life
was incredibly beautiful.
[Ash] Hm, a beautiful girl, huh?
That's even better than pirates.
Unless, of course,
she was really a pirate in disguise.
Maybe it's time to get a reality check.
[laughs]
-Oh!
-Melanie, this is Ash and Misty.
-Hello.
-So you're Brock's friends.
-He told me all about you.
-Great.
Wow, look at that!
-Do all those Pokémon belong to you?
-[Melanie] Oh, no.
This is a place where Pokémon
are able to rest and relax.
-Like summer camp?
-Well, sort of, but all year long.
You see, when Pokémon get abandoned
or injured, they can come here.
Melanie takes care of them
until they feel better. Then they leave.
So this is a Pokémon center
and Melanie is a Pokémon doctor.
Oh, no. I'm not qualified
to be a Pokémon doctor.
-This is more like a Pokémon health spa.
-Huh?
[Melanie] Here, the Pokémon don't battle
with one another.
They relax and try to enjoy themselves
until they've recovered.
Cool.
Melanie collects plants
to use for medicine.
She knows all about which plants
can help a Pokémon feel better
or grow stronger when it's too weak.
So you and Melanie both love
to take care of Pokémon.
We do.
[grunts]
Well, it looks to me like there's
something else Brock might love, heh.
[yelling]
-Be quiet! She might hear you!
-Heh.
I wonder who put that net up in the tree.
Probably the same person
who dug the hole I fell into.
[Melanie] I'm sorry.
I was the one who set those traps.
I wanted to catch Pokémon trainers
before they reached the village.
Since you got caught,
I guess they really worked, heh.
-But why?
-There are so many injured Pokémon here.
I have to protect them.
-So the bridge was a trap too.
-Yes.
Across this bridge
lies a lifetime supply of Pokémon.
How are we ever going
to carry them all?
Don't worry, we'll cross that bridge
when we come to it.
[all yelling]
I promised Melanie
we wouldn't capture any Pokémon here.
And did you seal the promise with a kiss?
Ow!
So that must mean
you really do love her. Ow!
Well, I guess I'll have to keep
your promise.
Only bad guys try to capture
sick Pokémon.
But are those traps tough enough
to keep robbers away from this place?
I mean, you'd have to be pretty stupid
-to fall into one of those holes.
-Hey!
[Team Rocket yelling]
This is the third hole we've fallen into.
How come nobody ever falls into our traps
but we always fall into theirs?
Well, this one was very cleverly hidden,
well made, and--
-I'm glad you're enjoying it so much!
-Meowth!
[all yell]
[all yell and mutter]
-[Meowth] Help me out! Help me out!
-[James] Get us out of here!
Ouch, my tail! Let go!
Stop pulling my tail!
[grunts]
Do you feel any better yet, Staryu?
Sorry about what happened in the forest.
Oddish.
I shouldn't have surprised you like that,
heh. You must've been scared.
Oddish.
Melanie told me
your old trainer got rid of you.
Was it really
because he thought you were too weak?
Oddish.
You know, some trainers
can be insensitive.
But not all of us are mean like that.
[giggles]
You just need to find a trainer
who understands you.
Anyway, I'm sorry for what I did
and I hope we can become friends.
Oddish.
[sobs]
-Huh?
-Oddish. Oddish.
You're sweet, Oddish. I am sorry.
All I think about lately is winning.
I hope I'm not becoming heartless.
-You were always heartless.
-Mind your own business!
Bulbasaur!
[all grunt]
-Hey, it's rude to tackle people!
-She's right.
[growls]
I know. You're just mad
because I was going to beat you.
-But you chickened out and ran off.
-That must be it.
Then let's see how tough you really are.
-[Melanie] Please wait. Please.
-Huh?
Bulbasaur is only trying
to protect Oddish.
Bulbasaur volunteered to guard
our whole village.
-[both] Huh?
-It protects all the injured Pokémon
whenever enemies try
to attack them.
[both] Oh.
Bulbasaur is the bravest
and most loyal Pokémon I know.
So that's why Bulbasaur attacked me.
It must've thought
I was taking Oddish from the village.
[Bulbasaur gibbering]
[Ash] Now what?
Bulbasaur doesn't like Pokémon trainers.
It wants you to leave the village now.
[Misty] But we're not here to capture
Pokémon. We want to help you.
It's true, Bulbasaur.
These are our friends.
[grunting]
Bulbasaur was worried
about the other Pokémon,
so it decided to be the village bodyguard.
Now, that's what I call bravery.
It would be great to have a Pokémon
like that.
To protect the world from devastation.
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love.
To extend our reach to the stars above.
Team Rocket,
blast off at the speed of light.
-Surrender now or prepare to fight.
-That's right.
We've said our lines.
Time to attack the village.
Those village idiots thought
their measly traps would stop us.
They thought
they had the home team advantage.
No such luck.
We're the home team now.
I congratulate myself
for this brilliant scheme.
Don't forget, I suggested tying balloons
on the stadium roof.
[warbling]
[both exclaim]
-Here we go again.
-Today only at Jessie stadium.
-It's the Team Rocket Pokémon challenge.
-The flying stadium was my idea.
Oh, heh.
All Pokémon are invited
to enter the stadium.
Step right up.
Yeah, we're not hosing you.
Well, maybe we are.
[all grunting]
They never run out of ideas, do they?
Hurry! Everybody get in the cabin!
Wait. No! Oddish!
[grunting]
Bulbasaur.
-Bulbasaur!
-Take Staryu.
Keep going, Bulbasaur! Ugh.
That rotten little pest.
He's always ruining our flawless plans.
Not this time. He's gathered them all
in one place for us.
Our super-vacuum will suck up them up.
[all] Let's go, team!
To steal them is our dream!
Let's go, Rocket!
Put Pokémon in our pocket!
[grunting]
Pidgeotto, I choose you!
Pidgeotto, Gust attack!
[squawking]
-And the tornado's winding up.
-But will it strike us out?
There goes the whole ballgame.
[all yelling]
[James] The home team
really got blown away.
[Meowth] So what are we going to do now,
challenge them to wind surfing?
[all yelling and screaming]
[Meowth] Looks like Team Rocket's
blasting off again.
Is everyone feeling okay?
I just had the wind knocked out of me.
Bulbasaur.
This village is well-protected
with Bulbasaur here.
Ash, don't you agree that Bulbasaur would
be an excellent addition to your team?
Oh, yeah, would he ever!
-I think Bulbasaur should go with you.
-Huh?
Bulbasaur stayed here
to protect the weaker Pokémon.
But this village is too small.
The bulb on its back can't grow.
It needs to go out into the world now
and I know you'll take good care of it.
Please do me this favor. Take
Bulbasaur with you on your journey.
He'll be a good companion.
But what will happen to the village
without Bulbasaur?
Yeah, who's going to protect you?
It's true that Bulbasaur has done
a great job, maybe too great a job.
You see, these Pokémon shouldn't
remain in this village forever and ever.
After they recover,
the Pokémon are supposed to leave.
But it's too safe here,
so none of them wants to go away.
They don't want to return
to the outside world.
Oddish.
But I think it's important
that all of them return to the wild.
That's where Pokémon belong.
And hopefully, someday,
they'll find good trainers like you.
Of course, taking care of sick Pokémon
will always be my mission
but I know my job isn't finished
until they return where they came from,
so it's the day a Pokémon leaves
that is most rewarding to me.
Melanie, I--
So you see,
it's time for Bulbasaur to leave here.
Please take it with you.
It won't be a burden, I promise.
Bulbasaur still has a lot of growing
to do.
I want it to be in a place where I'm sure
it can grow strong and happy.
I'm sure that place is with you, Ash.
Well, if you really want me to.
Bulbasaur.
[giggles]
What did it say?
Bulbasaur will join you on one condition.
It wants to battle you in a Pokémon match.
-Right, Bulbasaur?
-Bulbasaur.
Ha! If you want a match, you'll get it.
Oh, please let me battle with Bulbasaur.
-Please? Pretty please?
-No way.
-Pika.
-Bulbasaur.
Pikachu, go!
[both grunting]
Pikachu! Look out, Pikachu!
[grunting continues]
Ah! The Vine Whip is Bulbasaur's
special move.
Ah, Pikachu, Thunderbolt!
All right. Poké Ball, go!
We did it! We got Bulbasaur.
Pikachu.
Bulbasaur, I'll miss you.
[Melanie] Have a safe trip.
I promise to take good care
of Bulbasaur.
Bulbasaur, thank you for watching over us.
[gibbers]
-Uh, Melanie, I've been thinking.
-Yes?
Well, since Bulbasaur is leaving,
I wouldn't mind staying
and helping you out.
It's very kind of you but we'll be okay.
I wouldn't want to keep you
from all of your wonderful adventures.
Oh. Yeah, I guess you're right.
-Goodbye, Melanie.
-Goodbye. Good luck.
Bulbasaur.
Don't worry, Bulbasaur.
You'll see your friends again.
As soon as the Pokémon feel better,
they'll leave this village too.
Bulba.
Take good care of each other.
Bye-bye.
[sighs]
So what did Melanie say
when you told her you loved her?
-Did you kiss her goodbye?
-That's enough stupid questions.
Would you please stop embarrassing me
already? You know, okay, so she's cute.
-I understand that!
-[Misty grunts]
Did I miss something?
What's going on?
Bulba.
[narrator]
With Bulbasaur now at his side,
it looks like Ash is building
his own dream team.
Now it's on to Vermilion City.
Let's just hope our heroes
don't take any more shortcuts,
or we may never get there.
♪ Pokémon! ♪
Get those lips loose!
It’s time to Pokérap!
Come on, sing ‘em with me!
That’s the game!
There’s 150 Pokémon.
How many can you name?
♪ Gotta catch 'em all,
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
♪ Sandslash, Hitmonlee, Psyduck
Arcanine, Eevee, Exeggutor ♪
♪ Kabutops, Zapdos, Dratini
Growlithe, Mr. Mime, Cubone ♪
♪ Graveler, Voltorb, Gloom
We're almost home ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
Gotta catch 'em all! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Charmeleon, Wartortle, Mewtwo
Tentacruel, Aerodactyl, Omanyte ♪
-♪ Slowpoke, Pidgeot, Arbok ♪
-That's all, folks!
Can you name all the Pokémon?
Just put today’s song together
with the other days of the week.
That’s why you can’t miss a show.
You gotta catch 'em all!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Ooh, gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
Catch 'em, catch 'em ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all! Pokémon! ♪