♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny ♪
♪ Pokémon! Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, gotta catch 'em all
[narrator]
After crossing the grassland,
our heroes find themselves
in the Safari Zone
where wild Pokémon roam free,
just waiting to be captured.
Mankey! Mankey! Mankey! Mankey!
[trilling]
Wow, this place is like a dream.
Pokémon wherever you look.
It must be the Safari Zone.
Let's start catching them.
-Wait a minute, Ash.
-We might still be in the Pokémon reserve.
This has to be the Safari Zone.
Just take a look at all these Pokémon.
Ah, it's Chansey! Here's my chance.
I'm going to catch it.
[all yell]
-Freeze! Drop that Poké Ball.
-[groans]
My name is Jenny, safari ranger.
You're under arrest for Pokémon poaching.
[all gasp]
-Under arrest?
-Pi, Pikachu.
This is a national
Pokémon preservation area.
It's here for the raising and protection
of Pokémon.
I'm real sorry. I didn't know that.
Well, you look
like you really didn't know,
so I'm going to let you go
with a warning this time.
Oh, thank you.
Well, that's so nice of you, Ranger Jenny.
Well, I'm glad that's all cleared up.
[alarm beeping]
[both] Huh?
Another poacher!
Let us help you out, Jenny.
We want to make up
for what happened before.
-Thanks. Get on in.
-Right.
[engine rattles]
[all yelling]
[all grunting]
[Meowth]
There they are. We hit the jackpot.
Kangaskhan parent and child Pokémon.
[cackles]
All right, you guys, time to get to work.
[Jessie] Prepare for trouble.
[James] Make it double.
[Jessie]
To protect the world from devastation...
[James]
To unite all peoples within our nation.
To denounce the evils of truth and love...
To extend our reach to the stars above...
-Jessie.
-James.
While you two are standing around
reciting poetry,
the Kangaskhan are going to get away.
Come on, hurry up!
-Be quiet, Meowth.
-We know what to do without you yelling.
We have to say our poem
or it just doesn't feel right.
Now stand aside and watch us work.
What are you doing?
We're trying to catch the Pokémon,
not blast them.
Keep quiet and watch.
[all gasp]
[Pokédex]
Kangaskhan. A parent Pokémon.
Once approaching extinction,
they are now protected by law
and inhabit the Safari Zone.
Approach with extreme caution.
The Kangaskhan is a rare Pokémon,
which raise its children in its pocket.
They will attack viciously
and without warning
if they feel their young are threatened
in any way.
Wow.
Fire.
[all growling]
-Hey, what's that?
-Over there! Poachers.
-[all gasp]
-[Ash] It's Team Rocket.
[groans] We've got to stop them.
I'm afraid if we're going to stop them,
we're going to have to run away first.
[both] What?
-Huh?
-Ah! What's that?
[all snarling]
Kangaskhan are easily scared,
but once they're surprised,
they never stop charging.
[all gasp and scream]
That's it. Charge right into our net.
[all growl]
[laughs] Look at all the mighty Kangaskhan
we've caught in our trap.
-Well, well, which one shall I pick?
-That parent and child sure look nice.
[squeaks]
[growling]
We can't let Team Rocket
get away with this.
Pikachu.
Ah!
Look at those poor baby Kangaskhan.
Quick, Jenny,
we have to do something to save them.
It's no good.
I overheated the engine on the last stunt.
[all] Huh?
[all scream]
Kanga!
I claim this Pokémon for Team Rocket.
[screams and grunts]
Who did that? Who's out there?
[boy] Kanga!
What's that sound?
Kanga! Kangas!
Kangas! Kang!
Kangas, kangas.
Kangas, Kangaskhan.
What does that little savage think
he's doing?
You can't have them! We caught them.
[grunting]
Kangas, kangas, kang!
[all growl]
I don't like the way
they're looking at us.
They're staring straight at us.
Quit yapping
and let's get out of here fast.
Kangas, kang!
[all whimpering]
[grunts] Kanga!
[all scream]
Kangaskhan!
[both] Team Rocket's blasting off again!
[all chattering]
[grunts] Kangas, Kangaskhan!
[all]
Kangaskhan! Kangaskhan! Kangaskhan!
That's amazing how he can command
all of those Kangaskhan
just by yelling like that.
Hm, yeah. He's very good.
Just a kid, but he could become
a famous Pokémon trainer.
I hear something.
-[helicopter approaches]
-Huh?
[Ash] Oh! Who's that? [coughs]
Greetings. Please excuse the noise.
-Are you the Safari Zone Pokémon ranger?
-Yes.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Tommy's father.
I came here because I heard that
someone had seen my son, Tommy,
in this area.
Your son, Tommy,
is here in the Safari Zone?
Papa, I think we have to tell them
a little more about Tommy.
Of course. You're right. Forgive me.
-Right.
-Sure.
You can explain the rest
back at the station.
A splendid idea.
It happened five years ago.
Tommy was only three years old
when we decided take him with us
-on a family trip around the world.
-That's correct.
[Pokémon trill]
Mankey! Mankey! Mankey!
See, Tommy,
look at all the Pokémon down there.
-Here, take a closer look.
-Papa, be careful!
Don't worry, my dear.
Tommy's having such a good time.
-[screams]
-Oh! Oh, Tommy!
Don't worry about him, Mama.
He just wants to get a closer look.
What a smart boy our Tommy is.
[mother]
There's nothing but a parachute left.
Maybe if you had been holding him,
this wouldn't have happened.
It's your fault!
[whimpers]
Ever since that day,
we've searched high and low,
but we can't find him anywhere.
Pika. [whimpers]
Quit that, Pikachu.
You're going to make me cry too.
It's just like Papa said.
We looked as hard as we could
but couldn't find him anywhere.
Then someone sent us a picture
of a young boy
who leads a huge pack of Kangaskhan
here in the Safari Zone.
I always knew that this day would come.
Someone was bound to see Tommy somewhere.
I know it's a bother,
but would you consider helping us
in our search?
We'll do anything.
Here's the picture.
If Tommy is still alive,
he would be just about this age.
Ah, you mean Tomo.
You won't have to look far.
His address is listed right here
in the Safari Zone directory.
[gasps]
Really? Thank goodness.
We saw him out in the jungle
just before you came.
My friends and I'd be glad to help you
find him if you want us to.
Pika, pi.
-Oh, please let us help you.
-It would be our pleasure.
Thank you all so much.
Now we can finally be united with our son
and live together as a family.
Ah, it's lovely
riding through the jungle like this.
[all groaning and panting]
How'd we end up with a job like this?
It's because you had to go
and volunteer us all.
You're the one who said:
"Oh, please let us help you."
[groans] Why did we have to go
and open our big mouths?
I apologize for this.
Papa doesn't get outdoors much,
and he's not in the best of shape.
I admit it.
Pika. Pika?
[whimpering]
Wait, what's that?
[all] Huh?
Ow! My lumbago. Ow!
[whimpers]
-A baby Kangaskhan.
-It looks like it's injured.
-Leave it to me.
-Can you treat it, Brock?
Don't forget, Ash, I've been studying
to be the world's best Pokémon breeder.
You'll be just fine.
This'll sting a little, but it'll make
your wound heal faster. I promise.
[screeches]
-Look out behind you!
-Huh?
[groans]
-Pika, pi!
-Tomo!
You hurt Kangaskhan. That bad.
No, we didn't.
Brock was just trying to help
the baby Kangaskhan because it's hurt.
That is,
until you threw your boomerang at him.
Now apologize!
Uh, what's the matter?
You people or Pokémon?
Ah!
I'm a person, you creep!
Hurry, my dear. It sounds
like they may have found our Tommy.
Huh? Who you, old man?
I am Papa, this is your mama,
and you are our son, Tommy.
Tommy, come home
with your mommy and daddy.
They Pokémon or peoples?
They're peoples... Uh, people!
Tommy these two people are your parents.
Your mother and father.
They've been looking for you
for a very long time.
Mother? Father?
It's no good, Ash. He doesn't know them.
He was only three
when they were separated.
Take a good look. Try to remember.
This is your mother and your father,
and your real name is Tommy.
Think back, Tommy.
Try to remember, Tommy.
[all singing and humming]
[all gasp]
-Tommy.
-Do you know me, son?
Do you remember them now, Tommy?
[groans]
Tomo mama Kangaskhan!
Mama Kangaskhan!
[groans]
-What are you doing, Papa?
-He'll be fine.
We'll just take him home
and start from scratch.
Look what you've done to him.
Tommy, can you hear me? Tommy.
Tommy. Tommy!
Tommy, my little boy.
Mama. Mama!
[laughing]
[mother] Tommy. Tommy! Tommy.
-Are you all right, Tommy?
-Mama.
Tommy. Oh, my little boy remembers me.
That clonk on the head must have helped
bring your son's memory back.
Tommy, my boy, remember Papa?
Doh! [groans]
One memory at a time, okay, Papa?
Forgive us, Tommy.
You must have been so lonely.
We'll never be separated again.
Now let's go home.
Your mother and your father
have been looking all over for you
for years, Tommy.
I know it's going to be hard
to leave the Kangaskhan, Tommy,
but wouldn't it be a whole lot better
to live with your real parents?
Sometimes, the real parent's
the one who raises you,
but this is a real unusual situation.
Tomo mama Kangaskhan,
but this lady Tomo mama too.
You can't live with both of them, Tommy.
Kangaskhan mama too!
This lady mama too!
Tommy head feel bad.
Tommy. Huh?
I need your help.
Someone's poaching Kangaskhan again.
[all gasp]
[grunts] Kanga, Kangaskhan!
Tommy!
Come on, let's go.
[Tommy] Kanga!
Tommy must feel that those Kangaskhan
are his real parents after all.
He's completely turned into Tomo.
I guess we'll have to give up.
Don't say that, Mama.
Deep down, Tommy is still our boy.
Papa.
Yes?
All right,
let's get this show on the road.
Now I will present my impression
of an injured Kangaskhan
for your enjoyment.
[in a low voice]
Kangaskhan! Kangaskhan!
[all grunting]
Kangaskhan, kangas.
[growling]
They're headed this way.
They can't tell it's a fake.
[laughs] Our plan's a success.
We're finally getting our Pokémon.
James, put the Kangaskhan to sleep,
and we'll round them all up!
Firing tranquilizer.
[all grunting and yelling]
[growling]
[grunts]
Kangaskhan.
Now's our chance.
Let's get our new Kangaskhan.
Kanga!
[gasps]
You bad Kangaskhan.
Tomo angry! [grunts]
Kangaskhan?
-It's jungle boy.
-He ruined our plan last time.
This time, let's show him who's boss.
Rocket punch.
[screams]
That Team Rocket. We got to stop them.
Bulbasaur, I choose you.
Bulbasaur!
Bulbasaur, quick.
Use your vine whip now!
Bulbasaur!
Squirtle, I choose you.
Squirtle, Squirtle.
Squirtle, go!
Give them your skull bash attack.
Squirtle! Squirt!
Kanga!
Kanga, kanga, Kangaskhan!
-All that banging is giving me a headache.
-This ought to fix that.
Kanga, kanga, kanga!
[grunting]
Huh?
[Meowth] You've been a bad boy.
Tommy! Pikachu.
Pika.
Charmander, I choose you.
Char!
Pikachu, Charmander,
thunder shock and flamethrower.
-Pikachu!
-Char!
[grunts] Kanga!
[all yelling]
-Great!
-Tomo do it!
-Oh, no!
-Get in quick!
[laughs]
They think they have us beat, do they?
Let's give them a taste
of our super punch.
One super punch coming right up.
[all] Huh?
Don't worry!
We're coming to save you, Tommy!
[all screaming]
[all] Looks like Team Rocket's
blasting off again.
Tommy's parents saved us all.
They sacrificed themselves
so they could save their son's life.
They really loved him.
[whimpers and sobs]
[wails]
Pikachu.
[muffled singing]
You are my little Tommy
[all] Huh?
Tommy, your father and I decided
that if you love the Kangaskhan so much,
we'll stay here
and protect the Pokémon with you.
Let Mama and Papa
join your family, Tommy.
[all] Huh?
Papa. Mama.
[yells]
We'll be together from now on, Tommy.
Good.
[Ash] Do you think Tommy and his parents
really can be a family?
[Brock] Ash, they love each other.
They'll be just fine.
It might be tough, though.
After all, they were apart for five years.
And it's going to be hard for them
even to communicate.
Pikachu.
Pika? Pika, pika!
[all] Huh?
[laughter]
[all] Kangas, kangas, Kangaskhan!
[both] Kangas, kangas, Kangaskhan!
-I think you're right, Brock.
-Like I said, they'll be just fine.
Kanga, Kangaskhan!
[narrator]
Seeing the happy family reunited,
Ash remembers his own mother
waiting patiently for him in Pallet.
But now our heroes journey on,
eager for more new adventures
and more new Pokémon.
[all]
Kangas, kangas, Kangaskhan!
[all laugh]
I guess like son like father.
-♪ Pokémon! ♪
-Attention, all Pokémon trainers!
Do you got what it takes to be
the best?
Today, we’ll do 30 Pokémon!
It’s the ultimate test!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all, yeah! ♪
♪ Articuno, Jynx, Nidorina, Beedrill
Haunter, Squirtle, Chansey, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Parasect, Exeggcute, Muk, Dewgong
Pidgeotto, Lapras, Vulpix, Rhydon ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
♪ Charizard, Machamp, Pinsir, Koffing
Dugtrio, Golbat, Staryu, Magikarp ♪
♪ Ninetales, Ekans, Omastar ♪
♪ Scyther, Tentacool
Dragonair, Magmar ♪
Not bad, not bad!
Hey, don’t get cocky.
Tomorrow’s the hardest part.
We’re on our way up to 150 Pokémon!
There’s no stopping us!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all
♪ Pokémon ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪