♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me, and I'll teach you
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, gotta catch 'em all
[narrator] Dark City.
This looks like the next stop
on the journey for Ash, Misty and Brock.
Who knows what kind of chilling
new challenge
our heroes could face
in this dingy, deserted ghost town.
This place gives me the creeps.
It's the middle of the day
and there's nobody around.
-What's the deal?
-[Ash] Yeah.
[laughing]
Get back inside this house right now.
What if there are Pokémon trainers out?
Huh?
Why would she be afraid
of Pokémon trainers?
-Pika!
-Hey, you!
Go, Pikachu!
Pikachu!
[screaming]
[groaning]
[all] Huh?
They're little kids.
I'm sorry, but you guys
were throwing those rocks at us.
Chu!
-You guys are Pokémon trainers right?
-Huh?
Yeah, my name's Ash.
I want to become
the world's greatest Pokémon master.
I'm Brock, and I want to become
the world's best Pokémon breeder.
And I'm going to be
the world's best everything.
My name's Misty.
[grunts]
[all groaning]
Hey kid, cut it out, will you?
We don't care who you are.
If you work with Pokémon,
you better get out of our town now.
[both] Mm-hm.
Why? What's wrong with Pokémon?
[man] Stop it, boys!
I apologize.
These children don't mean to cause you
any trouble.
Come to my restaurant,
and I'll explain everything.
Well, okay.
In Dark City, there are two Pokémon gyms:
The Yas Gym and the Kaz Gym.
The two gyms are in the middle
of a gang war,
and they'll hire
any wandering Pokémon trainers
as soldiers to battle for them.
-I get it.
-Chu.
So that's why there's nobody
out on the streets here.
Hey, Pikachu, pour some ketchup for me,
will you?
Wh... Whoa! Whoa!
-Pika. Pi, pika.
-But I don't see.
What's the point
of fighting each other like this?
-Pika!
-Huh?
They claim that whatever gym wins
will become an official Pokémon gym.
-[Ash groans]
-[gasps]
-That makes sense.
-Chu.
Becoming an official Pokémon gym's
a big honor.
[distant crashing]
It's them!
[all] Huh?
-What is that?
-The Yas and Kaz Gyms are fighting again.
If you don't want
to get dragged into this,
you'd better go upstairs and hide.
Get ready!
Today, the Kaz Gym Is going to crush you!
Guess again!
The Yas Gym will wipe you out!
Go, Electabuzz! Thunderbolt, now!
[warbling]
[screaming]
We can't let them win. Attack, Scyther.
Scyther!
-[all] Ah!
-[man] Let's get out of here!
Is it always like this?
[all] Yeah.
Now I can understand
why everybody around here
hates Pokémon trainers.
That's not even a Pokémon battle.
It's more like a street fight.
Hmm, those bullies.
They don't even understand
what it really means
to be a Pokémon trainer.
[man whimpering]
Hey, cook.
Give me the lunch special for 30 people.
[Jessie] We've got to be at Kaz Gym
in less than an hour.
[James] Throw in an order of onion rings
while you're at it.
I'd like to, but you see,
the Kaz Gym hasn't paid its bill
in over in two years.
There's something familiar about them.
[Jessie] What? Are you telling us
we can't put this on our tab?
[James] Do you realize
we're Kaz Gym bodyguards?
Give us the food or else...
I'd like to but I can't.
I don't want any trouble.
You won't give us lunch,
but you don't want trouble, huh?
You're talking to the wrong customers
if you don't want any trouble.
Please leave me alone.
I don't want any trouble.
Trouble?
Trouble.
-[James] I can't resist, Jessie.
-[Jessie] Neither can I.
-Prepare for trouble.
-Make it double.
To protect the world from devastation...
To unite all peoples within our nation...
[all gasp]
[Jessie]
To denounce the evils of truth and love...
[James]
To extend our reach to the stars above.
-[Jessie] Jessie...
-[James]James...
Go get them, Arbok!
Weezing, attack!
-Arbok!
-Weezing!
-Meowth!
-Ah!
It's Team Rocket. I knew it.
Stop them, Pikachu!
Pika!
Starmie attack!
Go, Vulpix!
[both] Vulpix?
[howling]
-Rare.
-Medium.
Well-done.
-Meowth!
-[both] Ah!
-Nice to see you leave!
-Don't come back any time!
[man groaning]
Are you all right?
Thank you for saving my restaurant.
Aw, it was fun to beat Team Rocket.
You didn't do anything.
It was Brock's Vulpix that did the work.
[Ash]
Uh, yeah, I guess you're right about that.
That was great.
I saw everything that happened.
[all] Huh?
Excuse me, is there some way
we can help you, miss?
Those were some
of the strongest bodyguards from Kaz Gym.
How did you overpower them so easily?
You must be a very gifted,
very famous Pokémon trainer.
[moans]
Please, please.
You must tell me your names.
Gee, that's very nice.
If we get mixed up in this gang war,
it could ruin our reputations
as Pokémon trainers.
-Just make up a name, quick.
-Uh...
-I'm, uh, ketchup.
-Pikachu.
-Ketchup?
-Uh, no.
My name is really Tom Ayto.
[Misty groans]
Well, my name...
My name is Ann Chovie.
-Huh, huh, huh?
-Uh...
Oh, and my name Is Caesar Salad.
Oh, Tom, Ann, Caesar,
Would you consider joining our cause
at the Yas Gym?
Unlike those animals from the Kaz Gym,
we at Yas are truly worthy
of becoming a Pokémon gym.
Uh, well, you better ask Ann Chovie.
Well, we can't do it.
Isn't that right, Caesar Salad?
We'll do anything we can to help.
[groaning]
Pika!
Brock just can't say no to a pretty girl.
[grunting]
-Wow.
-Please, come right in.
Yas leader.
Let me introduce you to a great trainer.
This is Pokémon trainer Tom Ayto.
He's brought his two disciples to help us.
He brought us?
[chuckles]
Pikachu.
I saw them defeat the bodyguards
from Kaz Gym like they were nothing.
They're really strong trainers.
I'll decide just how strong they are.
Scyther, go!
Scyther!
Pika!
Scy!
Scyther!
Scyther, what is it?
-Whoa!
-Scyther!
Whoa, hey!
-Stop!
Scyther, return.
Scyther!
That's the first time my scyther
has been frightened so badly.
You are a powerful trainer.
-Well--
-You must work for me.
-I need your strength.
-Pi.
-First, I have one thing to ask you:
Why is it so important
that this should become
an official Pokémon gym?
That answer should be obvious.
What faster way is there
to make money in today's world
than by becoming
an official Pokémon gym?
Well, if that's your reason,
-I won't become your bodyguard.
-What?
Pokémon are not just tools for fighting
or a way of making money.
And I know because I plan on becoming
a Pokémon master.
I won't help you.
[thinking]
That was dramatic.
Whoa!
That was pathetic!
If you won't join us,
we'll make sure
you don't help anybody else.
Yas Gym, attack!
[grunting]
Ah!
-Wow, that was a close one.
-That Yas Gym plays rough.
I think the Kaz Gym plays
just the same way.
They think Pokémon battling's
like plain old fighting.
Imagine if they became
an official Pokémon gym.
Kaz and Yas keep getting stronger Pokémon
and they wreck our town
with their fighting.
If this keeps up, people will think
all Pokémon trainers are dangerous.
-Yeah, that Scyther is really scary.
-Pikachu.
I wonder how we get out so easily.
I don't know.
Scyther!
Scy!
Oh, ketchup.
[Pokédex] Scyther and Electabuzz
are both rare Pokémon.
They are able to distinguish colors
and become enraged by the color red.
Like the ketchup.
Scyther is the Yas Gym's
strongest Pokémon,
and Electabuzz is the Kaz Gym's
strongest Pokémon.
Huh?
If we work together,
we might just be able to beat them.
Listen up!
The Pokémon league inspector
will be coming through town any minute.
We have to run those Kaz Gym losers
out of town before he gets here.
[leader]
Pokémon league inspector is on his way.
We have to completely crush
those Yas Gym trainers
and show him we're the best.
This town's only big enough for one gym.
Ka. Pika. Ka.
[grunting]
All right, weather looks fine
and everything is all set and ready to go.
I'm only going to say this once
to youse guys.
Kaz Gym's going to be
the official gym of Dark City.
Save yourself some trouble
and just clear out now.
I'm afraid you have things all mixed up.
You're the ones
who'd better clear out and fast.
Leave now or we'll crush you
like the slimy insects you are.
Ooh! Now you're going to be sorry
you ever heard the name of Kaz Gym!
Today's the day
we finally destroy you once and for all!
[grunting]
I've heard enough!
Electabuzz, go!
Get them, Scyther.
[warbling]
Scyther, scy!
[all grunting]
Monchan!
Hitmonlee!
[grunting]
Electabuzz,
send them flying with a thunder punch!
[warbling]
[grunting]
Don't give in, Scyther!
Power up with sword dance, and cut attack!
Scyther! [growling]
Scyther!
[moaning]
-When do we get our turn?
-It's over already.
Meowth!
Go, Electabuzz!
Just burn that Scyther to a crisp.
Don't give in, Scyther.
Slice that Electabuzz to ribbons.
[grunting]
It's time. Do it.
[all] Heave-ho!
Huh?
[grunting]
Ah!
Hey, what's going on?
[al] Huh?
[all groan]
Scyther!
-Ah! My best gym suit!
-Scyther!
[warbling]
Huh?
-Scyther!
-Huh?
What are you doing, Electabuzz?
Hurry up and crush that Scyther!
-What's wrong with you, Scyther?
-Scyther!
-Cut attack, now!
[warbling]
[both] Ah!
Scyther!
[warbling]
-Scyther!
-Wait! Stop!
You're making a mistake.
I'm your trainer, Scyther!
[screaming]
What are you doing? No!
It's me, Electabuzz, your trainer!
[screaming]
You don't have the right
to call yourself Pokémon trainers
after what you've made them do.
But please, you've got to save me!
[screaming]
-Scyther!
-Ahh!
[both screaming]
Scyther!
Think they've had enough?
[Misty]
I think they've learned their lesson.
All right, Bulbasaur, I choose you!
Bulbasaur!
Scyther!
-Huh?
-Scy?
-Ther?
Scyther!
[grunting]
Scy...
-Scyther!
-Electabuzz!
Well, I hope you two
have learned your lesson.
Bulbasaur.
Shall we join together then?
At least until we've destroyed
those meddling kids.
-Chu!
-Huh?
[both] Come on!
Attack those kids on the roof now!
[all screaming]
They're going to have
to learn the hard way.
-Pikachu.
-Pikachu!
Pikachu, thunder attack!
Pi... ka-pika!
Chu!
[screaming]
-[Ash] Now then.
-[both] Huh?
Why can't we all just get along
like friends?
[both] Like friends?
-Now we'll teach you.
-I suggest you run.
[all gasp]
-Hold it right there.
-[all] Huh?
-What?
-And who are you?
I'm the inspector
from the official Pokémon League.
[both screaming]
Poké Ball, go.
[screaming]
Chansey, Chansey!
[men groan]
Chansey? That must mean...
That's right.
My true identity is Nurse Joy.
Uh...
I could never allow people
who use Pokémon for nothing
but street fighting
to open an official Pokémon gym.
-Please, Nurse Joy.
-Won't you give us another chance?
Only if you're willing to start over
from the beginning.
Of course we are.
Just tell us what we should do, Nurse Joy.
There's someone here who can do that
better than I can.
Who? Me?
[both] Oh, please.
Please teach us how to act.
Uh, well, you see,
Pokémon are really our friends,
so we've got to be kind to them.
But what about Pokémon battles?
Of course, you fight them
as hard as you can,
with all your strength, trying to win.
With all your strength?
Isn't that the same as fighting?
No, no. Not at all.
Sure you try to win,
but you don't try to beat each other.
[both] Huh?
[chuckles]
What is Ash trying to say anyway?
Heh, I don't think he knows himself.
Now, first, you'll have to fix
everything you broke in this town.
[both] At once, Tom Ayto!
Huh?
Oh, I should've picked a better name.
[grunting]
It looks like they've all had
a change of heart
and decided
to become true Pokémon trainers.
[all] Thanks!
You did it, Ash.
No, I didn't do it all by myself.
We all did it together.
We were wrong about Pokémon trainers
being bad guys.
Now we all want to become
Pokémon trainers.
[both] Right.
-We think Pokémon are the coolest.
-Just like you.
Oh, I'm not. It was nothing.
[all]
Can we have your autograph, Pikachu?
[groans]
Pi? Pika?
Oh, well, Pikachu really is the star.
-Goodbye now!
-We'll miss you!
Thanks for helping us!
[narrator] Now Dark City's a lot brighter,
thanks to our heroes.
[sighs]
Those kids really appreciate me.
[kids] We'll miss you...
Pikachu!
[Ash groans]
[narrator] After saving the town
and making some new Pokémon fans,
our heroes are moving on
to their next adventure.
Well, that was a complete waste of time.
Looks like we're through.
Huh?
Unfortunately we're not quite through yet.
[both] Huh?
Scyther!
[whimpering and screaming]
[James] Somebody...
[all] Help!
You guys up for the Pokérap?
There's 150 Pokémon.
You gotta name 'em all!
I'm doing 32 today, so try to keep up.
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ Zubat, Primeape, Meowth, Onix
Geodude, Rapidash, Magneton, Snorlax ♪
♪ Gengar, Tangela, Goldeen, Spearow
Weezing, Seel, Gyarados, Slowbro ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
Gotta catch 'em all! ♪
♪ Kabuto, Persian, Paras, Horsea
Raticate, Magnemite, Kadabra, Weepinbell ♪
♪ Ditto, Cloyster, Caterpie, Sandshrew
Bulbasaur, Charmander, Golem, Pikachu ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
All right, how'd you do?
Loosen those lips,
shake out that tongue!
Give it a rest, today's song is sung.
We'll be back tomorrow!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ It's you and me
I know it's my destiny! Pokémon! ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through ♪
♪ You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon! Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Pokémon! ♪