♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch them all
Pokémon ♪
[narrator] Ash and his friends arrive
in Mossgreen Village.
It's a quaint, cute place,
but it's so small
it doesn't even have its own Pokémon Gym.
There's no use stopping here
if they don't have a Gym.
-[Brock] We don't have any choice.
-Huh?
We have a big problem.
Check out our potion and antidote bag.
Huh? It's empty.
I'd say this is a good time
to stock up on supplies.
Might as well grab a bite to eat, too.
I'm dying for a cheeseburger.
[Misty] No way.
I want to eat in a nice restaurant.
-[Ash] Cheeseburgers are nice.
-[Misty] Are not.
[Brock] Will you two cut it out?
-Come on, let's go.
-Fine with me.
-Come on, Pikachu.
-Pika.
[narrator]
Say, what's that rustling in those bushes?
It looks like
those brats are heading into town.
Let's sneak ahead of them.
-Wait. Aren't we forgetting something?
-Forgetting what?
[groans]
Hey, Meowth, catnap's over.
Get up before I lose my... Ooh. Huh.
Argh!
[groans] He's burning up!
Ah. l don't feel so great.
Too bad we can't wait around
for you to chill out.
-Hold on.
-Hmm?
If we leave Meowth here,
he could collapse from that fever.
Don't worry.
He's still got eight more lives left.
That's a good point.
This time we're going to nab that Pikachu.
-Pikachu for me and you. Let's go.
-[Cassandra] Hold it!
-Hmm?
-Huh?
Oh, you poor thing. You're so hot.
How could you even think
of abandoning your Pokémon
when it's overheated like this,
you irresponsible trainers?
-Huh?
-Hmm?
-Does she think...
-That we're Meowth's trainers?
[both laugh]
Why are you laughing?
You must be joking if you think
we'd ever be the trainers of that thing.
Don't you recognize superheroes
when you see them?
You're superheroes?
Sometimes we both go undercover.
But our enemies soon discover.
[both]
We're the Team Rocket super squad.
You're super losers
if you'd leave a sick Pokémon!
-I guess you're right.
-We are sorry.
Don't worry.
I'll make something to cool you down.
[moans]
[moans] Meowth.
-Hmm.
-Here, drink this.
-Thank you.
-Whoa.
-Amazing.
It'll be fine now.
Just give it one of these pills
after each meal.
-Uh, sure.
-See you later.
Ah, she really cared about me.
Meowth's turning red again.
-Maybe it's getting sick again.
-I'm not sick.
-He's back...
-To normal.
[both] Oh.
Is anybody home? Hello?
[crunching]
Excuse me.
We'd like to buy some potions
and antidotes.
[cackles]
Got some snakeroot that'll cure insomnia
and grow hair on your nose and tongue.
-Grow hair on your nose and tongue?
-Uh, does it come in a no-hair formula?
Grandma, I've asked you before
not to frighten the customers.
I didn't mean to scare anyone.
I know, but we're here to help trainers
with our miracle potions,
-not scare them away.
-[both] Huh?
Uh, my name's Brock. Are you the owner
of this Pokémon pharmacy?
Yes, with my grandma.
I'm interested in Pokémon potions.
If you're not doing anything tonight,
maybe we could have dinner together
and talk about them.
Hm. Are all three of you Pokémon trainers?
-Uh, well--
-Instead of dinner,
how about a Pokémon battle?
-Huh?
-Okay, you can battle with me.
That's great. We can battle out back.
-To protect the world from devastation.
-To unite all peoples within our nation.
Yeah, well, unite all people
after that girl comes out.
-[Jessie] What girl?
-[James] Who do you mean?
[Meowth] That's her. It's the nice nurse.
Now, wait, Meowth.
Don't forget our mission
is to capture Pikachu.
-Huh?
-She's captured my heart.
[both sigh]
Paras, Paras, Paras.
This Paras will be your opponent.
Uh, a Paras?
[Pokédex]
Paras, the mushroom Pokémon.
Rare mushrooms grow on its back.
-Pikachu.
-Paras? Paras.
Paras, you can't give up already.
Seems like your Pokémon
doesn't want to battle us.
You're right.
I'd love for Paras to evolve
into a Parasect very soon.
But it's too cowardly to battle.
The best way for Pokémon to evolve
is by winning battles.
The more battles they win,
the quicker they evolve.
But what do you want to make Paras evolve
so fast for?
Because I have to have
Parasect's mushroom.
Why do you need Parasect's mushroom?
You see, after Paras evolves,
I'll use its mushroom to make a new potion
especially for Pokémon,
and I'll use the new potion
to help Pokémon all over the world.
She's too terrific to be human.
That's it, I'd give up all nine lives
to make Cassandra's dream come true.
-He's going to make a fool of himself.
-Oh, I understand.
You must think
this Cassandra is the cat's Meowth?
That ain't funny!
Don't be shy.
I know exactly how you feel about her.
You don't think I'm an idiot?
You might say that Cassandra's one female
who really knows how to treat a feline.
I was so unprepared for love.
Well, cupid's arrow strikes
when you least expect it.
Help me catch, Pikachu,
you two lovebird brains.
Just this once,
since it's for a good cause,
we're going to let Paras win, okay?
Pika.
Good luck, Paras. All the Pokémon on earth
are counting on you.
Paras.
Pikachu, electric... Uh, I mean...
What's the matter, Ash?
-Electric shock might be overdoing it.
-Yeah, you might be right.
-Look, Paras is making the first move.
-Paras.
Pikachu, thunder shock.
Or, uh, maybe just a teeny static bolt.
Pikachu.
Paras.
-Oh.
-Oh, no.
Hey, that wasn't fair.
But it was humiliating.
What a pathetic Paras.
How will Paras ever get any experience?
-Pika.
-Oh, this is a tough one.
What am I supposed to do now?
Look up, Paras' type,
and we'll just choose a weaker opponent.
Good idea.
[Pokédex] Paras has qualities
of both bug and grass Pokémon.
Grass-type Pokémon have a big advantage
against water Pokémon.
Right, a water type.
-Squirtle, I choose you!
-Squirtle.
Hey, that Squirtle is a water type.
-Maybe you can win, Paras.
-Paras?
Squirtle, use your water gun,
but just enough
to sprinkle the mushrooms a little.
Squirtle? Ooh. Squirtle.
Paras.
[sighs]
Paras, oh, are you hurt?
-Paras.
-Please give it one more try.
-Squirtle.
-Squirtle, return.
I'm not going to give up
until Paras has evolved into Parasect.
I choose you, Charmeleon!
-Char.
-Your turn, Charmeleon. Go easy on it.
Char.
-Pika.
-Charmeleon?
Charmeleon doesn't look like a loser.
-Char.
-Paras.
It's okay, hang in there.
-Char.
-No, stop, Charmeleon.
-Paras.
-Char.
[all] Oh.
-Paras, Paras.
-Paras, wait.
-Char. Char.
-What are you doing, Charmeleon?
-Char.
-Ah!
Oh, that wasn't nice.
-Char.
-Charmeleon.
It's way out of control.
Pikachu!
[moans]
-Pika.
-Oh. Thanks, Pikachu.
-Ash.
-Are you okay, Ash?
Uh...
Oh, dear, Paras has run away.
I didn't want to beat it.
Mm-hm, it's my fault for challenging you
to a Pokémon battle.
I was so happy when Charmander evolved,
but now I'm not sure I was ready for it.
Oh, Ash,
worry about your stupid Charmeleon later.
We've got to look for Cassandra's Paras.
You're right, let's get going.
Paras, Paras, Paras.
Paras, Paras, Paras, Par... Paras?
Paras.
Huh.
[Cassandra] Did you find Paras?
[Misty] No, we didn't.
There's no sign of it anywhere.
I'm really sorry.
This was all my fault.
-[Cassandra] No, Ash.
-Pika?
It's not you.
Poor Paras doesn't have any confidence
in its own abilities.
Oh.
Uh, so, what about this potion?
Uh, what's it supposed to do?
Um, I'm trying to come up
with a miracle potion.
[Pikachu squeals]
One that'll not only restore
a Pokémon's defensive powers,
but its attack power, concentration,
and its determination as well
and make it smarter, too.
-You're trying to make a smart potion?
-Pika.
When it's done,
you should give Ash a taste.
[chuckles]
I want all Pokémon to grow
and stay healthy.
That's why I need Paras to realize
how important it is
and to believe in itself.
-[both] And?
-And... and what?
And if James and I help this worthless
little Paras, what's in it for us?
What do we get?
I'll tell you what you get.
If you two make this Paras evolve,
then you could become rich
beyond your wildest dreams.
[both] Hmm?
Cassandra's miracle Pokémon potion
could make millions, maybe even zillions.
[both] Mm-hm, mm-hm.
And how do we get rich from her potion?
Once me and her are a cozy twosome,
she'll make me her company mascot.
-We're thrilled for you.
-But we won't get rich.
I was planning on making you two
my business managers.
I'll have a lot of money to manage.
But if you'd rather not, I'll understand.
[both] Hmm.
[James] Just imagine,
we'll have more money than we can count.
[Jessie] We can count on that.
[laughter]
Who cares about cash?
I just want to spend
the rest of my nine lives
with that trainer of yours, Cassandra.
I can picture it now, her and me
sitting on a porch on summer nights.
Who would have thought living with a human
could be so purr-fect.
[laughs] Ah. Ah!
What's the idea?
Stop daydreaming.
Hurry up, we want to get rich quick.
I can't do that
unless you lend me Arbok and Weezing.
What do you need those two for?
Hmm, 'cause losing battles
is their specialty.
He's got a point.
They're bigger losers
than the guy who invented homework.
How did we get stuck with such rejects?
Arbok.
-Paras?
-[meows]
Arbok.
Paras? Paras, Paras.
Congratulations to our champion.
That was stupendous, Paras.
-You're a heavyweight.
-Paras.
Now let's bring on our next challenger.
[wheezing]
-Paras?
-Meowth.
[groans]
Paras?
-Paras, Paras.
-[groans]
It looks like another knockout.
Slow down, tiger.
Don't get too much experience.
Paras.
-Hey, I think it's going to evolve.
-Paras. Paras. Paras.
-Oh.
-Needs more victories.
Let's see if it's tough enough
to defeat me.
-Put them up, champ.
-Paras.
Ouch. Oh, Meowth.
I'm a goner. You're too strong.
Paras, Paras, Paras.
Paras, Paras. Paras.
A few lousy wins
and it thinks it's Tarzan.
It's got confidence.
-Hey, Paras.
-It's the brats.
Maybe they can help us
get Paras to evolve.
-[Brock] Come on out. Hey, Paras.
-[Cassandra] Hey, Paras.
-Paras.
It's Paras.
There you are.
How'd it get up in that tree?
Paras, Paras.
It's acting strange.
I've never seen it act like this before.
I wonder what happened.
Maybe it's Paras' sparring partner.
-Paras.
-Pikachu.
-Paras, Paras.
-I think it wants to battle.
Oh, Paras,
you finally understand my dream.
That's excellent.
Pikachu, it's time to help Paras
evolve into Parasect.
Pikachu.
My plan is going to work.
-If it wins...
-We'll be rich.
-Get it, Paras.
-Paras.
Remember, Pikachu, go easy on it.
-Pikachu. Pika-pi.
-Paras. Paras.
Pika!
Pika. Pika...
Pikachu, mm-mm-mm.
Pika, pika.
Par?
-Paras, Paras, Paras.
-That's great, Paras wins.
-Paras.
-Paras sure looks proud of itself.
If you keep battling it like this,
then Paras is almost sure to gain
enough experience to evolve into Parasect.
Yes.
Charmeleon, one more time!
Char.
Charmeleon, I'm counting on you this time.
Hey, what's the matter?
Charmander was always totally obedient.
[laughs] Its trainer needs experience.
If the trainer is poor, the Pokémon
won't respect him and won't obey orders.
Oh.
Call it back. We quit.
Charmeleon's too strong.
-Charmeleon, return.
-Char.
See.
Charmeleon won't obey Ash.
-Char. Char.
-Paras, Paras.
Knock it off, Charmeleon.
Please, stop.
I got to do something to help Paras win.
-Meowth is right.
-Our zillions depend on it.
-Char.
-Paras.
-Paras, you can beat it.
-Paras?
What are you all doing here?
It's Team Rocket.
We're the official Pokémon pep squad,
here to cheer on our hero.
[Jessie and James] Go, Paras.
Paras, don't forget all the training
we gave you.
You're pumped for victory.
-There's no way you can lose.
-You're a winner.
They really helped train Paras?
Let's hear it. Give a cheer for our ace,
the great Paras!
[all] Paras. Paras. Stomp and stamp.
-You bet.
-[all] Paras. Paras. That's our champ.
Oh.
Char.
[all groaning]
Paras. Par? Paras!
Char, char, char,
char, char, char.
[all groan]
Paras. Paras. Paras. Par...
-Oh!
-Don't do it, Charmeleon.
-Char.
-Par.
[all] Huh?
Paras?
Oh.
[all] Wow.
[all] Oh!
Pika.
-Parasect.
-Oh.
-Wow.
-It really evolved.
[Pokédex] Parasect, the mushroom Pokémon,
it battles using poison spheres
that spread from the mushroom canopy
on its back.
We're all proud of you, Parasect.
I never doubted you.
Great job, Parasect.
Yahoo.
All aboard the gravy train.
-[laughs]
-Char.
[all] Huh?
Team Rocket's blasting off again!
Char.
-Parasect, stay back.
-Parasect.
Char.
What's that?
It's Parasect's special attack.
It's using spore attack.
[groans]
That's amazing. One spray.
If Parasect's spore attack
is that effective,
it'll definitely make a powerful potion.
Charmeleon, return now.
Looks like you have to evolve
into a better trainer, Ash.
Next time I'll be fine.
Pika, pika.
Thanks for helping me, Parasect.
I knew I'd be able to count on you.
Parasect.
Now it's my turn to help.
I'm going to make my miracle potion
and help improve
all the Pokémon in the world.
Parasect.
I'm sorry we caused
so much trouble for you all.
Well, losing on purpose
is the toughest thing we've ever done.
-Isn't it, Pikachu?
-Pikachu.
You'll keep on losing
if you don't bring up your skill level.
You promised to be nice, Grandma.
[Grandma laughs]
Let us know when you finish
your new potion, Cassandra.
I'll be your first customer.
See you later.
Thanks again.
Good luck on your journey, everyone.
Goodbye. Good luck.
[narrator] And just as Ash and friends
are saying goodbye,
guess who's dropping in?
[all groan]
Huh?
I'm so happy. I got to be the luckiest cat
in the entire universe.
A little tighter, please. [chuckles]
-Parasect.
-And here's my star pupil
who went from chump to champ
in record-breaking time.
How can we ever repay you?
Thanks to you,
we'll make the greatest potion ever known.
It was nothing after you cooled me off,
it was the least I could do.
-She's falling for it.
-We'll be rich.
Now that fate's thrown us together
to help the Pokémon of the world,
I guess it's only natural
to make me your company mascot--
-Never!
-Huh?
I'd never tear you away from Team Rocket.
You're a superhero team, aren't you?
-Well, we are super.
-And a team.
It was super heroic
to help out with Paras like that.
-Then why--
-[Grandma] We've already got
-a company mascot anyway.
-Huh?
Persian.
I found this Persian
snoozing in the backyard.
It's adorable.
Oh, Meowth, I promise to pamper
this Persian just like it was you.
Now you can go on being a superhero.
-There go our billions.
-And zillions.
I'm a hero, but I got zero.
[sobs]
[narrator] Cheer up, Meowth.
Every dog has his day.
Maybe you will, too... maybe.
-♪ Pokémon! ♪
-Attention, all Pokémon trainers
Do you got what it takes
to be the best?
Today we'll do 30 Pokémon.
It's the ultimate test!
♪ Gotta catch 'em all
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Articuno, Jynx, Nidorina, Beedrill ♪
♪ Haunter, Squirtle, Chansey
Pokémon! ♪
♪ Parasect, Exeggcute, Muk, Dewgong ♪
♪ Pidgeotto, Lapras
Vulpix, Rhydon ♪
♪ At least 150 or more to see ♪
♪ To be a Pokémon Master is my destiny ♪
♪ Charizard, Machamp
Pinsir, Koffing ♪
♪ Dugtrio, Golbat, Staryu, Magikarp
Ninetales, Ekans, Omaster, Scyther ♪
♪ Tentacool, Dragonair, Magmar ♪
Not bad, not bad!
Hey, don’t get cocky.
Tomorrow’s the hardest part.
We’re on our way up to 150 Pokémon!
There’s no stopping us!
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch 'em all, Pokémon ♪
♪ Catch 'em, catch 'em
Gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Pokémon! ♪
♪ I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was ♪
♪ To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause ♪
♪ I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide ♪
♪ Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
It's you and me ♪
♪ I know it's my destiny
Pokémon ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend
In a world we must defend ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all
A heart so true ♪
♪ Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you ♪
♪ Pokémon, gotta catch 'em all ♪
♪ Gotta catch them all
Pokémon ♪