Once upon a time, there was a man who died.
The man tried to keep spinning a story even after
his death, but the story just wouldn't move along.
The man lost patience and called a duck into the story.
The little duck tried her best for the prince, and eventually she
transcended her standing in the world and came to love the prince.
However, she was only a duck.
She was fated to someday turn into a speck of light and vanish.
Yes, that was the tear-jerking ending the story had decided on.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
And so, the prince and the
princess lived happily ever...
"Happily"?
Happiness in stories is at most only
a couple of lines at the end.
It's truly boring.
Now, show me the greatest tragedy!
The greatest tragedy where no one is
saved, and a happy ending never comes.
Congratulations.
Prince, what do you hope to do at this point?
"Finale"
Doesn't it matter to you what happens to the
girl sinking into despair inside of me?
I'll save the princess, no matter what!
Quack!
You mean to tell me you really intend to take a human
girl raised on my blood as your princess?
That's right!
Mytho!
Mytho, you...
You fool.
Those crows were once people.
Well? You can't fight them, can you prince?
What will you do, Mytho?
Crows, bring the prince's heart to me!
Give us your heart. Give us your heart.
Give us your heart. Give us your heart. Give us your heart.
Cursed raven, what a cruel thing you have done!
Give us your heart. Give us your heart.
Give us your heart. Give us your heart. Give us your heart.
Give us your heart...
Quack!
Quack...
What?!
Mytho!
Heart! Heart! Heart! Heart!
Give me your heart!
Give us your heart. Give us your heart. Give us your heart.
Give us your heart. Give us your heart.
Mytho!
Give us your heart. Give us your heart. Give us your heart.
Stop it!
Quack...
Ahiru! What are you doing?!
Give us your heart. Give us your heart. Give us your heart.
Quack!
Stop it!
Give us your heart. Give us your heart.
Fakir, we have to help Mytho!
Give us your heart...
Ahiru...
"The duck flapped her wings with all her
strength, hurrying to the prince's side."
"As if it had sensed her feelings,
a gust of wind came to her aid."
Give us your heart. Give us your heart.
Quack!
Stop it!
Qua...
Quack!
"The crows' attacks on the duck st..."
"St... st... still kept going"?!
Quack!
Ahiru!
Hey, wait!
Let go of me! I have to go!
What will you do when you get there?!
A useless knight can't protect anyone
even if he does go out there!
You'd just die in vain, isn't that right?!
You decided to write a story, didn't you?
Then write it to the end! Concentrate!
Damn it!
Someone's coming zura.
That's...
Get inside.
Your heart!
Quack!
Please, stop it!
At this rate...
At this rate, I'll just be letting them steal my heart.
So must I pierce my own heart once again
and seal him away? Is that my only choice?
No!
It's not like that, Mytho!
Damn it, do I not have enough power to
change the story after all?
Without the pendant, I'm just a duck.
Just a duck with no power.
Just a duck who can't do anything.
That's right, even though you transcended
your position as a duck and tried so hard!
But you see,
unfortunately this story
WON'T have a happy ending.
No matter how hard you try, the more you
struggle the more tragic it will become.
Why, you ask?
Who knows?
I won't allow you to lead the story toward tragedy!
Fakir, are you going to give up?!
There's no other way now!
What can I do?
As you dream of a happy ending, sink
into the depths of eternal despair!
The greatest tragedy has no finale!
Here and now, I will pierce this heart once more!
What?!
That's ridiculous! If you seal me
away, the princess will also be...
No matter how many centuries may pass,
I will return again and defeat you!
And after I have done that, I will end my own
life and go meet the princess in Heaven.
No!
You're going to lose your heart again,
and repeat the same thing all over?
After you finally got your heart back...
You mustn't do that...
You mustn't!
YOU MUSTN'T!
You mustn't! You mustn't do that!
Mytho, please, stop!
Tutu...
Don't give up!
Well now. Do you still intend to resist?
Fakir, I want to help Mytho.
One more time...
Ahiru...
It's no use. What in the world could a mere duck do?
You are Princess Tutu no longer.
What do you think to do?
Don't give up, everyone.
Don't let them beat you!
Let's give this story a happy ending.
The depths of despair...
I feel so calm here.
I won't be tricked by anyone anymore,
and I don't have to resent anyone.
There's nothing here.
Not even loving...
Nothing but to keep dancing until I die away.
Thank you.
The human girl with the blood of the raven from the story...
Your tragedy has lent a magnificent touch to my story.
Even though you'd realized the town was
being controlled by my story,
you still believed the raven's false
scenario, and now here you are,
getting ready to die away in
the depths of despair.
What? I wouldn't have thought you still felt sorrow.
This increases the tragedy even further. Thank you!
I know I'm just a duck...
And I can't even put on toe shoes, but...
I feel like I can dance for Mytho and Rue-chan and everyone.
Fakir, help me!
Ahiru...
Dance with me, everyone.
Prince...
Save the princess.
Tutu...
Let's all dance together.
And remember our true selves!
What do you think you can do?
You're nothing but a duck now.
The real me is just a duck.
But I can dance!
So I should be able to communicate
my feelings through dancing too.
I won't decide I can't do anything without ever even trying.
Because I'm the one who's going to make my story!
Let's all go back to the real selves inside our own stories!
Let's treasure our OWN feelings, and not
the ones someone's decided on for us.
"It was true that her dance didn't have
the beauty of Princess Tutu's."
"But it was overflowing with powerful emotion that shone
a warm light on the hearts of the people who saw it."
A mere duck...
If you want to dance that badly, dance
all you like in the darkness of despair.
Cursed raven!
Crows, dance with the duck until she
exhausts her strength and dies!
Quack?
Ahiru!
Ahiru?
I see, so he can write stories if they're about that girl?
Quack! Quack! Quack! Quack!
Quack!
Quack! Quack!
Tutu, I won't ever give up again. I'll kill the raven without fail!
That's another reason why I will save Rue!
Quack...
Qu-quack! Quack, quack...
Quack! QUACK!
Damn it! I can't stop the crows!
DAMN it all!
Quack...
Ahiru...
I've found you, you vile descendant of repugnant hands.
Let's not get violent.
All of the other book men have turned into crows.
Just cutting off your hands is not punishment enough.
Rue! You mustn't give in to despair!
If my voice reaches you...
Fakir is trying to end the story!
Please, just stop! Look at the town full of crows!
Don't resist him any more than this with your immature power!
The story is still being written by a mighty power!
All immature power will do is invite unforeseen tragedy!
I won't give up.
Ahiru...
Fakir, I can still keep going.
I can still dance!
All right.
Watch out!
FAKIR, WRITE!
Fakir's voice disappeared...
Fakir...
Quack!
Ahiru...
Fakir...
Damn it...
What happened?
Write! Write for the person who's waiting for your story!
Ahiru...
It's Fakir's voice.
Fakir, I can still...
"The duck stood up."
"No matter how much she was hurt, the
duck would not stop her dancing."
"Because it was the only thing she could do as she was now."
Rue! Rue!
"'Don't give in to the raven's blood."'
"'Don't be held captive by despair."'
"'Let's give this story a happy ending."'
"'Don't give up. Don't be afraid."'
"Her tiny body was so wounded that
she couldn't even stay on her feet."
"But in order to guide the prince and
everybody else to a happy ending,
no matter how painful it was, she
kept dancing without losing hope."
"The power flowed out from deep within the
duck's body without ever running out."
What is that? That light...
That's right, it's the light that always burned
in my breast when I thought of Tutu.
"One by one, that power warmed the people's hearts,
which had been frozen by the raven's blood."
"That power was..."
Hope!
"...hope!"
Impossible!
Hope?!
In my name as Prince Siegfried, I call the name of the princess!
RUE!
The prince's voice...
I'm here.
Rue, I've come for you.
Prince...
Let's defeat the raven.
Mytho, Rue-chan...
Mytho!
Here we go.
Yes.
The story is going to end!
It's going to end!
Mytho! Rue-chan!
I'm so... glad...
AHIRU!
Huh?
I know where the story is zura! It's this way zura!
I'm back zura!
Welcome back, prince.
The entrance to the story is this way.
What's this?
Here it is zura.
I see.
This thing was recording
everything that happened in Gold Crown Town as a story.
The mechanism that gives birth to
the tragedy Drosselmeyer enjoys...
Tragedy...
Fakir, what are you doing?
I'll write the rest.
Quack?
The prince can live freely as he pleases.
I understand.
Rue.
Yes.
I want you to come with me as my princess.
But I have the raven's blood inside me...
Raven's blood... I wonder if it's still inside me as well.
Prince...
I should love everyone, but...
But right now, I...
Right now, I want to love Rue the most of all.
Rue...
Idiot. There's nothing wrong with that.
I'm so glad.
You're Ahiru.
Quack.
I'm glad I got to meet you. Thank you.
Quack?
I love you, Ahiru.
I love you too, Rue-chan.
This is lovey-dovey zura!
Thank you Tutu, Fakir.
Once upon a time, there was a man who died.
The final story he spun was supposed to be a brilliant tragedy.
However, the story had an unexpected happy ending.
And it was triggered by one duck that the
man himself had called into the tale.
Be a little quieter!
To think a mere duck had that much hope...
My beautiful tragedy is ruined!
I never dreamed a character inside
the story would change the story.
Story characters...
Wait.
What if I'm a character in someone's story too?
Oh, well, even if I am, I'll just do what I want, that's all.
What? Oh, Uzura, you're here.
This story is over. You can't stay over there.
Now, why don't we go to another story?
This time, actually be useful to me.
I don't understand zura.
And there was a man who began writing a story.
That story full of hope
has only just begun.