Once upon a time, there was a man who died.
The man's work was to write and tell stories,
but he could not defy death.
The man's last story was about a brave and handsome
prince, who vanquishes a crafty raven.
But now, their battle will go on
for eternity with no end.
''I'm sick and tired of this!'' cried the raven.
''I'm sick and tired of this!'' cried
the brave prince as well.
The raven escaped from within the story and the prince,
in pursuit of the raven, did as well.
Then, the prince took out his own heart and sealed the
raven away by using a forbidden power.
Just then, from somewhere, ''This is great,''murmured
the man, who was supposed to have died.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
Quack.
Quack...
I want...
I want to dance with him too.
With the prince.
But I'm a duck.
Both my voice and appearance. Just a duck.
I can't dance with him, nor can I even hold his hand.
And his eyes always look so lonely.
Please laugh. I want to see your smile, my prince.
Quack!
Quack...
Well, well, you care for him, don't you?
Quack? Quack...
A little duck like you...
Quack!
Monster!
Huh?
''The Duck and the Prince''
To the girls' dormitory at Gold Crown Academy
it's come, it's come again today, the morning has
The dream I had, the weird dream...
Morning! Whoa! Ow! Ow!
Wait, wait!
I said, wait!
Oh, Java, your leg is all better.
Hey, Tiel, you're not allowed to gobble it all up.
Oh, Canary Mom, your kids are leaving
the nest soon, aren't they?
When they learn how to fly,
bring them with you, okay?!
By the way, what was Mytho-senpai doing?
Last night's dream was another good one.
Me being a duck really sucked as always, but I
got to see Mytho-senpai again after all.
Him being the prince was almost too perfect.
Mytho-senpai, good morning.
The school bell?
This is terrible! Oh, why didn't you wake me up?!
Pike and Lilie, you meanies!
Pike here.
Lilie here.
But, it's still 6 o'clock.
Scatterbrained as usual. She's so cute!
Oh, I'm Ahiru.
My name is Ahiru.
Maybe that's why I have dreams like that.
Oh, my dear Mytho-senpai.
lf I could dance a pas de deux with
you, even just once...
lf I got to...
I'd give my life for that.
I'm so sorry for being late.
Huh?
There's no one here.
Why?
Mytho-senpai...
Oh, I'm sorry! l... um... well...
Am I dis... disturbing you?
I am disturbing you, aren't l? Aren't l?
Aren't l? Aren't l?
Please excuse me! I will leave right away!
My body's like all jumbled up...
Rather, like I'm going to trip, like I'm going
to trip... My feet, my feet, my feet!
I tripped...
Mytho-senpai is... with Mytho-senpai...
is Mytho-senpai...
Mytho-senpai too... to Mytho-senpai...
if Mytho-senpai...
My...tho...senpai.
Wow, what beautiful eyes.
I feel like I'll get drawn in.
But they look so lonely.
It's like he's the prince I saw in my dreams.
Ka...
Kakakakakakakakakaka, hie, ho,
ha, he, ro, hin, ma, ka, me, so...
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry!
I've troubled you so terribly much!
I'm really a scatterbrain and I'm so bad
about things, and I'm always too hasty,
and Pike and Lilie say I sound
like a duck, so I'm weird!
I'm weird, aren't l?!
I think I'm weird myself too.
Not really.
What? I'm not weird?
No one's ever said that to me.
Hey.
Fakir...
Fakir-senpai?
I told you to let me know when
you go out, didn't l?
I know.
We're going. Stand up.
What's wrong?
My foot...
Foot? Did you twist it?
Yes.
You idiot.
What? WHAT?!
Um, well, it's my fault.
He saved me when I tripped and...
What are you doing, you idiot? Doing
pointless things like that.
So like I said, he was protecting me...
That's why I said it was pointless.
Stand up. We're going back to the dormitory.
You don't have to be so rough with him!
Shut up!
Pointless... well, sure, maybe, but he
didn't have to say it so bluntly.
Huh? The bell again?
What the?
My butt. You'd know if you looked at the clock.
I panicked, okay?
That's what makes you so cute.
Always be our clumsy and
scatterbrained Duck, okay?
But well, you had the honor of
talking to Fakir, so it's okay.
He didn't seem like a very nice person.
What did you say?! Fakir is the best!
Mytho-senpai is the best!
Oh, Ahiru, Mytho-sama has Rue.
An impossible love. And Ahiru to be disappointed in love.
How cute!
The teacher's here.
Yes!
Cat?!
You mean, Cat-sensei.
Cat-sense...
What's the matter?
A cat for a teacher? Um, is that how it was?
All right, quiet now.
lf you do not quiet down,
I will have you marry me.
Start in the first position.
Now, as you relevé, move your arms to
the second position.
Remember to keep your legs straight.
And now, the third position, arms en haut.
Don't stick your butts out!
Mytho-senpai...
Why did his eyes look so lonely?
Oh...
Your butt.
Yes, sir!
You were thinking about something
else, weren't you?
lf you don't practice seriously,
I will have you marry me.
Yes, sir! I'm sorry!
All right now, we'll be observing a
performance by the special class.
Members of the special class, please come in!
Rue-chan!
Wow, it's so pretty.
Totally unlike Ahiru.
Oh, she got depressed.
Oh, no, did she really get depressed? How cute!
ln the end, for Mytho-senpai, it'd have to be someone
like Rue to make a good match, wouldn't it?
Sad...
What'll I do?
I will not tolerate this any longer!
This time, I WlLL have you marry...
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Ahiru couldn't help but cry out because
she was so moved.
She's a troublesome child, but she's
cute, so please forgive her.
I still haven't apologized properly to
Mytho-senpai for getting him hurt.
I have to apologize.
Be grateful to us.
You were this close to being forced to marry Cat-sensei.
Thank you.
What's wrong, Ahiru? You're acting weird.
Weird?
Weird, would it be weird to suddenly show up after all?
Show up where?
But I don't have any choice except to suddenly
show up, so it's not weird, right?
Yes, yes!
So, where?
Even if it is weird...
It's normal for you!
I have to just go, right?!
So, go where?!
I'm going!
Let's go!
See you later!
So where are you going?!
So cute!
I'm not supposed to go into the boys' dormitory,
but I'm just going to apologize, so...
I have to apologize, so...
And I can't apologize unless I go inside...
Oh, you stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid,
stupid, stupid coward!
You're in my way.
Oh, um, is Mytho-senpai...
He's not here.
Then, um... where...
Go home!
Ouch.
How is his injury?
It's not serious.
I'd like to apologize to him...
No need.
Do you always act like that, no matter
who you're talking to?
Oh, he pisses me off!
Mytho.
Fakir.
I told you to stay in bed, didn't l?
Sorry.
Does your foot hurt?
I don't know.
What a wretch you are.
You're slow and utterly useless.
Don't get any silly ideas like trying to help someone.
Okay.
All you have to do is listen to what I say.
Man, I didn't get to apologize to
Mytho-senpai in the end. I suck.
I wonder if his injury's okay?
Such lonely looking eyes.
I bet there's some reason for it.
There's nothing I can do, but...
But if there were some way for me to help him out.
lf I were to be able to do something for him...
I'd give my life for that.
Huh?
What?
That person...
He's not here.
Yes, I am.
I wonder who he was?
Have you forgotten about me?
It feels strange, somehow.
Do you want to know? Do you really want to know?
Little Duck.
What?
The water has begun to flow. The
time has begun to pass.
Now, tell me a story.
I'm going.
On the way back, I'll borrow some
books for you from the library.
Don't read any books except the ones I bring you.
Thank you.
Don't make me worry, you idiot.
Okay!
What's ''okay''?
You're going to do something, aren't
you? I wonder what it is?
Nothing, really.
Like thinking of seeing Mytho-sama?
What?
Oh, my!
lf things go well, maybe even strike up a friendship?
Was I right?!
No, I hadn't thought that far...
Oh, no! That's the kind of spirit you should go with!
We'll make sure to cover for you being late somehow!
Ah, okay...
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
I wonder if it'll work out?
It'll be fine.
You think?
Because even if she fails, I'll comfort her.
I have to do it properly this time!
So, Canary Mom's kids are leaving the nest today.
Be careful!
No!
Oh, dear, the prince is going to die.
The prince?
The hero is going to die.
Die?
What's going to happen in this story?
Tell me what happens next.
ls the prince going to make it?
Who's going to save him?
Who?
I wonder who?
I'll...
Do you care for him?
Quack.
Do you want to be of help to the prince?
So, you're saying you're going to tell me this story?
Quack.
Very well, very well.
That's right. I'm going to save the prince!
Do you remember now? Who are you?
I am Princess Tutu!
Flower Waltz!
To think I was able to save you, Mytho.
It's like a dream.
You know my name...
Who are you?
I'm...
Do you remember now, Little Duck?
That's right, you're a duck. Just a bird called a duck.
Quack!
l...
Quack... Quack.
So, I was a duck.
Well, well, Princess Tutu has
gone back to being a duck.
Now, the story has just begun. What to do?
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
Quack...
I'm just a duck. And I thought I was a girl.
My, if it isn't Rue-san.
Mytho is going to be with me, now.
Anteater?
Would you dance with me?
Rue-chan, I'm really terrible at it. So, I'm
sure I'll be no good at all...
Don't worry, just follow my lead.
I am the feeling of bitter disappointment,
shattered and forgotten.
I've really and truly been able to
become Princess Tutu.
''Heart Shard''
All you children who love stories,
come gather around.