Once upon a time, there was a young
man with a beautiful face.
The people loved the handsome young man, but
he never showed interest in loving anyone.
This was because all he loved was himself.
When the young man, who neglected to love and sought
only to be loved, found someone he truly cared for,
he realized that he had lost even the
words to express those feelings.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
Calm down, Father.
If you get excited, it will affect your health.
You still do not have the heart? What of
the young and beautiful heart?
You see, Princess Tutu interferes every time...
Do not give me excuses!
But Father, when he sees Princess Tutu,
the old prince starts to awaken.
So...
If you are a girl of noble raven birth, then do not whine!
Hurry up and bring me a heart!
I understand, so please calm yourself, Father!
Poor Father...
"Crime and Punishment"
Oh, Mytho-sama...
When I think about Mytho-sama, I just feel so overcome.
Even when I'm eating like this...
...all my thoughts turn to Mytho-sama.
We have to get to our classroom soon.
Yeah.
Let's hurry!
You don't care about Mytho-sama
anymore either, right, Ahiru?
I get that, though. He's changed somehow, hasn't he?
He has?
The mysterious side is gone...
Or rather, don't you get the feeling he'll just take any girl?
He's a beast!
Ugh.
Teen idols need to be a little more approachable.
You mean they need to seem moderately stupid?
It's because he's not the real Mytho...
You're the one who returned the feeling of love to the prince,
without even knowing it was dyed in the raven's blood.
Tutu... help me...
Mytho must be the one suffering the most.
I want to return him to the old Mytho as soon as I can.
But how do I do that?
Bonjour, mademoiselle.
Mad?
Pike? Lilie?
Eep!
O young lady who has eyes of truth...
Please, take this.
Right... Thank you...
It could never hope to hold a candle to
the greatness of your love.
Um, who are you?
Non, non!
I understand your desire to know everything about me.
But I must not fulfill that desire. Because...
I am someone who is qualified to be a true prince, someone
who loves everyone and is loved by everyone!
A true prince?
However! Right now, the ladies of this academy are
consigning themselves to that man's false love!
You mean Mytho?
And that must be because!
Of my own shortcomings, mustn't it?
Because I just can't give everyone enough love...
Heavens, I beseech thee!
Please punish this sinner!
Here!
Olé!
Quack!
She was so flustered.
Mon cherie is a shy one.
There's no way to compare this punishment I've taken to
the pain in the hearts of the many women I'm hurting.
Femio-sama!
Quack, quack...
Quack!
Man, that scared me.
"True prince"? Was that guy just now a prince too?
What are you playing at?
What?
What do you mean?
It would be cruel to poor Father if we didn't
get him a sacrificial heart to eat soon.
I know.
He's never been very patient, you know.
I'm sick of waiting too.
Is someone there?
Tut... Ahiru!
You can go, Mytho.
But...
Go on, go.
Okay.
Wait, Mytho!
It's no use.
Rue-chan...
I told you, there is no Rue.
I just can't believe that.
Because I get this feeling you're Rue-chan.
It doesn't matter what you think.
The prince is mine now.
"Prince"? Did you call me?
Young lady.
Qua...
Give me your hand, s'il vous plaît.
You don't have to be so shy, my cute one.
You bloom like a flower, you fly away like a bird.
Oh, lovely you!
Oh?
That young lady is truly timid.
Oh, this cursed body!
Even as they are drawn to me, it prevents them
from even approaching me... this beauty!
I feel an intent gaze!
Mademoiselle, I beg your pardon for only
just now noticing your fervent gaze.
You say you're a prince?
Yes.
I am someone who is qualified to be a true prince, someone
who loves everyone and is loved by everyone!
I promise you that someday I will become a great
enough man to accept all the love in the world.
When that happens, I'm sure no one will
be able to help but love me.
Despite being a crow, you have been
born into an ugly human body.
And only I and the prince in the story can
truly love a pitiful person like you.
What magnificent confidence. You
have an almost blinding pride.
It's enough to make me hate you.
You're wonderful.
Femio-sama, couldn't this possibly by any chance be...
Be what?
The time to make a display of your charm, Femio-sama!
Aah!
Now, today we'll be testing your abilities.
However, there's no need to be nervous.
If you haven't neglected your everyday
practicing, you'll have no problem.
At times like this, it seems like nothing's changed, but...
Mytho...
All right, first up will be Mytho-s...
Cat-sensei!
I believe I'm the appropriate choice to dance the first solo.
You're Femio-san from the probationary class!
Ugh.
He's gross!
Exposure to true Art should be valuable
for everyone else as well.
He's really confident for someone in the probationary class.
Maybe he's really good or something?
Maybe...
He's really weird!
Er, Femio-san, it's not that I don't understand your
quest for Art, but learning the basics first...
It's all right. Genius is misunderstood in every era.
But someday, this dance of mine...
This love of mine will satisfy the hearts of all the people.
Yes, that is destiny.
Cat-sensei, if I were a woman, I would have MARRIED you...
However, I am not.
Montand!
My goddess.
Huh?
There is a feeling that gets across even
when it's not put into words.
A feeling that gets across even when you don't speak it...
What's wrong?
And another rose goes to you of the intent gaze.
Mytho!
That's the mime for "I love you"!
Words without a voice...
Are they a sign of the prince's comeback?
Or are they his death cry?
Which will it be? Which will it be?
Oh, I can't believe it!
I've had such a shock!
That was definitely the "I love you" mime, wasn't it?
And directed at FEMIO!
Come to think of it, Femio gave a
flower to Ahiru too, didn't he?
Yes, he did. He and Ahiru would go
well together, wouldn't they?
What's "go well together" zura?
"Go well together" is...
I suppose it means "lovey-dovey".
Ahiru is lovey-dovey zura?
We're saying that would have been better.
Oh! Thanks zura!
And here I thought Ahiru's prince had come.
Things have sure gotten complicated.
Who would've thought she and the old prince
would become rivals for the new prince's love?
He's a prince too?
Of course not.
He's just claiming to be one.
Why don't you take this chance to date Femio?
Yeah! That's a good idea!
Huh?!
Although this prince is on a much
lower level than the last one.
He and Ahiru won't get along and they'll never be
on the same wavelength, so it's sure to be fun!
That would be fun?
Definitely! So fun I could watch it all day and not get bored!
But it's not totally clear whether Mytho-sama's
mime was really meant for Femio or not.
Oh? Who was it for, then?
What if it was for ALL the girls, or something?
What a beast!
Mytho...
I think that was the real Mytho.
Because he seemed so... so sad.
His eyes showed so much pain.
It looks like you're feeling quite a bit better.
Yes. I'm sorry for making you worry.
Did something happen?
That mime was quite splendid, but it seemed so
sorrowful and fragile that I'm a bit concerned.
Nothing in particular happened.
I see. Well, rest for a little while longer.
Cat-sensei...
Yes?
When you feel so strongly that you would be willing to give
your life, that must be when love shines most brilliantly...
Perhaps so. But love cannot shine on that feeling alone.
What?
You cannot marry on that feeling alone.
What do you mean?
Oh, Rue-san. Here to visit him?
Yes.
We're going to go capture a sacrifice, aren't we?
No.
I'll do it.
You go back to your dorm.
YOU'LL do it?
What's so funny?
Nothing.
I look forward to great things from you, princess.
Again?
The ending is torn out.
Just my imagination?
Fakir!
What?
When they say at school that Ahiru "goes well together" and
is "lovey-dovey" and "it's good," what do they mean zura?
Ahiru is? With who?
No, never mind.
What does it mean zura?
I wouldn't know.
Don't keep it from me zura!
Hey, stop it!
Can you please be a little quieter?!
Oh, sorry.
Oh, even as I speak, I go on committing more and more sins.
My beauty is such that it's enough to make even Mytho swoon,
and it makes the maidens afraid to even approach me.
Deep down, they must want to sear my
image into their eyes!
Yes, they do!
Yet I cannot even save those maidens from their suffering.
Heavens, I beseech thee!
Please punish this sinner!
Here!
Olé!
Mon amour...
Can I have a moment?
What?
But of course! My heart is always open for you ladies...
Come.
Where to?
To a place where we can prove our love.
Doesn't the atmosphere down there seem kind of dangerous?
Could this be a battle?!
Rue-chan!
...if we didn't get him a sacrificial heart to eat soon.
I'm sick of waiting too.
Rue-chan, what are you...
I smell blood about to be spilled! Blood!
Ahiru?
Hey, she went after them.
What? No way! Ahiru must really love to battle.
Huh? I'm sure they went this way...
Say...
What is it you want to do, in a place like this?
Hey, you.
Are you scared?
Scared?
Me?
No word is more unsuited to me than "fear."
Well, if there were just one thing I feared...
I suppose it would be my own beauty.
If you lose your heart, you'll lose that fear as well.
I hope my Father will be happy with you.
What?
You mean you'll do me the favor of
introducing me to your father?
Yes.
But isn't this too sudden?
After all, we know far too little about each other.
It doesn't matter.
I need you.
What a sinful man I am!
To think I would bind your heart to me this tightly!
How... How terrible a sin!
I can no longer fully atone through
those lukewarm punishments!
Montand, it's time for THAT!
Yes, sir!
I don't need atonements.
What?
That's not what I want.
I understand. If you insist...
Even if it's just for one night,
I'll have you assuage my father's hunger!
Tonight, I will give my all to you.
Rue-chan, where are you?
That was Femio's...
There!
Love only me.
Regard all others with hatred.
Yes, I will love only you...
Only you...
I just can't do it!
Loving just one woman is something I can't...
Oh, who are you, mademoiselle?
It can't be...
Please forgive me for my rudeness, mademoiselle.
I couldn't resist your charms.
Wait!
Let go of him, Kraehe.
Who are you?
Dance with me.
With you?
I can't!
I couldn't choose just one of you, something so cruel would...
For me to take THIS much of the world's love all for myself...
My sin is great... Too great...
This is an eternal sin I can never atone for!
Jeez, nothing you're learning is good...
Heavens, I beseech thee!
Please punish this sinner!
Here!
O...
...lé!
Mon... âme...
Croak.
Kraehe!
Kraehe...
Come, let us go, Femio-sama.
Bulls...
What's going on?
Why bulls?
It's amazing zura! There are so many zura!
Oh, it's Ahiru zura.
Fakir!
Did something happen?
Well, no...
It's kind of like something happened and kind of didn't.
Even I don't really get it...
What's with that?
Say, Fakir...
What?
What are you doing that for all of a sudden?!
Mytho did this mime.
I don't know why he did it...
But that was the real Mytho, wasn't it?
Are you lovey-dovey with Mytho zura?
Huh?!
Mind your own business, Uzura!
You knew, didn't you?
Knew what?
That I wouldn't be able to capture a sacrifice.
So it didn't go well, then.
You weren't loved so much that he would give his life.
Poor baby.
Oh, dear. The second princess is a princess who won't be
loved no matter how much she confesses her own love.
Nothing goes the way you want it to, does it?!
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
Do you think it's possible to turn a
love made impure back to normal?
I want you to stick close to Mytho as much as you can, so...
A knight who wanders around unable to do anything?
It certainly is perfect for you, Fakir.
Does it mean he'll prepare a place for me to die?
Your sword is seeking blood, isn't it?
Cut down that useless knight!
Stop! Don't fight, Fakir.
"The Wandering Knight"
All you children who love stories, come gather around.