Once upon a time, there was a princess who was held captive.
She was imprisoned in the demon king's castle.
And with her freedom taken from her, she
had no choice but to dance like a puppet
to the tune set by the whims of the demon king.
One day, a hero came to fight the demon king,
seeking to save the princess.
However, there was no way the hero
could win against the demon king.
The hero did not know, you see,
that he himself was a puppet
created by the demon king.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
Fakir!
TUTU!
"Marionette"
Where am I?
Gears?
Why are they all stopped?
What am I doing in a place like this?
What should I do?
Fakir!
Drosselmeyer... The man who toys with the fate of all...
Is he out there somewhere, laughing as
he watches Mytho and her suffer?
Where is she right now?
Is she where Drosselmeyer is?
Where is that?
This story may have already progressed to the
point where there is nothing we can do.
In that case, the only one who can fight
is the one who carries the same blood.
So you're telling me to write?
There's no other way to save her.
Where's the exit?
I have to leave this place quick!
I can't stay here now that I've found out.
The remaining heart shards are in the five town gates.
I want to give them back to Mytho really soon.
And then Mytho will return to the story,
and I'll go back to being a duck.
What's this?
A puppet?
That's right! This is the puppet world.
Who do we have here? If it isn't Princess Tutu!
It's Tutu! It's Tutu! It's Princess Tutu!
It's Tutu! It's Tutu!
I wonder what Tutu is doing here?
Do you know where this place is?
Tell me! Why was I brought here?
Why is everything here stopped?
Well, listen to that! So Tutu doesn't know where this is?
Please tell me!
Tutu says she wants us to tell her.
Princess Tutu's in a pickle!
A pickle!
Answer me!
The one who stopped everything here is you, Princess Tutu.
This is the inside of the story.
You're the one who stopped it, Princess Tutu.
Stopped the story? I did?
That's right! Tutu stopped the story!
Tutu stopped the gears! She stopped
them! She stopped them!
Tutu stopped them! Tutu stopped them!
Stop it!
What?! My body... won't move...
Hear the voice which is voiceless and
see the shape which is shapeless...
So what am I supposed to do with that?
What am I supposed to write?
Damn it... I have to write...
I have to write.
Where is the heart?
Daughter, hurry up and bring me a heart!
Father... Now that I have dyed the prince's heart in
your blood, he is certain to be mine, isn't he?
Are you saying you cannot trust my words?
No! That is not it!
And to think that on top of that, you only think
of yourself and not of me, your father!
Of course I love you, Father! But...
It is only natural for a daughter to love her father!
You are pathetic.
To think you cannot even win the
love of the prince in the story...
At this point you no longer have
any value to me as a daughter.
Father!
In that case, at least give me your heart so that I am restored.
Forgive me! I'm sorry!
Stop, Kraehe!
Have I turned into a puppet?
Did I do something bad, is that why?
Huh? This is...
Uzura-chan!
I found Tutu zura!
What are you doing here, Uzura-chan?
I followed you zura. What are you doing zura?
I think I've turned into a puppet.
A puppet zura?
Um, er, it's not that I don't LIKE being a puppet, it's just...
Oh, Uzura-chan!
Puppets...
UZURA-CHAN!
Jeté entrelacé.
What? My feet are moving on their own!
Fouetté rond de jambe en tournant.
Drosselmeyer-san?
Is this the world where Drosselmeyer-san is?
How... Why?
I'm just a marionette, being made
to dance exactly as I'm told...
I don't like this.
I want to dance more... more freely...
That thinking is mistaken.
Marionettes are at their most free when they're
being manipulated by their strings.
You won't be able to leave this place
unless you acknowledge that.
What's a puppet zura?
Her name is Uzura.
Karon made her out of the bits of wood
from Edel that didn't burn away.
Edel-san's?
Am I not Uzura zura?
What's this zura?
It turns zura!
Caw, caw...
Hello, Kraehe. Come over here.
Prince...
Why the haunted look?
Let's enjoy ourselves.
I want to get all my feelings back soon...
And then I have to give the raven my heart.
What? What are you talking about?
You're joking, right? You're fated to marry me.
You?
You, who despite being a crow have been
born into an ugly human body?
YOU must be joking, right?
The only thing you're allowed to do is love me.
When you dyed my heart with raven's
blood, our fates were sealed.
But I did just what Father told me to!
Then I... Then I'd rather just take his heart out again...
But I don't have the prince's sword.
If I thrust this blade into the prince, he might die.
That's fine. If that happens, I too will...
When you've ripped out my heart, kiss it for
me and dye your lips red with my blood.
What's the matter? Can't you do it?
Looks like that's your limit.
Picking Drosselmeyer's grave to write at was pretty sharp, for you,
but if the words you should be writing aren't coming to you
without you even having to think...
Can you please be a little quieter?
And when I have so much I want to write right now too...
It's ironic.
I have to write fast... fast...
Dear me. You'd be so much better off if you'd only be a
good boy and let yourself be manipulated by the story...
Well, but that's fine too.
Well then! I'll be coming to see you very soon, Little Duck.
Huh?
Who's there?
Welcome to a gap in time, Princess Tutu.
Drosselmeyer-san!
Um, what did they mean when they said I stopped the story?
I'm... trying my best to return the prince's heart to him!
Have you found all the heart shards?
What? Um, I think the rest are hidden in the five gates...
Congratulations!
What? Then, if I return those to him, the prince will
go back to normal and defeat the raven...
No, no. That would be boring.
You're a story character, you can do better than that!
Story character? But I'm really just a duck...
But you're inside the story right now.
Everyone is. Look.
What?
Rue-chan!
Fakir...
Mytho...
Everyone's suffering, you see?
This is the way it has to be.
Confess your love and vanish as a speck of light or
never confess your love and lose your prince...
I believe you have something to suffer over too, Tutu.
Never mind that, I...
And yet! To think returning the prince to normal is
more important to you than your own problems!
You're different now than the duck you once were,
who only wished for the prince.
You should be in love with the prince and want to marry him!
Don't you?
I...
That's right.
It's natural to want to make the prince yours and yours alone.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
How about this, for instance?
Why not pretend you haven't realized that the remaining
heart shards are hidden in the five gates?
What?
After all, nobody else has realized, so if you do that,
you won't have to part from the prince.
But...
If you don't start thinking at least on that level,
you'll probably never be able to get out of here.
And the story will stay stopped too...
What is this? Tutu is here, and yet the gears are moving?
Oh!
Now THIS is interesting. The gears are turning backwards.
The story will double back.
What?
Even I didn't think of this!
Now, I wonder what will happen...
I don't understand anymore...
I believed that my marriage to the prince was
the fate the story had decided for us.
Was I wrong?
What should I believe?
Who should I believe?
I want to just go back to that time
before I remembered everything...
That time when I was Rue...
Help!
I'm sorry, Father!
Don't take my heart! Forgive me!
That's...
I'll be a good girl!
Get behind me.
That's the prince back when I first met him.
You don't have to worry anymore.
Does it hurt?
Um... Here's some water.
Thank you.
I have to go back.
Back where?
To where my father is.
Who are you?
I'm...
My pitiful daughter, who despite being a crow
has been born into an ugly human body...
I'm not a crow! I'm a person!
I'm Krae... no, Rae... Ree... Rue... Yes, my name is Rue!
Can I come see you again?
Yes.
Goodbye!
What's going on?!
The story is flowing backwards!
What?!
Stop it! Stop it with your pen, Fakir!
It's... doubling back?
I've experienced a lot of new feelings
since becoming a human girl.
I never imagined that my feelings
for Mytho would grow so much.
I'll never go back!
Not to that time when I clung to my sword and never said
anything but words that took away Mytho's freedom!
My feelings belong to me...
It's the same with anybody's feelings.
They're all precious feelings.
I'm not a marionette!
I won't sit and be frightened of fate
while everyone else faces it!
I want to protect Mytho!
I WILL protect him!
WE will!
Just now... I heard her voice...
That's right.
She changed me.
I can write. I can write a story about her!
Wait, but... These aren't my words.
What are they?
It won't move anymore zura.
It seems the story doesn't want
to go back any more than that.
Who are you zura?
Are you... a puppet zura?
I am a puppet.
I am you. You are me.
I'm not Uzura zura?
I am a puppet who could not have a heart.
But you...
Go back to Ahiru.
Wait zura!
These are her feelings.
"I want to go back... I want to go back and help Mytho!"
"I want to leave this place!"
Her feelings for Mytho are spilling up through
my hand and out onto the page.
"At that time, the knight who had cast
away his sword called her name!"
"In order to lead her out of the darkness!"
"AHIRU!"
AHIRU!
Fakir!
FAKIR!
Go on now.
Ahiru!
Fakir!
Did you write a story about me?
Yeah.
Thank you.
What is this?! For her to leave here without my permission...
She's not to be underestimated.
And thanks to this, the story is still stopped.
Oh? There's one who's still doubling back.
You'll find out something you'd rather not know!
What is this?
What's wrong?
My daughter's been kidnapped by the crows!
What?!
Okay, let's go search over there.
Thank you!
That's... me?
I'm... not the raven's daughter...
I had a mother and father...
I'm just a normal human...
What a wretched fate.
The story's finally started moving.
My, my... Thank goodness, thank goodness.
I'm not Uzura zura?
My heart isn't lovey-dovey zura?
Where am I zura?
I'm high up zura!
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
My love has only made you into this.
I have no right to love you.
The duck doesn't know.
She doesn't know about that.
Just now I felt afraid of Mytho.
Even if I put water on you, you won't go back to normal zura?
That's why I want you to help me, Autor.
This is the raven...
This frail love...
I have to protect it.
"The Prince and the Raven"
All you children who love stories, come gather around.