Once upon a time, there was a happy prince.
The happy prince knew no painful past
and he knew no painful future.
One day, the prince obtained a comforting warmth.
However, this warmth emanated not only tranquillity,
but also unhappiness, pain, and loneliness.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
What are you looking at?
Nothing. It's none of your business.
''The Prince and the Raven,'' huh? I see.
What?
It seems you're gaining an interest in what
Mytho was like when he was in the story.
What Mytho was like before he lost his heart.
Are you trying to say that I'm the
one restoring Mytho's heart?
Am I wrong?
Hold it!
What's so funny?
What would you do if Princess Tutu really existed?
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
''On the Night of the Fire Festival''
Yes, that's right.
Elongate your spine.
Say, have you made up your mind, Duck?
Huh? About what?
What?!
Did you forget what's going on today?
Uh, maybe I did.
Huh?
The Fire Festival.
Fire Festival?
Yeah, do you remember now?
We're asking if you've decided what to wear.
Um, what's the Fire Festival?
It's okay! It's okay, Duck!
You're really out of it if you live here and
don't know about the Fire Festival!
You're just too cute!
That's because, I'm just a bird to begin with.
Ahiru-san.
Yeah, yeah, so I'm a duck.
Ahiru-san!
I know that already.
I get it already, so tell me about the Fire Festival...
Very well, I will tell you.
Yes, sir.
The Fire Festival is a town festival where people dress
up in the old ways and dance around a bonfire.
I see. Now, I really understand...
And the important part of it is the golden apple given to the
couple who dances the most exquisitely at the main event.
Golden apple?
That's right.
It's said that a couple who's been given the golden
apple will be bound together forever.
Bound together forever?
But I guess that's got nothing to do with me.
Ahiru-san.
Right, because I'm just a duck.
But that's okay. I know it.
Ahiru-san!
I SAID, I know...
Oh, I'm so sorry.
There we go.
As punishment for allowing your mind to wander during
class, you will clean the lesson room for the advanced class.
If you don't do it properly,
I will have you marry me, meow!
And you'll go with me to the Fire Festival, meow!
Why don't you be good and clean for today?
I agree. Because if you happen to win by
some fluke, you'll end up bound to him.
Mytho.
Mytho...
And I told him not to leave without my permission!
The golden apple, huh?
Don't forget now.
The princess who saves the prince is
fated never to be with her prince.
I don't care.
Mytho...
He is a prince.
Is this the real you, Mytho?
Don't forget now.
The instant you confess your love,
you'll turn into a speck of light and vanish!
Uh, um, that is...
Oh, I'm on cleaning duty as punishment,
so please don't mind me!
Have you seen Rue around?
What?
Rue-chan?
Rue said she wanted to practice dancing for the
Fire Festival, so I've been waiting here all this time.
Oh, so Mytho's going to be
dancing with Rue-chan tonight.
Of course...
When I'm alone,
it's so dark and so cold.
Feelings?
Duck, are you going to the Fire Festival too?
Oh, he just called me by name...
What?
Let's dance, Duck.
Mytho!
I can't go to the Fire Festival...
Mytho wanted...
Mytho wanted to dance of his own will.
Could it be because he's regaining his heart?
If it is, I'd be happy.
Her again.
Damn.
Please excuse me.
Oh, what'll I do?! I danced
with Mytho the prince!
Have you seen Rue around?
But that was in Rue-chan's place.
She's practically like a duck.
Quack! Cleaning!
Hey!
That voice just now...
I knew it. It was him.
Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack.
What's the meaning of this?
Quack!
Dressed up in this silly outfit...
Rue said to wear it.
Listen to me, all you have to do is obey my orders.
Don't listen to what anyone else tells you.
That includes what Rue says!
You were dancing just earlier.
Yes.
What's with that duck-like girl that's
been scurrying around lately?
Duck-like? Well, I am a duck, but...
She's called Duck. Her name is Duck and...
I don't care about any of that!
There's no need to dance with the likes
of her just because she asked you to.
That's not what happened.
Rue didn't show up and I've been waiting by myself.
Then, Duck came, so...
You invited her to dance with you?
Yes.
Listen to me, don't keep making me repeat myself!
All you have to do is listen to what I tell you!
Don't get interested in stupid things!
I can't hear...
When you were wandering without any memory,
I was the one who gave you the name of Mytho!
I was the one who saved you.
I know.
Don't go to the Fire Festival either. Got it?
Being the way you are now is what's for the best.
But Rue wants me to dance with her.
Forget about her!
I have to let her know that I can't go.
Are you defying me?
No, but...
Come with me.
Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack!
Where are we going, Fakir?
Hey, Fakir?
Never mind, just come with me!
Quack, quack, quack, quack,
quack, quack, quack. Quack!
Quack...
The library?
Quack! Quack, quack, quack,
quack, quack, quack.
Quack! Quack!
Wow!
Rue-chan...
But Fakir took Mytho away...
Anyway, I have to go back to being the girl Duck.
Water!
Quack!
Yes!
Rue-chan.
Duck.
Um, you're supposed to meet up with Mytho, right?
Why do you know about that?
Oh, um, um...
You know, I'm on cleaning duty as punishment,
so I was cleaning here just earlier too.
And Mytho said he's going to practice dancing with you.
Wow, it's totally wet over here.
Of course, I made this mess earlier.
So, where's Mytho?
Oh, um, I think he stepped out for a bit.
You didn't go chasing after him like the other day?
Oh, well...
Of course, you did suddenly disappear that time.
Oh, sorry about that.
If you happen to see Mytho, please tell him that
I'll be going on ahead to the square.
Oh, okay.
Rue-chan.
Mytho will come find you, I'm sure of it!
You're like a real princess and you really suit each other,
so I'm sure you'll get the golden apple.
They definitely went in the library, but...
You stay there and behave yourself.
Why?
It's punishment.
I'm sorry. Don't be mad, Fakir.
I'll do as you say. Without you, Fakir, I...
What are you doing?!
What's this punishment?! Why do
you do such terrible things?!
And Mytho, you too! Why?!
Rue-chan's waiting for you!
You've finally regained some shards of your heart!
There's no reason for you to listen to someone like him!
Shards of his heart?
Your name's Duck? Just what do you know?
What do I know? Nothing, really...
Come to think of it, you mentioned
''The Prince and the Raven'' before...
You know that Mytho is a prince from
inside a story, don't you?
Did Rue tell you?
Rue-chan?
Rue-chan and this person both know Mytho's secret?
Mytho has no need of a heart!
What?
No need of a heart? What are you saying?!
There's no way he doesn't!
What do you know?!
I know everything about Mytho. I'm
asking you, what do you know?!
Well, sure, I may not know
anything about Mytho,
but if he has no heart,
he won't know what it feels to be happy
or to be in love, either. So...
Foolishness!
Even if he regains shards of his heart,
I'll seal them away!
If I shut him away in the darkness, he'll eventually
become numb to the dark as well.
He'll become numb to all sensations
and stop feeling all together.
That's...
That's just wrong!
Don't get carried away when you know nothing.
So high and mighty, like he knows everything.
When I restored the heart shards to
Mytho, he thanked me. He did!
Are you afraid of the dark?
You'll be okay.
But it's true, I don't know anything.
About Mytho...
Am I sticking my nose in where it doesn't belong?
Edel-san.
A flame can illuminate the darkness.
But without the darkness, its glow cannot even be seen.
Are you afraid of the dark?
I see that you are in the darkness of uncertainty.
But if you wish to shine for someone,
you must not fear the darkness.
I see. You mean I shouldn't fear
what I don't understand...
Right?
A path is open to you.
Oh? He's not here.
Mytho, where did you go?
Quack, quack, quack, quack. Quack!
Quack!
Quack, quack, quack, quack! Quack,
quack, quack, quack, quack! Quack!
This is what it looks like under the library?
Oh, a heart shard...
Who is it? Mytho? Are you there?
I'm just a little thing, but I flood the entire room.
What am I?
A riddle?
Wait, the voice is coming from the other side.
I mustn't fear the darkness!
Just a little thing that floods the entire room?
Oh, a sneeze?!
Too bad. Then...
I am a white snake that swallows the
sea, and my head is all red.
What am l?
Um, a white paint brush with red paint on it?
Too bad.
Then here's the last one.
I become shorter the longer I stand. What am l?
Um, a flower, maybe?
Too bad.
But congratulations. The person you're looking for is here.
What? Mytho is?
Give Mytho back!
No.
You are to stay here as well.
I can't do that!
You'll be okay, because I'm here.
Who... are you?
Oh, dear, will you be in the darkness forever?
Or can you regain your radiance
once again, Princess Tutu?
Are you there?
Who are you?
I am Princess Tutu.
You're wonderful.
Say, stay here and dance.
Then I'll illuminate you for the rest of your life.
You'll illuminate me?
That's right.
Oh, I know.
Just a little thing that floods the
entire room is the light of a lamp.
The white snake that has a red head
and swallows the sea,
and what becomes shorter the longer it
stands is the lamp's wick.
You are a lamp! I'm right, aren't l?
You are correct.
Give back Mytho and his heart.
No.
That bastard...
Dance with me.
With me?
Yes.
You dance. I'll illuminate you.
Okay.
Your light is so warm, why do you do this?
What do you want?
I...
I only want to keep shining for someone.
I just want to envelop them gently in warm light.
Wanting to shine for someone...
That's all, I don't want anything else.
And yet, somewhere along the way, I had become forgotten.
The people who were precious to me forgot about me.
No, they must not have needed me from the beginning.
That can't be true.
I thought they enjoyed my presence,
but that was only what I believed.
That can't... be true.
But right now, there is someone who wishes for this light.
Mytho...
Shutting him away like this? Is this how you want it?
Yes.
And I'll illuminate him. Forever.
Please, remember what it was like to
shine your warm light on people.
I haven't forgotten.
Then you should know.
That forcing your glow on people like this won't bring joy.
I love your warm light.
I think the people who were precious to you
were very happy, enveloped in your warm light.
It's sad that they no longer need you, but
it's something that can't be helped.
Because it's not something you can force on people.
If you want what's best for Mytho, give his heart back.
Because that will lead to Mytho's happiness.
Will it really?
It's what I believe.
Princess Tutu, I want to illuminate you more.
I am the feeling of affection, shattered and forgotten.
The feeling of affection...
Go back to Mytho now.
Mytho.
Princess Tutu.
Now, you should hurry.
There's someone waiting for you, right?
I was a fool for believing what that Duck said.
Mytho...
The Fire Festival ended long ago.
I'm sorry.
Mytho, what are you doing?
Mytho?!
Stop it, you're acting strange, Mytho.
This is how it should be, right?
For such kindness to be in your eyes...
Rue.
Rue-chan...
The prince regained the feeling of affection, but
what it illuminated was Duck's unhappiness?
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
Love? It's really not like that with me...
I'm sure she's pursuing a wonderful dream.
And she's probably also in love.
You will always wake up from a dream.
No, it's something you MUST wake up from.
Are you trembling?
I'm afraid of Princess Tutu.
I just wanted Mytho to smile. That was all...
Have I been... doing something terrible... to Mytho?
All you children who love stories, come gather around.
''Dreaming Aurora''