Once upon a time, there was a young woman.
The young woman was to marry a groom chosen by her
parents, and not her sweetheart, whom she loved.
She knew that her groom loved her very much, but did her
sweetheart care for her even more than that?
The young woman wasn't certain.
In the end, after wavering between the two of them, the young woman even became unsure which one of them she really loved.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
In searching for a way to return Mytho to the story,
I just took to hand whatever books struck me.
"The Forgotten Story"
So why do I choose only books whose endings are missing?
Why?
What meaning is there to these torn up books? I...
Found you!
Jeez, Ahiru, can't you even go a day without
getting yourself put on cleaning duty?
Of course, she can't!
I'm sorry.
Seriously, I'm telling you...
Ugh!
No way!
Huh? What?
Ahiru, you mustn't look right now!
This is a shock.
That's definitely...
What'd you do that for, all of a...
No, Ahiru! There's something you
mustn't look at RIGHT THERE, look!
Thank you!
Fakir...
He smiled!
That totally ruins his bad-boy appeal!
That's right, we need him to become a
full-fledged juvenile delinquent!
Who is this woman who can take the bite out of Fakir-sama?!
Huh?
An older-woman lover has made her appearance, huh!
We still don't know that she's his lover!
That's right, you should have unreasonable hopes!
You should make sure!
Be brave!
Oh, my...
Hey.
Oh, Fakir! Um...
Are you a friend of Fakir's?
She's calling her a "friend" right off the bat!
Well, that is...
Talk about the unfazed confidence of the adult woman!
I don't know if you'd call me a friend or a... a... well...
Oh, it's like I can see Ahiru's crying face before me!
I can't sit here any longer.
We were all just on our way to the ice cream shop. Right?
Huh?
Um, they were just here...
You're an interesting person.
I'm Raetsel. What's your name?
I'm Ahiru.
Ahiru-san, we're going to Fakir's house now.
Come along with us.
What?
Raetsel.
Oh, why not?
Right?
I'm impressed you found out where I was.
You can't hide anything from me, Fakir.
In our house there's still...
Oh, welcome home.
It's been a long time, hasn't it Karon?
Raetsel!
I can come in, right?
Sure.
Who do you go well together with zura?
What?
It's a new lovey-dovey zura!
Karon, this isn't your...
I don't think I've seen you since Mytho
and I entered Gold Crown Academy.
That's right. I was really lonely then.
Here.
Oh, thanks.
It's all right, I'm like an older sister to Fakir.
Older sister?
I mean, no, I wasn't really...
Ever since my parents died and I was taken in by Karon,
she's been like a surrogate mother to me.
Is older sister different from lovey-dovey zura?
Then is Raetsel lovey-dovey with Kar...
Hey, Uzura!
Lovey-dovey! Lovey-dovey!
How flattering. Do we look like that?
That would be nice.
You shouldn't tease adults.
You're going to treat me like a child, as always?
I'm at an age where it wouldn't be odd
if I married somebody, you know.
To me, you haven't changed one bit.
You're just like when you were romping
around with Fakir and Mytho.
That reminds me, where is Mytho?
Oh, yeah, he's at school. He's
completely wrapped up in his dancing.
But you always used to be with him,
saying, "I'll protect Mytho!"
I WILL protect him!
You're staying the night, right?
No, that's okay. I plan to stay at the water mill.
I'll walk you there, then.
Thank you, but I think I'd like to take
a little walk with Ahiru-san.
What?
I'm a tiny bit jealous.
Huh?
Fakir with a girl as cute as you...
Oh, no, I'm not cute at all!
And I'm always fighting with Fakir, actually
sometimes I just can't STAND him...
I wonder if it's thanks to you that Fakir has changed.
Say, is Fakir writing stories?
Stories?
The stories that boy wrote sometimes came true.
What? Stories came true?
He loved to write stories from the
time when he was very small.
They were just silly little stories, but
sometimes parts of them came true.
But after he came to Karon's house,
he completely stopped writing.
Raetsel-san?
Oh, I've said a little too much. I wonder if Fakir will scold me?
To think Fakir wrote stories... And they came true!
If he can do that... maybe...
Ahiru-san?
Oh, I'm sorry! I just remembered something I have to do!
Um, it was fun talking to you!
Fakir has changed.
No, the one who's changed the most...
is me.
Protect, huh?
How do I protect him? Who do I fight?
Help me, Fakir, my heart is...
In the story, you're no longer needed.
The fight has begun.
The story is moving... Whether I'm here or not.
But all I have... is a sword.
I'll protect Mytho with this sword.
There you are!
Fakir, I heard from Raetsel-san that
the stories you write come true!
What?
If you do have that power, then if you
write a story where Mytho is saved...
Fakir?
What are you talking about?
Huh?
I said, I heard the stories you wrote
when you were little came true...
So...
Be quiet.
Huh? But Mytho...
Shut up!
What do you mean, shut up? Why
are you talking to me that way?
If I could help Mytho by myself, I wouldn't ask you to do this!
But right now, I can't do anything, so...
I told you to be quiet!
I'll protect Mytho as a knight. I won't take orders from you!
Fak...
Fakir, why?! Listen to me!
Fakir! Come on, Fakir! If you can help
Mytho, then why won't you?!
What's with that attitude?
We were waiting for you so we'd be ready
whenever you came home crying!
So, what happened with Fakir-sama?
I don't care about that Fakir anymore!
Good, good! Get angry and cry as much as you want!
We'll give you lots of comfort!
And I thought we'd be able to help Mytho...
Why?
Lately it's like Mytho-sama is a totally different person.
He's scary somehow!
He makes the hairs on the back of my neck stand up!
Raetsel.
Mytho... I'm jealous of you.
Of me?
If I could live without changing, like you...
That's not true.
I'm different than I was before.
I've gotten my heart back.
Now I can even accept your love for me.
Well, that makes me happy. Maybe I'll call off the wedding.
Wedding?
That is Mytho-san. Which means the girl is Rue-san?
The two of them are getting married?!
Is that right, getting married...
Students of mine are getting married before me!
There is no happier thing for a teacher than this!
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You don't look very happy. Could it be you're wavering?
Of course not. What I said before was a joke!
Hans will love me from the bottom of his heart.
With him, I'm sure I can be happy.
You can't lie to your own feelings.
You've got a pure and beautiful heart, haven't you?
I'm going now, Mytho.
You have to love me. Sacrifice your life and love me!
If I do as Father says, someday he'll be my prince alone.
Right, Father?
The fight between the prince and the raven is being
fought with fiercer and fiercer desperation.
In a place where no one can see it, that is.
She's definitely toying with him!
That's right, a Fakir played thoroughly by an adult woman
and then tossed away like a tattered dishrag!
Oh, how wonderful!
I'd love for him to keep on like this and
become more and more of a delinquent!
Fakir said he'd protect Mytho, so why?
I'll protect Mytho as a knight. I won't take orders from you!
And it was starting to look like we'd
be able to work together too...
I don't like this.
I don't want things to stay like this!
Huh?
Hey, wait, where are you going, Ahiru?
Time for the second round, right?
Oh, Ahiru, you do so love battles!
I see, so Fakir said that...
I want to help someone, and he's someone
important to Fakir too...
So I thought if Fakir wrote a story,
maybe we could help him, but...
I'm sorry.
This is because I said something I shouldn't have.
What?
Ahiru-san, will you pretend you
never heard what I said before?
What? But if that person is saved, Fakir will be happy too...
But in exchange, Fakir will be hurt.
What?
A long time ago, a lot of crows once
showed up in Gold Crown Town.
Crows?
The crows attacked the townspeople indiscriminately.
Fakir was a child, but he must have
wanted to do something to help.
He wrote a story where he became
a hero and defeated the crows.
And then just like Fakir had written,
the crows came and attacked him.
But the ending was different than his story.
Afterwards, it was as if he'd sealed those memories away.
He never talked about it.
And he stopped writing stories too.
I didn't know that Fakir had something
like that happen to him...
He must still be unable to recover from it...
Ahiru-san, please give Fakir space.
What am I doing?
I came to get you, Raetsel...
My bride.
Lovey-dovey! Lovey-dovey!
Ahiru, what's wrong zura?
I'm the worst. What should I say to Fakir?
Do you want to say something to Fakir zura?
There's a lot of crows zura!
The water mill.
Could Mytho be doing to Raetsel-san...
Raetsel, I'll give you a love with no wavering.
You'll love only me, won't you?
Yes... Mytho...
Come, Raetsel, and give your beautiful heart to me!
I am Mytho's bride.
Wait.
Who are you?
I am Princess Tutu.
Dance with me, Raetsel-san.
Princess Tutu?
If you do have that power, then if you
write a story where Mytho is saved...
What is this awful feeling?
The power to make stories come true?
A power like that, in me?
Lovey-dovey, lovey-dovey, lovey-dovey...
It's ridiculous.
Fakir!
Could it be that Mytho is lovey-dovey with Raetsel-san zura?!
That's a lovely wedding dress.
You have someone you're engaged to, right?
Then why are you...
Karon knows how I feel, but he didn't say anything.
What?
But Hans... He tells me of his love.
He looks at only me, and holds me.
I love him too. But no matter what I do,
I see Karon's face in my mind!
You're suffering because you're wavering between two loves.
If you love me, your wavering will disappear.
You mustn't go over there. What's wrong with wavering?
That's something you feel because you truly love people.
I may still love Karon!
When I think that, being with him is so hard and so painful.
Karon?!
I don't want to waver anymore!
Raetsel...
That's right! If you love only me...
If I love only Mytho...
No! That's a mistake, Raetsel-san!
You should just forget everything else, and love only me!
Both of those are your true heart, Raetsel-san.
But is what you're trying to get right now your true feelings?
"True" and "false" have nothing to do with it!
People just love others because they want to be loved!
So she wavers because she wonders which one will love her!
That pain is how you really feel! So wake up!
You want to be happy with the one you love most, don't you?
I weighed their loves against each other
for the sake of my own happiness!
To escape from the pain of my wavering, I set
out to get Fakir to write a story about me!
Even though I knew it would hurt him!
I'm a horrible woman...
Everyone wants to be loved by the people they love.
It's not bad to feel that way.
I'm sure it's painful to waver between two loves.
But even if you run away from that, you
won't be able to escape the pain.
You should just love me!
Raetsel!
Mytho! I won't allow you to hurt Raetsel!
Interesting.
Stop! The two of you fighting is...
Mytho, do you feel nothing? Using even Raetsel?
I tried to save her!
Fakir!
"Save her"?!
Don't just prattle what's convenient for you!
What can YOU do, then?
A knight who couldn't even die shouldn't talk so big!
How pathetic you are.
How long do you mean to go on shaming
yourself wielding your play sword?!
Mytho, stop it!
You know you can't lay a finger on me!
This sword isn't for slaying you with!
Wake up! Remember your true self!
Mytho...
Stop it...
Shut up.
Shut up! SHUT UP!
Fakir!
Stop it. Don't hurt Fakir, you raven!
Mytho?
Run! Don't... Don't come near me...
Mytho...
Raetsel! Raetsel...
Fakir, I'm sorry. I...
I thought only of myself.
I forgot everything but my desire to escape my pain...
And I did something to hurt you...
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's not your fault, Raetsel.
Raetsel-san was suffering so much, but she told me...
She told me to give you space.
Raetsel-san didn't want to hurt you.
Fakir?
Take care of Raetsel.
Fakir...
Didn't want to hurt you...
Don't hurt Fakir, you raven!
If I could help Mytho by myself, I wouldn't ask you to do this!
But right now, I can't do anything, so...
What I can do...
That's right.
Fakir?
You're...
Raetsel!
Oh, did you write a story for me?
Karon, I'm going to marry Hans.
What?
I see. Congratulations.
Raetsel...
You see, I think I wanted to say a proper goodbye to Karon.
But I'll take this. Thank you.
Your story didn't come true, huh?
I suppose.
Huh?
I think I'll try writing one.
What?
A story about Mytho.
That's dangerous. That power is truly dangerous, you know.
You couldn't even completely become a knight.
Will you really be able to master it?
Well?
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
They took out the endings to stop the
stories from becoming real?
He's awakened.
This is dangerous.
It seems he's gained the knowledge, but that's all.
You're a direct descendant of Drosselmeyer's,
and this is your level?
That hurts.
You hesitated to take my hand!
Mytho was always kind to Rue-chan, but...
To those who accept everything, happiness.
To those who resist everything, glory.
Fakir, please wake up.
"The Spinners"
All you children who love stories, come gather around.