Once upon a time, a witch's curse put a
princess into an eternal sleep,
and one young man appeared,
intending to awake her.
But a voice whispered,
"Awaken the princess from her sleep?
What a cruel thing to do."
Is the princess not wishing for
the kiss of awakening,
but rather to continue to sleep forever?
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
So, you're awake.
Fakir.
What?
I wonder... What do I think of you, Fakir?
When I think of Rue...
When I think of you...
And when I think of Tutu...
Each makes me feel different,
but I don't know what those feelings are.
Tell me, Fakir, don't I need to
know what they are?
Don't think about such absurd things!
But...
Listen, you're just a useless good-for...
Are you trembling?
Oh, I just couldn't sleep somehow.
I saw Mytho smile.
I guess for Rue-chan, he'll smile like that.
There's no way that he doesn't need a heart!
Mytho...
I'll get your heart back.
Oh, Fakir!
Just what is he plotting?
Is he trying to trick Mytho into doing whatever he says?
Or is he after something else?
It's no use no matter what you're plotting.
Princess Tutu will get all of Mytho's heart...
Quack!
Qua... Qua... Quack... Quack!
Ahiru! Ahiru, let's go!
Maybe she mistook the time and left early again.
"Dreaming Aurora"
A theatrical troupe?
Says it's the Eleki Troupe.
Never heard of them.
"Sleeping Beauty," huh?
We are a touring ballet troupe called the Eleki Troupe.
Starting the day after tomorrow, we will perform
"Sleeping Beauty" at this theater.
Ladies and gentlemen, please come to see us!
I look forward to seeing you there!
Hey, did you see that flier? They're called the Eleki Troupe!
They're performing at the theater in town!
I want to go see them!
And so, today, we have received special permission for both
the boys and girls to observe the Eleki Troupe's rehearsal.
I hope you take this chance to get a taste of foreign ballet
and use that towards your own growth as a dancer a little...
Do you not think so, Ahiru-san?!
Um, well...
Do you not think so?
Oh, yes, you're right. I do not think so, either!
You do not think so?
Yes, you are exactly right, Cat-sensei. I do not think so at all!
What is it that you do not think so about?
Um, well, so, about wanting to marry you...
Was that wrong?
Mytho, you go back to the dormitory.
Okay.
Cat-sensei's all depressed now.
He might not be able to recover.
Yeah...
Does it bother you that the Mytho-sama isn't here?
Oh, my!
Fakir's coming alone.
You're bothered by what Fakir-sama does, too?!
Yeah...
Oh, my!
You said you weren't interested in Fakir-sama, remember?!
What's wrong with that?! She's at
that age when you fall in love!
It IS wrong! You're all lovey for Mytho-sama,
right?! Right?! Right?!
You're so cute because you don't know your own place!
Which one do you actually love?!
She loves them both! She's two-timing!
Love?!
It's really not anything like that with me. In other words...
Whoa!
Huh?
What an energetic student you are.
Uh, um...
Ahiru is so lucky!
Three-timing?!
My name is Paulamoni. I am the leading lady of Eleki Troupe.
It's nice to meet you.
Thank you very much for sharing your
precious time with us today,
Miss...
Let's dispense with the formalities.
I heartily agree.
I hope you'll all make yourselves at home as well.
It's here! It's finally here!
The premonition of love!
Oh, rejoice, my great desire!
This is my husband, Paulo.
Nice to meet you.
Now, come right on in.
Right now, this is...
It's so pretty.
You lucky dog, you!
Can't...
You got to be held like a princess by
such a wonderful person!
Oh, if you wanted to be held, I would've held you!
Can't breathe!
Just hold on a second.
An electric eel...
Let me introduce him. This is our troupe
leader and electrical guy.
Troupe leader?
Come on, steady supply!
The angle is the key in getting him to keep it up.
Was our troupe leader an eel?
What? Come to think of it, before we got to this town...
But of course that can't be, right?
Yeah, no way. Oh, well, it'll save us on the power bill.
That's true.
Is Rue Princess Tutu?
What?
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing. I'm sorry.
Really? Then let's continue.
Say, just watching is boring, isn't it?
Let's see someone else dance.
What?
Hey, Paulamoni, this is too sudden...
What does it matter? I want to see.
But...
Certainly!
I shall show you the results of MY lessons!
Now, are there any volunteers?
This is your chance to earn brownie points!
Even if you lose points, you're just back where you were!
No, no, no! I can't, I can't, I can't!
It cannot be helped then. I will pick someone.
Rue-s...
You.
Meow?
What?!
What do you say?
I can't do it! That is...
I can't, I can't!
Since she's saying she can't, let's not have her do it!
Please enjoy another student's dance!
If you'd like, I will perform myself...
Oh, I suppose it was too sudden after all. I'm sorry.
No, we'll dance! We were actually wanting to dance!
Really, it's fine.
Oh, that sure scared me.
What?
A shard of Mytho's heart?
Huh? Did I imagine that?
We'll have a run-through tomorrow,
so please come watch!
We will! Gladly!
I'm always nervous when I get up on stage,
but I've never felt like this.
I fell in love with that Princess Aurora
I saw when I was a child.
She seemed to still be dreaming even when awakened.
I wanted to become like that someday.
So, I danced the part of Princess Aurora all this time, but...
I'd begun to be aware that it was no use,
no matter how I polished my technique.
It's because I wasn't born with the same talent.
My dream, never to come true...
But...
No matter how depressed I was, I never felt like this before.
What's the matter with me? I'm afraid of performing?
Hey, Paulamoni!
Yes?
Help me out with making dinner for everyone.
Okay.
Ooh, that smells great!
If we don't feed our troupe leader soon,
we'll have a power outage.
You want to postpone opening day?
What?
You've got something on your mind, don't you?
Thank you for worrying about me.
But I couldn't trouble everyone else.
Don't worry, I can do it.
Would anyone like some gems?
Would anyone like some beautiful gems?
I didn't know you sold gems, Edel-san.
And Fakir said that he doesn't need a heart.
There's no way that's true, right? He's
weird. He's definitely weird.
You know, Mytho doesn't even know
what it feels like to be in love.
Even though Rue-chan loves Mytho. Isn't that sad?
Sad?
You think so, don't you?
Is it sad for Mytho? For Rue? Or for you?
What?
I'm not really...
So, no matter what Fakir does to get in my way,
I'm definitely going to get all of his heart back.
Rue-chan can make Mytho happy, but for a
bird like me, that's all I can do for him.
That's pretty!
The name of this gem is "dream."
Between a person who continues to dream and a person
who's awoken from a dream, who is happier?
Huh? Hmm, which would it be?
Anyway, what's this gem called?
"Hope."
What about this one?
"Adventure."
Then how about this one?
"Mystery."
Okay, what about this one?
"The author's convenience."
Weird name...
At any rate, my wish is to get Mytho
to smile again. That's all!
Bye!
That's right. I'm going to work harder and get
back all the shards of Mytho's heart for him!
All right! Go for it, Ahiru!
Yes, I'll do my best!
Mytho.
What?
Go on the ballet field trip tomorrow.
I can go?
On one condition. Don't listen to what Rue tells you.
Okay.
I'll come along too. Hurry up and go to sleep.
Thank you, Fakir.
Idiot.
The girl you called on today...
I wanted to see her dance too.
She had this glow about her, kind of a mysterious
charm that she just had innately.
Just had innately... Yes.
I'm sure she's pursuing a wonderful dream.
And she's probably also in love.
I can tell.
You certainly can tell a lot.
Yeah, because she's the same as
you when you were younger.
You will always wake from a dream.
No, it's something you MUST wake from.
You can't play the role of Aurora the way you are now.
You say it so bluntly.
Yeah, because the Aurora you aspire to be
is the kind of girl who continues to dream
even when she's woken from her dream, right?
But you're afraid to even dream.
That's because I can't become that Aurora.
Sure, there are some dreams
that won't come true,
but there's no rule that says you
can only have one dream.
What?
My dream...
is to enthrall people all over the
world with your dancing.
And to do that, I've even thought
of the perfect program for you.
Perfect for me?
So, how about it, Paulamoni?
Wanna try jumping on the bandwagon of my dream?
I had no idea you were thinking about things like that.
I'm a long way from waking from
my dream or my love, you know.
Paulo...
Thank you, Paulo!
I'll dance my final turn as Aurora in this town!
Yes, and your best Aurora!
There is no need for worry.
No matter how the witch may curse me, I will
surely never prick my finger on a spindle.
For though I may dream and dance, I will
never lay a hand on a spinning wheel.
That smile...
Was that because he was dancing with me? Or...
Our troupe leader is hopeless.
All right, everyone, let's take a break!
Excuse me, sensei.
How may I be of service?
I would very much like to speak with you.
What?! You would like to speak with ME?!
Yes.
You mustn't! However, if you insist, I, too, as a man will...
I was hoping you would allow me to see
that girl from yesterday dance.
What?
I just really want to see what it is that I am lacking.
Are you serious?!
So, why me?
I agree.
Someone else would be...
But I'm really bad at this.
I know.
This is an earnest request from Paulamoni-san.
Don't worry, please dance to your heart's content.
Even if my love were to end because of it, I will never...
hold it against you.
It's been a while since Ahiru's been in a pinch!
I've been waiting for this!
Say, Mytho, why don't you partner with
her for the pas du deux?
What? With Mytho?
No, Mytho can't. I'll go.
Why did you get involved?
Ooh, our troupe leader's expert opinion
gauge is responding.
Rue, what are you thinking?
Pathetic.
I'll take this chance to make this clear to you.
What?
Stay away from Mytho.
YOU stay away from...
You're an eyesore.
That's it. This girl's dancing is hardly elegant,
but it's overflowing with her own individuality.
Mytho's heart shard...
Owowow...
Are you okay?
What? Oh, yes!
I'm sorry I asked you to do this when you didn't want to.
It was splendid. Are you hurt at all?
Uh, no, I'm completely fine!
Uh, um, where's the bathroom?!
Go out those doors, turn left, and at the end of the hall...
All right!
Oh? The shard of the prince's heart is running away.
I wonder what it's so afraid of, Princess Tutu?
Wait!
Why are you running away?
Now, let's go back to where you belong.
I don't want to, I'm afraid.
No, you have to go back.
Why?
You just have to.
What for?
So that Mytho can regain his smile.
I'll take you back.
Come on, give me your hand.
Come on.
No!
Now, go on back to Mytho.
Mytho!
A piece of his heart's been returned.
What?!
Everyone, stay calm!
What's that?
What?
Hang in there, Mytho!
Damn that Princess Tutu!
Quack!
I'm afraid... I'm afraid!
Calm down!
What's happened to Mytho?
It's okay! I'm the only one here!
What is it? What are you afraid of?
Tell me.
Tutu...
What?
I'm afraid...
of Princess Tutu.
I'm afraid of Princess Tutu.
What?
That can't be...
The feelings of fear and uncertainty.
Yet another shard has been returned.
But the prince seems sad.
I wonder what's going to happen after this?
Why?
I returned a shard of his heart...
What's going to happen to Mytho?
Why was Mytho suffering?
Why was Mytho crying?
I just wanted Mytho to smile.
That was all...
Was it bad?
Am I wrong?
Have I been... doing something terrible... to Mytho?
That's right, this is how the story moves along.
In the direction most undesirable for all concerned.
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
Being Princess Tutu is meaningless. I could quit and...
I've always only had eyes for Mytho.
I'm still far from having loved him enough.
I'll never appear before you again, so rest easy.
This is the feeling of loneliness and the feeling of sorrow.
Who are you?
Princess Kraehe.
I see, so... you've finally appeared.
I will not give you anything. I will
not allow you to do anything.
All you children who love stories, come gather around.
"The Crow Princess"