Once upon a time, there was a man who died.
The man was writing a story about a brave and handsome
prince, who vanquishes a crafty raven.
When the man died, the raven and the prince
escaped from within the story.
The prince took out his own heart
to seal away the raven,
but it was a forbidden power that had
been granted solely to the prince.
The raven was completely sealed away,
but the prince's heart was shattered
and the shards scattered all across town.
Ever since then, in this town, stories
and reality have intermingled,
and it became a world where the
fantastical was no longer fantastical.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
A dream? Where am I?
What am I doing here?
What?
Quack!
Huh?! What?! Huh?! No way! No way!
No way! No way! No way!
Quack...
I'm just a duck. And I thought I was a girl.
When I saved Mytho-senpai, was that a dream?
Quack! Could it be that this is a dream right now?!
Neither is a dream, Little Duck.
Quack! Quack, quack, quack!
Who are you?!
My name is Drosselmeyer.
Do you want to save the prince, who's lost his heart?
The person I want to save is Mytho-senpai...
The prince was a hero, who fought
against the demonic raven.
That was when they were inside the story that I wrote.
Inside the story?
Yes, he came out of the story and lost his
heart in order to seal away the raven.
His lost heart was shattered and is
now wandering as shards.
Princess Tutu is the only one who can restore his heart.
Princess Tutu...
If you have the resolve, I'll turn you into a girl once more.
Into a girl? Really? I'll get to see Mytho-senpai again?!
If you have the resolve, that is.
I do, I do!
If I can be a girl and stay by Mytho-senpai's side...
Then, someday...
Someday, I may be able to put a
smile back on his face and...
If that's something I can do, then
I could wish for no more.
Congratulations. If you dream of it,
your wish will be granted.
That's what's so great about stories.
The duck will become a girl and the girl
will become Princess Tutu.
Stories are such wonderful things.
But remember this.
If you say or do anything resembling a duck...
Quack!
You just remember that.
''Heart Shard''
Oh?
This is Gold Crown Town and I'm...
Quack!
A duck?!
Quack! Quack, quack, quack! Quack,
quack, quack, quack!
Quack!
I AM a duck.
So, Mytho-senpai and the prince were all a dream.
Yeah, of course.
Oh, it's so calming to be on the water.
Quack!
Qua...
If you say or do anything resembling a duck...
Oh, this...
It wasn't a dream.
Huh?
May those who accept their fate be granted happiness.
May those who defy their fate be granted glory.
Who's that?
I am Edel. You are Ahiru.
You know about me?!
Even as a girl, you still have duck-like
qualities about you, don't you?
What?
The way you look.
The way I look?
Think of it as having had all your feathers plucked.
These are for you.
So, if I'm a duck as in the bird, since when
was the girl the me that I am, or rather...
The me from yesterday and the
me from the day before that
and the me from before that
was all me after all, so...
I don't understand what's going on anymore.
A story's birth is a sudden event.
The start, a happy accident.
The end, the fate for which it's meant.
A story that never ends is a cruel thing.
I don't understand what you're saying either, Edel-san.
Let us meet again.
Yes.
Oh, well, oh, well, oh, well, oh, well.
Oh, well, oh, well, oh, well, oh,
well, oh, well. Oh, well...
Mytho-senpai...
I turned into Princess Tutu and saved Mytho-senpai, right?
I wonder if he remembers?
I guess even if he remembered,
he wouldn't know it was me.
Oh! What would he think if he found out
I was a duck, as in the bird?
''A duck? You're the worst. No wonder you sound
like a duck. Shoo, shoo.'' Like that?
Or would he be like, ''Yikes, you stink like a bird!''
Or, ''My favorite food! Let's dig in!''
I'll keep it a secret.
Mytho-senpai...
The thing about the prince who lost his heart...
Oh, I haven't properly apologized about his foot yet!
I must go...
Oh!
Uh, um...
I'm so sorry!
What?
Is your foot still hurting?
Not really.
It's all better, then. Thank goodness.
I have to say something.
Are you reading a book?
Just look, it's obvious! Just look!
What the heck am I saying?
Do you like books?
Whoa, that sounds so snobbish! I sound
so snobbish somehow!
Is the book interesting?
Of course, it is. He's reading it
because it's interesting.
Not really.
Huh?
I don't think I particularly like or dislike books.
There they are again, lonely looking eyes.
Good day, Mytho.
Oh, Rue-chan?
Qua...
An anteater?! An anteater that eats ants?!
Why an anteater? Okay, well, I'm a duck, too, but...
May I sit next to you?
Sure.
What are your thoughts on Rue-san?
I don't know.
You love her, do you not?
Not really.
Then, might I ask you to be with me
instead? Would you be averse to it?
Not really.
No way!
Mytho...
She licked him!
Oh, excuse me please!
Quack!
Quack! Quack, quack!
Quack, quack, quack!
You can't come this way! You can't!
I can't do this as a duck!
How can I go back to being a girl?!
Um, what did I do last time? I know! Water!
I did it! Rue-chan!
Oh, I can't go all naked like this!
Um, so... Um, um... I know! Quack!
Ah, that is, oh!
My, if it isn't Rue-san.
Allow me to inform you.
Mytho is going to be with me, now.
What?
It seems it is clear who is the winner here.
Excuse us.
No! No! I'm pretty sure that's not true!
That wasn't for real and...
It doesn't bother me.
What?
You're a good person.
What?! With Anteaterina?!
Didn't Mytho-sama love Rue?
And now, of all people, with Anteaterina?!
Oh, my god!
What?
You dumped Rue, didn't you?
You're a terrible guy.
Am I?
It's because you don't understand people's feelings.
That's why you do things like that
without a second thought.
Sorry.
Idiot. That's how it should be.
With ballet, take a day off and you will know,
take three days off and those
around you will know,
and take a week off and the audience will know.
As this adage indicates, daily practice is most important.
And so, from now on, we will have a test
once a month to assign you to a class.
In the worst case scenario, you will be
dropped to the probationary class!
What?!
I don't want to be on probation NOW!
That, or I will have you marry me!
I don't want that, either!
Don't want...
Cat-sensei!
What is it, Anteaterina-san?! Meow!
Is the special class strictly limited to five people?
Yes, so?! Meow!
Then I suppose someone else will be
dropped to make room for me!
Oh, my!
This is a declaration of war!
What?
So, she means to take not only her
lover, but her status as well!
What?
What an exciting turn of events!
I shall dance a pas de deux with my partner.
Come, Mytho!
An even more exciting turn of events!
This can't be happening!
I guess it wasn't all talk after all!
A women's battle!
She's definitely good, but somehow...
there's no joy in it.
Rue-san, I would very much like to see your pas de deux.
But whether there is a partner for you or not...
That's so mean.
Rue-chan's in a pinch!
A pinch!
Would you dance with me?
Wha?!
Yes.
Ahiru's in a pinch!
What?!
Why with Ahiru?
Maybe an excuse for when she loses?
Good point.
Rue-chan, you know, I'm really terrible at it.
So, I'm sure I'll be no good at all...
Don't worry, just follow my lead.
Don't be nervous.
Okay.
I'll bet she's going to mess up!
I know!
I sense a storm brewing!
Jump.
You were wonderful.
Really?
It's like she wasn't Ahiru!
That's right! That wasn't Ahiru!
After the humiliation that I, your
girlfriend, just went through...
Do you not think anything of it?!
Not really.
Could it be that you did not do your best on purpose?!
I don't know.
Do not mock me!
If you had not been Rue's boyfriend,
I would not have asked you out, either!
Goodbye.
Um...
Have you come to laugh at me?!
No, I would never...
Oh, wait!
What?
Leave me alone!
What's going on?
Anteaterina-chan!
It's not fair! Not fair! Not fair! Not fair!
It's not fair...
I know how you feel. Go on and cry.
It IS unfair.
Mytho-senpai...
It is unfair...
It's so unfair, it hurts.
Please, stay with me always.
Of course.
No, what in the world is that?
I need you.
I need your broken heart.
Oh, that's...
Looks like you've found a shard of the prince's lost heart.
Now, reveal the mystery for me, Princess Tutu.
Who are you?!
Have you come to laugh at me as well?!
Anteaterina-chan, that isn't your partner.
Don't be ridiculous!
Dance with me, Anteaterina-chan.
I refuse! You couldn't possibly understand how I feel!
Go back!
Anteaterina-chan, is that your way of dancing?!
Yes! To make your audience surrender! THAT is art!
But that's not how you really feel, is it?!
No! I believe it from the bottom of my heart!
This is my way of dancing!
Then why do you seem to be in such pain?!
There's no joy in your dancing at all.
What are you so bitter about?
That is...
How wonderful.
Please tell me. What must I do to dance so wonderfully?
I don't know. Practice, I suppose.
I will work hard!
I will work hard and become able to
dance like you as well, Rue-san!
That will be impossible for you.
I want to win against Rue-san...
I wanted to win no matter what means I had to use!
That's not...
That's not how you truly feel, Anteaterina-chan.
Forget about your bitterness and your hatred
and show me your way of dancing.
I'm sure it'll be much more beautiful.
Dance. Let's dance together.
To your heart's content.
Be honest.
Be free.
Yes,
because that is your way of dancing.
I feel such joy!
You are...
I am the feeling of bitter disappointment,
shattered and forgotten.
This is not where you belong.
Must I... wander again?
You have to go back.
Can I go back?
Yes.
I'm so glad.
What?
I've really and truly become Princess Tutu.
Mytho!
What happened, Mytho?!
What is this feeling?
Feeling?
Now then, the special class will consist
of the same five people as before.
And Anteaterina-san?
Yes?
Your performance was quite fine as well, but
the decision is to wait and see for now.
Yes, I understand.
I have decided to stop copying Rue-san
and to find my own way of dancing.
I look forward to seeing it.
And Ahiru-san?
Yes?!
Your performance was also quite fine.
Yes, sir!
However, you owe it all to Rue-san!
Thus, you are assigned to the probationary class!
Quack!
I knew it!
You must never forget that Ahiru is a duck.
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
So, Mytho-senpai is a prince out of a story.
That's why he's so handsome.
I love you, Rue.
I wonder if Rue-chan knows about this?
Princess Tutu...
Princess Tutu?
This is ridiculous. That's just a story.
She's blessed with beauty, cleverness, and strength,
but the princess is fated never to be with her prince.
The moment she confesses her love,
she turns into a speck of light and vanishes.
''The Princess's Vow''
Quack!
All you children who love stories,
come gather around.