Once upon a time, there was a girl who
loved to dance very much.
The girl made the mistake of putting on a pair of red shoes
that would force her to dance for eternity once they were on.
The girl continued to dance day and night...
Oh my. This is a different story.
But...
Perhaps it is not entirely different after all.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
I want to know what you think of me.
I... I...
I'm a duck.
I'm really only a bird.
But what the prince sees is Princess
Tutu in her beautiful dress.
It's not me.
What... did I... just...
"The Black Shoes"
There are some things that just don't
change after a night's sleep.
Rue-chan and Mytho are still perfect for each other.
Fakir is still not nice.
I'm still a duck.
And outside the window, the sky is wide open as ever.
There's no problem.
Morning!
I am Rue.
I am not anyone else.
That's who I've always been.
And who I always will be.
Rue.
What?
I want to know.
Do I love you?
Tell me that you love me.
I love you, Rue.
Mytho, you love me.
I love you.
Do I really?
You do.
Then what is this feeling I have when I think of Tutu?
Tutu...
Tell me, Rue, maybe I'm actually...
You don't need to know any of that!
Isn't this kind of bad?
It looks bad.
What'll become of those two?
Ruin? Will they be ruined?!
Oh!
They'll be ruined, won't they?!
With this hand, I tried...
to pierce Mytho's heart.
It was because I believed that was best for Mytho.
But...
Now that Mytho himself wishes to regain his heart,
what can I do when I can't even stop him?
If there is anything I can do right now,
is it to accept fate by his side?
Without fear...
Fear?
Am I... the one who is afraid?
How about at the pizza shop?
What?
You don't know it? It's the red building on Church Street.
I don't, but what about the pizza shop?
What are you saying?
Huh?
What else could there be?
What?
Revenge!
What?! Revenge of...
Your confession, of course!
What?
Now that Mytho-sama and Rue-chan have
fallen to ruin, this is your chance!
Huh? What do you mean?!
Well, your confession the other day was
kind of lukewarm, you know?
No...
So, you can confess all over again!
Um...
Or rather, get turned down all over again?
Not that! What do you mean by ruin?!
What? What?
In other words, this is your chance!
Confession! Confession!
I'm telling you, I can't!
You coward!
Oh, Ahiru, you shouldn't roll down the hallway.
It's your fault.
Really?
You again, Ahiru-san?
Rolling down the hallway...
If you keep it up,
I will have no choice but to have you marry me!
I'm sorry!
Something's rolling down the hall incredibly fast towards us!
What was that?
Goatette-sensei.
If you roll down the hallway, you'll
be forced to marry Cat-sensei!
Have you come again to read that book?
Then, how about inviting him over to your house?
House?
Oh? Where is your house?
Oh, the lake...
Lake?
Oh, no, out towards the lake?
So, that means it's outside the town.
All we have in town is an old pond after all.
Now, that will be it for the beginner class lesson.
Next...
The private lessons for the advanced class will
start after this, so please leave immediately.
If you hang about, I will have you marry me!
Goatette-sensei is hanging about...
It seems you'll have to get married.
Meow, meow!
Mytho...
It's your chance!
Wonderful as ever, aren't they?
It doesn't look like there's any opening for Ahiru.
Don't lose heart, Ahiru.
That's right. After all, we already knew this to be the case.
I know.
Mytho is perfect for Rue-chan.
I know that I'm just a duck.
I want to know what you think of me.
I know what I think of Mytho.
But I can't say it.
If you become Princess Tutu,
you can save the prince,
but if you proclaim your love to him, you'll
turn into a speck of light and vanish.
I know.
But somehow, my heart aches...
You don't have to change at all.
You're fine just the way you are.
And yet, why do you try to change?
When I don't want to change.
When I want things to stay just the way they are.
Princess Tutu...
What in the world is there that I need fear?
Ridiculous.
The prince and the crow...
Written here is Mytho's tale.
The fate of a prince who tried to protect all who were weak
and to do that, hurt himself and even lost his own heart.
That's all.
May those who accept their fate be granted happiness.
May those who defy their fate be granted glory.
You're...
The story is continuing, the story is alive.
Are you saying...this is my fate?
Is it sad for Rue? For Mytho? For Ahiru?
Or for...
You know, Rue-chan, you dance en pointe so beautifully.
When you and Mytho dance, it's always so wonderful.
I'd love to dance like you, but there's
no way I can do that yet.
Did you want something?
Oh, uh, well...
Earlier, you mentioned Princess Tutu...
What are you babbling on about?
A fairy tale like that is of no importance.
You're your usual self.
Of course, I am. I'm not going to change.
If you want something, hurry up and say it.
There's not really anything.
You know, I think the first person to
dance en pointe was incredible.
Don't you?
The toe shoes of that person who first danced en pointe...
Do you know what happened to them?
What? No idea...
They were eaten.
What?!
By a person who worshipped that ballerina.
That's kind of amazing.
It's a stupid story.
Huh?
Strange.
What?! No way! What's strange?! Where?!
I've never talked about something like
this with another girl before.
Oh, could it be that you hate this kind of thing?
I don't think I hate it.
I'm glad. We can become even better
friends eventually, right?
You think so?
Hey, hey, Rue-chan, teach me about going en pointe.
Why do I have to teach you?
Because we're friends!
Why, what a cheeky...
Oh? Rue-chan?
What?
Hey, is that girl your friend too?
Huh? What girl?
She disappeared.
Now, that will be all for today's lecture...
Goodbye, Rue-san.
Goodbye.
I bid you good afternoon.
Do your best in detention again today.
Well, your failures are what make you
Ahiru, so don't let it bother you.
Ahiru, you can't go home yet?
Huh?!
Yeah, because I have to stay behind and
wipe the windows as punishment.
I see.
Friends...
That's the girl from...
She went into the art building.
So, she studies drawing.
Rue-chan.
Rue... sama.
Why did you take so long to say it?!
Besides, we've walked together and talked
all this time, so we're already friends.
So, it's Rue-chan!
You're like a real princess, and you really suit each
other, so I'm sure you'll get the golden apple.
You really suit each other, so...
Suit each other?
That is just an idea that you have
gotten stuck in your head.
You may need me, but I do not need you!
The person I need is Mytho,
but the one Mytho needs is...
Princess Tutu.
I wonder... What do I think of you, Fakir?
When I think of Rue...
When I think of you...
And when I think of Tutu...
Each makes me feel different...
I'm going, Fakir.
You're kidding, right?
I'm serious.
What would be the point in seeing her?
She might know something about Tutu.
Mytho is changing.
Into a Mytho I don't know.
That is something that cannot be helped.
We both even think differently, after all.
As you can see, even our interests and
what we eat are completely different.
That is why I do not want to marry you.
I have no intentions of changing my will!
My will...
Do you understand me, Goatette-sensei?
Hello?
You're one of the ballet students...
Well, I'm really bad at drawing pictures.
That's because you're in ballet.
I'm bad at ballet too, though.
Oh, you are? I'm sorry.
Oh, it's okay, it's okay!
Let me take a peek.
Wow, it's beautiful.
It's a drawing of Rue-chan...
I envy you, you draw so well.
Oh, did you draw these too?
Yes.
Oh? They're all drawings of Rue-chan?
Oh, but Rue-chan is so pretty, I can totally understand.
Hey, this one's signed.
So, your name's Malen? It's a cute name!
I'm Ahiru.
I don't understand.
What?
I don't really understand myself.
I've always liked drawing with
Rue-san as the model,
but before, I wanted to draw all sorts of other
things too, like fruits and landscapes.
But now, I can only draw Rue-san.
Princess Tutu.
Princess Tutu will change everything.
She will change Mytho.
At this rate, Mytho will grow more distant from me.
I won't allow that to happen!
Then what do you plan to do about it?
What?
A beautiful black swan.
Who is the heroine of this story?
Is it Princess Tutu? Or is it Princess Kraehe?
Princess Kraehe...
It hurts when I try to draw other things.
A story doesn't need two heroines.
A prince doesn't need two princesses.
Now, tell me what happens next.
Dance with me, Malen.
Who are you? I can't dance...
Don't worry, you can just dance freely.
The source of your pain is the false heart within your heart.
I'll remove it for you.
Then, you'll be able to draw the things you love again.
Really?
Yes.
You can go back to being your old self.
Thank you.
I want to remain the same, never changing.
I see.
Once again, Princess Tutu...
will change Mytho.
What's this?
Tutu, where are you?
What emotion are you?
I am the feeling of devotion.
You are a shard of the prince's heart which he lost.
The feeling of devotion, is it?
Kraehe...
I won't allow you to return such a thing to Mytho.
What are you going to do?
Oh, I don't know, what should I do?
No!
You'd better forget about restoring any
more heart shards to the prince.
But the prince is...
The prince says he wants to regain his heart.
Princess Tutu!
Oh, thank goodness, I've finally found you.
Kraehe...
Why?
Why do you look at me like that?
I...
Kraehe?
What's wrong?
Don't come near me!
I am... not needed?
Kraehe, why are you in such pain?
What?
Is it anything I can help you with?
Who... is Kraehe?
Fakir!
Be gone, you ugly crow!
Crow...
I remember now. I am a crow.
And I am the TRUE prima donna, Princess Kraehe.
I can take whatever I want, by force if need be!
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
Mytho and Kraehe's wedding?
With Fakir as witness...
The legend you told me about is all becoming reality.
It would be better if you did not involve yourself
in this accursed tale any further!
It's weird for your name to be Prince, so
how about taking the name Mytho?
You're going to Kraehe?
Because I feel that I mustn't run away...
What do you think, Princess Tutu?
Aren't we just perfect for each other?
All you children who love stories, come gather around.
"Cinderella"