Once upon a time, there was a girl who
loved flowers more than anyone.
She prayed every day for the whole town
to be filled with beautiful flowers.
To make that happen, she pulled up
all the ugly weeds in town.
Eventually the girl's prayers were answered
and the town was blanketed in flowers.
But they say the town that was filled with blossoms
of all colors looked gray somehow.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
Rue-chan.
Rue-chan?
"The Maiden's Prayer"
Rue-chan...
Rue-chan came back looking like herself.
Not like Kraehe.
But something is different. Is she really Kraehe after all?
Is it Kraehe's fault that Mytho tried to take Pike's heart?
Is something happening, behind the
scenes where I can't see it?
I don't want to fight anymore...
Say, why don't you fight one more time?
No!
But a chance like this doesn't come along
every day, so a magnificent battle...
We're not gonna!
Darn.
Besides, I used to be into Mytho-sama too,
but frankly my passion has cooled off.
At this point, I really don't care.
In the end, I've always been a Fakir-sama girl!
Fakir-sama definitely is cool lately, isn't he?
Like that air of mystery, for instance.
You mean that air of a shady criminal!
And that slight aura of darkness.
You mean that gloomy mood!
Wanna battle?
Bring it on!
What?! You can't!
Huh?
A battle would be...
Have you become a Fakir-sama girl too, Ahiru?
It's a three-way fight!
No! That's not it!
I'm saying I don't like fighting, or rather, you shouldn't fight...
How divine!
So divine!
It's Mytho-senpai and Rue-san!
I'm so jealous!
Aren't they divine?!
What? Is Rue-san hurt?
Mytho-senpai is so wonderful!
But if he'd carry me that way, getting
hurt might not be so bad.
I want to be held by Mytho-senpai like that too!
Um...
I have divine news for you all.
The Gold Crown Academy Fine Arts Week starts tomorrow,
and Mytho-san says that whoever wins this ballet contest
will be his partner in the Exhibition in place of Rue-san
who is injured and can't dance.
No way!
I won't lose!
This kind of chance comes once in a lifetime!
Don't rejoice just yet, ladies.
What?
The runner-up will have the great
opportunity to be my partner!
What's more, my partner in LIFE!
In other words, marriage! Marriage!
Viva mar...
I understand.
I've interpreted this to mean that everyone is aiming for
runner-up and has begun practicing hard right away!
I'm sure I saw Mytho and Rue go this way...
It's not so easy pretending to be injured.
"Pretending to be injured"?
Then she lied?
Do it right this time.
I know, Kraehe.
Kraehe? He just called her "Kraehe."
Mytho...
Bloom prettily! You too! And you too!
Wow!
What?
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to intrude!
It's okay. This garden belongs to everybody.
So pretty...
Aren't they?
Huh? No, that's not what I meant!
What?
Oh! I mean, of course the flowers are pretty!
But that's not all...
I'm Freya.
I'm Ahiru!
This is amazing. Did you grow all these flowers, Freya-san?
Flowers bloom on their own.
I just pray: "Bloom prettily, bloom abundantly."
Say, don't you have to practice, Freya-san?
You mean for the Arts Festival competition?
Yes.
I like ballet just like you do, so I'm going to practice later.
As soon as I'm finished taking care of these little ones.
You really love flowers, don't you?
Well, it would be wonderful if the world
were full of flowers, right?
Freya-san is what's wonderful.
It makes me wish I could become this wonderful.
But that would...
Never happen zura.
What? Really?
Really zura.
Not at all?
Not a chance zura!
Wait, who are you?!
It's not here zura. Where did you hide it zura?
Huh? What's not there?
Your duck's tail zura.
What do you mean, "duck"?
Where is it zura?
Quack!
Quack...
Quack... Quack...
You're a duck zura!
You DO have a tail zura.
Quack!
Quack, quack!
Just who was that kid, anyway?
Thanks to her I was late and now I have detention.
You're...
Huh? That voice is...
I'm not really hoping to win...
It IS Freya-san.
Do you hate me?
Mytho?
No, of course not.
Your beautiful heart makes beautiful flowers bloom.
If we put our abilities together...
I'm sure we could make a kind of flower
we've never seen before bloom.
There's no one in the world with such a beautiful heart that
they want to make the world happy with dancing and flowers.
Even you believe that, don't you?
I don't really...
It's all right to think that.
Because you're different from all those nobodies.
And you'll win the competition.
That's right. Everyone around you is your enemy.
Love only me, and regard all others with hatred.
Yes.
Pike, love only me.
Regard all others with hatred.
Yes, I'll love only you, and hate everyone else.
No!
These are...
The room's full of flowers we've never
seen before, isn't it Mytho-sama?
Tutu...
Freya-san.
The real you doesn't want to hate anyone, does she?
But Mytho wants it, so...
Tutu... help me...
Mytho...
Mytho-sama?
Mytho!
Freya-san!
You still haven't been completely soaked in raven's blood?
Hurry up and become my prince and mine alone.
The prince who loves me alone.
The story is progressing. Deeply, quietly...
In a place where Little Duck can't see it.
We'll be holding the ballet competition momentarily.
The winner will dance with Mytho-san as his partner.
I'm so jealous!
Really?!
How divine!
And the runner-up will dance eternally as my partner!
The participants must be feeling a nervousness
such as they've never felt before.
That's for sure.
After all, if they win it's Heaven, but
if they make one false step it's Hell.
Now, let us start the competition without delay.
Everyone try your best, aiming for this runner-up bouquet!
Mytho-sama is watching.
I don't want to lose.
No matter what.
The one to become his partner...
...will be me.
The mood's so tense you can hardly breathe.
I wish Ahiru could have been in the contest too.
Come to think of it, where is Ahiru?
Doesn't she care who becomes Mytho-sama's partner?
Does that mean she's completely a Fakir-sama girl now?
I sense a battle on the horizon!
Even Mytho won't be able to do anything
funny during the competition, right?
I'm just showing up out of the blue;
I wonder if Fakir is home...
Qua...
Here she is again!
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Oh, Fakir.
Fakir!
Huh?
But... But Fakir, do you know this girl?
She had a butt zura!
Did you do something to her?
I was looking for her tail and I found her butt zura!
Now look, you!
Quack!
Quack...
Her neck... Her neck...
Hey.
Her neck twisted, it twisted...
Twist, twist, twist...
Why are you hiding zura?
Shut up!
Here.
Have you calmed down a little?
Yes, thank you.
Who is that girl?
Her name is Uzura.
Karon made her out of the bits of wood
from Edel that didn't burn away.
Edel-san's?
Is that why she knew me?
No, I told her about you.
What?
I told her about you and Mytho and things.
But it looks like Edel's memories are gone.
Burned away in the flame that warmed my
body and guided you and Mytho...
Edel-san...
She saved our lives.
I'm glad I get to see her again, even if it's like this.
Now that you've told me, she does kind
of resemble Edel somehow...
Quack!
Quack...
Quack! Quack, quack, quack, quack! Quack, quack...
Ow!
What are you doing zura?
Shut up.
Anyway, didn't you have some reason for coming?
Yes. It's about Mytho.
A few days ago... he tried to take Pike's heart.
That didn't work, so now he's trying
to do the same thing to Freya-san...
The heart shard of love that Princess
Tutu gave back to him...
It was soaked in the raven's blood.
He'll find a young and beautiful heart for
my father and give it to him as a sacrifice.
Did you tell her about this?
Maybe I should. If I did that I could
make Tutu suffer, couldn't I?
Hey, what do you think happened to
Mytho? Did you find out anything?
No, nothing.
I see.
Okay. I just thought you might've found out
something, so I came to see, that's all.
Right...
Well, I'm worried about Freya-san, so I'm going to go back.
Wait.
I'll go with you. Uzura, I'm leaving you to house-sit.
Leave it to me zura!
Let's go.
Right!
"Edel"?
I don't get it zura.
This is no good.
The dancing is adequate, but their
expressions just don't work.
As it stands, there's no one who
qualifies for winner or runner-up.
Next contestant!
What novel dancing.
Above all, her expressions are great.
A victory candidate!
Next contestant!
It looks like the victory...
...has been decided.
No, you must mean the runner-up. Please
make her the runner-up!
Very soon, Father.
What a lovely fragrance. I can smell
the sweet scent from here...
I can hardly stand it.
This time I'll definitely bring you a
heart that shines blackly, Father.
And that is the time when your efforts
will be rewarded, my daughter.
Yes, Father.
Leave Mytho to me. You save Freya.
Oh, but if we just talked to Mytho...
You just need to do what I tell you.
Okay, I will.
Simply flawless!
She's the winner.
Yes.
Congratulations, Freya. My love is yours.
So she really did win...
Which means the runner-up is...
Meow!
Okay!
Unfortunately, no one qualified for runner-up this year!
And with that, I declare the competition over!
Meow, meow, meow! Meow, meow, meow, meow!
It's over.
Oh, that's right!
Hey!
Love only me, Freya. Regard all others with hatred.
Your heart is young and beautiful.
Dyed black, it's giving off a particularly strong fragrance.
You'll give it to me, won't you?
Yes.
Dance, Freya. Dance as proof of your love for me. And...
Give me your heart!
Freya-san!
Fakir!
Wait.
Dance with me, Freya-san.
Tu...
Quit showing up all the time. Hurry up and disappear.
Are you going to get in the way of Mytho and me again?
I don't want that!
Freya-san!
Yes, that's good, Freya.
Come into my arms.
Pull yourself together, Mytho!
Freya-san.
Is that love real?
Weren't flowers your hope, your prayer, your wish?
Yes, that's right, that's what I want, what I pray for.
So look. See how many there are?
Is this really what you wanted them to look like?
Listen closely... to the voices of the flowers you loved.
The voices of the flowers?
I can't hear them. I can't hear them!
Watch! Watch Tutu's dance!
I can't hear them! I can't hear the voices of the flowers!
Don't give up.
Remember.
Remember your prayer.
My prayer...
Yes, your prayer for everyone to be happy.
That was what you wished for, wasn't it, Freya-san?
Oh, I can hear them! I can hear the
voices of the flowers!
Why?!
Mytho, remember!
Why won't you love me?! WHY?!
Mytho! Remember your real self!
My real self...
There's no need to listen to a knight who should've died.
Kraehe.
The way you are now is the real Mytho.
Kraehe, did you do something to Mytho?
You're the one who made the prince like this, Tutu.
What?
Stop it!
You're the one who returned the feeling of love to the prince,
without even knowing it was dyed in the raven's blood.
You didn't tell her, Fakir?
I'm grateful to you, Tutu.
Mytho...
Hey, are you angry with me because I kept it from you?
A little.
I'm sorry.
Mytho is Mytho, right?
Even if he's got raven's blood in him, Mytho is Mytho,
so he'll go back to his old self someday, right?
Sure.
Uzura-chan's waiting for us.
You be careful of Uzura.
Huh?
Congratulations, Little Duck.
Now there's one less thing you don't know.
But would it have been better to stay ignorant?
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
I am someone who is qualified to be a true prince, someone
who loves everyone and is loved by everyone!
I told you, there is no Rue.
I just can't believe that.
Because I get this feeling you're Rue-chan.
Love only me. Regard all others with hatred.
When they say at school that Ahiru "goes well together" and
is "lovey-dovey" and "it's good," what do they mean zura?
Ahiru is? With who?
A feeling that gets across even when you don't speak it...
That's the mime for "I love you"!
"Crime and Punishment"
All you children who love stories, come gather around.