Once upon a time, there was a man who died.
The prince and the raven from the man's story
escaped from the story and fought.
Their battle ended with the prince taking out his own heart
and sealing the raven away by using its forbidden power.
The prince, who had lost his heart,
met a duck in a certain town.
Because of her love for the prince, the duck turned into a
princess and gathered together the lost shards of his heart.
The prince gradually regained his feelings, and at long
last, he was able to regain even the feeling of love.
And they lived happily ever after.
But did they really?
After all, the princess is fated to turn
into a speck of light and vanish
the moment she tells the
prince of her love for him.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
Quack...
My prince... He's so handsome.
Oh, that's right, the prince was able to
turn back to being a prince. And I...
Quack?! I... I'm just a duck now and...
I...
I'm dancing a pas de deux with the prince.
Not as Princess Tutu, but as me, a normal girl.
That's...
The mime for death!
Fakir?
Fakir!
Don't... don't die!
"The Raven"
Quack.
Oh, good, that was just a dream.
A dream of Fakir...
Fakir...
Quack!
Sheesh, what the heck am I thinking about?!
All right!
It was a dream, right? Right. Just a dream.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Really, all you guys ever think about is food.
You guys have no worries.
Hey, did you know I'm Princess Tutu?
I'm a prima donna who rescues the prince.
Well, not that it really matters.
It's been a week since then. I wonder
if his wounds have healed.
He must be okay, right?
Ahiru! Are you awake?
Hurry! Panic! Move really fast! Seriously rush!
Huh?
No way! It's that late already?!
What a great sound!
You don't have to panic THAT much.
But anyway, we're going on ahead!
Okay!
It really does feel like I'm still just Ahiru. Nothing's changed!
Rue-chan...
She'll come back, right?
Rue-chan is Rue-chan, right?
She's definitely not Princess Kraehe, right?
Oof...
Good morning, Ahiru.
What?
Good morning, Mytho.
Oh, Fakir...
Is your wound healed?
It was finally getting better, but seeing your
face has made it start throbbing with pain.
Grrrr...
She was worried because you weren't
in school for a whole week.
That's not a nice way to talk to her, Fakir.
Don't mind him, Ahiru. Will you keep being friendly with me?
You're the only friend I have that I can tell everything to.
Sure.
Tell everything to...
I'm hiding the fact that I'm Princess Tutu from Mytho.
And that I'm a duck too.
Am I unfair?
I have to tell him, don't I? But...
Ahiru?
Um, I... Well, the truth is... The truth is...
Princess Tutu.
Quack!
Oh, no!
Is flying over there.
No, maybe it's a crocodile? Which do you think, Mytho?
Quack...
There's nothing there.
And Princess Tutu and a crocodile are
totally different anyway, Fakir.
Fakir?
Oh? Right. Maybe I was just imagining things.
I really thought I saw a flying cow, but...
A cow?
It's nothing. Don't worry about it.
You're being weird, Fakir.
Huh? Where's Ahiru?
No idea.
She probably didn't like the way I
talked to her and went on ahead.
I see.
You have to be nicer to girls, Fakir.
What do you think of Princess Tutu?
Why are you asking me so suddenly?
She always disappears after she returns a piece of your heart.
Do you want to know who she really is?
Of course, I do.
Oh...
But maybe right now it's best for me not to know.
Because I'm sure she'll tell me someday.
Right now, I think it's more important to get all of my feelings back as soon as possible,
with help from Princess Tutu.
Mytho...
You'll help me too, won't you, Fakir?
Well, I am technically a knight, after all.
I was sure you'd say that, Fakir.
And then, I'll go back into the story.
Mytho...
That's what you want, then?
Yes, because I'm the prince in the story.
I see.
Shall we go? Cat-sensei will be angry at us if we're late.
Okay.
You give me a lot of trouble.
Quack! What are you talking about?! It's your fault!
You can just be late and have Cat-sensei get mad at you!
But wait...
Could he have done that on purpose so I
could hear what Mytho said?
Quack! I'm late!
Looks like Cat-sensei's pretty angry.
This is great. It's perfect timing. I hope Ahiru comes soon.
Step softly...
Ahiru-san.
Uh-oh.
That's you, isn't it?
Yes, sir! I left the dorm at
the same time as always,
but on my way here, a crocodile and a
cow were flying in the sky and...
Ahiru-san, you act like you own the place, as usual.
You're just like the students in the advanced class.
Oh, no, I don't think I'm that great.
If you keep coming to my class late, I'll have to either
drop you to the probationary class again...
Or... Or have you marry me!
Meow? Meow, meow?
Look how hard she's trying! Please forgive her!
The probationary class is one thing,
but just don't make her marry you!
Mytho...
I'm so glad I got to hear what he had to say.
I have to try even harder until I get
back all the pieces of Mytho's heart.
That's right, Ahiru!
I don't know what you're talking about,
but you have to try your best!
Now, you try your best and hardest,
and fail spectacularly, okay?
What calm days. What peaceful days!
But they won't continue forever, you know.
That's what's so great about stories.
Listen up, everyone. In ballet, the most
important thing is practice.
The second most important thing is practice.
Three, four, and five are practice too.
Why exactly do we practice, then?
We do it to master the basics.
Today, I'm going to tell you a story.
Listen carefully WITHOUT letting your eyes wander!
Yes, sir! Of course!
That's right, this was back when I was a
student in ballet school...
I happened to get the chance to observe
Meowzinsky-sensei practicing.
Wow, Meowzinsky-sensei?
Meowzinsky?
The legendary ballet dancer!
You don't know anything, do you?
It was when we ballet students were helping out
with a performance of Meowzinsky-sensei's.
I was still only a year and three
months old, a cheeky youth.
Yes, it was Meowzinsky-sensei himself,
the man renowned as a genius
for his novel choreography and his jumps
that people called miraculous.
But that day, all Meowzinsky-sensei did was just slowly,
very slowly, practice the basics over and over again.
Before I knew it, I found myself
asking him questions.
"I thought a dancer as famous as you would have
a more special practice routine," I said.
This is how he answered me...
"Someone who hasn't mastered the basics cannot
achieve advanced techniques or a noble spirit."
These shoes were given to me on
that very day by Meowzinsky-sensei.
And I swore on these shoes that I
would dedicate my life to ballet.
So basically he's saying, "Practice the basics diligently."
But I think some people will never improve no matter how
hard they practice the basics, so don't let it get to you!
These shoes have suffered a lot of wear and tear, but to me,
they are the most beautiful shoes in the world.
I wonder what's wrong with Mytho...
What?
Mytho!
So, you're back.
Fakir...
Where did you go after you disappeared
from class so suddenly?
I was looking for you.
I wonder what happened. I started to
feel sick, and after that...
You can want to go back to being the prince,
but that doesn't make it possible.
Don't try too hard.
And become like you? Is that what you're saying?
What?
That's impossible for me.
Say, Fakir, I have something to tell you.
Will you listen?
I trust you've firmly engraved
Meowzinsky-sensei's words in your minds?
Even if they diligently practice the basics, people who
aren't going to get good will never get good, so...
Wait, how did that go again?
Anyway, be on time for class tomorrow.
Yes, sir!
But I don't think I can do it.
Well, no need to let it get to you too much.
That's right! Being late is an essential part of your charm!
Hey, what happened?
What was that?
What was that scream just now?
Cat-sensei?
An incident? Has there been an incident?
Oh, that Ahiru doesn't even disguise her curiosity!
It's your fault.
No way!
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
Qua...
Where are you going, Ahiru?
Cat-sensei!
Oh dear, dear, dear, dear! Is it Ahiru's
fault? It's Ahiru's fault, isn't it?
Meowzinsky's shoes...
How awful.
Did Cat-sensei do that himself?
Why can't I get Mytho out of my mind? Why?
Ahiru! Where are you going?!
How did it go? Did you find Mytho?
Didn't find him.
Not anywhere.
Nowhere.
Not a trace!
I see...
Something going on with him lately?
With Fakir.
He's acting strange.
Yeah, strange!
I mean, in the library!
He's been holed up in there forever!
Research, maybe?
Does seem like he's researching.
That's so not-Fakir.
The library?
Whoops!
Forget we said anything!
Don't tell anyone we told you!
It's not like we're into being nosy.
Even though we are.
What's Fakir doing in the library?
No, right now, finding Mytho comes first.
Is he there?
I can't see.
Okay, then!
What?
Is that true?
I wonder if there's a huge commotion right about now.
Why did you do that?
The shoes filled with beautiful memories and dreams...
Is it funny? It's funny, isn't it, Fakir?
Ah, my daughter.
How are you feeling, Father?
Not bad. But not good, either.
Poor Father. But I have good news.
Oh?
The raven's blood you gave me...
It looks like it's begun to exercise its power.
I see, my blood that you soaked the
prince's feeling of love with...
Yes. I'm so glad I did just like you told me to, Father.
Of course you are.
The only thing I ever wish for is my
dear daughter's happiness.
The prince will keep changing, won't he?
Into a prince who loves crows.
And he will marry you and become my son.
Hey, Mytho! Is something happening inside you?
What if something is?
Will you intend to pierce my heart with the sword again?
But that sword is gone now, isn't it? Because you broke it.
I can't see very well.
It's not scary, it's not scary...
Oof.
Are you angry?
Even though I've finally regained my emotions?
Your heart isn't whole yet.
That's right. I have to hurry and get the whole thing back...
And then...
maybe I'll try offering it to a crow.
Who are you?
I'm...
That was scary.
What's wrong, Mytho?!
Help me, Fakir!
My heart is...
Mytho!
A crow... It can't be!
Tutu...
Mytho!
Pull yourself together.
Mytho...
Who am I? Fakir, I'll tell you right now. Just you.
Watch closely.
You...
Mytho!
Mytho, no!
Tutu.
Thank goodness.
Bravo! At last, the second act has begun!
Oh, dear. The knight, the prince,
and the two princesses...
It seems their roles will change just a bit.
Now, tell me a story. I'm looking
forward to it, Princess Tutu.
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
Didn't Mytho fall in love with Pike?
It's none of your business if Mytho-sama and I are dating.
Really, Ahiru? Is that really okay?
Who are you? Why are you inside me?!
So it was you? What did you do to Mytho?!
Show your true colors, Kraehe.
The prince is going to change. He'll love only me, and he'll find
a young and beautiful heart for my father and offer it to him.
You'll give me your beautiful heart, won't you?
"Coppelia"
All you children who love stories, come gather around.