Long ago, there was a warrior.
In order to protect his friend, the
warrior took his friend's life.
Long ago, there was a sword.
This sword had continued to fight for the sake of peace.
It realized that in order to protect the peace, it had no
choice but to kill the one who wielded it.
Thus it took its master's life.
The warrior and the sword had no choice but to do as they
did, but was that really what they ought to have done?
Uncertain of the answer even now,
they wander aimlessly.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
Where are you, Mytho?
There's nowhere else left to look...
Her again.
"The Warrior's Fountain"
Persistent girl.
Fakir.
You're awake.
Where's Tutu?
Don't worry, Tutu isn't around anymore.
What happened?
Tutu...helped me and...
tried to restore a piece of my heart.
Mytho, you...
Then, Kraehe...
Kraehe?
Yes, Kraehe, dressed like a black bird
took my heart shard and...
Tell me, Fakir, don't I...
Don't I need to regain my heart?
Forget about it.
But...
Listen to me. I brought you back here, because I
thought it would be safer with people around.
Put your worries to rest and sleep.
What... is this?
Why?
Who's there?!
Why did you bring me with you?
You're Mytho's...
Why? What do you mean that I brought you with me?
You want to know a lot of things, don't you?
I understand how you feel, because
I'm the desire for knowledge.
Desire for knowledge?
You don't remember how you brought me here?
I did? You're lying.
Why do you don black feathers?
No!
Do you have a special power dwelling within you?
Come on, tell me, which is the real you?
Stop...
Who are you really?
Stop!
I saw you!
What?
I most certainly saw you!
Confessing your love at the window?! Ahiru, you're so bold!
It was like a reverse Romeo and Juliet!
Though, it's horribly different since it's one-sided.
That's not what I was doing. Mytho's disappeared and...
Right! I forgot about that!
He hasn't been to class in a long time now, has he?
That's why you couldn't contain yourself
and resolved to confess, right?
That's not it.
Take this chance to attack, attack, attack all the way!
Um... No...
Though, you have no hope, since Mytho-sama has Rue-chan.
I'm telling you, that's not it!
Go for it and take your losses!
Lose and be crushed!
I was just...
He might show up to school today.
What? You think so?
You're hopeful, aren't you? You're so cute!
I wonder if Mytho will come?
If he does, you have to say it properly and clearly, okay?
Huh? Say what?
Of course, what else?!
What?
That you love him!
What?! I can't say that to him! Because...
Because if I said that, I'd disappear...
You coward!
Oh? Where are you going?
It's your fault.
No way!
Ahiru.
What are you doing?
Mytho...
You're okay...
I'm so glad!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I looked all over town, but I couldn't find you, so
I was wondering what had happened to you.
But I was so relieved to see you were okay and...
But I'm really glad you're okay.
You were looking for me?
Yeah. Oh!
That's right, he doesn't know that I'm Tutu, so...
Tutu...
Huh? Uh...
Do you know about Tutu?
Uh, um, well...
What are you doing?
Huh?
Fakir...
Mytho, you go ahead. I'll be right there.
Okay.
You.
Uh, yes.
You're such an eyesore.
Listen carefully. Never come near Mytho again.
If you go near him again, I'll make sure you pay for it.
Huh? So what happened in the end? Did she fail?
She got turned down in a somewhat
subdued manner, didn't she?
We'll just have to get her to do a revenge match.
Last night...
I saw Tutu return a piece of Mytho's heart to him.
Mytho also wished for its return...
Then, I saw that, and after that...
What in the world...
Who am I?
I ended up skipping the morning classes...
The look in Fakir's eyes that time was scary.
Mytho shouldn't be with someone like that.
But what should I do?
Hello, Edel-san.
Hello.
You see, Edel-san, I want to save Mytho from Fakir.
But Fakir told me not to go near him.
So... or rather... but, but um...
The name of this gem is "Courage."
It is a single gem made of two.
A single gem made of two...
Meaning that I should work together with someone?
But with whom?
I can't put Rue-chan in danger.
Restore my heart to me, Tutu.
If... If I let Mytho know that I'm Tutu...
Then, together, we might be able to stand up... to Fakir.
Fakir?
What is he to you, Ahiru?
Huh? What is he?
He's not really anything to me.
But he's a dangerous person to Mytho.
Oh...
What?
Edel-san?
Qua... Quack, quack, quack, quack.
All right!
This is the one!
No doubt about it! It's Mytho's scent!
Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack!
Someone's coming!
An iguana?!
That was close...
Qua...
Huh?
What? What?!
There.
You're so stupid.
There's no way you're going to find food in there.
I guess you wouldn't have wandered in if you knew.
Qua... Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack.
Quack, quack, quack. Quack. Quack...
You sure eat a lot.
Hurry on home. Don't come around anymore.
Somehow, it was like he wasn't the usual Fakir.
If you go near him again, I'll make sure you pay for it.
No, no! Of course, he's definitely a bad guy!
I'm not going to be fooled just because the bread was tasty!
He probably acted like that only because I was just a duck...
A duck...
If I'm going to tell Mytho everything, I better tell him
that I'm just a duck too, shouldn't I?
Quack...
What's that?
Ahiru says she has something important to tell me.
I will be waiting in the school's backyard at
5 o'clock this evening, Ahiru.
Did the girl not hear what I said to her?
You can throw it away. There's no need for you to go.
No.
What?
I'm going, Fakir.
You're kidding, right?
I'm serious.
What would be the point in seeing her?
She might know something about Tutu.
Her?
Yeah.
You idiot, there's no way she would.
But...
Don't get involved with Tutu.
Her existence will only bring you
unhappiness. Don't be fooled.
And right now, there's that Kraehe coming after you too.
I don't care.
If I tell you no, it's no! Got it?!
No.
Enough's enough!
I'm sorry.
I'm going.
So, I can no longer stop Mytho with words.
Oh-ho...
That is the prince's own sword, which
once shattered his heart.
Now, what do you plan to do with it?
This sword shattered the prince's heart
and destroyed the evil raven.
Now, grant it power once more.
Mytho...
Oh, er... Oh, er, um...
Huh?
Uh...
Ahiru?
Um, I... uh, actually... actually...
Tu...
Tutu...
What? No way! You knew...
You know about Tutu, don't you, Ahiru?
Oh, you scared me there.
Fakir told me that I shouldn't come here, but...
What? You talked to Fakir about this?
Yes.
Right, everything I tell Mytho goes straight to Fakir too.
Ahiru.
Yes?
I want to see Tutu.
What?
When I think of Tutu, I become filled
with the desire to see her.
Mytho...
I want to be with Tutu always.
What?!
My prince, you belong to me.
Kraehe!
That's right, that's the spirit.
The value of a treasure is most clearly
revealed when it is fought over.
Now, who will the prince go to, Princess Tutu?
Your hair, your cheeks, and even your heart all belong to me.
Please stop, Kraehe.
Princess Tutu.
Please return the piece of his heart that you took.
Please stop making the prince suffer.
Tutu...
Don't make me laugh.
Look, my prince, there is the one
making you suffer. Princess Tutu.
What?
No... She's wrong!
My poor prince.
The one you need is me.
I will always be with you.
Kraehe...
You are like a doll, but I will love you.
I will make you forget about Tutu.
We shall just give this heart thing to the crows.
No!
Who are you?
That is the prince's sword!
What?
So, you're Kraehe.
Do not address me so familiarly, you filth!
Are you a manifestation of the raven?!
Who am I?
The shard!
It's no use.
Princess Tutu.
Who...
Fakir!
I'm sorry you had to wait so long, Mytho.
It'll be all right now. You won't have to suffer.
What are you going to do?
Sit down.
I'll shatter your heart for you once again.
What?!
It's no use now, Princess Tutu!
Mytho!
YOU shattered Mytho's heart?
Why did you do such a terrible thing?
This would never have happened if you hadn't shown up.
I...
Tutu...
Stop it, Fakir!
Prince!
Is it my fault?
If I pierce my heart with this sword,
will that satisfy you, Fakir?
That's right. Then, you'll return to your old self.
All right.
What?
No!
Don't do it!
Mytho!
You'd rather be without a heart?!
Don't listen to her! Quickly, just pierce your heart!
Mytho, please!
Now, do it!
No!
Do it!
The other day, you smiled just a little, remember?
That time, I thought that must be the real you.
I think if your heart is full, you'll show even more of yourself!
Because that's the real you!
I'm sorry.
I can't save you from the suffering, because all
I can do is restore your heart to you.
Mytho...
I see. So that is the answer you've chosen.
Tutu, restore my heart shard.
Princess Tutu.
I want to know.
What?
I want to know what you think of me.
I... I...
Wait.
Tutu...
Why, Tutu?
I'm a duck.
I'm really only a bird.
But what the prince sees is Princess
Tutu in her beautiful dress.
It's not me.
Was what the sword pierced the prince's heart?
Or someone's feelings?
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
I am Rue.
I am not anyone else.
That's who I've always been.
Rue, maybe I'm actually...
Once again, Princess Tutu will change Mytho.
Kraehe, why are you in such pain?
Be gone, you ugly crow!
That's right, I am a crow.
And I am the TRUE prima donna, Princess Kraehe.
All you children who love stories, come gather around.
"The Black Shoes"