Once upon a time, there was a sad love
that would never be requited.
But that alone does not give birth to a story.
The man with the task of spinning this tale
of love was no longer of this world.
The story lives on with the
love forever sorrowful.
Having lost its storyteller, the story is now
wandering in search of its conclusion.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
''Giselle''
She really is impressive!
Truly a prodigy!
Will a day come when I can dance like that too?
So, you've finally gotten your head screwed on straight?
What?
What a wildly fantastical dream!
That's the spirit, Ahiru!
Recklessness is one of your good points!
Better to dream big!
That way, your failures will be bigger too!
There's nothing you can't do if you work hard at it!
For normal people, that is!
Well... For now, you have to get
out of the probationary class.
That's right...
When I'm Princess Tutu, I can dance any dance I want to.
But is that me?
Or someone else?
I'm just a girl in the probationary class.
Or rather, when you get down to it, I'm just a duck.
Maybe there's no point in me practicing.
Watch out!
Who are you?
Are you calling to me?
Fakir...
What's with that look on your face?
What? What look on my face?
What were you thinking about?
What?
Just now. What were you thinking about?
Someone is...
Someone is calling to me.
I don't know who it is, but I feel like I can
understand what that person is feeling.
The heart aches deep down, a desire to see
someone, to see them and talk to them...
Feelings like that... I have them too.
I was wondering if this is what it feels to be lonely.
What it feels to be lonely?
Mytho is regaining his heart.
Look at it! This face! I hate it! This face! Stupid emotions!
This repulsive face that's regained the feeling of loneliness!
Do you find it fun recalling such emotions?
Does it feel good, Mytho?
No...
Exactly! You have no need of a heart! You have no need!
If you were to regain such a thing...
If I were to?
Anyway, don't be so foolish as to want a heart! Got it?!
Yes.
I can't hear you!
I understand, Fakir. I'll do as you say.
Good, that's the way it should be.
Ahiru-san, as punishment for
disturbing the advanced class,
you will practice the développé by
yourself. Am I understood?
Yes, sir.
If you practice earnestly, I'll let you
back in the beginner class.
Oh, yes, sir!
If you don't practice properly, I will have you marry me!
Oh, I'm a bird, on probation, and to top
it off, I'm being kept after school.
I think I'll never be like Rue-chan. Oh...
It's Mytho.
Princess Tutu?
That's just a story.
The princess is fated never to be with her prince.
The moment she confesses her love, she turns
into a speck of light and vanishes.
That's just what happens in the story.
The story isn't real.
Though, it's true that Mytho is a prince
from inside a story...
But it doesn't matter!
Whether it's a story or it's real, I just
want to restore Mytho's heart!
That's right, I'm not thinking about being with him
or confessing to him or anything!
I'm not thinking about any of that!
I don't really understand.
It's okay. It's okay for you to be a
dummy, Mytho. Now and forever.
Mytho, you love me.
I love you.
That's right, that's all you need to know.
You don't need to understand anything.
And you don't need a heart, either.
What is it?
The feeling of wanting to see someone and talk to them...
It doesn't go away even when I see you, Rue.
Say, could this be the feeling of loneliness?
I don't know. The emotions that I'm feeling...
Rue!
Would you please stop making him recall stupid things?
Mytho, go back to your room.
Okay.
You better not be the one making
Mytho remember weird things.
Oh, please.
Then who else are you saying could have done it?
Maybe it's Princess Tutu from the fairy tale?
Maybe she's appeared in reality and...
That's absurd!
Try to stay away from Mytho from now on.
Don't keep ordering me around like that!
Oh? The piano's playing?
Where's Ahiru?
Ahiru...
Oh? What are you two doing here?
That's our line.
That's right, we came thinking you would be REALLY
depressed because you have to stay behind by yourself.
What are you looking so chipper for?
Thanks, but I'm really having fun right now.
Because with dancing, the more you
practice, the more it becomes fun!
Ahiru!
Don't force yourself! You can act sad when you're sad and
you can act like you're in pain when you're suffering!
Oh, you were suffering after all, weren't you?
It's your fault.
No way!
Are you okay?
Yeah... I'm... o...kay...
Say, why don't we keep her company too?
Hey, good idea.
What? Thank you!
It's all right. After all, this is for you.
Okay, let's all drop down to the
probationary class with Ahiru!
You still have a long way to go, Ahiru.
Ahiru-san!
Cat-sensei.
I have unfortunate news for you.
Meow!
Unfortunate news?
Ahiru-san, you have worked too hard.
Therefore, unfortunately,
I will have to hold off on having you marry me!
Oh, I see...
Also, I will permit you to return to the beginner class.
What?
Oh, thank you so much!
You did it! I'm so happy for you!
Thanks!
The wind's picking up...
Oh, Mytho...
What is it that you want me to do?
Who are you talking to?
What?
Mytho?
Huh? Where are you?!
Mytho?!
He's gone.
Mytho!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Huh? He's not over here, either.
I thought I heard you calling for Mytho?
Oh, yeah, I was.
Did you need something?
No, not need, but...
He just came out this way.
What? No one came out.
What? But I was sure Mytho...
It can't be, because I didn't see anyone.
Then, did he go that way?
It was you, wasn't it?
Huh? What?
You cried out suddenly when I was
dancing and interrupted me.
Oh, that was...
You don't seem to have the slightest comprehension as
to just how much focus is necessary when dancing.
Oh, if it's about that, I apologize!
But more importantly, right now, Mytho seemed weird,
or rather, strange... actually, that's the same, isn't it?
Anyway, I have to find him!
See you!
Wait! We aren't done talking yet!
Wait just a minute!
Mytho!
Stay away from Rue!
Mytho?
It's strange! It's definitely strange!
After talking to someone invisible, it was as if
time had skipped forward and Mytho...
I wonder which way he went?
Rue-chan.
Your name's... Ahiru... wasn't it?
You're a... pretty fast... runner.
Yes... I... am.
Don't imitate me! I'm... just... out of... breath!
I'm... sorr...
Um...
What is it?
Since there are two of us here, I was thinking
maybe it'd be faster to split up and search.
That's true. You're exactly right.
It's strange for me to be walking with you to begin with.
Strange... Yeah, she's right.
Oh, then I'll go look over here.
We can decide on a time or something
and meet up somewhere...
I've changed my mind.
What? Why?
It's more reliable if there are two pairs of eyes searching.
Oh, really?
So...
What is it now?
Have you been friends with Mytho for a long time?
You keep calling him Mytho, but don't you
think that's awfully forward of you?
But Mytho said that I could call him that.
And another thing.
We're not even friends or anything,
so don't call me Rue-chan.
Then, what should I call you?
Rue-sama.
Rue...sama.
Why did you take so long to say it?!
Because it's just weird. I'll call you Rue-chan.
It's cuter that way.
Cuter?
Besides, we've been walking together and talking
all this time, so we're already friends.
So, it's Rue-chan!
There's no sign of Mytho, is there, Rue-chan?
Oh...
What's that?
They're all... crying?
It's a funeral, so it's only natural.
Oh, Mytho!
Mytho!
What?
What is this?!
A dead end?
What is it now?
Edel-san!
Good evening, Ahiru. Good evening, Rue.
Why do you know my...
Edel-san knows everything. Even that I'm a bird...
Even what?
Anyway, I'm saying she's not suspicious.
She is too suspicious!
Edel-san, we're looking for Mytho.
And just now, something really weird happened.
He disappeared beyond that dead end
along with a funeral procession.
A story within a story.
What? A story?
There was once a very beautiful maiden
with a very beautiful heart.
Maidens all fall in love.
Hey! Your story has nothing to do with this!
But the man she fell in love with was a noble, unlike her.
It was a love never to be requited.
Did you hear me?!
Wait, Rue-chan!
So, what happened to that woman?
She took her own life.
If her love would not be requited in this world, she
would be reborn and see her love fulfilled then.
However, her fiancé never appeared and the maiden took
another man to the world of the dead in his stead.
This is the maiden's sad story within the story.
In this town, there was a maiden who met the same fate.
Just as in the story, she fell in love, and
just as in the story, she lost hope,
and just as in the story, she took
her own life, and then...
Is the story going to become real?
The story will become real.
In this town, where reality and stories intermingle...
Just as in the story, Mytho will be
taken in that man's stead...
I won't let that happen!
It's starting.
What?
The dead end!
A mansion?!
The maiden's soul has settled in the courtyard of
that mansion and has been waiting all this time.
Let's go, Rue-chan!
Yes!
Mytho!
And you're saying I'm that person?
If you say so, then maybe I am.
Mytho, who are you talking to?!
What is that?
That's the dead girl?
The pendant...
So, it was you who was calling to me.
The rosemary from Giselle?!
You mustn't accept it!
Rue-chan?!
You'll be taken away to the world of the dead!
Come over here!
Rue-chan...
I don't have the stamina to dance Giselle to the end.
If I had only done more basic training...
Rue-chan!
No!
Well, well, at this rate, the prince
will enter an eternal slumber.
Are you okay with that, Princess Tutu?
My prince, you must not accept that!
Why do you interfere? Who are you?
I am Princess Tutu.
I am fated never to be with the one I love, just like you.
Dance with me.
Amazing, she's continuing to dance
on par with the other girl.
If you share the same fate as I, then why
is your dancing not laden with sorrow?
That's because there are many other emotions
in my heart that won't give in to the sorrow.
Even if you take Mytho with you, it
won't dispel your sorrow, will it?
Because that sorrow is not how you truly feel.
I cannot know how much you have suffered, but
I do know that you have grieved enough.
So you can sleep in peace now.
Because you don't have to grieve anymore.
This is the heart shard called sorrow.
This makes people suffer.
But this is also an important emotion people have.
Princess Tutu...
The emotions returning to the prince are loneliness,
sorrow, all feelings people have no desire for.
Princess Tutu, is that going to bring
happiness to the prince?
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
Mytho... He's a prince.
Is this the real you, Mytho?
Ahiru, are you going to the Fire Festival too?
I was a fool for believing what that Ahiru said.
When you were wandering, having lost your memories,
I'm the one who gave you the name of Mytho!
I only want to keep shining for someone.
I don't want anything else.
And yet, somewhere along the way,
I had become forgotten.
It's sad that they no longer need you, but
it's something that can't be helped.
All you children who love stories, come gather around.
''On the Night of the Fire FestivaI''