Once upon a time, there was a man who died.
The story was interrupted and along with his heart,
the prince lost his kindness towards people
and even his memories of having fought bravely.
And scattered throughout the town,
the shards of the prince's heart
sought places to settle
and found their way into the people's
hearts who had voids in them.
Among those who were possessed by the shards
were some who ended up making their own tales go awry.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
I've really and truly become Princess Tutu.
''The Princess's Vow''
Tuck your chin in!
What?
This is no laughing matter!
If you can't even do that, you'll never
get out of the probationary class!
Stop it!
Don't be so unreasonable!
Ahiru isn't capable of doing two
things at the same time!
She just has to walk with a book on her head!
Even if it's something so easy, if she
can't do it, she simply can't!
Then she'll never be able to become a prima ballerina!
No, she won't! There's no way Ahiru could
possibly become one!
Don't say any more terrible things!
Look at how hurt she is!
Smile! Smile for me!
It's your fault.
No way!
But after getting dropped to the probationary class, isn't
Ahiru acting weird, being all goofy smiley since morning?
She's always been weird.
I'm talking more than usual!
Now that you mention it...
What?
Did something happen, I wonder?
No, not really.
Liar!
Not that anything happened, but...
So something DID happen!
Uh, well...
Spit it out.
Uh, um, oh, yeah... a dream, it's about a dream I had.
There's this really strong and handsome prince,
but this prince is fighting against an evil raven.
He can seal the raven away if
he shatters his own heart,
but when he loses his heart, he
also loses his emotions.
And this prince's eyes always look so
lonely, and for this prince, I...
Is that all?
What?
I've heard a story like that before.
Story?
That's straight out of ''The Prince and the Raven''.
What?
Here, it's this book, right?
The prince was a hero, who fought
against the demonic raven.
That was when they were inside
the story that I wrote.
Um, what's the name of the person
who wrote this story?
What? It's Drosselmeyer. That's
common knowledge.
I had no idea.
This is no time to be reading books like
this and grinning like a fool!
Two books would be impossible for you, Ahiru.
Make sure you can do it by the end of the day.
Good luck. You've got nothing to lose.
Don't you dare slack off!
Oh, so like, does Drosselmeyer-san
live in this town?
Huh?
He died ages ago.
What?
The story ends part way through too.
Right, right. I think he died while writing the book, didn't he?
What?!
Yes, he came out of the story
and lost his heart in order
to seal away the raven.
That means the person who was writing the story
died and the characters in the story came out?
Something that strange...
But I guess it isn't as strange as a
duck turning into a human...
So, Mytho-senpai is a prince out of a story.
That's why he's so handsome.
It's Rue-chan.
I wonder if Rue-chan knows about this?
Oh, Mytho-senpai!
So he's going on a picnic with Rue-chan.
Lucky her.
But in the end, I'm just a duck...
Maybe I'll practice or something.
Hey!
Have you seen Mytho around?
Is something the matter with Mytho-senpai?
He went out without telling me.
Who cares about that? He's Rue-chan's boyfriend after all.
What?!
So he's with Rue?!
What?
Where did they go?!
Answer me!
I don't know.
You're lying!
I'm telling the truth!
I wonder if he knows about Mytho-senpai?
Um, do you know the story ''The Prince and the Raven''?
What about it?
Well, it's nothing really...
It's just a childish tale.
Hah, acting so high and mighty!
And he doesn't even have a clue!
Mytho-senpai is a prince from inside a story,
so I'm the only one who knows about it.
I'm going to protect my prince...
I'm not playing hooky. I'm just taking a break.
I'm allowed to do that. Besides, if I
see Mytho-senpai and Rue-chan,
I can tell them that nasty guy
was looking for them.
Is it okay for me to tell them?
Truth is a shy little thing.
If you approach it, it will hide.
Edel-san?
Truth is a lonesome little thing.
If you move away from it, it will give chase.
Are you having doubts about something?
Uh, yes.
Well, you see, there's this person and there's another
person who's good friends with that person.
But that person also has another good friend.
But that person's friends aren't friends with one another...
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Wind makes flames burn and the treetops sway.
But flames burn trees to the ground.
So, wind and flames and trees, huh?
Does that mean they can never get along?
Who's to say?
But if the wind's too strong, it would put out
the fire and topple the trees too, so...
I don't get it.
But thank you, Edel-san.
If they're going on a picnic, maybe
they'll be at the park over here.
What?
Whoa, there they are!
Say.
What?
Tell me that you love me.
Qua...
What should I do?! Should I go back?!
I should go back, shouldn't l?!
I love you, Rue.
Really?
I really love you.
I'm thirsty.
What?!
I want some water. Get it for me?
Okay.
Whoa, he's coming this way!
What'll I do?! He'll see me!
Huh?
Man, they really are perfect for each other.
But they didn't look like they were having much fun.
If he were to say something like that to me...
Like that...
Ahiru...
I love you.
I really love you.
Pardon...
My-My-Mytho-senpai!
Hello! Um, since the weather's so nice today, it's bright
during the day, but I'm sure it'll be dark at night...
Stupid me, what am I doing stating the obvious?!
I have to say something funny!
Oh! I love taking walks! And you love Rue-chan, right?!
Oh, what the heck am I saying?!
Probably.
Huh? Probably?
I don't understand what the feeling of love is, but Rue and
Fakir are the only ones who'll tell me what to do, so...
You don't understand love...
Mytho-senpai...
Just Mytho is fine.
Oh, Mytho-senpai! I mean, Mytho! Your hand!
Oh...
Doesn't it hurt?!
Not really.
Why are you making that weird face?
Is it a weird face?
But you're hurt!
Fakir and Rue don't say things like that.
It's the prince's eyes. The poor prince who lost his heart.
That's why he doesn't know his own feelings,
not even about loving or hurting.
I'll do my best!
On what?
Oh, um, that is...
Nothing in particular, but rather, I want to work
super hard on all sorts of things and...
Oh, yeah! That injury!
It'll get worse if you don't wash it properly.
Thank goodness, it's not that serious.
Oh! The water that you went and got!
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry! I'll...I'll um, go get more!
Having said that, river water probably wouldn't cut it.
Rue-chan should have good tasting water, after all.
The water I could get from a house
around here wouldn't work, right?
Where should I get it from?
Oh? I'm not in town...
Did I walk too far?
My-Mytho!
Um, I'll go get the water, so just wait for me!
Or rather, where can I get water?
Oh...
There.
Oh, that's a restaurant!
Water from a restaurant would be perfect, wouldn't it?!
I don't know.
Open?
Ebine...
I wonder if that's the restaurant's name?
Excuse me...
Yes?
Uh, um, this is a restaurant, right?
Yes, it is! Yes, it is!
One moment, please!
Thank you for waiting!
Welcome! I am the owner and chef, Ebine!
Um...
How did you find out about this place?
Did you hear it from a friend?
No...
Then did you go out of your way to find it?
Oh, no...
Don't tell me it was by pure chance?
Uh, yes.
That is splendid! I've never had a customer like that before!
Now, please, sit down!
Uh, um, I'm not a customer.
Not a customer?
I came for some water...
Just... water?
Um, well... I'm sorry!
You're hungry, aren't you?!
Then, please have a meal while you're here!
What?! But I don't have any money...
It's okay, that doesn't matter.
What?
Oh, yes, I had some shrimp paté.
The pendant just glowed.
But does that mean she has one of the shards?
Where did Mytho go?
I don't know.
Don't take Mytho out without letting me know.
Mytho doesn't belong to you, now does he?
He doesn't belong to you, either.
Mytho mentioned ''feeling''.
What did you say?
Where is Mytho?
He went to get some water and hasn't come back yet.
By himself?
Who else would he be going with?
This isn't like you at all. What are you so frantic about?
Wait a minute!
You're going to look for Mytho, aren't you? I'm coming too.
Now, please help yourselves!
Um, but we...
You're right, this is far from enough, isn't it?
Oh, that's not what I meant.
I have to check to see if she has a heart shard or not.
It's cold.
So is this! And this! And this!
Why are they all cold? And there's not
much taste to them either.
And they LOOK so good.
Here's rainbow trout meunière!
This one looks warm!
Cold!
And now, rabbit cream stew!
Next up is piping hot dumpling salad!
Furthermore, grilled pork shanks!
They're all cold! Why?!
Um, don't you think something's strange here?
Is it?
Like why are all the dishes cold?
Or like why is she feeding us for free?
Who knows?
I see, Mytho doesn't even understand how
it feels when something's strange.
Here's dessert!
That concludes Course A!
Next up is Course B!
What?!
Um, hey, I'm going to the restroom for a bit.
Go ahead.
Now, then, I better hurry up and check!
Yes, that's right.
Our first customers in a long time. They're eating so much.
But I have to have them eat even more.
I wonder which will taste better compared to you?
Which will taste better?
A... gra...ve...
What should I do? At this rate...
I... I... I don't care what happens to me, but Mytho...
I have to at least protect Mytho!
I know a story that goes like this.
A brother and sister wandering in the forest
come across a gingerbread house.
Then, a kind old woman appears and
serves them some food,
but she was really planning to fatten up the brother
and sister, and to eat them afterwards!
Really.
It's no good! Mytho doesn't understand that he's in danger!
We have to get out of here while we...
Owow...
Recipes? And a photograph?
What are these?
What are you doing?
Oh!
Uh, uh, uh, um, I was
thinking of going soon.
No, you can't!
The food hasn't been eaten yet!
Who hasn't eaten what?!
More must be eaten! More!
So, who hasn't eaten what?!
I won't let you go back until the food's been eaten!
I'm already full!
I see.
Then how about you?
He's already...
You'll still eat more, won't you?
Probably.
Open this door! Please open this door!
If you're not going to eat, you can go home!
Oh, she locked it!
Mytho...
Come now, it's going awry. The story's going awry.
Heart shards make their way into the void in people's hearts
and make their stories go awry.
It appears a heart that is too pure is a heavy burden.
Now, how will you handle this story, Princess Tutu?
The little nuisance is gone now.
You have to keep eating more and...
What could that be?
Who's there?
Mealtime is over.
Rest a while, my prince.
Give back my customer!
My customer!
Dance with me, Ebine-san.
Dancing isn't for me... my job is to cook!
And to have my customers eat my cooking!
What are you going to do by having him keep eating?
I'm going to have him eat more and more!
Why?
Why? I just want him to eat lots and lots.
I want my precious customer to eat.
Because having your fill of delicious food is happiness!
I knew I'd find you.
This person's heart isn't where you belong.
Let's go back.
No! I won't let him go anywhere!
Ebine-san!
Stay away!
What feeling is that shard?
I just want him to enjoy my cooking!
That's what a restaurant is for!
Then why is your cooking so cold?
Why do you force him to eat it?
Why do you imprison him?
I want to know what it is that you're feeling.
Feeling...
Dance with me, Ebine-san.
Yes, back then...
I felt just a little uncertainty, but the rest of it was all
bliss and I could have burst with happiness.
A nice atmosphere. I had happy
conversations. Delicious food.
What a wonderful restaurant. A wonderful couple.
I would cook and ask, ''I wonder which
will taste better compared to you?''
He would always tease me and say, ''Yours
still has a long way to go.''
But that was happiness for me.
Oh...
I wonder which will taste better compared to you?
That's what those words meant.
But...
There's no one left to tease me when I ask about it.
I have the recipes that he wrote down, but the
person who cooked them is no longer here.
I was so lonely.
So, I wanted to at least have my
customers stay as long as possible.
I see.
You're the feeling of loneliness, aren't you?
The feeling of loneliness.
Yes, but this isn't where you belong.
I'm sorry. I'm going.
Don't go! I'll be all alone again!
Don't worry. You're not alone, Ebine-san.
Because you have the recipes left
to you by the one you loved.
Lots of dishes are waiting, wanting to be made.
A gift left to you by the one you love.
The power to turn loneliness into strength.
My Dear!
I feel like I can cook warm dishes again.
Warm, just like your heart.
I'll make this into a wonderful restaurant again.
Please help me, my Dear.
My prince, your feelings belong within you.
Your life belongs within your heart.
Thank you, Princess Tutu.
Mytho...
All right!
Mytho, what are you doing in this place?
Hey!
Nothing...
What happened?
Princess Tutu...
Don't tell me he knows it's me?!
She touched me.
Princess Tutu?
Ridiculous. That's just a story.
What?
Tutu is... part of the story too?
But I'm a duck...
She's blessed with beauty, cleverness, and strength,but the
thing is, the princess is fated never to be with her prince.
The moment she confesses her love, she
turns into a speck of light and vanishes.
Quack!
What's part of the story? And what's real?
Tutu is me and I'm a duck...
But Tutu is... Tutu is...
That's right, Princess Tutu is a tragic princess.
Stories aren't always guaranteed a happily ever after.
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
All I want to do is to restore Mytho's heart.
I'm not thinking about being with him or
confessing to him or anything!
I don't understand what this emotion is that I'm feeling.
You better not be the one making
Mytho remember weird things.
Maybe it's Princess Tutu from the fairy tale?
The story will become real.
In this town, where reality and stories intermingle...
I am Princess Tutu.
I am fated never to be with the one I love, just like you.
All you children who love stories,
come gather around.
''Giselle''