Once upon a time, there was a maiden.
The maiden wore tattered clothes and was
called Cinderella,
but she became a beautiful princess by
magic and danced with the prince.
Then at the stroke of midnight, the maiden left a glass slipper
behind and returned to being Cinderella once again.
The prince took the trouble to find this
maiden and took her as his wife, but...
Did the prince really love that maiden?
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
I remember now. I am a crow.
And I am the TRUE prima ballerina, Princess Kraehe.
I can take whatever I want, by force if need be!
Princess Tutu...
You have no intention of ceasing to restore his heart?
No, because that is what the prince wishes.
Do you mean to shatter the prince's heart again?
What if I do?
I won't allow you to do that.
Then will you kill me?
Could you kill me?
That's not...
Stop!
Why won't you defeat the crow
with her right before you?!
You can't protect Mytho only by restoring his heart!
Fakir!
But Kraehe was in pain...
Then that was your chance!
I could do it! If it came down to it, I could even kill you!
Tutu, run!
Why do you get in the way of regaining my heart?
Get in your way?
I want to get my heart back.
No matter what fate awaits me, I...
Fakir, are you trembling?
Why?
"Cinderella"
This is...
Why?
When in the world did I go back to being a duck?
I know!
Why?! Why aren't I turning back into a girl?!
The pendant...
This is good, Little Duck.
There's nothing more boring than a perfect heroine after all.
When the spell is broken, Ahiru is just a duck.
Now, show us well and good what the duck
will do, what the duck is capable of.
Quack...
What'll I do?
Without the pendant, I can't become a girl or Tutu.
Where could it have gone?
My pendant...
Just you try and come for it, Princess Tutu...
Fakir, are you trembling?
That's absurd.
Where are you, Princess Tutu?
Hey...
Oh! I must have fallen asleep!
You're that duck from the other day, aren't you?
The pendant!
What is it? Have you taken a liking to this?
I envy your innocence.
He's got it on.
Maybe Princess Tutu is among these girls.
Cat-sensei, I smell a tasty duck.
Hush, Crocodelia-san.
Maybe I'm thinking too hard.
Mytho's so beautiful.
He was always beautiful, but now, he's even more...
Is that because he's regained some emotions?
Isn't the Mytho-sama beautiful?
I bet Ahiru will be disappointed she missed it.
I wonder if Ahiru is suffering badly from the rejection?
I'd love it if she is.
I hope she'll be up to coming back to class soon.
Right, right, before she fully recovers.
Well, despite how she looks, she recovers quickly, so...
No!
Pike-san, Lilie-san...
If you continue to chitchat during class,
I will have both of you marry me together!
While we're at it, how about we include
Ahiru-san, who is absent today,
and all three of you can get married together?
You danced splendidly, Mytho-san.
You're beginning to convey more emotion over technique.
Yes, sir.
You are in love... are you not?
What?
I can tell, you see.
In love?
Very well.
I will hold a special class on being in
love after school for you.
Mytho is?
Yes, sir.
Being in love is a wonderful thing, but there are
some things you must be careful about.
In particular, during puberty, self-control is important.
Quack.
The pendant... The pendant...
It's not here!
Don't tell me he took it in there with him?!
Oh, he's coming out!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
Quack!
So, he had it with him, after all.
Is he injured?
No, it's a birthmark.
The pendant!
If I could just reach it...
Mytho, you don't know anything.
You don't know what the implications
are of regaining your heart.
What?
That damned Kraehe!
Is this to say that she does not see me as a threat?!
Mytho and Kraehe's wedding?
With Fakir as witness...
"Tonight at midnight, I will be waiting at the church..."
What is Fakir...
An antique shop?
Quack!
Karon...
Fakir...
Where's the sword?
You haven't been home in ages and not even a greeting?
There are plenty of swords in the shop.
No, THAT sword.
The Lohengrin Sword.
I need it.
I have to protect Mytho from the crows.
I can't give it to you.
What?
That is the sword meant for the knight to wield.
You promised that you would let me have it!
That was when you were a child.
Mytho is regaining his heart.
Princess Tutu has appeared.
The crows are returning as well.
The legend you told me about is all becoming reality.
If so, I am the knight in the story reborn.
Fakir is a knight reborn?
If I am the knight, it should be all right
for me to use the Lohengrin Sword.
Fakir, just leave Mytho be from now on.
What did you say?
It would be better if you did not involve yourself
in this accursed tale any further!
Why are you saying this now, at this late date?!
The day you took me in after my parents
had died, you told me, remember?
This mark of yours is exactly like in the legend that
has been passed down among our people.
I'm sure you'll grow up to be strong.
It's a sign that you are the reincarnation the
brave knight, who protected the prince.
And in time, it became a source of pride for me.
"If it was to protect the people, the prince
never feared being injured himself."
Wow, that's so great!
And then, my destiny was suddenly set in motion.
Karon, his heart isn't beating!
Karon?
The prince, who had lost his heart...
Mythos...
"Mythos" means a person of legend.
Did you know that?
Don't know.
You don't know anything, do you, Prince?
Sorry.
It's weird for your name to be Prince, so how about
taking the name Mytho? It's a cool name!
Okay.
Then it's settled! You'll be Mytho starting today!
Mytho had no emotions.
But whenever he saw something weak suffering,
no matter what dangers he faced,
he would try to protect it without hesitation.
Oh, Mytho! It's dangerous!
Oh, it's dangerous!
Mytho...
Mytho!
Fakir...
Stupid...
You're absentminded, so it's troublesome when
you go and do unnecessary things!
Sorry.
Don't go trying to help people.
Okay...
Just listen to what I say. I'll protect you.
I will protect Mytho, because that
was the promise I made.
Protect Mytho? But then, why did
you try to shatter his heart?
What you're trying to do isn't for Mytho's sake!
It's for your own sake, isn't it, Fakir?!
What?
Soon, the time to fight will come.
Are you sure you're not afraid you'll follow
the same fate as the knight in the story?
No...
You kept calling him a good-for-nothing so
the prince's heart wouldn't be restored,
and you enrolled him at Gold Crown Academy to make
him do nothing but dance, which he loved to do,
all because you feared to fight, didn't you?!
No!
With the way you are now, you won't
be able to protect Mytho!
Stop it!
Wash your hands of this!
That's enough! Any sword will do!
Stop doing this now. Do you understand?
Yes... I may be afraid, just as you say,
but I want to protect him.
Protect the pure-hearted Mytho, who's
always risking himself.
There's a shard somewhere around here...
Fakir!
I don't know anymore...
What's right and what's wrong?
But the one thing I can tell is that Fakir isn't lying.
I couldn't see any of it.
Fakir is the same as me.
No, he might care about Mytho even more than I do.
You...
You've caught me at a bad moment.
Quack.
You'll cry for my sake?
Quack?
You can have it. You wanted it, right?
Princess Tutu, I do not acknowledge you.
Fakir...
Oh, yeah! There's a shard at Karon-san's house.
Was this really the right thing to do?
There's no way to know.
No matter what you do right now, you'll only regret it.
You're right.
It's here, just as I thought.
Come now, if you don't hurry, the wedding will start.
Karon-san...
Princess Tutu!
I never dreamed you would really...
Dance with me, Karon-san.
So the tale is really beginning to move...
But I do not know what it is that I should do.
I have always regretted telling Fakir the legend.
No, I regret having hurt Fakir.
I can only do things that I regret for that child.
No...
You should be able to have faith in him.
Have faith?
Yes, if Fakir journeys down the path he believes in, I think
he won't regret it, no matter what the outcome.
Why not have faith in Fakir?
Have faith in Fakir...
I am the feeling of regret.
Princess Tutu, thank you. My doubts have cleared.
Do not be afraid.
Turn this page with your own hand.
I... I...
Will not succumb to such a miserable fate!
I'll change it!
My prince...
Princess Tutu...
I've brought you a shard of your heart.
Thank you.
Are you going to Kraehe?
Yes, because I feel that I mustn't run away...
Thank you, Princess Tutu.
For going to the trouble of returning
shards of his heart to my husband.
But whether you return those shards to
him or not does not matter anymore.
For the prince will become mine tonight.
I will have you bear witness...
As a sacrifice.
I've been waiting for you, Fakir.
Do what you must, so you have no regrets.
Karon...
My son...
What do you think, Princess Tutu?
Aren't we just perfect for each other?
I prepared a special seat for you.
Tutu!
First, a dance to celebrate.
If I wanted, I could do away with Tutu this very second.
Mytho...
My handsome prince, you are mine.
Kraehe, who are you? Why do you demand that I be yours?
That is because it is fate.
Fate? Whose fate is that?
It matters not whose fate it is.
Fate cannot be changed.
Not by anyone.
Back, you filthy raven!
Fakir...
So, the coward finally shows up.
I will not allow you to get near Mytho!
Kraehe, please stop!
What's wrong?
Why are you in pain?
She has... the stone back...
What are you doing?! Hurry and be gone!
Or will you settle it here and now?!
I don't want to fight you.
I have to hurry, or Fakir and Mytho will catch up to me.
If I'm caught wandering around this late, they'll be suspic...
What? No way!
Hey...
Eep!
Don't "eep" me.
What are you doing out this late?
What am I doing?
If I'm out this late, what else could I be doing but THAT?
That?
You KNOW what "that" is. Well, see you.
Hey, what's that...
What?!
Wait!
That pendant...
Good night!
Princess Tutu?
What'll I do?
Could it be that he's found out?
Oh, dear, it looks like your identity has become known.
What are you going to do, Princess Tutu?
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
I'm surprised, to be honest.
Of all people, I never expected it to be you.
Ahiru, do you know about Princess Tutu?
The one Mytho wants to see is not me,
but Princess Tutu, but...
I wish I could have stayed Rue forever
with Kraehe's memories erased.
But now...
The name of this gem is "love."
I am the feeling of love.
The feeling of love, is it?
Please stop, Kraehe!
All you children who love stories, come gather around.
"La Sylphide"