Once upon a time, there was a maiden
with wings of freedom.
The man who loved this maiden thought,
"If I could just bind those wings,
we would never have to be apart,
even for a moment."
But when the man wrapped the maiden's
wings in a magical shawl,
the wings fell off almost immediately
and the maiden died.
The man did not know
that the maiden's wings were her source of life.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
Now, then, all the characters needed for
the story are finally assembled.
A prince without the heart to love, a
knight who fears death,
a villain without resolve, and a princess
who cannot express her love.
Something's still missing.
Now, go on.
And this time, don't you become interested
in people's emotions.
Excuse me, won't you please take this?
It's quite pretty.
The name of this gem is "love."
Love...
I would advise you not to let it go.
It suits you very well.
No, I did not have the right to have this.
Someone like me never did.
I see.
Thank you.
"La Sylphide"
Princess Tutu...
She is?
I don't want to fight you.
It doesn't matter, regardless of who Princess Tutu is.
I will protect Mytho in my own way.
I'll protect him from the clutches of the raven!
Without fear!
I wonder if he really does know now?
You've been sighing all morning.
Poor thing!
It seems the scar from being rejected runs deep.
You seem happy.
No way!
Thanks for worrying about me, but it's not about
being rejected or anything like that.
It's okay! You don't have to tell us! We know!
Anyway, revenge! Revenge! You've just got to do it!
Right, you'll do it, won't you, Ahiru?
At any rate, you have to get him to notice you!
Then that means a present!
Oh, that might be a good!
You might even be able to find out
how he feels about you too!
Really?
Oh, my?!
And Fakir-sama too?!
Fakir...
If you give someone a present, you'll
know how they feel about you?
Oh, no, you were listening?!
We were overheard.
If you give him a present now, your ulterior
motive will be totally obvious!
When you say present, what kind of thing
are you talking about?
He's probing us!
What'll we do? How should we answer?!
What would you want if it were you, Ahiru?
Ahiru would take absolutely anything!
That's right, she would take anything she could get!
As long as it's given with love!
Even gems or bars of gold!
Love...
There needs to be love?
Mytho-san, I held a special class for you yesterday on being in
love, but it seems a special class on love is needed as well.
There's a difference between love and being in love?
Of course, there is.
If you do not even understand that,
you will not be able to get... get married.
Would you like to take the class as well, Fakir-san?
No, thank you.
Then Mytho-san, let us go.
Gifts are perfectly fine, but such things as anti-flee
collars can be rude, so caution is necessary.
Does he know... after all?
Fakir...
I want to ask you something.
Come with me.
What did you want to ask me?
Princess Tutu...
Qua...
You are, aren't you?
I'm surprised, to be honest.
Of all people, I never expected it to be you.
I have something I want to ask you too.
You're also fighting to protect Mytho, right?
Then why did you try to shatter his heart?
Why?
That is something that no longer matters.
The tale cannot be stopped now.
The tale?
If you're going to restore his heart shards, go ahead.
No matter what the outcome, I will protect Mytho.
Then let's work together, and...
No thanks.
Why?
I do not trust you.
Mytho...
If you regain any more of your heart,
you'll surely grow distant from me.
For I am a crow, your enemy.
Even though I love you so much.
I wish I could have stayed Rue forever
with Kraehe's memories erased.
But now...
Would anyone like gems?
Would anyone like a gem to give your loved one as a gift?
Welcome.
You are...
It has been a while, Rue.
As a gift?
Has this one caught your fancy?
The name of this gem is "love."
Love...
Oh, it's lovely, don't you think?
If you like it so much, I shall give it to you.
Are you sure?
Please, I have no use for it.
Why don't you accept it, Mytho?
Okay...
However, though this gem is strong, it is easily scarred,
though it is beautiful, it is easily tarnished,
and if it is fought over, it may
sometimes lead to death.
Please be very careful in handling it.
Do you like it that much?
Yes...
So, you're going to give that to me, aren't you?
Rue...
I'm sorry, this is...
I was just kidding.
I see.
I wonder just who the lucky girl is?
That's...
Say, would you let me see it for a second?
Okay...
It's beautiful.
But there's something important missing.
I wonder what it could be?
What? Really?
Oh...
I'm sorry. I know it's precious to you.
Say, would you let me borrow it for tonight?
I'll make it even prettier and fix it up for you.
So that you can secure the heart of the one you love.
Okay...
You can look forward to how it turns out.
Mytho...
I won't let anyone else have you.
I'll never hand you over.
Very good, very good.
Yet another necessary component of
the tale has been added.
Love filled with hatred.
This is an interesting device.
Fakir's found out, but it's strange somehow.
I actually feel rather relieved now.
I do not trust you.
Fakir is always thinking by himself, deciding
by himself, fighting by himself...
By himself...
Crying by himself...
And he won't show me his true face.
It was warm in Fakir's arms.
I bet that's the real Fakir.
Fakir...
What is it?
I'm thinking of giving a gift to Tutu.
Is that so?
You're not going to get mad?
Do what you want.
Don't turn your sword against Tutu.
Please, Fakir, promise me.
I can't make a promise like that.
Now, please don't stoop.
Yes, sir!
Thanks for waiting.
What do you think?
Wow, it's wonderful.
Isn't it, though?
If you give this to the one you love, you'll
be able to secure her heart forever.
Thank you, Rue.
Oh, man, I wish I could go home for once
without having to stay after.
Mytho...
Mytho!
What was that about? I don't know what
happened, but I better go after him.
Protecting the prince is also Princess Tutu's...
Thunder?
Mytho didn't have an umbrella with him, right?
I wonder where he went?
Princess Tutu...
I wonder where she is?
I wonder where he went?
Would anyone like gems?
Edel-san!
Hello!
It has been a while, Ahiru.
Now that you mention it, we haven't seen
each other in a while, have we?
Anyway, Edel-san, you wouldn't have
happened to see Mytho, would you?
If it's Mytho, he's searching for the person to give his gift to.
What? His gift?
If you give someone a present, you'll
know how they feel about you?
I want to know what you think of me.
I... I...
The person to give his gift to?
I know! It's Rue-chan, right?
Now that his feelings are coming back, he probably
wants to know how Rue-chan feels and stuff.
Yeah, yeah, that's it...
But if it were for Tutu...
But even if that were true, it's not to me as Ahiru,
but to Tutu, so it has nothing to do with me.
It has nothing to do with me...
Thank you, Edel-san.
Maybe he'll be someplace where he met Tutu.
Mytho!
Mytho, where are you?
Tutu...
Can I not see you?
Princess Tutu...
Tutu...
Mytho!
Ahiru...
Mytho...
What are you doing here?
Oh, it seemed like it might rain and I figured
you wouldn't have an umbrella, so...
Are you waiting for someone?
Yes, for Princess Tutu.
Ahiru, do you know about Tutu?
What? Oh, no, I don't, but...
I see.
Um, please use this.
Thank you.
I hope you get to see her.
Yes...
Bye!
The one Mytho wants to see is not
me, but Princess Tutu, but...
My, my, that is dangerous. That thought is truly dangerous.
Are you sure about this, Princess Tutu?
My prince...
Are you looking for someone?
Tutu...
My prince...
I finally got to see you.
There's something I want to give you.
It's lovely.
I want you to have this.
If that is what you wish, my prince.
I'll put it on you.
All right.
Thank you.
It's strange.
What is?
They said if you give someone a gift, you'll know how
they feel, but I still don't know how you feel.
I don't know what you think of me.
That's...
But...
It made you happy, so I think that's okay too.
My prince...
What?
This is...
A heart shard...
Come on out.
What feeling are you?
I am the feeling of love.
The feeling of love...
You are?
You don't have to wander anymore.
The place for you to return to is here.
I'm so glad.
Inside that ornament, it was so dark
and the terrifying crows...
Kraehe!
The feeling of love, is it?
I had intended to get rid of Princess Tutu with it,
but now I've found something great.
And I've also discovered your identity.
What?
What are you going to do, Kraehe?
What?!
Fakir!
Back off, raven.
My, my, that is dangerous. That action is truly dangerous.
You may be the knight reborn, but you are still just a human.
Are you sure about this?
However, the princess is also just a duck
and the prince is just a story.
It's dangerous when you aren't aware
of your place in the world.
Oh?
Just who are you, Princess Kraehe?
Are you really the villain?
Are you really the raven?
How dangerous, how truly dangerous.
Not knowing your place in the world
is dangerous, I tell you.
Stay away from Mytho!
Be gone, crow!
Kraehe!
Fakir!
See? What did I just say?
If you're the knight, you have to conquer
your fears and defeat the villain.
If you're the villain, you have to kill
the princess without mercy.
If you're the princess, you have to save
the prince with the power of your love.
If you're the prince, you have to use
your wisdom and courage...
Whoops, that's not possible.
I am Princess Kraehe.
Whatever I want, I will take by force!
Kraehe, what do you mean to do?
Kraehe!
How do you like it, Princess Tutu?
How does it feel to be bound by the prince's feelings?
What?
It hurts, doesn't it?
That's just how strongly he feels for you, you know.
Unforgivable...
Stop it, Kraehe!
You love the prince, don't you?!
Why?!
Why would you do something so horrible?
Oh, dear, the enemy now knows your identity
and you've even lost the prince.
How delightful. No, how terrible.
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
Once before, when I lost this necklace, you
held onto it for me. Remember, Fakir?
Would you hold onto it for me again?
It can't be... That duck?
Quack.
Have you gone back to being the doll you used to be?
Because I yanked out a piece of your heart...
But that knight was torn in two by the crow's claws
without his sword ever even touching the crow.
A useless good-for-nothing, who could
only talk of protecting the prince!
Please, stop doing this!
All you children who love stories, come gather around.
"Banquet of Darkness"