Once upon a time, there was a handsome slave.
What bound him were not heavy chains,
but the princess's love.
Every day, every night, the princess whispers her
love to the slave and the slave responds in kind.
Bound body. Bound emotions.
The slave or the princess?
Which of them is really the one who cannot move?
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
I...
Let go of me. I can walk by myself.
No...
That's right, princess Tutu helped me, and...
Binding my wounds? What an unnecessary...
Hey...
Oh, Fakir, how are your injuries?
Don't give me that. Why are you still Tutu?
What? Oh...
I thought maybe it'd be bad if I went into
the boys' dorm looking like my usual self.
Was that weird somehow?
No...
Sorry for having troubled you.
That's nothing at all.
Oh, are you okay? Can you get up?
However, that doesn't mean that I'm
going to cooperate with you.
But you're going to go looking for Mytho, right?
We could at least cooperate on that, couldn't we?
Let's look for Mytho together.
"Banquet of Darkness"
You can forget about everything.
And you can just fill every void you have with me.
No one will come here. It will be just you and me.
So all you have to do is love only me.
Tell me that you love only me.
I love only you, Kraehe.
Really?
Really...
It can't be...
How much?
If you love me, smile for me.
Just like you did on the night of the Fire Festival.
How?
Have you gone back to being the doll you used to be?
Because I yanked out that piece of your heart...
So, you've also shut away all your other
emotions because of that?
If that's true, then that's fine.
If you're going to love someone else,
better not to love anyone.
It's your fault, you know.
It's because you wouldn't look at
me when I love you so much!
No, you're not the one to blame, are you?
Yes, if you hadn't begun to regain your heart,
everything would have gone well.
And I wouldn't have had to remember
that I was a crow.
It's all that nuisance's fault.
Because she IS a nuisance.
If I am to have her leave, the sooner the better.
A single prince has no need of two princesses.
Isn't that right,
Herr Drosselmeyer?
What?! Impossible! Did she just call my name?
You're watching from somewhere, aren't you?
Oh-ho!
You are quite formidable to call on me.
I'll tell you the best story ever.
What?! Really?!
The best story ever must have the best ending ever.
And for that, a worthy stage is needed.
Yeah, you're right.
In that case, I've got a stage I've been
saving for just such an occasion.
A lake that no one has visited in 200 years...
I shall show you the way there.
Mytho!
He's not here either.
He's not around.
Of course, he is.
It's just that we haven't been able to find him.
Right...
Oh!
What about the lesson room?
Huh?
He might be dancing in the lesson room about now.
Why would he be?
What? Because Mytho loves to dance...
There's no way he'll be there.
But, but, the last time he got taken away,
he was back before we knew it, right?
So I thought it might be the same again this time...
Besides, there's nowhere else I can think of.
I guess we can go check it out,
since we have nothing to lose.
What? Oh, wait for me!
The school sure is quiet on Sundays, isn't it?
I guess.
Maybe it's Mytho!
Oh!
Meow?!
Hey...
Huh?
He can see you.
What? Where? What? What?
Huh?
Who dares to disturb my Sunday practice?!
Ahiru-san, as punishment for
disturbing my tireless effort,
I will have you marry me right away!
I'm so sorry!
What are you doing?
But...
Hey, there.
Mytho!
He's okay! Thank goodness!
Wait!
Do you know the story of the Prince and the Raven?
It's a story where a brave prince fights a raven.
There was a knight that the prince trusted.
But that knight was torn in two by the raven's claws
without his sword ever even touching the raven.
A useless good-for-nothing, who could
only talk of protecting the prince!
That's why the prince suffered great hardships.
The raven leapt out of the story and he had no choice
but to pursue it alone and seal it away alone,
by using a forbidden power of his own will.
That's right.
The prince took his very own heart...
Out of his body!
What?
It can't be!
He took out his heart himself?
It's true.
Rue-chan!
You don't know anything, do you, Ahiru?
Do you know about Princess Tutu?
Princess Tutu?! I don't... really know... anything...
You see, in the Prince and the Raven,
Princess Tutu is only presented in a few sentences.
A miserable existence that not even any of
the characters in the story wanted to be.
An insignificant existence that was forsaken even
by the story somewhere along the way.
Someone who could never hope to catch the prince's eye.
Just a little additional flare to the story.
Poor thing.
Rue-chan, why are you telling me this story?
So, you still haven't figured it out.
Rue doesn't even really exist.
What?
What?!
Have you finally figured it out, Princess Tutu?
Princess Kraehe?!
You can't be!
Because you're my friend!
We chatted together and danced together and...
Stop it!
That's true, but all that foolishness is over now.
Rue-chan!
I only came to get something the prince
left behind, so I will excuse myself now.
Left behind?
It is not something for a mere failure of a knight to have.
The prince's sword!
When did she...
Rue-chan!
Hurry up and come rescue the prince.
Oh, Edel-san.
Edel-san...
Water is drawn to fire, fire to darkness
and darkness to silence.
Now, let us go.
Go where?
Where you must go.
This place...
Edel-san?
It's locked.
You can go to where the prince and Kraehe are from here.
An entrance in a place like this?
Go on.
Thank you, Edel-san, for always being so kind to me.
This is not kindness.
What?
Puppets follow orders.
Puppets?
Yes, I am a puppet.
I have neither feelings nor a heart.
But Edel-san, you've always taught me all
sorts of things and you've been so nice.
So, I think of you as...
It was because that was the role given to me.
My orders end here. Now, go on.
Whose orders?
Edel-san...
Now, go on.
Ahiru?
Edel-san, thank you. We'll be going now.
Ahiru...
So warm...
And so soft...
Edel-san...
Now, hurry.
Okay, let's go!
Right...
Good grief, if you use a puppet for
too long, it can be such a pain
because they begin to take interest
in things like people's feelings.
Don't you forget.
Your role is to add a glow to the story in my place.
That's about all you're capable of doing.
Not knowing your place in the world
is dangerous, you know.
Scary...
Owowow!
You idiot! Walk more towards the middle!
You're already careless enough as it is.
Wow, this place is kind of incredible...
I better walk with my eyes forward.
You're really Princess Tutu, aren't you?
Well, yeah. What about it?
Well, I thought Princess Tutu was
more... sort of... you know...
Huh?
No, never mind.
Say, Fakir?
What is it?
Never mind, it's nothing.
What the heck?
If you didn't want to say, keep your
mouth shut to begin with!
Oh, um, it's nothing like that, but...
I don't think you're no good as a
knight or anything, you know.
What are you trying to get at?
It's not that I'm really trying to get at anything, but...
I didn't think you were very nice when I first met you,
but now, I feel like I understand you just a bit, so...
I'll say this right now, but I have no intention
of cooperating with you, all right?
I'll help Mytho in my own way. That's all there is to it.
Yeah, I know.
You know...
Hmm?
Never mind, it's nothing.
What's your problem?!
Don't stop in the middle when you've
started to say something!
The truth is, I've never thought about things like...
What exactly do I like about Mytho?
When I first saw him, it was just that I
thought he was handsome,
but when I looked closer, his
eyes looked so lonely.
And I thought if I became Princess Tutu,
I could do something for him.
At first, that's really all there was to it.
But now, I...
Damn!
Fakir?!
Run!
You idiot!
I'm sorry. Are you hurt?
It's a miracle I'm not.
What is this place?
I guess we have no choice but to climb up again.
We might be able to get out through the water.
I could go check it out if I became a bird, but...
It's covered with moss. I don't think we can climb this.
Damn...
If it's Fakir...
Fakir...
What is it?
Once before, when I lost this necklace, you
held onto it for me. Remember, Fakir?
Huh? What about it?
Would you hold onto it for me again?
What the heck is this all about?
Here...
Huh?
Wha?
What's going on? Where'd she go?
Quack!
A duck?!
She...
So, this wasn't a pendant for her to become Tutu?
It can't be... That duck?
You've caught me at a bad moment.
I don't think you're no good as a
knight or anything, you know.
She saw me crying.
She couldn't be drowning in there, could she?
Can ducks drown?
No, knowing her, it's possible.
That idiot!
Quack!
Quack! Quack, quack, quack!
Quack, quack, quack!
Quack! Quack, quack! Quack! Quack!
Why...
Why didn't you tell me?! Don't keep
quiet about things like that!
Quack?
It's playing dirty!
Quack!
Quack! Quack!
You say that, but it's not like I revealed
it to you because I wanted to!
But as a bird, I'm smaller and it's easier to check...
Did you see?
I didn't look!
Or rather, how was it?!
Isn't that what you should be bringing up first?!
But you...
Don't stand up!
We can get to the other side through the water.
I smelled a different kind of water, so
there's probably a lake up ahead.
See? It looks like we can still go deeper, right?
That's probably where Mytho is.
Are you okay, Fakir?
Huh? What?
A duck as Princess Tutu, huh?
What?
I'll tell you something you'll want to hear.
Back when I was still a brat, when I read
"The Prince and the Raven" to Mytho,
the thing he showed the most interest in was neither
what happened to himself nor the raven,
but what happened to Tutu, about whom
only a little was written.
He wanted to hear over and over again the part where
Tutu becomes a speck of light and vanishes.
Him coming to want to regain his heart is probably
because it's Tutu who returns it to him.
But they said Mytho took out his heart himself...
That's the kind of guy he is.
To protect someone, those who are small and weak...
That's Mytho's greatest wish.
And to do that, he'll have no regard for himself.
Even when he lost his heart, that was
the one thing he never forgot.
That's just the kind of guy he is.
Let's go.
Right!
So, you've finally come.
I've tired of waiting.
Mytho!
Welcome to the stage that I have been saving for this.
Now, tell me the best story ever.
Tell it to me with no regard for your lives!
Please, stop doing this!
I agree, let us put an end to it.
The prince's feeling of love is right here.
The heart that loves people, loves all the world.
It has yet to belong to anyone.
I wonder who this shard will choose? You or me?
Whose words will it be drawn to once
we've laid our hearts bare?
If the shard chooses you, I'll return the
prince and the shard to you.
Now, why don't you speak to it of what's in your heart?
Well, Princess Tutu?
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
Tell me, why do we have to fight in
this way? Because we are...
Ultimately, you are only borrowing
the power of Princess Tutu.
Just a sham of a princess, Ahiru.
No one else but you could smilingly
accept the fate of Princess Tutu.
You are my princess.
Yes, I am your true princess.
The real me is just a duck with
no powers of any sort.
But if I have you, I can change!
All you children who love stories, come gather around.
"Swan Lake"