Once upon a time, there was a child.
For the child, the world was filled with wonder.
How? Why? How come?
When one mystery was solved, two
new mysteries would arise.
When two mysteries were solved, four
When four mysteries were solved, there
would be countless mysteries.
In time, the child became consumed by these mysteries.
Yonde iru koe saa me o samashite
The voice calling, come now, wake up
Nakigao nugutte
Wiping a tearstained face
Mabushii hikari kigi no tsuyu umareru
The brilliant light and the dew on trees are born
Dare mo shiranai himitsu no mizube de
By the secret water's edge that no one knows of
Odore inochi no pa du duu
Dance the pas de deux of life
Kyou mo yume miteru
Dreaming again today
Sore wa yasashiku hageshii nagare ne
It is a gentle, yet fierce current
Doko made tsuzuku rabirinsu
How far does the labyrinth stretch?
Watashi wa yukou
I shall go
Nigirishimeru yume
The dream I hold tight
No! Stop!
Please, don't come near me!
Tutu...
No, I didn't mean to make him suffer!
Not knowing what all the feelings were,
like to be happy and to love...
I thought that was sad, and that's why... that's why...
Quack! Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack!
Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack! Quack!
"The Crow Princess"
I didn't mean for it to be like this.
Ahiru, we're leaving!
If you don't hurry, you'll be back to
being probationary Ahiru!
Okay!
Mytho hasn't been to class since that day.
Now, go on back to Mytho.
What are you afraid of?
I'm afraid of Princess Tutu.
It's my fault!
I wonder if Mytho-sama is all right?
It's been a week since Mytho stopped coming to class.
I wonder if he's with Fakir?
Fakir, too.
What the heck are they thinking?
Well, it's not like you can ever tell
what Mytho's thinking anyway.
Everyone did very well on the report on "Sleeping Beauty"
by the Eleki Troupe the other day.
Especially you, Rue-san.
It was brilliantly insightful. I would have expected no less.
Thank you very much.
And this would be Ahiru-san's report.
My!
Ooh!
"It was great. The end."
It was brilliantly succinct. I would have expected no less.
Thank you very much.
That was not a compliment.
I see.
At this rate, I will have to either drop
you to the probationary class again,
or have you marry...
That's fine.
What?!
No way.
You're fine?
You mean, about being dropped to the probationary class?
Or about ma-ma-ma-
Oh, no! What a terrible fever!
And what terrible goose bumps!
We gotta go to the doctor's office!
Excuse us!
Hold it right there!
If you wish to marry me, let us meet after school.
I will be waiting at the pizza shop...
What's wrong? You've been kind of down lately.
It makes me sad to see you like this.
The great thing about you is that no matter what happens,
you forget about it right away and cheer up again.
That's right, like a bird.
Oh, my! What's wrong?! Snap out of it!
It's your fault.
No way!
I don't know... I don't get it anymore.
What?
About what?
Don't worry, you never got any of the
stuff in class anyway, remember?
Not like that. I mean, things like what do I want to do?
It's just everything.
Wow, it sounds pretty serious.
Could it be...
Because Mytho-sama hasn't been to class at all?
I knew it.
At times like this, why don't you try
going to the Why-why Bridge?
A riddle bridge?
The Why-why Bridge. You don't know it?
It's an old bridge over the river to the north.
When you stand on that bridge and talk
about things you're not sure of,
they say out of nowhere a voice asks,
"Why? How come?"
Is this a scary story?
It's not scary.
As the questions keep coming and you keep answering
them, it helps sort out your feelings.
Why do you say it in such a scary way?!
But you know, that's not all.
That's right. If you can't answer the questions...
You get swallowed up by the river!
No!
Just kidding!
There's just a legend like that.
It's an old, old story.
What? Then, what about now?
I don't know, stuff like that probably doesn't happen now.
No!
If it doesn't happen, then talk normally!
But there are quite a few people
who say they really heard voices.
As they say, it doesn't hurt to try,
so why don't you go see?
Yeah, you're right.
That's our Ahiru!
Well, then...
Be careful!
Nothing to be scared of, nothing to be scared of.
I'm just going to make sure I know what I should do.
Make sure and...
What'll I do?
Uh, well... Are you here for the riddle bridge?
It's the Why-why Bridge.
Oh, right, right.
So, Rue-chan, even you have things you're not sure about?
Is it... about Mytho?
That's why I came here, but I've changed my mind.
I see.
I'm sure he'll come back to school soon.
Why do you think so?
Um, just a feeling.
I'm sorry, that was thoughtless.
See you later.
Oh, Rue-chan!
Rue-chan, you know that Mytho doesn't have a heart, right?
Of course.
So, well...
Do you think it would be better if he had a heart after all?
It doesn't matter.
What?
I've always only had eyes for Mytho.
Whether he has a heart or not, it won't
change the fact that I love him.
And I'll continue to love him.
I'm still far from having loved him enough.
Rue-chan said she loves Mytho.
I...
I'm just a bird, so something like that...
Mytho! Snap out of it, Mytho!
Mytho...
What is it?
Fakir, I had a dream.
There was a big black being and it...
Don't worry.
Who was that?
Don't let it bother you. You don't need to know anything.
Got it?
Where's Tutu?
Relax, no one knows that we're here.
So I can't see Tutu?
That's right.
If you stay in here, you'll eventually forget everything.
You won't be led astray by those stupid emotions, either.
That's what's best for you.
I want to make sure, but...
Both Rue-chan and Fakir say he doesn't need a heart.
And Mytho's suffering too.
Then, what is there to make certain?
Oh, a heart shard!
Being Princess Tutu is meaningless. I could quit and...
She wouldn't!
If I return this...
But then I'd go back to being a bird,
so if I just stay a girl...
Would that be sort of dishonest?
It would, wouldn't it?
I think I'll just put an end to this now.
Oh my goodness! The story will
be left hanging at this rate!
No! No! No!
I won't let it end here!
A character in a story would never say they're
going to end things at a spot like this!
I swear! Reality is just so...
Since it's come to this...
I have no choice but to use this
passageway of time once again.
It's old, so who knows how many
more times I'll be able to use it?
There was never anything I could do for him from the start!
I fell in love on my own, and I
believed what I wanted to.
What?
Long time no see, Little Duck.
What?!
Oh, dear, have you forgotten?
I'm Drosselmeyer.
But you're supposed to be dead...
I AM dead. Completely dead.
That's why I can only come meet you like this.
I came all this way so that I could show you that to quit
being Princess Tutu is absolutely foolish.
Now, you have to go restore the prince's heart to him!
What I got back for him were things like fear and tears...
That's right! Delightful, just delightful!
If you go back to being a duck, you'll
never get to see the prince again.
Drosselmeyer-san.
What is it?
Why did you give me the chance to be Princess Tutu?
That's easy.
What?
Because it would be fun.
Fun...
Oh!
No, because you're the only one.
I'm the only one?
That's right!
While risking everything for the prince, Princess Tutu
is fated never to be united with her prince.
How cruel! What a thankless role! No one wants to be her.
On top of that, the prince hates me now.
That's right. Truly delightful!
You see, don't you? If you don't do it, who will?
No!
It doesn't matter anymore!
Oh, what have you done?!
Quack!
Quack! Quack, quack, quack, quack!
Oh, Little Duck!
Not good!
I'll leave the rest to you.
Princess Tutu...
What is this that I feel when I think of Princess Tutu?
If what I felt in the dream was fear,
this is something different.
Who's there?
Fakir?
Is that you, Tutu?
Tutu?
Who's Tutu?
What kind of person is she?
Someone I fear.
You fear her and you're looking for her?
How strange. Why?
I wonder why?
Why are you afraid of her?
Because she's restoring my heart to me.
You don't have a heart?
No.
Is it better not to have one?
Yes.
Why?
I don't know.
Quack...
I don't have to worry about things like getting dropped
to the probationary class anymore either.
Edel-san.
Would you like some gems?
Your world as a bird, your world as a girl.
The world within the story and the world of reality.
The gem that links two worlds.
Will you close yourself to it all?
Quack...
When you had finally linked them?
Quack!
It doesn't matter anymore!
You're a strange person.
Hey, won't you come with me? To a place
where no one will come.
A place where no one will come...
Right. Because you're so strange and I
want to know more about you.
I want to know. I want to know more.
Okay.
Qua... Quack!
Mytho!
Quack!
Oh, no! Quack!
Qua, qua, qua, quack! Quack! Quack!
Quack!
Huh? What is this?
Quack! I can't catch up to him!
What'll I do?!
Since when do you not have a heart?
No idea.
How did you lose it?
How...
Oh, I feel like there was something that I had to do.
What's that?
I don't know.
I want to know. Don't you want to know?
No.
Really?
Probably.
Why don't you want to know?
It hurts when I try to find out.
How strange.
You and I are very alike.
Like you, I don't know what I am, either.
But you and I are the opposite.
What?
I want to know so badly, that it hurts.
Could it be that you're...
Keeping this up is useless...
If I could just...
If I could just become Princess Tutu one more time!
That's what I like to hear!
Not just once, but many more times!
Princess Tutu.
Princess Tutu? The person you're afraid of?
Don't be afraid. Let's go back together.
You're Princess Tutu?
Why do you restore his heart?
That's...
That's because I thought that was what's best for Mytho.
There are painful feelings, like sorrow and loneliness,
but there are lots of warm feelings, like joy and love too.
It was because I wanted to get those things back for him.
Because I thought you would be happier that way.
Because I never imagined you would suffer so much.
Tutu...
Don't cry, Tutu.
I'll come back with you.
Why?
You're afraid of her, but you're going with her?
How strange.
Mytho!
Where did he go?
Oh, um, I'm sorry.
But this will be the last time.
What?
I'll never appear before you again, so rest easy.
Farewell.
Wait.
I understand a little of what I'm feeling right now.
What?
This is the feeling of loneliness and the feeling of sorrow.
I don't want to never see you again.
But I bring you pain...
I don't care.
Even if it hurts, when I think of you, I can feel a
small light coming to life in my heart.
Me too.
If you disappear, I feel like that light
will be extinguished and vanish.
I'm afraid of that.
Restore my heart to me, Tutu.
Possessing this river is likely my desire for knowledge.
Return it to my heart.
But...
I see, so I am you.
Are you really sure?
Yes.
The heart shard!
Who are you?
Princess Kraehe.
Princess Kraehe?
What's this?
Give it back!
No!
I will not give you anything. I will
not allow you to do anything.
What?
Stay away from the prince!
Who... Who am I?
Mytho?
Mytho?!
Mytho...
Mytho!
Hey, Mytho! Get a hold of yourself!
Mytho...
I see, so... you've finally appeared.
Very good, very good.
The appearance of a new seed of calamity.
The deepening mystery.
And to the duck, who chose the path of suffering and
tragedy, goes an unstinting round of applause.
Yume miru you ni koi o shita no
I loved like I was dreaming
Fukuramu kokoro ga fukuramu no yo
It swells... My heart swells
Ikiteru tte suteki na koto to omotta
I thought how wonderful it was to be alive
Asu ga machidoushii
I can't wait for tomorrow
Anata no chikara ni naritai no
I want to be there for you
Donna toki ni mo watashi
At all times
Matte matte kurenai
Wait, it won't wait
Hashitte hashitte yuku no yo
Running, running along
Kaze mo amagumo mo oikoshite
Passing by even the wind and the rain clouds
Watashi dake no tsubasa habataite
Just beating my own wings
Confessing your love at the window?! Ahiru, you're so bold!
It was like a reverse Romeo and Juliet!
Somehow, it was like he wasn't the usual Fakir.
Look, my prince, there is the one
making you suffer. Princess Tutu.
Princess Tutu...
I want to know what you think of me.
I... I...
I'll shatter your heart for you once again.
All you children who love stories, come gather around.
"The Warrior's Fountain"