I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
Crybaby Usagi's Magnificent Transformation
I'm Usagi Tsukino, 14 years old.
I'm in the eighth grade.
I'm just a little clumsy and a bit
of a crybaby. That's about it.
Usagi! It's past eight o'clock!
Why didn't you wake me up earlier?!
Thanks a lot, Mom!
I tried many times. You answered
each time, remember?
I don't remember!
Oh, Usagi...
What? I'm in a hurry!
Don't you want your lunch?
Uh, yes...
I'm leaving!
Why does morning have to come?
I'm so sleepy.
Get the cat! Yeah!
Hey cat, bark!
Hey! Stop it!
I can't believe it.
Poor kitty. It's okay now.
Oh, did they put a band-aid on you?
You want me to take it off? Here.
But it did kind of suit you though.
Wha? A crescent shaped bald spot?
Oh! I don't have time for this!
Juban Municipal Junior High School
Usagi Tsukino! You're late again!
It's so mean, how could they make
a fragile girl stand in the hall?
I'm hungry.
I did skip breakfast,
so... time to eat!
What are you doing, Miss Tsukino?!
That's why you get failing grades!
What?! 30 percent?!
Yup!
Usagi, I can't believe you.
You're a girl and you were going
to eat your lunch early?
But I'm a growing girl.
You're my best friend, Naru.
You understand, don't you?
Usagi, how did you do on your test?
Umino...
Can't you tell by how depressed
she is? Of course it was bad.
Oh, did that hurt? I'm sorry.
You don't have to be so upset!
I didn't get a perfect this time
because I didn't really try.
A test is like a game.
How annoying!
Oh! Did you hear that Sailor V
appeared again?
Sailor V?
Yeah. She caught the robbers
from the jewelry heist.
Wow!
Isn't it great?
What is a Sailor V?
Don't be so impressed if you
don't know her!
Sailor V is the heroine in a school
uniform that's been causing an uproar.
Sailor V.
There's a rumor that she's actually
a special agent from the
police department.
Oh, there's stuff like that now.
Must be the end of the century.
But gems are beautiful,
I'd understand why they'd
want to steal them.
I know what you mean.
I want a diamond ring.
I want ruby earrings.
I wish.
Oh yeah, our store has been having
a jewelry sale since yesterday.
Want to come?
Jewelry sale?
They'll have rings and stuff
that even we can buy.
Really? I'll go!
Okay, then come over
on your way home.
I'll definitely go. I wish school
would end soon.
Umm... Usagi...
Have you still not found the
legendary silver crystal?
No, my lady.
Our great ruler wants a plentiful
amount of energy.
If you cannot obtain the silver crystal,
then let us first give our
ruler human energy.
Queen Beryl.
Will you leave that duty
to me, Jadeite?
My minion, the monster Morga,
is already gathering human energy.
I will leave it to you, Jadeite.
Yes, my lady.
Oh, how pretty!
It's so cheap!
Wow, there are a lot of people.
Thank you for always choosing us.
Welcome! Welcome! Please feel free to try them on.
Mom's awfully in to it.
Welcome!
Maybe she's inspired.
Come on in. They're all on sale!
Foolish humans.
Give all your energy to our great ruler.
It's gathering, the energy
of the foolish humans
who are taken by the
brilliance of the gems.
Queen Beryl will be very pleased.
Morga, collect even more energy.
Yes, sir.
Mom.
Oh, welcome home Naru.
I brought a friend.
Hello.
Thank you for coming.
It's crowded, but please look around.
Thank you.
I know, since you are Naru's friend,
I'll give you a discount.
Really? I'm so lucky.
How about this diamond? It usually
goes for about 500,000 yen.
500,000 yen?
But, I'll lower it to 30,000 yen.
500,000 to 30,000!
Sold!
Wait! I'll buy it! It's mine!
Wow! Look at that!
500,000 to 30,000! I want it!
Why don't you ask your dad?
But I failed my English test.
Oh yeah...
And I've used up all of my
allowance for this month.
Be strong, Usagi.
I should have studied harder.
Oh, die!
Hey, that hurts, Dumpling Head.
What? Oh, I'm sorry...
30 percent!
Study harder, Dumpling Head.
It's none of your business!
What's with him?! I can't believe it.
What a weirdo.
Brand New Sailor V Game
Huh, Sailor V?
They made a game already?
It must be nice being Sailor V.
You don't have to worry about tests,
and I bet catching bad guys
feels pretty good.
But me on the other hand...
I don't want to take this home.
Usagi Tsukino, I've finally found you.
*Kenji Tsukino*
*Ikuko*
*Usagi*
*Shingo*
I'm home!
*Kenji Tsukino*
*Ikuko*
*Usagi*
*Shingo*
Oh, you're back. You're late.
Yeah, a bit.
I bumped into Umino.
He said you got your tests back.
What?
Umino said that he got a 95.
Oh, really? That's amazing!
Umino's got a big mouth.
And what did you get, Usagi?
Well umm. Umm, well...
Actually, that is...
Let me see.
Here.
Usagi!
Yes?
Getting such a bad score.
I'm not letting you in the house.
Mom!
I can't hear you.
Ouch!
What are you doing, dummy Usagi?
Did you get locked out again?
I want a better sister.
You're my younger brother.
Sailor V kick.
Ouch!
Mom! Please let me in.
That's strange. I'm feeling a bit faint.
I feel weak.
What's happening to everyone
all of a sudden? Mom?
Mom?
I've gathered quite a bit of energy.
Mom...
She finally let me in.
I'm tired from crying so much.
Mom didn't have to get that mad.
I don't feel like doing homework.
Maybe I'll take a nap.
It's good that I can fall asleep
so easily at times like this.
Hey, it's the cat with the
crescent bald spot.
It's not a bald spot. How rude.
It talked. A cat... A cat talked.
My name is Luna. I've been
looking for you, Usagi.
Oh, I need to thank you first.
Thank you very much.
You really helped me out by
taking the band-aid off.
I can't talk and my sensory powers
are dulled when I'm like that.
I was having trouble because
of that band-aid prank.
But thanks to you, I finally found you.
Good night.
Usagi, this is not a dream.
C'mon, Usagi!
Fine then, I'll wake you up!
There!
Usagi, this is a present for you.
Really, I can have this?
Usagi, there are weird things
happening in Tokyo right now.
All right! Thank you.
Usagi, there are weird things
happening in Tokyo right now.
Usagi, listen to me!
There are strange things happening
in Tokyo right now.
An enemy the police can't fight.
Usagi, you're going to fight
these enemies.
You are a chosen warrior.
And your other mission is to find
our princess with the others.
That sounds sorta cool.
You still don't believe me, do you?
No, I believe you, I believe you.
Really? Then say this.
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Okay.
No way! What is this? I've transformed.
What is this? What does
this mean? Tell me.
Help! Someone! Help me!
Help! It's my mom!
That's Naru's voice.
What does it mean?
Help! It's my mom!
That's Naru's voice.
What does it mean?
Now do you believe me?
I don't really get it, but Naru
seems to be in danger.
Usagi, you have become Sailor Moon.
Now go and save her quickly.
Help me!
I...
Stop it, Mom!
I'm not your mom!
Your mom is locked up
in the basement.
After I kill you, I'll send her to
the other world with you.
Get away from Naru!
Who are you?
Um, I'm the Sailor Warrior
of Love and Justice.
Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Sailor Moon? I've never heard
of such a thing.
Awaken! My slaves that gave their
energy to my great ruler.
Hey, what are you people?
Oh no! I'm bleeding!
What are you doing, Sailor Moon?
You have to fight. You have
to destroy that monster.
Why? Why is this happening to me?
I'm going home.
This is the end.
Who's there?
I am Tuxedo Mask.
Crying isn't going to solve
anything, Sailor Moon.
But I...
Stop crying.
Take the tiara and yell,
"Moon Tiara Action" and throw it!
Why do I have to do that?
Just hurry up and do it!
Moon Tiara Action!
No way!
Morga, you screwed up. You idiot!
Good job, Sailor Moon!
I'll remember this night.
You did well, Sailor Moon.
He's gorgeous.
Hey, I had a really wonderful
dream last night.
A warrior of justice named
Sailor Moon appeared
and destroyed this monster.
What? I had the same dream!
Me too!
How strange.
Hey, Usagi. Usagi. Listen!
Be quiet. I'm tired, so let me
sleep a little more.
Good night.
In my dream, you and I were together
Protected by the stars
When we were friends,
it didn't bother us
And we casually talked to each other
But there was a moment when
I noticed only you
I want to become prettier
right here and now
Something changes when
you fall in love
I close my eyes and check
to make sure
I want to convey the thrill I felt
when we held each other