Unforgivable! He is the number one
enemy of all junior high girls!
Impure fraternization!
It's just unforgivable!
For the crime of staining everyone's
favorite hangout with evil...
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino. I don't look like
a super heroine, but I am!
As you know, I transform myself
by using a peculiar brooch
and fight against bad guys.
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
And my friends are the smart
and sweet Ami Mizuno,
and a slightly quick-tempered
psychic girl, Rei Hino.
Both of them are so dependable,
I feel like I'll fall behind.
But anyway, I just have
to do my best!
Usagi is Frantic! Rei's First Date
It's a nice and quiet place.
Yup! Perfect for a date!
So, do you like it?
I'm a bit surprised you
know of a place like this.
Really? I always come here to read
when I don't have cram school.
Mr. Kunitachi.
Oh, Ami.
So, you take care of this
big park all by yourself?
Well, that will be coming
to an end soon.
What?
The land owner sold this park,
and it's apparently being turned
into a business district.
I had no idea.
When this park is gone, the birds and
animals will have nowhere to go.
It's troubling.
And it's such a nice park, too.
Well, there is nothing
I can do about it.
All right! I'm going to bring a
boyfriend here before it's gone.
Jubancho
Shopping District
Where has everyone gone today?!
Are you okay?
You don't look hurt.
What are you doing to my Luna?!
If she's your cat, keep
a better eye on her!
She almost got run over!
None of your business!
Luna isn't like your everyday
ordinary cat!
Stop it, Usagi.
That's right. He saved Luna,
so you should thank him.
Yeah, yeah.
That's right. He saved Luna,
so you should thank him.
Yeah, yeah.
Why are you both taking his side?!
Hey.
It's you, Chiba.
Yo, Motoki.
Motoki...
You know him?
Yeah, we both go to
the same college.
You're...
...a college student?!
The stars know everything.
O stars, grant me your
mysterious powers.
The beta star of Cygnus, Albireo,
is noticeably brighter
again after 120 years.
So, this is the man who will
be influenced by Albireo
and reach his peak energy level.
I shall take the greatest
energy of his life from him.
Shoot! Okay, another 100 yen!
Are you sure it's okay to
waste so much money?
Oh, don't worry about it.
Are you sure it's okay to
waste so much money?
Oh, don't worry about it.
Wow. So, Mamoru lives by himself?
Yeah, in an expensive
high-rise apartment.
After all, he is the son of a rich family.
If he goes to the same
college as you,
he goes to that really competitive
school, right?
Yeah, I suppose.
But, Rei, why are you asking
so much about him?
Oh, no reason!
Mamoru Chiba. He and I would be
a perfect match for each other.
I've decided!
I will go on a date with
Mamoru in that park!
Okay, this'll be the last time!
Are you okay, Rei?
I'm done for!
I wish there was some way
to protect this nature.
You will protect it.
What?
Who are you?
People have forgotten the boon
that nature bestows upon them.
It is time for you to teach those
conceited humans the wrath of nature.
Me?
That's right.
You.
My loyal monster,
possess this hat and take
this man's energy!
You will teach the humans
the wrath of nature. You.
What are these?! Help!
By using the power of the monster,
you can control the animals
and insects at will.
The more you use that power, the
more your energy will increase.
According to what Motoki told me,
he's supposed to come
this way after school.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't looking where I was going.
Not at all. I should have
paid more attention, too.
If you don't mind, I'll take you
out for tea as an apology.
My! All right, I will join you.
Good.
Oh, it would be nice.
For cake or bread,
come to our shop!
Juban Bakery
Oh, it would be nice.
For cake or bread,
come to our shop!
Juban Bakery
For cake or bread,
come to our shop!
Juban Bakery
I'll bump into him on purpose and
make an opportunity for myself!
Sheesh! You're going to
gain weight again!
This is nothing!
Oh, it's Rei!
You're right. I wonder
what she's doing?
Here he comes.
Now!
Are you okay?!
I don't know what she was doing,
but Rei's pretty clumsy.
Speak for yourself.
I'm all right.
Okay, glad to hear it.
What?!
Excuse me...
Oh? You're that dumpling
head's friend.
Yes. My name is Rei Hino.
Please just call me, Rei.
Are you okay?
Sure, I'm fine, but...
I'm sorry. I will take you out
for tea to make up for this.
To make up for what?
Oh, well...
For making you step on my head.
What?
Well, okay. I won't mind
having tea with you.
Really?!
Yeah.
Well, everything turned
out okay in the end.
What the hell is he doing?!
He's a college student and he's
walking arm-in-arm with Rei!
Usagi, I don't think Mamoru is
such a bad person, you know.
Don't be silly! That's
impure fraternization!
Even the student guide says
that's absolutely wrong!
Anyway, Rei's in danger!
We're following them!
Sheesh. She's just jealous,
plain and simple.
Excuse me...
Would you like some sugar?
No thanks, I'm fine.
Oh, of course not!
Then I won't either.
I wonder what they're talking about?
I wish I could go in.
It's your fault for spending all
your money on ice cream.
I know! I'll transform into
a waitress and...
No, you can't!
Why not?
Because you're supposed
to use that for justice!
Why not?
Because you're supposed
to use that for justice!
Oh, come on! Just for a little while!
Miss Usagi!
What are you doing?
Umino...
Umino, do you have any
money on you?
Yes, I do...
Then how about going on a
date with me right now?
What?! Really?!
I can't keep up with the
way she thinks.
Mamoru, I know of a
really nice place.
Would you like to go there with me?
Sure, I don't mind.
Really?!
Everything is going
according to plan.
Shoot! I can't hear them
from here either.
Ami.
Luna!
What's wrong? You don't
look very cheerful.
Yeah...
Well...
It seems the construction company
that was working on
the park just left.
As a result, the park will
stay as it is for now.
So, we would like you to continue
to be the park's caretaker.
What? The caretaker of this park?
Yes. He was the same
until yesterday, but...
You should not come to this park
without good reason from now on.
You people don't deserve to
enjoy the boons of nature.
I wonder what happened to him?
That construction company is pitiful!
There's no way animals and insects
would interfere with the construction!
What?! What are these?!
What's going on?
I'll never do anything to this
park again! Forgive me!
This place is filled with
a powerful evil aura!
What?!
This must be the work of
the Dark Kingdom!
What?!
This must be the work of
the Dark Kingdom!
Oh, no.
Then Mr. Kunitachi could also be...
I didn't know there was a
park like this in this city.
But this park is going to
be torn down soon.
I heard they're turning it
into a business district.
I see.
It's such a nice park surrounded
by beautiful nature.
You think so too, Mamoru?
Yes. People should think about
taking better care of nature.
Mamoru...
What could they be chatting about?!
I'll just have to get closer to them.
Usagi, you're too bold.
This is not the place for...
We should have a pure relationship,
like good junior high kids.
But maybe a kiss wouldn't hurt!
Huh? Where did you go, Miss Usagi?!
Usagi!
Oh, so you're both here, too.
We can't leave those
two alone after all.
Don't be ridiculous!
Usagi, something terrible is going
on in this park right now!
Something terrible?
You guys again!
Mr. Kunitachi!
Foolish humans!
You people forgot the boon that
nature provided you with,
and the only way you can atone
for it is with your deaths!
The energy level has peaked!
Do it, Petasos!
Mr. Kunitachi...
All animals in this park,
massacre the humans!
Unforgivable! Mercury Power Makeup!
Usagi, don't just stand there!
I know that!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Mamoru, what is wrong?
What's this?!
What are these?!
Oh, help me!
Bubble
Spray!
The animals have been weakened!
Prepare yourself!
Mercury's on a roll!
Then I will use... Hand Flower!
Watch out!
Sailor Moon!
Petasos Rope!
Are you okay?
Yes, I am. But you weren't
feeling well...
Oh, it was nothing serious.
All right.
I sense a powerful evil aura.
Mamoru, stay here!
I'll be right back!
Sailor Mercury!
I will squeeze you to death first.
Mr. Kunitachi...
I can't forgive you!
Fire Soul!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Are you okay?
Can't you help me in a better way?
Is that any way to talk to someone
who just rescued you?!
I see. So, she's the one who
interrupted my date.
I can't forgive you for taking advantage
of Mr. Kunitachi's feelings!
You'll pay a heavy price for staining
everyone's favorite hangout with evil.
In the name of the moon,
we will punish you!
Hey, that's my line!
Fine, then! I'll take care of all
three of you together!
Tuxedo Mask!
Now's your chance, Sailor Moon!
Yes!
Moon Tiara Action!
Good-bye, sailor warriors!
He's so dreamy.
Ami, what have I been doing?
It's okay now. Don't worry. You
were just having a bad dream.
Good grief. That was awful.
Mamoru! Is it okay for
you to get up?
Yeah, I'm completely fine now.
Maybe Mamoru really is Tuxedo Mask.
There's no way this guy
can be Tuxedo Mask!
Huh? What's this Tuxedo Mask?
Oh, no, it's nothing at all.
He has to be! Mamoru is
surely Tuxedo Mask.
Oh, Miss Usagi!
Oh, Umino...
I looked everywhere for you.
Now, let us continue our date.
Umino, don't go making up stories!
What are you talking about?
You're the one who asked me out!
Really? Good going.
That's not it!
I'm telling you, it's not!
In my dream, you and I were together
Protected by the stars
When we were friends,
it didn't bother us
And we casually talked to each other
But there was a moment when
I noticed only you
I want to become prettier
right here and now
Something changes when
you fall in love
I close my eyes and check
to make sure
I want to convey the thrill I felt
when we held each other