What?! Really?!
We have just received information
that Rei's Grandpa has turned
into a monster.
No way! Then will Rei also
become a monster?!
Anyone who turns my favorite Grandpa
and Rei into monsters...
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino.
As you know, I'm a sailor warrior of
love and justice, Sailor Moon.
But it's not easy, you know.
I have to get a hold of the
legendary Silver Crystal
before the bad guys get it,
but to do that, I have to find the
seven rainbow crystals!
Oh, man. But anyhow, we've got
four sailor warriors now,
so it'll work out somehow.
Grandpa Goes Crazy, Rei's in Jeopardy
Oh, what a beautiful moon!
On a night like this,
some moon-gazing dumplings and
a cup of sake would be great.
Who are you?!
Zoi!
An evil aura...
So, this old man is one of the Seven
Monsters, just as I thought.
Be patient, I will take the rainbow
crystal out of your body soon.
Damn evil spirit!
Now, it is time to come back
to life, monster Jijii!
You!
I thought you were just
a decrepit old man,
but that wasn't bad!
Zoi!
What?! Hey, stop it!
I'm not raw garbage!
Grandpa!
Phobos?! Deimos?!
Are you okay? What in
the world happened?
What the heck? Talk about noisy.
Who are you?!
My... My name is Yuichiro Kumada!
Please, make me your apprentice!
What?
Inside this old man's body,
the rainbow crystal has
begun to awaken.
Just you wait,
I will make sure to take the
rainbow crystal soon.
Hikawa Shrine
What? Your Grandpa's acting weird?
Yeah.
Yuichiro, follow me!
What?! Do I have to do
something like this?!
Yes, Sir!
Okay, then!
Is this how I should be
spending my youth?
I'm out.
Oh!
Come on, wake up!
Grandpa, what's going on?!
Grandpa, you look cute in that!
Stop it!
You stupid, clumsy slowpoke!
You're a disgrace to this shrine!
Who is he?
He is Yuichiro Kumada. He became
an apprentice to Grandpa.
Oh, wow.
Yuichiro, are you okay?
Oh...
Miss Rei, you look wonderful
in a uniform, too.
Did you hit your head or something?
How could you, Grandpa?!
Shut up! Training to become
a Shinto priest is tough!
You can't do it with a soft attitude!
Training is all about mental strength!
What am I to do?!
The only person who'll take
over the shrine is you,
my granddaughter! I am so alone!
See? He's become emotionally
unstable these days.
It's weird!
No, it is not weird!
It is only natural that the
training is tough!
I will do it! I will endure
any kind of training!
All right! You totally fell for it!
Grandpa!
Usagi!
Wasn't that fun?!
Yeah, I love this kind of stuff!
You're the only one who
understands my jokes!
Grandpa! Enough is enough!
Excuse me, but if you're
concerned about me...
You be quiet!
But...
Shut up!
Yes, Ma'am!
If you keep doing these stupid things,
everyone's trust in our miracle-working
shrine will be destroyed!
Now, now, you shouldn't be
so uptight all the time.
You have to have a little
sense of fun!
That's right!
Usagi, this is our shrine's problem.
So, keep your nose out of it.
Rei's being mean to me!
Usagi, don't cry over
such a little thing.
But... But...
And you, too, Rei. You didn't have
to shove Usagi like that.
Rei, you meanie!
Rei! Honestly! If this is how
everyone's going to be,
I'll be better off studying
at cram school! Bye!
I think I'll going to kung-fu training.
What?
What's with them?! They won't even
seriously discuss the problem!
What?
What's with them?! They won't even
seriously discuss the problem!
Do whatever you want!
Excuse me, Miss Rei...
Shut up!
Yes, Ma'am!
So, what did you want to talk about?
About my Master...
Oh, please! Grandpa is no master!
The weather changes easily
in the autumn.
What?
The biorhythm of the mind and
body tend to become
disturbed more easily...
What are you trying to say?
I'm saying that once the weather
returns to normal,
Master's emotions may
also settle down.
Perhaps it would be better
to give him some time
and watch how things go.
Was it something I said?
Thanks!
You seem like you'll be more
dependable than you look.
What?!
Girl friends are no good. They say,
they're your friends,
but when you really need them,
they're so uncaring.
Rei looks like she's doing
pretty good over there.
Okay! Usagi's going
to be their cupid!
Usagi, stick your nose in where
it doesn't belong,
and she'll hate you even more.
Are you kidding?! This is my chance
to patch things up with Rei.
As usual, she gets hung up on
her own ideas so easily.
Ta-da!
Oh, Usagi!
You shouldn't use the transforming
pen for something like this!
Moon Power! Turn me into
a fortune-teller of love!
It's perfect!
Oh, she's just hopeless!
Ahem!
Just sit there and let me do my job,
for an accurate fortune.
I'm a wandering fortune-teller of love!
I shall now tell your fortune.
What?!
Oh, boy!
If the two of you kiss right now,
your love will come true!
Oh, no...
Kiss?!
This is ridiculous! Let's go!
Yes, Ma'am!
Oh, no, it didn't work.
Just what are you trying
to do, Usagi?!
Oops! You knew?
If you recall, I have Mamoru!
Don't do anything funny!
I am really never talking
to you again!
Never talk...
See? I told you so.
I made Rei mad again.
Cheer up.
Rei gets mad easily, but she
also forgets easily.
By tomorrow she'll be friends
with you again.
But she said she'd never
talk to me again!
She just said that in anger
because you pulled that weird stunt!
Oh, this rice cake filled with sweet
bean jam filling is delicious!
I can't think about rice cakes
at a time like this.
It's really delicious!
This really is yummy!
Right?
Oh, I know! I'll take
some to Rei, too!
I'll make it up to Rei with
these tasty rice cakes!
It's a good idea!
Are you sure? I think you'll just end
up making her mad again.
Don't worry, everything
will be okey-dokey!
You know, you really shouldn't!
Usagi is just so thick headed.
Training! Training! Training!
Miss Rei, I'll do my best!
Thanks.
Training!
Say, Phobos, Deimos, what
do you guys think?
Training! Training!
Say, Phobos, Deimos, what
do you guys think?
I won't give up!
Is Grandpa really acting weird
because of the weather?
Training! Training!
Is Grandpa really acting weird
because of the weather?
Training... Ouch!
So, you have appeared
again, evil spirit!
Tonight, I will be taking
that rainbow crystal.
Zoi!
What is this?! The aura
of an evil spirit!
Zoi!
It's time for you to give up.
The rainbow crystal is mine.
You're...
Tuxedo Mask!
I will be taking that!
Monster Jijii! Do away
with Tuxedo Mask!
This is...
Jijii!
Tuxedo Mask, you shall fall
prey to the monster Jijii!
Stop!
Jijii!
Zoisite! You coward! Fight me!
A monster!
Jijii!
Shoot! I've lost sight of him!
Tuxedo Mask. It's too bad, but
this rainbow crystal is mine.
Miss Rei, there's a monster
in the shrine!
Oh! Don't look!
I saw her!
This is no time to be worrying
about that!
I do worry, okay?!
We have to hurry and run!
Jijii!
What's wrong? Oh! A monster!
What's a monster doing here?!
Jijii!
Yuichiro!
Please run, quickly!
If it's for you, Miss Rei,
I won't mind dying!
Jijii!
Why you!
Miss Rei, please run!
Yuichiro!
Rin, Pyo, Tou, Sha, Kai,
Jin, Retsu, Zai, Zen!
Jijii!
Rei!
Grandpa?! That monster is Grandpa?
Jijii!
What in the world happened
to you, Grandpa?!
Jijii!
Grandpa...
Wait!
Jijii!
Grandpa, please wake up!
I'm your beloved granddaughter, Rei!
Jijii!
Usually, in situations like this,
he'll awaken to the little bit of
human heart left in him,
and he should hesitate to attack.
Jijii!
Grandpa!
This isn't a usual situation!
Jijii!
Stop right there!
I won't forgive you for being mean
to my dear friend, Rei!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
I'm a sailor warrior of love and
justice, Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Jijii!
Thanks, you saved me!
It's okay, you don't need
to thank me.
By the way, these rice cakes
are yummy! Try one!
You're such a dummy! This is no
time to be eating rice cakes!
Oh, right. Okay!
Wait! That monster is my grandpa!
What?! No way! That's Grandpa?!
I get it! His sudden personality change
was a symptom of this!
Jijii!
What do we do now?!
Rei, do something!
The monster's my favorite Grandpa!
I don't know what to do!
Rei, use the talisman! Immobilize
the monster with the talisman!
Jijii!
Okay!
Wake up already, Grandpa!
Be gone, evil spirit!
Sailor Moon, now! Hurry!
Jijii!
Grandpa! Please go back
to being a good boy!
Moon Healing Escalation!
Refresh!
Grandpa!
I'm glad.
Yeah.
Oh, Mako.
Hikawa Shrine
Hey, what are you doing here so late?
Well, Rei and Usagi split up
after fighting, right?
So, I thought I'd talk to Rei about
patching things up with her.
Oh, you, too?
What?! Then, you, too?
Female friendships tend to break
easily once cracked,
so I thought they should repair
things while it's still early.
Yes!
You're right!
These rice cakes with sweet bean
jam filling are delicious!
Aren't they, though?!
But where did that weird monster go?
Weird monster?
I can't believe you, Grandpa!
Don't you remember anything?
There's no such things as
monsters! Right, Usagi?
Yuichiro, are you sure you weren't
half-asleep and dreaming?
I bet you were!
I don't know. It didn't
seem like a dream.
Uh-oh!
I don't know. It didn't
seem like a dream.
Uh-oh!
Well, it doesn't matter.
Yuichiro...
What?
You seem like a stupid slowpoke,
but you're actually brave
and kind, aren't you?
This is youth! I'm living my youth
to the maximum right now!
Rei, have you fallen in
love with Yuichiro?
Don't be ridiculous! That's not it!
Grandpa's always yelling at him,
so I just felt sorry for him and
kissed him as consolation!
How sweet!
You've got the wrong idea!
Rei! I won't let you marry
the likes of Yuichiro!
Marriage! Marriage!
Don't say such weird things!
Marriage?!
Don't even think about it!
Stop right there!
What?
What's going on?
It's sure nice. Rei's getting married!
I am not!
Rei and Usagi are back to
being friends again.
It looks like there was nothing
to worry about.
You can't get married!
Hiru ni wa hana no kaori
Yoru ni wa hoshi no matataki
Soko wa daremo shiranai sekai nano
Shiroi kutsu o narashite
Shiroi tsuki no hashi watatte
Amai kisu no yume o miteru
ohimesama ga sunde iru no
Inori o sasagete moon
Kitto shiawase ni shitekureru
Maware maware tsuki no
merry-go-round
Suzushige na glass no
dress hirugaeshite
Itsudatte mimamotte iru wa
Moon moon princess