Endymion... Mother... Usagi
has learned everything.
Kunzite! You won't always get
your way in this world!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short
sunzen ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta no
miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
Tuxedo Mask, where are you?
Usagi, wake up! Big news!
Tuxedo Mask, I love you!
Usagi, Sailor Venus and Artemis
found the entrance
that leads to the Dark
Kingdom's hideout!
What did you say?!
Usagi's Awakening!
A Message From the Distant Past
I finally found it!
Good work, Sailor Venus!
Here we go!
Is this...
Let's take a look!
Energy?!
I would love to welcome you ladies
to the Dark Kingdom,
but preparations to receive you
are not ready yet.
So I will take you somewhere
more fun.
Give me a break!
Supreme
Thunder!
Sailor Moon!
If you quietly hand over
the Silver Crystal,
I will let you live!
I'm thinking the same, Kunzite!
If you tell me what you've done
with Tuxedo Mask,
I won't punish you!
What impudence!
I will send you to the chaotic world
of multiple dimensions!
Chaotic world of multiple dimensions?
It may be the primitive era in Africa
when dinosaurs roamed.
Or it could be the era in Europe
when fierce wars broke out.
I don't wanna be sent to a
messed-up world like that!
The Silver Crystal will be mine!
Damn!
Where are we?
These are the ruins of
Silver Millennium,
the land of gods that once attained
the pinnacle of glory.
Silver Millennium?
Who are...
I am here to bring you a message
from the distant past.
I am the incarnation of the
Moon Goddess, Serene.
I am the Queen of Silver Millennium,
Queen Serenity.
I am your mother.
What?! You're my mom?!
What do you mean by that?
I revived Luna and Artemis
from their cold sleep,
had them make contact with you
and watched over all of you.
We are long-living life forms
born on the moon.
Our mission is to protect the sacred
will passed down to us
on the moon, the legendary
Silver Crystal,
and to watch over and aid
the progression of Earth's evolution.
Remember, Serenity...
of the time when you were living
as the princess of the moon.
Serenity, you adored the
green trees and wind
of the beautiful blue Earth,
and often gazed up at it.
Then you found love.
Princess Serenity!
Prince Endymion!
Please pardon me for being
late to the ball.
I have been waiting for you.
Something terrible has happened.
What?
Most of us on Earth have been
brainwashed by Beryl.
Beryl?
Beryl has been possessed by
an evil energy called Metalia.
And now, she is taking advantage of
the humans' yearning for the
longevity of your people,
and getting ready to attack the moon!
Who's there?!
At the ball...
Endymion...
Where did everyone else go?!
Even if it's only us,
we have to find the Dark
Kingdom's hideout!
What is this place?!
The North Pole?!
Princess, may I?
Endymion.
There is no doubt that a bitter war
is about to break out
between your people and
us Earth people.
I will be your future enemy,
so it would be bad for my identity
to be known now.
So, please pardon my appearance.
You will be my enemy?
Metalia is not a human being.
She is a mass of evil energy.
Beryl is a witch.
By using the power of Metalia,
she is trying to conquer
the moon and Earth.
If we do nothing, this moon
will be destroyed.
We must not waste a moment
in obliterating Metalia,
who possesses an enormous
amount of evil energy,
and crushing Beryl's ambitions!
I would like your help in this, Serenity.
Will you believe what I just told you?
Yes.
Serenity...
Endymion...
It's terrible! It's terrible!
The people of Earth are attacking us!
Bubble
Spray!
Fire
Soul!
Supreme
Thunder!
Crescent Beam!
Starting today, I will rule both
Earth and the moon!
I will not allow anyone to defy me!
Our beloved Metalia, this is the
birth of our Dark Kingdom!
So, you are Princess Serenity?
I will destroy that pretty face of yours!
Beryl, I will not forgive you
if you lay even a single finger
on the princess!
Endymion!
Why do you protect the
princess of the moon?
You are the prince of Earth.
If you just marry me,
you could be king of both
the moon and Earth!
Beryl, you are being misguided
by Metalia,
who possesses evil energy.
Wake up! Rid yourself of the evil mind!
Shut up! I will kill you, too!
Endymion!
Serenity!
Stay back!
Princess Serenity...
She's dead! The Moon
Princess is dead!
Serenity...
Queen Serenity, if you use the
Silver Crystal, your life...
My life is nothing compared to peace
on the moon and Earth.
Moon Healing Escalation!
What?!
Lady Metalia!
Artemis, hang in there!
I'm fine. What about you, Luna?
No, I'm fine. I can't die until
we find their hideout!
This is...
We've found it!
Finally, we've found the entrance
to the Dark Kingdom's hideout!
We need to tell everyone right away!
But it is already too late.
Luna, Artemis...
Yes.
The Silver Crystal can be
used for peace
if it is used with the energy
of a good heart.
But, if it is used with the energy
of an evil heart,
it will become a terrible weapon.
Queen Serenity!
I have been able to seal Metalia
away with the Silver Crystal,
but there is no knowing when
she might be revived again.
And this Crescent Moon Wand
can only be used by a descendant
of this kingdom.
If Metalia should return to life
again in the future,
give this to Princess Serenity and
protect the peaceful world.
Yes, my lady.
Princess Serenity and all
of our sailor warriors,
may your love be fulfilled
in the future on Earth.
In the future on Earth...
...please live happy lives.
Queen Serenity!
We...
traveled...
into the past.
Now, we know why we're
Sailor Warriors.
Yes.
Mother...
Help!
Luna!
Artemis!
Sailor...
I won't let you hurt them!
Sailor Moon?! It can't be!
I sent you to the chaotic world
of multiple dimensions!
You won't always get your way
in this world!
Thanks to you, we've recovered
our past memories!
So, we will...
thank you now!
Shut up!
Don't give me that sass! You're still
wet behind the ears!
Give back Tuxedo Mask...
no, Endymion!
I won't mind returning him to you
if you quietly hand over
the Silver Crystal.
Sailor Moon!
You're more sinister than I imagined!
I'll never forgive you!
We are inside my own space.
Will your attacks still work
against me, I wonder?
Everyone, we have to combine
our powers!
Protect Sailor Moon!
Venus Power!
Mercury Power!
Mars Power!
Jupiter Power!
Everyone!
Even if you repaid us with nicer
haute couture dresses,
I would never forgive you for
cutting up a girl's clothes!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Moon Healing Escalation!
I am one of the Great Four of
the Dark Kingdom, Kunzite!
On my pride, I will not yell, "Refresh!"
What?!
Impossible!
With my own weapon...
Zoisite, guide me to the world
where your soul is drifting!
Sailor Moon, that was
tremendous power.
She's different than usual.
Luna, please hang in there.
Usagi... No, Sailor Moon...
No, Serenity, the Dark
Kingdom's hideout
is at D-Point in the North Pole.
If you don't hurry, the sunspot
will expand!
We have no choice but to
launch a surprise attack!
Okay! We'll march into the
Dark Kingdom right away!
Right, everyone?!
Yes!
In the name of the moon,
we will punish you!
Hiru ni wa hana no kaori
Yoru ni wa hoshi no matataki
Soko wa daremo shiranai sekai nano
Shiroi kutsu o narashite
Shiroi tsuki no hashi watatte
Amai kisu no yume o miteru
ohimesama ga sunde iru no
Inori o sasagete moon
Kitto shiawase ni shitekureru
Maware maware tsuki no
merry-go-round
Suzushige na glass no
dress hirugaeshite
Itsudatte mimamotte iru wa
Moon moon princess