Einstein and Hawking.
Geniuses are valuable because they
help make the world more peaceful.
I won't let them fall into
the hands of evil!
In the name of the moon, Sailor Moon
will punish you.
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino, 14 years old.
I'm in the 8th grade.
I'm clumsier than others and a bit
of a crybaby. That's about it.
One day, a strange black cat,
Luna, appeared
and gave me a peculiar transforming
brooch and made me a sailor warrior.
But, she wants me to fight
against bad guys.
That makes me really nervous.
Oh well, I guess everything
will be okay.
Is the Genius Girl a Monster?
Brainwashing School of Terror
Right now, the children of Japan
are forced to study day after day
and they are suffering.
I have heard that there are
more and more mothers
who are called "academic moms" who
push their children mercilessly.
The parents are desperate
to send their children
to the best kindergarten,
the best primary school,
the best junior high school,
the best high school
and the best college.
And? What about after graduating
from the best college?
What do they do?
I am not quite certain.
I will leave it to you.
Yes, my lady.
Girls 5
Usagi!
Oh, Mom. Look! This is so funny!
This is no time to be laughing.
How did you do on that mock exam?
Oh, that? The results are
coming out tomorrow.
I can't believe you asked.
Usagi, I won't ask for the impossible.
But please, just don't fail.
No matter what, if there's
a kid in first place,
there's always a kid in last place too!
It's not fair to yell at that kid just
because her grades are bad!
You don't study, but you're always
ready with an excuse.
I'm the one who wants to cry!
Good girl. It's about time
you started studying.
Obviously, you don't care about me.
It must be nice to be a cat.
What are you talking about?
Oh, I wish I could be a cat.
Maybe, you don't know,
but I've got lots to do,
like finding the princess.
Oh, you're reading a comic book!
I wish you would put more effort
into finding the princess too.
But...
Find the princess and fight
against the enemy.
That is your fate and
you can't escape it.
You can't do this to me!
Besides, who is this enemy anyway?
Something very evil that's not human.
I don't really get it.
To be honest, I don't really know
who they are either.
Please try the Sailor V game.
Sailor V
GAME
Please try the Sailor V game.
Sailor V
GAME
Code name 0091. This is Luna.
My secret password is "The rabbit
on the moon makes rice cakes."
"The moon rice cakes are sticky."
"When I grilled them,
they puffed up."
Have you found the princess?
Not yet. I still have no clue
where she is.
I see.
Sailor Moon is not as dependable
as I thought she would be.
I understand; do not grumble so.
Yes. By the way, I sensed a new
and strange energy.
This is her.
It could be another monster
sent by our enemy.
That's what I thought.
Investigate her quickly.
Yes, I will.
National Mock Exam Ranking Results
It's Ami Mizuno from Class 5 again!
1. Ami Mizuno
2. Eisaku Yoshida
3. Takashi Kitano
4. Momoe Yamada
1. Ami Mizuno
2. Eisaku Yoshida
3. Takashi Kitano
4. Momoe Yamada
Just what you'd expect from a genius!
1. Ami Mizuno
2. Eisaku Yoshida
3. Takashi Kitano
4. Momoe Yamada
As expected, Ami Mizuno's
at the top of our class.
Not only that, she's the best
in the country!
What?! The best in the country?
According to rumors...
Her IQ is supposedly 300.
Wow, she really is a genius.
Yes.
By the way, don't pop up suddenly
from such weird places!
Oh, it's Miss Mizuno!
I heard she attends
Crystal Cram School.
Hey, that's the new place
they just built, right?
My mom told me that
it's really expensive.
I heard that Miss Mizuno's mom
is a doctor.
They're probably rich.
However, she's on a scholarship,
so she's attending for free!
But she's got a bad attitude.
It's like she thinks she's better
than everybody else.
Oh, I can't stand people like that.
It's such a nice day!
Yeah, it is!
But, it must be nice to be so smart.
I always have to worry that Mom's
going to kill me.
Usagi! It's about time you started
going to a cram school!
No! No!
Usagi! It's about time you started
going to a cram school!
Oh, Miss Mizuno.
A cat?
I sense a strange energy
coming from this girl.
Oh, now's not the time!
You're so soft.
If only we didn't live in
a high-rise apartment,
I could get a nice cat too.
Luna!
Sorry, are you okay?
Is that your cat?
Yeah.
Since she came from the sky,
I thought she was an angel.
Luna an angel?
She's sweeter than I thought.
You're Miss Ami Mizuno
from Class 5, right?
I'm Usagi Tsukino from Class 1.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
This cat's name is Luna.
Luna? It means "moon", right?
You are a genius! You're the first
to know that right away!
If I become friends with her, I can get
her to help me study for exams.
Usagi.
She could be a monster sent by
the enemy. So, be careful.
No way!
What's wrong? Laughing so suddenly?
Oh, it's nothing.
By the way, Miss Mizuno,
do you play games?
No, I've never tried before.
Then let's play some. I'll teach you
how to play.
And in exchange, when
tests come up...
Don't worry, Luna. I think you're
thinking too much.
Obviously, something's
wrong with me today.
Miss Mizuno, do you
want to try? It's fun.
But it looks difficult.
You're very observant! This game
really is pretty hard.
So, you'd be doing good if you can
score 500 points on your first try.
You're pretty good!
Really?
Wow! Amazing!
No way.
Wow, she got the highest score.
Huh? What? Oh, my...
Hi, Usagi. I didn't know you were here.
Yes!
Wow, she's amazing!
I know.
There goes my help on exams...
Oh, look at the time!
I'm sorry, Miss Tsukino, I have
to go to cram school!
No, I'm the one who should apologize.
I didn't know you had
cram school today.
I go everyday.
Everyday?
I don't have any talents
other than studying.
Well, thank you. I'll see you again.
Bye!
I feel like we live in completely
different worlds.
Usagi.
Yes!
By any chance...
Yes, what is it?
I think this belongs to your friend.
Oh, is that all?
Oh, nothing.
I'll make sure she gets it!
Crystal Cram School
Ami Mizuno
Crystal Cram
School
Stupid human beings.
Keep studying and provide us
with your brain energy.
Oh? My floppy's not here.
Did I drop it somewhere?
Oh, well. I don't use it much anyway.
Miss Mizuno.
Use the Crystal Disk and study hard.
You're on a scholarship,
so you mustn't be lazy.
Yes, Ma'am.
I have high expectations of you.
I hate to say it, but that disk
gives me a headache.
"If you use our newly developed
Crystal Disks,"
"even you can be a genius!"
So, is this the Crystal Disk?
Usagi, be careful.
I'm just going to return this disk.
You worry too much.
Are you finally in the mood to study
a little, dumpling head?
You again!
Why do you always show up
at the weirdest times?!
That's not my problem.
By the way, wasn't that cat
just talking?
Are you kidding? Cats can't talk!
You're so silly!
That was so close. It'd be big
trouble if he found out.
Oh, I was in a hurry and
forgot to return this.
It's all his fault!
Usagi, let's go to the computer
lab at school.
Why?
I want to check out that disk.
You think this is suspicious?
I'll just warn you now. I don't know
how to use a computer.
Luna, you are something!
Knowing how to use a computer is
normal these days, Miss Usagi.
Oh, really?
Look! I thought so.
Oh, no! What is this sound?!
Offer the energy of your brain and
knowledge to our great ruler,
and become our loyal followers.
This is a brainwashing program!
And become our loyal followers.
It can't be!
So, she is a monster!
Crystal Cram
School
I still can't believe it.
Crystal Cram
School
But it's a fact! Get ready!
Okay.
Moon Power!
Turn me into a doctor who works
at a university hospital!
I heard someone is sick here!
Everyone, get away from
the computers right now!
Who are you?! Don't interrupt
our studies!
So, you are a monster!
Huh? What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
Transform into Sailor Moon!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
No way!
What?!
I am the monster of
knowledge, Garoben!
This genius girl is going to
sacrifice her brain energy
to our great ruler!
Which means Miss Mizuno
isn't a monster after all!
That's weird.
Stop this, evil villain!
Geniuses are valuable because they
help make the world more peaceful.
I won't let them fall into
the hands of evil!
Sailor warrior of love and
justice, Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you.
Question number one!
Genius Newton question.
Why do apples fall from trees?
How should I know? Ask
the apples, not me!
You idiot! If you don't know
the answer, take this!
You idiot!
I know! Because a hurricane came!
Oh! Luna!
I can't believe you! It's because
the Earth has gravity!
Because the Earth has gravity!
Then question number two!
What is gravity? Explain in
less than 50 words!
That's impossible!
If you cannot answer,
this is what happens.
What?! No way!
Come on, wait a minute!
Now is my chance!
Give up your genius brain energy!
It's not absorbing her energy.
Why is that?
You didn't use the Crystal Disk,
did you?!
You should study on your own
without using machines!
You impudent little...
What... What is this?!
That mark is...
I see! That strange energy was
from a sailor warrior...
Then, I'll just take your brain instead!
Prepare yourself!
Ami!
Use this!
Say, "Mercury Power Makeup!"
Mercury Power Makeup!
So, Ami is the second sailor warrior,
Sailor Mercury.
Ami?
Say, "Bubble Spray!"
Bubble
Spray!
What?!
Where did she go?
I'm getting cold.
What?
Shoot!
I have you now!
You fell for it!
Shoot!
Now, Sailor Moon!
Okay!
Moon Tiara Action!
Everyone, it's okay now!
I...
Yes, you're the second sailor
warrior, Sailor Mercury.
Sailor Mercury!
Sorry for mistaking you
for a monster.
That's okay.
But it's reassuring to have you
as one of us. Right, Luna?
Definitely.
Oh, thank you.
Especially when I need
to get ready for tests.
Usagi.
Yes?
Once again, I'm glad to meet you.
Let's work together, so we
can beat the bad guys!
Me too! I'm glad I met you!
She's such a tough girl, I think
I might not be able to keep up.
Yume no naka futari de ita yo ne
Hoshi tachi ni mamorarete
Tomodachi no toki ni wa ki ni sezu
Nanigenaku hanashite ita kedo
Anata dake ki ni naru
shunkan ga atta no
Motto kirei ni ima sugu naritai
Koi suru to nanika ga kawaru ne
Me o tojite tashikamete
Dakishimeta tokimeki sono
mama kono omoi tsutaetai