I am so happy!
We haven't gone to a hot spring
with the whole family in a long time!
What?! Why does a monster have
to follow us here, too?!
How dare you ruin our quality time
together as a family?!
I'll never, never forgive you!
In the name of Dad, Sailor Moon
will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short
sunzen ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta no
miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
It's such a nice day!
Since you have today
and tomorrow off,
you're going to thoroughly study
how to be a princess.
Okay, Usagi?
Hey, Usagi?
Wow, talk about unusual.
Did she get up already?
There's no one here.
Good morning, Luna!
Actually, the whole family has decided
to go to a hot spring!
We'll be back by tomorrow night,
so keep an eye on the house for us!
I'll bring back sweet bean jam buns!
Signed Usagi.
Usagi!
The Legendary Lake Monster!
Usagi's Family Ties
Sis, you're nuts!
Sneaking out of the house
so our pet won't notice!
What the heck are you thinking?!
Well, I've got my reasons for it.
Come on! Right there!
Shoot right there!
But it's been so long since
we've traveled together!
Even though it's like we're old people,
spending a night at a
remote hot spring.
Oh! What are you doing?!
Just let me do it!
What are you doing?! Give it back!
Oh, come on!
Oh, no! It's gonna break!
I can't believe you!
What's the matter, panicking
like that, Usagi?
I get it. Did you get it from a guy
you like or something?
Huh? Well, I guess you could say that.
What?!
Wait, Dad! The wheel! The wheel!
Usagi! Are you dating someone
behind my back?!
No! It's not like that!
Dear! Keep your eyes ahead! Ahead!
Oh, so you're not dating!
Of course, not. There's no way
you would be.
Wow, it's so beautiful!
It's kind of romantic.
There really isn't anything here.
The truth is, this lake
is where your mom and I met,
and it holds a lot of beautiful
memories for us.
Oh, Dear...
Mamoru's music box...
Mamoru...
Usagi, we're gonna get going soon.
Is something wrong, Usagi?
No, it's nothing.
So, is this the lake
where you detected an unusual
energy reading?
It is similar to the power
of our monsters,
but it is producing a slightly different
and very strong energy reading.
Endymion, start investigating
right away.
Yes, my lady.
Queen Beryl.
Lately, he has been acting
increasingly suspicious.
Could he possibly have begun
to notice
that his memories have been erased?
I doubt it.
But Kunzite, just in case,
follow him and keep an eye
on his actions.
Understood, my lady.
Endymion is completely
under my control.
It would be impossible for him
to question his past, but...
Wow! What a great view!
What a great view!
A remote hot spring inn isn't
so bad after all, is it?
Oh, Shingo. What are you doing?
Hurry up and get in! The water's fine!
But I don't wanna be in a mixed bath.
What are you being so shy about?
It's just us family here.
If you don't hurry, you'll catch a cold.
Okay...
Gotcha!
Stop it!
It's mine now!
Shingo! Give that back!
Usagi! Enough is enough!
It's okay, just let them be.
Hey, give it back!
Haha! Come and get it!
Hey, Shingo!
Wow! What a nice view! The lake's
right in front of us!
You let your guard down!
What's wrong?
Look, there's somebody by the lake.
Over there.
What? Where?
It can't be!
It is Mamoru.
Oh, wait!
Sis!
What's she in such a hurry about?
Mamoru!
It's not him.
The music box is playing again.
Mamoru!
That melody... Why does it throw
my heart into confusion?
Mamoru! It's me, Usagi!
Please! Don't pretend you
don't know me...
Mamoru? Usagi? I do not know them.
Those names have nothing
to do with me.
You can't mean that! Mamoru!
It's me! Don't you recognize me?!
Usagi!
Mom...
Mamoru...
Usagi, what's the matter?
You disappeared so suddenly.
No, it's nothing.
Oh, the "Legendary Lovers".
So, this is what you were looking at.
What? Legendary?
It's an old story that's been passed
down through the generations.
A maiden of the Heavens
had come down to Earth,
and a youth of the land
fell in love with her.
But a girl, who adored that youth,
turned into a monster
in a fit of jealousy.
And she attacked the villagers
indiscriminately.
The maiden from the Heavens
and the youth
sealed the monster in this lake
with the power of their love.
And having exhausted their energy,
they rose up to the Heavens together.
That's the legend of their love.
Sealed the monster in this lake...
Come on, let's go back.
Or you'll catch cold.
Mom!
You're such a baby.
Say, Usagi?
If you find somebody you love...
What?
If you find somebody you love,
bring him home, and introduce him
to your dad and me, okay?
Okay, I will.
Someday, I will.
I'll introduce you to him.
A monster sealed in this lake...
So, that is the origin of
the unusual energy.
Endymion...
So, he has already found out the truth
behind the mysterious energy.
O vengeful soul, sealed
within this lake,
I command thee to rise once again!
Come forth, ancient spirit!
Give him back!
So, Endymion has awakened
the ancient soul
that was sealed within the lake.
What will you do now?
Give him back!
Wait! Where are you going?!
Mamoru, we are so close, and yet...
Usagi, is something wrong?
What? Oh, well...
The moon was just so beautiful,
I was lost in admiration.
Yeah, it really is a beautiful moon.
Isn't it?
It's so beautiful, it makes you
want to cry, doesn't it?
Well, I'm going to take another dip
in the hot spring
and gaze at the moon before dinner!
So, excuse me!
I never know what a girl's thinking.
Sometimes, Usagi seems like
a total stranger to me.
My...
I won't give in! Even if... Even if
Mamoru has forgotten about me...
If I cry, he'd laugh at me.
Give him back!
Huh? Did you say something?
Huh? Give what back?
Give him back!
No way! This is not happening to me!
Usagi, what is that?!
It's a ghost! A beastly monster!
It's a monster! A monster!
Get down!
Give him back!
Run!
The trees!
It's poison!
That's it! I'm mad! Hey,
this is not funny!
How dare you ruin our family trip?!
What the heck are you thinking?!
Usagi, don't move!
Leave this to your dad!
Monster! You leave my family alone!
Dad!
Moon...
Dear, are you okay?
Another weird one showed up.
Don't be silly! He's on
our side! Probably...
I will not allow you to harm
innocent people!
Give him back!
Dear, hang in there.
Ouch. My back...
Tuxedo Mask, I wish I could help you,
but I can't transform here.
Run while you can!
Tuxedo Mask!
Hold it right there!
Sailor Venus!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Mercury!
Here we are!
Wow! The sailor warriors
of love and justice!
That's my line, damn it!
Give him back!
Bubble
Spray!
Everyone, now's our chance!
The inn is that way!
Okay, stick together!
Everyone, be careful.
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Here, here! This way!
How dare you frighten
innocent tourists,
and ruin Usagi's family's quality time?!
It's unforgivable!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Tuxedo Mask, you protected Usagi.
I knew you were a good person.
I love you.
Sailor Moon!
Crescent Beam!
Supreme
Thunder!
We did it!
Crescent Beam didn't work...
All right, then!
Moon Tiara Action!
This time...
No way! That's cheap!
This monster's not fair!
No, it's not a monster!
It's an evil phantom born of old,
fanatical jealousy!
She is right.
Sailor warriors, I am responsible for
awakening this ancient monster.
You girls, back off!
Sorry, but a phantom falls
in my domain!
Begone, Evil Spirit
Exorcise and cleanse with the
power of my purifying flame!
Begone, Evil Spirit
Rin, Pyo, Tou, Sha, Kai, Jin,
Retsu, Zai, Zen!
Begone, Evil Spirit
Begone, evil spirit!
Fire
Soul!
Amazing!
Now, Sailor Moon!
Oops! I almost forgot.
Moon Healing Escalation!
Refresh!
Finally, she's been freed from
her ancient jealousy,
and she's rising up to the Heavens.
It's so beautiful!
Tuxedo Mask!
I would say that what you did
was unnecessary,
but I will yield this time. Good-bye.
Oh, wait!
Tuxedo Mask...
Endymion. He is a strange man.
Usagi!
Hey!
Usagi, where are you?!
Answer me!
Sis!
Did she get eaten after all?
I should have just lent her my game.
Then lend it to me.
Sis!
Dad! Mom!
Usagi!
You made us worry!
Just like the wind, yeah
I'm sorry.
Spread out both hands, wow, wow
Dad risked his life trying to
protect us. Sweet Mom.
Spread out both hands, wow, wow
The sassy but adorable Shingo...
So, it's all right, all right
In the end, it's so nice
to have a family.
So, it's all right, all right
In the end, it's so nice
to have a family.
Toss your worries to the wind,
wow, wow
Wow, it feels so good!
Toss your worries to the wind,
wow, wow
What a nice view!
Toss your worries to the wind,
wow, wow
The magic of smiling
Tuxedo Mask...
I cast it upon you
I'll give you a mystery that only I have
Usagi, don't give up. You'll
have more chances.
I'll give you a mystery that only I have
Mako...
I'm okay, because I've got great
friends like you guys!
I can feel it
By the way, how did you guys
get way out here?
I can feel it
By the way, how did you guys
get way out here?
The next world
By the way, how did you guys
get way out here?
Luna told us.
I have faith
And...
We're not going to let you
I have faith
My dream will come true someday
have all the fun by yourself!
I can't breathe! Stop it!
Just fall in love
Let your heart sing, wow, wow
So, it's all right, all right
Take a deep breath, wow, wow
I won't let it end as just a dream
Hiru ni wa hana no kaori
Yoru ni wa hoshi no matataki
Soko wa daremo shiranai sekai nano
Shiroi kutsu o narashite
Shiroi tsuki no hashi watatte
Amai kisu no yume o miteru
ohimesama ga sunde iru no
Inori o sasagete moon
Kitto shiawase ni shitekureru
Maware maware tsuki no
merry-go-round
Suzushige na glass no
dress hirugaeshite
Itsudatte mimamotte iru wa
Moon moon princess