Frill-necked lizards, Mexican
salamanders, and human-faced
fish are all mad.
Mad, saying they're not toys.
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you.
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino, 14 years old.
I'm in the eighth grade.
I'm a Cancer. My blood type is O and
my birthstone is the pearl.
I'm clumsier than others and a bit
of a crybaby. That's about it.
One day, a strange black cat
named Luna appeared
and made me into a sailor warrior.
But she wants me to fight bad guys.
That makes me really nervous.
Oh well, I guess everything
will be okay.
A Monster's Scent!
Chanela Steals Love
I'm scared!
Tuxedo Mask.
Usagi, I will always be near you.
What's with all the racket
so early in the morning?
Why is there a cat here?
Cat
Get away!
Hey!
Take that cat out of my room now!
Oh yeah, Shingo...
You hate cats, don't you?
Here!
Stop it!
Here here.
Will you ever talk back to your smart
and beautiful sister again?
Breakfast!
Yes!
Saved.
What were you guys yelling about
so early in the morning?
That cat is Usagi's friend, right?
Yep, her name is Luna.
The shameless part is just like sis.
The fact that she's sleeping with you
sure makes it seem like she likes you.
Stop joking. She came in
without my permission.
I know, since we've all met.
Why don't we keep Luna?
No way.
Yes way. Yes way. Yes way.
No way! No way! No way!
Yes way! Yes way! Yes way!
Definitely no way.
It's just a cat. It should be okay.
Well, you two figure it out
on your own, okay?
Oh, great.
Why did you go to Shingo's
room anyway?
Well, actually I've been busy with
work and... accidentally...
Work? Were you chasing
a mouse or something?
No, I was looking for
the Moon Princess.
Moon pudding?
Hey!
Well anyway, try to get on
Shingo's good side.
Bye! I'm off!
Good luck!
Pet Shop Rope
How cute!
Oh, she licked my finger! How cute!
That's what I need to do.
Jadeite, do you have a new plan
to steal energy?
Yes, Queen Beryl.
The monster Iguana has set it up.
Humans have many desires.
Just a bit of catalyst can
turn that desire
into a very strong life energy.
In other words, the energy flows freely.
And we just take that from them?
It is all for our great ruler.
Proceed carefully.
Yes!
Hmm. Shingo doesn't like cats?
Yeah, when he was a baby,
a cat bit the tip of his nose.
The fear from that still
hasn't disappeared.
At least it was just a cat.
I was bitten by an alligator.
Why an alligator?
Oh, my mom probably left the latch
open and set it next to me.
Alligator! Alligator!
A latch?
Umino, you don't mean a handbag
made of alligator skin, do you?
They call it that too.
Umino!
Bye!
See you tomorrow.
Guess that didn't work.
Shingo...
The cat. What about the cat?!
Shingo, you don't like cats?
Mika.
A different kind of pet would be okay.
There's one that is perfect for you.
Huh?
There is a pretty neat store that
just opened up. Let's go.
Oh, okay.
Pet Shop Perfume
Doesn't it smell nice?
It's some perfume.
This scent is coming from
the pets here.
What?
Do you like the chanela?
Chanela?
Yes, these chanela emit a
perfume-like scent.
And each animal has a different scent.
Wow!
I'll buy this chanela.
I like this one.
But it's expensive, right?
Just bring the money when you can.
Really?
That helps.
What a nice smell.
I know.
As long as I have my chanela,
I don't need anything else.
Oh, it didn't work, huh?
I don't have to be a
house cat, you know.
No. It's not like you to
give up that easily.
Anyways, you're always lecturing me.
You need to set a good example!
Okay.
Shingo...
That's it!
This chanela is my pet starting today.
So hurry up and get rid of that cat.
You're being mean to Luna.
Usagi, I'm okay.
I'm sorry he did that.
Usagi! Tea is ready!
Coming!
Oh well.
That pet really does smell good.
Doesn't it? And this chanela
doesn't eat anything.
Well that's good, money wise.
Well, I agree it's cute. But...
Well then, we'll keep
Luna and Chanela.
I agree.
No way!
You are so cute.
Shingo! You're going to be late
if you don't hurry!
Shingo! C'mon, Shingo.
I'm staying home today.
What?
We'll always be together.
Juban Municipal Junior High School
What do you think of my chanela?
My chanela smells better.
Let's see. Not quite.
Those chanelas are pretty
popular right now.
Yeah, they're a huge hit.
But can they bring them to school?
Oh, it's Ms. Haruna!
Everyone hide your chanelas!
Let's start class.
Please open your book to page 234.
Oh, I want to look at my chanela.
I can't wait anymore.
So cute.
What are you people doing?
I'll have to confiscate it.
No, don't.
Ms. Haruna, are you okay?
I'm going home.
Me too.
Naru, don't you think
something is wrong?
I know.
I think the chanelas are cute,
but they're a bit weird.
Speaking of which, even Shingo...
I wonder if it has something
to do with it?
Hey Naru, do you know where
they sell chanelas?
Pet Shop Perfume, I think.
Do you want to go?
Sorry, I've got cram school today.
Oh well, I'll go by myself.
Will you be okay alone?
It's hard having a dumb brother.
You're such a good sister!
Pet Shop Perfume
So this shop has chanelas?
What am I going to do if I
become like Shingo?
Hey, Dumpling Head!
That voice...
Why do you keep showing up?
I can say the same to you.
You're not buying a chanela, are you?
Why?
Perfume doesn't suit you.
Shut up.
And I'm in...
Welcome.
Please take your time.
Thank you.
I should have come with Naru.
They are pretty cute.
Usagi, don't fall for that trap.
Luna? Why?
I was checking out this store because
something wasn't right.
You think so?
Don't look into its eyes.
So cute...
Usagi.
It's no surprise a pretty
customer like you
would pick out the cutest
chanela in the store.
How cute.
Usagi, I think you should return it.
If you get any closer, I'll kick you!
Usagi!
I don't like you.
It's okay, it's not your fault.
Coming through!
It hurts!
Usagi.
Cute kitty cat.
I can't leave her alone.
Oh, good.
Luna, what was I doing?
I'm sorry Luna. I just...
More importantly, I'm worried
about Shingo.
Okay.
Shingo, hand over that chanela!
No way!
What are you doing? Stop it!
You idiot.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm not giving anyone my chanela.
Usagi, there's no time
to be depressed!
We've got to follow him.
But where should we go?
That pet shop of course.
Now change into Sailor Moon!
What am I going to do if the chanela
looks at me again?
You can't be scared now.
You've got an important mission.
I know.
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
You are to spread these chanelas.
Do you understand?
Yeah!
Frill-necked lizards, Mexican
salamanders, and human-faced
fish are all mad.
Who are you?
They are mad, saying that
they are not toys!
Sailor warrior of love and justice,
Sailor Moon.
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you.
Why you...
Scary!
Shingo! Shingo!
It's usually at times like this that
the Tuxedo Mask comes to save me.
He's not coming.
Don't keep depending on others.
C'mon, use the Moon Tiara Action.
But Shingo's there...
Just yell, "Moon Tiara Stardust."
Got it.
Moon Tiara Stardust!
Oh, I didn't know I could do that.
Why you...
Over here, Sailor Moon!
I'm done for!
That monster's weak point is
at the base of its tail.
Moon Tiara Action.
Sailor V!
Oh crap!
Sailor V. Can I get your autograph?
I'm a huge fan.
I'm Sailor Moon!
Well, you're cute, so whichever.
Anyway, can I please have
your autograph?
But before that, I have to ask you
to do something, Shingo.
Huh? How did you know my name?
I know everything.
Shingo, I want you to be nice to
a cat near you named Luna.
That black cat is certain to
lead you to happiness.
Okay, anything you ask.
Luna, do you want ham next?
It's good that you two
are getting along.
Starting today, we're a family of five.
Okay, here you go.
Either way, it's pretty bad.
In my dream, you and I were together
Protected by the stars
When we were friends,
it didn't bother us
And we casually talked to each other
But there was a moment when
I noticed only you
I want to become prettier
right here and now
Something changes when
you fall in love
I close my eyes and check
to make sure
I want to convey the thrill I felt
when we held each other