There is no way a monster that plays
with an innocent girl's
emotions would...
There is no way he'd look
good in a tuxedo!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino. I don't look like
a super heroine, but I am!
As you know, I transform myself
by using a peculiar brooch
and fight against bad guys.
I'm the sailor warrior of love and
justice, Sailor Moon!
And my friends are the smart
and sweet Ami Mizuno,
and a slightly quick-tempered
psychic girl, Rei Hino.
Both of them are so dependable,
I feel like I'll fall behind.
But anyway, I just have to do my best!
Usagi Is Thrilled!
Tuxedo Mask's Love Letter
The stars know everything.
Leo shines in the
southern night sky.
And the star, Regulus,
presides over his strong leg.
Show me the weakness of the sailor
warriors, our despised enemies.
Tuxedo Mask!
Moon Tiara Action!
Fire Soul!
Good-bye, sailor warriors!
He's so dreamy!
I have found Sailor Moon's weakness!
Nephrite, Queen Beryl
is calling for you.
Nephrite, it seems the collection
of human energy
is not proceeding very well.
The universe was not
created overnight.
Do not talk back to me!
If you cannot defeat Sailor Moon
and the others,
I will sentence you to "Eternal Sleep",
just like Jadeite!
Such a terrible punishment.
I am one of the Great Four of the
Dark Kingdom, Nephrite!
I do not need others to
order me around.
I am already thinking of a way to
defeat Sailor Moon and the rest.
I remember Jadeite used to say the
same thing... I wonder if you can...
I swear that I will lure Sailor Moon
out and kill her, without fail.
Very well.
And I already have a plan.
Oh?
Miss Usagi Tsukino
Why?! Why?! Why?!
From Tuxedo Mask
It's from Tuxedo Mask.
"I love you more than anyone else."
"Please meet me at the MS Department
Store in Shinjuku tomorrow night."
Wow! All right!
Why the heck would Tuxedo Mask
send you a love letter?
You know why! Because...
He loves me!
But that's not right. How come he
knows you're Sailor Moon?
Love conquers all!
The power of love can
solve all mysteries.
In short, Tuxedo Mask's love is so
strong, he saw through my secret!
Tuxedo Mask has always helped you,
but we still don't know if he's
on our side or not.
You have to be careful!
Miss Usagi Tsukino
Junban Municipal Junior High School
No! Thatcan't betrue!
But it is. I also got a love letter from
someone named Tuxedo Mask.
Me, too.
Who is this Tuxedo Mask?
I have no idea.
Miss Naru Osaka
I wish this love letter was
from that person.
From Tuxedo Mask
I wish this love letter was
from that person.
Everyone, you must not be tricked
by the prank love letters!
Ladies should always be modest.
Do you understand?
Yes!
That letter may have been sent by
somebody vicious to tempt you.
Do not go to the MS Department Store
in Shinjuku. Do you understand?
Yes, Ma'am!
Good!
It's outrageous! Why didn't
I get a love letter, too?!
See?
Don't you think something is fishy?
That's true. We should probably
talk to Rei about this as well.
So, someone named Tuxedo Mask is
sending love letters? Oh! So close!
It seems like lots of girls got one.
I wonder if it's some
kind of promotion?
Who knows? Yeah, maybe it
is something like that.
Hi, Usagi!
What's wrong? You look upset.
Oh, I know. Lots of girls
got a love letter
from that guy called Tuxedo Mask,
but you didn't! That's why
you're upset, isn't it?
You're wrong! I did get one!
Then, why are you sighing so much?
It's terrible!
How could Tuxedo Mask send love
letters to those other girls?
Hikawa Shrine
What? Rei, you're sick?
I caught a cold and I
have a high fever,
so I can't go out, even though I have
an invitation from Tuxedo Mask.
It's just awful.
I'll take care of you.
Miss Rei Hino
Thank you, Ami.
[Skipped item nr. 120]
She will come! Sailor Moon is
in love with Tuxedo Mask.
She is certain to come here tonight!
This is where Sailor Moon will die.
Oh, Mr. Sanjoin!
It's me!
I'm a member of Juban Junior High's
tennis club, Naru Osaka.
I remember now. Are
you out shopping?
Yes...
Would you mind if I asked
you a question?
What?
You wouldn't happen to
be Tuxedo Mask?
What?
You wouldn't happen to
be Tuxedo Mask?
What?! Why do you ask?
Oh, it's nothing. I was just
wishing you were.
It's something that crossed my mind.
Could she be aware that I'm the one
who sent those love letters
by using Tuxedo Mask's name?
Could this... Could this
girl be Sailor Moon?!
I'm sorry for asking you
such a silly question.
Naru.
Yes, Sir?
You're the cutest girl at
Juban Junior High.
What?
I've been interested in you for a
while now. I'll see you tonight.
Tonight? By tonight,
does he mean...
I want to bare my heart to you.
I love you more than anyone else.
Please meet me at the MS Department
Store in Shinjuku tomorrow night.
Tuxedo Mask
tomorrow night
It really is him!
You're the cutest girl at
Juban Junior High.
I've been interested in you
for a while now.
Mr. Masato Sanjoin...
I want to bare my heart to you.
I love you more than anyone else.
Please meet me at the MS Department
Store in Shinjuku tomorrow night.
Tuxedo Mask
I want to bare my heart to you.
I love you more than anyone else.
Please meet me at the MS Department
Store in Shinjuku tomorrow night.
Tuxedo Mask
Why?
I want to bare my heart to you.
I love you more than anyone else.
Please meet me at the MS Department
Store in Shinjuku tomorrow night.
Tuxedo Mask
Why did Tuxedo Mask send love
letters to all those people?
I don't get it! I'll just
have to ask him in person!
Date etiquette, rule number one!
Wear clean underwear
and a nice clean outfit!
Date etiquette, rule number two!
Wear a nice, non-offensive fragrance!
Date etiquette, rule number three!
Brush your teeth and be
ready just in case.
Date etiquette, rule number four!
Use a soft pink lip color
for a neat, innocent look!
Just like that! Oh, what am I thinking!
How embarrassing!
Tuxedo Mask?
Tuxedo Mask? Oh, no...
Mr. Masato Sanjoin, where are you?
Here!
Welcome.
That voice... So, you are
Mr. Masato Sanjoin!
You can recognize me by my voice?
Of course.
Your voice and the way
you carry yourself...
You are none other than
Mr. Masato Sanjoin!
Do you love Masato
Sanjoin that much?
Since I heard what you
told me this afternoon,
I have become a prisoner of love!
Sailor Moon!
Reveal yourself! Show me
who you really are!
Maybe I should have told
Ami and Rei after all.
Where are you, Usagi?
Oh, Ami, I'm sorry.
I'm in Shinjuku.
Is she going on a date with Tuxedo
Mask behind my back?!
Mr. Sanjoin...
What's wrong?! Transform
into Sailor Moon!
What are you talking about?
Are you not Sailor Moon?!
I love you.
What tremendous energy!
Mr. Sanjoin...
Oh, Naru!
Why is Tuxedo Mask...
No! That's not Tuxedo Mask!
Naru, wait for me!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
It's happening again!
My head...
This girl was not Sailor Moon,
but I have obtained an unexpectedly
vast amount of energy!
Release Naru!
Who are you?!
A tuxedo is not fitting for a monster
who toys with a girl's love!
You're...
I'm the sailor warrior
of love and justice,
You're...
I'm the sailor warrior
of love and justice,
Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon, I
will punish you!
How were you able to tell that
I am not Tuxedo Mask?
It's the intuition of a girl in love!
Sailor Moon Kick!
If you want this girl,
you can have her!
Naru!
You're Mr. Masato Sanjoin!
I am Nephrite, one of the Great
Four of the Dark Kingdom!
Nephrite?!
Sailor Moon, I became Tuxedo
Mask in order to lure you out.
O Regulus, star of Leo, shining
in the southern night sky,
grant me your power!
I'll tear your body to pieces!
No! No!
Who's there?!
So, you sent those love
letters using my name
in order to lure out Sailor
Moon! Unforgivable!
Oh, he's the real one!
He's so gorgeous!
Tuxedo Mask...
Sailor Moon! Go now!
Okay, Mr. Real Tuxedo Mask!
Fool! Do you think you can
get away from me?!
Come!
Go!
Tuxedo Mask, watch out!
Moon Tiara Action!
No way! It's not working like usual.
Sailor Moon, get in the elevator!
Yes!
You fell for it!
Oh, no! It's a trap!
What do you mean?
This elevator will go up to the roof.
What do you suppose will happen
when it gets to the top floor?
So, what will happen?!
By the law of Earth's gravity,
the elevator will fall!
Your bodies will be flattened
into pancakes!
I don't wanna become a pancake!
Tuxedo Mask!
We must do something.
What's going on? My
life is in danger,
but my heart is pounding like crazy.
Sailor Moon!
A kiss?
What are you doing? We're
getting out of here!
Right!
Come on.
It's the top floor! Jump off!
Okay!
I did it!
I can't hold on anymore!
Do not give up! We will get
out of here somehow.
Until then, we should distract ourselves
by talking about something.
Okay. Let's see. Let's see.
Why do you always rescue me?
My blood roars and it makes
me want to rescue you.
I've secured a foothold!
Can you get onto my back?
Yes!
I know why. It's because
you must love me.
Oh, I can't believe it! I'm spouting
such nonsense!
Let's see. Who are you?
I think I can guess who you are.
You're Motoki, aren't you?! Oh,
I've said something silly again!
Sailor Moon.
Yes?
I cannot help but feel that I knew
you somehow long, long ago.
Something is stirring in the
corner of my mind,
but I just cannot remember it.
We're going to fall!
Calm down!
Okay.
Let's see. What's your hobby?
What are your favorite foods?
Oh, I'm so stupid! I keep coming
up with weird questions!
It's just sad!
Tuxedo Mask!
Sailor Moon, you should never have
come here without telling us!
I'm sorry!
That was close.
Thank you for rescuing us.
I have a cold, you know.
How dare you take that chance
to go behind my back
and drape yourself all over
Tuxedo Mask?! It's not fair!
Oh, it wasn't like that!
Stop fighting!
Not you, too, Ami! You're going
to side with Sailor Moon?!
No! I just want to quickly
take Naru to a hospital!
Everyone, be good to one
another. Good-bye!
Oh, please wait!
Tuxedo Mask...
I do not deal well with girls fighting.
Queen Beryl, Nephrite boasted that
he would defeat Sailor Moon.
But in spite of it, he was
not able to kill her.
He should be sentenced
to "Eternal Sleep."
The energy that Nephrite brought
back has enormous power.
In light of that, I will not
punish him this time.
But my lady...
I can punish him anytime I want.
Zoisite, stop worrying about others
and tend to your own business!
Hurry up and find the Silver Crystal!
Yes, my lady!
All humans become focused
on something
at least once in their lives
and produce an enormous
amount of energy.
That girl, Naru... The powerful energy
she produced was unbelievable.
It seems she truly loves my disguise
as Masato Sanjoin.
What a foolish girl!
In my dream, you and I were together
Protected by the stars
When we were friends,
it didn't bother us
And we casually talked to each other
But there was a moment when
I noticed only you
I want to become prettier
right here and now
Something changes when
you fall in love
I close my eyes and check
to make sure
I want to convey the thrill I felt
when we held each other