What's worse than old men who are
envious of youth and popularity,
are those that think nothing
of peoples' feelings.
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you.
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short
sunzen ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino, 14 years old.
I'm in the eighth grade.
I'm a Cancer. My blood type is O and
my birthstone is the pearl.
I'm clumsier than others and a bit
of a crybaby. That's about it.
One day, a strange black cat
named Luna appeared
and made me into a sailor warrior.
But she wants me to fight bad guys.
That makes me really nervous.
Oh well, I guess everything
will be okay.
Punish Them!
The House of Fortune is the Monster Mansion
Hurry! Hurry!
Wait for me!
This place is really good.
I know, it's been on TV a few times.
Wow, look at the line.
Foolish humans.
What? You still haven't found the
legendary silver crystal?
No.
Hurry. Our great ruler is waiting
for a lot of energy.
Leave it to us.
Is that you, Jadeite?
Yes.
As you heard, we still have not found
the legendary silver crystal.
So I want human energy instead.
Queen Beryl, it has already
been taken care of.
Wake up!
Come on!
There.
I can't breathe.
You won't be able to succeed
in our mission like that.
Good!
Look at the time!
Why didn't you wake me up earlier?
Gurio Umino.
Here.
Um. Kenji Oota.
Takayuki Kamikawa.
Here.
Yuuji Kimura.
Good morning, Usagi!
Go stand in the hallway!
Why are you out here with me?
That's... Well... It's hard to explain...
Weirdo.
Yes.
What did you want to talk
to me about?
I want to go on a date with Usagi.
And trade dairies and even talk to
her parents about the future.
..Mom.. ..Dad..
And trade dairies and even talk to
her parents about the future.
That'll never happen.
I'm sorry, I don't think it'll work if you
come straight out and ask.
So I should attack her from behind?
No, no.
Go to a fortune teller and ask her
what you should do.
I already know the answer then.
This fortune teller game was made
according to my ideas.
According to this, Usagi and I are
supposed to get married.
Thank you.
The Happy Couple
I don't mean that.
I mean a real fortune teller.
I see.
There's a fortune teller house
that opened in Juubangai.
I heard that they are pretty good,
so why don't you try them?
Okay.
Huh?
What happened? There is
usually a long line here.
I guess it's because there is
competition now. Look.
House of Fortune
It's awfully gaudy.
What is that?
The beauty from Juubangai.
What? Is it the same kind of
fortune telling that you do?
Yeah. Everyone likes new things.
Read me.
Okay, thank you.
There's a man that likes you right now.
And it's someone you see all the time.
Someone I always see...
Maybe it's...
Looks like he's not here yet.
Hey, Usagi.
Perfect timing. I'm about
to start working.
Hello, Motoki.
Usagi, the Sailor V Game
just came in.
You haven't played it yet, right?
Not yet.
C'mon! C'mon! There, there!
C'mon! C'mon!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
Oh, game over!
It's pretty hard, isn't it?
Uh... yes.
I'll show you how to do it.
Oh I'II...
My treat. Here Usagi, watch carefully.
See, at this point, you have to
get this item.
See, and you kill it.
Makes me nervous but I'm so happy.
See? You understand now?
The rest you just keep shooting.
Luna, what are you doing here?
Oh, is this cat's name Luna?
Huh? Yeah.
It's been around here lately.
I wonder if it's a stray?
What are you doing?
Stop it. Okay, I'm going! I'm going!
Well, bye!
Oh but, we're still in the
middle of the game.
I'll come again.
I'll be waiting.
I feel good every time
I see your face.
We were having a good time!
Is it okay for you to stop somewhere
on your way home?
Well, it's not a good thing.
As long as you understand.
Like I told you this morning, Usagi,
you have a mission.
Where are you going?
I'm going to have the old man
tell me more about Motoki.
I was too late.
I should probably wait and ask the
old man from Juubangai.
But I want to know right now.
Usagi, what are you doing?
Never mind, never mind.
Oh, I know. I'll tell my own fortune
on which one I should go to.
If it's right side up,
I'll ask the old man.
If it's upside down, I'll go to
the House of Fortune.
Ow!
Oops.
It's that smug guy again.
That hurts, Dumpling Head.
Is that all you can say?
You'll never have a boyfriend if
you don't act more ladylike.
Well, thank you so much!
My good mood's all gone.
How irritating.
Amazing...
Look at my eyes.
You are a wonderful servant of evil.
You can do whatever you desire.
I will do whatever I desire.
I will soon be able to
collect the energy.
Hey! Usagi!
Oh, Dad. Shopping?
Yeah, I got home early for a change
and your mom got me.
Dad, you're so sweet.
I leave all the housework
to your mom.
This is the least I can do.
I bet Motoki will be like Dad.
By the way Usagi...
Huh?
What were you doing out until now?
It's not good to be hanging out
after school.
I'm sorry.
Usagi, what is with the cat?
It seems like it's following us.
Oh, it's my friend.
You have some strange friends.
Did Umino say anything to you?
About what?
I think Umino likes you.
What?!
But he's innocent so he's
too shy to say anything.
Usagi, let's go on a date!
What's wrong?
It's not a good idea to come to
school dressed like that.
Who cares? Usagi, let's go
on a date today.
You know...
He's gotten brave all of the sudden.
Umino, what is that outfit?
Umino! What are you thinking?
Thinking this!
No one will marry me now!
That is enough!
What are you doing, Yuuji?
Ms. Haruna, you are supposed to
walk quietly in the classroom.
What did you say?
What? Umino went to the
House of Fortune?
Yeah. I told him about it.
I think Yuuji went too.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
You don't have much of a brain.
So stop acting like you're
better than us!
Yeah! Yeah!
So stop acting like you're
better than us!
Yeah! Yeah!
Take that! And that and that!
Keep on making trouble.
The rebellious energy of the young.
What are you doing?
What is this?
Hey, Usagi!
What's wrong with you?
Wanna kiss?
I don't like you when you're like this!
I hate you! Hate you! Hate you!
Let's get out of here.
I feel some kind of evil energy.
Usagi, it's okay now.
Oh, I feel better.
Umino and the others just left.
What was he thinking?
Usagi, it seems something evil has
been causing these incidents.
So, Umino and the others...
They are probably being controlled.
The House of Fortune is suspicious.
The guys have been weird since they
went to the House of Fortune.
That's great! Good job finding that out.
Give me a new item as a reward.
In your dreams! Let's go.
What? Fight again?
I'm kind of scared.
What are you talking about?
Transform into Sailor Moon.
Do I have to?
You have to.
Let's see.
I forgot what I'm supposed to say.
It's "Moon Prism Power Makeup"!
Oh, that's it!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Everyone, you did very well.
Now, I'll have you wreak
havoc in town.
Yes!
Sounds like fun!
What's worse than old men being
envious of youth and popularity,
are those that think nothing of
peoples' feelings.
Who's there?
Sailor warrior of love and justice.
Sailor Moon!
Sailor Moon?
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you.
Hey, watch it!
You don't have time for that.
Oh, yeah.
Get her!
Stop this!
No!
If you get any closer,
you're going to get hurt.
Another intruder?
Who's there?
Tuxedo Mask!
Don't ever give up no matter
how hard it is.
Okay.
Good-bye! We'll meet again.
Thank you, Tuxedo Mask.
That would have hurt.
C'mon, Sailor Moon, the tiara!
Oh yeah.
Moon Tiara Action.
Bam, you failed.
Yay!
Take care!
What?! I flipped Ms. Haruna's skirt?
And you tried to kiss Usagi.
Then you broke the window
of the teacher's office...
Hey, where are you going?
All that's left for me is misery.
Good morning!
Usagi. Uh... about yesterday...
Don't worry about it!
You're right! I shouldn't
worry about it.
You're okay when you get bad grades
on your tests after all.
I need to be more like you.
Sheesh! He doesn't even know
the trouble I go through.
Oh no.
Yume no naka futari de ita yo ne
Hoshi tachi ni mamorarete
Tomodachi no toki ni wa ki ni sezu
Nanigenaku hanashite ita kedo
Anata dake ki ni naru
shunkan ga atta no
Motto kirei ni ima sugu naritai
Koi suru to nanika ga kawaru ne
Me o tojite tashikamete
Dakishimeta tokimeki sono
mama kono omoi tsutaetai