Sometimes, a girl can't stop loving,
even if she knows better.
She'll find a love she
wants to believe in,
no matter how painful it is.
A girl always wants to believe
that love conquers all.
If there's anyone who tries
to get in their way...
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish them!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino. I don't look like
a super heroine, but I am!
As you know, I transform myself
by using a peculiar brooch
and fight against bad guys.
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
And my friends are the smart
and sweet Ami Mizuno,
and a slightly quick-tempered
psychic girl, Rei Hino.
Both of them are so dependable,
I feel like I'll fall behind.
But anyway, I just have to do my best!
Naru's Cry! Nephrite Dies For Love
Say, Naru, I think it would be better
if you forget about him.
I can't.
What?
No matter how bad he is,
I still love him.
Oh, boy...
Usagi, you have someone
you love, don't you?
What? Me? Well, yeah.
Then, you should understand
how I feel.
Naru Osaka. Why did the Black
Crystal respond to that girl?
Was that the energy of love?
I will protect Mr. Sanjoin!
Because I love him. I love him
with all my heart, so...
It's ridiculous!
Sailor Moon knew that girl's name.
That girl must know Sailor
Moon's true identity.
Just you watch, Sailor Moon!
I've found it.
So, that is the Black Crystal
that's supposed to reveal
the location of the Silver Crystal.
Jewelry
The Black Crystal is responding again.
This girl...
Could the Silver Crystal be something
inside a human body?
No.
The Silver Crystal is not
inside this girl.
Mr. Sanjoin?
Masato Sanjoin is only a disguise.
My real name is Nephrite.
I do not want to lie
to you anymore.
Please just stay there and listen.
Okay.
You are a wonderful girl.
Thanks to you, I have learned what
love is for the first time.
In the evil organization I have been
a part of, there is no love.
We betray each other and kill each
other for our own gain.
I thought that was normal,
but your love opened my eyes.
Now, I am thinking that I would
like to join Sailor Moon
to fight against the evil organization.
If you know anything about Sailor
Moon, please tell me.
I'm sorry, but I don't know anything.
Can you not trust me?
No! I trust you! But I really,
really know nothing!
I see, I'm sorry to hear that.
Oh, please wait!
Mr. Nephrite...
If this girl knows who Sailor Moon is,
she is certain to contact her somehow.
Oh, my, what a foolish man.
Has he fallen in love
with a human girl?
Master Zoisite!
You three, I believe you've heard
everything you need to know.
What a stupid man.
Let's attack him now!
Now, be patient. Nephrite
is a superb warrior.
We don't want to get hurt by making
any ill-planned moves.
We'll take that girl as a hostage
and lure him out.
Yes, Sir.
How can I find out where
Sailor Moon is?
Usagi! Phone call!
Who in the world is calling me
in the middle of night?
Hello?
Hello?!
Usagi, I'm sorry for calling you so late.
Naru!
What's wrong?
I just thought you're the only
one I could talk to.
Did something happen?
Mr. Sanjoin... Mr. Sanjoin is
looking for Sailor Moon.
What?
Mr. Sanjoin is in trouble, but
I can't do anything for him.
What's wrong with Mr. Sanjoin?
Naru, are you crying?
I'm sorry for making such a weird call
to you in the middle of night.
I'm okay now.
But...
Really, I'm okay.
I feel calmer now after talking
to you, Usagi. Thank you.
Are you sure?
Usagi?
I'll bet Nephrite is closing
in on Naru!
You're too slow!
I'll going on ahead!
Hey, I'm not a cat!
Hurry up and come, okay!
I know that!
Oh, what is this?!
I know! It's must be the work of
a monster! Where are you?!
Show yourselves! Come on!
Okay, then! Moon Prism
Power Makeup!
You have finally revealed
yourself, Sailor Moon!
Nephrite!
The true identity of Sailor Moon is
Usagi Tsukino. I saw it clearly.
No way!
Please! Don't tell anybody that I'm
Sailor Moon! Okay?! Please?!
There is no need for you
to hide it anymore.
Not exactly. So, please?
Do not worry you are
going to die here!
I don't wanna die!
Someone...
Prepare yourself, Sailor Moon!
Defeat is not befitting of the
beautiful Sailor Moon.
I shall be your opponent!
Tuxedo Mask!
Help! Mr. Nephrite!
That voice is...
What's wrong, Nephrite?
We shall conclude this
fight another time.
Sailor Moon, I know who
you are now!
I will be able to attack you at
any time now! Be ready!
What'll I do?! He knows who I am!
Do not give up just because he
knows who you are now.
Good-bye.
Tuxedo Mask...
Jewelry
Oh, no! I need to contact
the sailor warriors!
Hand over the Black Crystal
in exchange for the girl?
One of Zoisite's minions...
That idiot! Who cares what
happens to that girl?!
Hurry up, Nephrite.
Will he really come for this human?
Well, if he doesn't show up,
we'll just kill the girl.
Poor thing. She's scared.
Mr. Nephrite!
Die!
Did we get him?!
I will never hand over the Black
Crystal to you guys!
Tell that to Zoisite!
Mr. Nephrite, thank you.
You do not need to thank me.
I do not even really understand
why I rescued you.
And I have kept deceiving
you for a long time.
I may continue to lie to you,
even after this.
That's okay.
If you'll just stay close to me,
I don't mind being lied to.
Oh, no! You're injured!
It's okay.
No, it's not! You were hurt
because of me!
It's okay.
No, it's not! You were hurt
because of me!
It would be bad if those scary people
come back, so come this way.
Now, take your jacket off.
Okay.
In San-chome,
there's a place that serves really
good chocolate parfaits.
Chocolate parfaits?
Yes. You don't like them?
Oh, no, I like them.
You're lying.
See? Sometimes we lie with
kind intentions, too.
Thank you.
I always thought it would be nice
to go to there one day
and have a chocolate
parfait with you.
It's a little dream of mine.
It sounds good.
Let's do it someday.
Really?
Do you think I'm lying?
Not at all. I'm so happy!
Oh, come to think of it,
does the evil organization give
you Sundays off, too?
You laughed!
It's weird. My eyes are tearing.
Mr. Nephrite!
You let your guard down.
Those thorns will keep sucking
your energy until you die!
What a miserable way to die.
If you do not want us to kill the girl,
hand over the Black Crystal!
Very well.
Hurry, run!
No!
Run!
No! No!
You idiot! Run!
No!
Do you think you can pull them out
with the strength of a human?
Hurry! Hurry up and run!
That's enough. It's okay.
What?!
Impossible!
Mr. Nephrite, please don't die!
Damn it, I'll take care of both
of them at once!
Die!
Are you okay?
Mr. Nephrite!
Good work, all of you. The Black
Crystal is mine now.
You should be happy to able to
die with the girl you love.
You guys make sure to have
plenty of fun with them.
You coward.
Are you ready?
Run!
No!
Hold it right there!
You're really mean, trying to interfere
with two people in love!
Sailor warriors!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Stand under a cold waterfall and
reflect on your conduct!
In the name of Mars,
I will chastise you!
We will take care of you
guys first! Die!
Bubble
Spray!
Now!
What?!
Where are you?!
Fire
Moon Tiara
Soul!
Action!
Mr. Nephrite...
Sailor Moon...
Yes?
It looks like your identity
may remain a secret.
No, please don't die!
I'm sorry.
What?
I don't think we'll get to eat a
chocolate parfait together.
No...
I have ended up lying to you
to the very end.
Please forgive me.
I'm glad I met you.
Mr. Nephrite?
No! You can't! You promised!
You said we'd eat a chocolate
parfait together!
No!
This is... This isn't fair!
Mr. Nephrite!
Yume no naka futari de ita yo ne
Hoshi tachi ni mamorarete
Tomodachi no toki ni wa ki ni sezu
Nanigenaku hanashite ita kedo
Anata dake ki ni naru
shunkan ga atta no
Motto kirei ni ima sugu naritai
Koi suru to nanika ga kawaru ne
Me o tojite tashikamete
Dakishimeta tokimeki sono mama
kono omoi tsutaetai