The doll with blue eyes was
stomped flat by a monster!
A doll has all the heart and
soul of its creator!
I bet even the dolls for the
Girl's Day Festival are upset!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino. I don't look like
a super heroine, but I am!
As you know, I transform myself
by using a peculiar brooch
and fight against bad guys.
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
And my friends are the smart
and sweet Ami Mizuno,
and a slightly quick-tempered
psychic girl, Rei Hino.
Both of them are so dependable,
I feel like I'll fall behind.
But anyway, I just have to do my best!
Shingo's Innocent Love!
A Sorrowful French Doll
Nephrite, how are things going
with the sailor warriors?
I believe you had entrusted
that matter to me.
It seems you are having
quite a hard time.
I would be more than happy
to help you.
The operations are bound to go better
with two of us rather than one.
Don't you think so, Queen Beryl?
That is a good idea.
Nephrite, work with Zoisite and...
I refuse.
That is a good idea.
Nephrite, work with Zoisite and...
I refuse.
Oh, dear. Do you intend to
defy Queen Beryl?
I am not doing this for Queen Beryl!
I am doing this for myself!
Excuse me!
Nephrite...
Everything went just as planned.
Now, Queen Beryl will have lost
confidence in Nephrite.
Oh, Usagi. You're early today.
This is what normal people do,
stupid Usagi!
Shingo, it seems Mika won
the French doll contest.
Really?!
I seem to remember that Mika's
mother is a famous doll maker.
Like mother, like daughter.
Well, Mr. Shingo Tsukino,
how do you feel about having
a celebrity for a girlfriend?
Stop it!
This was brought to you live
from the Tsukino residence.
Stupid Usagi! You're gonna be
late again! I'm leaving!
I got up early this morning,
there is no way I...
Look at the time!
I'm gonna be late!
Miss Tsukino, out in the
hallway you go.
It's amazing how you never get
tired of being late every day.
Leave me alone.
Excuse me, are you
Shingo's older sister?
Yes, I am.
Shingo is so mean!
Did Shingo do something?
Today, at school...
Shingo. Shingo.
Oh, Mika. Congratulations on
winning the contest!
Shingo, here.
What is it?
This is the French doll that
won in the contest.
Is it okay? It must mean a lot to you.
Yeah, because you were always
there when I needed to talk.
They're so in love!
So, when's the wedding?!
I don't want it!
It's not my fault.
And Shingo didn't even
apologize to her!
I felt so bad for Mika.
Please talk to Shingo about this.
Shingo's definitely in the wrong!
Usagi...
As his older sister, you should
have a word with him.
Right. Anyway, just let this wise and
pretty older sister handle this!
I'll make sure that Shingo
apologizes to Mika!
Come in.
What's wrong? Why do you have
all the curtains closed?
I can concentrate better this way.
Oh, are you already making
the next one?
She looks like she's
about to start crying.
You think so?
But I don't think that's a bad thing.
Show me the doll that won the
contest. Let's compare them!
I don't have it.
I'm letting someone
borrow it for a while.
Who?
Well...
Show me when you get it back then.
Okay.
The stars know everything.
The Lyre's Orpheus is beginning
to play his harp of sorrow.
The target Orpheus has chosen
is Mika Kayama.
I will take your energy.
I'm sorry Mika. It was my fault.
I know you worked so hard
to make that doll...
Oh, I can't! I can't! I can't!
I can't write this letter!
Shingo! Your sister
needs to talk to you!
Oh, I can't! I can't! I can't!
I can't write this letter!
Shingo! Your sister
needs to talk to you!
Come in.
Ouch! What was that for?!
That was for Mika!
What?!
You broke Mika's doll
today, didn't you?!
Go apologize to her immediately!
I don't want to hear about
that anymore! Get out!
Okay, then I'll tell Mom
and Dad about this!
What do you think will happen?
Uh-oh
Uh-oh.
You'll do exactly as I say, won't you?
Okay.
Then, go to Mika's house and
apologize right away.
Got it?!
I get it.
I'm sorry! It was my fault!
I'll make this up to you, even if it
takes me the rest of my life!
Okay, I'll go with that!
Wow! Awesome car!
Kayama
Yes?
I am Masato Sanjoin. I spoke
with you on the phone earlier.
Wait just a moment, please.
They've got a guest.
I guess I'll come back later.
I had thought that Pierre Dumoe
was the only one
who could make such classic dolls,
but this has changed my mind.
My, you are such a flatterer.
I see that your daughter
is also very talented.
Her name is Mika.
The doll you entered in the contest
the other day was wonderful.
I would love to see that doll.
Oh, the doll is...
Mika, why don't you show him the
doll you're making right now?
Okay.
Oh, this is wonderful!
Excuse me.
Her sad expression is just so...
Monster, Jumo!
Bring Mika Kayama's energy to
its peak level and steal it!
Isn't that great, Mika?
Would you make ten more dolls
just like this one?
What? Ten?
This doll will sell out very quickly.
We are holding a private exhibition
starting this Saturday.
Of course, my daughter's work
will be there as well.
Please come see the exhibit.
I will be looking forward to it.
You finished it awfully quickly.
It's strange, but suddenly
I feel so motivated.
Now, I have to make the second one.
I understand how you feel, but
why don't you go to bed?
You have school tomorrow, remember?
I'll be fine.
Now, don't say that.
Come on, let's clean up.
Shut up!
What? Mika is?
She's been making dolls since
yesterday without any sleep.
I tried to stop her, but she
wouldn't listen to me.
I don't know what to do.
I'll talk to her.
Mika, Shingo's here to see you.
I don't want to see him.
Mika, I need to talk...
Go away!
I wonder if Mika's still mad at me?
Shingo, here you go.
Huh? What is this?
As a caring sister, I can't ignore
my kid brother when he's upset.
You apologized to Mika, didn't you?
Well, the thing is...
I didn't know that.
Mika's always been so sweet,
I couldn't believe it.
Did I hurt Mika's feelings that badly?
Cheer up! Oh, I know!
Why don't you bring her a present
when you visit next time?
Girls love getting presents!
Okay.
Usagi, what's wrong?
I know what I told Shingo,
but Mika still isn't acting
normal, you know?
Usagi, you're very sharp today!
When it comes to my darling kid
brother, I do everything I can!
Besides, cursed dolls
sound interesting!
Spare me the scary stuff!
Well, it could be something to do
with the Dark Kingdom;
we should keep an eye on Mika.
Oh, right. In that case, let's have
Ami and Rei handle it!
Usagi!
Okay, I got it.
Yoshiko Kayama
Doll Exhibition
Well? Do you see anything, Luna?
No. The curtains are closed,
so I can't see inside.
According to Shingo, Mika hasn't
been going to school either.
The only lead we have left
Yoshiko Kayama
Doll Exhibition
Classic Dolls
The only lead we have left
Yoshiko Kayama
Doll Exhibition
Classic Dolls
is this private exhibition
that starts tomorrow.
Is this private exhibition
New Sailor V
Sailor V is nice, but I like
Sailor Moon better.
Yeah, me, too.
Okay, that's what I'm going to get her!
A present for Mika?
Yeah.
Wow! It's cute! Good job!
You think so?
I'm sure she'll love that piggy!
It's Sailor Moon!
Oh, really. The real Sailor Moon
would cry if she saw it.
It's the thought that counts!
The thought!
Well, she's the envoy of love
and justice after all, right?
Right!
And the dolls that this person
makes are really adorable!
Oh, here we are.
Juban Art Museum
It's wonderful. This exhibition
seems like a success.
Thank you very much.
Where is Miss Mika?
She's making the last one
in the anteroom.
She worked herself to exhaustion
to make those dolls.
Is that right?
Nothing looks particularly out of place.
Oh, that's Rei!
Oh, you're right.
Wow! They're so adorable! Mamoru,
don't you think they're adorable?
Yeah...
Oh, that doll is made by the
doll maker's daughter! Look!
What?
Oh, that doll is made by the
doll maker's daughter! Look!
What?
Oh, don't you know?
I'm not too much into dolls.
Oh, Mamoru, you don't like dolls?
No, it's not like I hate them.
I'm so glad! Then shall we go?
Sure...
Do you want something?
No, pardon me.
I mistook you for somebody else.
Mamoru! Hurry!
Reception
How is Mika?
Well, actually...
Sis, I changed my mind.
What are you talking about?!
Mika is in the anteroom.
I'm sure she'll be happy to see you.
Okay! Come on, let's go, Shingo!
Okay.
Usagi...
Finished!
Mika, here...
The energy level has peaked!
Now, Jumo!
Mika!
Usagi, transform now!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
I'm the sailor warrior
of love and justice,
Sailor Moon!
How dare you break the doll Shingo
worked so hard to make?!
A doll has all the heart and
soul of its creator!
I bet even the dolls for the
Girl's Day Festival are upset!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
She's incredibly enthusiastic today.
I hope she'll be all right.
Oh, no! Help!
I knew it.
You won't escape!
Sailor Moon!
Bubble
Spray!
Oh, saved.
Sailor Moon, are you okay?
We should have come a little later.
Watch out, Sailor Moon!
Not again?!
Begone, Evil Spirits
Rin, Pyo, Tou, Sha, Kai, Jin, Retsu,
Zai, Zen! Begone, evil spirits!
I can't breathe!
Usagi!
Fire
Soul!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Your attacks are all useless!
They can cut like knives!
I'm getting an energy reading from
the monster's right leg!
Sailor Moon!
Aim for the monster's right foot!
Moon Tiara...
It's no use! I can't do it!
Who's there?!
Tuxedo Mask!
Now!
Right!
Moon Tiara Action!
What have I been doing?
Shingo!
You're awake.
Oh, Sailor Moon!
I punished the bad monster!
I hope you two get along well
together forever.
Sailor Moon rescued us!
Look what happened to the
present I made for you...
A present for me?
Um, I'm sorry about what
I did the other day.
It's okay.
After all, you came to my rescue.
Thank you!
Juban Municipal Primary School
Shingo, this is for what you did
for me the other day.
Wow! It looks just like her!
Sailor Moon is just
so cool, you know?!
So, you like Sailor Moon that much?!
Oh, that's not what I meant.
Wait, Mika!
It's not easy being a popular guy.
Yume no naka futari de ita yo ne
Hoshi tachi ni mamorarete
Tomodachi no toki ni wa ki ni sezu
Nanigenaku hanashite ita kedo
Anata dake ki ni naru
shunkan ga atta no
Motto kirei ni ima sugu naritai
Koi suru to nanika ga kawaru ne
Me o tojite tashikamete
Dakishimeta tokimeki sono
mama kono omoi tsutaetai