An enormous evil power
is about to be revived.
Finally, the time for the
final battle is here.
O sacred moonlight, please
give me strength.
Jupiter, Mercury, Venus, and Mars,
we will always be together!
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
The sunspot has continued
its abnormal expansion
and all over the world various
natural disasters, such as
earthquakes, volcanic eruptions,
and hurricanes are occurring,
believed to be due to
this phenomenon.
Concerning this, the
Meteorological Agency
has said that this is a first
in observation history
and they cannot say how
it will affect Japan.
We have to do something
about it soon.
And they cannot say how
it will affect Japan.
The Sailor Warriors Die!
The Tragic Final Battle
Okay, everyone, thank you
for waiting!
This is Usagi's special curry and rice!
I'm so touched that you
cooked dinner!
Oh, Dad, you're making such
a big deal out of it!
Okay, everyone, shall we dig in?
Is this really edible?
How rude! It looks bad,
but the taste is for real!
What's wrong, Usagi? Is something
the matter?
It's spicy!
I knew it.
Hikawa Shrine
Finally, it's time.
I can't wait!
I can't believe we've finally
come this far.
Hey, hey, Rei.
Did you at least kiss Yuichiro
before you left?
Why are you asking all of a sudden?!
Because if something were to happen,
you'd regret it.
Nothing like that is going to happen!
Ouch! You're mean! I was
just worried for you, Rei!
It's none of your business!
Usagi, let's stop thinking
about "what ifs".
She's right.
Like me? When this is all over,
I'm planning on having
a full-blown romance!
Mako... You're right. I'm sorry.
Love, huh? Maybe, me, too...
Come on, we don't have time
for chitchat.
Everyone, makeup!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Mercury Power
Mars Power
Jupiter Power
Venus Power
Makeup!
You're going to D-Point in the
North Pole in one shot!
How?
You'll combine your powers to teleport.
We're injured, so we'll stay behind
to avoid getting in your way,
but you'll be okay, right?
As long as the sailor warriors
work together,
you'll be able to defeat
Queen Beryl for sure!
Sailor Teleport!
Good luck!
May everyone comes home safely.
It's COLD!
How can you all act like
there's nothing wrong?!
Shut up! If you stand up straight,
you won't be cold!
When it's cold, it's cold
no matter what you do!
This certainly doesn't bode well.
Everyone, I found it!
A large amount of evil energy is
being released from over there!
Queen Metalia will be revived shortly.
I will not allow you to interfere!
Whoever wants to give them a
death sentence, come forward!
Please allow us, the DD Girls, to
take that assignment!
Wait!
The evil energy reading
is growing stronger!
It's coming!
Tuxedo Mask...
Tuxedo Mask!
Wait! It could be a trap!
This would usually be a trap.
But...
You get targeted first because
you're so simpleminded!
But...
I'll check into it right now.
Help me, Sailor Moon.
Sailor Moon...
I just can't leave him like that!
Wait, Sailor Moon.
Wait!
Sailor Moon!
Wait, Sailor Moon.
But he's suffering! How can you
ignore him like that?!
Let me go!
Everyone, watch out! He's a monster!
What?!
I told you so!
I'm sorry!
Hey, monster! How dare you trick me?!
I was a fool for being so gullible,
but you're bigger fools for crushing
a girl's innocent feelings!
Because, because, you've
seriously made me mad!
So, now...
You talk too much!
Anyway!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Oh! Five?!
You guys don't stand a chance
against us in D-Point!
Sailor Moon, I love you.
What kind of ninny would fall
for the same trick twice?!
Don't fall for it as I'm saying that!
But what if he's the real
thing this time?!
See?!
But!
Don't underestimate us!
Oh! Motoki!
Moon Tiara...
Fire...
We can't! Jupiter will get
caught in our attack!
Don't worry about me! Hurry,
go to where Queen Beryl is!
You've got some nerve using
electric shock against me!
What?!
Prepare yourselves!
Supreme Thunder!
You impertinent little...
Die!
Why you!
Jupiter!
Everyone...
We're coming to help you!
I'm done...
Instead, everyone hurry to
where Queen Beryl is.
No! We can't! We have
to all go together!
Mako, remember what you told me?!
That you'd have a full-blown
romance when you got back!
That's what you told me.
You shouldn't lie!
The King of Hell will yank
your tongue out.
There's no time for crying, Princess.
Come on, cheer up...
Mako!
You can't! You can't die!
Come on, let's go.
No!
Sailor Moon!
If this is what we have to go through,
we should just give them the
Silver Crystal.
What are you saying?!
That's right. That's what we should've
done from the start!
Listen, Queen Beryl! You can have
the Silver Crystal!
Wait, Sailor Moon!
Listen, Queen Beryl! You can have
the Silver Crystal!
Idiot!
Listen, Queen Beryl! You can have
the Silver Crystal!
Let me go! Because I have this,
that's why Mako...
I just want to get this over with
and go home...
I'm sorry, but please understand.
Don't waste Jupiter's death.
They're coming!
Okay!
You three go on ahead.
I'll hold them here.
But...
Past this point, we'll need
your powers,
since you have stronger attacks!
So, go!
Ami, you're not going to...
I won't die.
That's a promise!
Yes!
Now, come and get me!
Urawa!
So, I get to see this kind
of illusion too.
Bubble
Spray!
It's an illusion, but it has real heat!
Okay, the origin of this illusion
is the stone on her forehead!
I'll have to get rid of the origin
of the illusion.
Bubble
Spray!
Hurry up and turn into a roast pig!
How rude!
Then how about a baked potato?
Die!
Maybe this will be the
last time I use this.
I can't use my illusions anymore!
Ami's...
Ami's dead!
Don't cry like a baby
every single time!
Remember, more enemies
will be coming at us!
But... But I never expected
something like this...
Watch out!
Minako!
Stop it! You can have the Silver
Crystal, so let Minako go!
If you do that, I'll never forgive you!
Fool! Begging for her life
won't do you any good!
We'll take the Silver Crystal
after we kill all of you!
First, we'll take care of this one!
Minako!
Crescent
Beam!
Minako!
Sailor Moon.
What?
We always fought, but it was fun.
Why are you saying?!
I have to say it, just in case
something happens.
We said we weren't going
to talk about "what ifs"!
Oh, wait! I understand!
I'll do the rest by myself!
I'll beat them all and beat Queen
Beryl, and I'll come home,
so, Rei, go back home ahead of me!
I don't want you to die!
You still have the final big battle
ahead of you,
so you have to conserve your energy.
Oh, come on, no one
says I have to die!
Okay, Rei's gonna go take
care of them real quick!
Fire...
They're fast!
Rei!
Rei?
You're mine!
Rei!
How dare you?!
Now, that finally leaves
just the princess.
Rei!
Prepare to die!
What?!
I'm not done yet.
Fire
Soul!
Just like you said, I should
have kissed Yuichiro...
I really wish I had.
Mako...
Ami...
Minako...
Rei...
I know, this is a dream.
It's just a dream.
When I wake up,
everybody will say, "Good morning!"
Just like always.
And Rei will call me,
"Clumsy Usagi"...
Come on, cheer up.
Usagi, be strong!
Don't give up hope!
Usagi, stand up!
Okay.
We'll always be together!
Everyone...
Now, run!
Okay!
That's right! I'm not alone!
Never alone!
During the day, the
fragrance of flowers
During the night, the
twinkle of the stars
It's a world no one knows about
With white shoes clicking
Cross the white moon bridge
And there lives a princess,
dreaming of a sweet kiss
Offer a prayer to the moon
It will surely bring you happiness
Go round and round, the
moon's merry-go-round
Make that serene dress made
of glass flutter in the wind
She's always watching over us
Moon, moon princess