Hey, hey! A human's transformed
into a monster!
There's no way I can punish him!
It's a first time experience
for Sailor Moon.
This is no time for that kind of talk!
Oh, I'm just gonna toss all the
rules out the window!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino. I don't look like
a super heroine, but I am!
As you know, I transform myself
by using a peculiar brooch
and fight against bad guys.
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
And my friends are the smart
and sweet Ami Mizuno,
and a slightly quick-tempered
psychic girl, Rei Hino.
Both of them are so dependable,
I feel like I'll fall behind.
But anyway, I just have
to do my best!
Jupiter, the Brawny Girl In Love
Awaken, oh great ruler.
With this supremely blissful energy,
return to life, my great ruler!
The energy of humans has revived
me from my long sleep.
I have long awaited this day!
But at times,
my consciousness is still drawn
into the depths of slumber.
Find the legendary Silver Crystal!
The legendary Silver Crystal
is necessary
for me to completely revive!
But we know nothing of
its whereabouts.
When the Seven Monsters
have been revived along with
the rainbow crystals,
the legendary Silver
Crystal will shine!
Oh, no, I'm late! I'm late!
Hey, Usagi! You forgot something!
Oh, thanks! Can you
bring it with you?!
Oh, ouch!
Ouch!
Sorry!
You broke my leg! Ouch!
Yo! What're you gonna do
about this, Missy?
Stop it!
What?!
I saw everything!
She just bumped into him, and
you're getting on her case?
Talk about cheap.
What did you say?!
Hey, you might be a cutie,
but you're not getting away with that!
You bitch!
Amazing.
Are you all right?
Oh, yes!
Be careful.
A rose-shaped pierced earring.
That's so nice.
When the Seven Monsters
have been revived along with
the rainbow crystals,
the legendary Silver
Crystal will shine!
I seem to recall that a long time ago,
our allies, the great Seven Monsters,
were sealed away by our old enemies.
Oh, our strongest warriors of legend,
the Seven Monsters!
Damn our hateful old enemies!
Into the seven shards of the
legendary Silver Crystal,
they sealed away the Seven Monsters,
and dropped them onto the Earth.
And those seven shards are
called the rainbow crystals.
Rainbow crystals...
What of the Seven Monsters?
They were reborn as human beings,
and have lost their memory
as monsters.
I see.
So, if we recover the rainbow crystals
from those human beings,
we can get a hold of the legendary
Silver Crystal, correct?
Yes. And the strongest warriors, the
Seven Monsters will also be revived.
I have modified it so it will only
respond to the rainbow crystals.
Thank you.
Zoi!
One of the rainbow crystals
is in this man's body.
Hurry! Let's go! The seats
will be taken!
It's lunch time, lunch time.
My tummy is groaning.
That's the girl with the rose-shaped
pierced earrings!
Miss Usagi!
Don't show up out of nowhere!
Oh, no, that girl transferred
into Class 6 today.
What?
Her name is Makoto Kino. She has
enormous physical strength!
What?
Her name is Makoto Kino. She has
enormous physical strength!
Rumor is, she was kicked out of
her previous school
because she got into a fight.
You'd better stay away from her, Miss
Usagi. If you're not careful...
Huh?
Oh, Miss Usagi!
Wow! Her lunch looks
so cute and yummy!
Her pouch is adorable, too!
Oh, those seasoned rice
balls look so yummy!
Who's there?!
Hello!
Oh, it's you. I didn't know you
went to this school.
I'm Usagi Tsukino!
Why don't you join me?
Oh, okay! Thank you
for this morning.
What?!
Would you like to have some?
What?! But I don't eat
too much, though...
What?
Thanks for the food!
It's good!
I'm glad you like it!
I don't know why,
but everyone here's scared of
me and won't talk to me.
Hey, Mako. Oh, sorry, you're
okay with Mako, right?
Oh, sure.
Your mother must be a genius chef!
Oh, this? I made it myself.
What?! That's amazing!
Wow! Teach me, teach me!
Oh, maybe I should get you to
fix my lunch! Just kidding!
Miss Usagi is a genius when
it comes to making friends.
Crown
Hey, Mako, why don't you wear
our school uniform?
Crown
This is more my style.
I see.
Oh? I wonder if Motoki's
not working today?
Who is this Motoki? Oh, is he...
your older brother?
Bro...
No, no. Motoki is...
Excuse me?!
Usagi!
So, this is where you were.
What is it?
Well, Luna says that
girl bothers her.
That girl? You mean Mako?
Right.
I think you're thinking too much, Luna.
Oh, shoot! It beat me!
Mako!
What?
Let me introduce you.
This is Makoto Kino. She just
transferred to Juban Junior High today.
Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you, too!
And this is the smart Ami
and the meanie Rei.
Who are you calling a meanie?
You!
I didn't hear you. Who did you say?
What year, month, day, day of the
week, hour, minute or second
was I ever mean to you?!
That's why you're mean!
You guys really get along.
What?! No way!
She's always picking fights with
me whenever she sees me!
Who picks the fights?!
You do!
They say, the more you fight,
the better friends you are.
She's got a point there.
Oh, she's so cute!
That cat with the crescent bald
spot is named Luna.
She's staying at my house.
Wow!
Wow! He did it again! It's amazing!
What?
Wow! It's amazing! He got two! Wow!
That's something!
Oh, Usagi!
Oh, Yumi!
Did you see that?!
Yeah, I did!
That guy's called "Joe, the
Crane Game Raider."
Crane Game Raider?
What the heck is that?
He's a genius crane game player!
They say that when he goes
after an arcade,
it loses every last one of its
stuffed animals to him.
Wow, isn't that amazing, Mako?
He looks exactly like him.
Mako?
My senior...
Hello, there? Mako?
Mako? Earth to Mako?!
What could have gotten into her?
There we go! Oops!
I've found you!
What the?!
This will be over quickly.
Zoi!
Stop it!
Stop right there!
It's not nice to pick on people
weaker than you.
Shoot!
You'll get hurt if you interfere!
What are you doing?
Not too bad.
Barbaric.
You injured my precious face!
Mako! Whoa, what's going on?!
A fight?!
Shoot!
Wait!
What's wrong?!
Are you okay?
Mako, what happened?
Let go!
Just leave me alone!
Oh, but...
What's wrong with him?! We were
worried for him and...
Oh, Mako?!
What's wrong?!
I felt it.
Felt what?
I felt a strong evil aura coming from
the guy she was just fighting.
What?!
He might be part of the Dark Kingdom!
No way!
Then Mako and that guy are in danger!
Wait for me!
How long are you going to
keep following me?!
Well, it seems like someone's
after you, so...
I'll be your bodyguard!
There's no reason for anyone
to go after me!
You've won too much on those
crane games, so... Bang!
Maybe the arcades hired a hit man!
No way.
Hey, teach me the trick to
those crane games.
You could never do it.
What's wrong?
Welcome!
Hey.
I want to have a cup of
coffee by myself!
What a jerk!
That's why I like him...
He looks exactly like my senior at
school who broke my heart.
That's totally the face of a girl in love.
You don't need to keep me
company, you know.
Now, now...
He's telling you to come inside!
You did it!
What shall I do?
What are you saying after
all this time?!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Oh, wait a minute! Wait!
No waiting! Go for it, Mako!
Well, uh...
Have a seat.
Okay.
Don't get the wrong idea.
What?!
It's just too annoying to have someone
standing outside staring at me.
Okay.
The reason I'm good at crane games
is because I have a kind
of psychic power.
Psychic power?
I've had a strange power
since I was a kid.
What?!
So, do you get it now? No one
else can imitate what I do.
That's why I told you that
you could never do it.
But you know... Isn't that
called cheating?
I don't care! I should make
good use of my talent.
I don't know about that.
Can I help you?
Oh, I'd like a large curry and rice...
No, that's not what I meant!
A milk tea.
Help!
That man!
You're going to leave a girl
behind and run?!
I don't care about that girl!
She just followed me!
What did you say?! And you
call yourself a man?!
I don't care! Anyway, a huge
girl like her isn't my type!
Zoi!
Just as we thought, he's from
the Dark Kingdom!
Oh, Mako! Are you okay?! Mako!
He said the same thing...
Mako?
Damn it!
Help!
You don't need to run.
You're one of us.
One of you?!
I'm taking the rainbow crystal.
So, this is it.
Stop right there!
Sailor Moon!
You're a bit late, Sailor Moon.
Who are you?!
Let me introduce myself.
I am one of the Great Four of the
Dark Kingdom, Zoisite.
What?!
I'll leave the rest to you,
monster Geisein!
He disappeared!
He's gone!
Geisein!
He's turned into a monster!
Geisei...
I'm a huge fan of Sailor Moon!
How dare you do this to her?!
That's...
Take this!
Amazing!
Geisein!
Watch out!
I can't move!
Sailor Moon!
Wait!
You're a sailor warrior!
Luna, you spoke!
Hold this transforming pen and say,
"Jupiter Power Makeup!"
And help Sailor Moon!
Okay.
Jupiter Power Makeup!
Sailor Jupiter!
Mako is?!
My guardian, Jupiter!
Brew a storm! Call the clouds!
Bring down the lightning!
Supreme Thunder!
Geisein!
Supreme Sundae?
Okay, one more time!
No, you can't!
What?!
That monster still has the
heart of a human!
He was originally a human being!
What?!
Then, what are we supposed to do?!
Turn that monster back
into its human self!
But, how?!
What's this?!
It's the Crescent Moon Wand!
Say, "Moon Healing Escalation!"
Got it!
Moon Healing Escalation!
Refresh!
You are the fourth warrior,
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Jupiter?
Sailor Moon, we now have
all four sailor warriors.
You have to become the leader
and protect the princess!
Me?! The leader?!
That's right! The Crescent Moon Wand
is proof that you're the leader!
Crown
Take that and that and that!
And that and that!
I hate... I hate men!
One more time!
Hi, Usagi!
Oh, Motoki!
I heard that Crane Game Joe
was here yesterday!
I wish I could've seen him!
Really? Oh, let me introduce her.
She's my friend, Makoto Kino.
Hello!
He's exactly like my senior at
school who broke my heart.
What?!
Yesterday, you told me he looked
exactly like Crane Game Joe!
No, his voice sounds exactly the same.
Oh, Mako!
What a weird girl.
In my dream, you and I were together
Protected by the stars
When we were friends,
it didn't bother us
And we casually talked to each other
But there was a moment when
I noticed only you
I want to become prettier
right here and now
Something changes when
you fall in love
I close my eyes and check
to make sure
I want to convey the thrill I felt
when we held each other