How dare you manipulate the
children's hero, Red Man,
and turn the special natural treasure,
Lake Akan's Marimo Balls,
into weapons?!
The Hokkaido Tourist Association
never gave you permission
to do that, did they?!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino.
As you know, I'm a sailor warrior of
love and justice, Sailor Moon.
But it's not easy, you know.
I have to get a hold of the
legendary Silver Crystal
before the bad guys get it,
but to do that, I have to find the
seven rainbow crystals!
Oh, man. But anyhow, we've got
four sailor warriors now,
so it'll work out somehow.
Umino's Resolve! I'll Protect Naru
Code name 0091. This is Luna.
My secret password is "The rabbit
on the moon makes rice cakes."
Please respond.
"The moon rice cakes are sticky."
"When I grilled them, they puffed up."
So, how are the Sailor Warriors
coming along?
Well, one of them still needs
to be more self-aware,
but the rest of them are
doing fairly well.
The day when all five sailor warriors
will come together is near.
What? Really?
Yes. Therefore, I think it may be good
to tell them about that issue soon.
Are you sure?
The Dark Kingdom seems to be
getting impatient these days.
We need to heighten the sailor
warriors' awareness of the situation.
I understand.
Finally, it's time to tell
them everything.
What does Luna want with
us in the middle of night?
Everyone's here, I see.
Has another monster appeared?
You must not be surprised!
Oh, you scared me!
Listen very carefully to what
I'm about to say.
I was sent here from that moon!
What?!
From the moon?!
Why?!
No way!
Why did you come to Earth?
To awaken you girls.
This is sort of unbelievable.
But if Luna says so,
I'll believe her.
Thank you, Ami.
The princess you're looking for is a
descendant of the Moon Kingdom.
A descendant?
Of the Moon Kingdom?
There's a kingdom on the moon?
It's like a fairy tale.
You girls are certain to
find the princess.
And you have to protect the princess.
There's not a moment to lose.
Hey, Luna.
Is there really a rabbit on the moon
that makes rice cakes?
Excuse me!
Beautiful.
They really are pretty.
However. The true beauty of the
rainbow crystals is only revealed
when all seven are gathered together.
Do you not think so?
For you, Master Kunzite,
I shall get a hold of the rest
of the rainbow crystals.
I will be counting on you.
Once we get all seven
rainbow crystals,
we will be able to obtain the
legendary Silver Crystal.
I want the legendary Silver Crystal
as soon as possible,
so that I may see Queen Beryl
smile with delight.
Oh! This is not fair!
That fried shrimp looks so good.
Trade it for my green pepper?
If you want it, here you go.
Thanks!
Woohoo! You two make
a perfect couple!
Are you boyfriend and girlfriend now?
Do we look like it?
We're not like that! We're just
friends. Just friends.
Just friends?
Friends, huh?
Umino's not a bad person,
and he helps me study
since he's smart...
But I just don't have that
special feeling for him.
You can't be so moony!
This is where you have to
be more aggressive!
But I don't know what to do.
Then, since I have lots of
experience in romance,
I will tell you what to do.
Here it is! You need to transform
into a cool guy!
A cool guy? For example?
Be just like Tuxedo Mask!
Tuxedo Mask would be?
Tuxedo Mask is...
I see! So, if I become
this Tuxedo Mask,
I'll get to be Naru's boyfriend?!
What? No, uh, that's
not what I meant.
You need to learn from Tuxedo
Mask's example and...
Okay! Starting today, I will
be Tuxedo Mask!
This is the birth of
Tuxedo Umino Mask!
Hey, has someone been following
us for a while?
What?
Be good, be good now! Stop it!
Tuxedo Umino Mask is here!
Evil minion, baring your
fangs at Naru!
In the name of justice,
I will punish you!
What are you doing?!
Excuse you! How frightened you
must be, my poor doggy.
What are you doing, Umino?
I am not Umino.
I am Tuxedo Umino Mask
of love and justice!
Well, then. Good-bye!
What the heck?
Crown
Hey, you wanna go in for a bit?
Good idea.
No! You must never make stops
on your way home!
You will end up spending
all your allowance, too.
However, if you absolutely
insist on it...
You have to step over
Tuxedo Umino Mask!
Excuse us, then!
Tuxedo Umino Mask may die,
but justice will live on!
What's wrong with Umino?
Who knows...
Hi, Usagi!
Motoki!
Oh, that's right. I have
two free tickets.
Are you interested in going?
Free tickets?! For two?!
He's asking me out on a date!
A movie with Motoki!
Yes! I feel a little shy!
I'm too old for the Red Man Show
at the amusement park, so...
Red Man Show?!
Oh, I guess you guys are too old
for the Red Man Show, too.
I'll take them!
What?! You're going to go?!
No, you and Umino are going!
What?!
I shall accompany you!
I'm not sure about this.
Umino's trying really hard
in his own way.
You should be understanding of that.
That's okay. I'm not...
I'm just not...
Okay, okay. I get it. I'll go.
Happy now?
Yes! Tuxedo Umino Mask is
cheerful yet again today!
Come forth, my new power!
I have managed to improve
the Black Crystal.
With this, I'll be able to transform
humans into monsters.
Master Kunzite,
soon, I shall steal the rainbow crystals
back from the sailor warriors.
Jewelry
In order to lure Sailor Moon
out into the open,
I'll use Naru Osaka by turning
her into a monster.
Who is it?
Tuxedo Mask!
He found out what I was going
to do already? Impressive.
Out of respect for you, I shall
withdraw this time.
What the heck was that?!
But I'm glad I was here.
Who's there?
It's Tuxedo Umino Mask!
What time do you think
it is right now?!
Well, we haven't decided on a meeting
time for tomorrow, so...
Naru!
When should I be at the amusement
park tomorrow?!
9 o'clock? 10 o'clock? 11 o'clock?!
12 o'clock?! Hello?!
Okay, I'll see you at 12 o'clock.
Okay, 12 o'clock then? Let's
have lunch together!
Tuxedo Umino Mask will make lots
of your favorite fried shrimp!
Usagi, what happened to your
task of finding the princess?!
After everything I told you!
Monster Fighter
Red Man Show
After everything I told you!
Monster Fighter
Red Man Show
You weren't listening to a
word I said, were you?
Monster Fighter
Red Man Show
I was listening. But see,
as a sentimental girl,
Monster Fighter
Red Man Show
I'm worried about how my friend's
romantic life is going.
Monster Fighter
Red Man Show
Can you understand that?
Honestly! You have absolutely
no sense of duty.
Anyway, why are you following me?
As a sentimental messenger
from the moon,
I'm worried about my foolish
sailor warrior's actions.
Can you understand that?
Oh, there they are!
Hey, Usagi!
Monster Fighter, Red Man
Red Man has arrived!
Red Man, Leg Attack!
I'm glad you didn't come
in that weird outfit.
Are you kidding? It's right in there.
If something should happen, I'll
transform, so please don't worry.
Oh, boy...
Red Man, Punch!
Black Crystal, transform
that girl into a monster.
Zoi!
Victory! Red Man!
He transformed into a monster!
It's a monster against monster fight!
Monster Akan has arrived!
Monster?!
Oh, I cannot believe I messed up.
Go! Go!
Take these Marimo Balls
from Lake Akan!
What the heck are you doing?!
It's dangero...
Luna, what's going on?!
This must be the work of
the Dark Kingdom!
Naru!
Take these Marimo Balls
from Lake Akan!
Run, Naru!
Usagi!
You cannot run now!
Stop it!
Umino!
Tuxedo Umino Mask will protect Naru!
Take these fried shrimp!
Don't! Umino!
Why you!
Akan!
Umino!
Tuxedo Umino Mask will protect Naru,
even if it costs me my life!
Umino...
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Eat this!
Akan! Akan! Akan!
Umino!
Naru, hurry! Run!
Akan!
No!
How dare you turn the
natural treasure,
Lake Akan's Marimo Balls,
into weapons!
The Hokkaido Tourist Association
never gave you permission
to do that, did they?!
Akan!
I'm the sailor warrior
of love and justice,
Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
All's well that ends well, I guess.
Zoisite!
I was waiting for you, Sailor Moon.
I have a favor to ask.
What?!
Please give me the rainbow
crystal that you have.
You've gotta be kidding!
Then, you don't mind if everybody
wrapped in Marimo Balls
suffocates and dies?
What?!
In a couple more minutes,
the people trapped inside will begin
to have difficulty breathing!
Now, hand over the rainbow crystal!
Come on now! I'm waiting here!
Okay...
Here.
Good girl.
You're...
Tuxedo Mask!
I cannot let you have that
rainbow crystal!
Shut up!
Akan!
Zoi!
Tuxedo Umino Mask... is fighting.
Moon Tiara Action!
Just a little bit, okay?!
Moon Healing Escalation!
Refresh!
Wow, Usagi did pretty
well on her own.
Oh! No!
The rainbow crystal!
What?!
I have the rainbow crystal now.
No way! Give that back!
Good day.
Darn that Zoisite!
The rainbow crystal!
I will get that rainbow crystal back!
Thank you, Tuxedo Mask!
You do not need to thank me.
When I have gotten the rainbow
crystal back, I will take it.
What?
Good-bye. We shall meet again.
Monster Fighter, Red Man
Red Man has arrived!
I guess that was part of the show!
That was amazing! I've never seen
something like that before!
Monster Fighter, Red Man
That was amazing! I've never seen
something like that before!
Monster Fighter, Red Man
Red Man, Leg Attack!
Thank you, Umino. You were very cool!
Just call me Tuxedo Umino Mask.
Tuxedo Umino Mask...
Usagi!
Letting the rainbow crystal get
stolen was a huge failure.
Are you listening, Usagi?!
Please tell me, music box...
I don't understand what's on
Tuxedo Mask's mind.
I will take the rainbow crystal.
Hiru ni wa hana no kaori
Yoru ni wa hoshi no matataki
Soko wa daremo shiranai sekai nano
Shiroi kutsu o narashite
Shiroi tsuki no hashi watatte
Amai kisu no yume o miteru
ohimesama ga sunde iru no
Inori o sasagete moon
Kitto shiawase ni shitekureru
Maware maware tsuki no
merry-go-round
Suzushige na glass no
dress hirugaeshite
Itsudatte mimamotte iru wa
Moon moon princess