Figure skating is the beautiful
winter sport everyone loves!
How dare you use it as a weapon
to hurt an innocent girl?!
It's totally unforgivable!
In the name of my favorite skaters,
Katarina Witt and Midori Ito,
Sailor Moon is gonna
punish you, okay?!
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
They're wonderful!
You can tell why Janelyn and Misha
are Olympic gold medallists.
So beautiful!
Ouch!
Oh!
Usagi!
But if she likes figure skating,
maybe she's becoming more aware
of herself as the princess.
Yes. After all, figure skating was
the most popular sport
in the world of the moon.
I know! The princess's skating
was especially beautiful!
What?! Really?!
I guess I was gifted with
a lot of talent!
Stare...
Paired With a Monster?! Ice Queen Mako
Figure skating...
If I use this sport, supposedly
the most popular
among the girls on the moon...
You could lure Sailor Moon out
and finally take the Silver Crystal
away from her.
Is that what you are saying?
On my honor...
You will lure her out
and stake your honor on
this makeshift trap?
Endymion!
If you are a proud warrior,
should you not attack your
enemy head on?
A battle is meaningless
without a victory.
If you had not interfered unnecessarily,
we would already have the
Silver Crystal in our hands!
Heh, I wouldn't know about that.
Well, enough of that.
Kunzite, you may set that plan
into motion immediately.
Yes, my lady.
What are you doing, Misha?!
What about you?!
What kind of timing was that
on that jump?!
That's because you...
Oh, damn it all! That's enough
practice for today!
Wait a second!
Janelyn, I thought we were
Olympic gold medallists!
If these terrible practices continue,
I'm going to go look for
a new partner!
That's my line!
I cannot allow you to break up.
You two have been given a mission,
and that is to work for
the Dark Kingdom.
Wow! I had no idea we had
a skating rink like this.
Yeah, they just built it!
And to commemorate its opening,
the Olympic gold medallists,
Janelyn and Misha are
going to coach us!
Isn't that amazing?!
But, so, why did we have
to come, too?
I have an open national
mock exam tomorrow,
so I need to go home to study.
Oh, the thing is...
Only groups of five girls get in free!
Yup, yup!
Groups of five?
Why?
See?!
There's something suspicious!
It makes you want to check it out,
doesn't it?!
It's one of those, "Ask, and you
shall be answered," things!
Shouldn't that be, "Ask, and
you shall receive?"
Oops!
Shouldn't that be, "Ask, and
you shall receive?"
Oops!
Oh, really?
It doesn't matter which it is!
Come on, let's go ask!
Wow! There are so many people!
They're all just here
out of curiosity.
A skating rink... Brings back
memories, doesn't it?
I know! Oh? Where's Usagi?
Oh! Oops! Hey, wait, everyone!
It hurts!
Oh, it's the usual pattern.
She certainly delivers, doesn't she?
Oh, Usagi.
This is just so embarrassing!
Janelyn! Misha!
Where?! Where?!
It's really them!
They're skating!
Oh, Misha!
He looks just like him...
Everyone, thank you for coming!
Let's all have fun today,
skating together!
Yeah!
Of course, we will!
No matter what you're doing,
the basics are important.
The first step is getting
used to the ice.
Okay!
Then, since you're an energetic group,
come on out into the rink first.
Oh, yes!
Oh, no! I still don't have
my skates on!
What are you doing?! Hurry up!
Oh, but...
Usagi, you slowpoke!
Rei's being mean to me again!
Okay, here we go, then! Now!
There!
Usagi?
What?
Is this your first time skating?
Don't you worry!
After all, I was an expert at this
on the moon world!
Then, I'll be going.
One, two. One, two. One...
Mako...
She's good!
Not bad. I'm gonna do it, too!
Usagi, time for your brilliant debut!
Usagi!
I knew it.
This isn't how it's supposed to go...
That's not right!
Oh, boy.
I'm not going to expect
a lot out of Usagi.
Wow!
I remember now.
Sailor Jupiter was also an expert,
considered to be as good
as the princess.
Mako looks so wonderful.
Wow! That was amazing!
Very nice! Now, everyone,
let us all skate!
Okay!
Usagi!
Hang in there.
My brilliant debut...
Ouch!
No...
Master Kunzite!
Find Sailor Moon through her
athletic abilities and agility.
Does it look like it will work?
You can count on me.
My judgment as an Olympic
gold medallist is flawless.
Good. However, you have never
actually met the sailor warriors.
Do not let you guard down.
Yes, Sir!
No...
Sailor Moon is known to be
a superb warrior.
They say she has a clumsy side,
but this is out of the question.
Misha?
Wonderful girl, would you please
skate with me?
Excuse me, if you'd like,
I'm free any time to be...
He's so gorgeous.
The way his hair hangs...
It looks exactly like my senior at
school who broke my heart.
Oh, Coach?
Something isn't right.
Is this girl Sailor Moon?
Then, here we go.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry! I know I'm heavy.
Not at all...
In apology...
Wow! It's amazing!
She lifted a man up into the air...
It's a technique no one in the world
has accomplished yet!
This is...
Amazing.
Misha, how could you pass over me?!
Were you serious about breaking up?!
Today's free lesson is now over.
Everyone, please leave the rink
and go home immediately.
Why?!
That's no fun!
Excuse me, I have to go home now.
I won't let you go.
You are the best partner
for me in the world.
Coach...
Too bad. I hope they do it again.
But at least we got to
see them in person.
Hey, everyone.
Where are Usagi and Mako?
Mako has to stay behind.
The coach is giving her
a special lesson.
I'm so jealous!
Oh? Usagi was with us until
just a minute ago.
She's such a turtle!
What's going on?!
Something's wrong!
Could it really have been another trap
set by the Dark Kingdom?!
Shoot!
And I run swiftly over here.
Employees Only
I can't just back down and go home!
I'm gonna get them to
give me lessons, too!
That girl is skating so nimbly
with my Misha!
Misha!
This isn't fair!
This is just so exciting!
That's so mean!
What the heck is this?
Oh! Don't tell me this is...
You must have had some
figure skating experience.
Won't you tell me the truth?
Coach...
Misha!
Misha, so you and I are
really over, aren't we?!
If I have to give you up to
an amateur like that,
I'd rather kill you!
What?!
Wait!
Oh! Coach, run!
Don't jump to conclusions, Janelyn!
I was just trying to find out whether
she was Sailor Moon!
That's a lie!
It's true, her technique is first class,
but you cannot form a pair
based solely on that!
I thought you knew that!
Coach, you weren't...
Misha, it's too late! I can't stop now!
Take your hands off her!
A monster?!
Janelyn!
Triple Axle Kick!
Come with me, Misha, my partner.
We are the greatest pair.
Coach was a monster?!
We are amazing after all!
We are the best pair in the world!
Misha!
Janelyn!
Together, we are the Zoyrin Geller!
Now that you have seen us,
we cannot let you return alive!
Coach!
Combination Jump Attack!
Oh, Mako! That's it!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
I'm a sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
We will deliver the finishing blow!
Go right ahead!
How dare you use graceful
figure skating as a weapon
to hurt an innocent girl?!
Sailor Moon will not let you
get away with it!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Sailor Moon!
We have been waiting for you!
The Silver Crystal will be ours!
I won't let you have it!
No way! I can't skate, even
when I'm transformed?!
Sailor Moon, prepare yourself!
Death
Spiral!
Die!
What?!
That was...
Tuxedo Mask! You rescued me!
Do not misunderstand.
I just do not like their
underhanded method,
which has dragged an innocent
bystander into this mess.
What?
After I have brought the monsters
under control,
I will return for the Silver Crystal.
No, you wouldn't...
Master Endymion, your help
is not necessary!
We will not hold back,
even for you!
Do you think you could win
in a fight against me?
I think it'd be better if you
didn't taunt them.
Interesting!
Have a taste of the techniques
of gold medallists!
I told you so!
Double Spin Kick!
Jump!
Here we go!
I'm skating!
What impudence!
They're coming!
Jump! High!
Easy for you to say!
Die!
Oh, fine! To hell with it!
I jumped! I jumped all on my own!
I'm so amazing!
A nice jump, Sailor Moon!
Thanks.
Sit Spin Kick!
This is it!
Supreme
Thunder!
Jupiter!
Coach, please stop!
Go back to who you were!
Why you!
Everyone!
So, you are all here,
sailor warriors.
I pity you, Endymion.
If you had not interfered,
this need not have happened.
What is this?!
It's cold!
Master Kunzite...
This is the icy hell of
absolute zero temperature.
Once you have all turned
into ice figures,
I will return and take my sweet time
getting the Silver Crystal.
Damn you, Kunzite!
It's cold!
I can't hold out much longer!
We're going to die!
So, that's it!
It stopped.
We're saved.
Sailor Moon, hurry!
Oh?! Okay!
Moon Healing Escalation!
Refresh!
Janelyn...
Misha...
Oh? Huh? Tuxedo Mask,
where are you?! Tuxedo Mask?!
Mako...
What? Don't think my feelings
have been hurt!
I'm not gonna let it bother me!
Man, I better just find another
nice guy soon and...
Huh?
He's gorgeous!
The shape of his nose
looks just like my senior at school
who broke my heart!
Oh, Mako!
During the day,
the fragrance of flowers
During the night,
the twinkle of the stars
It's a world no one knows about
With white shoes clicking
Cross the white moon bridge
And there lives a princess,
dreaming of a sweet kiss
Offer a prayer to the moon
It will surely bring you happiness
Go round and round,
the moon's merry-go-round
Make that serene dress made of glass
flutter in the wind
She's always watching over us
Moon, moon princess