Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short
sunzen ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino. I don't look like
a super heroine, but I am!
As you know, I transform myself
by using a peculiar brooch
and fight against bad guys.
I'm the sailor warrior of love and
justice, Sailor Moon!
And my friends are the smart
and sweet Ami Mizuno
and a slightly quick-tempered
psychic girl, Rei Hino.
Both of them are so dependable,
I feel like I'll fall behind.
But anyway, I just have to do my best!
A Powerful New Enemy!
Nephrite's Evil Crest
Jadeite randomly stole
energy from anybody.
If you ask me, that is a ridiculous
way to take care of business.
Really?
Then Nephrite, how would you do it?
I will not go after big groups
of people like Jadeite did.
I will show you that I can get enough
energy from one individual.
Is that so?
All humans are controlled by
the movement of the stars.
And every one of them
has their own fate.
The same is true of their energy.
Each human has a moment in their
life when their energy level peaks.
In short, I will read the movement
of the stars
and go after the humans when their
energy level has peaked.
You seem very confident.
Zoisite, why are you here?
Overconfidence can be your downfall.
Go away!
I will infiltrate the human world
and take advantage of
their weaknesses.
I do not need advice from you!
I can picture you throwing yourself
at Queen Beryl's mercy.
Ooh, how scary.
Nephrite, I leave this
in your hands.
Oh, there she is!
Rui, how are you doing?
Do you think you can win the
next tournament?
I don't know.
Everyone in Japan is cheering for you.
Please say something!
Sorry, but I have practice.
The stars know everything.
O stars, grant me your
mysterious powers.
The proud Sagittarius, Chiron,
is about to fire his arrow at the
center of the Milky Way.
The target that Sagittarius
has chosen...
Rui Saionji, I will take your energy.
Saionji, go for it!
Saionji!
Yeah! She did it!
Rui, sister, you're the best!
I never knew.
Knew what?
That Rui was your older sister.
Huh?
I will punish you if you keep
secrets from your friend!
Huh?
I will punish you if you keep
secrets from your friend!
You're so stupid, Usagi.
Stu...
That's mean, Naru! You didn't
have to go that far!
I'm an only child. Besides, we
have different surnames.
That's true. But didn't you
just call Rui your sister?
Well, Rui's mother has been a good
customer at our store for a long time.
So, we've been playing together
since we were little.
She's only a year older than me, but
she's been like a big sister to me.
Oh, so that's why.
Wow, he's gorgeous!
Oh my god, you're right!
I heard that he's a
successful businessman.
Do you know him?
He's supposed to be the president
of a company
Do you know him?
He's supposed to be the president
of a company
that was established around
here recently.
That was established around
Wow!
He's so handsome!
Please don't enter the court
without permission!
Use your weight more
when you hit the ball!
What?!
Your racket, please.
Here...
Okay, try now!
Rui!
A fly could land on
a serve like that.
Who are you?
Masato Sanjoin, just
an eccentric coach.
I'm sorry.
My loyal monster,
possess this racket,
bring Rui Saionji's energy to
its peak level and steal it!
Just think of putting your
weight behind the ball.
Yes, Sir.
Someone come receive her serve!
Me, me! I'll do it!
When did he get in there?!
First come, first serve!
Miss Saionji, I'm ready any
time you are!
Amazing!
Did you see that?! It's amazing!
Thank you so much...
The more you use that racket,
the more your energy will grow.
Oh, shoot!
It feels good.
She's so cool!
Something's not right with Rui.
Jubancho
Shopping District
Code name 0091. This is Luna.
My secret password is "The rabbit
on the moon makes rice cakes."
Please respond.
"The moon rice cakes are sticky."
"When I grilled them,
they puffed up."
I have found out who the enemy is.
What? Really?
Of course!
Right.
The name of the enemy organization
is the Dark Kingdom.
Right.
The name of the enemy organization
is the Dark Kingdom.
They seem to be after human
energy for some reason.
Human energy?
Hikawa Shrine
Dark Kingdom...
We have to brace ourselves
to get these guys.
Let's go after them and crush
them with one blow!
The way we are now, we aren't
capable of that yet.
Exactly! Right now, you need to study
more and make yourselves more fit.
I know! How about playing tennis
to make ourselves more fit?!
There's this super-cool coach
named Mr. Masato Sanjoin.
I see. So, you're going to give
up on Tuxedo Mask?
I didn't think about it like that.
That is a problem...
I'm glad I have Ami and Rei.
If Usagi was all I had,
the Dark Kingdom would have stolen
all of mankind's energy by now.
What?!
Maybe it's some kind of mistake that
Usagi is a member of our group.
What?!
Maybe it's some kind of mistake that
Usagi is a member of our group.
What's with you?! What's with you?!
What's with you?!
Both of you, you're going too far.
Ami! Ami, you're all I've got!
You're the only one who
understands me!
So, why don't the two
of us play tennis?
Oh, but I have cram school. Sorry.
Knew it!
Miss Saionji...
What's wrong? If it's about the racket,
I already gave you another one.
Let's keep going.
Yes...
Rui, you weren't like this before.
Jewelry
I'm sorry for the short notice.
That's okay, I don't mind.
You have something on your mind?
Well, I don't know what to say.
I'm just worried about Rui.
Now, she misuses tennis
equipment and things.
She never did things
like that before.
It's like she's a totally
different person.
Maybe she's just tense because the
important tournament's coming up.
That's what I thought at first,
but that's not it.
I wonder what's happened to her?
Rui, did something happen?
If there's anything I can help
you with, just let me know.
This is none of your business.
If there's anything I can help
you with, just let me know.
This is none of your business.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why Rui
would act like that.
I think maybe something
terrible has happened to her,
but she won't say anything to me.
I see.
Hey, Naru. Why don't we
investigate what happened?
I will help you!
Usagi...
Cheer up!
Is this the tennis
school Rui goes to?
Yeah. She practices
here after school.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing!
I have a bad feeling about this.
This couldn't be the work
of a monster, could it?
Oh, but if I do a good job here,
I can get back at Luna and Rei.
Usagi...
Hey, are you all right?
What a ball!
What's wrong? You're both pros!
You should be able to hit this!
Please give us a break!
Okay, here comes the next one!
Stop!
Out of my way!
No! Please stop acting
like this, Rui!
Out of my way!
No! Please stop acting
like this, Rui!
Get out of my way, Naru!
No!
Naru is worried about you!
Move!
The energy level is at its peak.
Go, Tesnie!
Your energy is mine now!
It was a monster after all! Okay!
It's time to show them what
you've got, Usagi!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
A monster can never
aim for the ace!
Misusing tennis for evil deeds...
I bet even Navratilova
is crying now!
I'm the sailor warrior
of love and justice,
Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon, I
will punish you!
Impudent girl!
What is this?!
This is so sad!
It's so high!
I should have come here
with everybody!
You look good out there!
Who's there?!
Tuxedo Mask!
If you interfere with me,
you will end up like her!
It looks fun. Why don't you try it?
You fool. Then you can find out
for yourself if it's really fun!
You're so cool, Tuxedo Mask!
He did it! Oh?
Thank you so much!
Don't let your guard down!
Okay!
Why you...
Watch out!
Yes!
I never thought I'd get to fight
with Tuxedo Mask.
I'm so happy!
Take this!
There! There! There! There!
And this and this and this!
What is this?! Hey, stop it!
What are you going to do
if it hits me?!
And this and this and this!
What are you going to do
if it hits me?!
We'll finish her now!
Okay.
Die!
Now!
Sailor Moon!
Yes!
Tuxedo Mask, are you all right?!
Do not worry about me!
Use your tiara, quickly!
Got it!
Moon Tiara Action!
Sailor Moon!
Not too bad!
I guess it means she's
growing up a little.
Oh, he's not there!
I wonder if Tuxedo
Mask is all right?
Juban Municipal Junior High School
Rui said she doesn't remember
anything she did.
Well, at least she's doing fine
now, so it's good, right?
Yeah, that's true.
Naru, do you want to play a little?
Sure, I guess if it's just a little.
Go easy on me, okay?
Oh, I can't do that!
Naru, you can serve first!
Okay, then I'll give you my
lethal magic serve!
I'll bet it'd be fun to play tennis
with Tuxedo Mask.
Sorry, Usagi!
Usagi, please wake up!
Yume no naka futari de ita yo ne
Hoshi tachi ni mamorarete
Tomodachi no toki ni wa ki ni sezu
Nanigenaku hanashite ita kedo
Anata dake ki ni naru
shunkan ga atta no
Motto kirei ni ima sugu naritai
Koi suru to nanika ga kawaru ne
Me o tojite tashikamete
Dakishimeta tokimeki sono
mama kono omoi tsutaetai