Everyone, thank you for
giving me courage.
Evil beings, in the name of the moon,
Princess Serenity will
seal you away!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
So, this is the Dark
Kingdom's stronghold.
Ami, Rei, Mako, Minako...
I'll do my best to the very end!
Usagi's Everlasting Wish!
A New Reincarnation
So, little girl, you have come.
I will show you what Hell is.
Welcome, Princess! You have
done well to come this far.
I praise you for a job well done.
Queen Beryl.
Yes, I am Queen Beryl.
Endymion, kill the princess!
As you wish.
Moon Healing Escalation!
You are wasting your time.
You are still not a
full-fledged princess.
Even if you use the Silver Crystal,
you will not be able to
remove Queen Metalia's
dark energy from Endymion's body.
Stop wasting your time and quietly
hand me the Silver Crystal.
Sailor Moon.
Die.
Mamoru...
Dumpling Head.
Soon, the sun will be covered
entirely by sunspots
and Queen Metalia will be revived.
That is enough, Endymion.
Cut off the princess's head!
It's no use!
Soon, Queen Metalia will be revived.
When she fills this world
with her dark energy
by using the Silver Crystal,
she is certain to utilize its
power to the maximum.
Everything you have been doing
will have been meaningless!
Endymion has dark energy within him.
You will not be able to
defeat him so easily.
Stop...
Sailor Moon!
Die!
Please stop!
Please remember.
I am Serenity.
In the distant past, we swore
to love one another.
I am Serenity of the Moon Kingdom.
Anyone who opposes the
Dark Kingdom must die!
You are just being corrupted
by the bad energy.
Please regain your gentle heart...
I don't want to.
I don't want to fight you!
So, please.
What?!
Who am I?
I can't remember anything!
Am I all alone?!
No, you're not.
You have me.
What?
Don't worry. You're not alone.
Mamoru!
Usagi...
Thank you.
Mamoru...
I'm so glad!
I will not forgive you, Princess!
Trying to steal Endymion
from me again!
I will not forgive you!
Mamoru!
Endymion, why do you
protect that girl?!
If you had married me,
you could have been the
king of all the worlds!
Impossible!
Mamoru, hang on!
How can something
like this defeat me?
Energy?!
Is Endymion's love for that girl
destroying my body?!
I won't accept it!
I will never accept it...
Mamoru! Mamoru!
Hurry, leave this place!
What?
And go back to being an ordinary girl,
and find a cool boyfriend
or something.
You're the coolest, Mamoru.
Mamoru...
Mamoru!!
Queen Metalia, please
lend me your power.
Please give me the power to
defeat that hateful girl!
Very well.
The time has come to bestow
hatred and suffering
to all living creatures in this universe.
Queen Beryl, kill everything
and everyone
and turn the world pitch-black!
I'm sorry.
I can't kiss you.
Rei, Ami, Mako, and Minako...
They all died
before they could even kiss
the boy they loved.
So, I can't find happiness
just by myself.
I'm sorry, Mamoru.
I'm not going to run away.
There are still things I have to do.
Watch me. I'll do my best.
I have finally obtained the
energy of darkness.
I will rule this world!
So, you have come, Princess.
This time, you will die.
Princess!
Die!
Jubancho Shopping District
It's the end.
The end of the world has come!
Queen Metalia's dark energy
has been released!
Wait, Luna!
Out of my way!
I'm going to D-Point!
It's useless!
There's nothing we can do now!
I know all that!
But, at this rate, Usagi will...
She'll unleash the power
of the Silver Crystal!
Then Usagi will die,
just like Queen Serenity!
I know! But there's no other way
to save the world now.
Don't do it Usagi!
Don't unleash the power
of the Silver Crystal!
If you do, Usagi, you're going to die!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Why?! Why you go to such
lengths to defy me?!
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Why?! Why you go to such
lengths to defy me?!
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
You dream of a beautiful future,
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
but you are sure to eventually realize
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
but you are sure to eventually realize
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
that this world is already
ugly and filthy!
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
No! I have faith!
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
No! I have faith!
Guided by the light of the moon
In love? Friendship?
Or, in the trust between people?
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I have faith.
I have faith in this world that
everyone tried to protect!
We will meet again and again
Fool! There is nothing left to believe
in this rotten world!
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
Together once again, weekend,
God, grant us a happy end
Please! Please, Silver Crystal...
Together once again, weekend,
God, grant us a happy end
Past, present, and future,
I'm crazy for you
Make me believe even more
in the world
Past, present, and future,
I'm crazy for you
that everyone had faith in!
Past, present, and future,
I'm crazy for you
The fond memories of when we met
You shouldn't talk so
casually about love.
The fond memories of when we met
Hikawa Shrine
Don't get the wrong idea!
The fond memories of when we met
Hikawa Shrine
Don't get the wrong idea!
I'll never forget your gaze
Hikawa Shrine
I don't care for Yuichiro like that.
I'll never forget your gaze
So what if he already
has a girlfriend?
I'll never forget your gaze
So what if he already
has a girlfriend?
From among the thousands
of stars, I can find you
We just have to go for it!
From among the thousands
of stars, I can find you
As long as they're happy,
that's all that matters.
From among the thousands
of stars, I can find you
That's all that matters.
From among the thousands
of stars, I can find you
That's all that matters.
You even turn coincidences into
chance, I love that way of life
Everyone...
You even turn coincidences into
chance, I love that way of life
Now that I have obtained
the energy of darkness,
You even turn coincidences into
chance, I love that way of life
Now that I have obtained
the energy of darkness,
I will not be sealed away
by the Silver Crystal!
Everyone, lend me your strength...
Please!
Coming across a strange miracle
We will meet again and again
Mercury Power!
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
Mars Power!
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
Jupiter Power!
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
Venus Power!
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
Moon Prism Power!
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
Moon Prism Power!
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
What is this?!
Everyone, thank you.
When I wake up in the morning,
a pure white curtain of lace
is rustling in the breeze.
The cuckoo clock in the room
says it's 7 o'clock
and Mom's voice says,
"You'll be late if you don't get up!"
I'm still half asleep,
and I think, "Please let me sleep
for 3 more minutes."
I'm late for school every
single day like clockwork,
my teacher makes me
stand out in the hallway,
and I get failing grades on my tests.
The crepes we'd all eat
on the way home.
We'd gaze dreamily at a party dress
in a show window.
The little things bring such joy
and I'm happy.
I wish...
I wish I could go back to
that kind of normal life.
I want to go back.
I'm late!
I'm leaving!
It's a miracle.
Not only did the sunspots disappear,
but everyone was also transmigrated.
In the moonlight, I look up at
the sky and I think of you
But I feel a little sad for them.
In the moonlight, I look up at
the sky and I think of you
Hikawa Shrine
But I feel a little sad for them.
In the moonlight, I look up at
the sky and I think of you
Hikawa Shrine
They've even completely
lost their memories
In the moonlight, I look up at
the sky and I think of you
They've even completely
lost their memories
In the moonlight, I look up at
the sky and I think of you
of when they were friends.
In the moonlight, I look up at
the sky and I think of you
Don't worry.
In the moonlight, I look up at
the sky and I think of you
What?
In the moonlight, I look up at
the sky and I think of you
They just need to meet
each other again.
In the moonlight, I look up at
the sky and I think of you
They just need to meet
each other again.
I close my eyes and
I whisper your name
You're right.
I close my eyes and
I whisper your name
Juban Municipal Middle School
I close my eyes and
I whisper your name
National Mock Exam Results
1. Ami Mizuno
2. Rika Kazuya
3. Hiroshi Yoshida
6. Hitoshi Koyama
7. Kazutoshi Itou
8. Fumie Hisamatsu
I close my eyes and
I whisper your name
Jubancho Shopping District
I close my eyes and
I whisper your name
Jubancho Shopping District
Oh, I wish I had studied more.
I close my eyes and
I whisper your name
Jubancho Shopping District
Oh, I wish I had studied more.
My tears are like the rippling
waves of a crystal
Jubancho Shopping District
My tears are like the rippling
waves of a crystal
Darn it! I'll get rid of it!
My tears are like the rippling
waves of a crystal
That hurt, dumpling head.
My tears are like the rippling
waves of a crystal
Thirty points?!
The Ioneliness fills my heart
Study harder, dumpling head.
Well, excuse you!
The Ioneliness fills my heart
No matter how far apart we
are separated, my love
It's none of his business!
No matter how far apart we
are separated, my love
What a silly girl.
No matter how far apart we
are separated, my love
Hey, wasn't that guy
sort of cool looking?
No matter how far apart we
are separated, my love
Hey, wasn't that guy
sort of cool looking?
Our hearts can now shine as one
How can you say that?!
He was so obnoxious!
Our hearts can now shine as one
Oh, so you say now.
You never know. It might have
been a fated encounter.
You're just my love
Gag! Stop it! I have my own dream!
Dream?
That's right!
That I'll find a cool boyfriend who'll
protect me no matter what!
That's my dream!
Hiru ni wa hana no kaori
Yoru ni wa hoshi no matataki
Soko wa daremo shiranai sekai nano
Shiroi kutsu o narashite
Shiroi tsuki no hashi watatte
Amai kisu no yume o miteru
ohimesama ga sunde iru no
Inori o sasagete moon
Kitto shiawase ni shitekureru
Maware maware tsuki
no merry-go-round
Suzushige na glass
no dress hirugaeshite
Itsudatte mimamotte iru wa
Moon moon princess