Go round, merry-go-round!
Go up, pink Ferris wheel!
This is a great place! An amusement
park that entices girls!
It's a terrible crime to use our
innocent, dreaming hearts!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you.
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino, 14 years old.
I'm in the 8th grade.
I'm clumsier than others
and a bit of a crybaby.
That's about it.
One day, a strange black cat,
Luna, appeared
and gave me a peculiar
transforming brooch
and made me a sailor warrior.
But, she wants me to fight
against bad guys.
That makes me really nervous.
Oh well, I guess everything
will be okay.
Usagi vs. Rei?
A Nightmare in Dreamland
Hikawa Shrine
When the three of you get together
like this, it's so heartening.
But, we shouldn't get overconfident.
Our battle is still ahead of us.
Hey! A Sailor V comic book!
No! I haven't finished it yet either!
Oh, come on! Cheapskate!
Rei, you have a nice encyclopedia.
Let me borrow it!
In other words...
Rei, don't pull it too much!
You'll end up tearing it!
So what I'm trying to say is...
That's enough!
Having three of you is meaningless,
if you're always like this.
Be more aware of yourselves
as warriors.
I'm sorry.
Easy for you to say.
So, what do you want us to do?
Like I've been saying,
you girls need to work together
to find the princess!
How?
She must have a sign hanging
on her saying who she is.
How?
She must have a sign hanging
on her saying who she is.
Oh, okay!
Come on, you two...
She doesn't?!
Unbelievable! Then there's
no way we can find her.
Then let's do something else until Luna
gets information on the princess.
Something else?
We'll protect everyone from the eerie
enemies that threaten the peace!
You're the best, Ami!
Another Disappearance?!
Look at this!
Oh, this is Dreamland!
Dreamland?
Remember? It's a new amusement park.
They say something mysterious
is going on in Dreamland.
Something mysterious?
Of the people who went to Dreamland
in the last week,
fifty have gone missing.
To think you allowed a third
sailor warrior to join them...
Jadeite!
Yes, my lady!
You do not have many opportunities
left to redeem yourself.
I'm already working on a plan to steal
a large amount of energy.
Really?
I will also kill those three
sailor warriors, without fail!
Do not forget what you have just said!
Remember, I can always replace you!
I understand.
Dreamland
Management Office
Information Desk
Park Announcement Office
Dreamland
Management Office
Information Desk
Park Announcement Office
So, I do not think these incidents have
anything to do with Dreamland.
But the fact is, fifty of your customers
have gone missing!
The number of people who came in
and who came out of here
has been the same everyday.
It is not as if those people
disappeared here.
Now, any more of this will be
considered obstructing our business.
Please leave!
How violent!
Stupid humans...
If the number matches,
did those people disappear on their
way home from Dreamland?
But it's strange that only people
who come here disappear.
That's true.
Oh, where did Usagi go?
I'm sure she's goofing off
somewhere again.
No way.
Yay!
Yahoo! Yahoo! I'm riding a horsie!
Yeeha! Whoa! Whoa!
I can't believe you!
Just what were you thinking, Usagi?
I'm sorry, I was wrong.
Be more responsible! And you call
yourself a sailor warrior?!
Don't be so bossy!
I do a good job when I have to!
A lion?
Hello.
It...
It spoke!
Don't worry, he's a mechanical lion.
You're the Dream Princess!
I wanted to see you!
You said it's mechanical?
Yes. It's controlled by
a remote control.
It's amazing!
Something's wrong!
What?
You're adorable, Mr. Bear!
Usagi!
Get off!
What are you doing?!
I sense a strange aura coming from
that Dream Princess.
That can't be...
You just don't get it because
you're so dense!
Hey!
Is that any way to treat your senior?!
I have a show at the candy house
in an hour.
Please come and see me.
Of course!
The candy house?
That must be the candy house!
I have to go!
Come, sailor warriors.
I will suck out all of your energy
until nothing is left.
Once someone gets in here,
they can never get out.
I see nothing wrong.
Okay, let's split into
two groups and look!
Ami will come with me.
Usagi, go with Rei!
What?!
If you don't want to, that's fine!
But...
Then, we'll see you later.
We're going, too!
Don't be so bossy!
Are you suspecting the
Dream Princess?
My hunch is usually right.
She doesn't look like a bad person.
You just don't understand.
Look! Even the animals are adorable!
Your name is also an animal,
since it means "rabbit".
What do you mean by that?
Oh, no!
No! Don't get on that animal!
Why? It's mechanical, but
it's safe, you know.
I don't care, just get him off!
Okay, then.
Let's do it again later.
No! You should ride it now!
Hey!
It's not a big deal!
Oh, you're so happy-go-lucky!
Rei, you're just too suspicious! Relax!
No!
It's okay!
I said, no!
I said, it's okay!
What are you doing to my boy?!
Mommy.
It seems like we're just playing.
This is the best way to patrol.
I am sorry, it is a stop signal.
Please wait for a moment.
Oh, man...
Hey!
What? You, again?!
Wait a minute! You rammed me
with your rock-hard head!
That's no way to treat me,
you dumpling head!
Dumpling head, is it?
I can so see that!
They also look kind of like
hot spring buns.
Oh, you're right!
They also look kind of like
hot spring buns.
Oh, you're right!
See?
That's enough, both of you!
Anyway, what's a guy doing on
a toy train all by himself?!
Could it be you're actually
a really big loser?!
You make me laugh! Hahaha!
It's so funny, my tummy hurts!
I've got my reasons for being here!
She just had to touch a sore spot.
Hey, Mr. Panda!
Don't keep doing this stop and go!
A show will be starting at
the candy house.
Mr. Panda, stop! Stop!
A show will be starting at
the candy house.
I cannot just stop and go anytime.
He's so inflexible!
Hey, hey! The guy sitting
in front of us...
Doesn't he sort of look like
Tuxedo Mask?
No, he does not!
He looks nothing like him!
Luna!
Oh? Where's Ami?
Inside!
No fair! No fair!
Why did she get to go in by herself?!
I feel an evil aura.
Wow! These are real sweets!
Amazing!
These candies look like gems.
They're beautiful!
We may find some kind
of clue in here.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Welcome to the candy house!
Please enjoy the show!
Okay!
It's like a dream.
I wish I could stay here
like this forever.
No way! This just can't be possible!
I will take your energy while
you are dreaming.
I see! That apple collects energy...
As I thought, this is the place where
everyone disappeared.
What's wrong?
Something's happened inside!
What?!
Oh, no! Ami is...
It's no use! It's locked!
No! Ami!
Don't cry about every little thing!
Aren't you worried about Ami?!
I didn't say that!
No, Rei, you're a cold person!
I realize that now!
Don't jump to conclusions!
Both of you, transform now!
Mars Power Makeup!
Come on, Usagi, you, too!
Don't waste time!
I know!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Fire
Soul!
Let's go!
She's being bossy again!
So, you have come, sailor warriors.
Today will be your last day!
Welcome to the candy house.
I have been waiting for you.
Be careful! This is an illusion!
Here, this is a present for you.
Oh, thank you.
Stop it!
Sailor Mars!
I'm sorry! It's my fault.
You're in big trouble now.
The poison will spread through your
blood and you'll turn into stone.
See?
Don't panic over something this small!
Be gone, evil spirit
Rin, Pyo, Tou, Sha, Kai,
Jin, Retsu, Zai, Zen!
Be gone, evil spirit
Be gone, evil spirit!
Thank goodness!
I'm so glad for you!
There's no time to cry!
It's time you revealed who you are!
Very well.
Please wait for a moment.
I am the monster, Moolyd.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, the pleasure is ours...
Hey!
Oops!
Hey, monster!
I can't forgive you for using the
innocent hearts of dreaming maidens!
By maidens, are you
referring to yourself?
Does it really matter?!
Well, anyway!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Ooh, how scary.
Let's go have another dream, shall we?
Watch out! It's another illusion
created by the monster.
I'll be all right this time! I won't fall
for anymore stupid traps!
I don't know about that.
The sound of a horse's hooves!
It's coming this way!
Be alert!
Tuxedo Mask!
He's absolutely gorgeous!
He's so cool!
Hey, hey!
That's a trap!
Hey!
Hello?!
You're falling right into
the enemies trap!
You really did fall into the trap.
I will take your energy while
you are dreaming.
Oh, please wait for me!
What?
You should dream only when
you're sleeping. Goodbye!
What? Where's Tuxedo Mask?
What is this?
Was Tuxedo Mask really
here after all?
I will let you dream one more time.
Let's get out of here for now!
I shouldn't have come all by myself.
Ami!
Are you okay?
You came here to help me!
I hope we can, but...
Uh-oh!
Everyone, that apple is what
absorbs the energy!
What?!
All three of you need to work together!
Right!
Mercury Power Makeup!
Oh?
Aim for that apple!
Okay!
Bubble
Spray!
Oh? Where am I?
Be gone, evil spirit!
Moon Tiara Action!
Fire
Soul!
I cannot move.
Shoot!
We did it!
Darn you, sailor warriors.
You will pay for this!
Listen!
You were able to win because
all of you worked together!
Don't forget about what
happened today.
Yes, I know!
Hey, isn't yours bigger than mine?
Don't be ridiculous! You picked
which one you wanted!
Trade with me!
No way!
Dreamland
Hey, trade! Trade!
In my dream, you and I were together
Protected by the stars
When we were friends,
it didn't bother us
And we casually talked to each other
But there was a moment when
I noticed only you
I want to become prettier
right here and now
Something changes when
you fall in love
I close my eyes and check
to make sure
I want to convey the thrill I felt
when we held each other