I cannot forgive anyone who toys
with a girl's precious time!
Even the cuckoo in the
cuckoo clock is mad!
In the name of the moon, Sailor Moon
will punish you.
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino, 14 years old.
I'm in the 8th grade.
I'm clumsier than others and a bit
of a crybaby. That's about it.
One day, a strange black cat,
Luna, appeared
and gave me a peculiar transforming
brooch and made me a sailor warrior.
But, she wants me to fight
against bad guys.
That makes me really nervous.
Oh well, I guess everything
will be okay.
Usagi's Misfortune!
Watch Out For the Rushing Clocks
What?! Did you say the second
warrior showed up?
Yes.
The nerve!
Then all the more reason to hurry
and collect energy for our ruler!
Queen Beryl, I have a great idea.
Humans produce more energy when
they are psychologically stressed.
For example, when they
are pressed for time.
So, if we steal their time and
cause them to rush about,
we can efficiently collect
their increased energy.
Very well. Proceed with your plan.
Yes, my lady.
Harajuku Station
Entrance
Wow! There are so many people!
Harajuku Station
Entrance
I guess you've never come
to places like this before.
I'd read about them in books,
but that was all.
Ami, you're still young.
You need to go out more!
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
Anyway, since we're here,
let's have as much fun as we can
window-shopping!
Okay.
Ta-da!
Let's go over here next!
Oh, wait!
Look, look, Ami!
What do you think?
I like this one!
I don't think so!!
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Hey, did you find
anything interesting?
Yes, lots.
Ami, what kind of books do you read?
Shall we show each other
what we got?
It's all words!
It's all comics!
I'm tired.
Me, too.
What's going on? There are
so many people.
I don't know.
Clock Look
Big Spring Bargain Week
I don't know.
Clock Look
Big Spring Bargain Week
Oh, an opening sale.
Clock Look
Big Spring Bargain Week
Look at all those people.
Fifty to seventy-percent off!
Oh, wow, that's so cheap!
Wanna check it out?
I already have the watch I got
from my mother, so I'm okay.
You should act more your age!
It's free if we're just going to look.
So, it'd be a waste if we don't!
Welcome.
Please feel free to look around.
Wow! They're so cheap!
Are watches usually this cheap?
Nope, looks like this place is special.
It's unbelievable!
Look! It's so weird!
It's cute!
You're right!
Wow, it looks just like Luna!
Maybe I'll buy this one.
After all, I'm always late for school.
How do you like it?
It's a nice bargain.
I know. It's so cheap.
It may be cheap, but my wallet
still can't take it!
And if I'm late to school one more
time, I'll break my own record!
Usagi, if you want, I'll come
get you every morning.
So, please don't cry.
Yippie! Ami, I love you!
I'm home!
Hi, Usagi. I got you something
nice today.
Wow, talk about rare! So, what
did you get for me?
Here. I went shopping with Naru
and Umino's mothers today.
Clock Look. So, you went there too.
The clock store we stopped by was
having an incredible sale.
Umino's mom bought seven clocks!
Oh! This is...
Isn't it nice?
I just remembered that you are always
late for school. Am I nice?
Thank you!
Looks like God didn't
abandon me after all...
Usagi, which part of this clock
looks like me?
Look very carefully! I'm better
looking than that clock!
Yeah, yeah... You're right.
Since Ami will be here tomorrow, I
don't need to worry about being late.
First of all, that cat
looks so sneaky.
Yeah, you're right... Good night.
Really, Usagi! Do I look
as sneaky as that cat?
I wonder if this is...
Yes! Oh, Miss Mizuno!
Is Usagi still asleep?
No. She already left.
What?! Already?! It's only 7 o'clock.
Are you kidding? Her brother,
Shingo, left home before 7.
You need to hurry.
Otherwise, you will be late.
Oh, I'm late! Then, see you tonight!
Okay, see you later!
Now, I have to vacuum the rooms
and do the laundry.
Oh, no! It's almost time for dinner!
What are you doing?!
Oh! I'm late!
They're late!
I can't wait anymore!
I'll go out there and get everybody!
Me, too! I can't stay here
like this anymore!
Then, me, too! Somehow,
I can't stay still!
That's enough! You can study
by yourself today!
I have no other choice.
It's already 8, and most students
haven't even shown up yet.
Anyway, I have four dates today.
So, I cannot stay here like this.
I'm sorry.
Then, me, too!
Once I finish eating my lunch,
I have nothing left to do.
That's right!
In old days, they used to say,
"Fall in love, life is short!"
You are so wrong!
Anyway, we shouldn't waste
our time like this!
You're right! Let's go home!
Why are the shops opening so early?
Ami!
I'm glad I found you.
I don't know what is going on, but
Usagi left home early today.
You, too. Why are you
in such a hurry?
I think something is wrong
with this clock.
Ami, can you check this?
I had no idea.
Anyway, let's open this and see...
Oh, yeah...
What is this?
To put it simply, it's a
compact supercomputer.
It's really useful for analyzing
and calculating things.
Are you sure I can have this?
Of course! Usagi would never
figure out how to use it,
but I know you'll be able
to use it easily!
Thank you, Luna.
Anyway, can you hurry
and check the clock?
Oh, of course!
That was...
What was that?!
Ami, look!
It's empty?
I thought so. This is
no ordinary clock.
The weird way people are acting
must have something to do
with that Clock Look.
Oh, no! I'm hurt! I need to rush
to the hospital!
Oh, I'm in trouble!
My plane already left!
Now, I have no choice,
I'm going to run to Paris!
Stupid humans, rushing
to your deaths.
The more you hurry, the more
energy you produce.
Once I collect all the energy
created by your impatience,
our great ruler is certain
to be very satisfied.
All the energy collected by
my clocks will be gathered
in this gigantic clock no matter
where they are.
You certainly know how to
manipulate time, Ramua.
Your magical power really paralyzed
their sense of time.
Thank you for your kind words.
Now, I leave everything to you.
There is a possibility
that they will appear
because of the commotion.
So, be careful.
Yes, sir. You can count on me.
Oh, it's slow, it's so slow!
It's too slow! Why is this bus
so darn slow?!
Oh, it's slow, it's so slow!
It's too slow! Why is this bus
so darn slow?!
Please be quiet! You're not the
only one getting impatient!
Then, do something! Remember?!
You're the one driving!
Ouch! What's going on?!
If I can't go left, I'll go to the right!
I've been doing this for ten years!
I'm a genius, out of my way!
Stop Next
Oh, the bus!
Excuse me! I need to get off!
Please stop the bus!
Unfortunately, I've decided that
this bus will run express today!
So, don't expect me to stop
until the last stop!
What?!
So, don't expect me to stop
until the last stop!
What?!
Just stop the bus!
It's weird. Nobody at school
answered the phone.
Where did Usagi go?!
What shall we do?
I'm not comfortable doing this
all by ourselves.
I know. I guess we have no choice
but to find Usagi.
I'm getting off!
Oh, my bus! My bus!
We're going to be late!
What were you thinking?!
You should know I'm too busy for this!
Oh, Usagi!
Oh, Ami!
Clock Look
So, this is the monster's hideout!
50 - 70% Off Big Bargain
Clock Look
Expensive watches * Jewelry
So, this is the monster's hideout!
Clock Look
Expensive watches * Jewelry
Wait, Usagi!
Clock Look
Expensive watches * Jewelry
If you act like this, they'll notice us!
How can you stay so calm?!
You think that clock store
is behind this, right?
Then, we should just
charge in already!
Usagi, you're completely under
the spell of the monster.
I have so many things to do today!
Go home early, eat snacks and
finish the rest of my game.
Then, take a bath... Oh, I didn't
know it's so late already!
Okay, I got it.
I'll figure out a way to get in.
So, just wait a minute. Right, Ami?
We could try to get in from the back,
but the enemy could already
be waiting for us.
Then, through the front! The front!
It doesn't matter which way we go,
if it's going to be a trap anyway!
Now, Ami, let's transform quickly.
What?! Already?!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
You, too, Ami! Hurry!
Thinking isn't going to
get us anywhere.
Okay. I know they say, "Nothing
ventured, nothing gained."
Not you too, Ami?
Mercury Power Makeup!
Okay, let's go!
Oh, wait for me!
Now, Moon Tiara Action!
I'm so unlucky...
Sailor Moon! That door!
I know!
Who's there?!
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
Likewise, Sailor Mercury!
We're here to fight you!
Well, well, I'm impressed. I never
expected you to show up so early.
I cannot forgive anyone who toys
with a girl's precious time!
Even the cuckoo in the
cuckoo clock is mad!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
You're nothing!
I'll show you that this is where
you're going to die!
Now, come and get me, Sailor Moon!
You're not getting away!
Oh, Sailor Moon!
Are you ready, Mercury?
Yes!
Clock Look
Expensive watches * Jewelry
Be careful, Sailor Moon,
Sailor Mercury!
Where did she go?
Be careful, Sailor Moon!
The monster has probably set
a trap somewhere.
I'm getting irritated.
You coward! It's cheap
not to show yourself!
I'm waiting right here.
Why don't you come?
You don't have to tell me that,
I'll be right there!
Oh, wait! It's dangerous to
just walk around blindly.
Mercury, just follow me!
Sailor Moon!
Not here!
Sailor Moon, if you just walk around
without thinking, we'll get lost!
Don't worry! Because
I've got you, Mercury!
Hey, what's that?
It's a computer. Luna gave it
to me just a while ago.
That looks awesome!
What's wrong? Are you still there?
Shut up! I'll be there soon.
So, you just wait!
Remember? You're the one
that's cheating here!
Oh, no!
And you're trying to...
Sailor Moon, this way!
Oh, that was scary.
It seems like time here can go
faster or slower.
And sometimes it goes backward.
It's really unstable.
Then, there could be a room
where we become grannies?
Yes...
I'm the sailor warrior, Sailor Moon.
No way!
So, they're not here.
Have you found something yet?
Just a minute...
I'm getting irritated.
Just as I expected.
Found something?
It seems like this maze is set up
in a certain way...
Then, where is she?
There's a 78% probability
she's this way.
Let's go!
Okay!
Nice job. You finally found
where I am.
But this is the end!
I hope you are ready.
You're the one who should get ready!
Oh? I can't stand up. Why not?
Finally, it's starting to work.
Your energy has been sucked away
by my clock.
What?!
Her energy?
Now!
It hurts!
Sailor Moon!
You're in my way!
I can't move...
I just stopped your time.
So, enjoy watching Sailor Moon suffer.
Sailor Moon!
Oh! I got my power back!
Oh, no! My energy!
Now, I can move!
Bubble
Spray!
Darn it! Where did you go?!
Are you all right, Sailor Moon?
Thank you. I'm okay now.
She's over there!
Okay!
Moon Tiara Action!
Clock Look
Expensive watches * Jewelry
Oh! Usagi! Ami!
Jubancho Shopping District
This time, I'm really exhausted.
I don't want to get stressed
out anymore!
I know!
I don't want to get stressed
out anymore!
I know!
Usagi! Big news!
A cake shop is doing a
speed eating contest!
Really?!
Let's go! Hurry!
It hurts!
I don't think her personality
will ever change!
It hurts!
I don't think her personality
will ever change!
It hurts!
I suppose.
In my dream, you and I were together
Protected by the stars
When we were friends,
it didn't bother us
And we casually talked to each other
But there was a moment when
I noticed only you
I want to become prettier
right here and now
Something changes when
you fall in love
I close my eyes and check
to make sure
I want to convey the thrill I felt
when we held each other