The blue sky! The sparkling sun!
Summer vacation is finally
here for us girls!
But... But how dare they interfere
with our vacation?!
How dare they steal summer away
from these helpless young girls?!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino. I don't look like
a super heroine, but I am!
As you know, I transform myself
by using a peculiar brooch
and fight against bad guys.
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
And my friends are the smart
and sweet Ami Mizuno,
and a slightly quick-tempered
psychic girl, Rei Hino.
Both of them are so dependable,
I feel like I'll fall behind.
But anyway, I just have to do my best!
The Summer! The Ocean!
Our Youth! And A Ghost, Too
There!
We're here! We're here!
The Kagawa
Wow!
It's the ocean!
The smell of the ocean is so good!
It seems like a nice place.
I wish I could have brought Naru, too.
Usagi, this trip is not for fun!
We came all this way for training camp
to become better sailor warriors!
I know that!
Inaka Hama
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
Is the pension you reserved close by?
Inaka Hama
Yes, it looks like it's on the
headland up ahead.
Rei, this pension had better be
a nice place.
Don't worry!
Really?
"The blue ocean! And yachts sailing
with their white sails unfurled."
"A European-style pension
on the headland
with a great view of the sunset."
"A white private beach is just
waiting for you!"
A private beach?!
Motoki!
Tuxedo Mask!
Oh, that would be wonderful!
This is it! Yes, yes! This is youth!
Summer vacation!
What? Oh, no, wait for me!
Are we there yet?
Are you sure we aren't lost?
You're the one who insisted
it was this way!
It's your fault for not properly checking
things out! Rei, you moron!
What did you say?!
Oh, lightning!
This is bad. It looks like
it's going to rain!
Let's hurry!
Yes!
I'm scared of lightning!
Usagi!
What's the matter?
Who's there?!
I'm sorry.
It's raining!
Please, this way.
Let's go!
Okay.
Yeah.
I hate this!
Lightning is scary!
It looks creepy.
Pension Adams
This is it!
This is the pension I booked!
Gag! You're kidding me!
What?
It looks spooky.
Thank you, you were a great help.
We're soaking wet.
Are the flowers okay?
Oh, yes.
I'm glad.
Welcome!
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Are you the guests with reservations?
Yes! We're from Tokyo and
my name is Rei Hino.
We have been waiting for you.
Please!
Thank you.
It's nice to meet you. Oh?
Nice to meet you!
How long are you going to make a
fuss about this? It's embarrassing!
But...
Sakiko!
You're so noisy!
Where were you?!
Come here right this minute!
Yes, Father.
I'm so tired! I'm hungry!
I bet you would be, after making
such a commotion.
Speak for yourself, Luna!
Oops.
But don't you think the people here
are a little weird?
What if this place turns out to be
a haunted house?
Yes?
Excuse me.
What's going on?
Over there...
What?
Oh, it came on. Sorry for disturbing
you. Dinner is ready.
Honestly!
Usagi!
But her neck snaked out and...
That's enough!
I'm sorry! Ami, help me!
No, Usagi, I'm not helping
you out anymore!
Why not?!
Wait!
They are such raucous girls.
But they seem like nice people.
Sakiko, stay away from those
frivolous girls! Understood?!
Yes, Father.
How about a second helping?
No, thank you. I'm already full.
How about some dessert?
I don't want any!
Rei, you idiot! Why did you book
a pension like this?!
Because this place is
incredibly cheap!
But the cooking is good
and the costumes of the
employees here are fun.
Thank you.
Those two are our selling points.
What?!
Not again!
I don't like this! It's creepy!
Is the owner crying?
It is not me.
That was scary!
Who's there?
What was that?
We didn't see anything!
Of course, not. It's just our eyes
playing tricks on us.
Could it be a monster?
I don't feel any monster aura.
But I did feel some kind
of strong power.
Good girl. You're a good girl.
You are a very good girl.
Sleep. Go to sleep.
Good. Good girl. Go to sleep.
Sleep, sleep.
Good. And now, you'll slowly,
very slowly wake up.
Slowly, very slowly.
Woohoo!
The blue ocean!
Wow! It feels so good!
It makes yesterday's commotion
seem like it never happened.
I know, it feels so good.
But you know...
I know.
This is definitely a private beach, but...
If it's because people avoid
coming here...
The silhouette of a ship
sailing off the coast.
A flock of seagulls flying.
Where are the white yachts?
Where are the cool guys?
Who cares about the ocean?!
But, I'll have fun anyway!
She's so happy-go-lucky.
Math II
Oh, that girl named Sakiko
didn't come out of her room
this morning either.
Didn't come out of her room
Now that you mention it...
Ami, you brought your
text books with you?!
Yes.
Oh!
Ami! Youth is a priceless thing
that you only have once!
Studying is important, but you have
to play when it's time to play!
I think it's important to create
nice memories that way!
Usagi...
Usagi is actually saying
something reasonable.
Okay, I understand.
Usagi, let's have lots of fun!
Yeah! That's what I want to hear!
Here!
Okay!
Ouch!
Oh... Here!
Ouch! Both of you are so mean!
Hey! Wait!
It's night again. I'm scared.
Luna, you're there, aren't you? Luna?!
I'm here! How many times
do I have to tell you?!
But I'm scared!
Begone, Evil Spirit
Begone, evil spirits!
Now, no one will disturb us at dinner!
But that was no ghost. It was a
stronger, more tangible power.
Let's just do it.
What?
I'll go crazy if things like this
keep happening everyday.
We have no choice, but to do it.
I agree, but we can never
let those girls find out.
Right!
Oh?
Sakiko.
Huh? Oh, Miss Ami.
Oh, my. And I hadn't even
introduced myself yet.
I was watching you from
here all afternoon.
Ladylike Rei, slightly clumsy Usagi,
and the cat, Luna.
Sakiko, are you Ionely?
Cheer up! You remind me of how
I was not so long ago.
Because you're all by yourself.
I know! The best thing to do is to
become friends with Usagi!
She'll cheer you right up!
But I...
It's okay!
Sakiko!
How many times have I told you
not to talk to strangers?!
Father...
Excuse me.
You girls should get
out of here quickly!
That is, if you do not want to be
in more frightening situations.
What?
Father! Ow! Father, that hurts!
Father!
Ami and her friends
are nice people!
I was so close to becoming
friends with them!
Shut up!
Sakiko, you have a strong
psychic power.
Learn to master that power!
No, I can't!
Then just let me take care of it.
Your power has improved quite a bit,
thanks to my hypnosis.
Or are you saying you won't listen to
your father, your only parent?!
Father...
Now, focus on this coin, Sakiko.
Focus your attention on this coin!
All those people laughed and said
our psychic powers were fake.
Now, show them your
incredible power!
With your psychic powers,
you will become the pioneer of
the spiritual community.
Sakiko...
Ami! Rei! Where are you?!
What is this?!
You saw us.
Stop!
Usagi!
Rei, they really are ghosts!
It's okay! They're just normal
human beings.
But...
But right now, there's a
tremendous power
being brought into existence
somewhere in this mansion.
What?!
Something is coming.
Begone, Evil Spirit
Now, create the figure of a ghost!
That should be easy for you by now.
Scare all those noisy girls!
Stop!
You are...
Good, Sakiko!
You've done a splendid job!
Now, scare all those girls!
We'll get back at everyone
who called us fakes!
Good! It's perfect!
What? What's wrong?
What is this?!
It's here!
Sakiko...
Rei, you idiot! You just had
to book this pension!
This isn't the time for that right now!
Usagi! Rei! Transform now! Help him!
Sakiko!
No, I don't wanna!
Okay!
We're all going to become possessed
if we don't do anything!
What?! Oh, fine then!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Mercury Power Makeup!
Mars Power Makeup!
I'm the sailor warrior of love and
justice, Sailor Moon!
Likewise, Sailor Mercury!
Likewise, Sailor Mars!
Mean ghost, ruining the vacation of
these helpless young girls!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will...
punish you!
But, I'm still scared!
Sakiko, stop! Stop it!
Can't you hear me?!
Sakiko! Sakiko! Wake up! Sakiko!
I don't want to.
I don't want to anymore.
Moon Tiara Action!
No way!
Sakiko! Wake up! Please!
Sakiko!
Oh, I...
Father!
Sakiko, can't you erase that
ghost somehow?!
It should have disappeared once
I woke up! Why is it still here?!
I'm scared!
Mercury!
Father!
Sakiko, run! You cannot control
that ghost anymore!
What is going on?!
Sakiko didn't want to listen to
her father anymore,
and that feeling was magnified,
making it uncontrollable!
Are you all right?
Run, Sakiko!
Father!
I am sorry. I knew you just wanted
to live like a normal girl, but I...
Father!
Sakiko!
Stop it!
Father!
Sakiko!
Everyone, I just wanted everyone
to acknowledge
that Sakiko possessed
truly strong powers,
and though I knew that she hated her
powers, I continued training her.
And I used the guests who happened
to come to this pension
to conduct experiments.
Then, what about those other people?
They were probably just
scared of the ghost
and tried to conduct an exorcism.
Oh, okay.
Here!
Ouch!
Ouch! Why do you guys
keep picking on me?!
Hey, Sakiko, you laughed at me,
didn't you?!
Wait!
Will there really be no more ghosts?
We're such scaredycats,
we just can't deal with
apparitions and ghosts!
Don't worry. It'll never show up again.
Not ever.
Yume no naka futari de ita yo ne
Hoshi tachi ni mamorarete
Tomodachi no toki ni wa ki ni sezu
Nanigenaku hanashite ita kedo
Anata dake ki ni naru
shunkan ga atta no
Motto kirei ni ima sugu naritai
Koi suru to nanika ga kawaru ne
Me o tojite tashikamete
Dakishimeta tokimeki sono
mama kono omoi tsutaetai