Even if we're preoccupied
by the spring weather,
playing with girls' dreams of love is
abominable! Abominable snowman!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you.
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino, 14 years old.
I'm in the eighth grade.
I'm a Cancer. My blood type is O and
my birthstone is the pearl.
I'm clumsier than others and a bit
of a crybaby. That's about it.
One day, a strange black cat
named Luna appeared
and made me into a sailor warrior.
But she wants me to fight bad guys.
That makes me really nervous.
Oh well, I guess everything
will be okay.
Mysterious Sleeping Illness, Protect
The Girls' Hearts In Love
Jadeite, what of the energy that
we are to give our great ruler?
Queen Beryl, please give us
a little more time.
Everything is going as planned.
Is that so? It had better
work this time.
Yes. We had some interruptions before,
but this time I am working
secretly with my minion Flowa.
Very well, it is all on your shoulders.
Keep that in mind.
Yes, my lady.
My old diary was full of you.
And my diary now is full of the past.
I want to see you. I want to
see you one more time.
I want to tell you my true feelings.
This was sent to us from Haruna
the Dreamer from Juubangai.
Haruna!
That's our teacher's name.
Nah. Can't be her.
We're sharing everyone's
love letters on this show.
For those whose letters are read,
we will send you a flower brooch
that makes love come true.
I want a flower brooch.
#10 Midnight Zero.
Usagi!
I want your love to blossom.
I'll be back tomorrow.
This is J-Dite.
Usagi!
I've never written a love letter before.
And there's the problem of
whom to write it to.
Usagi!
Oh! What?
You should probably go to bed.
You'll oversleep again.
Besides, you don't have time to
listen to late night radio.
You're a chosen warrior.
You have a very important mission.
Yeah, yeah! I know that!
I'm going to bed!
Is it a new modern disease?!
Mysterious sleeping
illness going around!
Is it a new modern disease?!
Mysterious sleeping
illness going around!
Is it a new modern disease?!
Mysterious sleeping
illness going around!
Once you've fallen asleep.
I want to get that and rest for a while.
What are you talking about?
We need you to work hard!
I'm just kidding.
If I were asleep I'd miss your
delicious cooking.
You're such a flatterer, Dear.
Oh, I'm totally late!
What?! Usagi's still here?
I forget.
Good morning! Good-bye!
What am I going to do?! The teacher's
going to yell at me again!
Naru, where's Ms. Haruna?
She doesn't seem to be here yet.
Lucky me!
It's unusual for Ms. Haruna to be late.
Let's see, I'll take roll call now.
Actually, today will be self study.
Just study whatever you want.
Today, I'm just...
So, so sleepy.
Usagi, what could be wrong
with Ms. Haruna?
Don't ask me. How would I know?
But I guess it's really lucky for me!
I hate it. Usagi never listens
to what I say.
She's probably being scolded
by the teacher right now.
Serves her right!
Hey!
We meet again, kitty.
I hope he didn't hear me talking.
You're not with Usagi today?
Oh, she's probably at school right now.
Looks like it was okay.
There, there, I'll get you some milk.
Wait just a minute.
I wish Usagi would treat me like this.
Oh, I wonder what it is?
I wonder what's wrong?
She won't wake up
no matter what we do.
Is it that exhausting to be a teacher?
You know, I heard there's a disease
going around just like this,
where you don't ever wake up.
So you get to sleep forever! How nice.
Why?
Because...
You get to stay in your
dreams forever.
I bet that's a lot of fun.
Huh?!
You think so?
Mr. President, we got more letters
addressed to Midnight Zero.
Again? Why do we get so many
responses for a show that
doesn't even exist?
What should we do?
Never mind, just put it
away somewhere.
Good grief.
I'll take care of those.
Oh really? Thank you.
No problem.
Oh Naru, you listen to
Midnight Zero too?
Of course. I've sent them
many love letters.
Really? Written to whom?
It doesn't matter.
You can just write it to your
future boyfriend.
That's a good idea. I didn't think
of that. My future boyfriend.
Ouch!
I'm sorry I wasn't paying attention.
Usagi!
That's good. Apologizing
to the telephone pole.
But it may be a problem if the warm
weather is affecting your head.
What did you say?
Hey, do you know that guy?
He's gorgeous.
He is not!
He ticks me off.
All right.
Okay, I'm going to really get
this letter written.
Usagi, a love letter doesn't
really mean much
if you don't give it to
the person yourself.
Don't talk to me right now.
Okay. Okay.
Future boyfriend. Future boyfriend.
It's no use. I can't think of
anything to write.
I failed Japanese too.
That has nothing to do with it.
I know.
I'm going to go see Mr. J-Dite
from Midnight Zero
and ask him how I should write it!
What?
I've decided. Let's go, Luna!
Hey, wait!
What?
But this is FM 10 right?
Yes it is. But we don't have a show
called Midnight Zero.
What?
Now go home.
That's weird.
That's strange.
Good evening, it's time
for Midnight Zero.
See. They do have it.
That guard lied.
It's still strange.
It says that it should be a different
program on FM 10 right now.
That must be wrong because it's on.
The first love letter we will read is
from Naru who lives in Jubangai.
Naru!
It's nice to believe in fate.
Good morning.
Wow!
That's the flower brooch?
Yeah, it arrived this morning.
Naru, hurry up and open it!
Okay!
Wow. It's so pretty.
Hey, that's the same as Ms. Haruna's.
Really?
So the letter that was from
the Haruna in love was...
The teacher's.
That's kind of strange.
Wow! How cute.
I'm...
awfully...
sleepy.
Naru!
Hey, what happened?
Naru! Naru!
Not Usagi too!
What's wrong with you, Usagi?
Get a hold of yourself, Usagi!
Oh, that's...
Tuxedo Mask.
Tuxedo Mask, could it be that you're...
my future boyfriend?
I can't believe I said it.
It seems that way.
Oh my God! Yay! I'm so happy!
Oh, Tuxedo Mask, if you are my
boyfriend, show me your face.
With pleasure.
Usagi!
Oh good, you're awake!
Naru!
Usagi, this is a case.
There must be something going on
at that radio station.
Yeah!
We've gathered quite a bit now.
It seems the experiment
was a success.
Flowa, I never thought
that young women
with dreams of love would have
so much energy.
The flower brooch puts girls to sleep
and absorbs their dreams of love.
This brooch that you created
is very useful.
It's about time for Midnight Zero.
Hey Luna. How are we
going to sneak in?
The guard is going to stop us again.
Don't worry.
What's this?
Use this pen.
Huh? What's this pretty pen?
This is your new item.
If you use that, you can disguise
yourself as different people.
Really? How does it work?
Just yell, "Moon Power!"
"Moon Power." Right, okay.
Moon Power, make me into
a beautiful newscaster!
Yay, I've transformed!
Did you have to add the
"beautiful" part?
Okay, Luna, we're going.
Got the attitude down.
I knew it!
Good evening, it's time
for Midnight Zero.
So that's Mr. J-Dite? He's so cool!
What are you saying? He's the enemy!
Are you sure?
Oh! He's been taking over
the program.
You're right! All right!
Wait a minute!
Our first letter today...
Sorry to interrupt your program but
this is an emergency news flash.
We have learned that the
flower brooches
that have been sent from this
show are very dangerous.
What?!
Do not touch them if they
are sent to you!
What are you saying?
Everyone, think about it.
A love letter means nothing if you
don't give it to the person yourself.
Wake up from your dreams.
Hey, that's my line.
Who are you?!
Usagi!
Don't think you'll get away with this!
It's a monster!
You're kidding me!
Usagi, now's the time.
Okay!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Sailor warrior of love and justice,
Sailor Moon!
Trying to ruin girls' dreams of love is
abominable! Abominable snowman!
Did you need to tack on
"abominable snowman"?
Oh yeah!
Anyway!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
You're the one who keeps
interfering with us.
Then you must be their boss.
My name is Jadeite.
Sailor Moon! En guard!
You won't get away!
This is where you die!
Go away!
Die!
Sailor Moon, use the
Moon Tiara Action!
Where are you aiming?
Jadeite!
What? You want to fight me now?
Moon Tiara Action!
No! You're kidding me!
Take that!
Watch out!
That hurts!
This is Tuxedo Mask.
Good-bye. We'll meet again.
Tuxedo Mask.
Huh?!
My dear Tuxedo Mask,
from the first day I met you, I've...
Are you still doing that?
Midnight Zero is over.
It doesn't matter, I'm giving this
to him myself. Give it back!
Really? Then I'll read it for you.
Ahh! Don't!
Good morning. I'm sorry to have
worried you, but I'm much better now.
I'm refreshed. Let's all study hard.
Give me back my love letter.
Love letter?
Wait a second...
Let me read it too.
Miss Tsukino.
No!
In my dream, you and I were together
Protected by the stars
When we were friends,
it didn't bother us
And we casually talked to each other
But there was a moment when
I noticed only you
I want to become prettier
right here and now
Something changes when
you fall in love
I close my eyes and check
to make sure
I want to convey the thrill I felt
when we held each other