Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Unforgivable!
What's unforgivable?
Taking advantage of what everyone
longs for, a white wedding dress,
and tainting the eternal dream
of innocent girls
is absolutely unforgivable!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino. I don't look like
a super heroine, but I am!
As you know, I transform myself
by using a peculiar brooch
and fight against bad guys.
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
And my friends are the smart
and sweet Ami Mizuno,
and a slightly quick-tempered
psychic girl, Rei Hino.
Both of them are so dependable,
I feel like I'll fall behind.
But anyway, I just have to do my best!
Dream of a White Dress!
Usagi Becomes a Bride
Home Economics Room
Darts
This is how you make darts.
Another chocolate parfait, please.
I wonder what's the matter
with Ms. Akiyama?
I can't stand it. It's because of that
home economics class.
I'm so sleepy.
Ms. Akiyama used to be so
enthusiastic about sewing.
It is because...
Why are you always showing up from
the least expected places?!
The reason Ms. Higure Akiyama
is acting weird...
...has a great deal to do with
her engagement.
Engagement?!
Yes! Higure Akiyama, 34 years old
and still single.
Ms. Akiyama has wished with
all her heart to get married
and her greatest dream of her life
is to have a luxurious wedding
in a wedding dress that
she made herself.
Higure, I'm a dull business man
with no status or savings,
and I'm not tall at all either.
I cannot give you a very big
wedding reception,
but will you... but will you marry me?
Yes.
He may not be what you'd call ideal,
but as long as there's love...
That's being soft!
Always have high, limitless ideals!
If there's a handsome guy,
I'll go after him and catch him!
My goal is to get married
before I turn 25!
Miss Usagi, you don't mean that!
Ms. Akiyama!
Ms. Sakurada...
What are you doing?
Oh, were you thinking
about your fiance?
Oh, no...
Wow! This silk is beautiful!
Didn't you say you were going to
sew your own wedding dress
for the ceremony?
Yes, but I haven't been able to
find a silk cloth that I like,
even though I already have
the design for it.
Hang in there!
You absolutely must complete
a fabulous wedding gown
and have a wonderful ceremony!
After all, I'm counting on meeting
my future husband
at your wedding reception!
Okay, I'll do my best.
I better work hard, too!
The stars know everything.
The star Vega...
The tears of Lyra's Vega
fill the heavens,
but they cannot cross
the vast Milky Way.
The woman about to shine her
brightest under the light of Vega
is Higure Akiyama.
I know who my next target is!
Juban Hall
Wow! Congratulations!
She is so beautiful!
It's so wonderful! Please be happy!
Wow...
A bride! She looks great!
That's got to be the dream of every
girl in love. One day, I'll also...
No, no. Bring it more this way!
Handmade Wedding Dress Contest
Okay, that's perfect. Hurry!
Grand Prize
A Free Wedding Reception
What's this? A handmade
wedding dress contest?
The grand prize is a free
wedding reception?!
Handmade Wedding Dress Contest
A grand wedding reception!
And my groom will be...
Tuxedo Mask!
Motoki!
I'm so happy! This is bliss!
Oh, but I'm not good at sewing.
I could never make a dress!
Hey, hey!
It's says a free wedding reception,
but what if the woman doesn't have
a fiance... No, I mean...
What if there's no set date?!
The ceremony can be held whenever
the grand prize winner wishes,
no matter how many years
in the future that may be.
Wow!
All right! Then I better hurry and find...
Rei.
Oh, Usagi!
What are you doing here?
Oh, nothing really!
What about you?
By the way, your mother is a
full-time housewife, right?
Huh? So, what about it?
Usagi.
What do you want?
Handmade Wedding Dress Contest
Grand Prize: A Free Wedding Reception
First Prize: VCR Deck
Second Prize: CD Player
Rei, what's going on?!
A handmade wedding dress contest...
So, your name is Rei?
Yes!
Oh, dear...
I didn't know Usagi had
a nice friend like you!
Oh, yes! We go to different schools,
but we are very good friends!
How can she say that?
She just followed me home.
That's my cake!
Usagi! She's just
unbelievable sometimes.
Go ahead, please help yourself.
Wow! Thank you!
What's going on, Usagi?
I don't know!
Your homemade cake is delicious!
You must be a wonderful cook!
Oh, my!
You goody two shoes! One look,
and you can tell it's from
the cake store in front of
the train station! Ouch!
That hurt!
Usagi is one lucky girl!
You are such a wonderful mother,
you must also be good
at sewing, right?
What?!
It has always been my dream
to learn sewing
from somebody wonderful like you!
For example, sewing a wedding dress.
Sewing, you say?
Thank you for having me!
If she's not good at sewing, why didn't
you just tell me so earlier?!
Hey! So, you were planning on
making my mom help you
and participate in that wedding dress
contest, weren't you?!
Why you little, dirty, lying,
sneaky, tramp!
You're unbelievable! If you have
time for a contest like that,
I wish you'd train yourself more
in preparation for the
monsters' next move!
You too, Usagi!
Huh? What? Hey, Usagi!
A wedding dress contest?
That's right. And Rei's talking
about participating too!
Ami, doesn't that get
on your nerves?!
Not really. I don't have any plans
to get married anyway.
Don't you get it? It's a dream!
A dream! Every girl's dream!
Hey, Ami, I know you get good
grades in home economics.
Teach me how to sew?
Well, if you really want me to.
Yay! I'm not gonna lose to that Rei!
What?!
If you want to learn the basics,
these should get you started.
The actual sewing lessons
will come after that.
Ami, you're something else...
It's mine! No, it's mine! Don't!
I'm first! No, you're not!
I'm the one who'll win the contest!
No, I am!
I got this first!
No, I was first!
Ms. Haruna...
Oh, this silk is...
Beautiful.
It is very beautiful.
Excuse me?
This is a wonderful silk.
A silk worthy of becoming
your wedding dress.
Oh, I can just see you standing under
a sky full of stars
and walking along a shoreline.
Every star is sure to sparkle and
bestow their blessing upon you.
Here.
I wish you happiness.
A grand wedding reception for free?!
I didn't know that.
See? Naru, that's why I have
to enter the contest!
Don't you think so?
I get it now.
You nod off all the time during
home economics,
but you even visited Ms. Akiyama at
her home to ask her about sewing.
I knew something fishy was going on.
Because I just don't know what to do.
But making a dress isn't
that easy, you know.
Not to mention your
short attention span.
I'll be fine!
After all, they say, "A woman's
conviction can crack a rock."
What does that mean?
Oh? Did I get that saying wrong?
What the heck is she up to?
Juban Heights
Hey, who is the guy?
He and the bouquet
don't go well together.
He looks like a loser.
You shouldn't say things like that.
He's visiting Ms. Akiyama's apartment!
Don't tell me that's...
Ms. Akiyama's fiance?!
Miss Higure?
What's wrong?
You won't even answer my calls.
Are you feeling okay?
Miss Higure?
What? Miss Higure?
Well, I...
What is this?!
Listen carefully!
Don't come near my place until the
dress contest at Juban Hall is over!
If you do, I'll break off our
engagement! Got that?
The dress... The dress... I have to
hurry up and make my wedding dress!
Miss Higure...
No way! That was our Ms. Akiyama?!
By the contest, did she mean...
She can't be! It'll be a really tough
competition if she participates, too!
This can't be happening!
I'm in trouble!
You know...
I sense something's wrong
with that teacher.
What?! Our home economics
teacher, Ms. Akiyama?
Yes, I definitely feel the aura of
a monster, but it's not clear.
Come to think of it, Ms. Akiyama
has been gone for a while.
See? So, we need to get the help of
Rei's powers, and everyone...
Hey! Stop!
What are you going to do with the
only rental wedding kimono we have?!
Hey!
Ouch!
Honestly! I thought you were going to
elope with some guy!
I hope you're not...
Oh, you still don't trust me!
There is no way that I will participate
in that Juban Hall contest!
Of course, not!
It's unforgivable to use a sacred
wedding dress for their promotion.
Shame on them!
Why is he so mad?
Excuse me dear,
how about having your wedding
ceremony at our shrine?
It's much cheaper than having it
at Juban Hall.
No, thank you. I don't have anybody
right now anyway.
Ooh! I'm single! If you'll take me...
Here I am.
The beautiful thief, Usagi Hood.
It's perfect!
Usagi!
I hope you're not planning on using
my favorite curtains to make a dress!
Please have mercy, Governor Tsukino!
I'd love to buy the cloth for a dress,
but my allowance...
Mom!
Here is my proposition.
Huh?
To pay for the price of new curtains,
I will suspend your allowance for
the next three months.
Governor Tsukino!
Besides, there aren't that many
days left until the contest.
Can you get a dress done by then?!
But the grand wedding reception...
I just can't give it up!
Juban Hall
Ladies, thank you for participating
in this contest!
Thank you, thank you so much!
It's a huge success! Huge!
I wish I could...
Don't cry, Usagi.
You did your best.
I wish I could...
Don't cry, Usagi.
You did your best.
Well, I'll acknowledge the effort
you put into stabbing your fingers with
a needle over and over again!
Rei!
Anyway, we need to watch and see if
anything suspicious happens.
Usagi, you're going to infiltrate
the hall as a contestant.
You meanie! You know
I don't have a dress!
You have the transforming pen,
don't you?
Oh! I'd forgotten about that.
Moon Power!
Turn me into a beautiful bride!
I did it!
How do I look?
I could win for sure with this!
Don't you wish you were me?
Usagi!
You wouldn't win fairly.
You're only participating, okay?!
I knew it.
Ladies and gentlemen!
'92 Your Handmade
Wedding Dress Contest
Ladies and gentlemen!
'92 Your Handmade
Wedding Dress Contest
We will now start the handmade
wedding dress contest!
Where is that teacher?!
I can't find her!
Please be quiet! And now...
Ms. Akiyama! Wow!
Excuse me, we cannot have
you doing unplanned...
Shut up!
Oh, you're my ideal bride!
Please marry me!
Shut up! You actually think you're
good enough for me?!
All the men in the world should
fall to their knees before me!
And all the women should
surrender to my beauty!
I am the winner in this contest!
I and no other!
Don't, Usagi!
Don't look at her eyes!
Oh, I don't believe you, Luna!
You saw, didn't you? You pervert!
This isn't the time for that.
The energy level has peaked.
Come out, monster, Widow!
Ms. Akiyama! So, you finally
showed up, you monster!
It's just as creepy as the other ones!
Who are you?!
Wait!
The Happy Couple
Hey!
The wedding dress is the eternal
dream of innocent girls!
No one will get away with tainting
that pure white dress!
That's not fair!
You two get all the cool parts!
Okay, then!
Since I lost the chance to win a free
grand wedding reception...
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Mercury Power Makeup!
Mars Power Makeup!
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
Likewise, I'm Sailor Mercury!
Likewise, I'm Sailor Mars!
In the name of the moon,
we will punish you!
Impertinent girls!
No!
Idiot!
I will weave a beautiful shroud for you!
But, of course, I have to
weave you in it!
No, no, no!
Bubble
Spray!
What is this?!
Fire
Soul!
Are you all right?
You're being such a baby!
But I hate spiders!
You! Where are you?!
Moon Tiara Action!
Oh...
Where am I? What was I doing?
Congratulations! You did it!
Please be happy!
She is so beautiful!
I can't believe he was
still waiting for her
after all the things she said to him.
Well, I guess you can't judge
a man by his looks.
But I still prefer a good looking guy!
Hey, Usagi!
Did you know that the person
who catches
the bride's bouquet will get
to marry next?
What?!
Really?!
It's mine!
No, it's mine!
No, I'll be the first!
Yume no naka futari de ita yo ne
Hoshi tachi ni mamorarete
Tomodachi no toki ni wa ki ni sezu
Nanigenaku hanashite ita kedo
Anata dake ki ni naru
shunkan ga atta no
Motto kirei ni ima sugu naritai
Koi suru to nanika ga kawaru ne
Me o tojite tashikamete
Dakishimeta tokimeki sono
mama kono omoi tsutaetai