What is this warm light?
Am I the princess? What should I do?
I don't know! I don't know what to do!
What can I do?!
Tuxedo Mask, everyone,
please help me!
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same
land, miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
Mamoru was badly injured,
trying to protect Usagi!
Then the rainbow crystals
reacted to Usagi's tears
and turned into the legendary
Silver Crystal.
I never imagined that Usagi
was the princess!
But there's no doubt about it.
This warm aura around her...
She's the Moon Princess!
She's finally awakened!
Memories Return!
Usagi and Mamoru's Past
Sailor Moon...
Princess... Princess Serenity...
What?!
Princess?!
Then Sailor Moon was the princess
we've been looking for?
And the true identity of
Tuxedo Mask was Mamoru.
The princess has awakened.
In that case, I'll just kill you and
take the Silver Crystal!
Zoi!
What?!
Tuxedo Mask...
All this for me...
Serenity...
I remember everything now.
Serenity, I am Endymion.
Endymion...
Now, I know. I am Serenity!
Endymion!
Endymion...
So, you're Endymion.
Sailor Moon!
She's all right. She just fainted.
Thank goodness.
Her memories of when she
was the princess
probably came back to her
and overwhelmed her.
Mamoru, please wake up!
He's badly injured.
This is nothing...
Master Kunzite...
Master Kunzite,
Sailor Moon is the Moon Princess.
I see. So the princess awoke,
and the rainbow crystals
were drawn to her.
I will allow you to live for
a while longer yet.
What?!
What did he mean by that?
You allowed the Moon Princess
to awaken
and lost the Silver Crystal as well.
That was poorly executed, Kunzite.
My lady, I am very sorry.
However, the princess has
just now awoken
and has yet to fully master the use
of the Silver Crystal.
I would ask that you wait
a while longer.
Very well. I will leave it to you.
By the way, Zoisite, I hope you
are ready to face your fate.
Please wait. Just one more chance.
You tried to kill Tuxedo Mask
against my orders, did you not?!
But I...
Did you think you could fool me?!
I will take responsibility for that.
Please wai...
Master Kunzite!
Clean up that mess!
Yes, my lady.
My great ruler, Queen Metalia,
please awaken.
Endymion, I have so longed
to see you.
He was once the prince of the Earth.
To think he had transmigrated
into this world somehow.
Use the power of darkness to restore
Endymion immediately.
Yes, my lady.
I am sorry, Zoisite.
I tried to ask Queen Beryl
to revive you, but...
I am happy.
For I will die in your arms.
But please grant me my last wish.
What is it?
I want to die beautifully.
How beautiful.
I am so happy, Master Kunzite.
I loved you, Master Kunzite.
Forgive me, Zoisite.
Is there really an exit around here?
There is definitely a way out,
but it's a little troublesome.
What do you mean?
This dimension is apparently
an imaginary space
that's been sealed off.
In short, theoretically, the real
dimension we were in
is not directly connected to the
three-dimensional space here.
Instead, they should be connected
only in two-dimensional space
with the positive and negative
phases reversed
and passing through
zero-dimensional space.
Anyway, can you hurry up?
I guess we can only depend
on Sailor Mercury now.
We're counting on you.
We can't just hang around
here forever.
I know.
Sailor Moon.
It looks like you're awake.
Tuxedo Mask!
Where? Where? Where is he?! Tell me!
He couldn't have...
He's alive!
Really?
But he was taken by our enemy.
By our enemy?
I see.
Everyone, please listen to me!
Now that the princess has awakened,
I think it's time to tell you everything.
Luna, all your memories came back
when the princess awoke, too, right?
Yes, it's all clear now.
Wait a minute!
What are you talking about?
About our previous lives.
And about the moon kingdom
called, Silver Millennium.
Long, long ago,
there was a kingdom on the moon
called, Silver Millennium.
It was a very peaceful paradise.
Around that time, the Earth was
taken over by an evil spirit!
It invaded Silver Millennium
in order to try and obtain
the enormous power of
the Silver Crystal.
The kingdom was destroyed
in the fierce war,
but with the power of
the Silver Crystal,
they sealed away the evil spirit!
You are those four warriors who
fought back then, now reborn.
Then, are we people of the moon?
No, we're all genuine Earth humans.
So your parents are
really your parents.
You see, the queen of the moon
wanted the princess and
the rest of you
to live happily as normal girls,
so she transmigrated you to
this most peaceful era.
But even in this era,
someone unraveled the seal
on the evil spirit.
So, that evil spirit is the leader
of the Dark Kingdom?
That's right. If none of this
had happened,
all of you would be living
happily as normal girls.
But if we don't protect the Silver
Crystal and defeat our enemy,
we cannot have a peaceful world.
And our duty is to fight
for that cause!
You understand, don't you?
We have to work together and fight
so we don't repeat the tragedy
of the past again.
I understand.
Yes, let's fight together!
I don't want to.
Sailor Moon...
I just don't want to fight anymore.
Are you serious?
But I just don't want to!
You're the princess!
How could you say that?!
Being told I'm the princess doesn't
make me feel like one,
and it doesn't make me happy at all!
I'm just Usagi Tsukino.
Usagi, don't you understand
what your mission is?!
I don't care about any
mission anymore!
So what about my previous life?!
It has nothing to do with me!
What's with all of you?!
I just don't want to fight anymore!
If everyone...
If everyone ends up like Mamoru...
I don't want to see that! It's too sad!
I don't want this!
Ouch...
You're a coward... A coward!
You're a coward!
Yes, I'm a coward.
I'm not strong like you are, Rei!
Rei...
Mamoru did all that just to protect
a coward like you...
Sailor Moon still needs
some more time.
But...
She'll go back to being the
same old Usagi in a while.
Until then, let's all watch over her.
By the way, Luna, I found the exit!
Good! Then, I know we're still
not done talking,
but let's get out of here first!
Come on, let's go!
I am surprised you found the exit.
Luna, Artemis, find someplace safe!
Okay!
Be careful, Venus!
Everyone, take care of the princess!
I'm going to fight with you!
Thank you.
You are wasting your time.
Don't underestimate me!
Supreme
Thunder!
No way! He's absorbing the energy!
How about this?!
Crescent Beam!
It's not working.
In this dimension, he'll absorb
all the energy!
Then, what should we do?!
That's not enough...
...to defeat us!
Then, die!
Watch out!
Take care of the rest, Mercury!
Usagi, wake up.
You will be fine, I know it!
Are you ready?
Fire
Soul!
Fool!
Are you ready, Princess?
I am your opponent!
Do not interfere!
Tenacious fool!
Ami, hang in there!
Usagi, be brave!
Ami...
Usagi, be strong.
Usagi...
Everyone... Everyone...
Everyone...
Tuxedo Mask, please
lend me your power.
Sailor Moon...
Tuxedo Mask?
Fight, Sailor Moon!
The Silver Crystal...
Raise the Silver Crystal!
Yes!
Do you mean to step into Hell
voluntarily, Princess?
Fine, then.
I will take revenge for Zoisite!
Please...
Please, Silver Crystal!
What?!
That girl...
So, she has learned to use some
of the Silver Crystal's power.
Serenity...
Endymion, can you still not
forget about her?
Even though it will be
forever unrequited,
no matter how much
you love Serenity.
Thank you, Tuxedo Mask.
You saved us.
Thank you, Sailor Moon!
You'll fight with us, won't you?
Everyone...
Yes!
Looks like we've cleared
the first hurdle.
You did a good job, Usagi!
Let's all keep working together
and do our best!
As long as we do, we'll be able
to overcome any hardship!
Yes.
And Tuxedo Mask is certainly
alive somewhere, too.
During the day,
the fragrance of flowers
During the night,
the twinkle of the stars
It's a world no one knows about
With white shoes clicking
Cross the white moon bridge
And there lives a princess,
dreaming of a sweet kiss
Offer a prayer to the moon
It will surely bring you happiness
Go round and round,
the moon's merry-go-round
Make that serene dress made of glass
flutter in the wind
She's always watching over us
Moon, moon princess