Minako's boyfriend is a handsome boy
who was born in London!
But what do you know?!
A pretty older lady named
Katarina showed up.
What to do? What to do
with this love triangle?
Anyhow, anybody who makes
a girl in love cry,
in the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short
sunzen ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta no
miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
Sailor Venus's Past, Minako's Tragic Love
Let's see.
Not here...
Not here, either.
That leaves...
Sorry for being late.
Oh, I am dead tired.
How was it?
The Japanese confectionery
store we checked
wasn't the doorway to the
Dark Kingdom's hideout.
I see. So these aren't
the places either.
Monsters are being sent in
one after another from
the Dark Kingdom.
There has to be a doorway
for them somewhere.
Rei, how about the places
you guys checked?
No leads whatsoever.
Not one place that looked like
the entrance to a hideout.
That just leaves us with Minako.
I'm so tired!
Usagi, everyone's working hard,
so be a little more patient!
But, I'm starving!
What did you just eat
at that confectionery?
Three plates of sweet dumplings
and two cups of jelly with fruits!
It was yummy!
But that's not close to being enough!
You guys are pretty rowdy in here.
How was it?
Big disappointment.
We checked all the public baths
in Tokyo, but we found nothing!
I see. Thanks for your hard work.
Why don't we call it a night
and go home for today?
Good idea.
Usagi, we're going home!
What is this?!
This is...
It's the same as that other time.
What other time?
The way the sunspots are spreading...
It's just like when the Moon Kingdom
was destroyed long ago.
What?!
When the sunspots blanket the sun,
I shall be brought back to life
from my eternal slumber.
Queen Metalia will be revived?
Once Queen Metalia is revived
and we get hold of the Silver Crystal,
the world will become mine.
The day you will hold the Silver
Crystal should not be too far away.
What?
I found somebody who knows
Sailor V's true identity.
What's this?
She is a policewoman,
who works for Interpol in England.
I received information
that she used to care
for Sailor V like a younger sister.
It sounds interesting.
Sailor V is certain to be related
to Sailor Moon in some way.
I will leave this matter to you.
Yes, my lady.
What is happening?!
This man possesses the same
wavelength of energy that I do.
He is worthy of inheriting my energy.
What's wrong?
Tuxedo Mask...
You must have had a bad dream again.
I understand how you feel, Usagi,
but it's bad for you if
you keep worrying.
You need to get enough sleep
and eat properly.
I know...
I have no problem with
eating properly, but...
I guess I just wasted my time
worrying about you.
Somehow, looking at the moon makes
dumplings taste better.
Oh, I'm so happy!
Sorry, Usagi!
What's wrong, Artemis?
It's terrible! Minako's disappeared!
Water... Give me water!
I wonder if she found the passage
that leads to the Dark
Kingdom's hideout?
Give me water!
If she did, she would take me with her.
Water!
Don't you have any idea
where she might be?
There is one thing.
She got a phone call from
a woman named Katarina.
This might have something to do
with that woman.
I thought I was gonna die!
Idiot.
Minako...
No, Sailor V.
I was surprised when I learned
that you were well.
Why didn't you let me know
that you were alive?
I hear you still transform into Sailor V
to do good deeds.
Yes.
I want to help you, too.
Say, you're friends with the
sailor warriors, aren't you?
Won't you introduce them to me?
What about Allan?
Is he doing all right?
Yes, he's fine.
Allan wanted to see you, too.
Katarina, I guess you kept
wearing that necklace.
Of course. You gave it to me
for my birthday, after all.
Anyway, I want to be of
some use to you, too.
Please, introduce me to
the sailor warriors.
Katarina, you are a great
international police officer,
but this is our problem.
I don't want to expose you to danger!
I'm glad I had a chance to see
you again. Thank you.
Good-bye!
Minako!
Wait!
Master Kunzite...
It does not seem more questioning
will help us.
Transform into the monster,
Papillon, and attack that girl!
Papillon!
Allan...
Minako...
A butterfly at this time of year?
Who's there?!
If you died once, you should just
let me kill you!
You're a monster, aren't you?!
All right!
Venus Power Makeup!
What?! Minako was Sailor Venus?!
Crescent Beam!
You're wasting your time.
What?!
I know the way you fight. Take this!
I know your weaknesses,
inside and out!
You're Katarina? Why?
Now, tell me the identity
of your friends!
Katarina, please...
Sailor Venus!
Oh! What should I do?!
That monster looks tough!
Usagi, let's get on that thing
and get out of here!
What?! That's impossible!
I don't know how to pilot a boat!
Then, why don't you turn
into a sailor?!
Oh, right!
Okay, then!
Moon Power! Turn me into
a cute sailor!
Let's get out of here while we can!
Okay!
How did you find me here?
We hit all the hotels that had
a Katarina staying there.
Then, we found out she was staying at
the Hillside Hotel with
a view of the pier.
Where did they go?! I won't
let them escape!
Anyway, we have to...
It's coming!
All right, time to go full speed ahead!
It looks like we'll make it!
Usagi, thanks a lot!
No problem!
Usagi, let's find shelter in that luxury
liner anchored over there!
Roger!
I can't go any further!
Quit dragging your feet!
You were just sitting on my head!
Anyway, let's hide somewhere!
Where are they hiding?
It looks like there's nobody
here, after all.
But don't let your guard down.
The monster is aware that
we got on this ship.
By the way, Venus, you were
calling that monster Katarina.
Just who is she?
Luna, sometimes, there are things
people don't want to talk about.
It's okay.
It was just about six months ago.
I got information
that one of the Dark Kingdom's
monsters was in England,
so I went to London.
There, I fell in love with Allan,
whom I'd met.
Then, one day, I came across
a crime in progress.
Wow!
It's amazing!
Thank you!
After that, we became good friends.
She taught me English
and acted as my confidante too.
I adored her like a big sister.
And she took care of me like
I was her younger sister.
Katarina! Allan! Hurry!
I also introduced Allan to Katarina
and the three of us had
a lot of fun together.
Then, one day...
Minako!
Allan...
Allan, Minako was... Minako was...
What happened to Minako?!
Be strong. You have me.
That was when I first realized
that without my knowing it,
Allan and Katarina had...
I disappeared from both their lives.
I thought it would be happier for them
if I just pretended that I was dead.
So, you came back to Japan and...
You devoted yourself to fighting
against the enemy
to try to forget those sad memories.
No!
I don't like that. That's so terrible.
Usagi...
Are you so happy you're going
to be killed by me
that you're crying?
This place will be your grave!
I'm in a bad mood right now!
You better watch out or you'll get hurt!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
What?! You are Sailor Moon?!
At this point, I don't care if
you found out who I am!
I'm a sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Enough of your nonsense!
I won't run away today!
I'll never forgive anybody who crushes
an innocent girl's love!
Die!
Moon Tiara Action!
Please save her!
What?
She was turned into a monster
because of me!
She knew I was a sailor warrior.
That's why the Dark Kingdom used her.
None of this is her fault!
You adored her like your own sister
and she betrayed you!
Please help her.
But she stole your boyfriend!
He...
But she's the person Allan
fell in love with.
Please.
Okay, then!
Moon Healing Escalation!
Refresh!
Katarina!
Minako...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I didn't know your feelings.
I thought you were still a child.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What in the world happened to
Minako?
She looks so sad.
Shouldn't we go to her side?
We should just let her be by herself.
What?
Because Minako is much more
grown up than we are.
This is how it should be.
Because the person he chose
is Katarina.
As long as they're happy,
that's all that matters.
That's all that matters.
Hiru ni wa hana no kaori
Yoru ni wa hoshi no matataki
Soko wa daremo shiranai sekai nano
Shiroi kutsu o narashite
Shiroi tsuki no hashi watatte
Amai kisu no yume o miteru
ohimesama ga sunde iru no
Inori o sasagete moon
Kitto shiawase ni shitekureru
Maware maware tsuki no
merry-go-round
Suzushige na glass no
dress hirugaeshite
Itsudatte mimamotte iru wa
Moon moon princess