It's inexcusable to use music for evil.
I can't forgive anybody who tries to
take away a man's right to love.
Bach, the father of music, is angry too.
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you.
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino, 14 years old.
I'm in the eighth grade.
I'm a Cancer. My blood type is O
positive and my birthstone is the pearl.
I'm clumsier than others and a
bit of a crybaby. That's about it.
One day, a strange black cat
named Luna
gave me a peculiar
transforming brooch
making me into a sailor warrior.
But, she wants me to fight bad guys.
That makes me really nervous.
Oh well, I guess everything
will be okay.
Protect the Melody of Love!
Usagi is a Cupid
It stole the plant's energy, this music...
Queen Beryl, this music has subliminal
high-frequency waves hidden inside it.
The humans that listen to this
will become like the plant...
Interesting...
Try it.
At once!
Kurene.
Place the high-frequency wave on
this tape into the humans' music.
As you wish.
Jewelry
Naru, this is a good song.
Isn't it? I highly recommend it.
This is jazz, right?
Naru, you are so mature.
I know... If you have any questions,
just ask me.
Yeah, yeah.
Hmm, Yusuke Amade, huh?
Isn't he great?
He's probably a wonderful
and mature man.
I'd like to go out with him.
I'll pass.
They'd turn you down first.
Today... Today, I'm going to confess.
Jam Records
The stereo that plays this tape will
become infected with the evil virus.
In other words, any music
recorded in this studio
will have the subliminal
high-frequency wave in it.
Here it is!
I can't believe I left it here.
Yusuke is going to be mad at me.
Ms. Akiko.
Mr. Amade is here to see you.
He is in the lobby on the first floor.
I'm coming.
Yusuke didn't have to come on
such a rainy day like this.
Yusuke!
Oh my, you're soaked.
You didn't use an umbrella?
You were probably too busy thinking
about music, weren't you?
Uh, yeah.
Here is the demo tape
from the other day.
It was really good. Let's discuss
the recording next week or so.
Um, it's your birthday today, right?
Oh, you're right...
Ms. Akiko!
It's terrible! We made a
mistake with the mixing.
What? Again?
Sorry, I've got to go already.
I'm working late again tonight.
Here.
Use my umbrella on your way home.
It's the pink one at the entrance.
And think of a title by next week!
Okay?
Look more carefully...
I wrote the title. It says,
"A Waltz for Akiko."
What annoying rain.
They do say spring showers are long.
Oh well.
Well, I'll see you at school tomorrow.
Okay, bye.
Maybe I'll play a little.
You shouldn't be at an arcade
so late at night.
Come on, it's only for a little bit.
Honestly!
Look out!
What?
Oh, my new outfit is all wet!
Ouch!
You!
Help me! Don't kill me.
Please don't... Not my life!
Wait a second...
I'm not going to kill you.
Huh?
What? You're being targeted?
Yeah, and you probably wouldn't
believe me, but...
What is it?
The thing that is after me is actually...
A monster...
A monster?!
Yeah...
It was probably my imagination.
Sorry for telling you
such a stupid story.
This is fine.
What?
I've got a job at that music club.
Music club?
Oh yeah, dry cleaning money...
Sorry, I don't have any money
with me right now.
Will you call me at this number later?
Pianist
Yusuke Amade
Will you call me at this number later?
Pianist
Yusuke Amade
Yusuke Amade...
Yusuke Amade!
See ya!
So that was the Yusuke Amade
from that CD.
That's not important, Usagi!
The thing that's after him is a monster.
We can't leave him alone.
Yeah, it's a chance to understand
the world as a grown-up.
We can't not do anything.
Does she really understand?
You idiot! You haven't gotten
the tape back yet?
I'm sorry, I almost had him,
but he got away.
Stop giving me excuses.
Yes, Sir.
Anyway, proceed as planned.
Do you understand?
If the tape is not returned,
consider your life to be over.
Yes, Sir.
So this is the music club?
Won't they refuse to let children in?
What are you talking about?
Moon Power, change me into
a cool grown-up musician.
So? Don't I look like an adult now?
But, they may not let cats in.
There he is!
No, you have to stay still!
You're supposed to be an accessory.
Have you decided what
you would like?
Um, a cream soda.
What?! I'm sorry, we don't
have that here.
Oh, nothing then.
That old guy looks pretty cool when
he is playing the piano.
Usagi!
He's gone!
Oh, Mr. Amade, I'll give you a ride.
Just meet me in the parking lot.
The car is already running.
I wrote that song just for her...
I wonder if she's just a bit dense.
It's that old guy's voice!
Hurry!
Okay.
I'm going to kill you for
wasting my time.
Mister!
Mister? Are you okay?
My tape... Give it back.
Tape?
"A Waltz for Akiko."
Usagi, the monster is trying to do
something terrible with that tape!
Hey mister, you're driving
like a maniac!
I won't let anyone have that tape!
Not anyone!
Even if it's a monster.
You're awfully angry...
That wasn't just an ordinary
demo tape.
Because you made it for
Ms. Akiko, right?
How did you know that?
I might not look it, but I'm
pretty mature too.
Of course, I'd notice.
It's only a crush. I know it
must be funny at this age.
Age has nothing to do with it.
Even an old guy like you has
the right to be in love.
Oh, thanks.
Anyway, why are you following
the monster with me?
I'm on the side of those in love,
on the side of justice.
Oh, I get it.
Over there! There it is!
The rain has stopped. You can see it
with the lights from the city.
Okay.
Hey, little girl.
Are you sure it landed here?
Yes, I'm sure of it.
Jam Records
Oh no, Ms. Akiko and the
others are inside.
What?
I'm going to have you
sleep for a while.
When you wake up and start
recording again,
all the music will contain subliminal
high-frequency waves.
Ms. Akiko!
Stop right there.
You!
Give me back the tape.
What?
Huh?
That isn't my tape.
What?
Give me back the tape!
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
If you want her to live,
give me the tape.
Ms. Akiko!
That's so mean!
Hurry up!
Yusuke.
All right...
Akiko!
This is the end. Give it up.
Usagi!
Okay!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Concert Hall
Sailor warrior of love and justice,
Sailor Moon.
I won't allow you to use music for evil.
Even the father of music Haydn
is mad, you know!
The father of music is Bach!
If you hadn't said anything,
they wouldn't have noticed.
Anyway...
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you.
This is bad! It's some kind of
high-frequency sound wave!
High-frequency sound wave?
I get it. Sound, right?
So, how does it feel to get attacked
by your own amplified sound waves?
Usagi, now!
Moon Tiara Action!
Jam Records
Yusuke, you are so stupid. What would
you do if you hurt your hand?
Then you wouldn't be able
to play the piano.
I know.
But if something had
happened to you...
Then I really wouldn't have been
able to play the piano.
What?
Yusuke...
I envy Ms. Akiko. Having someone
like Mr. Amade in love with her.
Jewelry
Usagi, did you hear that
Yusuke Amade got married?
Yeah, that's what I heard.
I'm devastated. I had a crush on him.
Yeah, he's nice and brave...
What? You sound like you guys
know each other.
Because we do!
Yume no naka futari de ita yo ne
Hoshi tachi ni mamorarete
Tomodachi no toki ni wa ki ni sezu
Nanigenaku hanashite ita kedo
Anata dake ki ni naru
shunkan ga atta no
Motto kirei ni ima sugu naritai
Koi suru to nanika ga kawaru ne
Me o tojite tashikamete
Dakishimeta tokimeki sono
mama kono omoi tsutaetai