I had no idea that obnoxious
guy was Tuxedo Mask.
And finally, Zoisite and
Tuxedo Mask face off!
Oh, what is going on?!
Anyway, the only thing I can do
right now is beat the bad guys.
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
In order to trick Tuxedo Mask,
Zoisite disguised himself
as a fake Sailor Moon.
We fell right into their trap
and into big trouble!
And Tuxedo Mask was injured, too!
It's just terrible!
Sailor Venus appeared, so we
managed to escape danger.
But is Sailor Venus really
the Moon Princess?
What will happen to us now?!
The Sparkling Silver Crystal!
The Moon Princess Appears
Sailor V, no, Sailor Venus...
By any chance, are you the princess?
No, I'm not.
Like you, I'm another warrior,
here to protect the princess.
I can't believe it.
My idol, Sailor V, is standing
right in front of me.
Nice to meet you, everyone.
Nice to meet you, too.
Nice to meet you.
By the way,
I'm sorry to interrupt when we've
all finally come together,
but we're currently investigating
a certain area.
Let's get together tomorrow evening
at the Hikawa Shrine,
and I'll tell you the details then.
Then, see you later, Luna.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Well, everyone, see you later!
She's gone.
She's rather impatient, isn't she?
But she's so cool!
Queen Beryl, why did you
order us to pull back?
We were so close to taking
the rainbow crystals
and finishing off Tuxedo Mask.
It was our great ruler's order!
Our great ruler's?
Our great ruler told me not
to kill Tuxedo Mask.
Instead, she demanded that
he be brought here alive.
What do you mean by that?!
Silence! Orders need
not be explained!
Understood.
Damn!
I could not protect her!
Sailor Moon.
What a wonderful room.
How did you find me?!
Once I found out who you were,
it was easy to find you.
My dear Mamoru.
What do you want?
Say, since we know who you are now,
why don't we just go ahead
and settle this?
Settle this?
That's right. We will fight for each
other's rainbow crystals.
Fair and square.
Sounds good. Okay, I'm in.
Good boy.
How about we meet at the skyscraper,
Star Light Tower in the Bay Area?
All right.
Then I will be waiting for you
at five this evening.
Good night, my dear Mamoru.
Juban Municipal Junior High School
Okay, then I will see you tomorrow!
It's already spring!
Everyone's waiting for me,
and she just had to pick today
to keep me behind!
Oh, Rei's gonna pick on me again!
You clumsy slowpoke! Moron! Retard!
That's...
What are you so depressed about?!
What's wrong?
Oh, dumpling head.
Perky as usual, I see.
Well, sorry! I can't help it if I'm perky
24/7, 365 days a year!
Keep it up and never change, okay?
Huh? What the heck? I don't
know how to react now.
What? It's blood. When did it...
Could he be... injured or something?
Dumpling head!
What are you doing?!
What about you?! What
are you doing here?!
I just came here because
I was worried about you.
Worried about me?
That injury of yours...
If you keep wandering around
like that, it'll never heal!
That's none of your business.
That's true, but...
Go on home!
You didn't have to say it like that!
Hey, wait! Hold on!
He's here!
Zoisite?!
No! What is this?!
I can't believe this!
You idiot! Why did you follow me?!
Because!
Hikawa Shrine
This is too late, even for
slowpoke Usagi.
They said she hasn't
been home either.
And she wasn't at school, too.
Even the communication device
isn't getting through!
Something's definitely wrong!
I have a bad feeling about this.
Anyway, we have to find Usagi!
She's at Star Light Tower!
What?
Who are you?
Did you forgot about us already?
Artemis! Then, you're Sailor Venus?
Normally, I go by Minako Aino.
I'm in the 8th grade
just like all of you.
According to our investigation,
the enemy seems to be up to
something at Star Light Tower.
If you cannot use the communication
devices, that must be it!
I bet Usagi just decided to
go there by herself!
If Usagi were that kind of girl,
I wouldn't have any problems.
Anyway, let's hurry to
Star Light Tower!
Okay!
Welcome.
I will leave our rainbow crystals here.
Now, hurry up and take
yours out, too.
Before that, please let this girl go.
After you take out your
rainbow crystals.
All right.
What is so funny?!
No, I'm just happy because
you're so dumb.
Shoot!
These rainbow crystals are mine now.
That's playing dirty!
Ah-ah. If you move now, that girl
will be burned to a crisp.
Zoisite, take care of the rest.
Yes.
Damn!
Zoisite... Why are he and Zoisite...
You scum! How dare you leave
a scar on my face?!
Just you remember this!
Mamoru Chiba, if you want the
rainbow crystals back,
come to the observation deck
at the top of the building!
Rainbow crystals? How does he know
about the rainbow crystals?
Now, please enjoy your fill of terror.
Watch out!
Run!
The injury on his shoulder...
Yesterday, Tuxedo Mask was also
injured in the shoulder.
He couldn't be, right?
Oh! I hate this!
Make it to the elevator!
Open, quick! Come on!
We're saved.
Not really.
Oh, no! What is this?!
It seems like we're trapped.
So, this is the Star Light Tower.
It looks like just another building.
Usagi and Mamoru are in the elevator.
What?!
What do you mean?!
All the doors are closed!
Meaning we can't get inside?
This isn't good.
My guardian, Jupiter!
Brew a storm! Call the cloud!
Bring down the lightning!
Supreme Thunder!
We'll just have to force
our way in! Let's go!
Right!
What a bunch of pests!
We have gotten a hold of
the rainbow crystals,
and Mamoru Chiba is as good as ours.
If I could finish off the sailor
warriors on top of that...
Go pay them back for what
he did to your face.
This elevator is taking so long.
It just keeps going up.
Hey, why were you talking about
the rainbow crystals?
Oh, sorry. If you don't want to talk
about it, that's all right, too.
I just wanted to recall my past.
Because, in order to get
my memories back,
I have to collect the rainbow crystals,
and get a hold of the legendary
Silver Crystal.
He even knows about
the Silver Crystal.
My parents were killed in a car
accident when I was six.
I'm sorry, but it was too
late for the couple.
But their only son, Mamoru,
has miraculously survived.
Who am I?
I don't know. Who... am I?
Ever since then, I have not been
able to remember anything.
Since then, I started seeing the same
dream over and over again.
The Silver Crystal... Please, the
legendary Silver Crystal...
I want to get a hold of
the Silver Crystal,
and get my past back.
Why did I just tell you all that?
I thought you were the most
obnoxious guy in the world,
but now, I'll move you up
to second place.
Thanks.
Tuxedo Mask?
No, that can't be! Right!
There's just no way!
Sailor warriors,
this is a worthy place
for you to die!
What's going on?
Sailor Venus!
Power outage?
Farewell.
What is it?!
What should I do? If I transform into
Sailor Moon, he'll know who I am.
But if I stay like this, we'll both die!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
What?!
Sailor Moon?
I must report to Queen Beryl
that Mamoru Chiba was
killed in an accident.
What accident?!
What?!
For misleading everyone with
your cowardly tricks,
and for picking on us, I'm going
to make sure you pay!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
Sailor Moon, I'll take care of you
along with Tuxedo Mask!
What are you talking about?! I don't
see Tuxedo Mask anywhere!
He's right here!
It couldn't be...
No way...
Study harder, dumpling head!
Crying will not solve anything!
The dumpling's turned
into puffed pastry!
Today, you are the star, Sailor Moon!
If you keep eating like that,
you'll turn into a meat bun!
Good-bye, Sailor Moon!
You're Tuxedo Mask...
You were very brave today.
Leave the rest to me.
I can't! Because you're injured!
I want you to run!
Sailor Moon, I will protect you!
Tuxedo Mask...
Enough with the games. Let's settle
this now, Tuxedo Mask.
Sounds good,
but you need to promise not to
lay a hand on Sailor Moon.
Of course! Let's fight fair and square!
Yes, fair and square.
Victory is mine!
Hang on! Hang in there!
Are you okay, Sailor Moon?
Yes.
Why do you look like you're
about to cry?
Softly, listen closely
I'm glad you're safe...
Tuxedo Mask! Tuxedo Mask!
The sweet sound of your breathing
Stand still and look carefully
We came too late!
The moonlight begins to
shine on your eyelids
Tuxedo Mask...
The moonlight begins to
shine on your eyelids
Tuxedo Mask!
The moonlight begins to
shine on your eyelids
Just by watching you sleep
I feel my heart being squeezed so
Releasing the seal on
the magic of night
Let us go in search
I've dreamed of it for so long
Just for you
The one and only
Where is it?
The legendary sea
It's the Silver Crystal!
So, that's the legendary Silver Crystal?
The legendary sea
Quietly, it unleashes the light
The crystal of glass
Please have faith
Sailor Moon!
When you have obtained love
Please have faith
What is going on?
When you have obtained love
Please have faith
What is going on?
When you have obtained love
That is the very moment
In your right hand
The crystal of glass
Begins to sparkle
Princess! The Moon Princess?!
She has finally awakened.
Begins to sparkle
Now, embracing it for eternity
Moonlight
Hiru ni wa hana no kaori
Yoru ni wa hoshi no matataki
Soko wa daremo shiranai sekai nano
Shiroi kutsu o narashite
Shiroi tsuki no hashi watatte
Amai kisu no yume o miteru
ohimesama ga sunde iru no
Inori o sasagete moon
Kitto shiawase ni shitekureru
Maware maware tsuki no
merry-go-round
Suzushige na glass no
dress hirugaeshite
Itsudatte mimamotte iru wa
Moon moon princess