The illustrations done by a mysterious
beauty, Yumemi Yumeno,
are said to make romantic
wishes come true.
Somehow her illustrations
just feel very nostalgic.
What?! This innocent maiden
has one of the rainbow crystals?!
What'll I do?! Oh, I don't have time
to worry over this!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino.
As you know, I'm a sailor warrior
of love and justice, Sailor Moon.
But it's not easy, you know.
I have to get a hold of the
legendary Silver Crystal
before the bad guys get it,
but to do that, I have to find the
seven rainbow crystals!
Oh, man. But anyhow, we've got
four sailor warriors now,
so it'll work out somehow.
Illustrations Of Love, Are Usagi and
Mamoru Getting Closer?
Of the seven rainbow crystals,
two have been taken by
meddlesome outsiders
and only one is in my hands.
And three of the great Seven Monsters
have already been defeated.
Zoisite, how do you intend to take
responsibility for this?
Queen Beryl, please grant me
a short period of grace.
The next target is this girl.
I shall obtain the rainbow crystal,
even at the cost of my life.
I assume you know what will
happen if you fail?
Yes, my lady.
That's why...
It's definitely autumn.
There are couples everywhere.
Oh, Tuxedo Mask, are you
my enemy or my ally?
At any rate, he's got his eye on
our precious Silver Crystal,
so we should consider him
our enemy for now.
No! No way!
Oh, I have no idea
who the man I adore is
and these scary monsters
just keep showing up!
Why am I the only one who
has to suffer like this?!
Usagi, sorry for making you wait!
Naru! So what is it?
What do you want to show me?!
You'll just have to wait until
you see it. Let's go!
Okay!
Let's have something to eat later!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
The Crescent Moon Wand
is so important,
and she's so careless with it,
I can't believe it!
Yumemi Yumeno's Exhibition
Wow! They're so beautiful!
Aren't they?!
Yumemi Yumeno's illustrations
are really popular right now.
But there are only couples here.
That is because Yumemi's illustrations
are illustrations of love.
Umino!
Yes!
It's true.
They say having one
of her illustrations
makes your romantic
wishes come true!
Yup, yup, yup, yup.
Makes your romantic
wishes come true!
Yup, yup, yup, yup.
I'm gonna buy a poster
on the way home!
Here, look. This is supposed to be
Yumemi's self-portrait.
Wow! She's so beautiful.
She totally fits the image of someone
who draws illustrations like these.
But the artist herself is
a mysterious beauty,
who never appears in public.
Wow, then she could actually
turn out to be ugly.
Oh, Usagi!
What?
It's no good. No good.
I'm not inspired at all.
But Yumemi hasn't put out
anything new lately.
Some rumors say she's in a slump
and no one knows where she is.
I'm right here.
Slump!
That's possible. Poor thing.
What's wrong, Usagi?
I don't know, this picture just
feels very nostalgic.
Yumemi Yumeno's Exhibition
This is...
Please find the Silver Crystal!
It's similar to the dream
that I see all the time.
Now, then...
Come on, let's go this way next!
Hey, hey, don't pull me!
Hurry!
Oh, excuse me.
My glasses... My glasses...
Are you all right?
This is it! You're him!
Oh? Isn't that Motoki's friend?
Oh! That jerk!
He's with someone other than Rei!
I can't just ignore this! Sorry, Naru,
can you go home by yourself?
Usagi!
Umino, make sure you walk
Naru all the way home!
Oh, buy a poster for me!
Oh, yes, Ma'am! Leave it to me!
Oh, Usagi.
I'm all alone with Naru now, due to
unexpected circumstances.
Oh, this is strange.
I used to become sad when my Usagi
would leave me behind.
Am I a boy with many loves?
Umino, you sure you don't
have a fever?
Well, that is...
What is it?
If you want something, will you
just come out and say it?
That is, would you model...
I saw it, I saw it!
I'm gonna tell Rei about this!
You've got the wrong idea, Usagi.
How do I have the wrong idea?
You're holding her hand so tight.
What?
You fit my image perfectly!
I'm so lucky today!
Please model for me!
What?! A model?!
Please. Please come in.
Wow! Your garden is so pretty!
Please, um, Mamoru.
I will make some nice coffee
for us right away.
You pushed us into coming here,
but it's not like I have
a lot of free time.
Oh, come on!
College students goof off all the
time anyway, don't they?
But these look like
Yumemi Yumeno's illustrations.
What?! Could it be that you're
Miss Yumemi?
It doesn't fit your image, right?
Someone who does
illustrations like these
should be more wonderful and
more beautiful, right?
That's why I portray myself
as a beauty.
Don't tell anybody about this, please!
Don't tell anybody? You mean,
nobody knows about you?
Including your friends? Not anyone?
I don't have friends. But it's okay.
I'm satisfied as long as I can
create good illustrations.
Here, drink it while it's hot.
Usa, you sit here.
What?! You want to do a picture
of him and me together?!
Don't be so happy!
What?!
I don't want to model for
this kind of drawing.
Please! Have a seat.
I'm the kind of person
who can't envision a drawing
without models!
I've had a hard time finding the
right models these days.
It's just for today, so please!
Oh, fine.
Rei would hit me if she
saw me right now!
But now that I look closer,
he is handsome.
Oh, what am I thinking!
I'm supposed to be devoted
to Tuxedo Mask!
Ouch!
What are you doing?
None of your business!
Wow, I feel like this is going
to be a great drawing!
I think this could become
a masterpiece!
Oh, where did Usagi go?
She's so hopeless.
This is me? I can't believe it!
Just sit still. Sheesh.
I'm doing it just this once out of
respect for the good coffee.
You're so lucky. How come you can
draw such wonderful drawings?
Whenever I'm drawing,
I always wish in my heart
that whoever looks at this picture
will become happy.
I wish they'll meet someone wonderful.
So, that's why they call your pictures
"illustrations of love."
You're so kind, Miss Yumemi.
But because of that, you can't
even make friends...
It can't be helped. Yumemi is supposed
to be incredibly beautiful.
If people find out that I'm her,
it'll ruin everyone's dream.
But...
A person who cannot
make herself happy
should have other concerns
than strangers' happiness.
You're so cold!
Wow, this drawing is wonderful!
Look! She draws wonderful
pictures like this one!
How could you say
something like that?!
Oh!
What?
This scene shows the girl
handing her lover a gift
as proof of her love.
But somehow, whenever I draw
these two, I always feel sad.
I know what you mean.
It feels so nostalgic,
it makes my heart ache.
As proof of her love?
Juban Construction
Yumemi Yumeno, soon, I will restore
you to your monster form.
Your homemade cookies
were delicious!
I'm sorry for keeping you so late.
But maybe, you would have preferred
Mamoru to walk you home.
No way! Please!
You're misunderstanding!
Oh, it's Yumemi Yumeno!
It's so pretty!
Someone who can draw like this
must be a wonderful person.
Miss Yumemi, I think you're
thinking too much.
You can draw these wonderful pictures,
you're nice and you're really
good at baking cookies.
You're a very wonderful person!
Usa...
Cheer up! Okay? Good night!
You're a very wonderful person!
That was a great thing to say,
if I do say so myself!
I hope Miss Yumemi cheers up!
Usagi!
Oh, it's the Crescent Moon Wand.
You dropped it in the park.
If you don't want it, I'll have
someone else take care of it.
No, don't! It's just because I was
thinking about Tuxedo Mask.
But you seem all cheered up now.
What? Oh, well...
I'm so relieved. Your problems
are so small and simple.
And you recover quickly, too.
Ouch!
Fine, so I'm simple! Luna, you jerk!
Oops. I just told her the truth.
Did I go too far?
Oh, Luna!
Girls worry a lot because
we're complicated!
It's responding in the direction
of Miss Yumemi's house!
Quietly hand over the rainbow crystal
and revert back into a monster.
He's beautiful, but he's also scary.
Who are you?
Zoi!
Wake up, monster Vena!
I had no idea Yumemi was a monster!
This can't be...
Oh, I'm scared.
I don't have time to be scared,
but I'm still scared.
Everyone, a monster's appeared!
Math III
Sailor warriors, gather together!
Okay!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
How well it worked!
Safety First
Juban Construction
How well it worked!
Safety First
Juban Construction
Not so fast!
Safety First
Juban Construction
What?!
Miss Yumemi is so nice
and full of dreams,
I can't forgive you for taking her away!
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Sailor Moon, whatever!
Go, monster Vena!
That's good, Vena!
Play with her more!
Oh, no!
Ouch!
No!
Tuxedo Mask!
Leaving so soon?
You're not getting away!
Oh, Tuxedo Mask!
Miss Yumemi, please don't
get in my way!
Remember the kindness in your heart!
Please!
Fire Soul!
Everyone!
Sailor Moon, you've done
well by yourself!
Bubble
Spray!
Everyone, she's a nice, good person!
Please go easy on her!
Let's have the rainbow crystal!
Impertinent bastard!
Zoi!
This will be the end of you!
Moon Tiara Action!
Sailor Moon!
Tuxedo Mask!
You saved me tonight.
Oh, no... Oh!
That is your pendant, isn't it?
Princess...
What? Do you know the princess?!
We're looking for her.
No, I don't know anything.
But if that is your mission,
you hold onto it.
Are you giving this to me?
Well, then could I have
something else, too?
Would you return the rainbow crystal
from the other day to me?
No. I cannot give that up.
The rainbow crystals are
significant to me as well.
Even the rainbow crystal
that you obtained...
Given the chance, I will take it
without hesitation.
What?!
Then are you our enemy after all?!
With regards to the rainbow
crystals, perhaps so.
Good-bye!
Tuxedo Mask...
Oh, no! It's not over yet!
Supreme
Thunder!
Please stop attacking her!
She's pretty weak now.
Sailor Moon, now!
Okay!
Moon Healing Escalation!
Refresh!
Juban Gallery
Usa!
Miss Yumemi!
Why did you invite us out here?
I thought you didn't want people
to find out what you look like?
I've quit hiding.
Wow! It's so beautiful!
It looks pretty good,
considering the model.
Oh, you're so twisted.
Oh, this picture...
From now on, this will be
my self-portrait.
Thank you!
You gave me the courage to openly
announce that I'm me.
Wow, I'm so glad, Miss Yumemi!
Hiru ni wa hana no kaori
Yoru ni wa hoshi no matataki
Soko wa daremo shiranai sekai nano
Shiroi kutsu o narashite
Shiroi tsuki no hashi watatte
Amai kisu no yume o miteru
ohimesama ga sunde iru no
Inori o sasagete moon
Kitto shiawase ni shitekureru
Maware maware tsuki
no merry-go-round
Suzushige na glass no
dress hirugaeshite
Itsudatte mimamotte iru wa
Moon moon princess