Oh, God, please save the soul of
this girl with a broken heart!
Zoisite, committing evil deeds
in a sacred place...
You're not getting away
with this anymore!
In the name of God,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
Hi, I'm Usagi Tsukino.
As you know, I am the sailor warrior
of love and justice,
Sailor Moon!
At last, the fourth member
of our group appeared!
She's sweet and she's strong.
Makoto Kino is Sailor Jupiter!
With all four sailor warriors
together now,
it's like we're unbeatable now,
you know?
Bring A Smile To Naru's Face!
Usagi's Friendship
Quickly...
Quickly. Please find the Silver Crystal.
Please tell me!
What is the Silver Crystal?
Who in the world are you?
The Silver Crystal...
Once you find the
Silver Crystal, everything...
That same dream again!
Who is that princess?
Am I Tuxedo Mask?
The Silver Crystal...
If I can get my hands on it,
will it answer all my questions?
You have obtained one of the
rainbow crystals already.
But, Zoisite, what is your next plan?
Yes, my lady!
The Black Crystal already senses
another rainbow crystal.
The next rainbow crystal is
inside this man's body.
I shall leave it to you.
Juban Municipal Junior High School
Naru's absent again.
Mr. Nephrite...
I'm sorry.
I don't think we'll get to eat a
chocolate parfait together.
No...
No! You can't! You promised!
You said we'd eat a chocolate
parfait together!
Mr. Nephrite!
Naru...
What?
You're going to visit Naru?
Yes, I am. She hasn't shown up
at school for a week now.
I bet she still hasn't been
able to recover.
What?
I thought Naru was out
because of a cold.
Honestly, you're just so dense!
Anyway, once we get to Naru's house,
make sure to cheer her up!
Of course, I will!
If that's what you want,
just leave it to me!
Jewelry
Sorry for showing up
without any warning.
We were just sort of wondering
how you were doing.
Well,
I was completely under the impression
that you were absent
because of a cold,
but could it be your heart was
broken or something?
You moron.
What was that all of a sudden?
Don't you have anything else to say?!
What?
Okay, then...
Then why don't we go somewhere
and eat a chocolate parfait?
Why you! You are just so...
Ouch...
Usagi.
You want to go out somewhere?
What?
And maybe have something
good to eat?
Naru...
Okay!
Yeah, yeah.
Hikawa Shrine
The power that could even
blow up a planet?
That's right! In other words,
apparently the Silver Crystal
has that much power,
depending on how you use it.
So, it has tremendous power.
So, where is this Silver Crystal?
I still don't know that yet.
But I found out that there are these
shards called rainbow crystals.
Shards?
That's right, the rainbow crystals are
pieces of the Silver Crystal.
Of course, that is a story
I heard a long time ago.
There were these bad guys
in the Dark Kingdom
called the Seven Monsters.
But apparently, someone
trapped them inside
the seven shards of the
legendary Silver Crystal.
With the rainbow crystals
dwelling inside of them,
the demons became
good-hearted humans
and came down to Earth.
And having become humans,
they led peaceful lives.
But Zoisite is trying to take the
rainbow crystals out of them.
If he can take the seven
rainbow crystals,
he can get a hold of the
legendary Silver Crystal!
On top of that, it also revives
an evil monster,
so the enemy is killing two birds
with one stone.
As long as I'm in this,
there's no way I'll let those
villains get their way.
That's what I was going to say.
But how do we find the people who
possess the rainbow crystals?
The wand that I gave Usagi
will respond to them!
What?!
In that case, I'm against letting
Usagi hang on to that wand!
Why?
You let her have it and she'll
just use it as a hammer
for some amateur carpentry!
I don't think even she
would go that far.
There!
But she may use it for
something close to that.
I trust Usagi!
It's true that she completely
lacks a sense of duty,
and she's not dependable.
But that's why I want to give her
the status of the leader,
to give her more confidence!
Give her more confidence?
That's right! I think if she's given
an important role,
she'll gain a little more
sense of responsibility.
That will never happen!
Please! Give her a chance!
Please just acknowledge
her as the leader!
I'm still against it!
I think Usagi could...
I suppose. It'd be nice to see
how things go first.
I guess Usagi just doesn't inspire
people's trust in the end.
I still don't know much about her, so...
Of course!
Once you get to know Usagi better,
I'm sure you'll agree with me!
Hi hi!
Oh, Usagi?
Everyone's here discussing something
important right now.
Would you mind coming over here?
Oh, sorry! But I have to go to
Chinatown in Yokohama
with Naru and Umino to eat tons
and tons of good food now.
Unbelievable! And at such
an important time!
Chinatown
Excuse me, but what's wrong
with you two?
You've been so quiet this whole time.
Chinatown is right over there.
Miss Usagi, you brought lots
of money with you, right?
There are so many tombs,
but I guess there isn't one
for Mr. Nephrite.
Naru...
I know! I want some Peking duck!
I've never had it before.
Wow! I can't wait!
I'll finally get to taste the Peking duck
I've always dreamed of!
I see! So, you want to become a
Peking duck that badly?!
No, I want to eat it.
Oh? Where's Naru?
What? Naru!
Father!
I want to you to tell me!
What should I do?
Someone very precious to me died...
He suffered so much,
but I couldn't help him.
You have a very beautiful heart.
I am sure that person's
soul was saved.
But now that I've lost him,
I have nothing left.
That is not true. Love will be right next
to you before you know it.
Turn around and you will find love.
If I turn around, there will be love?
You're...
My, my.
You're the person...
What a coincidence.
Fancy meeting you here.
Naru!
Where in the world did she go?
What?!
Emergency! The wand is responding!
Luna! Why are you here?!
Never mind that! Hurry up and
take the wand out of your bag!
Okay!
That wand is telling us the location
of the seven rainbow crystals!
The seven rainbow crystals?
I'll explain everything later!
There's a chance a monster will appear
where the wand is pointing to!
What?!
Use the transmitter to call Mako!
Mako's around here, too?!
Chinatown
Okay, so the origin of the signal
is in the cemetery?
I will be right there!
The response is getting stronger.
Hurry!
Who are you?
Wouldn't you rather learn
more about yourself?
I am just a simple priest.
Do you really think so?
This Black Crystal here will
tell us who you really are.
That was Mr. Nephrite's... Don't!
Let go!
Please don't do any more bad things!
Oh, no! Naru!
Wait until Mako comes!
Naru is in danger! I can't wait!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Stop this violence!
Why don't you worry about
yourself instead?
That's as far as you go!
Who's there?!
Sailor Moon!
Committing evil deeds
in a sacred place...
You're not getting away
with this anymore!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
So, you've shown up.
But you're too late.
The rainbow crystal is mine!
Zoi!
Shoot!
That's...
I see it! Come forth, rainbow crystal!
Father!
A rainbow crystal...
Where is the rainbow crystal?
Father...
Wrong! I am not a priest!
That's right. I am the monster Boxsy!
You can't be...
I can hear the crowd cheering me on.
I am a champion! Wow!
Boxsy, knock out Sailor Moon!
Hey, wait! I'm not a boxer!
All right! We'll have a fight to see
who's the real champ!
I told you I'm not!
This can't be real!
I am a champion! Lovely punch!
Sailor Moon!
Mako, hurry up!
I am the king of kings!
Stop! Please, Father, go back
to being a normal priest!
Stop your babbling!
Naru!
Umino...
I am a champion! Lovely punch!
Watch out, Sailor Moon!
Tuxedo Mask!
A true boxer would never hit
a beautiful young girl.
Instead, he would embrace her gently.
Boxsy! Knock out that snooty guy, too!
All right! Come, come!
A lovely punch!
I am a champion! Triple punch!
This is nothing!
This is...
Mako! Over here!
Okay!
Jupiter Power Makeup!
Sailor Jupiter!
I see, so you're my next opponent!
My guardian, Jupiter!
Brew a storm! Call the clouds!
Bring down the lightning!
Supreme Thunder!
Now! Sailor Moon!
Okay!
Moon Healing Escalation!
Refresh!
Do you believe in God?
I do. Love thy neighbors.
That is...
This rainbow crystal is mine!
Good-bye!
One day, I will take it back from you!
Sailor Moon! We have to get
that rainbow crystal back!
Tuxedo Mask...
I see. Now, I know my true identity.
I am Tuxedo Mask.
There!
Thank you so much.
Naru, that's...
It's okay, because Umino got hurt
trying to save me.
Oh, well...
Usagi, sorry for worrying you.
I'll go back to school starting
tomorrow.
Naru...
I'm sorry, Mako. I asked you to
come all the way out here
because I wanted to show you
Usagi's good side, but...
But at least I've found out she's
very caring about her friend.
Mako!
That sounds pretty.
Where did you get it?
Oh...
...just something I picked up.
Yume no naka futari de ita yo ne
Hoshi tachi ni mamorarete
Tomodachi no toki ni wa ki ni sezu
Nanigenaku hanashite ita kedo
Anata dake ki ni naru
shunkan ga atta no
Motto kirei ni ima sugu naritai
Koi suru to nanika ga kawaru ne
Me o tojite tashikamete
Dakishimeta tokimeki sono
mama kono omoi tsutaetai