You say you'll do haircuts for free,
but you take advantage of girls
who have little allowance!
I can't forgive such a
crooked monster!
Tuxedo Mask, you agree
with me, don't you?
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
Endymion!
No more... No more about me
being the Moon Princess.
No more about having to fight
against the Dark Kingdom.
I don't want that. I just want
to stay a normal...
Usagi, hang in there! You have
to keep yourself together!
You said that you would fight
together with everybody,
but you're actually still...
It's heavy! It's heavy, Usagi!
Tuxedo Mask, where are you?
Please be all right.
Usagi...
Usagi is Confused!
Is Tuxedo Mask Evil?
Juban Municipal Junior High School
Hey, hey, Usagi! Take a look!
A new hair salon's open for business
in Juban Shopping District.
The salon's owned by Kariko
Tokoyama,
who just won the world hair
design contest last month!
And that's not all! Are
you ready for this?!
She's going to cut hair free
of charge for a while
in celebration of the grand opening!
Isn't it wonderful?! Let's go!
What's wrong? You're
not very energetic.
Hikawa Shrine
It's true.
Usagi doesn't seem to be sleeping
well these days.
Even if she falls asleep for a little bit,
she seems to just have bad dreams.
Poor Usagi.
We still don't know what happened
to Tuxedo Mask
after the enemy took him away?
No, he's still missing.
Usagi's so worried about Tuxedo Mask,
she can't focus on anything right now.
That's not good.
We need Usagi to be more aware
of herself as the princess,
or we'll be in big trouble!
But it can't be helped.
The man she loves has been abducted,
and we don't know what's
happened to him.
I can understand how she feels, too.
Oh? It's rare to hear you show
concern for Usagi.
Mamoru did all that just to protect
a coward like you...
Mamoru did it all...
Sorry.
I know it must be tough, but there's
no time to indulge Usagi!
That's right! This is all so we can
crush the Dark Kingdom's ambitions!
She needs to become a full-fledged
princess as soon as possible
and master how to use
the Silver Crystal.
I wish I could somehow
help Usagi recover.
Crying doesn't suit you,
dumpling head.
You're so mean!
Is my hairstyle really that weird?
Kariko Tokoyama
That's the hair salon that
just opened, isn't it?
Minako...
Sorry, you didn't answer, so
I decided to just come in.
Hey, Usagi,
how about a new hairstyle
for a change of pace?
What?
How about the appealingly mature
and stylish bob cut?
Or the slightly bold sauvage style?
Or how about a nice and modest
look with long, straight hair?
A girl's mood can change a great deal,
just by changing her hairstyle.
Yeah. A hair salon, huh?
Kariko Tokoyama
Kunzite.
Queen Beryl.
No matter what it takes,
we must steal the Silver Crystal
from Sailor Moon!
Yes, my lady!
You still do not know who
Sailor Moon is?
Please give me just
a little more time.
Do not take too long.
Find out who Sailor Moon
is immediately,
and steal the Silver Crystal!
Please leave it to me.
I have already set the next
plan in motion.
Really?
This is a strand of Sailor Moon's hair,
which I obtained during battle.
I will find the person with
the same hair,
and uncover Sailor Moon's
true identity without fail.
Good. Act with care.
Yes, my lady!
Hello.
Welcome to Kariko Tokoyama.
Could you do something
with this girl's hair?
Of course.
My, you have such beautiful hair!
Please come this way.
If there are any itchy spots,
please just tell me.
Okay...
Usagi, I hope you feel
better after this.
Please stay like this for a while.
No. That girl is not Sailor Moon either.
Thank you for waiting.
Please come to the hair steamer.
Oh, no. I just came here
with my friend.
Then please give our hair
steamers a try.
I'm sure we won't disappoint.
Our hair steamers use a special steam
that even fixes damaged
hair in no time.
Well, I guess it's okay.
It's free, after all.
Please stay like this for a while.
I have found you, Sailor Moon.
Oh, could you move a little
more to the right?
I have finally found out who
Sailor Moon is!
Ms. Kariko, are you done
shampooing my hair?
I have found you, Sailor Moon!
What?!
Minako?!
No!
You must not sleep!
Now, hand over the Silver Crystal!
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
The computer told me that your hair
is the same as Sailor Moon's!
What?
I see, that's when Usagi's
hair got onto me...
So, you absolutely refuse to hand
over the Silver Crystal.
In that case, I have some ideas
on how to change your mind.
Oh, no!
Oh, no. The Dark Kingdom turned
Ms. Kariko into a monster!
Wait there, Minako,
I'll rescue you soon.
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Stop it!
She is not Sailor Moon!
Impossible!
You say you'll do haircuts for free,
but you take advantage of girls who
have little allowance!
Sailor Moon will not forgive such
a crooked monster!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
To think you came here on your own!
Just like a slug jumping
into a heap of salt!
Slug?!
I am the monster Mitsuami and
I will melt you like a slug!
Usagi...
Wet hair must be dried!
No!
I will shave your unwanted hair!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Why you...
Monster Mitsuami! No! Ms. Kariko!
With the Crescent Moon Wand,
I will turn you back into the old
Ms. Kariko Tokoyama!
Moon Healing...
This is...
It can't be... It can't be...
Tuxedo Mask!
You're safe! I'm so glad!
I am not who you think!
What?!
I am a commander of the Dark
Kingdom, Endymion.
You can't be!
Sailor Moon, hand over
the Silver Crystal!
Why? How come?
Finally, the engine started.
What?!
Mitsuami! Take the Silver
Crystal from her!
Yes, Sir!
This can't be happening.
I shall shave your head!
No way!
I have to contact everyone with
my communication device.
Tuxedo Mask is our enemy?
All right.
Venus Power Makeup!
Sit still and just let me
shave your head!
My head will come off if you
shave my head with that!
What are you doing, Mitsuami?!
Hurry up and get the Silver Crystal!
This can't be...
Are you ready now?
Stop right there!
Everyone!
Fire
Supreme
Soul!
Thunder!
Bubble
Spray!
Shoot!
Now, Sailor Moon!
Okay!
Moon Healing Escalation!
Shampoo, rinse, refresh!
Refresh!
Tuxedo Mask!
You're safe!
Mamoru...
Sailor Mars, he is not the
Tuxedo Mask you know!
He is a commander of the Dark
Kingdom, Endymion!
That can't be true.
It's not true, is it? Please just tell
me it's a lie, Tuxedo Mask!
Roses have thorns.
You must know that even a
red rose turns black
when exposed to a wintery blast.
Why?
Are you really going to fight us?
I do not enjoy fighting women,
but I will show no mercy in order to
get the Silver Crystal!
Endymion, withdraw this time.
What?!
This is an order from Queen Metalia!
Sailor warriors, it seems your time
of death has been postponed.
What?
Women's friendships are fleeting.
Just like a fragile flower, they fall
apart at the slightest breeze.
Be careful.
Good-bye.
Why did you tell me to come back?
Endymion,
I cannot have you die.
It seems Endymion has become
a warrior of the Dark Kingdom,
both in mind and body.
Yes, my lady! The brainwashing
was very effective!
From now on, I expect Endymion
to be quite useful
as a warrior of the Dark Kingdom.
Ms. Kariko is just an ordinary person,
who has nothing to do with our fight.
I don't want people like her to get
mixed up in our fights anymore.
Well, she finally seems
to be more aware
of what it means to be the princess.
But, I'm glad that Tuxedo
Mask is still alive!
Oh, boy...
Just how is she aware of being
the princess again?
No! She's just trying to
act tough there!
At the very least, it means Usagi
has grown up as a person.
You, too, Rei. You can't mope
about this forever.
You're right.
Tuxedo Mask is probably just being
controlled by the bad guys
and being used by them!
So, I'll restore him back to his old
self with the power of my love!
Hiru ni wa hana no kaori
Yoru ni wa hoshi no matataki
Soko wa daremo shiranai sekai nano
Shiroi kutsu o narashite
Shiroi tsuki no hashi watatte
Amai kisu no yume o miteru
ohimesama ga sunde iru no
Inori o sasagete moon
Kitto shiawase ni shitekureru
Maware maware tsuki no
merry-go-round
Suzushige na glass no
dress hirugaeshite
Itsudatte mimamotte iru wa
Moon moon princess