What?! I didn't know Motoki
had a girlfriend!
Zoisite! Anyone who gets
in the way of lovers
deserves to get kicked by a horse,
and turned into a pancake!
What? It's not your fault?
As if I care!
Sailor Moon is looking for
a boyfriend right now.
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino.
As you know, I'm a sailor warrior of
love and justice, Sailor Moon.
But it's not easy, you know.
I have to get a hold of the
legendary Silver Crystal
before the bad guys get it,
but to do that, I have to find the
seven rainbow crystals!
Oh, man. But anyhow, we've got
four sailor warriors now,
so it'll work out somehow.
Total Chaos!
The Messy Square Relationship
We have a ten percent
chance of rain today.
What?!
Darn it! You can never believe
the weather forecast!
"Ten percent" my butt!
I can't believe it!
Hey, watch where you're going!
Sorry...
If "sorry" solved problems,
we wouldn't need the police!
Oh, that voice is...
Motoki...
Mako, are you all right?
Yes...
I'm really sorry.
I was a little lost in thought.
Don't you have an umbrella?
Then, I'II...
Motoki's voice sounds so much like
my senior in school who
broke my heart.
Oh, I wish time would just stop now.
Mako.
Shall we go now?
Oh, okay...
Mako, I heard that you're a good cook.
Oh, I guess.
That's great. Cook me something
when you get a chance.
Of course, anytime!
And please let me do the cleaning
as well, while you're at it.
Wow, that would be a great help!
Here!
Write down your address, phone
number and your favorite dishes!
Here. Mako, you're so funny.
Everyone says that!
So, your favorite dish is
rice with hashed beef.
I wish it had kept raining longer.
Oh, nothing!
Mako, I'm sorry, but I need
to stop by my school.
Oh, I see.
Then I'll come over next Sunday to
make rice with hashed beef!
Makoto Kino, heading home now!
Oh, um...
You've made a cute little friend.
Reika.
Is she your new girlfriend that
Mamoru was talking about?
Don't start on that.
I'm just kidding.
By the way, considering
how you're dressed,
is our date tonight canceled again?
I'm sorry! It looks like it's going
to take all night!
It's okay. More importantly, did you
make up your mind about that?
I'm still not sure.
I see. It's a decision that'll
change your life,
so you should think it over
carefully before deciding.
You're so sweet.
But...
What?
Yo, you two!
Oh, Mamoru.
Oh, shoot! Mamoru, if you've got time,
have tea or something
with Motoki for me.
I'll call you later!
What's wrong? Got a problem?
Well, Reika's...
She may go to Africa to study.
Africa? Just what kind of
research is she doing?
That's the really amazing thing!
It's research on finding out
where life began on Earth!
So, what's going to happen?
I don't know. It seems like
she's still not sure.
That's not what I meant!
I was asking you!
Well, I want her to stay
close by if possible,
but I can't restrict her future.
That sounds just like you.
Oh, I just remembered!
Do you like rice with hashed beef?
What? No, not particularly.
Oh, okay.
Mako's coming over to cook
for me in a couple of days.
If you want, you can join us...
Mako?
Oh, one of Usagi's friends?
You know how Usagi feels
about you, right?
Yeah, they're both cute.
Cute?
You know, you were just talking
about Reika earlier.
You gotta be joking.
They're still in middle school.
Hi, I'm cute little Rei!
It's not like that.
I just think if I had kid sisters,
they'd be like them.
Kid sisters, huh?
Could it be that Motoki's
incredibly dense?
Kohan
Coming.
Good morning! It's Makoto Kino!
Wait, wait a second!
Hi, Mako. What's up?
Well, excuse me!
What?!
It's a mess in here.
Don't worry! I know men don't
clean their rooms often...
Or maybe never.
Kamikaze
Okay! Let's do it!
Do? Do what?
Oh, come on. Cleaning, of course.
Cleaning!
I'll have to do it in 30 minutes,
or I'll be late.
Okay, let's do it!
Who is this?
Oh, her name's Reika.
She's not your younger sister, is she?
Oh! Is she your girlfriend?!
Oh, well, sort of...
Juban Municipal Junior High School
It's rare to see you agonizing
over something.
Mako!
What's wrong? You seem kind of down.
Did someone break your heart again?
Just kidding!
It pisses me off when someone
says it so straight up!
I was just kidding.
Anyway, yours truly, the cupid of love,
is here to listen.
Maybe you'd be better off worrying
about yourself instead?
Luna!
It could help just to talk.
Who broke your heart?
Motoki.
Shock!
There's nothing for you to be
so surprised about.
Yes, I do. I have feelings for
Motoki... Motoki...
I love Motoki, too!
What?! You do?!
That's terrible! Terrible!
But I thought you were in love
with Tuxedo Mask.
I love them both!
Make up your mind!
Hold on a second.
Both of you, stop it!
He's got a right to choose, too,
you know...
Oh!
He's got a right to choose, too,
you know...
Oh!
Now, what?
If Motoki broke Mako's heart,
it means that Motoki
has somebody else.
In other words,
that somebody else is...
Me!
Wrong! Her name is Miss Reika!
What?! No way! I can't go on now.
Pull yourself together.
So what if he has a girlfriend?
We've got nothing to lose
if he says no.
We just keep trying to win him over!
Mako...
Crying doesn't help anything.
You're right. If we don't keep trying...
There's no tomorrow for
the sailor warriors!
Why is it that I feel there's
no tomorrow regardless?
Crown
Are you ready?!
No hard feelings, no matter
who wins, okay?
Okay! So, let's go in order
of height here.
What is this, P.E. Class?
Yo, dumpling head!
Here comes another useless guy.
The dumpling head and the big one
are here together...
I get it. Is it confession time?
Uh-oh!
Bull's Eye
Here's some friendly advise.
Just forget about Motoki.
What's with you?!
This is none of your business!
You're such a jerk!
I'm just saying you're both like
troublesome kid sisters to him.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Kid sisters?
You're lying!
It's not a lie.
If you don't believe me, why don't you
ask him yourself, dumpling head!
Don't worry.
I'll ask him about it anyway!
And I'm not dumpling head!
My name is Usagi Tsukino!
Honestly! How many times
do I have to tell you?!
Yes, Ma'am, dumpling head!
Motoki!
Oh, Usagi, Motoki is off today.
D'oh.
Do you know that Motoki
has a girlfriend?
Miss Reika, right?
What are middle school kids
thinking these days?
Oh, but if she goes to study abroad,
it's not like you guys wouldn't
have a chance...
What?! Study abroad?!
It's not like you guys wouldn't
have a chance...
What?! Study abroad?!
What are you saying?!
Tell me all the details!
Oh!
What are you saying?!
Tell me all the details!
I should never have said that.
Mr. Nasty Guy!
So, this girl is our next target.
A model student at
Azabu Technical College.
She is quite beautiful.
Master Kunzite! How could you?!
Under that skin, she is
an ugly monster!
And you think she is better than I...
Zoisite, jealousy does not suit
such a beautiful face.
Zoisite...
I don't know you anymore!
Even this rose is no match
for your beauty.
Master Kunzite.
I shall bring you the rainbow
crystal without fail.
Azabu Technical College
I came here to convince Reika
to study abroad, but...
What should I say to her?
Let's try raising the temperature of
the subject a little more tomorrow.
Yes, that could be interesting.
Bye, I'll see you tomorrow!
Good night!
It's her.
Oh, excuse me...
Oh, you're the girl who
was with Motoki.
What do you want to
talk to me about?
Well... Do you intend to study abroad?
My, news certainly gets around.
I know, was it Motoki who told you?
Please don't dodge the subject.
I don't know yet.
I'm still undecided.
The university over there has
a professor that I admire,
but parting with Motoki is...
If Motoki would stop me...
Hold it! Just who do you
think you are!
You wouldn't go if Motoki
asked you not to?!
If that's how you feel, forget
about studying abroad!
You can only choose one!
Love or study abroad!
He who runs after two hares
will catch neither!
Shoot! I came here to convince
her to study abroad.
The weight of this bag is the
weight of my love! Yeah!
Oh, we turn right here.
Mako, you sure know the way well.
Finally, I get to see
Motoki's apartment.
Motoki...
Usagi, you look so nice in that apron...
Will you marry me?
Marry you?
Usagi...
Oh, but...
I'm still not ready emotionally.
But if it's with you, Motoki...
Usagi! Usagi!
Stop it!
What?
Oh!
Believe me, you'll never need
to worry about that!
Kohan
Oh, welcome, you two.
Come on in.
Wow, it's so clean, just like
I thought it'd be!
I guess a nice guy really does
keep a neat room, too!
Gag!
I guess a nice guy really does
keep a neat room, too!
Gag!
Oh! A half-finished cup of coffee.
Sniff, sniff! I can smell Motoki.
What did you come here for anyway?
Usagi.
What? Oh, no, not yet.
I'm still not emotionally ready.
Wow, you're amazing, Usagi!
I didn't know you need to prepare
emotionally to cook.
What?!
Come on, Usagi, shall we get started?
Okay! Let's do it!
Mako, just tell me what to do!
Then would you peel the carrots?
What? I'm not good at peeling things.
Then would you mince the onions?
What?! I don't wanna do that,
it'll make me cry!
Then, would you cook the rice?
What?! I don't know
how to wash rice...
Bash
What?! I don't know
how to wash rice...
You are just unbelievable!
But...
Hello. Reika?
Motoki, I... I've decided.
I'm going to Africa.
What? I can't hear you.
I made my decision.
I want to see you, Motoki.
Okay. Okay. I'll be right there.
What?!
Usagi, Mako, I'm sorry, but...
Oh, okay, okay.
We'll see you later!
Oh, were you listening?
Moron!
Watch the place for me while I'm gone.
Ouch! I cut my finger!
He's so late.
Oh, and here I was, wondering
why she was so late.
So, she's still over here.
Oh, no! There's a rainbow
crystal close by!
Smack!
Ouch!
Huh? What? What's going on?
Both of you, transform now!
Oh, Motoki hasn't come back!
I'm getting mad!
That's right!
He invites two pretty girls over and
makes them watch his place!
Motoki, you big jerk!
Usagi...
I'm just kidding.
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Jupiter Power Makeup!
You're quite brave. But you should
stop wasting your time.
You could never defeat me!
Barbarian.
Zoi!
Motoki!
Stay asleep for a while.
You, monster!
You are the truly ugly monster.
Monster Rikokayder, one of
the Seven Monsters!
Seven Monsters?!
That's right, you're a monster.
Now, look very carefully.
Rikokayder!
Miss Reika was...
A monster?!
Sailor Moon, Sailor Jupiter, be careful!
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
Today, we are not...
...the same as usual!
Broken heart power, 10,000 volts!
Currently looking for a new boyfriend!
Not Mako, too.
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Girls who don't have boyfriends
are nothing!
What did you say?!
This is all your fault to begin with!
There!
Watch out!
The rainbow crystal is mine now.
Who's there?!
So, you insist on interfering.
I will not let you have
the rainbow crystal!
Wow! Tuxedo Mask!
Hey, hey! What about Motoki?
Right now, my heart belongs to
Tuxedo Mask completely!
Here, here, here!
What is this?! It's disgusting!
The protist is the origin of all life.
And you are also one of them.
What?!
She's saying you've got
a single-celled mind.
My guardian, Jupiter!
Brew a storm! Call the clouds!
Send down the lightning!
Supreme
Thunder!
Big Flask!
My Supreme Thunder...
Here!
Watch out!
You saved me...
I can't believe my Supreme
Thunder won't work!
You dodged it, but I've still got
lots of lightning left.
Oh, no! Sailor Jupiter, do something!
I'll send both of you to Hell!
Bubble
Spray!
What is this?!
Ami!
Rei!
I'm glad we made it in time.
Did you know how long
it took to find you?
Fire
Soul!
You should take better care
of lab equipment!
Do not waste resources!
Come on, do your thing already.
Don't order me around!
It's your fault for being so spaced out!
Who's spaced out?!
That's enough!
Moon Healing Escalation!
Refresh!
Seems like they have
finished over there.
Looks like I have lost.
You can have the rainbow crystal.
You are so naive, Tuxedo Mask!
This rainbow crystal is mine!
Zoisite, I will return
the favor someday!
Motoki!
Reika!
Any passengers on Flight 658
to San Francisco,
who have not yet checked in,
please do so quickly.
Reika, I won't say good-bye to you.
Yes, I'll write you.
I'll wait for you, forever.
Motoki...
Passengers boarding Flight 762
to Nairobi, departing at 3:50,
Motoki...
Passengers boarding Flight 762
to Nairobi, departing at 3:50,
please come to #8 gate...
Well, I need to go now.
Be careful.
Mako, let's give up on Motoki.
But, Miss Reika might find
someone nice in Africa!
No way!
You counted yourself out!
No, I didn't!
You gave up on him, didn't you?
I haven't given up yet!
Motoki's mine!
No, you can't have him!
During the day,
the fragrance of flowers
During the night,
the twinkle of the stars
It's a world no one knows about
With white shoes clicking
Cross the white moon bridge
And there lives a princess,
dreaming of a sweet kiss
Offer a prayer to the moon
It will surely bring you happiness
Go round and round,
the moon's merry-go-round
Make that serene dress made of glass
flutter in the wind
She's always watching over us
Moon, moon princess