Love, it is gentle. Love, it is pure.
And yet, he takes advantage
of such a girl's affections!
Sailor Moon will arrest you on the
charge of romantic fraud!
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino. I don't look like
a super heroine, but I am!
As you know, I transform myself
by using a peculiar brooch
and fight against bad guys.
I'm the sailor warrior of love and
justice, Sailor Moon!
And my friends are the smart
and sweet Ami Mizuno,
and a slightly quick-tempered
psychic girl, Rei Hino.
Both of them are so dependable,
I feel like I'll fall behind.
But anyway, I just have to do my best!
Wish Upon A Shooting Star!
Naru's Pure love
Naru...
So this is love...
There! There!
Usagi, you're such a child.
Oh, you're too kind!
Then are you a grown-up?
Well, of course. Because I'm...
...involved in a mature romance.
Naru, you need to have
someone to love first!
Oh, please, Usagi. Of course,
I have someone.
What?! Then are you in
love with Umino?!
Oh, it better not be Tuxedo
Mask or Motoki!
They belong to me!
It's not them. I told you,
it's a mature romance.
Okay, then, I'll tell you.
It's Mr. Sanjoin.
What?!
What? You don't have
to act so surprised.
I know he's a bit older than me,
but an age difference doesn't
matter when you're in love.
Well...
Anyway, he's absolutely
not good for you!
Forget it, I shouldn't have
told you anything!
What'll we do now?
We need to tell Naru
that Masato Sanjoin is Nephrite
as soon as possible.
Maybe we can wait a little and see.
It's easier said than done, when
you consider Naru's feelings.
We won't know how it'll
go unless we try it!
Hold on, Rei. Usagi,
what do you think?
What? Well, I think we ought
to tell her, but...
Then, what are we going to do?
Anyway, just leave everything
concerning Naru to me!
Leaving it to Usagi worries
me even more.
Where has Nephrite gone?!
He does not appear, no matter how
many times I summon him!
Queen Beryl is furious!
How terrifying!
Nephrite, you had better be ready
to face the consequences!
Nephrite is already a candle
flickering in the wind.
How I pity him.
I no longer have time to worry
about stealing energy.
Now I must obtain what I need
in exchange for the celestial globe.
You again! What do you want?
My, you shouldn't treat me so coldly.
Queen Beryl is furious.
She is looking for you.
Kunzite told you to come check up
on me, did he?
Well, well...
From your attitude, you don't seem
to have any good plans ready.
Mind your own business!
Get out of here!
Oh, how scary. Here's some
friendly advice.
Why don't you retire,
before you truly anger Queen Beryl?
Shut up!
I will find the Silver Crystal and
get the better of you!
You're terrible! The Silver Crystal
is my assignment!
It doesn't matter who's assignment
it is! Whoever gets it wins!
I'll get a hold of the Silver Crystal
and restore my honor!
Unbelievable! Just you
remember this!
I cannot believe I lost my composure
with someone as petty as Zoisite.
The stars know everything.
When the sun creates a sinister
perpendicular angle
between Neptune and Mars,
the guide to the Silver
Crystal shall appear.
And that is...
...the Black Crystal.
So, this is the guide that will lead
me to the Silver Crystal.
Is it saying that little girl has
the Silver Crystal?!
Master Kunzite, I am so upset!
Let Nephrite do what he wants.
But, Master Kunzite, what if he...
If Nephrite happens to get a
hold of the Silver Crystal,
we can just steal it from him!
You are a genius, Master Kunzite.
Zoisite, for the time being, let the
monsters keep an eye on Nephrite.
Yasha! I know you are there!
You heard what he said!
Yes, your wish is my command.
Jewelry
No, I can't.
What's wrong? You're the one who
volunteered for this, remember?
That was just a spur of
the moment thing!
Stuff like that happens all
the time, you know?
It only happens all
the time to you!
What should I do? Oh, I know!
What are you going to do?
This is a great chance! I should
go talk to Motoki for advice!
I wasn't expecting much, but...
Crown
Good, that's it. Jump there! All right,
that's good. Keep it up.
Motoki...
Good, that's it. Jump there! All right,
that's good. Keep it up.
Motoki's drooling all over her!
Oh, and he's so close to her!
Motoki, your Usagi is right here!
This aura...
Yo, Dumpling Head.
Hey, Motoki!
If you keep ignoring her,
your dumpling will turn
into a puff pastry.
He's just kidding! I'm not
a puff pastry at all!
Oh, Usagi! I didn't know you were
here. Sorry about that.
Hello!
I'm almost done with my shift.
Usagi, you want to go out for a
cup of tea or something?
Yes, of course! I want to ask you
for some advice, too!
Oh, I'll tag along. I've got nothing
better to do anyway.
What?!
That's a good idea.
I agree!
My friend, Naru, is in love
with a bad person,
but she doesn't know that he's bad.
And?
Well... What should I do
in this situation?
If I tell her the truth,
Naru will...
I don't think you need
to be in any hurry.
You could wait and see a little.
That's true...
He thinks the same way as Ami.
Waiting and watching won't
change anything.
Telling the truth is a form
of courage, too.
Mamoru may be right.
Naru might get mad if
you tell her the truth,
but as her friend, it's something
you have to tell her.
Okay! Now that I feel better,
I'm hungry! Excuse me?!
I'd like a fruit parfait, mixed
sandwiches, a strawberry short cake,
and a glass of juice!
Motoki, do you have money?
I think I can manage.
Don't worry! This is my treat today!
Oh, could you bring me a
mixed pizza, too?
Courage. Courage. All right,
you gotta be brave, Usagi!
Coming!
Oh, Usagi. What's up?
Naru!
I'm going to say this with courage,
but Masato Sanjoin is a bad person!
On top of that, he's not human!
Oh, that's not what I meant!
Anyway, he's scary!
That's why you should never
go out with him!
So, just forget about him
completely! Okay?!
But I'm...
Okay? Just give up on it!
Really? So, you talked to Naru?
Yeah! I finally worked up the courage
and I told her everything!
So, did Naru understand you?
Wait, don't tell me you said all that,
then just came back without
waiting for a response.
I can't believe you! Then, why
did you even go there?
But I'm sure she understood me.
I should have gone with
you after all.
I know what Usagi said,
but... Oh, he's just so gorgeous!
Mr. Sanjoin...
Naru, it's for you. It's from somebody
called, Mr. Sanjoin!
Our hearts really must
be linked together!
Yes. The Sankaku Park close by, right?
Yes, I'll be there right away!
I'm going out for a bit!
What? But it's so late.
Sorry for asking you to
come so late at night.
No, not at all. It made
me really happy.
I came to say good-bye today.
What?
Oh, I see. I guess I'm a bother
to you, aren't I?
No, not a bother at all.
It's more about not wanting to drag
you into a dangerous situation.
What?
To be honest with you,
I'm being threatened by
some bad people.
It would be terrible if you got
caught in the middle,
so this is good-bye. I'm glad
I got to know you.
Wait!
Please let me know if there's
anything I can do for you!
The Silver Crystal. If I only
had the Silver Crystal...
What is this Silver Crystal?
If I just hand over the Silver
Crystal to them, I'll be free.
Oh, no. I'm sorry. Please
forget I said anything.
The Silver Crystal...
Wow! It's beautiful!
This type of crystal is very
rare in the world.
Wow! It has a silvery sheen!
That must be the Silver Crystal.
Mr. Sanjoin, please wait here.
I'll bring it right away.
I'm pretty sure it was this key.
Oh, it opened!
This is the one.
Who's there?! What are you doing?!
Naru, what are you doing with that?
Naru!
Mom, I'm sorry!
Naru, what's happened to you?
Hey, Luna, let's not do this.
What are you saying?
We're going to make sure Naru
understood what you said, right?
Besides, we have to do this now
because you didn't do it
right the first time!
I know that, but...
Oh! It's Naru's mother!
Have you seen my daughter?
Is something wrong?
She grabbed the store's
jewelry and took off.
What?! Do you have any idea why?
She got a phone call from somebody
named Masato Sanjoin and...
He's a bad guy! I'll help
you look for her!
I can't forgive him! How dare he take
advantage of Naru's feelings?!
Usagi, transform now!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Luna, let's go!
Okay!
The Black Crystal is not responding.
This is just a regular crystal.
I'm so glad I was able to
help Mr. Sanjoin.
This is...
The Black Crystal is showing
a response!
Why?
This girl is worth investigating.
I want you to help me with something.
Would you come with me?
Come, shall we go?
Yes.
Wait a second!
How dare you take advantage
of a girl's love?!
I'll arrest you on the charge
of romantic fraud!
Don't interfere in my business!
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Sailor Moon, what are
you doing here?
Naru, don't be tricked! Masato
Sanjoin is really Nephrite!
He's a member of an evil organization
called the Dark Kingdom!
No! It's a lie! Mr. Sanjoin
is not a bad person!
Right, Mr. Sanjoin?
Mr. Sanjoin?
O stars, grant me power.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Sailor Moon, get a hold of yourself!
No more games!
Starlight Attack!
So, you managed to just barely
dodge it. But when I strike next,
I will not miss.
Oh, you're so pitiful!
Sailor Moon, hang in there!
Sailor Mars has arrived!
Sailor Mercury has arrived!
So, the three of you are here. I'll send
all of you to Hell together!
Bubble
Spray!
Damn! Where are they?!
Fire
Soul!
Mr. Sanjoin!
I didn't know she was still here.
Moon Tiara Action!
Shoot!
Mr. Sanjoin!
She's crazy!
I will protect Mr. Sanjoin!
Naru!
Please stop!
I don't believe it. It stopped.
Please don't hurt Mr. Sanjoin!
We cannot let him go!
Get out of our way!
No, I won't! Not even if you kill me!
This girl cares for me...
Why do you go to such lengths
to protect him?!
Because I love him.
I love him with all my heart,
so I'll protect him, even
if it costs me my life!
Naru...
Does this Black Crystal respond
to a kind heart?
Sacrificing her own life
to save another...
Is this what human love is?
Is that the Silver Crystal?
Hand it over!
Naru!
Nephrite saved Naru...
Mr. Sanjoin saved me.
Naru!
Damn you, Nephrite! You intend
to protect a human?!
Traitors must die!
Moon Tiara Action!
Such regret...
Nephrite, why don't you be a little
considerate of Naru's feelings?!
I have returned the favor.
Excuse me, that is not what
I'm talking about!
Don't you have a heart?!
You're wasting your breath.
Of course, he doesn't!
Obviously, you guys know nothing!
Listen! Once we get
the Silver Crystal,
the whole universe will belong
to the Dark Kingdom!
The Silver Crystal? What are
you talking about?
The Silver Crystal...
It sounds familiar.
You can pretend to be champions
of justice for now,
but that won't last for
much longer!
Until then, you can keep blathering
on about your love and justice.
Good-bye.
Mr. Sanjoin...
Naru...
Oh, shooting star, please, if Nephrite
cares about Naru,
don't let him do any more bad things.
In my dream, you and I were together
Protected by the stars
When we were friends,
it didn't bother us
And we casually talked to each other
But there was a moment when
I noticed only you
I want to become prettier
right here and now
Something changes when
you fall in love
I close my eyes and check
to make sure
I want to convey the thrill I felt
when we held each other