My first kiss under the moonlight
with my adored Tuxedo Mask!
And yet, and yet...
How dare Nephrite show up and
ruin the nice romantic mood?!
In the name of the moon,
Sailor Moon will punish you!
Gomen ne sunao ja nakute
yume no naka nara ieru
Shikou kairo wa short sunzen
ima sugu aitai yo
Nakitakunaru you na moonlight
denwa mo dekinai midnight
Datte junjou dou shiyou
heart wa mangekyou
Tsuki no hikari ni michibikare
Nando mo meguriau
Seiza no matataki kazoe
uranau koi no yukue
Onaji kuni ni umareta
no miracle romance
Shinjite iru no miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino. I don't look like
a super heroine, but I am!
As you know, I transform myself
by using a peculiar brooch
and fight against bad guys.
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
And my friends are the smart
and sweet Ami Mizuno,
and a slightly quick-tempered
psychic girl, Rei Hino.
Both of them are so dependable,
I feel like I'll fall behind.
But anyway, I just have
to do my best!
Romance Under the Moon!
Usagi's First Kiss
Oh, I'm so late!
Wow, a check point?
Is there something going on today?
Oh, Naru, good morning!
Good morning.
What's wrong? You look kind of down.
Yeah...
Naru.
Yes, Sir?
You're the cutest girl at
Juban Junior High.
Reveal yourself! Show me
who you really are!
I don't understand. What in the world
does Mr. Sanjoin think of me?
Naru, wake up! We're
going to be late!
Hurry, Naru!
Made it!
Hey, Miss Usagi, did you know?
The first princess of the Diamond
Kingdom is visiting Japan!
Diamond Kingdom?
It's the country that produces
the most gems in the world.
I heard they're holding a dinner
party tonight at the embassy.
So, that's why they were doing
all those inspections.
Princess Diamond will be inheriting
the legendary secret treasure
that has been passed down
through the Royal Family.
And that secret treasure is apparently
going to be introduced
to the world for the first time
at the dinner party!
Secret treasure... I wonder how
amazing it could be?
It's no use! I can't imagine it!
I'll go look at it and let you know.
What?
My family runs a jewelry shop,
remember?
So, I got a hold of a special invitation
to the dinner party.
Wow! Naru, you're so lucky!
I wish I could go, too!
"The final mystery of the century
will be revealed tonight!"
The Final Mystery of the Century will be
Princess Diamond Hates the Media!
"The final mystery of the century
will be revealed tonight!"
The Final Mystery of the Century will be
Princess Diamond Hates the Media!
"Princess Diamond visits with the
legendary secret treasure"
The Final Mystery of the Century will be
Princess Diamond Hates the Media!
"Of the Diamond Kingdom's
Royal Family!"
A legendary secret treasure...
The legendary secret treasure
of the Diamond Kingdom...
It could be the legendary
Silver Crystal.
I shall look into it.
Leave that to me!
Nephrite, don't interfere!
Searching for the legendary
Silver Crystal is my job!
The Earth is under my jurisdiction.
What?!
I will look into it!
Please leave this to me!
Nephrite, if the Diamond Kingdom's
legendary secret treasure
turns out to be the Silver Crystal,
it will be a pleasant surprise.
With the power of the Silver Crystal,
we shall revive our great ruler
and our Dark Kingdom will
dominate the world!
But my lady...
Nephrite, what is your plan?
I have my way of taking care
of business. Just watch.
Nephrite has failed every time!
Why did you assign him to this?!
He is in a tough situation,
and he is very desperate now.
Zoisite, the impatient always lose.
But, Master Kunzite...
Nephrite can be ousted
any time we please.
We shall take this opportunity to
see just how skilled he is.
What? A princess?
Yes. I'm thinking that the princess
of the Diamond Kingdom
just might be the princess
we've been looking for.
No way!
Not necessarily. We can't completely
ignore Luna's intuition.
I think there is a need to
check into this.
How?
Princess Diamond is surrounded
by lots of bodyguards.
And we can't get into the hall that
the dinner party's being held at.
We know all that!
Our mission is to use our brains to
find a way around that, remember?!
Rei, you don't have to pin me
with such a scary look!
Don't cry to gloss things over!
Anyway, let's go to an area close
to the dinner party tonight.
And we'll wait for a chance to check
whether Princess Diamond
really is the princess we've
been looking for.
Okay.
Usagi, I need you to have a more
passionate sense of duty!
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Oh, Dad, what's up? Why are
you all dressed up?
I'm going to the Diamond
Kingdom embassy.
What?! The dinner party?! No fair!
I wanna get in, too!
Dad's going there as a magazine
reporter. It's work.
Later. I'll tell you everything
when I get back.
I'm going to get inside, no
matter what! Oh, I know!
What are you going to do?
Oh, you can't!
Moon Power! Turn me into
a pretty princess!
Look at my dress! It's wonderful!
Honestly! You can't use
the transforming pen
like it's some kind of toy!
You're wrong!
I have a mission!
I did this so I can find out
if Princess Diamond
is the princess we've
been looking for.
Really?
This is useless.
The Silver Crystal...
Look for the Silver Crystal!
What is the Silver Crystal?
It's the same dream again.
Diamond Kingdom Embassy
So, this is the place for
the dinner party.
Oh, Usagi!
Usagi!
Excuse me, your invitation?
I am the princess of the
Ivanovich Kingdom!
What? Ivanovich Kingdom?
Talk about close.
Wow! A masquerade!
It's wonderful! It's like something
from a foreign movie!
That is Naru Osaka.
This is perfect.
Excuse me, Miss, would you
please dance with me?
What?
It's me.
Mr. Sanjoin!
Did you come here by yourself?
Yes...
I came here in place of my mom.
I never expected to see you here.
You have made my day!
Mr. Sanjoin.
Oh, lucky Naru. She's already
found a partner.
She looks just like Usagi.
I wonder if Usagi will be as beautiful
when she grows up?
Oh, it's Dad!
He's taking pictures without
even realizing who I am.
Excuse me!
Oh, no!
If the Diamond Kingdom's secret
treasure is the Silver Crystal,
and if I can get a hold of it, I will
surely find out who I am.
Let's see... Let's see...
That girl...
In a distant past...
I feel like I've seen her before.
Mr. Sanjoin is so wonderful.
I don't care what happens
to me anymore.
You are like a star shining
in the heavens!
Please look at me.
Yes...
Naru Osaka, you are now
under my control!
Yes.
I transformed into a princess,
but it's no fun if I'm alone.
Would you care to dance?
Oh, Tuxedo Mask!
No way! It can't be! How could
this be? It's like a dream!
What is this? It's strange...
I feel like I've danced with him
before, a long time ago.
Who are you?
I'm Naru! I'm a friend of
Princess Diamond!
What did you say?
Everyone is just interested in
the secret treasure.
I only wish I was more beautiful...
I know I'm just a throw-in with
the secret treasure.
Princess, someone calling
herself your friend...
I'm Naru! May I come in?
Oh, please!
You seem like a fun person.
May I help you?
All I want is the legendary
secret treasure!
What's going on?
Move! Out of my way!
The legendary secret treasure is mine!
Princess Diamond!
Something is wrong!
Has she lost her mind?
Usagi, it's terrible! Terrible!
Princess Diamond has gone to the
balcony with the secret treasure!
What?!
Oh, Nephrite!
Oh, Princess Diamond,
please wake up!
Let go!
I'm falling!
Usagi!
Tuxedo Mask?
Both of you can fall and die together!
It seems like something is going on.
Tuxedo Mask, you're always in my way!
Just think you're lucky to die
with a beautiful princess!
Fire Soul!
My Tuxedo Mask will
live on forever!
It's all over!
Shoot!
Stop, Nephrite!
Who are you?!
I would like to know
who I am as well.
To do that, I must solve the mystery
of the legendary Silver Crystal!
Are you our enemy or our ally?
If we are looking for the same thing,
I could be your enemy.
Tuxedo Mask!
Usagi, hurry!
Oh, right!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
What could have happened?
This is an unexpected incident!
This is a huge scoop!
Come back to life, my other self!
Clear the way!
Any who disobey shall be sacrificed
to the great ruler!
What is this?!
I'm the sailor warrior of love
and justice, Sailor Moon!
Likewise, Sailor Mercury!
Likewise, Sailor Mars!
I'll never forgive you for possessing
the innocent Princess Diamond!
The legendary secret treasure,
the Silver Crystal, is mine!
The Silver Crystal?
Begone, Evil Spirit
Oh, Nephrite!
Suffer and die!
I can't move!
We'll die at this rate!
I'll see if I can do something about it!
Bubble
Spray!
How shameless of you to mislead
Princess Diamond!
In the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Moon Tiara Action!
We did it!
Princess, are you all right?
What have I been doing?
By any chance, could you
be our princess?
My glasses... I cannot see anything
without my glasses.
Excuse me, Princess Diamond, you're
our princess, aren't you?
The cat! The cat spoke!
I guess she's not our princess.
Yeah!
What have we been doing?
I have no idea.
Oh! My precious film!
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for waiting.
And now, Princess Diamond will reveal
the world's final legendary
secret treasure.
What have I been doing?
A 2,000 karat diamond.
It is a statue of the Diamond
Kingdom's first princess.
What a waste of time.
Looks like we're back to square one
with our search for the princess.
Oh? Where's Usagi?
I'm so exhausted!
Time for some juice.
Oh, this is so delicious.
Oh, excuse me.
In a distant past,
I feel as though something
similar happened before.
I feel like my memories may return.
This gentle warmth...
This has happened in the
past somewhere.
It feels so familiar.
Yume no naka futari de ita yo ne
Hoshi tachi ni mamorarete
Tomodachi no toki ni wa ki ni sezu
Nanigenaku hanashite ita kedo
Anata dake ki ni naru
shunkan ga atta no
Motto kirei ni ima sugu naritai
Koi suru to nanika ga kawaru ne
Me o tojite tashikamete
Dakishimeta tokimeki sono mama
kono omoi tsutaetai