Finally, I've become super famous, too!
Just kidding!
Actually, a fake Sailor Moon
suddenly appeared
and started being a great hero!
But I had no idea this was
our enemy's trap!
Tuxedo Mask, watch out!
Okay, then! This is when
the real Sailor Moon
has to do something in the
name of the moon!
I'm sorry I'm not straightforward,
I can say it in my dreams
My thoughts are about to short circuit,
I want to see you right now
Moonlight that makes me want to cry,
midnight that keeps me from calling
Because I'm so innocent, what should
I do? The heart is a kaleidoscope
Guided by the light of the moon
We will meet again and again
I count the sparkle of constellations
to foretell the future of my love
We were born in the same land,
miracle romance
I believe in it, miracle romance
I'm Usagi Tsukino.
As you know, I'm a sailor warrior of
love and justice, Sailor Moon.
But it's not easy, you know.
I have to get a hold of the
legendary Silver Crystal
before the bad guys get it,
but to do that, I have to find the
seven rainbow crystals!
Oh, man. But anyhow, we've got
four sailor warriors now,
so it'll work out somehow.
The Last Sailor Warrior,
Sailor Venus Appears
Prepare yourself, Sailor Moon!
I am your opponent, Nephrite!
Tuxedo Mask!
Stop this!
Zoisite, what is the meaning of this?
I do not wish to see such
scenes again!
Queen Beryl, these are actually all
scenes showing Sailor Moon
when she was rescued
at the last minute.
Are you talking about Tuxedo Mask?
Just who is he?
Unfortunately, we do not know.
However Queen Beryl,
he has appeared virtually every time
Sailor Moon has been in danger.
If we make use of this,
we should be able to lure Tuxedo
Mask out into the open.
So, you are saying that
you will take back
the two rainbow crystals he stole?
Zoisite, I hope you know this
is your final chance.
Yes, my lady. I am very aware of it.
Wait, Zoisite!
Oh, Master Kunzite!
If you want to lure Tuxedo Mask out,
you will first need a plan to draw
the sailor warriors away
from Tuxedo Mask.
Queen Beryl, I would like to have the
honor of accomplishing that.
Very well.
Bring all seven rainbow
crystals before me.
Yes, my lady.
Master Kunzite, I will do this for you
and not for anyone else.
I will even die for you.
Touzai Bank
Touzai Bank Juban Branch
Hands in the air! And hand
over the money!
Hurry up!
Ouch!
Who the hell are you?!
News
Kume Newscaster
And now for some news.
The sailor warrior, Sailor Moon,
whose actions have been the
talk of the town lately,
arrested a bank robber.
Today, around 2 o'clock
in the afternoon,
the robber forced his way into
Touzai Bank, Juban Branch,
Touzai Bank
Automatic
the robber forced his way into
Touzai Bank, Juban Branch,
and demanded money from the female
tellers while firing his rifle.
Usagi?! No way!
This is it! This is it!
I'm so happy!
This is the right way for a middle
school girl to spend her holiday!
Usagi, if you eat too much,
you'll gain weight!
But I just can't stop!
Oh, no!
Help!
It's Sailor Moon!
So, she's the Sailor Moon
everyone's talking about!
Wow! She's so cool!
Good job!
Thanks!
She didn't cut the rope
on purpose, did she?
Sailor Moon...
Why?! Why was Sailor Moon there?!
What about me?!
Calm down, Usagi.
Anyway, let's contact Luna and
everyone else and follow her.
Okay.
Only the sailor warriors and Tuxedo
Mask will be able to follow her.
Hurry up and come. I am waiting
for you, Tuxedo Mask!
Refrigerated Warehouse
She should be somewhere in this
direction. I've lost sight of her.
Who would have expected that a fake
Sailor Moon would show up?
I know.
I saw the news on that
bank robbery, too.
Of course, I didn't think
that was Usagi.
We would have nothing
to complain about
if the real Sailor Moon was as
hard working as her.
You're so mean!
The question is, what is the fake
Sailor Moon's goal?
Is she our enemy or our ally?
An ally...
Luna, could she possibly be
the fifth sailor warrior?
What? No, uh...
There's just something
fishy about this!
Besides, how dare she use
the name of Sailor Moon
without my permission?!
I gotta catch her, and make
her pay license fees!
Oh, no!
That is not the problem here!
Let's go, everyone!
Okay!
That guy is one of the
Dark Kingdom's...
Oh, no! We need to rescue her!
Wait!
It's dangerous. This could be a trap!
Even if it is a trap,
I just can't watch Sailor Moon
being treated like that!
I agree.
Everyone, transform!
Moon Prism Power Makeup!
Mercury Power Makeup!
Mars Power Makeup!
Jupiter Power Makeup!
What annoying and wasteful lights.
The only true beauty is the
radiant darkness.
The darkness of the Dark Kingdom
will shade the entire world.
I cannot wait to see it.
Not so fast!
You have terrible taste, tying
up a girl and hanging her!
I'm the sailor warrior
of love and justice,
Sailor Moon!
Likewise, Sailor Mercury!
Likewise, Sailor Mars!
And I'm Sailor Jupiter!
In the name of the moon, I will
severely punish you!
So, you are here.
I am Kunzite, one of the Great
Four of the Dark Kingdom!
Sailor Moon and sailor warriors,
prepare yourselves!
What?!
How do you like this beautiful
darkness?!
It's quite impressive.
Fire
Soul!
Sailor Mars, you good-for-nothing!
He's tough!
What's wrong?
Supreme
Thunder!
The power is being sucked
into the darkness!
Is that the extent of the sailor
warriors' powers?
Sailor Moon!
Is this a trap?
Shoot!
What are you doing, Sailor Moon?!
Zoisite!
You poor thing.
I will soon put you out of your
misery, Tuxedo Mask.
Zoi!
Running will do you no good.
I will take the rainbow crystals
this time for certain.
Zoi!
Oh, no! We're trapped!
Let me try something!
Supreme
Thunder!
It's no use! The power is being
sucked away by the barrier!
Give it up! You will never
break this barrier!
Here, here, here, here!
I've found you.
Die!
Zoi!
Oh, this man is...
My, you look handsome unmasked.
But I won't let you get away.
Prepare to die!
Crescent Beam!
It hurts! Ouch!
Who are you?!
Shoot!
How dare you make a fool of me?!
I don't care who you are! I'll tear
you to shreds! This isn't fair!
I can't breathe.
The air...
How do you like the taste
of my darkness?
Master Kunzite, please be careful.
In addition to Tuxedo Mask, there
is another enemy nearby.
Zoisite, did you fail to capture
Tuxedo Mask?
Such cold words! I was just
about to take care of that.
Tuxedo Mask! Look!
This is the end of Sailor Moon
and her friends!
What? Tuxedo Mask?
If you want to save them, come out
with the rainbow crystals!
Surrender yourself, Tuxedo Mask!
Tuxedo Mask, don't come out!
I can't hold on anymore...
Sailor Moon!
Wait!
We did it, Master Kunzite!
That's right! In the end, there is
no way for you to win!
Struggling will only bring
you more suffering!
It's important to know
when to give up.
No! You're wrong!
No matter how hard it is, you
must never give up!
It's the same voice again!
Oh, that voice is...
Who are you?!
Sailor warrior, Sailor Venus!
If you will pardon me,
I have arrived!
Crescent Beam!
Master Kunzite!
The barrier is gone!
Sailor V! You're Sailor V, aren't you?!
What?
Sailor...
V?!
She is the warrior of justice,
Sailor V!
And her true identity is...
Sailor warrior,
Sailor Venus!!
Luna, long time no see.
Artemis!
Damn it!
Master Kunzite, please run!
I will take care of them!
Wait, Zoisite, Kunzite!
Queen Beryl!
That is enough! The situation has
changed! Come back now!
Why?
Quiet! I am telling you to pull out!
We have no choice.
But Master Kunzite...
Sailor warriors, we shall finish
this battle another time!
Tuxedo Mask!
He's gone!
Anyway, looks like we're safe now.
Now, we have five warriors
and two cats.
Everyone is together now.
Sailor V, no, Sailor Venus...
Oh, by any chance, are you the
princess from the moon?
During the day,
the fragrance of flowers
During the night,
the twinkle of the stars
It's a world no one knows about
With white shoes clicking
Cross the white moon bridge
And there lives a princess,
dreaming of a sweet kiss
Offer a prayer to the moon
It will surely bring you happiness
Go round and round, the
moon's merry-go-round
Make that serene dress made
of glass flutter in the wind
She's always watching over us
Moon, moon princess