After the battle for BREW, each side started the next step of their plan.
However, Shibusen’s students have yet to cast away the shadow of their failure.
I started my own solo investigation to specifically understand Shibusen’s true intentions.
But... because of that, my suspicions towards Shibusen have intensified.
I've arrived.
From today onwards this...
will be my workplace.
Presented by SoulEaterFan
私は落ちている
ダウン自分の影に
Hold your breath
Deadly Night awaits us
怖いしないでください
You desired it,
the world like that
to reflect in those eyes
あなたの夢えの赤ちゃんのことを参照してください
Even if those dreams will be scary
For your sake, Fairy Blue
Breaking of stars
was decorated by
黒い紙の月
So don't stop believing!
あなたがしているときに
失われたここ私は午前
あなたの魂は永遠に
As long as I'm looking at
the brightly shining moon.
http://www.souleaterfan.com
Yeah, I’m glad you're here!
The technology advancement consultant from Shibusen's Oceania branch,
Buttadaki Joe, aka BJ.
What's up?
Don’t mind, it's nothing.
Let's get straight to the main problem.
You called me here at such a time; does this mean that the project has already begun?
You're too hasty! I haven't said anything yet, right?
Oh, I'm sorry. I can't think of any other reason as to why you'd call me here.
As you know, during the recent battle for BREW, Arachnophobia got the upper hand
and, because of that, I thought we had to prepare ourselves as a precaution.
And that’s why I called you here.
Seems like we’re not in a very good situation.
A bad situation indeed. And one that’s out of my control.
Which means, with BREW out of our hands, what are we to do with the plan?
Our side has managed to gather a number of Eibon's Demon Tools.
Even so, that makes it even more difficult! So, could you think of a way to help me finish my plan?
From the start, I was the one who thought of such a plan.
Well, let's try it.
Eh, would you do it?!
But, I have one condition.
What condition?
The coffee...
Coffee?
Replace all of Shibusen's instant coffee with coffee beans!
I want you to change the coffee to Mandheling if possible. Let it be top grade coffee beans.
And the coffee must definitely be bought from Uncle Bob's shop!
This is absolutely unacceptable. The coffee mill must be bought, based on what I have brought and arranged.
Even the coffee filters should be paper, I'm okay! I want you to prepare the cone type.
Mandolin?
Mandheling!
Asura's
Temptation
~The Big Man's Uncontrollable Irritation?~
Asura’s Temptation: The Big Man’s Uncontrollable Irritation?!
What?After Kid, even Black Star disappeared as well?
What on earth is going on?
Tsubaki isn't here either. I wonder what happened...
Who knows?
Speaking of Black Star... It seems like he’s in a bad mood.
Why did I lose?
I am a man who will surpass god.
But then...
why?
Why do you thirst for such power?
I wonder where Black Star went...
Tsubaki.
Nygus-sensei!
Do you have a moment?
What’s a person from the technology advancement department doing here?
You sure have fast ears.
I thought I hadn't been here that long.
And what do they call you?
Death the Kid. I'm Shinigami's son.
Oh, so you're the one.
What did you come here for?
You would surely know what my honorable father is planning.
Construction works.
Huh?
The water pipes in Shibusen have become old.
That’s why he called me.
Such an obvious lie...
Coming all the way from Oceania for such a thing…
Oh yeah! The boiler up ahead should be changed as well.
That’s the work of the technology section, huh?
There’s no boiler up ahead.
In the past few months, Shibusen has been putting all its strength into collecting Demon Tools.
And, with such timing, an investigator from the technology department section arrives.
It's normal to assume there's a link.
If there’s a pipe that never rusts inside the Demon Tool, that really would be something for people to cheer about.
Wait! I'm not done talking.
Let me advise you on something.
Huh?
You're overestimating me.
Oh yeah, is Uncle Bob in good health?
Uncle Bob?
The boss of the coffee shop outside. Uncle Bob's Rumba coffee!
It's so nice that it makes people want to dance!
Hey everyone, let's dance! Everyone, together!
I don't know who that is.
So, you don't know him...
That's a pity.
Oi!
So then...
First, I'll have to get rid of these things.
It's over.
Don’t think you've won just yet!
What?
Black Star.
You don't understand the Fey Blade.
You will never be able to properly use the Fey Blade.
Shut up! Such a matter, to the great me-
No. You can't.
It's over, Black star.
You've lost.
Finally, I found you!
Tsubaki.
So, you're in such a place.
What are you doing?
Thinking of a method to surpass god.
I know that.
You're skipping classes, is that alright?
I skipped class in order to look for you and ended up here.
Yeah, that’s true...
Just now, Nygus-sensei told me... not to use the Fey Blade mode anymore.
What?
She said it’s causing too much of a strain on your body.
Such a joke.
I’ll never give up on using the Fey Blade mode.
I understand.
Black Star will surpass god, right?
God, huh?
Black Star?
Oh, Kid-kun.
Where did you go off to?
Sorry. I just went to investigate some things.
Investigate?
Anything is fine, but... Before you do that, you have to tell us.
I'll explain after our classes.
But for now, you'll have to help me with something.
Huh?
Where did you go, Kid?
Did anything happen?
No, nothing.
At this stage, I can't let Maka or the other students notice anything.
From now on, if I'm not careful in my investigations...
Oh, Black Star.
You finally showed yourself. What time do you think it is?
Hey Kid, come out for a while.
What's up? Is there any problem?
Watch this, Kid...
Oi!
Again?!
You bastard! You destroyed Shibusen's symmetrical beauty! Bastard! Idiot! I won't forgive you!
Come down here, Kid.
Let's have a duel.
What?
Indeed. How's Crona?
Acting a bit oddly... she doesn't stop talking.
Hey Eruka, did Crona ask you anything?
Now that you mention it, she asked about Stein's condition during the battle for BREW.
Indeed, that is unusual, that such a child would ask those things.
Now that you mention it, it's true...
Such a pity.
That child...
probably won't be of much use soon.
What is this? Why are you two…?
For a guy thirsty for battle, doing such things is nothing unusual.
But...
Hey, hey.
Huh?
The opponent this time is Kid, huh?
The judge is here.
Wait, both of you. Why is do you need to do this? Stop it!
Tsubaki-chan?
I'm sorry,
but this is something that Black Star feels he has to do.
Bastard. Do you know how I feel after the symmetrical balance of Shibusen has been torn apart?
God of Death Martial Art. Stance of Sin.
I can't stand it any longer. I have to quickly use all my strength and beat you to a pulp.
Then, start the repairs.
Let’s go.
How long will you keep your hands in your pockets?
You want to win without using your hands?
Maybe.
Strong!
He’s fast.
Not enough time to guard!
He's going to shoot his wavelength.
It's over.
No wavelength?
Black Star.
When I first met you, we were in front of these doors fighting.
Compared to then, your power in battle has gone up a few levels.
But you...
became sort of weak.
He's lost self confidence.
That's the reason that prevented the wavelength from coming out.
Is that possible?!
Interesting, huh?
It only takes a small thing to change the soul's wavelength.
I've known Black Star since he was an infant.
He has talent.
And his soul is also strong.
He's also a hardworking guy.
No matter if it is against older students, or a large group of people.
He can beat them all, one by one.
His life is one in which he keeps on winning.
But his recent loss streak,
especially his fight with the samurai known as Mifune.
It was a total defeat.
I think it was around that time, when he first started acting oddly.
Even if he would go easy on his opponents, he doesn't have the strength to fight back.
Are you saying that Black Star...
Can't properly use the Fey Blade mode.
And that became one of the major reasons he lost self confidence.
You can't blame him. People with weak souls would have run away a long time ago.
But that idiot only knows how to surge forward.
Why are you impatient?
Impatient?
Just that the people around me are too retarded.
He doesn't have to push himself that hard. When he grows up, there will be a way...
Long ago, I was very handsome.
Adults fondly remember the past, and children use the future to escape.
But that guy lives in the present. That's why he must find the correct path.
That's all crap.
Living like that is useless.
It's not even a game, you idiot.
Sid.
Yeah. Those eyes. That wavelength.
White Star.
Are you chasing your father's path?
Black Star! The broken cone thing is fine. Just stop!
I can't stop. If you want to stop, then you're really asking for your death!
What happened to you, Black Star?
You want to surpass god, right...?
Um...
There's no need to apologize.
This will always happen, as long as he goes on living with all his strength.
But...
What’s important is what’s next.
As long as he can safely go on, it's fine.
He's alright now.
Black Star should understand it perfectly already.
Ah, I hope so too.
What are you doing? This was your idea.
That's true but...
It's unsettling. If you're not going to say anything, then you may as well not care for him.
How can I not care for him! He's our friend!
That's why you shouldn't be standing here doing nothing. Do it!
Wait, wait! I still haven't thought of what I should say! Wait!
33456, 33457, 33458, 33459, 33460
33461, 33462, 33463, 33464, 33465,
Hmm...
33466, 33467.
I found him.
Arachne-sama,
I made you wait for so long.
The madness amplification machine has been completed.
Sorry for troubling you.
The preparations have been completed.
From now on, it will be my turn.
That stupid old man.
Something happened.
I stop working from now
Uncle
Bob!
I can't dance like that, right?
The NOISE is kicking
around the preestablished harmony.
Flaring up and glaring
at the present.
I sneak in.
That time at the GARAGE I saw a dream about unchangeable HEART.
So this day and the same tomorrow gets mixed.
I'm roaring noisily
around in sensibility.
My singing heart plays the BEAT.
There's definite evidence.
Hold it in your hands.
Lose it
In the fading moments.
Tears have been secretly shed.
Everything
Gets revealed here.
Gets adjusted to the ordinary time.
I think that's the way it should be
Following the unclear yellow light.
Go through the darkest nights.
At that time I was too afraid.
But now I'm sending off my life.
You always reflect.
In my proud heart.
We should only protect our beliefs.
Embrace them.
It starts all over everyday.
I'm drowning in the raging waves.
Still haven't awaken from my dream.
We're all here.
I always hear.
The voices of my fellows.
I'm looking for a way to shake off the solitude.
In the winds of waiting.
I have no other way but to move forward.
I believe in the way of life.
Yeah.
Crona's Escape
~Your Smile, Please?~