There's a drawing of a snake in the sky!
What are you doing? Daddy's hungry and waiting.
Did you see the snake drawn in the sky, too, Mama?
It's just a cloud, though, isn't it?
However, Mama's not good with those kinds of clouds...
Those kinds of clouds?
It's a dog!
Oh no, you don't! It's dirty, so don't pet it!
Come here, doggie!
What's wrong?
Are you lonely?
Rachel?
Petting a stray dog...
You didn't listen to Mama, so don't blame me when something happens to you.
Rachel?
Yes, I'm sorry, Mama.
Presented by Soul Eater Fan Subs
If the light of connected souls points toward your heart
Can you now hear a resonance stronger than words?
Our eyes barely even meet, but our fates are intertwined
Our destinations are the same,
so run through the unbearable night along with me
Even if the radiance that we've chased so far
Continues into bad dreams
If the light of connected souls points toward your heart
Can you now hear a resonance stronger than words?
It doesn't matter why we met, but the pain we suffered
Of when we were entranced
and touched each other can now become clear
www.souleaterfan.com
This is the blueprint we brought back from Arachne's research facility for the Demon Tool,
but after some research, we've come to understand this as a part of the Book of Eibon.
Should we destroy it immediately?
No, please seal it in the secret vault.
But, such a dangerous thing...
Nygus!
Understood.
Sid and Nygus.
I assume you're well aware of this,
but this subject is to be handled with the utmost secrecy, okay?
Rachel,
aren't you watching too much TV? It's been on forever.
Do as Mama says.
You'll be scolded if you aren't a good girl.
Good night, Mama.
Good night.
Hey, don't you think Rach's behavior was a bit weird?
You think so?
She was a bit of an airhead all day...
Kids grow up without their parents noticing.
Changing a bit is not something to be surprised about...
But...
I guess you're right...
What? What is it?
Mama, Papa, a scary snake appeared.
She has a big mouth and she's going to eat my head.
A snake?
Is that so? You had a scary dream, right?
There, today you get the special place.
Papa will scare that snake away.
Right, Mama?
Yeah...
Medusa's
Revival!
~Spider and Snake, Fate's Reunion?~
Medusa's Revival!
Spider and Snake, Fate's Reunion?
Let's start the lesson...
Now, take your seats already.
I was worried for a while there. It's great the magic wore off.
Yes.
I'm completely refreshed!
Enough to go wild!
Then shall we do that to begin with?
Could you not stand up?
Let's have a party after school.
Surely, if Maka comes, Crona will tag along too, right?
The whole gang!
The troublesome person is late, though...
That Black Star... He's probably fighting again, right, Tsubaki?
Yes.
Whimsy, isn't he? He completely ignores you and goes off on his own...
It sort of comes with the package, so I can't do much about it...
Please attend the lesson.
The next one, I'll aim at you.
Sorry I'm late.
Fighting again?
Hell yeah! During Sis Marie's session.
So, the result?
I'm the man who'll exceed God!
I obviously won!
Whatever the result, you're late...
Stand in the hall.
I'll kill him.
Stronger!
I wonder what's with Black Star...
He's doing nothing but fighting all the time.
Facing opponents more powerful than himself without his Weapon, ten fights, ten victories.
Quite the beast, isn't he?
As I said last week, as of today we're starting a new class.
The Witch Arachne who was awakened by the Kishin's Wavelength of Insanity,
and the organization she leads, the Arachnophobia...
This is a lesson about how to fight against them.
Rather than having me explain it,
it'll be quicker if you learn it through your bodies.
That's because some kids in this class are stupid.
He's got his eyes glued on us.
You're both completely shameless, aren't you?
Now, the kids I name are to come forth, please.
First, Ox-kun...
and his partner, Harvar.
With rehabilitation in mind, Maka...
Alright!
and her pair, Soul.
And finally, Black Star...
come back.
In or out, please make up your mind!
How come you're breaking that much of a sweat?
As for you, since you'd trash the classroom with a Weapon...
you go unarmed.
Up till now you've only matched your partner's soul wavelength, right?
However, against a great enemy, kids like you fighting on their own would only get crushed.
So, in order to get around it, what I want to achieve is Team Soul Resonance.
Team Soul Resonance?
As this is the first lesson, you can come all out at me together.
No way... asking that out of the blue...
Now, come... I'll dissect you!
Scary...
Alright!
Mama, I'm hungry!
Yes, yes, hold on.
It's almost done...
There's still some, so you can have seconds, okay?
Yes!
Thanks for the food!
Must've been my imagination.
Is this what they call "a mother's touch?"
Such a plain and boring taste...
Ew, a spider!
How did it come in?
Now, get out!
Arachne...
For her to have already noticed...
Rachel?
Mama...
I'm going out to play.
Wait, Rachel!
Where are you going?
An important friend is waiting...
Let go.
Just who are you?
Are you really Rachel?
Oh, no...
Talking to your child as if she's some stranger.
She's a very good girl.
Obedient and easy to use.
No way...
Don't forget to lock the door.
They come in because there are openings...
both snakes and spiders.
Bye then, Mama.
Rachel!
Matching our souls within a team... how are we supposed to do so?
Who knows? Doc's switch is on, we can only try to hit and see...
Let's do it.
Although I highly doubt our souls and theirs would resonate.
Die, you bloodthirsty idiot!
You...
Four-eyes, die!
What happened to the other two?
Over-analyzing is also bad.
I know, but in a place where there are so many people...
You...
Chance!
Thunder King!
Huh?
Do you have a death wish, huh?
You're the one who got in the way of my attack.
You're in the way.
Maka...
Dammit, you clumsy fool!
Don't mind, don't mind...
Thunder King!
Huh?
My, my...
It's worse than I expected...
Enough already.
Doc, please bear witness as I beat up Ox-kun!
Fight as much as you want during recess.
As you wish. I always wanted to challenge you to a duel, anyway.
No words will reach them.
Do you think you can win against me, the one named the Wise General Thunder King?
Shut up!!
With this, eleven battles, all wins.
Don't include Ox-kun in my battle record!
Ox-kun, are you alright?
He beats up his teammate when he should be learning teamwork.
Does he think we have all the time in the world?
Pretty carefree...
What does Shinigami-sama intend to do by storing the Book of Eibon?
There's no need for us to know.
Enough questioning.
Shinigami-sama's collection...
It's so fearsome that I lose the will to peek.
No need to restrain yourself.
You should drink, as well.
Do you not require new blood?
It is an honor.
It might be poisoned, though...
Don't get cold feet...
Even if your petty life is taken, the Book of Eibon won't come back to our hands.
I deeply apologize for such a mistake taking place while I was there.
If you feel responsible, I shall give you another chance.
Being able to test Mifune's power is already an accomplishment by itself.
Indeed. He's a crucial asset to our war efforts.
"Crucial," you say?
If the person judging him is useless, how good does that make him?
Stop that rusty racket, you dirty chainsaw.
Wanna personally feel just how rusty it is?
Interesting.
I'll suck you completely bloodless and turn you into dried food!
Police Stinger!
Eh? He's flying...
That's it?
I'll say it clearly... you're old!
Then you shouldn't mind if I return to my form from 800 years ago!
Three-Piece Police Stinger!
That's nice. Go back to your youthful days.
Should we take a commemorative picture?
Either way...
When I turn you into minced meat, it'll be too small to even be photographed!
You brat!
Senile sack!
Arachne-sama!
What is it?
There's a guest for you, Arachne-sama.
Guest?
Who might it be?
Well...
She claims to be your younger sister.
Really?
Very well...
Let her in.
Oh my, such a lovable appearance,
Medusa.
Even after 800 years, you still remember me perfectly.
I have been observing you.
So that I would not lose sight of you no matter how much time passed by.
As always, spying is your forte.
You haven't changed a bit, either.
Coming to greet me bearing no fear whatsoever.
Have you not yet learned?
Even taking such a heedless appearance...
It's quite fine to fool people, don't you think?
You surprise me with your tenacity.
Even after taking in that amount of damage from the Shibusen people,
you did well to survive by scattering your soul.
Under those circumstances, what I had to avoid the most...
was to have my soul eaten by Stein and his Death Scythe.
That's why the moment the finishing blow struck,
I scattered my soul and resurrected through the snake that managed to escape.
No matter how much of a witch you are, it was far too dangerous...
When you were only saved by the circumstances of the moment.
Yes...
I was successful because the moment the Kishin, Asura, resurrected,
the overflowing Wavelength of Insanity stirred up my magical power.
I'll pass... on using such methods again.
Then why did you come here?
800 years ago, during the battle with Shinigami, there was the predicament of a traitor.
You sneaked into my castle all by yourself and
now you think I'll just let you go home?
That's just an old story...
Let's get along.
After all, we revived at the same time.
You've all come to greet me on my resurrection?
You went to all that trouble, but I'm not much into parties...
Let's meet again, big sister.
You're no fun to bully.
I will see you out.
Is that okay, Arachne?
For now, I will leave her be.
Keep on tangling yourselves in my web all you want...
Don't just waltz in, Medusa!
What if I become unable to leave the castle?
You're to keep surveillance here, Eruka.
I-I know.
I thought I was finally free...
You won't get your freedom so easily.
So, what do you intend to do next?
I'm borrowing this.
I must go back to pick up something important I forgot.
In Death City, that is.
The NOISE is kicking
around the preestablished harmony.
Flaring up and glaring
at the present.
I sneak in.
That time at the GARAGE I saw a dream about unchangeable HEART.
So this day and the same tomorrow gets mixed.
I'm roaring noisily
around in sensibility.
My singing heart plays the BEAT.
There's definite evidence.
Hold it in your hands.
Lose it
In the fading moments.
Tears have been secretly shed.
Everything
Gets revealed here.
Gets adjusted to the ordinary time.
I think that's the way it should be
Following the unclear yellow light.
Go through the darkest nights.
At that time I was too afraid.
But now I'm sending off my life.
You always reflect.
In my proud heart.
We should only protect our beliefs.
Embrace them.
It starts all over everyday.
I'm drowning in the raging waves.
Still haven't awaken from my dream.
We're all here.
I always hear.
The voices of my fellows.
I'm looking for a way to shake off the solitude.
In the winds of waiting.
I have no other way but to move forward.
I believe in the way of life.
Yeah.
The heated
runaway express!
Left Behind by the Great Warlock?~
~The
Demon Tool