I'm telling you,
your mission here has already ended.
Hurry up and pack your things,
there's still a lot of things that Medusa needs your help with.
But...
I don't want to leave here.
Personally, I'd love to let you stay.
But I wonder what Medusa has to say about that...
This is the first time that I've ever had friends.
If I leave now, then I'll never get to see them again.
Shut up and stop acting like a cry-baby!
Just do as your told, you idiot!
It's only a matter of time before they discover what you did.
If Shinigami finds out that you made Marie swallow Medusa's snake
so that we could destroy Stein,
He'll definitely crack you open with a million hits of his "Direct Braining Shinigami Chop"!
And that's not all,
that Maka will surely weep in sorrow.
No matter what you do, the fact that you betrayed them will never change.
Presented by SoulEaterFan
私は落ちている
ダウン自分の影に
Hold your breath
Deadly Night awaits us
怖いしないでください
You desired it,
the world like that
to reflect in those eyes
あなたの夢えの赤ちゃんのことを参照してください
Even if those dreams will be scary
For your sake, Fairy Blue
Breaking of stars
was decorated by
黒い紙の月
So don't stop believing!
あなたがしているときに
失われたここ私は午前
あなたの魂は永遠に
As long as I'm looking at
the brightly shining moon.
http://www.souleaterfan.com
Hey, get your ass out here!
We've traveled all the way here!
We'd expect nothing less than a cup of tea!
Has the cold gone to your head?!
Huh?
You're talking to the Kishin,
Who do you think you are? To him, your words are like a flea's sneeze.
Then I suppose yours would be that of a flea's fart?
What, you got a problem with that?
Arachne-sama,
please wait!
Please let us take the lead.
You stay here, I'll go in alone.
Arachne-sama...
Crona's Escape
~Your Smile, Please?~
Crona's Escape: Your Smile, Please?
Kishin, Asura,
My name is Arachne,
one who worships you.
I've come for you,
would you please let me see your face?
Just like the rumors, your cowardice knows no bounds.
Are you confining yourself here to regain your power?
Or,
Are you cowering in fear from Shinigami?
Seems like you've gotten tired of hide-and-seek and have decided to show yourself.
Come here!
Threatening a helpless woman like this,
You really are a cute boy.
There you are,
I've been looking everywhere for you.
What do you want?
The time has come to purge this land of Shinigami,
I want you to fight together with me.
800 years,
that's how long I have been holding in this hatred just so that I can take my revenge on him.
I believe that's the same with you, right?
If we don't stand together, there'll be no chance of winning.
Do you want to have your skin ripped off and become sealed in the darkness again?
Come, let's do this together.
Even if it costs me my life, I'll always protect you.
You can feel it, right?
My heartbeat.
My heart...
will never rest until I get my revenge...
This is good!
Hey Crona,
next time, join us in the Chain Resonance training!
If you're there, I think our powers will become even stronger!
Y-Yeah...
There's no need to worry!
I'd expect that much from you.
U-Uhh....
Here Crona,
eat as much as you want.
Sure...
Your face is ugly, but your cooking's really something!
These are not made by me.
They're made by Marie-sensei.
Huh?
Even though she has her hands full taking care of Professor Stein,
she still worries about how we're doing.
I'll make the person who did that to the Professor pay.
But first, I need to build up my strength.
Hey, why don't we pay him a visit?
If Crona comes with us, I think he'll be really happy.
I-I...
I need to go to the toilet!
Huh?
If you want to go then go alone!
I'll stay here and eat.
Hey, hold it you...
I haven't had enough yet!
What's wrong with them?
I can't tell them.
There's no way I can tell them the truth.
Just like Ragnarok said,
I can't stay here any longer.
You really are a good child.
You finally understand what you must do.
There's no place for you to return to, other than by my side.
Medusa-sama...
What are you doing?
Huh?
Dropping something so important.
Maka?
Erm...
Yes?
M-M-May I ask you something?
Of course!
You can ask me anything.
Erm...
About your mother...
Oh, right now, Mama is still a missing person.
M-M-Missing?
But occasionally, she sends me postcards.
Seems like she's on a journey around the world,
I wonder where she is right now...
Leaving a child behind and going missing?
This is too heavy...
What was she like?
Like someone you'd see on the cover of a magazine.
The cover?
She's strong, still, even if she was angry at something you did, she wouldn't raise her fist.
I guess she's the kind of person that makes you feel like she's calm and collected.
I find it impossible to imagine how she's like...
Then... what was the most memorable moment you had with your mother?
I'd have to say the day when she got divorced.
Huuh?
That day, she was the coolest ever!
This is strange, this is really too strange, Maka.
Did I say something weird?
Uh... No...
Erm, so what do you think about your mother then?
I love her, of course.
Putting that aside, is it okay for you to not go to the toilet?
Yeah...
500 bags of concrete,
200 tons of metal,
and I also need 30000 of those 55mm diameter bearings.
It's urgent, so please have them sent to me as soon as possible
Are you planning to build a skyscraper?
From a small leak in a pipe to major construction,
if Shinigami-sama asks me, I'll have them done.
You're just another one of those cunning people.
Oh,
there's one more thing that I need your help with.
Please tell me if you see Uncle Bob from that coffee shop.
I just can't dance if it's not his Rumba Coffee.
There's also one thing I forgot to mention,
rather than sandals, I think it's better for you to wear safety boots.
I don't think it's that easy to change something that makes me unique.
Buttataki Joe,
just like the steam above his coffee cup,
he's a man one can easily understand.
Why is he the consultant?
Is it because he resembles Father in a certain way?
Making a fool out of everyone with their fake smile,
while never showing anyone their true faces.
Now it's perfect!
Exactly what the hell is this?!
It's a total mess!
Who the hell would play this kind of prank?!
Forget about that, we've lost him!
What?
Where has he run off to?
Stop doing that!
What a bunch of nosy kids,
they don't even know the taste of coffee and yet they want to know the truth.
When I arrived during my afternoon patrol,
it was already empty like this.
Maybe she left.
What are you saying?
Ever since she moved here,
she's been acting weird, hasn't she?
She always seems to be forcing herself to fit in.
Even when she was with us, she seemed to be in agony.
Don't tell me,
you didn't notice?
Anyway, if this gets to Shinigami-sama's ears, it'll be a big problem.
I must go find her.
Hey, Maka!
Geeze...
Running off like that without the slightest clue of where she might be...
Crona,
Where are you?
Where have you run off to?
Why?
I don't understand.
Saying that you left, it's a lie, right?
Crona...
Man am I glad,
Now we can carry on with our lives without ever seeing those gloomy faces again.
You too. Once we get back to the hideout, you'll totally forget about them!
I'm not going back to Medusa-sama.
Huh?!
I just wanna go to a place without any people.
There's no way a wimp like you can make it alone!
Make up your mind!
If you won't go back to Medusa then turn back to Shibusen!
Stop it, there's no way I can go back there, right?
Saying all those lies and still being treated so nicely...
That would only make me feel worse.
Shut up! You idiot, do it before we've traveled too far!
Stop it.
I said, stop i...
Please forgive me, Arachne-sama.
Having your body beaten so badly while I was right there with you...
It is really inexcusable!
We've succeeded in persuading the Kishin to join us.
Rather than tears, I'd expect some wine for celebration.
Certainly, please have this.
Everything on my end is settled as well.
Unfortunately, he got three of ours while they were taking him to his room.
He's just like a child left trembling alone in the darkness.
Before anything else, we'll have to first make him comfortable.
Yuck!
How long do you intend to stay here?
We'll become sun-dried anytime soon.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I can only stay calm in a place with nobody else.
I can't do this anymore,
I'm gonna evaporate if this continues.
It's the same as that time,
the beach without sea.
We met at that sea-less beach.
Please be my friend.
You had the smell of the sun.
We are like the day and the night,
it was impossible for us to become friends from the very beginning.
It's all just a short dream.
It'd be fine if I just forget all about it.
Crona!
Are you sure it's really this way?
Yes, I can feel the presence of her soul.
Crona!
Maka...
Stop the bike, Soul.
Crona, I finally found you!
We'll get you out of there right away.
Hey Soul, give me a hand here.
Why did you come here?
I never said I needed your help.
Go back.
Just go back!
Crona?
You don't even understand anything about me.
Just leave me alone!
I-I betrayed you.
I'm the reason Professor Stein turned all weird.
I made Marie-sensei drink Medusa-sama's snake.
She didn't even suspect it.
She even praised me for being a good kid.
She shouldn't have cared for me.
Treating me so kindly,
trusting me like that...
Is she an idiot or what?!
Ridiculous!
You,
stay there.
Maka... Hey!
If you say anything that bad about Crona again, I'll never forgive you.
You're weak,
and you're excessively timid, but you always put others before yourself.
You always end up hurting yourself because of that.
Aside from that, I also know...
Crona, you laugh with the cutest face.
Medusa told you to do it, right?
You only did it because there wasn't any other choice, right?
Am I right?
Tell me that's the truth!
I couldn't tell her...
Huh?
Because she's my mother,
I couldn't tell her that I hate doing it.
But...
It hurts.
I don't want to hurt anyone anymore,
I don't want to make anyone sad!
I don't want to be separated from Maka!
I'm weak,
that's why I might end up betraying you again.
I won't let that happen again!
I promise, I won't!
It's okay now, let's go back.
Now, we have two people down there.
How are you going to get back up here?
Geeze,
this isn't cool at all.
Hmm... I can understand how you feel,
but she signed this contract.
Anyone who violates this contract will be exiled.
It is necessary for us to do this to protect the order of the world.
But Crona knows what she did was wrong.
She said she wants to apologize to Marie-sensei and Professor Stein face-to-face.
Maka!
This is not something you can get away with by just apologizing.
Crona did something that she never should have.
I don't want to hear that from you.
Huh?
You're no different, all you did was break the promises you made to me and Mama.
How many times did you ask for forgiveness, saying that you'd never do it again?!
You're not someone so unreasonable.
You should know the severeness of this case.
I don't know!
Such absurdity, I don't want to understand it!
It's not like Crona's really a bad person!
Hmm...
Shinigami-sama!
Huh?
A report just came in from security.
She has appeared.
"She" as in?
The mistress of all snakes...
Medusa.
Why are you here?
I have no intention of fighting.
I'm here to surrender.
The NOISE is kicking
around the preestablished harmony.
Flaring up and glaring
at the present.
I sneak in.
That time at the GARAGE I saw a dream about unchangeable HEART.
So this day and the same tomorrow gets mixed.
I'm roaring noisily
around in sensibility.
My singing heart plays the BEAT.
There's definite evidence.
Hold it in your hands.
Lose it
In the fading moments.
Tears have been secretly shed.
Everything
Gets revealed here.
Gets adjusted to the ordinary time.
I think that's the way it should be
Following the unclear yellow light.
Go through the darkest nights.
At that time I was too afraid.
But now I'm sending off my life.
You always reflect.
In my proud heart.
We should only protect our beliefs.
Embrace them.
It starts all over everyday.
I'm drowning in the raging waves.
Still haven't awaken from my dream.
We're all here.
I always hear.
The voices of my fellows.
I'm looking for a way to shake off the solitude.
In the winds of waiting.
I have no other way but to move forward.
I believe in the way of life.
Yeah.
Cut the Cards
~Medusa Surrenders to Shibusen?~