I've come to make a deal.
Presented by SoulEaterFan
私は落ちている
ダウン自分の影に
Hold your breath
Deadly Night awaits us
怖いしないでください
You desired it,
the world like that
to reflect in those eyes
あなたの夢えの赤ちゃんのことを参照してください
Even if those dreams will be scary
For your sake, Fairy Blue
Breaking of stars
was decorated by
黒い紙の月
So don't stop believing!
あなたがしているときに
失われたここ私は午前
あなたの魂は永遠に
As long as I'm looking at
the brightly shining moon.
http://www.souleaterfan.com
She's here.
Even with her Soul Protect on, I can tell...
That Medusa is behind this door.
Is someone there?
I'm thirsty.
May I have a glass of water?
That bitch...
Medusa!
Oh, a girl's voice.
Is there something I can do for you?
It's all your fault.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand what you mean.
It's your fault that Crona's suffering!
Oh, you're Crona's friend?
How is she doing?
I know you've been using Crona all this time.
I'm so worried about her.
She's always been such a weak child.
Why did you make her do such things?
You dare call yourself a parent?
If it's possible, I'd like to see her.
It's been so long since I last saw her.
Stop playing dumb.
But, I wonder what she will say...
if she sees me like this.
I told you to stop playing dumb!
Calm down, Maka.
Let's just go.
It's useless, talking to someone like her.
Hey Medusa,
enjoy the rest of your life in this dark cell.
It's an end befitting for the likes you.
Let's go.
Unfortunately, I don't think it will end like this.
Don't you agree, Professor Stein?
Cut the Cards: Medusa Surrenders to Shibusen?
But even so, that was really unexpected.
Who would've thought that she was still alive,
moreover, surrender to Shibusen?
I'm sorry.
But that time, we definitely finished her off.
Well, we're talking about witches here,
so anything is possible.
The problems start here.
Huh?
It's Medusa that we're talking about here,
we cannot deal with her using ordinary methods.
Why have you come?
I've come to see you.
Do you think you can walk out of here just like that?
The world itself has begun to move.
Besides,
you should know, right?
I do not place a bet on something does not guarantee my winning.
We'll see.
Are you alright, Professor Stein?
Your voice is trembling.
It's pitiful, seeing the madness slowly consuming you.
Is this really the time for you to be worrying about others?
I need you.
So join me.
I suppose you didn't surrender so that you could tell me all this.
Cut the Cards
~Cut the Cards: Medusa Surrenders to Shibusen?~
So long as you are bound by the laws,
you'll never be saved.
Come with me.
Together, we shall witness the dawn of a new world.
The time is upon us.
That's why, you...
I-I...
Sorry to interrupt your conversation.
Go home, Stein.
You should still be under house arrest.
Come with me, Medusa.
Where are you taking me?
Are you going to be the one interrogating me, Death Scythe?
Hey, Mister, why am I dressed up like this?
My hands hurt.
Give it up,
I'm not falling for that.
Oh?
But you talked to me.
At least now I'm one step ahead.
I'll let you talk as much as you like soon enough.
Well then,
shall we begin?
It's useless to get information out of me through torture.
Huh?
You cannot do anything to my body.
For you see, this body is "borrowed".
We're talking about infiltration and takeover, huh?
As a parent, you should know too.
Give that body back already.
I'm only borrowing this body until my magic power fully recovers.
I'll return it, eventually.
You'll never cease being a low-life, huh?
Oh, is it really okay for you to say that?
I might just turn out to be your savior, you know?
Huh?
I'm holding some information that is very useful for Shibusen.
Information?
I want to see Shinigami.
Stop with the jokes!
It's impossible for me to fulfill such a demand.
Besides, do you think we would believe the information you'd provide us?
I knew it would come to this.
Huh?
Then, I'll make you believe me.
When I was alive, I was also good when it came to shoveling.
That's the kind of man I was.
But what could Medusa be hiding in a place like this?
Huh?
Huh?!
This is...
BREW!
The results of a thorough inspection tell us that this is the real BREW.
Then, I will talk to her directly.
According to her, it's about making a deal with us.
A deal, huh?
Damn, what could she have in mind,
Giving up BREW so easily...
The fact that Medusa possesses BREW also come at a surprise.
Shinigami-sama,
Undoubtedly she is planning to use Shibusen.
It would appear so.
But,
I think there's the need for me to meet her in person.
Then...
Yup,
I'd like you to call her here immediately.
Stare...
Shinigami.
I can see that you're in high spirits, huh?
Because of what you did, the world is now in total disaster.
Even so, I'd like to show you my gratitude for believing in me.
Let's get to the point.
First, I'd like you to remove these restraints.
Since I'm standing in front of you, I don't think having it off will make any difference.
Those restraints, if you really wanted to remove them, you would have had them off long ago.
It would be meaningless if I remove them myself.
If you do anything funny, I'll rip you to shreds without warning.
Shinigami Chop!
Erm, Shinigami-sama...
Well, one strike is the least she should have expected.
This is it! The attitude that I hate the most in Shibusen!
Even during the time when I was still the nurse, I was trying desperately trying to adapt to this attitude.
So, what's this deal you are speaking of?
M-My panties...
Dammit, he's doing whatever he pleases.
I miscalculated.
Anyways, can you please put me down?
Pumpkin panties?! Maka also wore that when she was still little.
It's so cute!
This is getting too weird,
I must somehow bring them to my pace.
Well then, let's get back to the topi-
I wonder what it would look like if a woman wore bloomers.
I think it'd look good.
Because, in the past, they always wore them.
But if you think about it now, it kinda feels perverted.
They've started their own discussion on panties.
Stop this nonsense right now!
Ah, it was rude of us to be talking about this in the presence of a woman.
That doesn't matter to me!
So, what is this deal you're speaking of?
Put me down!
Pumpkin panties!
If you continue doing that, I'm gonna kill you!
What, can't even take some jokes?
Even when "Repetition after repetition" is the fundamental of jokes, huh?
You're talking about Tendon, right?
Yes, yes. Tendon.
If that's the case then let's do it three more times!
Hey, why is she backing up?
Hey, I'm not going to pick you up by the hood anymore. Please come here.
It's a promise!
What do you think?
About the conditions of the deal,
they aren't bad even from your stand point.
With that, you'll be able to find the answer to your biggest question right now.
What about if you stop making it sound so important and just tell us.
If you don't tell us right now,
I'll pick you up by the hood again.
You're already holding me by the hood!
Pumpkin panties!
Just stop this already!
Okay, okay! I'll tell you!
Honestly...
My card is...
The location of the Kishin.
Impossible!
Shibusen is putting all its effort in locating him and yet not a trace of him could be found anywhere!
That piece of information,
can you prove to us that it isn't some kind of lie?
I can't,
as long as I don't have your trust.
Ah...
Then tell us the location!
We'll go check it out.
I'm not that stupid.
What?
Because if I tell you, then it wouldn't be a deal anymore.
So what's the condition?
It's no big deal.
I want you to guarantee me and my comrade's safety, as well as to release me from custody immediately.
Just that?
Yes, just that.
Hmmm... But I suppose that is a condition that I cannot accept.
If that's the case,
then I guess you'd rather choose to live your life in fear of Arachnophobia?
Arachne?
What do you mean?
Are you saying that Arachnophobia and the Kishin have some kind of relationship?
You'll know soon enough.
It's alright.
I'll protect you.
I'll always be by your side.
I'll erase everything that makes you feel uneasy.
That's why, it's alright.
Mosquito.
Yes,
activating the madness amplifier.
What's that?
Seems like it has begun.
Please explain,
will you?
Arachne has taken in the Kishin.
And by using his power,
she's trying to spread his insanity throughout the entire world.
It's a pity, Medusa,
with this, the deals off.
Oh, but why?
It's such a tremendous insanity wavelength,
locating the source of the wavelength would be a piece of cake.
Unfortunately, that's impossible.
What?
Arachne has set up relay stations all around the world.
The insanity wavelength's source has thus been cleverly hidden.
If you look one-by-one, the world's going to be consumed by madness before you know it.
What do you think, Shinigami-sama?
Take it? Or leave it?
Just for a short while, would you give me some time to think about it?
Medusa's intentions are clear.
She's trying incite a conflict between Shibusen and Arachnophobia.
If that's the case, she can just sit and watch.
If you already realize that, then...
Even so, I can't leave the situation the way as it is now.
Then what should we do?
Hmmm...
I'm thinking about the same thing...
Using the information she'd give us and wipe out the Kishin and Arachne both at once?
Or get rid of Medusa while it is still a simple task?
It's okay.
There's no way they can turn down that offer.
There's no other choice.
I've won.
But if that's not how it turns out, then...
Which will it be?
Medusa,
you're free to go.
What's up?
Something wrong?
Maka?
You should take a good look at this.
Huh?
You'll understand once you see this.
Erm...
Excuse me.
Medusa!
Hey, what's going on here?!
I don't know the details,
but Shibusen has made a deal with Medusa.
Why?
I want to know that too.
Don't worry, Maka.
This isn't the end.
There will still be plenty of chances.
I'll definitely beat the crap out of her, and when the time comes, I'll let you land a hit on her.
Is this how honorable father's going to do things?
Why?
Why do they let her go just like that?
Shinigami, and Shibusen...
you shall become my pawns from now on.
Stein?
Geeze, you didn't even turn on the lights.
Stein?!
Stein!
And on that night.. Professor Stein disappeared.
My dried lips
are exposed to
the freezing sun.
Overflowing tears
with its reflecting shine,
keep falling down my cheeks.
Hoping to make up,
I have been looking for you
in dreary places.
When our fingers made contact
the only thing that was scrambled
was your loneliness
The wish we held on
in the middle of our heartbeats,
if only that was our destiny...
Although I have lost you,
the memories you left behind,
along with your image,
even now
remain within' me...
Winding and Sliding
~The Dancing Doctor, A New World?~