Tsubaki, Fey Blade mode!
On it!
Presented by SoulEaterFan
私は落ちている
ダウン自分の影に
Hold your breath
Deadly Night awaits us
怖いしないでください
You desired it,
the world like that
to reflect in those eyes
あなたの夢えの赤ちゃんのことを参照してください
Even if those dreams will be scary
For your sake, Fairy Blue
Breaking of stars
was decorated by
黒い紙の月
So don't stop believing!
あなたがしているときに
失われたここ私は午前
あなたの魂は永遠に
As long as I'm looking at
the brightly shining moon.
http://www.souleaterfan.com
Hey Kid,
why are we flying all the way out here?
It's not like it was my decision.
I don't want to talk about it either.
Well, would you at least tell me where we are headed?
Okay...
fair enough.
It's an area called Sekikan.
Sekikan?
Like its name,
it's like a coffin made from stone.
C-Coffin?
Originally, it was a typical village,
but that was about twenty years ago,
before that incident occurred.
Incident?
Yes.
One day, they all suddenly disappeared...
The humans in the village.
You don't mean... a mysterious disappearance, do you?
The cause of it remains unknown.
But, like the villagers, the people sent to investigate the place vanished.
Because of that,
everyone gave up on the investigation,
and instead put the area under lockdown.
I can see it.
It's right there...
Sekikan.
The Last
Demon Tool
~The Weaponless Kid's Impossible Mission?~
The Last Demon Tool: The Weaponless Kid's Impossible Mission?
Look at this...
This wall looks terrible, almost as if the builders were trying to desperately cover something up before anyone discovered it.
Like what Shibusen is trying to do right now.
Hey, don't you think the mood here is getting kinda scary?
Monster! Monster!
Can you stop saying those things right now!
No way! No way! No way! No way!
There's no way I'm going in there, absolutely no way!
Monsters or whatever, you know I can't deal with those things.
It was even written in my fortune-telling ticket that I should never get involved with those things again!
Don't worry, I'll be going in alone.
Are you sure?
Whether it's a virus,
or a chemical substance,
or a monster's doings,
or even a totally different cause.
All we know is that every human that's gone in has never returned.
Without knowing what the cause is,
I simply couldn't bring both of you along.
That would just be too dangerous.
I hate to admit it, but you do have a point there.
I think this is also the reason honorable father sent me, not someone else, on this mission.
But wouldn't it be dangerous to go alone?
Of course it will be.
That's because the recent series of actions taken by Shibusen
are based on the belief that they would lead them to the Demon Tools.
Demon Tools?
If I don't come out in forty minutes, I want you to go back to Shibusen.
Don't even think about going in to find me.
Postponing the final battle with the Kishin for something like this...
I shall see with my own eyes, just how great a tool it really is.
Connection with thirteenth squadron lost.
Fifteenth and seventeenth squadron, remain in contact and attack the enemies in area 34!
The battlefield is in chaos.
It's pretty bad out there, huh?
Don't you think we should give some orders?
If we knew what those "orders" would be, then we wouldn't be having a headache here.
However, I find any kind of orders better than doing nothing and watching them suffer.
It would be fortunate if those impulsive orders didn't make the situation worse.
Can you stop looking at me with those eyes?
Certainly, it'd be great to be free like you two are.
I, too, sometimes would think...
how great it'd be if I could do whatever I wanted, the way I wanted, and wherever I wanted...
Maybe not.
His words sting.
We're not the only ones feeling irritated.
If only his soul wasn't bound to Death City...
he would've been the first to make it to the battlefield.
So this is the forgotten village.
I haven't felt any odd changes since I've come inside.
There's nothing abnormal about the air, so it's normal that I can't sense any form of life.
But, I'm sure there's something out there.
What's that?
Where the hell am I?
Is this really the inside of an ancient ruin?
Hey~ supervisor,
I'm not your supervisor.
It'd be great if you would just call me BJ.
Supervisor, it's lunchtime.
Like I said, I'm not your supervisor.
Supervisor, we've prepared some coffee for you too.
Even though I'm not your supervisor, let's have some of that coffee.
The coffee.
Here you go.
Dig~ in~
This is... the coffee?
Is this it?
It's a key?
But it sure is a big key.
But is this really alright?
Obtaining a key so easily in a huge ancient ruin such as this...
Or is this a fake...
No, there should be no doubt that this is the real thing.
Wait a minute.
I said wait a minute.
Hey, Maka.
Hey, Maka!
Stop running!
We both know that you're running hard...
but do you know where you're heading?
Oh...
I have no idea.
Geez, you should really think about the consequences before you take action.
I did ask you what you wanted to do,
but you won't get to Medusa by just running around like that.
Yeah, you're right.
Sorry.
So, what are we gonna do now?
I'll use my Soul Perception ability to seek out Medusa's hideout.
Medusa has her Soul Protect on, right?
But it's different for Professor Stein.
Besides, Crona and Marie-sensei are also looking for her, right?
If I can sense their soul, I'll use them to get to her.
Professor Stein, who even Shibusen couldn't locate...
and Crona and Marie who went after him.
So, we're trying to find three people that could be anywhere in the world, without any clues?
I can't even begin to imagine that.
But I'm sure it'll turn out alright.
I think, somehow it'll turn out fine.
Eh?
For that, I need your help, Soul.
Uh... Sure...
Damn it!
Is this the security system that's protecting the Demon Tool?!
Do you have the qualifications?
Huh?
Do you have what it takes to wield the Demon Tool?
Hey clown,
why are you doing this?
Was it also you who attacked the villagers?
Answer me!
I can't allow humans to come into this place.
Those who lay their hands on the Demon Tool shall receive no mercy.
Then, you're the one responsible for what happened twenty years ago?
That would be correct.
This is the resting place for the last Demon Tool.
The last Demon Tool?
Those humans foolishly dug out this ruin twenty years ago.
They weren't qualified.
That's why I ate them.
I ate them all.
They were delicious.
All criminals shall be purged.
That's why, you too,
shall be eaten!
Did you think I'd let you eat me so easily?
Are you trying to run away?
I won't let you get away.
With that huge body of his, he'll never reach me here.
What a simplistic design.
See, what did I tell you?
What the hell?!
Good, I got out.
All that's left now is to meet up with Liz and Patty.
What?!
Damn! There was another one?!
Chow time!
Kid sure is slow.
I-It's okay...
N-No matter how long he takes, h-he'll definitely make it back.
I believe in him!
Do your best, Kid!
Hey, Sis...
don't you think it's best if we went and got him?
Are you k-k-kidding me?!
Who would go into a scary place like that?! Don't be ridiculous!
Well, why don't we both go in and get him?
Did you hear a word I just said?
Huh?
Yeah, I did. You were telling me the story about Mr. Pig, right?
You should listen when others are talking to you!
Huh?
I didn't hear that! I didn't hear that! I didn't hear anything!
Damn, they're persistent!
Symmetrical!
Not symmetrical.
Symmetri-
Not symmetrical!
That's a good pose!
That's undoubtedly the true symmetr-
They just can't see the beauty of it!
Just a little bit more... If I can reach that building...
Give it back.
Give us back the Demon Tool.
Kid-kun, we've come to get you!
Y-You guys...
Well, we can't help it.
So, you've conquered your fear of monsters?
Heh.
Whoa!
Wah!
Patty!
Understood!
How dare you destroy all the buildings around here.
I'll make you pay for what you've done!
Give it back! Give it back! Give it back!!!
These enemies...
This looks bad! They're too stiff!
If that's the case...
Resonance stable. Noise at 2.7%.
Black Needles... fully charged with soul wavelength.
Feedback in five seconds.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Firin'
At least let me finish this with beautiful symmetry.
Death Cannon!
Mission accomplished.
Unable to activate auto-recovery... System not responding...
Damaged received: 92%. Activation time remaining: 3 minutes.
He's still not dead?
Behold, you who defeated this guardian.
It's different from the voice before.
This voice...
Be warned.
Let me ask you, do you have the will to use the Demon Tool?
For those who do not possess the will, there shall be no glory...
Only destruction awaits.
He could be right.
Huh?
Who has the right to say that what we're doing now isn't a sin that can't be atoned for?
Who can tell for sure, that Shibusen will never use the Demon Tools for evil deeds?
So this is the Demon Tool of this mission?
Yeah, it's hard to believe that it was protected by such a security system.
This could just be the real thing.
So, what are we going to use it on?
I don't know that yet.
If I knew,
then things would be much simpler.
Huh?
Are those words you heard bothering you?
Yeah.
Because of that, I'm now wondering if giving this Demon Tool to honorable father is the right thing to do.
Let me ask you.
For those who do not possess the will, there shall be no glory...
Only destruction awaits.
With this, you'll be the last man standing.
My dried lips
are exposed to
the freezing sun.
Overflowing tears
with its reflecting shine,
keep falling down my cheeks.
Hoping to make up,
I have been looking for you
in dreary places.
When our fingers made contact
the only thing that was scrambled
was your loneliness
The wish we held on
in the middle of our heartbeats,
if only that was our destiny...
Although I have lost you,
the memories you left behind,
along with your image,
even now
remain within' me...
Coward Crona's
Determination
~For You, Who Are Always By My Side?~