You must hurry.
Hurry up, Stein.
Rid yourself of your fake skin.
Give in to your weight and walk on.
The glorious light illuminating the way out is almost in your sight.
Stop, Stein.
Where do you think you are going?
Shouldn't you be under house arrest?
I'm looking for my way back.
The fog is too thick
and I've lost my way.
You've been taken over by the madness inside you.
What are you talking about?
I'm a hound loyal to the law,
I'm guarding this door so that no insanity can pass through.
If you ever come near this door again...
What the hell?
Presented by SoulEaterFan
私は落ちている
ダウン自分の影に
Hold your breath
Deadly Night awaits us
怖いしないでください
You desired it,
the world like that
to reflect in those eyes
あなたの夢えの赤ちゃんのことを参照してください
Even if those dreams will be scary
For your sake, Fairy Blue
Breaking of stars
was decorated by
黒い紙の月
So don't stop believing!
あなたがしているときに
失われたここ私は午前
あなたの魂は永遠に
As long as I'm looking at
the brightly shining moon.
http://www.souleaterfan.com
I wonder what happened to everyone.
Since nobody came,
the morning classes have been cancelled.
Heh, you're talking about them?
They must be afraid of the madness
and are refusing to come outside.
They're probably hiding under their blankets, shivering as we speak.
But, there's no need to worry!
Kishin or whatever, I'll kill him in a second by myself!
Well, if it's me, I don't think it'll take even one second.
Soul.
Hey.
Acting all tough, don't be peeing your pants if you see him.
Don't be stupid.
Where's Maka?
About that...
She said she won't be coming.
She's too worried about the Professor and Crona,
she can't concentrate on anything.
Hang in there a little bit more.
Even Medusa has been released,
so I think you'll be forgiven too.
Hey,
what happened to Professor Stein?
Has he come back?
Tell me.
Doesn't Professor Stein's disappearance have something to do with Medusa-sama?
Maybe,
but there's no need to worry.
It's the Professor we're talking about.
He'll definitely come back for all of us.
Stop the search?
Why?
Stein is already outside of the city.
As things are now, we cannot afford to send anymore people to help search.
It's obvious where he is.
He's gone after Medusa.
If that's the case, then it'll be worse.
Because Shibusen can't even lay a finger on that witch.
There is a Deathscythe's special mission waiting for you.
So please return to Shibusen as soon as possible.
Are you fine with that?
Not as a Deathscythe, but as a former partner,
can you really just give up like that?!
He's been fighting all this time...
With the madness inside him.
There's no way he would give in so easily.
That's Medusa for you,
there's never been a witch that's been able to make a deal with Shinigami.
From now on,
it'll be enough for us to just watch Shinigami and Arachne kill each other.
But if it doesn't go well,
we'll have two ferocious pawns coming for us.
Shinigami will never violate the contract.
Besides, do you think Arachne can really handle the Kishin?
Just wait for an opening and then we'll make our move.
Where are you going this time?
I'm going out to meet my lover.
Winding and Sliding
~The Dancing Doctor, A New World?~
Winding and Sliding: The Dancing Doctor, A New World?
Don't cry.
If you can make it through the jungle of anguish,
the lake of happiness will be there waiting for you.
No matter how lost you are, there'll always be only one way out.
Are you girls lost too?
"Girls?"
You know,
I've been alone all this time.
That's why, I'm very happy...
To be able to meet you here.
Come with me.
The path ahead will take us to the door that leads out of here.
That girl's a witch.
You can't stay here forever.
There's somebody waiting for you, right?
Open the door and leave this place.
But be careful of the witch.
If you let yourself be taken away by insanity,
then you'll never find the way out.
Then what should I do?
Simple.
Just think of the place that you should return to.
Think of the place...
Who are...
Hmmm...
Reaction to magic - zero.
It remains inactive.
Should I just hit it with my wavelength to activate it?
No, there should be some kind of trick to this.
Bleh...
With all this bad coffee, my head is beginning to feel heavy.
What the hell...
This is...
Isn't it a big discovery?!
Who would've thought that Eibon's book would have a hidden page.
And it contains the answer we need.
In order to activate BREW, we need a key, which is also a Demon Tool.
Let's dispatch the search party immediately.
This mission is suitable for Kid.
We've become quite distant nowadays.
I doubt he'll take this mission on.
Because he's suspicious about our plan, huh?
Well, rather than father-and-son relationship, we should prioritize the plan.
No matter what, let's have him help us.
And one more thing,
that man...
I'd also like to ask the help of Uncle Bob.
Erm...
Who was that again?
You've forgotten?
That old coffee shop owner!
Just one drink would make anyone dance.
Uncle Bob's Rumba Coffee!
If it isn't for that, Mandheling wouldn't be called the brown jewel, the finest of all coffee.
Mandolin?
It's Mandheling!
Without his coffee, my concentration keeps slipping.
And I should have been able to discover the trick behind BREW sooner.
If I keep going like this, it will start to affect my work.
Is it really that bad?
Yeah...
Actually, I wouldn't mind asking the helping hands of a cat too.
"Asking the helping hands of a cat" is a Japanese idiom meaning that one is extremely busy to the point that even a cat's help would be appreciated.
A cat?
It's smells so nice my saliva's dripping.
Lunch is almost ready, so please wait a little longer.
Lunch? Isn't this just a lump of black stuff?!
Which reminds me, isn't it supposed to be Maka's turn to cook today?
Where is she?!
She's locked herself in her room and refuses to come out.
I wonder if my delicious fish would cheer her up.
Hey hey, Soul, how about helping me taste it?
Eh?
Now, say "Aah."
Whut thu hell aw you doing?
Huh?
Why did they let her go?
If it wasn't for her, then Professor Stein... even Crona...
No, I can't do this.
If this continues, I'm gonna be overtaken by insanity.
There's something for you.
It's from Mama!
The place I should return to...
Huh?
Wait, Stein!
The laboratory...
It's good that I've reached home,
but I've violated the curfew, and ran off without permission.
I wonder what kind of excuse I should use.
Marie!
What are you doing, Marie?
Look, Stein, such a small world.
It looks just like a prison covered by the clouds.
There should be a world out there that's more suitable for you.
Goodbye.
Marie!
Aww, she died.
Just the way you want it.
Actually, you've always thought she was very cold, right?
That Marie...
Looks like you went through the wrong exit.
As I thought, you've been corrupted by the madness inside you.
What happened to Marie?
Don't worry.
You'll forget everything once you've been reborn.
Your old memories, your name too.
What are you going to do to me?
It's judgment for breaking the law and calling forth the insanity.
I'm going to dissect you and fix you up from the inside.
Stop!
No!!
There's so many pictures.
Yeah, Mama sent them all to me after she reached each of her destinations.
It's been quite some time since she last sent one, so I was a little worried.
As expected, your mother is really cool, huh?
Huh?
Just a while ago, you were still depressed,
but you're all okay now.
Yeah.
Hey, where did she send it from this time?
Huh?
There's something written there.
Oh,
you're right.
I wonder what it is.
Yo.
Being a teacher only means trouble.
I never thought I would become one.
However...
Being around those children is just so much fun, I'm unable to quit now.
You're like me too, right?
Stein.
This face, I can't let those children see me like this.
No need to be afraid, Stein.
Without dissecting you, the dawn of the new world will never come.
Yes, you'll be reborn,
ridding yourself of your fake skin...
Shut up!
Shut up!!
Shut up!!!
This is the fruit of life.
It will save you from all your suffering.
You'll feel better.
Don't be fooled.
That's just a shadow, it has no body.
Just an illusion that you created.
Are you...
Me?
Please don't be so nervous.
Well, have some tea.
Erm...
Don't tell me you're also a coffee lover?
Mandheling or whatever, please don't start telling me such complicated things.
I have a request.
Please...
Please let me go to Medusa-sama.
I want to bring back Professor Stein!
You are still under arrest for betraying Shibusen.
Are you asking me to trust you?
I must go.
For the sake of Maka, who defended me...
I must do it.
Sure.
Huh?
You also want to settle everything with Medusa, right?
Yes.
Eh, you sure have some guts.
Mi-Miss Marie!
She wanted to talk to you, that's why I called her here.
Sorry.
Not only did I l-lie to you,
b-but Professor Stein too...
I don't need your apology.
Raise your head.
If I held a grudge because of something a kid did,
then I wouldn't deserve to be called an adult.
Stein's matter,
I can't allow it to be entrusted to you alone.
That's why,
I'm coming with you.
Just now,
when I went through that door,
I was lost for a moment.
I was wondering if this is really the place that I should be returning to.
You should be satisfied.
Ah, yeah.
Even with all the laws set by God, I managed to come all this way without feeling any guilt.
Yet...
Yet?
So why have the feeling of guilt born now?
Rather than fulfilling your own lust, you found something much more important, right?
You already know the right choice, don't you?
That's why you called me, right?
You'll open the right door, and go through it.
The world that you seek awaits.
The world that I seek...
There's only one way out.
The place that I should return to...
Right on!
Damn you, it's only because I went easy on you!
Then be serious and try to win it back.
The one who gets the ball in next shall defeat the Kishin.
What?!
Hey...
You idiot!
Geez, is this really the time to fool around?
Isn't it okay?
Taking a break is also necessary.
Not you too, Tsubaki.
Maka, catch!
Hold on a minute, didn't I tell you I'm not good at basketball?
Here, Tsubaki.
Yay, I'll be the one to defeat the Kishin!
What, you're going to betray me, Tsubaki?!
Beats me.
Huh, what?!
Does it really matter who defeats him?
Let's just kick his ass,
so that we can play basketball together again.
Don't space out, Maka!
Yeah!
Hand it over, you lowly commoner!
Go!!!
It went in.
Yahoo! Did you see that?!
My miracle head shot!
Huh?
So the one who will defeat the Kishin is me!
Hey, your head is twisted!
You're all so carefree, huh?
Kid.
You skipped school again, didn't you.
That's just unfair, you know?
I've come to tell you something.
Huh?
The one who leaked the whereabouts of the Kishin to Shibusen was Medusa.
So that means...
No mistake, they released Medusa in exchange for that piece of information.
How can they believe a witch's word just like that,
while putting the lives of the students at risk?
I can never understand that.
Anyways, it's no longer safe to believe in Shibusen without being cautious.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Rid yourself of your fake skin.
Give in to your weight and walk on.
The glorious light illuminating the way out is almost in your sight.
This is the way out?
My dried lips
are exposed to
the freezing sun.
Overflowing tears
with its reflecting shine,
keep falling down my cheeks.
Hoping to make up,
I have been looking for you
in dreary places.
When our fingers made contact
the only thing that was scrambled
was your loneliness
The wish we held on
in the middle of our heartbeats,
if only that was our destiny...
Although I have lost you,
the memories you left behind,
along with your image,
even now
remain within' me...
Charge!
Baba
Yaga's
Castle
~Why is Everything Suddenly so Unclear?~