The Lost Island…
Here because of an accident long ago, a special field was formed.
And the struggle for the Demon Tool between Shibusen and Arachnophobia began.
The battle of epic proportion began across the island.
We infiltrated the field in search of Professor Stein and Marie.
And the scene we witnessed within… was a visual memory from a distant past.
Presented by SoulEaterFan
私は落ちている
ダウン自分の影に
Hold your breath
Deadly Night awaits us
怖いしないでください
You desired it,
the world like that
to reflect in those eyes
あなたの夢えの赤ちゃんのことを参照してください
Even if those dreams will be scary
For your sake, Fairy Blue
Breaking of stars
was decorated by
黒い紙の月
So don't stop believing!
あなたがしているときに
失われたここ私は午前
あなたの魂は永遠に
As long as I'm looking at
the brightly shining moon.
http://www.souleaterfan.com
Damn.. they just keep coming.
Now what?
Twenty minutes will be up soon. Kim, give the signal for retreat.
I've got your back!
Make sure I'm covered.
Let's do it Jacky!
Okay!
They're planning something!Aim for the girl!
Ox!
Yeah!
Chain Resonance!
Change Pixie!
Like hell!
Royal Thunder Drill!
Flash of lightning!
Thunder Combination!
Thank you!
Let's do it Jacky!
Mosquito's Storm!
~Old
Days World's Time Limit is 10 Minutes?~
Mosquito's Storm!
Old Days World's Time Limit is 10 Minutes?
Where are they hidden?
Target sighted.
Welcome to the trap area.
One more step… left.
The stench of gunpowder!
Hit!
I've got him! Now, Nygus!
Nygus!
Die!
I see.
Seeing how you fight, I can understand how Black Star was raised.
You're really good. I've got nothing against you.
With skills like yours, wouldn't you do better not working for that evil organization?
Such a pity.
Is that… an order to retreat?
Now I have no reason to fight you.
Now it's up to you whether you lay down your sword or not!
However if you let me go, you may be attacked from the shadows again by me.
Sounds like fun.
Go.
All troops withdraw!
Withdraw!
Stein!
What is wrong with you?
I'm being consumed…
by insanity.
Franken, get a hold of yourself!
The insanity!
Why now of all times?!
What is going on inside of you?
If you don't watch me, I might do something regrettable.
There they are!
Professor, Marie-sensei, are you alright?
Why are you guys here?
What are you doing.
You disobeyed my orders.
It's been twenty minutes since you entered. You must get out of here, quickly.
Our bodies are turning into an image.
What about the tool?
We still have more than 10 minutes so we will search for the tool.
Lets go!
Hurry and go!
Wait… just a second!
If I try to chase them in my state, I'll only die.
I'll give them what they deserve later.
Since we already ignored orders we may as well finish the job. Where's the Demon Tool at?
The longer I'm near you the more disobedient I seem to become.
Lets go in through the gate.
Someone's there!
Is he part of the image?
He can see us. Come to think of it I've seen him before.
So is that thing he's holding…?
I expected to run into some people from Shibusen but you guys seem vertically challenged.
Give us the tool and we will let you go.
Let me go?
Child, you underestimate me.
Whether I have or have not, have you looked at your body?
What?
It seems he's reached the limit of staying within the field.
We still have ten minutes. There's no reason to attack you.
As long as we keep you in the field nature will do the work for us.
I see.
My old body can't handle more than twenty minutes.
I see, I see.
Have it your way. Shall I take a little of the past for myself?
400 years?
No 100 should suffice.
Respect your elders! This is me one hundred years ago!
Now I have ten more minutes, so we're even.
Hey, his top half got so big that his legs are dangling.
Is it supposed to be like that?
How should I know?
Maybe you should ask him yourself.
You guys look delicious now that I look at you.
Who is this guy? Another image?
And things were getting good to.
We don't know for certain yet.
It's…
Eibon.
Did you just say Eibon!
This is Eibon?
Do you know him Kid?
U-uh no…
We don't have a lot of time left.
We don't have time to play anymore.
Ignored!
This is a bit over my head but that Demon Tool is mine!
Wait Black Star! Eibon…
Don't be stupid Kid, we only have ten minutes! Ten minutes isn't enough to stand out!
Ten minutes is too small for guy like me that exudes brilliance every second of the day!
You're nothing but a shrimp! Living life like it won't end…
that's why you'll always be a shrimp! You half-brained moron!
Kid!
Black Star is right, our priority is the tool.
Let's go!
Yeah!
M-Maka, Black Star!
Kid!
You've said enough!
This old man lacks quite a lot of balance. I wouldn't touch him with a ten-foot pole.
Right! That's the spirit!
In the end this is all you can do.
The me of a hundred years ago… was the time I was at my strongest!
No way!
He doesn't have a single scratch.
This isn't good.
None of us can align our wavelengths as a team.
The only one who can is Maka who excels at soul perception.
What should we do Soul? We can't beat him without using chain resonance.
I have within me the ability to communicate everyone's wavelengths through Maka.
You know the way to do that.
Don't you, Evans?
Don't call me by my family name, you piece of shit.
Come, come this way.  We're already setup for the concert.
Give care to the injured.
We were done in pretty badly as well.
Sid you should get some care quickly too.
Yeah, you are right.
Sid-sensei!
Kim, Jacqueline well done.
Where are the others?
Well the professor and Marie never returned so Maka's team went after them, and Ox and Kilik are engaging the enemy.
What?! Azusa can you try to find them?
I apologize… Because of the field I can't see from this distance.
It'll take too long to get there with this poor footing.
Azusa gather ten people that are able to move!
Sid...
But with those wounds…
Nygus, hurry and treat these wounds.
Roger.
We only did beautifully at the beginning… our enemies were elite as well.
Who cares how we did it? We won.
Professor! Marie-sensei!
What happened!
Kilik, Ox, watch over the professor!
Marie, what are you going to do?
The effects of the field won't go away just because you left momentarily.
You're only going to die by going back in.
But then…, but then they will…
Everyone is still inside?
Let us go instead.
Idiots! No way!
I can't let any more students go in!
If you don't listen then I'll make sure you get failing grades on all your classes.
You'll be expelled!
What do we do Ox? We can't afford a failing grade.
What have I got to be undecided over Harvar?
A foolish question.
Shibusen students protect their own.
Wait!
Expulsion… I'm the one that looks like a fool.
A new teacher like me doesn't have the power to do that…
Like threatening them would stop them anyways.
Even though I'm an adult, their teacher, I can't do anything!
What do I do! What if they don't come back?
Don't cry Marie.
The failure of this mission, everything…
all of it is my responsibility.
All of it!
I'm sure by now you realize the difference in power.
Shut up and give us the Demon Tool.
Do you know what this BREW inside of my hat is?
Of course you don't. But yet you do so much for it.
It must be youth.
You brats know nothing of it's value.
With BREW in hand Arachnophobia will soon have the world.
Quit while you have a chance Shibusen.
Shut up you dumbass! Shut your mouth gramps!
Tsubaki! Fey Blade Mode!
Okay!
Demon Tool? Who cares Baldy?
Who cares about that? This isn't a fight between Arachno-whatever and Shibusen!
Lets do it! This is my fight with you!
Maka! Kid! Become the shadow of my shadow!
Shadow Star!
You won't break through my body of steel with an attack like that!
Maka!
You bastard!
I'm saying I'll be your opponent.
We'll lose at this rate.
And now I'll take care of you all at once!
Feel the sting!
How's this?
The weight of a hundred years ago.
Everyone! Wake up!
Shall we call the curtains?
Nope, the shows just starting, right, Soul?
Polis Stinger!
You haven't got the time to sit on it. Come, I have the perfect stage set.
The black blood will spread to everyone, won't it?
A team resonance is an indirect connection.
It wont spread if you don't resonate strongly with Maka.
Come to the black room.
Turn your connection into sound. Accelerate the black blood in your veins.
I know.
Do I have it in me?
The piano plays.
Making the madness play me.
How am I supposed to know?
Everyone, listen.
From now on our resonance will be told in sound.
Through sound? Can you do something like that Soul?
Yes, I thought about it during the countermeasure training.  Our wavelengths will communicate through Maka.
We can only do this because of Maka's ability of soul perception.
But how do we communicate?
I play the piano with my soul.
The sound will communicate directly with your souls.
Huh?
What's so funny?
Because we were trying to come up with a plan for how we could get you to play the piano when you didn't want to.
Don't be so self-important!
We only have five minutes to do this. It's a shame we only get a five minute concert.
Won't you play for us, Soul?
We've been looking forward to this. -Right?
What do you think?
Nice crowd!
No need to worry it's all tuned up for you.
That so?
The NOISE is kicking
around the preestablished harmony.
Flaring up and glaring
at the present.
I sneak in.
That time at the GARAGE I saw a dream about unchangeable HEART.
So this day and the same tomorrow gets mixed.
I'm roaring noisily
around in sensibility.
My singing heart plays the BEAT.
There's definite evidence.
Hold it in your hands.
Lose it
In the fading moments.
Tears have been secretly shed.
Everything
Gets revealed here.
Gets adjusted to the ordinary time.
I think that's the way it should be
Following the unclear yellow light.
Go through the darkest nights.
At that time I was too afraid.
But now I'm sending off my life.
You always reflect.
In my proud heart.
We should only protect our beliefs.
Embrace them.
It starts all over everyday.
I'm drowning in the raging waves.
Still haven't awaken from my dream.
We're all here.
I always hear.
The voices of my fellows.
I'm looking for a way to shake off the solitude.
In the winds of waiting.
I have no other way but to move forward.
I believe in the way of life.
Yeah.
Release,
Seven People's
Resonance Chain!
~Concert of Creation and Destruction?~