The way of a demon or the way of a warrior?
Black Star,
on which path will you walk?
Shut up!
And quit barking orders at me!
In the end, he still chose to walk into darkness.
BLACK STAR!!!
Where am I?
What the-!
Let go of me!
Let go of me, goddammit!
STOP!!!
Those images...
Presented by SoulEaterFan
私は落ちている
ダウン自分の影に
Hold your breath
Deadly Night awaits us
怖いしないでください
You desired it,
the world like that
to reflect in those eyes
あなたの夢えの赤ちゃんのことを参照してください
Even if those dreams will be scary
For your sake, Fairy Blue
Breaking of stars
was decorated by
黒い紙の月
So don't stop believing!
あなたがしているときに
失われたここ私は午前
あなたの魂は永遠に
As long as I'm looking at
the brightly shining moon.
http://www.souleaterfan.com
Hey, Free, can you hear me?
Loud and clear.
It's been a while since I've lost communications with Medusa.
By the looks of it, I think she's probably...
Probably dead, right?
I'm thinking the same thing.
What do you think, Mizune?
I see.
If that's the case...
Yeah, time to bail out.
Huh?
Is there something wrong, Ox?
Uh, no...
Then hurry up and move on.
Yeah...
The Miraculous
Raging Flip
~ : Fly! Our Death City's Robot?~
The Miraculous Raging Flip: Fly! Our Death City's Robot?
BREW,
unlock.
It begins.
This is-!
It's getting bigger!
Just watch closely,
This is Eibon's ultimate creation,
the Demon Tool, BREW's true form.
Shinigami,
the preparation is complete.
Thank you.
Honorable father,
what kind of power does this BREW has?
The Demon Tool, BREW,
its power lies in its ability to take the form of its wielder's desire.
Taking the form of its wielder's desire?
According to its wielder's soul power, and how great his desire is,
its effect changes.
And therein lies its biggest irony.
It is the kind of Demon Tool which,
if used in the wrong way, would lead to the destruction of the whole world.
The power of the tool has left even its creator in fear,
forcing him to create a key to it at the cost of binding his own soul.
In short,
Eibon the Demon Tool,
is but Eibon's soul itself.
And it is he, himself, that's the safety device that is able to activate BREW.
Shinigami-sama,
my final research has led to nothing but sorrow.
The destruction of friendship,
betrayal,
the conspiracy of the witches,
and the eternal separation with the one I love most.
But in the end,
at least I'm able to make some amends by helping You.
Those words, which you said to me at that time...
Even if you surpass death itself, you will only find grief and sorrow ahead.
This is the first time that I feel like I understand what that means.
Eibon...
Save the world...
Fool!
Shinigami-sama, can you hear me?
There's a change in the front line: the enemy has a new weapon.
We will not be able to hold the line if this continues.
Seems like there is the need to speed things up.
I can't think of anything to say for this kind of situation.
But you just spoke, Sis.
Oh, sorry.
I'll keep my mouth shut then.
Yeah, then I should do the same too.
A Demon Tool that takes the form of its wielder's desire.
What is honorable father's desire?
Well then, let's give it a shot.
This is-
Honorable father!
Death City is-
So it's your turn now, Nakatsukasa?
What? Have you finally decided to come and suck up to me?
Today, I only come to bid you farewell.
Huh?
Do you not understand?
What are you talking about?
You've lost.
What?
And now you're on the verge of being swallowed by the souls of those warriors who have lost even their will to survive.
This is a place deep inside the Fey Blade,
the final destination of those who have strayed from the path of the warrior,
their souls ripped apart by fear itself.
Then, what I saw earlier...
Farewell, boy.
We shall never meet again.
Bragging that you would transcend God,
but instead, this is where you end up.
Huh?
Hold it there, damn deer!
Black Star, living in the world of darkness,
one who robs people of their dreams, a dweller of the darkness.
A peaceful death is the least I can offer you.
You're beginning to look much better than before.
It would seem that someone has chosen the path of a warrior.
The path of a warrior?
What?!
I'll never show you my tears.
These are the tears of those who died with regrets.
If there's a way to take away these regrets,
I'll make sure I find it.
Foolish words!
You've already lost.
Despair is all that remains, you can never change th-
Stop that bullshit!
I've not lost just yet.
If it's fear that you speak of, then I'll stand and face it.
I'll never give up.
The only time I lose is when I die!
As long as I don't admit defeat,
then it'll never be a loss!
Are you telling me that you're going to get rid of the regrets of even those whose souls have fallen before this blade?
Try to keep up, Nakatsukasa.
I'll show you a world which no one has ever seen.
Our souls, together with you till the end.
Mifune, let me tell you something.
The path I choose is neither the path of a warrior nor a path of a demon.
It's a path that not only surpasses saints, but even God himself!
I'm only going to follow my own path!
Neither a warrior nor a demon's path, but a path of your own?
Come, Black Star!
Mifune-san.
What are you waiting for?
Just finish me.
You've already given up, bodyguard?
There should still be someone that you need to protect.
And besides, you must also keep the promise you made with Tsubaki.
A kind warrior like you, who loves children, could be a model for us at Shibusen.
If only you would become one of our teachers...
What...?! Me, become a teacher?
Let's go.
First, we'll get that princess of yours.
That old fart, so he's not as useless as I've thought!
You sure are an easygoing fellow.
What?!
Don't tell me you really didn't notice, did you?
Damn, you're irritating!
Just get on with what you wanna say!
The attack has been indiscriminate all this while.
In other words, you've been abandoned by Arachnophobia.
What?! Are you serious?
Yes, I'm serious.
Dammit!
Too weak, too weak!
As expected from Lady Arachne,
only she would've known that just by sacrificing some of our own forces, the battle can become so one-sided.
You're next!
So it has come to this?
DIE!!!
What the-?!
What's that?
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?!
Phew,
We barely made it in time, huh?
What... is that?
Honorable father's desire...
Due to the fact that He rooted His soul to Death City in order to seal the Kishin,
His body also become bounded to this land, unable to go out.
His desire to come all the way here cannot be compared with anyone.
So this nonsense is how it is realized?
Well then, let's see how far this thing can go!
Mosquito, counterattack.
Understood!
NOW IT'S THAT CASTLE?!
What is going on here?!
Is all this real?
COOL!
Come get me!
Here I come!
This is really testing my patience, damn it!
Honorable father, don't be too reckless!
EAT THIS!
WHAT ABOUT THIS!
KEEP DREAMING!
HOT!
IT'S HOT! REALLY HOT!
Honorable father!
EYE POKER!
Killing move,
RAGING FLIP!
WHAT?!
Now's the chance!
So this is the power of a Deathscythe,
Clairvoyance.
Shinigami-sama, target located.
At the middle-top section of Baba Yaga Castle.
The Kishin is there.
Thank you, Azusa-chan.
Kilik and the others have also done a great job.
Hold on tight!
Just you wait!
EAT THIS!
Inexcusable!
What?!
Impossible!
He swallowed the Kishin!
My dried lips
are exposed to
the freezing sun.
Overflowing tears
with its reflecting shine,
keep falling down my cheeks.
Hoping to make up,
I have been looking for you
in dreary places.
When our fingers made contact
the only thing that was scrambled
was your loneliness
The wish we held on
in the middle of our heartbeats,
if only that was our destiny...
Although I have lost you,
the memories you left behind,
along with your image,
even now
remain within' me...
The Weapon
Shinigami Had
~Towards Uncertainty,
Filled with Darkness?~