Ahh, Arachne-sama...
The reaction of my mistress's soul has disappeared!
Presented by SoulEaterFan
私は落ちている
ダウン自分の影に
Hold your breath
Deadly Night awaits us
怖いしないでください
You desired it,
the world like that
to reflect in those eyes
あなたの夢えの赤ちゃんのことを参照してください
Even if those dreams will be scary
For your sake, Fairy Blue
Breaking of stars
was decorated by
黒い紙の月
So don't stop believing!
あなたがしているときに
失われたここ私は午前
あなたの魂は永遠に
As long as I'm looking at
the brightly shining moon.
http://www.souleaterfan.com
Hey, Maka, you're ready for what's coming, right?
Of course I'm ready.
Shinigami-sama can no longer fight, so it's all up to us now.
Asura's Awakening
~The Arrival of the World's End?~
Asura's Awakening: The Arrival of the World's End?
That's...
The Kishin...
What an ominous presence.
Let's get going, Tsubaki!
Yes.
Hold on, Black Star. I'm coming-
Mifune, you and that midget should get as far away from here as possible.
Why you! An is not a midget!
Are you sure you want to do this?
You should know already
that I'm the man to surpass God.
Black Star!
Kid, what the hell is that?!
What's that?!
It's a barrier.
Wha-?!
In order to heal his body, which got injured when fighting with Shinigami,
He intends to go into a deep sleep.
Huh?
That's impossible!
If he does that...
The wavelength of madness will continue to expand,
and he will be able to take control of this world without even needing to fight.
We can't just sit back and let that happen.
Liz! Patty!
Sure!
Coming!
I must protect,
in the place of my honorable father, as a Shinigami,
the order of this world!
Death the Kid, where are you going?!
Wait!
Without a Technician, just what do you think you can do?
Out of the way! Out of the way! Out of the way!
Out of the way! Out of the way! Out of the way! Out of the way!
Yo, Maka. You're late, as usual.
Sorry. A lot happened, you see.
Kind of unbelievable that we still meet each other here, even after taking different courses of action.
But still, it's a good thing that we met here, right?
Yeah, I couldn't agree more.
Everyone, I need you all to pay attention to your soul at all times.
Don't let your guard down.
Because if you do, you'll soon be consumed by madness.
That's something we must avoid at all cost.
We know.
That debt last time,
I'll make sure I pay you back with interest!
For the order of this world,
and also for honorable father's revenge,
I will make you pay!
If we can make it out of here alive, I'll never be afraid of ghosts or monsters anymore.
Huh? Sis, then you'll be invincible!
Hey, Patty, I'd appreciate it if you would stop talking about invincibility in front of the man who is closest to being invincible.
Huh?
Black Star.
Show it to me... The moment when you surpass God.
Sure, just sit back and watch!
Ready, everyone?
What's that?! It's totally different from what we saw just now!
Not only that, he has become so much bigger!
Has he eaten Arachne's soul?
I don't care how you look,
I'll just beat the crap out of you!
Insects.
Insects are good.
It seems like a few insects managed to make it in here.
Concentrate!
Soul's performance is about to start.
It's showtime!
That's a one-in-a-million combination of two opposing powers:
The anti-demon wavelength and Black Blood together.
There!
What's wrong with that skin of his? It's so hard!
The attacks are working.
Let's keep up the pace!
Okay, Maka?
Yeah.
Damn! Is it really working?
It's working. Just look around you.
That's-
The barrier is weakening.
That's the best proof that we're beating him back.
Is that really how it is?
That's got to be it!
The Chain Resonance is also going very well.
We'll use this opportunity to defeat him!
What could it be...? This sensation...
It feels as though a forgotten worry is bursting its way out from deep within my heart.
Could it be...
More! Keep increasing the tempo!
Soul, are you even listening?!
Shut up! Of course I'm listening!
You guys just shut up and follow the flow of my performance!
Let's increase the tension!
We're gonna go full out until the climax!
Death Cannon!
Demon Hunte-
Soul!
This is the end, Soul.
The world belongs to me now.
Soul!!!
You've gotta be kidding me.
There's no trace of even one wound on him!
The surgery was successful.
If she remains stable, then the wound will heal up without worry.
Yes, I understand.
But...
But?
I said something I never should have said to her...
That I wouldn't be able to trust her until we got you back.
And although I was there the whole time, I couldn't do anything and let her get hurt.
It's because I forced her into that tough fight that she got hurt.
Then just tell her.
Huh?
Crona is still alive.
Just tell her when she wakes up.
About how you feel.
Crona,
are you okay?
Crona?
I must go...
Eh?
to where Maka is.
You're so persistent. How long do you intend to keep this up?
It's obvious that they've betrayed you.
Shut up already!
I'll kick their ass for sure!
But before that, I'm going to kick yours!
Who's next on your list again?
Isn't it obvious?!
It's gonna be that old hag Arachne!
That's a surprise.
Just how easygoing can you get?
What is it this time?!
Arachne is already dead.
What?!
And the proof is that all the forces except you have begun to abandon this place.
Arachnophobia has been destroyed.
Impossible!
So how is it gonna be?
Don't take too long to decide, because this place will be swarming with Shibusen's people before you know it.
Or do you plan to fight everyone by yourself?
I'll go easy on you for today-
He bit himself.
Just you remember,
I'm definitely going to kick your ass!
Your insults formed a pattern.
Shut up!
Listen up, you damn priest!
You won't be so lucky next time!
Goodbye!
What's that?
It's a barrier created by the Kishin.
We think it's similar to the Death Room,
where we can't do anything from the outside.
I see.
The spreading of the madness is still not slowing down.
We even made Death City move.
But in the end, we still can't defeat the Kishin?
Fools!
Eh?
Are your eyes just for decorations?!
Ge-!
Why does someone with eyes that look like they're for nothing but decorative purposes get to ask me that question?!
There's still hope.
What do you mean?
Before the barrier was sealed up, we managed to confirm that Death the Kid,
Black Star,
and Maka Albarn made it into the barrier.
The battle is not over yet.
Maka and the others, are inside?!
The chances are slim,
but if it's Maka Albarn's anti-demon wavelength, then...
I see.
If she manages to harness enough power, it might just be possible to defeat the Kishin.
Whatever the case, it'll be the same here.
Huh?
For us, watching from here is all we can do.
Soul.
Soul!
Soul!!
What's happening?
What happened to Soul?!
I don't know the details either.
But-
He overused his powers.
Wha-
The Kishin disappeared!
In order to push all your powers to their maximum levels, he used whatever he could and let the burden on him keep increasing.
Take it as something that's been building up all this while.
So... it's all because of the Black Blood?
Trying to fabricate a power that you can only obtain by giving up your body to the insanity,
it's inevitable that the body will someday fail.
Everything would've turned out fine if only he had given up his body for it.
If he had done that, his life would've become one that is without fear.
Don't get ahead of yourself by spitting out meaningless words!
Stop this!
Don't be affected by his provocations!
There's no need for you to be caught up in his pace.
Stop kidding me!
From the beginning till the end, everything is going with my pace!
And stop thinking that you can stop us with those petty tricks!
My God... He dispelled the illusions just by using his fighting spirit!
I expected no less, Black Star.
But we're still facing a big problem.
With Soul like that, we don't have anyone that can synchronize our chain resonance.
Kid, support, support.
I know. I don't need you to remind me.
It's like the attacks aren't affecting him at all!
If we don't gain some foothold before the Kishin decides to strike back,
we're gonna lose this!
His pulse is getting weaker.
And he's beginning to look pale too.
If this goes on...
Soul,
I...
What are you doing, Maka?!
Huh?
Just go to him!
Maka, you're the only one who can save Soul now.
Hurry up and bring that idiot back!
Black Star...
Kid...
I promise you,
we'll do anything we can to hold the Kishin down.
Are you kidding?
By the time you come back, it'll all be over.
Unfortunately for you, Maka,
you won't be able to witness the moment when I surpass God.
It's useless. You're too late!
Stop the foolish talk! It's not something for you to decide!
I'll be your opponent!
I'm leaving the rest to you two.
Soul, I'm coming to get you now.
It's weak, but I can feel it,
Soul's wavelength.
Huh?
Wha- What was that?
What's going on here?
That's... the sound of a piano.
Soul.
I've been waiting for you, Maka.
Soul?
Ya. It's me, Maka.
Black Star!
I'm tired of playing around.
Now get lost!
I'm not going to let you touch them.
Because I promised them, you see.
We keep the promises we make.
That's how we Shibusen students are.
Kishin Asura,
this will be your end.
My dried lips
are exposed to
the freezing sun.
Overflowing tears
with its reflecting shine,
keep falling down my cheeks.
Hoping to make up,
I have been looking for you
in dreary places.
When our fingers made contact
the only thing that was scrambled
was your loneliness
The wish we held on
in the middle of our heartbeats,
if only that was our destiny...
Although I have lost you,
the memories you left behind,
along with your image,
even now
remain within' me...
Sink or Swim!?
~The Men Who Exceed God?~