Presented by Soul Eater Fan Subs
If the light of connected souls points toward your heart
Can you now hear a resonance stronger than words?
Our eyes barely even meet, but our fates are intertwined
Our destinations are the same,
so run through the unbearable night along with me
Even if the radiance that we've chased so far
Continues into bad dreams
If the light of connected souls points toward your heart
Can you now hear a resonance stronger than words?
It doesn't matter why we met, but the pain we suffered
Of when we were entranced
and touched each other can now become clear
www.souleaterfan.com
Hot!
Why do we have to come to this dusty place with such strong ultra-violet rays?
Father's orders.
Stop complaining.
You must have heard of it, right?
The Runaway Express that runs on the desert without rails.
Hot!
The famous train in the Sahara that hasn't stopped running for 100 years?
Yeah.
100 years, huh?
How does it keep on moving?
It seems a Demon Tool is involved.
A Demon Tool?
If used for evil, it has the power to cause world-wide catastrophes.
This Demon Tool is apparently being targeted by Arachnophobia.
Hot!
Stopping them...
and securing the Demon Tool is our mission.
The heated
runaway express!
Left Behind by the Great Warlock?~
~The
Demon Tool
The Heated Runaway Express!
The Demon Tool Left by the Great Warlock?
Hot!
Thanks to your Shinigami skin, you don't get sunburn, right, Kid?
Then, there's no need to put on a mantle, is there?
I just feel like it.
Besides, it's because of my resistance to poison...
that these three stripes reappear right away even after I dye my hair, which is quite annoying.
There it is.
A train station in the middle of the desert?
Now, let's hurry!
It's almost time for its arrival.
Your spirits are oddly high.
How come?
For over 100 years, it's been running on its assigned route, with perfect timing,
as if it were always precisely following its timetable!
Wanting to see it once is a given!
That's it?
Someone's already here?
Seems to be a child.
Well, this is a sightseeing spot after all.
Good afternoon.
My, my, it sure is hot, isn't it?
Hey!
Yo...
Hey, chibi! At least give us a proper greeting! Didn't your sister teach you anything?
Would you cut it out?
Did you just click your tongue? Are you looking down on me?
I'll turn you into minced meat!
Well, well... There are a lot of sand pits here, so play with your sis, okay?
According to the timetable, it should be about time it arrived.
I'm looking forward to the Runaway Express.
Done!
Alright! Good girl, good girl.
That little kid is a bit suspicious...
What's going on? If this keeps up, it'll be late.
The train always arriving precisely on time was a false rumor, huh?
What a let-down...
Oh, it fell down.
Awesome!
You're too late, Shinigami's errand boy.
I, the Fisher King, have already made the big catch.
The Demon Tool belongs to Arachne-sama!
Fisher!
Is that Arachnophobia's assassin?
Soul protect release.
What?
A witch response?
Then she wasn't a tourist?
No, she might have been a tourist who was also a witch...
Look!
That witch had planted a bomb!
It left in the blink of an eye...
It looks like a huge worm!
Save your thoughts for later!
Hurry and transform into guns!
Okay.
We're chasing them!
Go, go, go!
There it is.
I'm the first one on the train! I'll be taking the Demon Tool.
What? They've already caught up?
Rod Launcher!
Kid-kun, incoming attack from three o'clock!
How about that? How about that?
How do you like my Rod Bombs?
What was that?
Good, I'll hide in the smoke and get close to the train.
Kid-kun, the train is turning right!
This is bad!
Damn, it sure is violent.
If I have to watch out for attacks from both sides and above, then boarding the Runaway Express will be tough.
Patty, can I count on you?
Sure!
It's okay if I finish that enemy scum, right?
I'll leave it to you!
Hey! Hey! Show your face!
There you are!
Die, Rod-man!
360° Kickflip!
Perfect.
What are you doing, Kid?
Why are you doing skateboard tricks at a time like this?
You fool! This is the only place where you can find such massive sand banks!
If I don't do at least one or two tricks, it'll be an offense to the desert, right?!
What?!
Look! We're at the next bank already!
Patty! No-Hander!
3600°...
No-Hander!
What the hell are they doing?
Alright. Patty, return to weapon form.
Okay...
If I stay on the roof, I'll just be a target.
It look likes the guy inside is further ahead already.
I'll detach this linkage and send those punks flying along with the rear carriages!
Where did that pervert go?
There he is.
You're pretty fast, skateboard kid.
But this is goodbye. Disappear along with that carriage!
Damn it!
He released the linkage, huh?
That was close! So there was another one in the sky...
However, you can't stop me!
Crap! In a moment of confusion, I jumped to the back!
Fisher!
This guy's a total idiot...
An idiot! An idiot!
What an idiot...
Damn it!
Fisher!
This is goodbye, once again!
Liz, Patty!
Linkage!
What?
This feels great!
So refreshing!
Damn it!
I will take the Demon Tool!
I won't let anyone near the engine room!
He ran away!
Liz, Patty.
Rod Launcher!
That bastard... His firepower is too reckless!
What?
Damn it...
This is...
This train's power source...
The Demon Tool, Eternal Spring.
I won't let you have the Demon Tool!
This Demon Tool belongs to Arachne-sama...
This is our goal, the Demon Tool.
With this, we can bring this runaway train to rest.
What a wicked Demon Tool...
It really disgusts me.
You ignorant Shibusen brat...
That Demon Tool is the work of the Great Warlock Eibon.
Eibon? That's probably just a useless villain anyway.
Eibon and Shinigami are the same person.
Are you mocking my father?
What? You're Shinigami's son?
I'll show you something good.
Open the box where the Eternal Spring was stuck.
The box?
Are you saying there's something inside this?
The Spring alone is not the whole Demon Tool.
It's a set that includes both the key and the box it fits into.
Now... Now... Now...!
Look at the plaque behind the box's cover.
This is...!
Eibon... and...
Death.
Shi... Shinigami.
There's no mistake. This is my father's handwriting.
Why is my honorable father's signature on this thing?
What's wrong, Kid?
What's written next to Eibon, the one you called the Wicked Warlock?
Whose signature is that?
What is this?
What is the meaning of this?
That's...
What?
You're...
Sid-sensei.
Leave the rest to me and the Africa branch's salvage unit.
You guys go rest.
Kid, this guy's soul... belongs to you.
Take it down! Take it down!
Sid, a witch flew away.
Our target is the Eternal Spring.
Leave her be.
Now, you kids, go take a rest at the camp.
We have cold drinks there.
Yes, thanks!
Thank you!
I'm grateful.
We can finally get out of here!
And yet again, another Demon Tool is in Shibusen's hands.
It's no use...
I can't find a single clue in the Level 1 information reports.
Eibon and Shinigami are the same person.
Who the hell is Eibon?
Yes, how can I help you?
Are you looking for a book?
I want to research in every book about a certain person, all the way up to the ones in the highest level block, Level 4.
May I see your student ID?
I'm very sorry.
One-Star and Two-Star students only may go up to Level 2.
Teaching staff are allowed to go up to Level 3.
Finally, both Death Scythes and first-class Technician all the way up to Level 4.
You, sir, are still a One-Star.
You may not request anything but Level 1 books.
Look at the back of the card, please.
Yes.
My deepest apologies!
So you are the honorable son of Shinigami-sama!
If you'll wait for a brief moment, I'll retrieve the requested book immediately.
Please do.
I'm still a One-Star Technician.
If possible, I wanted to stand on equal footing with everyone, but...
like when I asked my father about the Kishin, he wouldn't give me a straight answer.
My only option is to investigate it myself.
Did you find it?
Yes, in the Level 4 block, there is a single volume related to Eibon.
Then, please tell me which shelf it's in.
Quickly.
About that, you see...
It seems it hasn't been returned since it was last borrowed two months ago.
Do you know who borrowed it?
I will go myself and ask that person to return it.
I apologize...
Due to my own incompetence, I can't determine who borrowed it.
The signature on the loan card...
there's nothing but an "M" written on it.
I'm sorry...
I deeply apologize.
Still, who would borrow a book like this?
The book was borrowed roughly two months ago.
April 1st...
The day of the Kishin's resurrection...
The NOISE is kicking
around the preestablished harmony.
Flaring up and glaring
at the present.
I sneak in.
That time at the GARAGE I saw a dream about unchangeable HEART.
So this day and the same tomorrow gets mixed.
I'm roaring noisily
around in sensibility.
My singing heart plays the BEAT.
There's definite evidence.
Hold it in your hands.
Lose it
In the fading moments.
Tears have been secretly shed.
Everything
Gets revealed here.
Gets adjusted to the ordinary time.
I think that's the way it should be
Following the unclear yellow light.
Go through the darkest nights.
At that time I was too afraid.
But now I'm sending off my life.
You always reflect.
In my proud heart.
We should only protect our beliefs.
Embrace them.
It starts all over everyday.
I'm drowning in the raging waves.
Still haven't awaken from my dream.
We're all here.
I always hear.
The voices of my fellows.
I'm looking for a way to shake off the solitude.
In the winds of waiting.
I have no other way but to move forward.
I believe in the way of life.
Yeah.
Drying Happiness
~To Whom do
you Shed Tears in the Moonlight Shine?~