... Rico
A-order?
. Your marriage has ended negotiations
Huh?
! Without you are here there is no one here
! I do not want to leave you
.. I want to stay there with Kemeto-sama
.. and Haku-sama
.. and Karen-sama
. And with you, Ika-sama
. I do not know what should I do
No. quite a bit, something we will
I will something, you understand?
... this is
! Important commoner
Although I am lacking experience please Aqublna Forever
. It should be out of the woods now
Say, what I turn to us?
. As of Orzogaoa themselves, I can not the heart of a good engagement
. Rico whole fate depends on you
Oh, this city from the outside?
It looks exactly as "the land of commoners" huh?
. It is not
What speeches?
. Look over
. There are a lot of guards
! Let me see! Let me see
when ?
. Most likely that someone had leaked what I do for my mother
. And aaah, they have wooden swords
What we have to do?
. The first thing you do is make you responsible for this commoner
. While everyone attract to your area, quickly Sonzlq
. I am in charge impossible from there
... that they
They use swords, right? Seem very adept in which
Huh?
! I want to fight them! I want to fight them
! I wanted always fighting against others Alsyafon
! I wanted the experience of my ability
We go through this to go to a place Arzogaoa, right?
. E-this is true
. Yup
. A person authorized what it did this
! I will go
! My name is Karen Genro, in my capacity as I want a clean fight Hospitality
! The Art of Karen sword style
! Dissolution
Damn, where they went?
Commoners really deceiving a group, huh?
. But things will go a little differently today
! Get ready for new Tguenita art style sword Karen
! The only expansion
what about that ?
Are you the heroine anime Ufa!?
! Well, it's our chance
What ... ?
We are trapped
. We have to do something
But what do Imknnav against this number!?
. Let them me and continued
! Let us continue the progress forward, according to
! Wait
! The art of sword style Karen! Fifty-eight whirlwind
! Excessive
! Wait a minute, Masumi-sama
! Stay away from the road, Takemia
... Masumi-sama, take this difficult for you
! But please, it's time to let go of your sister
! I refuse
Masumi-sama
! Takemia
. Masumi-sama, I now see the strength of Azimtk
! I will command, and you guys have continued
where is she ?
. To the stairs and then to the right
. Thank you, Haku
! Slow down Kemeto, a little slower
How can you say something like that?
Maz--?
Initially people, machines now?
! It's now League
Huh? What do you plan to do?
Where did you get this kind of control?
! I 100/100 firing in the trash
! Kemeto
! Yup
! A-Antzerona
! What is that ?
! Oh no
. From this road
. From here Control Room
! Good job, Haku
! Haku
! Are you fine ?
! Yup
. I'm fine
! Oh no
! Will not do it
! Now you can
! Haku! good luck
! Beautiful, Haku
! Kemeto what stands? Flansra and go
Yup
Haku? Is this the right way?
. Ommmm, behind this room and by
Here, it is true?
What is that ?
! It started
This is bad ! How can we stop this?
! Ahtersa
! We get out of here immediately
Are you okay you guys?
. Sorry to make you waiting for
! Karen! What is the story of this outfit?
. There is a room in the palace, where the flow of time is different from the outside world
-- What ? And the Spirit Room
! Here is coming again
! Watch this, Kajorzaka
. At the beginning of decay and then full over, then the only expansion
! This is the art of the sword style Karen: final technical
! Raise the effect of what does not end
! Give your contacts some consistency
! I did it ! I stopped moving
! Do not worry about me, continued
Kajorzaka?
! Curse ! What a way to inflict damage
! we will wait you
! .. Takemia
! ... Masumi-sama
. I have become stronger
. A little boy will not stay forever
. I have penetrated this
! This will be faster, huh
.. If you wish
Kemeto-sama?
. Lara Lara, he was a friend of Rico school
. As I see you've come all this way for your boyfriend on Rico
. thank you very much
. With this we are a little busy now
. We will Nthmlk for some time later
Llano ..
Yup ?
. I oppose this
! I am completely opposed to this marriage
.. Kemeto-sama
Why this ?
- because they are reluctant to
. Rico is not hesitant to accept
Is this not true, Rico?
. Rico understands, as the daughter of a family Arzogaoa
. Exactly how important this engagement
This is not what you really want, is not it?
We have made tracing family laws by, right?
So what is this?
- self-denial for the benefit of the family
.. Rico is aware of this completely, and the nature of this matter
. And the important call, this will Rico, and the duty and everything
. Ami like you will not understand us
. No I do not understand
. More than a month since it provided for Sicaen
. I still do not understand there INSAT
. The world they live different as well as the food they eat
. I tried to clarify things Amyin them, but they did not understand well
.Trivh Our vision is completely different things
. Probably we will never understand each other, too
... But
.. even though
- I and these girls
- Club members commoner
! We were able to be friends
.. and above this, the time we spent at the club commoner
.. Do you have an idea how much fun we have had
.. and the extent of the pain we feel now because we Snfterq
About Rico?
.. Kemeto-sama
. Even if it's so, P Rico has decided and accepted this
! This has never accepted
! Ica
, This is true for me, I thought that is being hated by others
. And not to find you inconvenience source is important
. But these things a little bit, but important
. I discovered the importance of doing what you want to do
. This is staying with Kemeto and Haku and Karen and Rico
... I know we do not have the right to say anything here
.. but at least
! At least waited until Rico accept the situation
! It's our dear friend
! I beg you
. Our guests will leave
. Come on, this way
! Hi ! Kemeto do something
Something like what?
! Let me go
... Mom
! I will leave the house
Rico, do you understand what you are saying?
. My understanding is certainly
... At the moment you leave your family Arzogaoa
. Vstvkadin's eligibility to return Sicaen
. Sicaen allowed a school for girls from prestigious families only
. It's not a place that has frequented girl no longer Arzogaoa
.. also ran away if away from home and back to Sicaen
. Sntha up Ttjolin streets
! Rico
! Come to my house
. It's house-Ami
! The upper rules and restrictions Sicaen will not mean anything
... you will never be at able to go to school after her
.. I can not give you the same life that Thzin by now
But would you like this?
... e-Do you mean
! Will convince my parents, I'll do my best
! I'll do my best to make sure your happiness Rico
! Yup
Although I am lacking experience please Aqublna Forever
! Leave this Ali
. My father, my mother and thank you for everything you Fltmah for me
, Our son had heard Rico-san's strong tendencies
. Somehow he is surprised perhaps to say that he also shocked
. He said he would return to school
.. Hoku-san if we were able to bring down the whole affair
Well, what can I say?
. Rico, you may Taatzojin from you like
! Mom
! thank you very much
.
.. Kajorzaka-san
! A-order
. Take care of by Rico Forever
--Hah? -- Mom ! I'll be very happy
Lato, what do you mean?
Ye will be married, right?
Huh?
I've just made it, is not it?
! Come to my house
... you will never be at able to go to school after
.. I can not give you the same life that Thzin by now
But do you want?
! Will convince my parents, I'll do my best
! I'll do my best to make sure your happiness Rico
! I've certainly something similar
.. you two Tarafan each other
What is your first job being betrothed?
! Yup
! Ah, Kemeto-sama will meet Boualdak
! one moment please
What there are, Kajorzaka-san?
.. Lato, truth
, Do not tell me what I said after all
You will not tell us that you did not mean everything I said, it is true?
.. Kemeto-sama
For-what? P-aunt?
Why what?
I Ami! Are you sure about this matter?
.. As you can see, Kajorzaka-san
. I have come to Oanqrk
The reason I want you. Therefore strongly Kobna law
No No, this messes! You hate me, right?
.. Yes, I Ahtqrk, for this reason will take you to our family
. So I can Tazepk all that gutted
. I look forward to this, Arzogaoa Kemeto-san
! Now was Etemadi, also
! please wait
! I am against
! I strongly oppose Kemeto marriage and Rico
! Yup ! It seems this also opposes Kajorzaka
. It has already decided
! I will not let this
. If you have a bold, this Avoiding
! What do you do may kill me
! I will not let the eye askew like you owned Rico
! A-Wait! It's not so
! Rico will always be my little sister
! I do not understand you
- I will definitely stay - flatmate
--Rako, can you stop him
"100 Greatest idea of ​​marriage"
! The common folk magazines such amazing
For what do you read this?
! This is unfair, Arzogaoa
what are you doing ?
"زيجزي"
You said you do not want to let us, right?
At least I will meet you once from time to time, okay?
-! Flatmate - from speaking on
To meet you?
! I will kill for Sister knot
! Masumi-san, please stop
! Takemia
! I'm sorry ! What I said was a misunderstanding really
. Kemeto-sama, lift your head please
. It was my fault jump to conclusions
. My mother and I both can not be ashamed more
. Please, do not concern yourself
- Oh, um, I'm sorry even before the misunderstanding, Arzogaoa-san, I
. Please, Nadini Rico
... Er, Rico ... maybe I am very bold with you
! that's not true
... Well .. Nations
Hi ! What Tflah you both here and Hdkma?
For-nothing wrong with this, is not it?
! Meeting of the Club! We have a meeting of the Club
. There are few options for but to meet you again today the happiest yourself
.Ano, Kemeto-sama if really ran away from my house
Are you planning to take me to your home?
. Certainly
.. Maybe I will run away from home
Huh!?
After all this has happened! what are you talking about ?
. Â-Ica-sama, this is not your business
This is definitely my business thou from the cause of all this mess
! I am not the cause of all this
- will Tbakan - Haku
- ordinary member of the club from now on - of no avail! Completely useless feasibility
! Karen, Stop this
- if I did not close by
- was not one to take it, it is true - Hear whatever, just my
- e-this is not true - Return the underwear, Haku
Do not disappear at dusk Hani Larry
Kemeto where you are and what you are doing?
. Well, I'm not saying that this is a bad thing
But what will we do, Maaike-chan?
. I think we have to start withdrawing his tongue
. Oh Mikey-chan You are very silly
! I am really sorry
. Sicaen school after all this geeks may come from time to time
Ah, good day
. Good day
! Gates you
. I tend to wait for one death naturally
. But Madam once he catches it goes mad for a long time
How long are you talking about?
.Flanry ... almost five years
five years
. I wonder how long will stay where Gates
. Dear Mom and Dad
. Currently, the "Gates" popular in Sicaen
I thought I understood the ethics of all this world expanding
I thought so it's enough to follow what leads me to him daily
. But here I am here, I can not put a name to this
Feelings that can not be predicted, and the usefulness of the guide
The dividing line between the cheek mixing red, dark blue
And before I know about it, it made it hard to say inside or outside my heart
Do not disappear in the twilight, near to see what it all I
I'm sure that everything will be an opportunity to love
Bring your tears and your dreams, which are forced to hide your smile Well?
I will come to you days that you will Mhassoda everyone
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go for this
I love thee, O
I hope that my have won admiration followed the rest of the Alonimat and my projects in my blog Vergil-sub.blogspot.com ♥ Jana ♥
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
I am deeply fascinated by the commoners
I Odrsk every day
You did not pick up telepathically so far?
what are you ? cool ?
Oh, you understand, you hide Khgelk, huh?
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go
Here's my love of
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
! Gates