Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go for this
I love thee, O
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
I am deeply fascinated by the commoners
I Odrsk every day
You did not pick up telepathically so far?
what are you ? cool ?
Oh, you understand, you hide Khgelk, huh?
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go
Here's my love of
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
! True, finally we finished the construction for the field trip
. For this there Stzhabon all start from tomorrow
Building ? What kind of place where we will go to him!?
... we park so we set up to allow Misses
. To experience themselves in the vernacular culture
... it's a
Shynmw-Land
Land commoners
What is that ?
. Kajorzaka-Be we would like you to offer advice to students in Chinmoland
Huh? I ?
... since your arrival here
. At school has become the climate is more pleasant
... Reports say that there is no negative effects on students
. As we were worried
. After all, there is a boy nearby girls can be Ajtahedn
E. Is this true?
Although when we say "boy" we mean a pervert man who loves muscle
Who Tqsdenh b man loves oblique muscle!?
Am I wrong?
.. If you're a normal, safety Vlogel on INSAT
- the Edok anniversary of direct Siqt
! When my dream to be the biggest man muscles
"School Girls Sicaen"
... In case, you are faced with an opportunity to put your feelings in colloquial use best
. Please, it has proven abilities to the fullest
. Full reason of your birth, for this moment
! My life cheap
What kind of this place!? I can not really wait to see Chinmoland
Episode 6 notify out
... a-order
! Berger Tryuki Group, with Cola Zero to drink
. Rico-sama We can go now
. Flansra
! Okay
Hey, Ica, do you understand this?
! Lesson non-systematic is the main event
. For all you have done so far in the club commoner
. You can say that this is your killing
If you've made it as we practiced it would be okay, what is your goal!?
. T-electronic addresses exchange
. The face of the game
... Yes I know
Loosely
! Welcome to Chinmoland
. The park, built so that you can experience the vernacular life
... Ansate, from Vdilkn Mtawa yourselves in this wonderful time
.Alzy Stqdouna as factors
So what it seems!?
... the gate made it to boast, but they did not heed her
So what makes them so obsessed! ?
. This is really Chinmoland
. It Chinmoland
Designed from the front. We have a train station is amazing
! Masoha-sama, cohesive
! Finally we got to this dimension! You should not Tekhsary your strength
! Traffic signal
! Line Mshah
! This is the first metric that I see where one
! Flanqtah
. You have to raise your right of yours
! Oh, true
Allen Indulge yourself, too?
What was this?
. Distribution of fabrics known as happens in the outer train station
! No one goes through such a cloth
! It's a soft silk, and contain moisturizers to prevent skin irritation
It will not harm you. Therefore, no matter how many times used by the
! Listen to
. Well, Asmhoi me direct you to our first picturesque
. This is the most popular restaurant among the commoners
! Hi
! Oh
. In this restaurant, at first you offer your request at that counter
There ?
... There are lists at the counter
. Do you see them and you offer your application writer
Learned, after this we will sit down on the table, is not it?
. No, your place waitin
T-mean! You're there until you stay here prepares the food! ? Standing!?
. Yup
Wait, but ... there are several dozens of minutes and stops! ?
. Must be the most difficult times of the common folk are eating
For-what is this?
. Because you are carrying this restaurant food ended yourself
... This training
"It's called" self-service
Self-service ? We carry ourselves? This shock?
! What a wonderful is
. This completely independent
! Certainly ! It will be a tough lesson for us
. This makes me painfully aware, over the auctioneer who grew up with
! Commoners really amazers
! In this case, I am ready to wait for an hour or two until
! Yup ! We will wait with pleasure
. No, but no need to wait for all this
"This restaurant is the service" fast food
. General and its base is the speed
. Food equipped within a minute after ordering
Accurate !?
. They said twice
How can industry so fast!?
. I can not imagine this
Who are commoners exactly!?
! Well, they're ... commoners
. Yes thats right
. Well, again, please have made requests
! Go! that's it ! Taught you how to proffer demand, is not it?
! Berger Tryuki Group, with Cola Zero to drink
. Well, Aaidyha
M-Berger Tryuki Group, with Cola Zero to drink
! one more time
! ! Berger Group Tryuki
! What Tamutaih Akhreign idealism, Stand at the counter and say
! Berger Tryuki Group, with Cola Zero to drink
what are you afraid of !? , Arise, be gone
. It's NAIL
! I will go-BASIS
! They called on Rico-sama
! good luck
Hello to you, do you Sttnaulin food here?
Huh?
. Llano ... is not here .. Sakel food on the table
. Arzogaoa-sama, I'm sorry but ask that you choose to eat in the restaurant
. Or Stokhven meal wrappers and you leave
. Oh, I understand, I can take them to the tea party
. Food can be a picnic
. This would be great
. Your request, please
. It is impossible to say something
. So we stumble from the selection from the menu sometimes
. This generates a unique type of pressure
! Rico-sama, be strong
Come on ! This is, it's the perfect time, right?
. No benefit
. The most popular is the burger Tryuki group
... Kemeto-sama
. Decca Max is also a traditional food here, but it may be too much to you
. A-then, I'll have a pager Tryuki group
Very good, what do you want to drink?
Tea mixture looks good, is not it?
. Well, I will ask it
. Very good, please wait on the side of the counter
. Thank you very much, Kemeto-sama
. It Kemeto-sama for you
. Always here to support it
. this one please
Otrgbin group luck?
. No, not those, the game only
Huh?
... I mean
. Oh
. It is very interesting to consider him
. Well, all of us Flanokl
- This really is the time until you Ica
! It - it's very good
! What kind of meat! The moment you entered it, leachate flowed from it
! What a seasoning! What a grease owned! What a sweetness
. It's not as fat meat clenched regular beef
! But the original good meat flavor is still present
! Uh ! Finally, I learned what is the beef
! All meat land which ate so far was rubbery
- Kinsarh rubber! These Kalkekh carrying strongly meat
! Soft and fragrant smell mixed with the final fabric
! It's really the perfect grain of wheat fields of golden thin
! Flan covered gently like the sun, which encircle the earth
! Not blocked by their presence, but they elevate each other
! When Aodaan together they elevate to a completely different world
! Heavenly harmonies sweep my mouth
! Pythagoras ... Pythagoras
Pythagoras: mathematician what Baraf his relationship with Shaw Khkhkhkh
! Hi ! This material is not extreme
K-Kemeto-sama!?
Is there something?
. Definitely ... the taste of this dreaded sandwich
... But there is a simple and balanced flavors of bacon
. With the audit, you can get the maximum Decca
! And more than anything, there is something you need to provide the maximum
How it is supposed to cost the burgers?
! Millions of yen will not be enough for him
... Do not mock these Almax, who has Besnaath
! Vlakht out
! Kemeto-sama angry
. I'm not sure why, but it seems very vital
Haku-sama!?
Are you on your way to a room Kemeto-sama?
. UN-hmmm
... Unfortunately, Kemeto-sama and others Ihzawn Padres non-systematic
. They went on a trip to Chinmoland
. Kemeto-sama, from the depths of my heart I'm really happy to get this trip
! Happy to hear this
! Rico-sama they enjoy there a lot! Let us go and see
! Certainly
! So, I'll go with you
! I see
. I lost punch
.. Ica really good at this, so I thought it would be useful to have
. But I guess that the ladies Ihbn small woolen animals nice
. Look, take it simply and will come from this way
. Let's wait patiently
! sorry
... Kemeto-sama Do you mind that shows us, how we play
Hunting Game Doll!?
. Please help us
... Er, I do not ..
! I'll be fine, go
.. But
. I'll go and buy something to drink
. Well, there are those Soltqt, this viewed soon
. Go ahead
- give it to me - certainly
! U-Thank you very much, I will keep it for the rest of my life
. Well, now Aqali as I did
.. for .. h-Well, here I am
! Uh, well, Stay away from the bottom
Verse ? Huh? What have you done !?
. There is nothing wrong, you can Tsoba on those
. Click on the button length now
. here we are
! H-Well
.. Kemeto-sama
. Come on, View close we step back slowly
How is that ?
.. h-Well, .. k-big and strong ..
. We're almost there
! Uh, not yet
. No, all there
! Oh no, I want more
. Go ahead, here is
. thank you very much
Well, I apologize now ... huh?
! Kemeto-sama, trained me to do so too
! I also beg
! I can not feeling aground
. Kemeto-sama, please taught us how to do this
One I've picked up easily by a few, right?
Huh? Where went Ica?
Kemeto-sama? What is that ?
. Huh? It's a game dance with music
Do you want to try?
! Certainly
. You have seen? So
. So you are doing
Two can do it, do you want to try?
. Yup
. Oh, I'm not forced to gouge your shoes
! I did
! that's cool
. Yes, but all have to do everything
! everything ?
! I'm so sorry
! It is impossible to do everything
. Maybe Games very tough on us commoners
What are you doing!?
! So
! They focused on the instructions that appear on the screen
! ready ? Click! Under ! Click! Under
.. Keep your feet together the best of what you have
! The next difficult part, stay loose
! H-Well
! Aagafza
! After the ban ends! Abekayam together, beautifully and adherent
! Well, science
! So
! We have done
... I mean ... Lato
. Thank you very much, Ika-sama, you are very experienced in this
. A-I think this
! Leica-sama, please teach us how to play too
! I also please
! As you want
! Leica-sama, thank you very much
. The most important thing is the sense of rhythm need from
- Once you've Tatadon it - did it
.. Fletokd everyone that he can do, rest your bodies equipped
... Grande hazelnuts, almonds, vanilla and caramel extra
! Caramel sauce Rumba Balhuklath chip dignified Voamkun with extra quantity
! E-this stunning, Ica-sama
! See full confidence in this very comfortable
Do you think this!?
Commoners used this kind of incantation bring coffee for, right?
Nights rigor, that we can do Do you think too?
. Yes, Ahidin, this was the level of high demand
. Normal situation, he asked for a latte hot or cool Seiken okay
Rico-sama, what we demand!?
. I'm curious about the Voamkun
- Yes, what is the Vwamakon - Rico-sama?
.. It Vwamakon
What is the small hole here above?
Ah, Ica-sama, what do you do?
.. huh? Well, it's
Can you be the place drink it!?
. True, Racboni, I will prove to you
! too hot
Â-Ica-sama?
Are you okay, Laika-sama?
! Use these Go ahead
. There is nothing wrong
. Sorry, sorry
! Oh, the classic test of this catastrophic
. It is certainly a difficult one
.. Otto
Do you use all of you Hoatvkm portable?
. Yes, sometimes
. But in order to see each other every day, that he "sometimes" already
. Yup
So, you are not Trusselon each other often, huh?
. No, we hide it from others in the chapter
. For this, we are doing this little in our rooms before sleeping
What about you, Laika?
Huh?
. Clearly, I do not do it
! In this case, send me
! Yes offcourse ! Flanrsl you
Huh?
! Ica-sama, please send me too
Not quite that sent you?
! Certainly
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Translation of Vergil Vergil-sub.blogspot.com waited for the coming of our translation episodes
I thought I understood the ethics of all this world expanding
I thought so it's enough to follow what leads me to him daily
. But here I am here, I can not put a name to this
Feelings that can not be predicted, and the usefulness of the guide
The dividing line between the cheek mixing red, dark blue
And before I know about it, it made it hard to say inside or outside my heart
Do not disappear in the twilight, near to see what it all I
I'm sure that everything will be an opportunity to love
Bring your tears and your dreams, which are forced to hide your smile Well?
I will come to you days that you will Mhassoda everyone
What you are doing, Haku-sama?