Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go for this
I love thee, O
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
I am deeply fascinated by the commoners
I Odrsk every day
You did not pick up telepathically so far?
what are you ? cool ?
Oh, you understand, you hide Khgelk, huh?
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go
Here's my love of
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
! I want you to teach me all the stuff slang AZ
! Club commoner
! Accordingly, I hereby declare the establishment of the club commoner
. There may be some negligence on our part
. Rather, I want you to be activated
Huh? For what-Tvdilna about Arzogaoa Rico?
. We Amyin use the word "Atsuo" with our friends
. Easy to use for this slipped me
. It seems that ye are talking together in harmony
! My party plan to be the most popular girl in the classroom
! I am now quite strong
Episode 4 Incident Tea Party
Tea Party?
right Now ?
... Yes, if you wish
. This is not a very large order
. Just to be together for some time in my room
! Oh no, I did not mean anything when I said in my room
. That's just ... something we do all the time
. Therefore, there is no deep significance in my call
. Yeah, well, I think this is shameful
.. Maybe at other times
. Yes, for this is something we do all the time
- But Kemeto-sama, invite you today a special request
. M-Please, do not expose her Bala
. Oh Nations
What you said? Do you have any plans after this?
. No, nothing specific
.. In this case, please
. Well, I will accept your offer gentle
T-tarried What do you think yourself active?
. You have plans, right? With me
Aika-sama Was this not something you should not say for Kemeto-sama?
... A-Llano
! vvah
For-our club activities, is not it?
Huh?
Not less huh me Forgot my plan?
! No time you have to do a concert tea
What do you mean by "doing"?
So what you do, right?
. I do not do this, in addition to that your plans are not very urgent
M-What? I want to go to Arzogaoa Rico room for this class?
. For-no, not so
! In any case, I'm urgent Let us go from here, we do Boukttti off
. H-Well
! Sorry, Arzogaoa-sama I have prior arrangements with Atsuo
... festival
I am really sorry
. Please do not worry about this
. I hope to accomplish with your business Aika-sama without incident
.Thank you
! Wait
Kemeto-sama will not come today, is not it?
It is busy, not an opportunity for us in this
What made him busy exactly?
. In addition to the only one that seems to open with Kemeto-sama-sama is Laika
. I'm sure that Aika-sama was asking Kemeto-sama tips
Tips ?
. Yes, it is desperate because of the circumstances surrounding us
. For this reason, it is hoped to help him
. Kimio-sama arrived here since shortly
. And he distinguished man
. There is no one better than him to ask him Nashah
. Certainly
.. for-but I think that spend every day with him in the room Kemeto-sama
. Not very Malov
. One day, I wish to visit Kemeto-sama Room
. And arrived at the door
... but I heard the voice of that girl enjoy herself so much
. This made me think twice about entering
. Most of this recently she was left with him until late
Oh. Are you sure?
"Commoner club"
. Listen
. I want there to be some food in the common folk concert
. Some candy or something
Well, what about some cheap crackers, such as the "Aumialo"?
Oumialo?
It is found in places called shops
. Girls buy these sweets and eat in the classroom after school
! Oh, this sounds good, Flanvolh
Experts concert at the grassroots after school
! This will be the name of the party
It looks great, huh
! I know, it is true that it will be very interesting
. I wonder if everyone will be happy with this wish to be happy
. Thinking about this, from a recent change in their room
. Show callers together very well
-Traiqa pulling his arm, and how they talk - Llano, INSAT does not wish any one of you more tea?
... privacy away from us and the way Kemeto-sama
In the hunt Aika-sama, you could be a disturbing relationship between them?
.. Could it be and offers advice
.Klihama becomes more friendly
And become already Habib and Habiba?
. There is no doubt this day in his room, according to the two are
- e-Do you think it is right now ... they're so
! that is enough
Rico-sama
Huh? What speeches?
. Arzogaoa-san, I Kajorzaka
. I'm here
What happened ?
. I can not talk to you in this regard, Kemeto-sama
Is this by chance it comes to me?
! Nothing like this
! Â-sorry
. And then screamed at Kai-sama
. I left the room without the ability to say any other word
. This is the first time I
What do I do?
.. this is
! Important commoner
. welcome back
you are here ?
So how is Arzogaoa Rico?
Huh?
I went to her room is not it?
How do you know that?
! I became curious when I left for this Tbatk
. Too late
E-this does not really matter, is not it?
So how delightful it?
. It's very frustrating
I bet you're thinking of a way to help her, right?
How do you know this?
. You are the kind of men
So you thought about anything?
... Hmmm, well the easiest way would be to apply someone
. To calm things down.
. But in this case Valammer includes every chapter
. According to the case Arzogaoa-san
. I think we need an event or something like that
.He different would raise the morale Arzogaoa-san in a way it
"To give them the courage to say" in this case, things will succeed
! Which makes it related Bama
. Something you do not know anyone yet
.But appropriate to correct things as well
But what it can do all this?
There is something, is not it?
Huh?
! I said there is something, is not it? , Her perfect thing
- But you were the one who went
! Well, I do not think that there is no better than this idea
You sure about this matter?
I said it's good, is not it?
- Yes, you're a girl from hell, huh
! In fact, it's not good
. I do not want to end up causing a problem with
! I mean, I thought that this
... I want to be more popular girls in the classroom
. And to live the life of a school fun with others
! All this royal
. But I can not share the chapter so
I can not let Arzogaoa Rico in the wind, is not it?
. And I hate to give up more about it after all this thinking about it
You know what I mean, right?
. You are really a girl from hell
Do you want me to prepare some snacks for you?
! AUO
! Foolish
! You are not really a girl from hell
. Everyone thanks assemble together
"We are going to" experts concert at the grassroots after school
. This is something that girls do commoners often after school
. And I want you experience it also
Hello, Ojibwe
Could this be ... Rico-sama?
E-Are you sure that her voice is similar to another voice and by?
What do you mean by Ojibwe?
Oh, what are you talking about!?
! All of you Aoenbauna .. As you know
. Atrko for this Arzogaoa-san, it's without any defect in its
... Protect
. Llano, today asked Arzogaoa-san to wear slang Kfattah
"The girl who wears this uniform so-called" Jarraud
Sweep?
Her hair looks like from another country, how has it?
! Very long eyelashes
! Her lips look very moist and very attractive
! Oh mobile phone
Rico-sama What you are doing?
. O INSAT, look Bdakh Taulatkm
" new message"
! Oh
! They sent us all
. Please click on this button here
" I'm sorry "
.Aatha INSAT, I'm very sorry to make you Tqlqon
... Oh no
! Do not put your head please Taathamqa
. Thank you very much, but
. Kai-sama I am very sorry about the terrible thing that I said that day
Rico-sama, what are you talking about?
! I was ... I was totally my fault because I was a very difficult
.Kaa-sama did anything wrong Valuation, the whole error is located on the
! No, this is not true
! Well, we express what we did pictures and pick up my predecessor together image
Tuberculosis?
.Anzera to my phone
T-Rico-sama
. I took a picture
! Oh
. Phone even able to take pictures
. And they are able to send them through text messages
. Commoners take pictures of themselves with their friends so
. And then send them to each other
we are friends, are not we ?
! Yes Yes
! Nights my happiness
. Ali Hoarding this for the rest of my life
! Bakatkm, please come with me and took my predecessor, too
! Rico-sama - please Take one with me also
Let me also -and I am also
.Kemeto-sama Thank you very much
. Will not be able to provide enough gratitude for today
. Said to your ability to do
... Also, Kemeto-sama, the fact that you thought about this
. A great gathering for me makes me very happy
... Kemeto-sama, I
! Arzogaoa-san
. The truth is that the idea of ​​today is not me
. Laika is one of them thought
. It supposed to be a secret, but it is safe to tell you this Arzogaoa-san
... Atsuo wanted to be bad Tsadegk
. The rest of the girls in the classroom, Arzogaoa-san
. It is attended by all this for the vernacular concert
! But abandoned you, Arzogaoa-san
. Atsuo It's really a girl from hell
. For this I thought of doing her thing
- In any case, Arzogaoa-san if you could help me
What is the matter ?
Arsvjava-years - he
I hate you
Huh?
! I see you ... despicable
! I heard everything from Kemeto-sama
everything ?
! everything
! you fool
Huh?
What is this story? I heard everything, right?
So you have to be grateful to me, is not it?
! Arzogaoa-san
What ? what are you doing !?
I said what your problem?
! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid
... e-hai
! Kemeto! help my
! Why not do you use the words of respect
Kemeto-sama, what Tnadea simply Laika?
. You are ! If you come to for advice in the first place
! Encountered flash of this was to get
Huh?
But I thought about the surrender and escape, what happened in this regard?
It's something very small
Very small thing
! you did not understand me ! You do not know how I feel
! I can tell the ideals
Do you have any idea of ​​the extent of the concern Qlgueth you?
! I was very disturbed by the presence of something in a failed partial
! I have chosen that someone tries to say things unwanted
. I did not ask you to never, because you can do anything
! Always what you see from the bottom of your nose for all
!I do not do that
! You have to try to get more consideration from everyone
I was thinking about you right? I let you get on my idea, is not it?
! I did not ask you to never
! You hate your courage
-I hate you ! I hate you ! I hate you ! -I hate you ! I hate you !
! And aaah, Ofajadhm
! Both Fajdehma, with the other Contracting
. ! The softness of their muscles have an impact on the other
! Which led to the emergence of a great engineering
! T-stopped, you both
-! Shut up -! Shut up
-! Kimio - Kemeto-sama
. It's my fault
! P-what are you talking, this is my fault
. No, it's my fault
- he is right in this regard - he is right in this regard
! Hey, do not tell what I'm trying to say
! You stop talking and restore what I am saying
. Think of something
. A good, lady commoners Stsubhan in the twinkling of an eye
. You do not loveable Minesweeper from the foundation
. Especially in the way you speak
. I used to be like them, according to the word "Dcio wa" and everything
Oh really ?
. But when I was in fourth grade and faced a terrible fever and collapse
. When I woke up, I started talking so
Huh? how did this happen ?
. I do not know, maybe my memories at that time had gone
. And something happened to me instead
... Hmm
. In addition to all this good will not be good with it
. I'm fine way things are going, your games and manga fun
- In addition to that I alone with you
-You very healthy, huh? - Nothing dirty in that
Oh, do you come to visit?
Ummm
. I'm not here because I want to visit
So what you are doing here?
. I do not have to answer that
... Kemeto
Order entry? I mean for the club commoner?
. Ummm
. Kemeto-sama
. Allow me to enter the club commoner, also
Huh?
Wait, what you all want to join?
. H-Well, that must answer, this is a future for
. Because I want to be with you, Kemeto
. I do not want to be with you, but because of unavoidable circumstances
. I think it's better to join
... You are also, in other words you will all want to join, well
! Wait a moment
! I oppose! I oppose this, I understand?
! Especially is, it's the last one I want to see them join
... Do not say it, to be completely honest
Arzogaoa-san is trying to reach a solution with you, true, Arzogaoa-san?
If not Thabay this, you can leave, right?
I'm wrong
... and something else, Kemeto-sama
! A-order?
. Nadini b t-Rico start from now please
. You can enjoy your tea with the rest of Bhflat chapter
And work with them, is not it?
. I'll be definitely nice with the rest of my friends in the season and I'm in the club
This is normal and by, is not it?
A-you hate me, is not it?
. Oh, Leica-sama did not hate anyone in my life
. Leica-sama, I prefer to love each other to be in friendly conditions
. Be my guest director from here
! No, you will come out of
Since when these both are very Dodtan?
! Haku
! B-meaningless ... How .. How all of this, which is meaningless to him
What Tltkotain a picture of this?
-Haa - I have no desire whatsoever to be in your girlfriend
! neither do I
! Stop this you all
For what these big scissors?
What do you plan a piece, what began very Tguetrbin from the bottom halves?
! These videos for men muscle is the best
! If possible, I wish I could get a sandwich between these Mvtolen muscular men
, Excuse me to doubt your
... Kajorzaka-sama You are really a unique man
Who may be sexually raised from the muscles of another man, huh?
... Kemetom-sama
. Perverted
. It's not so
! Do not look to so
"In the next episode"
When they did not Tqlaa Almriol?
! I am very envious, I want to kill him
Should I took off my clothes, too?
I thought I understood the ethics of all this world expanding
I thought so it's enough to follow what leads me to him daily
. But here I am here, I can not put a name to this
Feelings that can not be predicted, and the usefulness of the guide
The dividing line between the cheek mixing red, dark blue
And before I know about it, it made it hard to say inside or outside my heart
Do not disappear in the twilight, near to see what it all I
I'm sure that everything will be an opportunity to love
Bring your tears and your dreams, which are forced to hide your smile Well?
I will come to you days that you will Mhassoda everyone
! Whatever only get out of this obscenity from here
! I love the owners of muscular men and girls who Abdn in elementary school
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Translation of Vergil Vergil-sub.blogspot.com waited for the coming of our translation episodes
According to friends