Episode 11 Is this not the sky which was seen Kemeto-sama?
.. Kemeto-sama
what is wrong with you ?
.. we have carried us chalk, this
Are you daily rotating day?
! No, I'm doing this on my responsibility
. So make teachers feel comfortable when our education
And what brought you here, Kemeto-sama?
. I forgot Mqmutai
. Ah, this is a habit
H-really?
. Kemeto-sama, you're very careful
Do you think this?
. Yes, I think
. Very beautiful
. Yup
Pure air is definitely here, huh?
Kemeto-sama, is the sky that you look at it other than this?
. I do not think the sky in the cities in this purity
. This is something, I would like to see him
M-What there are, Kemeto-sama?
.. right, lashy’
. Let me close the curtain
. But, I think it is not possible for me to see the city skyline
. If there was anything, say, according to
. If there was anything I can do, it will help my
you will do ?
A-Yes, what? Is there anything?
... So
. do not be shy
In this case, Kemeto-sama, do you still lag far behind the separation of flowers?
. Huh? Oh flower arrangement, quite honestly I'm an idiot in this
,,, even if you wish I was not too bold
... I will not mind to teach you what I know
... This
. both of us
. Yes, this would be a great help
Does this mean?
Both of us only?
What about tomorrow Saturday or Sunday, the day after tomorrow?
. Any one of them is good
. A-ear Kemeto-sama, this date
. Yup
Also, Can I ask something else?
What is the ?
. I want you to call me by my first name Kalochriat
. Please Nadini, Rico
But ... huh, Arzogaoa-san this will be outside of your status
please
. I'll think this is definitely
Well, what we do today in the club commoner?
Arzogaoa-san Is there something you want to do?
. Kemeto-sama, remember what it promised please
.. huh? Uh, it is true
Which promise ?
This is the secret, true, Kemeto-sama?
Head ?
What do you mean, "the Secret"?
! Yup ! Tell us
. I mean, it is not as if I really want to know
... With this as a member of associates dedicated to the club
. I want us to share less information, this is what it is all
. In war, information is a crucial element determines victory or loss
. It seems to be a sword put pressure on my neck here
This is the secret between us we are only two, true, Kemeto-sama?
! Hey you, tell us what is
. Please stopped violence
Yup ?
. sorry
Kerio?
.. Rico-sama
What speeches?
. Hoku-sama and Masumi-sama here
my mother and my brother ?
. They Antzernak the Director of the Office
This sudden, Kerio Have you heard anything?
. No
. I see
. Well, all excuse me please
. Kajorzaka-sama, you are required to join it
I ?
! I strongly oppose this
. Quieter, Masumi
. Please forgive me but I brought Rico-sama-sama and Kajorzaka
. Come in
. Mom, I've been a long time
. I am very grateful that you came to see me
I am grateful as well. Are you okay?
. Yes, everyone is very agree with me
. Sure, it's good to hear this
... You are
A-order?
what's your name ?
. K-Kajorzaka Kemeto
. I see
. I am pleased to see myself from any kind of people is the colloquial sample
Are you sure about this matter? The boy to allow your stay in Sicaen
What if you got anything for Rico?
. لا داعي للقلق
ريكو هل انت بخير ؟ لم يصبك اي شيء اليس كذلك ؟
. لا ، انا أعامل بلطف شديد ، أخي
هذه الأعين تقول
أختي هى ألطف فتاة في العالم
! لقد قالها
! هاي ، حافظ على المسافة
ابقى بعيداً عن ريكو ايها العامي
اخي ! ماذا تعني بقولك هذا ؟
! من فضلك اعتذر لـ كيميتو-ساما
... ايه ، لكن
! حتى تعتذر له اخي ، فلن اتحدث معك
! ر-ريكو
. من فضلك لا تقلق ، ماسومي-ساما
. من غير الممكن له ان يؤذي ريكو-ساما او الاخريات
كيف يمكنك قول شيء كهذا ؟
.. كاجورزاكا-ساما خصيصاً هو نوع من الرجال
. الذى يتعرّف على الإثارة الجنسية فقط من الرجال اصحاب العضلات الكاملة
أليس هذا صحيحاً ؟
اخي ، لديك جسد لياقي ، اليس كذلك ؟
! لـ-لا ، هذا بحد ذاته مشكلة
! وجود هذا المنحرف على مقربة ، سيضر في تعليم ريكو
! ايتها الرئيسة ! انا مُصر
... ماسومي
ألا ترى بأنك تضع الجميع خارجاً ؟
. اجلس
... ريكو
أجل ؟
. تم الإنتهاء من الحديث عن زواجك
هاه ؟
. ساتوشي-ساما من عائلة كونوي
... We will pay our respect after tomorrow on Sunday
. This statin home with me now
. Remember the main family, Kenshi-sama Meeting
And his wife from the offer at the end of last year, right?
... I received a request to marry immediately after that
. The talk has continued between the families
... like us, Conwy family is the legitimacy of the three adult family Arstqatih
. And supposed to be Satoshi-sama graduated with honors from the Higher Studies Standeov College of Business Administration
. This is very good
... A-Mom
What's wrong, Rico?
, Kajorzaka-sama
. I am very pleased that you were able to get my respect today
. Long time ago, this school was a place to look for brides
... those parents who have sons
. Visit the school during her work as spectators
. When they find students consider him well
. Understanding Itqrbun of his family to talk about marriage
. Even finished, a student leaves until graduation
. All this in order to marry or at least until we prepare him
What speeches?
Is this a normal thing?
.. I descended a bit these days
. But for the family Arzogaoa it is very possible
Than you are frustrated?
Not quite this you guys?
.... I do not think this is true
when ?
... discussion without considering the opinion of the girl
Suddenly they show they say we finished the day after tomorrow we will leave now
While ignoring all her wishes, this can not be true, is not it?
.. Okay
.. When you put it so
... So you guys if you were in the store Arzogaoa-san
Will you continue with this and Ttjozon?
... I'm not quite sure, but
Ah, do you think about cutting engagement Rico-sama by accident?
Huh?
... It's not about cutting her engagement
. I just think that Arzogaoa-san opposition to this
How can you be sure?
. I do not know, but these are my feelings by
Well, Kemeto What do you do?
who is this ?
Brother Arzogaoa-san?
! Do it
! I'll give you my email! Hurl
Well-h ..
What phone do not have the type of Gelabulsaaz?
Is this something worth anger?
. Masumi, we will leave
. H-Well
! You are useless
Huh? What happened, according to?
Kemeto What about the club commoner?
Huh?
. What we will do today, I decided now
. I do not know why ask me
. Arzogaoa-san is always decide
. Oh, yes, Rico decides to always
Modern Literature
. Perhaps to go and talk to Rico
For-not as if I or destabilize them sad or anything like that, okay?
As you know ... the fall of the club commoner
! Without anything, it is annoying
. You are right in this regard
. I'll call her at night
Arzogaoa is not in Seiken, how you plan to talk to them?
Ah, Ricoh phone at school and by, huh?
. I've removed the lock, now it's normal phones
! Thank you, Haku
Incoming call
Hi ?
I can question related?
. As I am, Ica
Ica-sama?
I heard from Kemeto
. I think that you can not do anything Failtk have decided
What he said Kemeto-sama?
. Ignore the desire of the girl is not the right thing
And .. ?
. This is the summary
I see
So what would you do?
. You must become like my mother
. Ornamental and mental agriculture we have obtained in Seiken for this purpose from the beginning
. Just like my mother and my grandmother and the rest of the other ancestors
... vlhza
Vmphaaudhat marriage This is also the same, right?
. Yup
, Arzogaoa family respects the traditions
. As long as we do this, we preserve this until such time
. Yup
This is the first time we talk over the phone, Ica-sama
Who said that?
. We made our fair share of the fight
. All this seems long ago now
. I know it seems old, but I enjoyed it
... I'll think to stop when Seiken to say hello sometimes, this
! Stop
If I left it with me it will share in the coming sports hall or in the next picnic?
! Without you here, there is no one here
! I do not want that ! For this reason I want you to be here
! Soardha! Soard certainly Khtopetk
... I want to
. I do not want to get out of school
. I do not want to leave school
. I want to be there with Karen-sama-sama and Haku with you and Ica-sama
. I do not know what I do
. There is nothing wrong we will order what
We will something, okay?
What speeches?
.. Listen ... UN, Lato
Is it about Arzogaoa-san?
! what is it ? Colaha
! She said she did not want to go out
Huh?
, Rico said she did not want to get out
. And did not want to leave the place
.. or Karen or Haku and I
. I do not want to leave Kemeto-sama
! Or you, too
... Oh
. For this we are going to do something I said what
. I do not know what we have to do
. After that we got this dimension, Vlace we can do only go here direct appeal
.. Karen, Haku
Direct appeal? but how ?
. Brother Arzogaoa-san was trying to consult with us
.. he certainly has his contract with his sister
. I think he was opposed to her engagement
... if we got his e-mail at that time
. There is nothing wrong
. I already have it
! Fantastic Haku
Soqlk to my car and take you where I want you to cut off the engagement
He wants us to cut off this engagement?
. It seems I'm not ready last option I will use this
! Stop
Here you have the courage? The engagement between the Conwy cut off all family and Arzogaoa?
! That's right
! What a terrible thing I thought about doing
, This is absolutely true
... this is
! Important commoner
. Well, we're almost at the car park
Where do you think you are going?
.. There is no doubt that you are here to exercise really tonight
To try to explain the joints of the muscles in women, is not it?
! Certainly not as well as
So what exactly?
. It Arzogaoa-san
It's the club's activities commoner?
. If they were, Vlace worries me
Perhaps the request of something?
Huh?
. Please tell me why you have found
. Because it is a member of the club commoner
Is this the reason?
. From this road
. Enter
"In the next episode"
What is that ?
. Sorry to make you waiting for
! Stay away from the road
! Because you are one of our dear friends
I thought I understood the ethics of all this world expanding
I thought so it's enough to follow what leads me to him daily
. But here I am here, I can not put a name to this
Feelings that can not be predicted, and the usefulness of the guide
The dividing line between the cheek mixing red, dark blue
And before I know about it, it made it hard to say inside or outside my heart
Do not disappear in the twilight, near to see what it all I
I'm sure that everything will be an opportunity to love
Bring your tears and your dreams, which are forced to hide your smile Well?
I will come to you days that you will Mhassoda everyone
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Translation of Vergil Vergil-sub.blogspot.com waited for the coming of our translation episodes
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go for this
I love thee, O
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
I am deeply fascinated by the commoners
I Odrsk every day
You did not pick up telepathically so far?
what are you ? cool ?
Oh, you understand, you hide Khgelk, huh?
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go
Here's my love of
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
! The final technical art of sword Karen
! Come to my house
Although I am lacking experience please Aqublna Forever
. Please Aqublna forever