. This lab Cedoma Haku-sama, which Stmthleenha from today
. H-Well
... Caring for Haku-sama has special rules away from the rest of the INSAT
. For this I hope you accustom yourself on this matter
What can these rules be?
. Haku-sama can not dressed herself
Huh?
. This is all of the functions of the maid
. H-Well
. Plus they choose their meals every day of the week
. And these meals will never eat
. For this, please be careful of this
. Science
. So let's go now to see Haku-sama
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go for this
I love thee, O
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
I am deeply fascinated by the commoners
I Odrsk every day
You did not pick up telepathically so far?
what are you ? cool ?
Oh, you understand, you hide Khgelk, huh?
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go
Here's my love of
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
. I wish I never wake up
Episode 3 It was paradise parks
How are doing?
Do you used to life here?
. No, I still could not really satisfaction
"My mom and you have a new message"
"From: to my mother: I am Topic: How life there?"
"We've got a hot spring"
Hot spring? What is the meaning of this ?
Did not you explain this? As it gets
... to thank you for accepting to be the general sample
. Your home has got major renovations
. Hmamkm has become a hot Kalenbua natural
. And all your family members are very happy
I have they sold me versus hot spring?
... In any event, to ensure that you worry about your family
. You have to send them a text message
"Wall to wall muscles here, so much fun"
Delete Save Cancel
Deleted
When you come to without any validity!?
If allowed, the master of Kajorzaka
... A-Er-oh
. No, you tell him please
! He puts his hand on the handle
! A-I can not even use the bathroom safely
Terrible news on the hot spring, I have perished accustomed to life here and entertained myself
Is it a student here?
! Young Miss write on the walls
. Perhaps to talk to her
Wah Wait What you are doing!?
Hey, put this to what you Tkhalaan your clothes?
I read first. I have Hailin and Ricky and Verlana of Mokhtaratne
You reader really greedy
... This was soon, if they saw me so
. I'll be mentally ill and a simple and clear
. Hurry and put on a cold'll get
. They have gone
what !?
Are you rip from my clothes?
No! You are of your own uprooted, do not remember!?
When I had to take off my clothes!?
! I do not know
But you can not wear now, okay?
. I can not obey this order
why not ?
. I can not Pair
Huh?
Oh really ?
You can not link buttons as well, correct?
. This is harder than I thought
. Well, we finished
. I Cedoma Haku
. A-Oh, well, I Kajorzaka Kemeto
Kemeto?
. I have seen me in the orientation Commoner meeting a few days ago
. I was in my lab over the previous two days
Your laboratory?
This is the sound as alert Seems low blood sugar
. Say you're hungry and by
What I will do with you!?
What is that ?
. Ramen had to, that we have mourned our food Amyin
But it is not for Ramen and received by, he recipe original food
"Ramen Hot Pepper oil cooler"
. I can not eat it
Huh? Also food? Well, I have no choice
. Come on, some holistic
. it is good
. What do you know? You can eat yourself
What do you think ?
. I can eat
. Well, soon you will come back to your bedroom
- I will pursue with you there
. You can not sleep here, too
-Hia, Awake
! AUO ...! Do not suddenly Retrace
Huh? You are you write
As I said, what Tqlaan your clothes!?
.. I am here you commoner for the activities of the club today
Huh? what is wrong with you ?
! E-this is not as it seems! Do not misbehave understanding
! None of you think it has happened
! Dear deviant
Listen, you understand how to wear your clothes yourself, okay?
. Hmmm? It this way, right? let's go
Kemeto, you too?
I see your house, right?
. Yup
. There
Huh?
And I walked with Hakko-toxic to the house, right?
... Thank you very much, well then
Huh? digital camera ?
. Yes, to record what has Haku-sama wrote on that statue
. We will go to the scene to take a picture
Huh? What do you mean ?
. Well, let's see
Haku-sama is involved globally in the fields of mathematics, industry and others
... So far, the famous business around the world
. I have written conclusions Haku-sama
Huh? just awesome
. This building was built from the financing that Rbanh inventions Haku-sama
. Now, Haku-sama come time eating time
. Oh, but I already feed it
Is there something wrong?
... for-not
Haku-sama, do you have already eaten?
Have I done something wrong?
No, no! By the way what was it?
! Ramen, Ramen lhzy ddth ×
... you are kidding
Llano ..
! nothing ! Thank you for Aatnaik b Haku-sama so much
. See you later, Haku
what is wrong with you ?
. stay here
Are you fine ?
. There is nothing wrong, in order, I also
when ?
. I'm not sure
... Llano
! For-nothing wrong! I'm fine, please continued
. Come and Zurina again
Okay ?
. I'll do
. Yes, see you later
. Sozork again
Haku-sama did this?
! Really surprised, for it is our Haku-sama
! Which if left can not put her underwear on their own
! Which does not have any interest at all the Academy
... I grabbed his shirt and said
"stay here"
! No way
! Yes
- This is not according to, and
! I've eaten before they come here
! No way
But Haku-sama eat what regularly every day of the week right?
"Today is Wednesday for this is the day," Skoppelas any neighbors
What brought this strange coincidence Al tends!?
! Bring this! Alramen commoner
Were there any exceptions previously?
! No, never
It did not fall in love, is not it?
. No, it's Haku-sama
. But Haku-sama girl and put it aside their appearance in the fourteenth
We will not be able to keep them Aionna more, huh
. Kemeto-sama today we have a row flower arrangement, as you know
. I wonder that you are able to arrange flowers
. Kemeto-sama to meet you will be fine
... In addition to that if there was anything Vsosaadk
. I beg and asked me relieved at any time
. OK I will
. Yes, Forever
Huh?
Verse ?
what is happening !?
! It has a sword on its side
! an insect! an insect! an insect! an insect
! an insect! an insect! an insect
... I was scared so much
Huh?
! Imaginal, commoner has called for the insect and tried to cut
! Karen-sama really miss enormous
--Hah? Not so it's not, it's simply
! E-this is true
! O wretched insect, Soqtek now here
! Taatcyr with them
! O pond scum
! The pond is not an insect
! A-Hist
In any case, who you are?
! My name is Karen and Genro Sotrg land, O poor worm
! Kemeto-sama, watch
! Run them
! Aunmaro flourished, the insect is food
! The art of sword Karen cutter! the decision
Who said that you can avoid them?
! Do not be rude
! the decision
! Dear small pond light movement! A-I mean, the insect
I Stnadana b pond scum, is not it?
! not like that
Well, how do you like!?
: The art of sword Karen cutter, the number of Whirlwind 58
! Excessive
! Do not look to us, O commoner asshole
! Uh, not again, Kemeto-sama sees Bmaita again
. Do not tell me that this is the result of that technique shortly before
! For what-you
! How dare you be this chutzpah
. No, this was you
! Dear boy! Miserable! Dear boy vulgar
! Take your time! Stguetlina! Really Stguetlina
! Damn, at this point all you can do is stop it by force
! Sonhik
! Behold, I am coming
... it's a
. Khaddiqh Committees
! Of
Are you fine ?
... How strong! Do you say you are from the commoners!?
Huh?
! jbny
. Oh, I say that I am in the latter in the weak
What are you ?
Boycotted Karen, who invented unavailing against weaker commoners!?
You Taatalim yourself, this stunning
. In fact, I'm not really the weakest
! Do not accept this! I want to re-fencing
one more time
! Soqtek and my name, which was re-Ttalkh
Huh! A-Wait a minute
! Behold, I am coming
. Impossible, I did not see the common man even attack
. Huh? Most likely this is because you have done previously
And you weaker!?
"... terrible nights Fezaatkm Dear people" Amyin
! I told you I did not do anything that I've done for yourself
... I did this for myself!?
. Right
I understand ..
Do you understand now?
! This is frustrating, you're in a completely different level
! No! No! No
. Okay
. I've overtaken, I admit you as sir
What kind of monster callee you?
! But remember this! At the moment, which will become the weakest me where I'll take your life
What is the worst! Tsthinin Bsiedk! Dragon in the world of demons
. But even then, you can I use what suits you best
. I heard that he had made Karen servant by force
! Commoners do not really believe
! Here it is
Hmm? what is this !?
! My party's plan to become the most popular girl in the classroom
... So this lousy person like me to call
! Can invite everyone without difficulty! I am now quite strong
! What ? Do not look too happy
. nothing
Oh, then what do you think of my plan?
. Not a bad idea, but I think it's going to be tough
. Because you'll need a lot of mobile phones
. You can not provide this
! So do something in this matter
! Easy for you to say this
. It does not seem there is no way here to get setups Han
. This is possible
Oh, true, do you have any Haku agreements with the development of smart phones?
And I said that there is a group of such samples in your laboratory?
. Here you are, you're lucky
... this is very good
But when you sit so?
. Nothing I can do, it does not move
! You can certainly do something despite the appearance they are in middle school
! What you do is not true
. middle School ! Here again you exaggerate
Come on, Llano ... Haku-sama let us go and sit down on the pillow, okay?
What do Ottaghdan yourself so!?
! I do not put myself
. Forgive me on this entry
What do you need?
- As I said earlier
! Kujurzaka! What is the meaning of this small girl
! Not completely meaningless, yes, absolutely no sense, no sense, no sense never
! This is really meaningless
So, when I came here?
. As I said earlier, I come to you now
I will keep it up beside you as much as possible and
. At the moment I feel I am able to've beaten, I'll kill you
Yes, this is the main goal, but not Tguetlina
! (B) I am having sent that thing which is incredible in my face as I did
! I did not draw anything
! A-Protect
Are you here ?
! I was here all the time
Are not nice with everyone, but I am?
Tsun-Boers, has a healthy persecution complex, is not it?
! I'm not Tsun-Boers
Our club activities ..
Huh?
This time our club activities, right?
... Yup
.. So ... Let the two of these Tagadran
Where in injury Gluing together?
! No
What do you love him with this?
-- What ? Way there and sit
! you idiot
What is that ?
! This brought by her maid
. Gelathm Ahoudrohm here
when did this happen ?
! At the moment, you can not connect to online services or slide
Do I have to make them able to this!?
No, Can you make these phones to communicate with each other and by?
. I can
. Ica, take that Tredenh
. Huh, oh, well
... u-thank you very much
what about that ?
. I am not interested in these games
No, huh?
! Hey, take a picture of me
... Well, Well, here's
! Amazing, what a cute, I'm sure I Zarifa
Haku, Otrgbin that you take one too?
. I want one with you, Kemeto
! Huh? A-then I'll do
! No room for the three of us
! If we did this, Fsnflha
! Wah, you do not pay a very Tguetrbin
! A-O deviant
! So try to avoid me
! Hey, say this Haku as well as
No, e-hai, Haku Do you sit on my feet again?
! This is the right place for these conditions
--Mn impossible that we can all of us, uh learned, let us make Karen
--of the
.. Let me be with you, too
. Okay
! Let us take one for all of us
! Wah! Observe your arms, dear pervert
! not me
! E-hai, you're sitting on my feet
Huh? I ?
! Not you
I thought I understood the ethics of all this world expanding
I thought so it's enough to follow what leads me to him daily
. But here I am here, I can not put a name to this
Feelings that can not be predicted, and the usefulness of the guide
The dividing line between the cheek mixing red, dark blue
And before I know about it, it made it hard to say inside or outside my heart
Do not disappear in the twilight, near to see what it all I
I'm sure that everything will be an opportunity to love
Bring your tears and your dreams, which are forced to hide your smile Well?
I will come to you days that you will Mhassoda everyone
. Well, Good evening
. Yes, Good evening
I got a new message Kemeto
Terrible news on the hot spring, I have perished accustomed to life here and entertained myself
"In the next episode"
Model entering the club?
Since when you are very approachable?
! Â-sorry
You forgot my plans?
! I can not finish the same way
. I wonder that the secret of all this
Tea Party event
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Translation of Vergil Vergil-sub.blogspot.com waited for the coming of our translation episodes
! you idiot