. Please request
! Than you are afraid, go
. It is as a screw
! I'm so sorry
! It is impossible to do everything
What do you do !?
! So
! We have done
! Ica-sama, please Teach me to play, too
! I also, please
! As you want
Do you all use cell phones?
. Yes, sometimes
What about you, Laika?
. Clearly, the Aoflha
! In this case, send me
! Yes offcourse ! Let me send you
Huh?
Super Market
Episode 7 Altson pure Madenha
! I tell you that this is not bad, it's design
! It is part of fashion
I understand ..
. Ica-sama, you really know about the vernacular culture
... Yes, Well
Ica-sama, what kind of clothes?
Hmm? What ? What ?
. On average they play, it will be fine
. Maybe I have to leave intact
. this is good
. Sales employee will this for you
! For-not as it seems
! For-not at all interesting to me in something meaningless
.Ugoda here just a coincidence so
! Often, you will never see me in a place like this
Yup ! Where is the evidence on which I stand here I am, is I?
So, it is I?
. I liked this, right? There is nothing wrong in his experience
!... why you
. Do not be deceived by yourself
Did you forget what happened before, you're useless in me from the forces you've beaten?
. If you want to eliminate you managed a flash of lightning
. Oh, this is fun somewhat
.Now, to make them wearing clothes that you love
-- it's a command ! Aqlaa your clothes and
! A-Olpsona yourself! Continued until saturation and Use me
.. No, no
This is what you love, right?
- A-Listen, I really
! Artdehm, this is
I am done ?
. No benefit
Huh?
. This stain total shame
. You are very nice, as you know, I think you'll be fine
! M-What did I say, in any case, I do not like to be prominent
! This is the final humiliation
. Avthia, this is
! M-how villainy emanating from you
! Looks great on you, Karen-san, I have succeeded
! Women's things like this
No, this will not work can not be too small?
... good hips and everything, and I know Banhnaiadtha from her waist to the bottom
... But the rush of the way these clothes inside Fajdaha
. It's not very Alanciaba--, graceful
... This soft bulges Milkiness leak skin
! K slice pork chain tied, No No Mr Vianman
. Comparable chip pork is considered a lack of respect for Fajdaha
! No, it's right as "Aevrdasnt Avalon", which seeks to Alofajad beloved
Aevrdasnt Avalon: Legend of the King chose is the place where King Arthur was transported after his death
! King Arthur! King Arthur
. A-Laugh if you want, I have always been aware of some way about them
- My legs is graceful marking
! They are not Sameentan they also must be
! They are great ways
! For this Karen, I do not want you to analyze yourself so
.. After all I love them, even if you stop all the world against me
! I will continue to say that I love
Huh?
! Please, Artdehm from now on and let me see you doing this
! I want to see you wearing this outfit again and again
.. at least you ..
... and-Cdetni
! I see that respond to this
! Ah, I received a message
! Okay
. Ward Ali that this
... Oh, but I was already in the middle of pink on Assaggi-san
. The completion of the first
You are sure that Instant fun, huh?
. Yes, I think this
. I know that I and put you out, this trip
Huh?
. I mean, that you and I share the same Alrvh
. No, nothing wrong
. I mean, I formed friends now
. And strange to have two do not love each other together Micharcan
. It would be comfortable for both of us when this ends
. A-Yes, I certainly hate after all
Huh? Than you are angry?
. I am not angry
... Listen, Arzogaoa Rico
What is there?
. This is the message I am sending all now
. Check with them so make sure that it is fine
You have to ask from Kimto-sama this request, is not it?
. But this is something I want to make sure of it as you can see
. This is really an important message
. It has a reason to avoid all yet
What do you want me to read?
You are the most popular girl in the classroom, right?
. Hate to admit this, Loken this is not for nothing
. I think you always know how others feel and what is the right that we have to do
... Sometimes I think about little ways you say things
. And the way you attract things together really wonderful
For this reason I want you to check them probably do not love me
! But you are the only person who I asked him this, please
. Okay
! Oh really ? Horrible
. It's a long
. I used to write letters
! It was not complicated
. I continued to read and read, but the primary goal has not become clear never
. Long apology at the beginning is not important
. In general, all these words to say words Kemeto-sama I can say that
. heavy
A-Do you think this!?
. Yes, Adjalleha more intensive and informal
... For example, leave the this part, so
K-How is this?
. "Listen, I have something important to say
There is a reason to avoid you so far
I have a tendency to say in all frankness what I think, Do you know this?
Because of this, my friends were hurt in the past
Because for this avoided talking with others
I am afraid to be repeated this again
I really wanted to become a friend Mekn
Sorry for all of this from now on, be my friends, okay?
- Tancubashi Ica "
Such a simple thing better?
. This is enough, in fact, still a little bit long
Huh?
. You do not need a lot of words in the beginning
why not ?
I mean, you fend off already become close to their friend, is not it?
. Oh, yes, well I have sent
. Already did it
. My God
. Thank Rico
. Because of you I can finally to become good with the rest of the season
! I have made a lot of friends
. I think this is a high
are you awake ?
... Yup
. I wish I never wake up
why not ?
. Even in this lesson Extracurricular it is like the habit
Do you really hate me for this term?
. Well, despite this we are sure to do their duty as a servant
. To be an expert, it is the only honorary that lasts me
How did I know what I think!?
. Someone who owns 5 nerve cells, it is easy to read it
! I am very capable of being a stunning speech B5khalaaa only nervous
. Yes, amazingly
! Now I'm stuck with 5 neurons
Ica-sama, would you like breakfast with us?
. Please this way
.. Ica-sama
. When we go back, let's Nhzy tea concert
. I also
. I, too, please
. Her good
. Yes, I'm happy with this
. Come on, let us sit Kemeto-sama
. Yup
! Yes thats right
.. Kemeto
. Good for you, everyone Osubhta friendly
.. I'm happy because I found the courage
. Well, you also worked hard
. Now, after trying very easy It is as
. Do not Tgtra yourself
. Still everything because of you
U .. Thank-you
Yes, the end of this club commoner sign?
Huh?
I mean, did not the club until Tsahba popular?
.. From now on, the Awaguetk after school will be staying in the Tea Party
. And Stndman regular clubs, also
. I have Oafeeta participation
. The elevator came down here
. see you later
. And aaah, this is a wonderful feeling
. It seems like a long time did I have the bath by
Huh?
Huh? Kemeto?
! A-Ica
When you're here?
I question yourself thing, girls Hzawa their time yesterday, is not it?
! I decided to come again the others
The others?
! Sorry to make you wait, Ica-sama
. Ah, the morning show as well as stunning
. Sure, it's a good feeling
. Well, then, Flandechl
! I packed quickly, I can not breathe
What is there?
! Â-ah, it's a very good feeling and by
. Oh, Ica-sama, you silly
... sense of warm wet towel, which covers the end of her background
... small, but they are still bound to be exhilarating
.. Fajdaha Naeman and Dasman, high-quality sweets
! Fuck her body, which looks like it's candy Ica I am talking about
. Ica-sama seems to face reddened Awfully
- This is because Kemeto
Huh?
! This was soon mandate Altson pure crazy
! If you were not careful, what comes out Baklha
. Huh? Your hand just Ica-toxic fat seemed unusually
. It also looked like it came out of a strange angle
. They must Khyalatna
. Steam plays tricks our minds
So, what about Kemeto-sama?
! Huh? Nothing ... never
. By mentioning this, Ica-sama you and Kemeto-sama, ye close significantly
Huh? Do you think this?
. I am very envious
. Yes offcourse
Tell me the truth, how close your relationship?
. For-nothing to say
. But you two always together
... This may be
... but this will not be true anymore, too
Ica-sama, you got something?
.Hah? ... I'm fine
.Aoh, myself. Do something
Are you sure you're okay?
! Â-Ica-sama
Huh?
This .. my ass
. Mzag has gone too far
! Â-sorry about this
... Oh no
... ... perceptually fading
! I'll be out in a minute or two
. Well, we'll go without you
! Kemeto
! M-What did you do! Do something quickly
! artificial breathing
- ventilator is not a kiss
. It covers the area around the mouth
! So there will be no contact between the lips
! I have not finished yet
Ica-sama, did not end after?
! Soft lips Kemeto and feeling really great
Did you wake up ?
... a-order
. I wish I never wake up
why not ?
It is remained unconscious long?
. We met at ten in the lobby of the hotel
. This leaves you only 20 minutes, so please be prepared
Ah, Yumka-sama, cohesive
Hey, Ika, what is there? what happened ?
. lashy’
! I can not afford this anymore
! This got us very quickly
! P-Flanthrk all out
Hey, what do you get?
. The word that came out is that we Ntuaad
Huh? How did?
... Kajorzaka
. You are a liar
! I really hate ...
A-then, this is what happened
K-you both have not receptive to each other, right?
. For-we not accept each other
In that case, you should not correct the misunderstanding?
. If I liked the cool things
. There is no such current
. Wait ! Flanbaky a little longer
. If I said this, Ica-sama
. Thank you
. At this rate, Vsochark with you again, until the next opportunity arises for us
When you look so happy?
A.-I'm not happy at all
You are pleased with this situation, the extent to which hate me?
- No, I'm not pleased
... Yesterday, I thought you might Tkui a nice girl
! But surely this is enough, I really hate you
! Me too
. good morning
. Please wait a minute
What is there?
. This has dropped
. Oh, thank you very much
. Not at all, to wash you
. Please Use this instead Freely
Huh?
.. Now, if Adhirtna
A-Llano ... When someone from the family Kojo works as a maid?
. Miyuki-sama you are Kodjo that were not the daughter of the main family
. This is not worth your interest to ask him
Are there special conditions by chance?
. I apologize
are you awake ?
... a-order
. I wished I never wake up
Next Episode
. It was my result 80
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go for this
I love thee, O
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
I am deeply fascinated by the commoners
I Odrsk every day
You did not pick up telepathically so far?
what are you ? cool ?
Oh, you understand, you hide Khgelk, huh?
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go
Here's my love of
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
. I told you not to move
Almkaanakh excessive is the curse factor
Do you deliberately Stmtna four times?
The Ica-san a lot of friends
I thought I understood the ethics of all this world expanding
I thought so it's enough to follow what leads me to him daily
. But here I am here, I can not put a name to this
Feelings that can not be predicted, and the usefulness of the guide
The dividing line between the cheek mixing red, dark blue
And before I know about it, it made it hard to say inside or outside my heart
Do not disappear in the twilight, near to see what it all I
I'm sure that everything will be an opportunity to love
Bring your tears and your dreams, which are forced to hide your smile Well?
I will come to you days that you will Mhassoda everyone
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Translation of Vergil Vergil-sub.blogspot.com waited for the coming of our translation episodes
This is a mistake