. Dear audience, please listened to well
, From today onwards
. This boy will serve us as a slang sample
. Named Kajorzaka-san Kemeto
Would you like to ask our commoner anything?
the ring
Welcome Bama
. By Kymytv
Huh?
. Go and buy me tea
Verse ?
! what is wrong with you ? You're going to go to there anyway
Heck ... you are fine as usual, right?
. Thank you very much, I am very thankful
. Yes offcourse
A-Where am I?
... What
Get the hell!?
! Hey, wait a minute.
. Well, Karosaka Kemeto-sama
. I did not want to cause a stir for this resorted to this
. But it has caused an uproar
But in any case, where I am and you?
... calling someone the way you speak to
. Without a doubt, you are from the lower class really
. I'll give you details later
. Please follow me
. Excuse me because I did not introduce myself at the beginning
. I Kodjo Miyuki
. nice to meet you
... This is the Palace of the daughters of the richest people
! Who learn how women Rviat from There will be among the upper class
. In addition to this educational institution has remained hidden from the public by
. Sicaen School for Girls
For girls?
. You will join this school from today onwards
Verse ?
. Completed all the paperwork
. I asked for permission from your parents
What are you talking about! What I'll do here?
Or tell me, what am I?
. Well, then, come please
Do you Taatjahlaina?
. We can say that this school for the elite elite
. Because boys can not register here.
. All workers and students from the girls
. No exceptions
. with this
. We were there some problems in previous years
some problems ?
. I Kimachi Soiree, a secondary student
. Genuine oh please headmistress
. At the outset, let me apologize, it seems that Miyuki-chan has used non-traditional ways to bring you here
. Miyuki-chan, Aatdhira's Kajorzaka
. I am really sorry
... Verse ? Did not this
... So
what's the problem ?
... after graduation
... girls are sent to the outside world commoner
No choice but to deal with the opposite sex
. As a result of this understanding of the extent they shocked the difference between the school and the outside world
. And end up living locked online
How is that ! For this matter?
... These days there are some individuals who have called for change
. According to the habits of school
. We need to talk with those who are above us for such a case
.. It was so
How do you choose!?
. To be a sample of the class commoner
Sample slang?
. This is true, sample slang
... We brought Dastardly like you to live with us
. In this way girls can get used male
. For And if it was a boy, two birds with one stone we'd multiply
. The inability to chat male colleagues become a problem recently
. In fact, a big problem
. But this way, all the problems will be solved
! Wait a moment
I understand Osbabikm, but I want to know what I am?
... Kajorzaka Kemeto
. An ordinary student from a public school
. Notes, height, weight, hobbies, everything your normal
. In the middle school they are accustomed to your call for Sebastian that you care about everyone
. You are very Ami
. And the ideal choice to be our sample
. None of this seems Kalmjamlh
. Can be, but the next part of something special
.. You have a completely different feature for everyone
Trait ?
. Those are ... you look like a man
. Above all, you have a muscle Mania to become a muscular man by
- Right
. Wait
I do not need something?
Who is obsessed muscles?
Am I wrong?
. According to the report, you often spend your time beside the boys and do not talk to girls
. Tamqa more
. For your choice
. What was a great help told us by a friend of your childhood Hannah Larry-san
... those small
. In any case, this is completely wrong, I'm perfectly normal
. What a problem
. Yup
. We are in trouble
Huh? what is wrong with you ?
... if you were not obsessed with muscle
. You have to live in
. Place out of the picture
. In order to protect the purity of students
... if I stayed in this school
. We have to cut Edok condoms
... I love
! Muscle
. This is a good ear
. Seem more sensitive than I thought
. I am relieved
. This is the first year a row, which will join him
. Most of them did not speak to men by
. Try not to scare them off
. Certainly
. I leave the rest to you now, Miyuki-chan
. As Thamrin
. I am class representative of this chapter
. My name is Arzogaoa Rico
. Every first year students were Antzerok
. We're pleased to meet you
.. Er, Llano
. The name is Kajorzaka Kemeto
The name ?
"He said," Name
. True Vamh offer themselves as he did
. Dear girls
What was this?
What's that sound ?
. Listen, my girls, please Stay Hadiat
Rejected it!?
A-Could that be?
. Telephone
. Also known as smart phone
Telephone ?
smart phone ?
. As you can see, it is small enough to carry anywhere you go to him
. It is common that the use of ordinary people
E-A-T-P!?
this thing !?
.. small thing like this phone
. Maid-chan
Ymknny Lms·h?
. Go ahead
. Thank you
! Ah, it's very light
. So they use something wonderful like this in their daily lives
. Oh really
. Amyin are very nice
. Oh girls, it Kemeto-sama's property
. We bring it back to him
. you are right
But how do we do?
. Thinking alone, it makes me feel as if my heart explodes
. I'll do
! This is the Rico-sama
. We can rely on
. Kemeto-sama
. Thank you to let us see something like this
What have you done !?
. Wait a minute, Kemeto-sama
. You apologize properly
! Keren
. At your service, Ricoh-sama
. please enter
. As expected from Rico-sama
. It gave him
. Thank you
Arzogaoa-san
. Rico-sama
. Ica-sama
. Of
Hey, what do you get?
. Dear sordid
Let me ...
! kiss you
! Let me kiss you
If Ami accepted like you will become reality every aspirations, true?
! Let me kiss you until all my dreams come true, dear vile
. Stop this, this is completely wrong
. Untruthful ! Seenba talked about this in the morning tea
Do thy Stsedkin Alseenba that were not in the world never commoner or Stsedkina I commoner!?
. A-You are wrong
. I did not believe her words never
! Dear stupid vile
. The most stupid is that you dont believe that kiss Ami will achieve all your dreams
. But I did not believe her
.Aoh So, what if I told you that if you three times and then Dirty Nbana All your dreams will become reality!?
Oh really ?
! So ?
. No way
So ?
.. Do not tell me
. That's right ! All my dreams will become reality now
... It
.. In fact
! Here is there
. I really regret, Kemeto-sama
. There was something bothering me for this reason you're looking for you
. Leica-sama Amsktk suddenly disappeared
. Surprised
! What do you do
.. Er, Lato
. Leica-sama
! Leica-Lama
. He ran away again
What speeches?
. We did not talk to us never
. Maybe there's something bad us
. You will live in this building Kajorzaka-san
. We have prepared a special room for you to stay out
privet room ?
. Right
. We spent a considerable amount of money to prepare for your arrival Onevsa
. Sure it will Tafrg
. I understand, sorry for the inconvenience
. Do not worry, now prefer
. We brought all your gadgets
. And Rtbnaha exactly the same way in your parents' house
. Appear as a room sleep
. You are right, it's like
... We used a special way to bring all things
. In addition to the mobilization of installation and protection
. 100 million yen, its outcome
100 visits?
. I hope that you enjoy Bbakaik
. To be in such a dirty room
A dirty room?
I am not obsessed with muscle?
! Tbotai of socks
Tjmiatk of socks?
... No
Are not these images to the feet of girls?
... I do not mean
Do you lie about being obsessed with muscle?
! Yup
! I love muscle
Huh?
. In addition to it now, I'll be Keji Miyuki personal servant Kajorzaka-sama
Personal Khademta?
. In this school there is a personal maid for each student interested in
So ... you'll be Khademta
. Well, even if you do not intend your servant do anything for you
You will not be doing anything?
. Well, then, in the 15 o'clock there will be a meeting to clarify things about the commoner and joining
. Until that time, please relax
. I lied to you, vile
! I did it more than 5,000 times and did not get anything
. 5000 times? Note it was the third time
A.-Hist
. It is to blame for Kzbk Ali
. Believe me you from
! The Tnfve thing this folly
... What is this
In this room?
. There are a lot of things that did not see it before
. Everything just things seamy
.. Maybe some of my dreams, the Han
! If used sordid things perhaps my wish will become reality
What ?
. Maybe he became a popular girl
Do not tell me that this is your dream all the time?
Yes, do you have a problem?
. not really
. But you do not need security for such a thing
. I think that if you acted in a normal girl would be enough
. If I did this, not enough
. you do not understand anything
. Well, maybe you're right
... But
. Now you're talking to does not seem that you are in trouble
Oh really ?
. Yup
. I ... I'm very bad at lying
. Often say what I think
. No one loves me
. But I do not want to be a bad disconnect with others
... for this reason
. Taatrkin distance between the students of your class
. Yup
. But I want everyone authentication
. I do not want to be alone
. I want to talk to them all
. I want to have the student life surrounded with friends, too
. During the period of food I pretend to sleep
. As usual, and do what I do not even go back to the bedrooms with others
! I do not want this more
! When I say all this is simple like you for the years
Well, do you want this experience?
Camera !?
control unit
control unit ?
shghlyha vhsb
Surprised!?
! I am surprised
! J ... took me surpise
. I can not act so in front of Ami
. To hide this way
! Oh, this is impossible
. Foolish nights
. It does not connect anything
. This tired
! Of
Yup ?
. He taught me how to become a slang
What ?
Slang?
! Ato ... something Kaltkulaid or from the tribe
! Something like
. Now the existence of the years in our school
.. And also, if I knew imitate, it is possible
! No, certainly my wish will become reality
! And it will become popular
... for this reason
! I want you to teach me [a, b, c] vernacular life
. When he became a woman every commoner students quarterly to Satqrbena
. I designed
! Club commoner
! I'll be the club now commoner
! Ami Club
! True, the club commoner
! Will you and I only, but it will be the club
. Will be more cyclical activities, but will you and I just
It sounds good, right?
. well, okay
. I will start the activities of the club
. At first I want to know how to play this game
Do you want to question our common man any question?
. So, Yasuda-san Mary
Have you used the methods of spending previously?
. Oh, I did order
E. This means that you have used the money to buy tickets, right?
. No, I do not use the ticket
... Otto
This card crossing
. It's prepaid, ie they pay the money before hand
. When you pass it on the scanner, the money is deducted from the expense
. I did not understand anything
. World commoner developed a very sophisticated culture
. unbelievable
. I did not have to talk to him about a few commoner world Bmarafta
. No, it's not so
. The world is not a commoner big thing
. Amazing, this really incredible
. As expected
. We need to know more about the world commoner
. Stunning world commoner
. just awesome
! Okay
Next Episode
. Ali said Larry bodies for students quarterly
Clothes inside?
. Come on, see
. It would be good if you did not wake up
... Think
Rico-sama yearns to us
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Translation of Vergil Vergil-sub.blogspot.com waited for the coming of our translation episodes
. I can smile now