Kemeto, you're here, right?
. I will go
M-m-m-What do you want, and why it is best that I have and you just?
. Yes, .., it would be better to be with you only
, The reason that why I told all the other girls you are busy today
And the activities of the club was canceled?
. Yup
Episode 10 I was curious in this matter some time ago, but what is the "Gates"?
Than you are tense for this class?
! A-Hist, do not benefit as you know
. We're friends enough so do not be tense never
How do I meant this?
. Nothing - just the way you said it
. Now, come and sit here
what is this ?
. Present
Wah, huh?
! No
What do you mean by not?
. Thus did Oniha
when ?
. I think I wanted to give it to you now
. Vasily vafthyha
Yellow Men suit?
... like you're always telling me
! HURRY and Asiri famous person, O foolish
Right ?
. Therefore, I decided it was time to take out everything, as well as
. This suit is your secret weapon to become a famous person
My weapon secret?
"This is true, if I wore this suit and you" the Gates
! Will it become a popular short time
... Listen
I was curious about this all the time but what is the "Gates"?
. It's a greeting between friends is common among all commoners
. Looks suspicious
I have cheated me several times previously, is not it?
I did ?
! Yes, I've done
. Well, certainly something like this might happen once or two
. But this time, it's real
. Look
"It is" the Gates
"This man is called to Dandi Sakon who invented a" Gates
. Thanks to the spread of "Gates" has become famous at home
. "This is true, he was wearing the same suit and the type of" Gates
... and more
388.000 emerged as a result of the word Dandy Sakon
388,000 lajlh appearance?
. This means that there are 388.000 pages in the world wrote about the Dandi Sakon
388.000? In the world ?
... "This is true, and for" Gates
781.000 appearance?
! just awesome ! It is amazing
A lot of people are doing b Gates
! There are also plenty of illustrations
- Gates became among the commoners as one of the great apparitions
. I mean greeting among colleagues and a sign of friendship
This is true, is not it?
.. Yes, the man who lifted jests Gates is
. irresponsibly sạkwn
Tell me who is the man jests?
.Achkas their work is to make people laugh
. This looks great
Well, you know what you have to do, right?
! Yup ! To change this, right?
"You look perfect, I crushed him, loveable as" Laika Dandi
! Ica Dandy! I loved this
Gates
How do ?
. Not good
. You have to expand more Kadimk
.. Â-ah, this is true
. And also, Ajta them slightly down
! Yup
! Gates
. This is good, do not forget your sense of the
- Well, let's go and see the other - Next, advanced body
. After you say Gates Tdoran cycle and Tltefin, so
. Gates Trace B round roll
! Faster
! Gates, then roll
! Gates-roll
that's it ! This is the skill of advanced Gates and lap
Gates and lap
... Now finally generally smug and put your left hand right foot
! And Recessive quickly from there
. Like you Takhtvien away from the Pavilion theater
So ?
! Do not say anything
! Correct example, U. irresponsibly
. I have accomplished the goal, I now have to reveal the truth for Ica
. And multiply to the core again
! I will go and see everybody now and has become popular
Huh?
! antzr fsdtito
... Awu
Is that ...?
.. Yes, this is certainly Fajd, and found Fajd here, it means
What happens here?
What are your intentions?
. This voice-san Kodjo
... it must mean that it is good and smooth and even different from humans
. And certainly not marble or something non-organic has a high quality of attractions
.. I seem to Sonzlq horizontally and touch something
No ! Can not have this! Does this mean I am inside the skirt Kodjo-san now?
! I'm sorry ! This was not intentionally
... It's not about the place, which touched him by someone
.. but for the person who caught
Huh?
: This psychological importance of paramount
. In fact, I am thankful to you, I am very conscious now
. thank you very much
.. No, I tell you
Perhaps I now have to admit to myself that I ask for advice
! I'm sorry
! Oh true, Ica
Given purpose, which arrived this morning Ica-sama's?
When you want to give her something?
. Huh? It's something we use common folk club
. In other words, it is
Huh?
, I Siirt by the worst instincts
, The insect that is going to fire
. Feature often appear in children of primary school if they wish to apply for a girl that they love
! I'm not like this
Are you are not well?
B-certainly I'm not well! What are you talking about?
Are you sure you are not well?
. Well, I'm interested only in muscle
. So, then, this saving you
Ica-sama, what this outfit?
! Oh, this is not your business, to the meeting
Tmhly, fsdtito
What do you mean by none of your business?
! How you can be so fast! this is scary
Scary ? No, what is this outfit?
You say that this strange outfit?
M-What is it?
! These clothes worn by ordinary celebrities
! Gates
What is that !?
"It's called the" Gates
. A greeting between friends and knows all the common folk
. These clothes are worn by the "man jests" Dandi Sakon "who invented
Is this what a Kemeto him your story-sama?
. This is true, even Kemeto is gave me these clothes
Kemeto-sama did?
Do you loved them? Very elegant, huh?
.. certainly yellow color vibrant
. The fact that they Potency clothes make you look so comic
.. think about you've got a nice clothes from Kemeto-sama
! Ica-sama I am very envy
. H-Well, what do you get to like them too? I will ask him one for you
Do you mean this?
. Yup
. thank you very much
. no problem
. I thought that "Gates" is something that has got out of Ica-sama
. No "Gates" is something that is doing more than 781.000 around the world
! 781.000 people? unbelievable
A-ato Ahi so? Gates?
... No, no
! Gates
E-so?
. Yup
. So your hands
this is ?
. Yup
. Well, Tabaana
! Certainly
Gates
So salutes commoners each other, what can I say?
! This is a great freedom
is not it ?
! We can not stand here so
! Let us see this wonderful colloquial greeting others
! great idea
! Of! Ica
Damn, where did you go?
! Ica
Ah, Kemeto-sama
! He, Kemeto-sama
! Oh
! "Kemeto-sama has just finished teaching the others," Gates
! We have done Kemeto, all of us can make friends with commoners
! Flannery Kemeto-all of you poison the fruits of our efforts
! In order for Flanflha
! great idea
! Well, here we
... Astt, and
! Gates
! Oh, Hattori
. I did not hear you for a long time
. There is nothing here only girls
At the beginning, I thought that in the hands down is the best, You know what?
. But since I came to this school, I realized something
. Best Men
... When you are dealing with the girls you have to Ttroy
But with the guys you can simply take it
. Really I miss the smell of men and fat fitness that build a good feeling
. I began to feel nostalgic
- This e-
! This is bad
Kemeto wants to go home?
.. Yes, I have said to stay in the whole environment is claustrophobic girls
. He longed for the other men
Does this mean that he longs for the muscles?
. In fact, nothing has been said in this regard
Are you going Kemeto away?
. Let us think all of us in something so as not to make this happen
But, what can we do?
! I got it
! We can become men
what do you mean ?
... We will give ourselves a little male
! And bees replace other men
. We got you, we will play a desire Korzaka in the presence of other males here
.. Well, then, Flanqom as far as we have to become more masculine
. Even Kemeto-sama remains in this school
! Yup
. So again
Ica-sama, what we have to do starters?
... huh? A-Yeah, let's see, let's see
. Flantsrv as it does Kemeto
. This is true, Kajorzaka is the only male who Talva with him
. Tradition is the beginning of all the art
! A-order! That's right
.. copy Kemeto huh? Mm no specific thing comes to my mind immediately
. This is true, after I pointed out to him Valomr difficult
SAL A, there is a way to copy Kajorzaka
! So
K-Karen-sama?
.. When Otusband with Kajorzaka
. It always lowers his gaze
! It looks specifically here
This is true, huh?
. Kemeto-sama lowers his gaze vectorial So, too
. Let us try this
! Right
! I got it ! I thought about a way to copy Kemeto
! I love muscle
! Oh
! This is like Kemeto-sama, true
! In this case, also Vsontaleg
! I love muscle
! I love muscle! I love muscle! I love muscle! I love muscle
! I love muscle! I love muscle
! I Djaltona angry now
Take your time!
This is not like Kemeto in fact, is not it?
. Ah, you're right, I am sorry
. Djaltona angry now
. Djaltona angry now. Djaltona angry now. Djaltona angry now. Djaltona angry now
. Kemeto do so, for sure
. But I have a feeling that this is something useless this
What is, Arzogaoa?
. I do not know, I do not know what is
. But I have a feeling that something different
! that's it
Do you know what is it?
.. muscles! The men in the video who built themselves
But we are still young women, is not it?
! This is true! This is the crucial difference
! Kemeto likes muscles, which means we also have to do with them
! This is certainly true! Let us go the strategy of muscles at once
. thanks for waiting
It is made well, is not it?
. Muscle
. With this, there is one of them
! Well, Sortdaha
! What about me, I want to see me Kemeto-sama muscular way
Let me do it
. No other choice but to report stone paper scissors
. A-order
! Stone Paper Scissors
! I am the actress is
! Okay
Okay ?
Huh?
. Error
. Do not you look more than a young lady boasts Badilaha so
What you expected more Menhma?
. Hairstyle
. It's right, you'll at least have to have such hairstyle Kemeto
... No, we have to have the ultimate male, which means
Hairstyle Samurai hair?
. Yes, Calcamuray, I heard Kajorzaka say once
"The samurai was a model for Japanese men"
E.-this makes us leave our clothes and I can not wear a skirt
. You are right in this regard
. When it comes to masculinity, there is nothing more than a noble man
. Let's put this
. In this case, also with walking sticks
. mustache
. Amazing, this will be it
! T-loveable Potency
. Hard to move Balorjae and I wear this Sokhalaha
What else ? Have you forgotten something?
. I forgot the smell of men and fitness mast, built a good feeling
! I am owned by me
. Kemeto-sama said he longed for the smell of men
The smell of men?
. Smell the task, it is true
What is the smell of men exactly?
the meat ?
. After I pointed this certainly carries the meaning of this
In any case, how a person can earn the smell of meat?
. Spices yakiniku
Golden yakiniku
This is - how can I say that it smelled awful meat, huh?
. I have a feeling in remembrance in this regard
. It is certainly
! If wore this smell will surely smell Potency
. Â-Ica-sama, you Sodaha
It supposed to be placed in the same places perfume, right?
. If not Tmaenai
. We put some of them, too
. Yes, everyone Vlastef
What story Hattori?
! We will enter
.. Okay
! One, Some potential
! Kajorzaka! Good weather Flantbarz
. Go Madam
I'm not a lady! As Raiankm all look Ksalsh the yakiniku?
. what's going ? All acting strangely
! This is because you said that you will leave
I will leave ?
. Yes, I said you do not like this school more and you will leave
Huh?
. Kemeto-sama, you said that when you are dealing with the girls you have to Ttroy
- That's why I
! That is why we have said that we have to take the place of other boys
! This should keep you
. They appear as fools
- High - Kemeto-sama
- We did this for you
. Yes, thank you for this
! You should not worry, I will stay in this school
- Oh! I have our concern - I am very happy - because I am sorry Oqlguetkm
! I Djaltona angry now
--What is the matter ? - What are you talking about - Are you okay?
"In the next episode"
Your body convenient, is not it?
How can you say?
. Locks may be freed
! Stay away from Rico Dear commoner
. We have completed negotiations of your marriage
! Without you here, no one here
Is this not the sky which was seen Kemeto-sama?
I thought I understood the ethics of all this world expanding
I thought so it's enough to follow what leads me to him daily
. But here I am here, I can not put a name to this
Feelings that can not be predicted, and the usefulness of the guide
The dividing line between the cheek mixing red, dark blue
And before I know about it, it made it hard to say inside or outside my heart
Do not disappear in the twilight, near to see what it all I
I'm sure that everything will be an opportunity to love
Bring your tears and your dreams, which are forced to hide your smile Well?
I will come to you days that you will Mhassoda everyone
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Translation of Vergil Vergil-sub.blogspot.com waited for the coming of our translation episodes
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go for this
I love thee, O
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
I am deeply fascinated by the commoners
I Odrsk every day
You did not pick up telepathically so far?
what are you ? cool ?
Oh, you understand, you hide Khgelk, huh?
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go
Here's my love of
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
. Please Nadini, Rico