Did you wake up !?
... a-order
. I wish I do not wake up forever
why not ? Do you want anything?
. I told you the maid assigned to you
. Morning business part of my career
. Oh alright
And aaah! What ..?
. It will help you to change your clothes
! For-nothing wrong if they were all the same for you
. I can not allow this! This duty must be carried out maids Sicaen
. Even if you Ami is unattractive
. Obsession with muscles and oblique
... True, if not gonna act as an effeminate freak muscle
! I could not live here
You think things are immoral, right?
! I was not
You're thinking muscles, right?
"Episode 2 Rico is aspire to be like"
Good morning, Rico-sama
. good morning
Is there something?
.. Ah yes, Well
From this road
As we get out of the back door?
Did you forget the reaction that happened yesterday?
. When he graduated, Vstkhalq sensation
. This brief period of time out of the back door
. Okay
!... You are
M-What are you doing here, O commoner?
Have you ever heard something?
! Yes, on commoner
. In this way quickly
. I understand this is for you Babak normal
. But not as a popular person like you will come out from the back simply
. This indicates that what I have to qualify me be popular, too
! Remember correctly? The club's grassroots activities begin today
Er, what's wrong today?
. Er, I can not seem to settle and by
why not ?
... specifically .. I mean we do not have servers specific to help us
! you are kidding
. I do not have maids Amyin
. Listen! I'll tell you all about Amyin but in return
Do you mind news about this place? School here as life?
. All this pain in the neck cramps will you Arzogaoa Rico
. It is Chairperson of the Committee
.Ovdil that you are activated
Huh? For what-Tvdilna about Arzogaoa Rico?
, Because you are not a luxury lady
. While Orzogaoa-san is very beautiful, if this aura surrounding
. As if from another world
- This makes me Atwater, I do not feel any of this from you
! AUO
! when ? Dear SOD commoner from me
... Kemeto-sama
. good morning
. UN-hmmm, good morning
. I looked for you everywhere, I had the pleasure to meet you
. A-order
. Ica-sama, good morning to you too
By the way, some to have the May I of your time after school today?
. Well, I have no problem
, Ah, wonderful, we welcome your party, Kemeto-sama
, This Snntzerk in the exhibition hall - Ica-sama any case, you also
! Ah, I wonder that I did something that has changed her mood
! It's become a really weird oddball when it gets this, huh
Well, you Sthalin this issue, Miss Rico?
. Yup
"Put Duke milk in spices Darjeeling"
! Excellent
. Very elegant, and beautiful work
. Rico-sama, really impressive
. He came amazingly seen
! Rico-sama has achieved a new record
! And graceful as well as your figure
. Thank you very much, but
. Well, the following is Tancubashi-san
. Stunning, very ingenious, meaning mono
Â-Ica-sama Is difficult to remove?
.. Well, Kajorzaka-san
! Behold, I am coming
. new registration
! This was amazing, Kemeto-sama
! I never imagined that you can jump to this dimension
I've jumped the way that always do it by, is this very cool?
. This was an incredible, Kemeto-sama
. We did not appreciate even jump like you
. Men really are different
! I can not put a stick landing so well
With reference to this, where I went Atsu?
Atsu?
Do you mean Ica-sama?
. A-order, we Amyin use words such as "Atsuo" with friends
. This is just ... it's easier to use for this slipped me
, Now that I have indicated this, Kemeto-sama
You and Ica-sama were you Tmsheean together this morning, is not it?
. It seemed that ye very rivals to each other
... Well, for
So, in fact, that the fault lies on us, is not it?
. Maybe it is better if I did not volunteer that they do not want to
. Arzogaoa-san and friends do not like
. Most likely there is something else may have their reasons
. Please do not for this Tloha for this
! Since we may not love Ica-sama
... huh? I mean
... We were delighted by saying that we did not do anything
. Offer to Ica-sama unhappiness, Kemeto-sama
. If it so we can certainly ratification
. Yes, we can certainly
I --mtokdh right -I, also I will do my best
. Kemeto-sama, here
! he is here
So go Amyin!?
Verse ? This proximity to look
! I have stumbled
Is there a way in order to walking?
! No
"Tea," "French cuisine"
! What is that ? How can this be written in Japanese! I can not understand anything
Kemeto-sama, what do you ask?
. Well, a Japanese meal
. So I will ask a Japanese meal as well as
. I also
. I will ask the Japanese meal also
. Thank you for waiting
What is that ?
. Japanese meal, I heard that "the Maine Cup" is the main food
... This is as of ways Amyin
! Even Amyin do not eat "Cobb Min" always
Do you pop your tongue I did not it?
So, do you go back on this?
-Hassana, certainly will Kemeto-sama
Huh?
Is this food ... the smell is unusual?
Do not you know what is the "Maine Cup"?
Maine Cup?
Well, do you know what is Alramen?
. Well, I've heard some stories
! S-stories, huh? Well this kind of immediate Alramen
. In other words, it's easy to issue
. Tadhavin hot water and you can eat
Just by adding hot water!?
E. That's all what you do to cook?
. Rico-sama this is unlikely
! As on the box a lot of words written by
. Here are some of the old architecture in my house for decoration
. P-any case, we eat such a thing often
! Ah
. It really eaters, there are also other ingredients
This may be Robien, but what those things yellow and brown?
! Imagine! Only by adding water it takes this form
How does this work ?
If you are interested, do you want to try it?
. Maya-sama, Go ahead
. No, Kai-sama, you Aflleha
! Hey girls ! Flanhark command from you want to participate
. Comes and stands here
! Right
. Excuse
. As you like
. one moment please
. If I got such a treasure of Kemeto-sama
. The simple white ceramic pot, it would be impolite never
.. huh? Exaggerate about it too much
! Let us use our finest dishes
So this is a "Maine Cup" which eats Amyin, is not it?
. I wonder how it tastes
! Smell so wonderful
. It is impossible to have a good taste as expected
! Thank you very much, Kemeto-sama
. B-Sure
! Well, all of us Flanokl
! Thank you for this meal
! This delicious
! No way! No way
! I did not taste anything like never
. Between delicious soups and pasta stromal
! The entire dish is uniquely refreshing
! I can make this a regular order
. This is certainly an unprecedented experience
. I will never forget this day, never, or even flavors known to
! For the rest of my life
Do you simply eat food big order for them!?
. Ah ... the food is really comfortable with everyone is
! Hello to your welcoming party, Kemeto-sama
Are you surprised?
Unbelievably ! Thank you, Arzogaoa-san
Not at all, just my thinking in this small meeting makes me enjoying
! Well, here it is here Kemeto-sama transferred Nkhbkm
! Nkhbkm
Is there something?
. Oh no, I was thinking about how Ruatk
. You are responsible for this concert after all
. At all, Kemeto-sama You are the reason for this
. In many ways, is not known to us
. My idea of ​​myself to see when your eyes are something completely different
. I am happy because I congratulate you so, Kemeto-sama
Kemeto-sama, do you want to dance?
. Er, do not uh, I do not dance not dance by
. Valawam do not go to dance to a place like this
. Oh really ? Perhaps you are ignorant, please forgive me
. No, h .... Well, let me try
Arzogaoa-san, Can you show me how?
! A-I wish gladly
.. Let's see, my hand
... Ah
Are you okay, Arzogaoa-san?
. A-order
. You do not have to put a great effort in which
. I can not really dance, for this you will not know if it slipped never
. For this matter, I may be I'm from the slip
... Kemeto-sama
Well, how do you start?
... a-order, it is true
... Hmmm
Huh?
... Oh
! I think, we're dancing
! What an innovative dance
. This equally common folk act Bsjathm
! He was like hell
. It seems that Arzogaoa-san was hit too dizzy
Arzogaoa-san
Huh? Huh? What ?
! Long overdue
To what extent do Ardtna wait!?
. I had no choice, they have set up my party welcome
. I had to come as you know
! Hav, do not bother, the club told me all about commoners
What we do at the beginning?
"Commoners Club"
... Take your time! I'm thinking in this regard. Let us see what the common folk who do
Say, O commoner, what is this?
what is this ? It Mangga
Mango ?
"200000000 folder may sell" " 'the Avatar Tonva, legend begins now."
Do not know what this?
How do you read this?
. Uh, you do not know how to read paintings
. So let's see, it reads from right to left and from the top down
... Hmmm
".. it must be." "Chaser Mistraal .." "who does not know anything." "In this city."
"... weapons and Alrdaouat ..." "which I received .." "from that man ..."
! Vaaaaash! Hmmm
"All this was for this moment," "cloak the second body ..." "souring Aazonomi"
... Weah
how are you ?
. I'm a bit surprised you
What did not say anything about this before?
about what ?
! That all commoners in high school have psychic powers
It's really pure, huh?
... No way ! Dear commoner, you do not mean
.. huh? No, do not tell me
It's impossible to believe that, right?
! In this case, it will be also psychological
! If commoners managed to do this so there is no reason you can not do it like me miss
! I really believe it's what a pure beyond the border
"أرعدي"
! And then my robe for each Sokhv rows and do Andama
! Ica-sama you amazing
! From now on it must be Ica-sama Chapter Center
Oh, Tanona? Well that's what everyone says, this
Can you see them?
. Oh dear quieter commoner, even if he became the most famous girl dismissal
. I will keep talking to you, you have to honor this
. Well, it's better for you to Taatdrba away
This is a way of awakening the sleeping inner robe and put him in the contract, right?
... No
! So
Huh? Is not this different from what the manga?
You are not slang, you miss, right?
That's right, you're right, what is the second part please?
. Well, now I try to do everything you shown together
. When Tflanha, Stkdran to stop time
, From wearing a golden robe
... towards the horizon
... around the role of
"I get it"
. Nothing happened
Do you really stop?
... of
! just awesome ! It became a psychologist
O foolish commoner
Do you see? Do you see?
! Well, it's time to write "Achenja" on your forehead
E-huh? My cheeks swollen, why?
. E-So, then, there is a limit to the extent of my ability to stop time
. To experience this more later
Dost thou aloud, what gives "Achejna"?
Hey, how you? How did I know what I intend to write it?
! ... l-do not tell me .. Do not tell me
! This was the whole representation, I am very, very sorry
.. Kemeto-sama
Kerry ah, thank you
! M-What is this? Round water droplets fall on a wonderful curvatures
. With this enough meat bone to be wonderful
... if she wears knee socks, it will be the disparity between
... between the parts and the tightest blown clear area
- it will be literally "clear" devastatingly
! ... Alofajad idealism that can easily captious, Do not you know
! Wah, sorry
... I want by
... take me ... Kzojtk
. All of you please, on page Avcho Ktabkm 28
Throughout this time, do you work on that yesterday did not exist?
. Well, please, and Tksmwa pairs Begin Mhadttkm
... Arzogaoa-san, let's start
Yono means engagement in Japanese
Yono?
-Hah? - This is not too early on this
... ah, but in my grandmother's day
. Was said to be betrothed and graduated from the school is common
Arzogaoa-san?
. Oh, do not bother with this nothing, Let us continue
"We are waiting for"
marriage ?
Huh?
. right Now ? A-uh, for sure
. But to make it a wonderful ceremony everyone is happy
. Even if suddenly started I plan, it will get very early
! You should not tear up the leaves, Arzogaoa-san
! When're so Pttaiwitha
! What is the World Heritage site which is trying industry
"Travel" for any places will be good? Inside ? Or abroad?
Rico-sama, what happened to you?
"In the next episode"
! My name is Karen Genro
. Are you left these both are
. Covered with muscles and a lot of fun
Are you from my clothes you will take off?
! How dare you be this chutzpah
! Kemeto-sama, watch
. It's ... Committees
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Translation of Vergil Vergil-sub.blogspot.com waited for the coming of our translation episodes
The next episode was paradise parks