. It seems that your relationship with Haku is not bad nor good
... because of the kind Haku abused very understandable
. It will require of you more unknown to understand each other
. Haku-sama does not seem that you eat
Is there something?
Is that?
Haku-sama
does this mean
"Episode 9 Kajorzaka-sama here
.. So
Do you say it?
! Yup ! I mean, our Haku-sama
! Want Kajuseraka-sama to know more about them
! Haku-sama has become a young Miss
... In any case Flandao Kajorzaka-toxic to the lab
To make recognizes Haku-sama more
! Let us begin now
. Tmhluwa We can not let Haku-sama discovers our intervention
. This is true, I have just started to become Miss
It is a very sensitive
! Okay ! Think of a way to make Kajorzaka-sama come here in a natural way
! Yup
- Say, O commoner
What is the maid cafe?
maid ?
Cafe ?
. Ah, you know what is the cafe, right? There are staff waiting to be maids
. Huh? I think you said that there is no factors for maids
... as they have appeared in the manga of thy
- Well, that
. Most of this, there are several oddity among them
As if the mechanism to be Miss, it formed to be a terrorist firing from Oshaltha
! It has sensors and ornament Kalmkhalb grow them
! Dear deviant
... it is not, the maids who display in the manga and light novels
. Not only fictional creations
. And not as any maids in the lives of common folk
So, what is the maid cafe?
. It is, they maids in the cafe maids
. And not who work such as domestic real agents in this school
. They completely Mokhtlvat for maids who go and meet Tarafhn
Maids go to meet?
. For the factors, the maid is someone looking forward to it
Maids?
Looking forward to it?
. Maids are something common folk can not reach him
. You can say as if they were some kind of celebrity ..
. A special kind of person
Kemeto-sama, do you think this is what it?
... Well, when I arrived here at the beginning and I saw a lot of maids here
... Nheikk on Cannon are domestic divine honest
. I was very teased
In other words, Kemeto-sama you say you love the maids?
. Well, something like that
! So Let us learn today about domestic commoners in maid cafes
Huh? Well, for
. I guess that this is good
. We have to resolve the matter
! And aaah! Stop trying to take control
. In this case, I will go and finished off the cafeteria
booked up
. Welcome to your home, Sir
Sir? I, I am your servant Kemeto-sama!?
Is there something wrong?
! L-No, nothing at all
Lato .. How many attendees to your party today, sir?
. just one
. So allow me to Eric table
. Prefer your list, when preparing for your order please ask
. Yes, thank you
. This is like to be a summary of
! I ! I ! I ! I ! I
What ?
Is it not strange that you ask how many attendees to your party, sir?
Otherwise this what you mean by saying that when preparing for your application?
. This is more like a representation, this does not benefit from it
. Now, now, Kemeto-sama
. Ica-sama has an idea
- huh! I think they represent beautifully - this let us not shrink them put to
- and serious - .. Ica-sama Leave you this
What kind of silly nonsense!?
Ideas Bakatkm was strange too, is not it?
. No, not specifically
! liar
. I did not think anything of this too
For what you sit here and according to what we do next Arna
. Kemeto-sama, if kindly
. A-order
! In fact, here is where it turns
. The part that you know the maids Khastkm found in domestic commoners
.. For example, if asked, the maid juice Stkhaddmna juice
! With all her love
. I am very sorry, but I do not understand what you mean
. Do it, until we see
Kemeto-sama, please?
Verse ?
. what is wrong with you ? We will not understand even tryna
- No, I just can not
! Stflha certainly
! To make its taste delicious, some of the Mio-Mio, Kerr-Bio
! Come on ! Do not Ttrajawa
Kajorzaka-sama is interested in maid?
. Yup
! I got it
.Hassana, let us learn about bringing omelet rice
... Thank u-wait, sir
. I will give my love now, to emphasize the taste of good omelet rice
- to make a savory taste, Mio-Mio
! I can not, as a human creature I can not do this very embarrassing it
! I apologize now for me and for everyone in the cafe maids
. The now-Sosm image of this ketchup
. It's very good
! Hi ! Haku, not now
! His service Bhabay
! It is not love as much as anything else is red
Haku, you are interested in the game?
. Love-Love, Mio-Mio, Stone Paper Scissors
! One-two-three zap
.. Love-Love
. E. Do you play again? Okay
. Love-Love, Mio-Mio, Stone Paper Scissors
! One-two-three zap
.. Love-Love
No rule states that you play until you win the maid, okay?
. Haku-sama, the next part of the fun of us still lies ahead
Kemeto-sama, what we have to do now?
... h-Well, let's see there is also dancing and singing
! Oh, I love to sing, Please let me
Wah, Kemeto you had to say that, is not it?
Huh?
. Well, if I dared to stand before you Vsogne best of my abilities
. No, wait a minute
"Please listen to" Ava Maria
! Haku, Ahtersa
Hey, what you are doing?
! ... T-stop
! Stop this
! You have no talent
! J-nights chutzpah, everyone praises over the sound quality
! They avoid your feelings
! You have to Tkhvda all the points obtained for this
K-Kemeto-sama, what do you think?
... t-Otto
! Haku
! Let me care about you two together in this debate there
How can I leave you care about it?
. I apologize
. Ica-sama, Rico-sama, Karen-sama will wash your clothes
. For this, please go to your room and your clothes Gero
. Now this thing is completely different
What do you mean by this?
. Café maids maids women do not clean up any business
Huh?
! Do not clean the?
. No, they do
What about washing clothes and wear clothes and see you every morning?
. They are not heeding any of this
... In other words, they're so attending the food for you
And play Mew-Mew and Kerr-Bio but women do not in any kind of personal care never?
. Yup
How can this?
You can be nicknamed even a servant?
So, Kemeto-sama Do you like slang maids?
. I do not Olhm
Kajorzaka-sama
. Ah, thank you for everything you have done previously
! Pardons
. You are servants eukaryotes Mzhlat really
! You think this is? Oh, I have an idea
If approved, Can you come to see us at work?
. A-Yes, I would like to see this
. Please enter
. Excuse me for snooping
To see this again this place is huge, huh
So it is not clean everything requires a lot of work?
. Oh no, something like this is a piece of cake
Well, let me show you everything about the facility, okay?
. Huh? H-Well
. This lab Haku-sama
me too ?
. They Haku-medal crew, they will register their observations and arrange
Oh, yes?
.. Otto
! Kajorzaka-sama here
. I was watching ... It's great how accurate place
. In fact, I would like to say it's great
Haku-sama, what do you say to explain to the Kajorzaka-sama place?
... Er, I want to see the maids
. Well, no matter what
. Do not bother them, Come on, let's go
... Okay
! Sand box yours, I used to my mind purer
. That's logical
Is this something she created, Haku?
. Oh really, it's very good
Huh? Want to make something together?
. Okay
.. Otto
. It happened and that was all of them at the break
. Even the maids get time off
. That's right
. Do not Tarna any attention Khsy on the side of the road
.. Okay
What do you make?
. a house ! Also collect Kemeto
. Okay
Ummm ? What speeches?
Do you have big hands?
Haku, small hands, huh?
. This will not replace is
. What ? Nothing wrong with this
Is there something wrong?
. No No, never nothing, please continued
- What do you mean, b continued? - This teaser
. Okay
Are you loved?
Haku-sama, it's time to diet, right?
Is the time limit for this late? Haku eating do you want?
. This answer is good
. There is a cafeteria for the crew, this Kajorzaka-sama joined us please
... Oh, but
. Miss is taking care of friends is part of our mission as domestic
. H-Well, I do not mind doing this
... Otto
. It is a time of our food, as well as
. Do not bother us
. Do not think of us feels like more than a piece of herb
. Sorry, I am afraid that we have a shortage of dishes, so you two participated this
Haku ♥ Kemeto
. All the maids working here
. For this, we always draw the hearts of things
- but our names - this is normal
Well, do you Sospb a problem if asked individual dishes?
-- I apologize ? - I said that we need individual dishes
. Sorry, but individual dishes also carried out
- Huh? But you Tmlkounam not it? A group of them were stacked in
! Ah
. Sorry, I have all Asagtthm
This was a deliberate clearly, is not it?
... I have a lot of lab maids work hard mental
. This sometimes intense pressure on us so
! Should not be a place of work like this, is not it
. Well, let's put this aside, please Feltokl
. both of you
Is it good?
. it is good
. Please consider us your leftover ideas from the past left on this earth
What kind of this science fiction!?
Ummm ? Excuse me, can I get a spoon as well?
... very sorry, but the lack of a minimum Alamaalq
- this please continued to kiss and ye not take part directly --hah
. Determination saves miracles from happening, and for this reason called miracles
- Oh, it's there, I'll have one by
. Very sorry, but it has recently become infected with panic as soon as you see the silver stuff
. Murrieta, you are stressful, according to
If this is true, it has to see a doctor, is not it?
.. Kemeto
So do you want to eat?
.. Okay
. it is good
! Awake mana, things have started to become good just
. Bring something to drink it
.. A-Oh, thank you very much
. Sorry, but that's all we have
! Now, I know that this is not true
. This is the only type of straw found
When this kind possessed anyway!?
And you are there, those straws, right?
. Are all dysfunctional, all closed-ends
! Sure, some straws are so sometimes. But it will not be repeated in this form
! I apologize for the Japanese industry
. Well, Kajorzaka-sama continued
.. .. This will not end, even drink
Thus Raatkma two, not Konkma Habiba Habib seems?
Huh? How is that ?
Oh, for
. I always look at the top of her head because she is always in my lap
But it has a beautiful face too, huh?
- What speeches
! Head of servants
Huh? Head of the servants all of this influence?
.. Sakimura
! Present
. Request an urgent investigation had arrived from the company
. There is no response in the lab, this applied to inquire from me
Our top go too?
What ?
. Sorry for my staying long day
. We have Ogillna Keji-san we end up, too
. There is nothing wrong, do not worry in this regard
So, what do you think? Do you understand a little more now?
.. Nations, to be honest, I'm not quite sure what to do maids
. No, I do not mean this
... lkny
. I saw the face of Haku who do not know about it for this was it nice
! Please come whenever you want
... Er, well
! Hey ho
! Nkhbkm
! Our plan things have developed dramatically
. Although the arrival of president of the servants was a surprise
.. saying this, do you know that the president of the servants are Kajorzaka-sama chose
To be slang sample?
.. I know, in fact, there was another candidate to be Akhittarh
. But the head of the servants put its last word
What can this? Do you felt something? Or something like that?
. In fact, the Kajorzaka-sama good reputation
. Well, anyway, we owe thanks to the President of the servants to bring it to us Kajorzaka-sama
! We will continue to make things dramatic here
! All of us together
! Yup
! To make a good taste, some of Mio-Mio and Kerr-Bio
Haku, you are interested in the game?
. Love-Love, Mio-Mio, Stone Paper Scissors
! One-two-three zap
.. to make a good taste
! Mio-Mio, Kerr-Bio
! No, I can not by
Next Episode
What are your intentions?
. According to the best men
! We love muscle! We love muscle
! You have made me angry now
I thought I understood the ethics of all this world expanding
I thought so it's enough to follow what leads me to him daily
. But here I am here, I can not put a name to this
Feelings that can not be predicted, and the usefulness of the guide
The dividing line between the cheek mixing red, dark blue
And before I know about it, it made it hard to say inside or outside my heart
Do not disappear in the twilight, near to see what it all I
I'm sure that everything will be an opportunity to love
Bring your tears and your dreams, which are forced to hide your smile Well?
I will come to you days that you will Mhassoda everyone
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Translation of Vergil Vergil-sub.blogspot.com waited for the coming of our translation episodes
Spices yakiniku
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go for this
I love thee, O
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
I am deeply fascinated by the commoners
I Odrsk every day
You did not pick up telepathically so far?
what are you ? cool ?
Oh, you understand, you hide Khgelk, huh?
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go
Here's my love of
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
! love them
! Ica Dandi, I loved this
I was curious in this matter some time ago, but what are you're going to get?