... Today we have on the air YAMADA Misaki
. Star of the upcoming high school and the rising voice and Hanai Larry Chan-Actress
! Hi ! I Hanai Larry
. This third with us perpetrators of
. For this I think we greet you own biting
! And we will take the ideas of the greeting of your demands
! Larry and sent them you will make a very happy
! Curse
"Foolish Yamada Gu had" made sound money "or" Kyota-B
! So make Larry more incitement there to get a guide
... What a troublesome ... What a troublesome
! Curse ! I was not disturbed by this limit by
Dear Larry, I Appley Well, I can configure many friends do not worry about me Kemeto
! I'm not well, damn
Haku?
Episode 5 Just friends
Are you here to visit?
. Before anything else, put some clothes
. All I have is the potato
! What Thpinh, potato censer, or french fries or potato cake
Potato cake?
. It is as cakes Alorozk but made from potatoes
! You have to Tsenai potato paste and then fried in a skillet
. It's good
. I want it
Are you sure you want something you Btboukh I?
You usually eat within a structured agenda, right?
. Sakel anything I made you Kemeto
Oh, okay then I'll make something delicious, okay?
... Kemeto
Hmm?
. I want to do something
! Well, Make dough balls
. First, wash your hands
. Oh, I have an idea
Very nice, huh?
Ltyfh?
. Yup
It's really hard satisfy, huh
! ... Haku
Wait a moment, why not Tkhalaa Almriol?
. For-if there was nothing, put your underwear at least
! This makes it look Kalmjnonh
Well, ready to eat?
Is it good ?
. delicious
Delicious, huh?
What is the thing that closes when a person enters it, but he opens up when it does not enter?
Oh, puzzle?
"The answer is" trains crossing
. That's logical
Otnin that it is not a mystery?
Gas ? what do you mean ?
Oh Well, I've already in this kindergarten or elementary school
. I do not remember when I was kindergarten
Well, what about the elementary school?
What I did so Tstmtay in the past?
. "Proved hypotheses" Arjodk
Huh?
Robots carrying objects painted many of the CPU circuits manufactured
A.-oh, well, can I question one
! Well, come on
"The father of the frog" Linq "strongly" Arepett-Arepett
Chirping: is the voice of the frog
"The mother frog revision purity" educated-educated
So, how Linq frog son
... Arepett? Educated? It does not sound members depends on the type
124!
How do I thought about this!?
The correct answer is "Achargvh" for this it is not to croak
Achargvh: voice tadpole (son of frog)
. Haku I expect that you are not good at these things
. another one
. Okay
When the car wrapped around the turn, what is the thing that you lose definitely?
Gasoline?
It does not lose gasoline, is not it?
Parts?
This will be scary
People ?
! This will be really scary
The answer is --azn
Not yet
Have you ever thought one?
Rupture of the frame particles?
This is likely rupture when going in a straight line, too, right?
"The correct answer is" Speed
Haku, you can not even think about it
! another one
. Sorry, I have implemented
! another one! another one
.Hia Haku, Sakoumura-san is waiting
! vaah
. I want to stay with Kemeto
. Haku, you can see me again tomorrow
Doll?
Haku
What was all this?
. It seems that Kemeto-sama-sama and Haku together well progressing
As a matter Atodhan, Arzogaoa?
. What do crime
Ica-sama What idea on this matter
! It is clear that this is beyond the border
! This always bothered me, but it was recently wondrous
.. when I speak with Kemeto even slightly
! It begins to cling to him and become distracted by
. It can cling to me
... When I play with him one against one in his game
! The Haku cling to Kimto, I thought he was ignored
! It began to take off her clothes to interfere with us again
. I do not think we have to wear clothes force
what do you mean !? They do this deliberate
. Clearly when you eat biscuits
. I have consumed them directly from the hand of Kemeto-sama
! This is, how can I express it
! This is unfair ! Seen only Thabtunai
-! For - for sure
! I am very envious, I want to kill him
. S-kill him will not succeed
. It is still to blame
. When they are given candy always smiling
. It seems like you enjoy every bit of it
It is like a servant, like hers Seibestan
Do you have to take off my clothes too?
Huh?
! For-nothing! nothing at all
! We must banish Haku from his grasp
... If we do not do something, it certainly will start
! By little of this and a little of that for Haku
! A-I will not accept this
! You are right, this crime and we have to stop this
! A-order, we prevent crime before you get
! At first, clearly-let's talk with Haku medal
. You will come in any moment now, specifically
K-Kemeto-sama is out on a mission and will not come back today
! one moment please
Kemeto is not always here, is not it?
. Yes, this can be fun and us girls as we
I want to spend some time with you Haku-sama
. Come on, come on, GO us
. A-I know, I will prepare us some tea
.- Yes, Well - true, for
. E-Is there something Haku-sama? Let's drink some of it
. For-what? I've the same thing as usual
. Probably not her appetite
. no, not this
what do you mean ?
. Haku eat directly if he arrived, however, someone by
when ?
No, often this is true?
! If this was what I Tredenh did not leave your choice
! Yo, I Kemeto, I love men and muscle girls who appear in primary school
. Go ahead, Haku whole biscuits from my hand
when ?
Aika-sama What we have to do!?
. I do not know why ask me
Kerry? Kerry?
Do you called Rico-sama?
... In fact
. Haku-sama I brought you some sushi rolls Baltona
. It does not really eat anything that does not exist in today's list weekly
.Aal grief
! E-this is true, we have to talk to Haku
. A-Yes, you're right
- and, Haku
! Wah, this Stop
! Haku-sama, please keep your underwear
! B-to no avail
! Ah, no avail, the right of Paradise is useless to this
! There is something wrong with this! I hate this
! You are in the way! Palinodial
What it is, Aika-sama?
! Wah Rico, do not lie here and by, her underwear place Return the
! Haku, take off your clothes Stop
! useless ! useless ! useless
! Karen, you can death by
Do Kemeto-sama that every day passes!?
! Nations, it should not be, it is much easier to deal with this when they do it is
. So what you are saying she closed her heart towards us
. Probably
. Excuse me, Haku-sama I'm here to bring you
! Haku-sama! Haku-sama! Please Awake
! I'm here to bring you, let's go back to your room
. Kemeto-sama is not here today, I understood
. Just friends
. Hsna, flnzhb llbyt
"The father of the frog Linq" Arepett-Arepett
"The mother frog revision" educated-educated
So, how Linq their son?
Oh, puzzle?
Father "Arepett-Arepett" and mother "educated-educated"?
.. So .. son frog son frog
! It's a very nice, no benefit
Huh? Frog son Ichergv this he is not Linq
A-Llano, m-long time ago
Oh, it may be, again?
. If you leave your sweetheart for more than one month alone
. Suppose you're too busy
. Yes, Llano, I'm sorry
Dear asshole, I was very worried, and I thought you did not love me anymore longer, learn this?
! This may Marica-tan, take my share
... But if it was not her voice Larry's
So how you will feel vectorial?
. Oh ... A-I love you
Sorry, did I hear you well, say it again, okay?
! What a poor game
-! I love you - I'm here, Kemeto
What do you do ?
Huh? Habiba in your game?
So, what you're saying is it's not real, right?
. Yup
I want to tell him how horrible this, but what do I do!?
. Perhaps to choose my words carefully
. What do you think I came out of your imagination
. Let me say this, I do not play this because I want
. A friend of mine is a voice actress for this game
Sound actress?
When Talban game, the characters are talking and stuff, right?
. It's the voices of such
! Oh, well, let me hear her voice
. Well, talk to them a little
. I had the pleasure to meet you, I'm Marieke
. Huh? I had the pleasure to meet you, I Tancubashi Aika
You girlfriend, right?
. A-Yeah, something like that
. Do not Taatutri
. H-Well
In fact, I am a bit nervous, too, this thing happens to Kltana, huh?
! He fell with it
. Kajorzaka Kemeto-sama Please bring to the Director of the Office
. What can this be! I will come back quickly
It also seems to go along with each other, right?
! We are certainly in order as well as
Listen, Can you to be my girlfriend?
! B-certainly, even death separates us
Could you tell this again?
- until death separates us - a good day, Kemeto-sama
what are you doing ?
. Huh? Oh, Llano ... it will be a new friendship
... O-Oh
. For-if you are looking for Kemeto it is not here
. Haku and Karen are not here too, and I am busy for this Atrkina alone
. The room looks bigger and our existence we both are by
So when I came?
. There is a book I want to read this what it is all
You are not not like to stay with me by, too?
When she did not leave?
Aika-sama
M-What?
When there are girls depicted on all the covers of the paintings?
I do not know, because the chain has a girl as a key figure
. But all other chains as well
. These novels go to men, this is not it strange
. I said I do not know, borrow and book your room Agheroah
. sakhbrh lajlk
What you read here in his room?
In addition, what about down from his bed?
. Reading while plopped here of bad manners
. Oh, okay
! A-Aika-sama, I can see your underwear
! AD-backup
! This you, true, nights horror
Because Kemeto-sama is not here, you are very comfortable, is not it?
! Or Well, I will go back to my room
. Please Relax, when he returns Kemeto-sama
. Both of us will be completely Hidtan
what is this ?
! Hey, do not Tqterpa much
"Euro-Yuri"
This atmosphere is full of girls, too
Most books Kemeto-sama like this, is not it, what?
Because, pervert, right?
! Oh, what you are saying! Kemeto-sama man
. Maybe a pervert man
! Oh, but you know something
. Must be Kemeto-sama is very interested in girls
Oh, what do I do!?
What do you mean by what do I do?
"E-Are you interested in this," I have got these tickets from a friend to me. "" I do not think wrong. "
"This is not what you think, it is not so, let's see," "I got this from a friend if you want, we can go together."
"Ummm"
. I loved these characters that really show here
"Y-Good morning"
"Ayano-chan Good morning," "Good morning"
.. she's talking and behave in an unusual way
I have delayed the day, you got anything that is not a big thing
... but I like the way they work serious and diligent
"Listen t .. t ... Toshi"
. So as not to reveal its goodwill
"Toshicoche-soba." "Have you eaten spaghetti Toshicoche soba?"
. Yes, it is the basic personal
Ammmmm What I'm saying?
Huh? Personal basic?
! This girl ! Aniha
Oh, Is this the intended?
Excuse me, I did not leave any impression I have! ?
! I can not believe this, it's a great superhero girl who can not anyone that Ala
. I'm going to get some crackers
What is that ?
Huh? What do you do here, too?
. Look like a kind of juice, you could be a kind of vernacular drinks
! This Socherb
! Na-not fair, I want to drink too
! M-what your problem, I'm from her grandmother
! In addition to the other girls you may be something, but you have someone else you want to allow him this
. Okay
Huh?
There is one of them, no other option
.. for-luck
..K-cups
. Bring some cups, you Soharkha
When you're excited now?
. I'm not exactly excited, I can not wait to drink
! Oh, yes, well, Flanejrebha
-Hassana - in order to drink
What is that ?
The bubbles were awful
! But hey what Besgueth Ali, O filth
! I've done-for ideals
. This completely lost hope
Wait, what you are doing!?
. Well, I will be stuck if not Okhalaha
What there are, Ica-sama?
.. lashy’
. How did you Ttnatha so?
. Hey, nothing wrong
! No, not, as a student of Seiken, Vavcgark body very much
. So let's see
! There is nothing wrong
- just give them to me
Leica-sama, Leica-sama, are you okay, Laika-sama?
! Oh, excuse me
! I am very sorry, nights negligent
Do you hit?
! Whatever Abaadi these outrageous things away from here
P-obscene? Do you mean Otdaia?
What may I mean other!?
! Please Recessive for your words
! No way ! Abaadiha me really
Would I move, what is obscene specifically in Otdaia?
! Sosdha
! Only Abaadi this out of my way
! No, I will not do it ! Will not until you move Ttrajaa for your
! I apologize
! For-not as you think
! Kemeto-sama, I have missed the understanding
Kemeto, where are you? What are you doing!?
! In the next episode
"This training is called" self-service
According to the game
! Confect the cream Faberoukeno
I thought I understood the ethics of all this world expanding
I thought so it's enough to follow what leads me to him daily
. But here I am here, I can not put a name to this
Feelings that can not be predicted, and the usefulness of the guide
The dividing line between the cheek mixing red, dark blue
And before I know about it, it made it hard to say inside or outside my heart
Do not disappear in the twilight, near to see what it all I
I'm sure that everything will be an opportunity to love
Bring your tears and your dreams, which are forced to hide your smile Well?
I will come to you days that you will Mhassoda everyone
! Get out
. I will go
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Translation of Vergil Vergil-sub.blogspot.com waited for the coming of our translation episodes
what are you doing ?
! too hot
In the next episode "notify out"
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go for this
I love thee, O
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
I am deeply fascinated by the commoners
I Odrsk every day
You did not pick up telepathically so far?
what are you ? cool ?
Oh, you understand, you hide Khgelk, huh?
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go
Here's my love of
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
"It is the land of commoners"