I brought tea.
Here you go.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Here you go.
Thank you very much, Asahina-san.
Haruhi established the SOS Brigade back in May...
...and we are already in the month of June.
Actually, during that period...
...I happened to be involved in a world-cramping incident...
Well, let's just leave that aside.
Today's story goes like this.
Everyone!
We're entering the baseball tournament!
Ninth
City
Amateur
Baseball
Tournament
Accepting Teams
Ninth
City
Amateur
Baseball
Tournament
Accepting Teams
Ninth
City
Amateur
Baseball
Tournament
Accepting Teams
Since that day...
...nothing out of the ordinary ever happened...
Thermodynamics
Particle Theory
Astrodynamics
...and I was able to enjoy a brief period of peace and tranquil tedium...
...but oh, was it brief.
Because...
Whenever her face lights up with that smile...
...I end up being run ragged and exhausted.
What did you say we're entering?
This!
The Boredom of Haruhi Suzumiya
The Ninth City Amateur Baseball Tournament.
So. Who's entering?
In this grass-lot baseball tournament?
We are, obviously!
When you say we...
...are you including the rest of us?
- We'll need to find four more people.
As usual, she only hears the things she wants to hear.
Do you know the rules for baseball?
Of course, I know the rules.
I joined the baseball team for a bit...
...so I know the basics.
But it was dead boring so I left immediately.
So why do we have to participate in a tournament...
...playing that dead boring baseball?
This is a chance to make our existence known around the world!
If we win this tournament...
...it could be a chance to make the name SOS Brigade stand on its own!
It's a great opportunity!
Right?
Isn't it a nice idea, Mikuru-chan?
Um, but...
Right?
Baseball sounds good, yeah?
Just so you know, we're aiming for the championship!
Not a single loss will be tolerated!
I really hate to lose!
Okay?
Why not?
Don't give your consent so cheerfully.
How about objecting every once in a while?
It sounds much more productive than walking around in search of...
...aliens or UMAs, in my opinion.
So? When's the game?
This Sunday.
The day after tomorrow!?
That's way too soon!
But I already turned in the application.
Don't worry.
I named the team SOS Brigade!
There won't be any mistakes in that department!
Where are you planning on pulling together the other members from?
Just grab any bored-looking people we see walking around.
She's serious about that.
Got it.
You just sit tight.
First off, Taniguchi and Kunikida probably don't have anything to do.
Those are fine!
Haruhi referred to classmates as objects.
Let's see...
Two more, huh?
Um...
If it's okay, my friend...
Then we'll do that!
Anyone works, apparently.
Wait.
Asahina-san's friend?
That's making me a little worried.
Her friend from when and where?
It's okay.
She's from this time...
...someone I met from my class.
Then, allow me to join in.
I can think of an acquaintance who has expressed interest in our...
I'll take care of it.
With that decided, let's start training!
Training!
Training, you say?
Right this instant?
That's right!
Where!?
Over there!
Okay! Okay!
And so we ended up participating in a tomfoolery of a baseball tournament.
Why is that?
The answer is simple.
Basically, Haruhi was just...
...bored.
Hey, you.
Let us use this place.
And your baseball equipment, too.
What are you talking about?
We have to practice baseball right away.
You're in the way, so leave.
Like hell we're gonna leave!
It's just for a little while!
Right, Mikuru-chan?
Um...
A predictable adolescent response.
Okay!
Let's start with a thousand hits!
Here we go!
The future of the SOS Brigade rests upon that ball!
Catch it!
This is the first I've heard about our future resting upon such a minuscule ball.
Another round!
Mikuru-chan! Here we go!
It hurts!
Are you okay?
Can you stand?
You mustn't, Kyon-kun.
If you're nice to me...
...it'll happen again...
Hey! Kyon!
Mikuru-chan!
Come back here!
She's retiring due to injury!
That's enough.
Next, the baseball team take the field!
Why us?
Okay!
That's enough for today.
Quite amazing.
That was exactly one thousand.
The fact that you counted to one thousand is what's amazing.
Hey, Nagato.
Could you make it rain on the day of the game?
A huge one that'll cancel the game.
It is possible.
However, it is not recommended.
Why's that?
Alterations to the local environmental data...
...may result in aftereffects to this planet's ecosystem.
How long will these aftereffects last?
Between a few centuries and ten millennia.
Then I guess we probably shouldn't.
Yes.
And just like that...
...here comes the day of the match!
It really didn't need to come.
So you're Kyon-kun?
I've heard a lot about you from Mikuru!
Um.
This is my friend, Tsuruya-san.
I'm Taniguchi!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Kunikida.
Man...
I couldn't turn down a request from my buddy Kyon!
Taniguchi-kun...
Oh, boy...
...and Kunikida-kun, right?
I'll remember that!
Kyon!
Let's have fun today!
Come here for a second.
What are you thinking!?
You're going to have that thing play baseball?
Hey, I watched a game the other day.
"Thing" is a bit rude now.
The catcher...
That "thing" is still my sister.
She introduced herself as an 11-year-old fifth grader.
She's such a sweet little girl that it's hard to believe she's related to you.
He hit a home run!
Anyway, the baseball tournament we're entering is open to the general public!
This isn't Little League!
I know that, Miss Haruhi!
That is exactly why I brought my sister!
Our chance of victory is nil.
Regardless, this is Haruhi we're talking about.
Watch us end up winning by accident!
That would definitely be a pain in the ass.
If we add a fifth grader into the mix...
That's why I was really happy when I got to come along today!
...it'd be a joke if we won.
Very well.
It's a good enough handicap.
I'd feel bad if we slaughtered the other team.
Apparently, she seriously intends on winning.
By the way...
...we haven't decided on a batting order or positions yet.
What are we going to do?
I already thought that through.
You don't have any problems with deciding through this, right?
One for batting order and one for field position.
Also, I'm the pitcher and lead-off.
So all you came up with was a method to decide.
What?
Do you have a problem with that?
It's a democratic method.
They used lottery to choose their government in ancient Greece!
Taniguchi
Yuki
Tsuruya-san
Kyon
Mikuru-chan
Koizumi-kun
Don't compare the ancient Greek government system to modern Japan batting order selection!
Kunikida
Kyon's Sister
Tsuruya-san
And you're the only one who gets to choose your own position.
How is that democratic?
_ _ _ _ _ _
Name
_ _ _ _ _  _
Position
_ _ _ _ _ _
Haruhi Suzumiya
_ _ _ _ _  _
Pitcher
_ _ _ _ _ _
Mikuru-chan
_ _ _ _ _  _
Right
_ _ _ _ _ _
Yuki
_ _ _ _ _  _
Center
_ _ _ _ _ _
Kyon
_ _ _ _ _  _
Second
Oh, well.
_ _ _ _ _ _
Kyon's Sister
_ _ _ _ _  _
Left
Looks like I'll get to go home even sooner than expected.
_ _ _ _ _ _
Koizumi-kun
_ _ _ _ _  _
Catcher
_ _ _ _ _ _
Kunikida
_ _ _ _ _  _
First
_ _ _ _ _ _
Tsuruya-san
_ _ _ _ _  _
Third
After all, we were just told that...
_ _ _ _ _ _
Taniguchi
_ _ _ _ _  _
Short
...our first opponents are a college team, the Kamigahara Pirates.
The leading candidate to win this tournament.
The game is called at ten runs...
...so now would be a good time to start packing up to go home.
Play ball!
That was a totally weak pitch!
The rest of you follow my lead!
Please go easy on me...
Strike!
How dare you throw a real pitch at Asahina-san!?
If you hit her, there will immediate brawling!
A brawling bash!
Strike!
Mikuru-chan!
Swing like this!
Like this!
Strikeout!
Hey!
Why aren't you swinging the bat!?
Strike!
Strikeout!
Yuki!
You can't hit the ball if you don't swing!
Kyon!
You better get a hit!
You're clean-up!
What can you possibly expect from a clean-up chosen through lottery?
Strike!
Haruhi doubled off this pitch?
Strikeout!
Moron!
What are you doing!?
Crap.
Let's shut them out!
Play!
Strike!
Strikeout!
Nice pitching!
Too easy! Too easy!
Foul ball!
If all you can throw is straight pitches in the strike zone...
I got it! I got it!
...once they figure that out, you're going to get hit.
And our defense has more holes than an anthill in a savanna.
No!
U-Um...
Like a sieve!
The fact that we only gave up two runs this inning...
Great play!
...must be because the other team's goddess of victory is running late.
I suppose that everyone wants to take it easy on Sunday.
Way to go!
SOS Brigade
Kamigahara
Pirates
Strikeout!
Continuing, our offensive in the top of the next inning came to an abrupt end...
SOS Brigade
Kamigahara
Pirates
...and our opponents easily built up their lead in the bottom.
It looks like we can end this in the next inning.
Out!
That's a toughie.
Just getting the bat on the ball took everything I had.
It looks like we're going to need that.
Hey! Timeout!
W-Wait!
Suzumiya-san!
S-Stop it!
- Stupid! Come on!
Get undressed and change!
Mikuru!
- Looking good there.
Can I take a picture?
It's so cute!
It might go better with a ponytail.
Come on.
Start cheering.
Um... How do I do that?
Like this!
C'mon! Yell it loud and clear!
E-Everybody!
Please hit the ball!
Please do your best!
Just watch me!
Strikeout!
There's no way I can hit that.
No matter.
I wasn't expecting anything from you.
Safe!
Mikuru-chan!
You better hit it this time!
- Mikuru! You can do it!
Asahina-san!
Strike!
Mikuru-chan!
This! This!
What is she doing?
Is she trying to reduce the magic points of the opposing pitcher?
It would appear that she's giving a sign.
Did we ever decide on any signs?
No.
However...
...she's probably signaling for a squeeze.
A squeeze towards first with two outs?
Even one of those lame duck managers could do a better job than this.
Presuming that Asahina-san's chances of hitting the ball are practically none...
...using a squeeze when least expected to surprise the opposing team...
...may possibly cause the infield to commit an error...
...or perhaps she thinks that even Asahina-san can at least manage to make contact with the ball.
They've all figured it out though.
Strike!
Strikeout!
Mikuru-chan!
Come over here and buckle down for some pain!
This is punishment! Punishment!
Let everyone look at your funny face.
Please stop...
Are you an idiot?
It's your fault for giving signs that make no sense.
Just steal home by yourself or whatever.
Things have taken a bad turn.
I really don't want to hear it, but go ahead.
Closed space has appeared on a scale never before witnessed.
It appears to be expanding at an alarming rate.
As long as Suzumiya-san retains her foul mood, it will continue to expand...
...and those will also continue to rampage around.
Just because we're losing?
She's so full of it.
You sound as though it doesn't concern yourself...
...but this incident is largely due to you.
After all, we drew lots to determine the batting order.
And consequently, you became clean-up.
I'm not particularly happy about it.
You became the clean-up batter...
...because Suzumiya-san desired it.
It wasn't coincidence.
And then...
...she was disappointed by your dismal performance.
So sorry about that.
In any case...
...let us do everything possible to prevent the game from being called this inning.
If the game ends now...
...it will mean the end of this world.
Come on!
We're starting!
We must do all we can to hold them to two runs.
Two outs. Runners on first and second.
SOS Brigade
Kamigahara
Pirates
Current score: 0-9.
The game will be over in another run.
It's coming towards me!
Make it...
Make it!
Amazing!
Nice play!
Way to go, you!
- That's my buddy!
Picking up where we left off...
Your face is really close.
What do you want?
During the previous incident, when you and Suzumiya-san were in the other world...
...how did you make it back?
Don't remind me of that.
If we use that method again...
...it may get us out of this crisis again.
I refuse.
I thought you would say that.
Then I shall go secure our means to victory.
After all...
...her interests should coincide with ours.
Nagato-san's finally...
Is something up with her?
She seems to be reciting an incantation.
Incantation?
What's that?
Um...
Classified information.
An incantation, huh...
That was incredible!
Where are you hiding that strength?
This has been modified with a boost in attribute data.
What's that mean?
Homing mode.
That ball's gone!
I see. Homing mode, is it.
Oh, boy...
There's a limit to ridiculousness.
Whatever the case...
...any more of this and we'll be in trouble.
In a variety of ways...
That's enough.
I see.
Strike!
I'd forgotten...
...but there is a time limit of ninety minutes per game.
Which means the next inning will be dropped.
If we last through this inning, we'll win.
Is it really okay for us to win?
We cannot afford the alternative.
Thanks to our efforts...
...the expansion of closed space has been checked.
But if they make a comeback now, it'll be a walk-off loss.
There's no need to think about how bad of a mood Haruhi will be in then.
And so I have an idea concerning that.
Seriously?
Very serious.
To make it through this inning while giving up a minimal number of runs...
...this is our only remaining option.
Oh, boy...
Ball!
Hey!
Be serious about it!
I let you take my place...
...so if you lose, you have to treat everyone!
I know.
After all, the fate of the world rests on my pitching.
The world sure isn't worth much these days.
Thanks to this "Mysterious Ball"...
Strike!
...as christened by yours truly...
...it appears we've avoided destruction.
S-Strike two!
Strikeout!
The next pitcher struck out in three pitches...
...and what would probably be the last batter had chalked up two strikes.
Strike two!
Kyon!
Finish it with the next pitch!
I don't need you to tell me to end the game.
Sorry, Kamigahara Pirates.
Lucky!
It's a wild pitch, Nagato!
Pick up the ball and throw it!
Hurry up!
Second!
Here!
Huh?
I'm terribly sorry.
We happen to be a slightly unreasonable group.
G-Game over!
Thanks to Nagato's bogus magic...
...we've ended up winning, but...
What shall we do about the next game?
Continuing onto the next round...
...would be inexcusable to the Kamigahara Pirates. Besides...
The truth is that I need to go help my colleagues soon.
We'll be short on members, too.
Let's forfeit.
That sounds best.
It would appear that it is a bad idea to allow Suzumiya-san to be bored.
We should take that into consideration during future endeavors.
You've had your fun, right?
Koizumi had to leave because something came up.
My legs and arms are completely worn out.
If it's okay with you, I guess that's fine.
I'm pretty hungry anyway.
Let's go have lunch!
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you so much!
Not at all.
I'll be going then.
Wait.
About that bat...
I didn't know I had it in me.
So you're Yuki Nagato-chan?
I must have talent for baseball.
I've heard a lot about you from Mikuru.
Everybody eat up!
It's all Kyon's treat!
Oh, well.
I managed to get my hands on some unexpected extra cash.
Here's to the success of the Kamigahara Pirates.
C'mon! C'mon! Swing harder!
Sorry I'm late!
Hey!
Which one do you want to do next?
Soccer
Tournament
American
Football
Tournament
Soccer
American
Football
Tournament
Soccer
American
Football
Tournament
How many people do you need for soccer and American football?
Will the members from last time be enough?
Thermodynamics
Particle Theory
Astrodynamics
As I watched Haruhi's first-class smile...
...I considered which one would require less people.
American football! No!
Make it Japanese croquet!