It's one problem after another
I'm too scared to even go home
I'll kill you
I guess I'll spend the night outside
My hand, It's become stiff
The zombie force that caused this is really strong
That long fingered bastard
It's him
That monster has appeared
I'll catch him!
Do you think you can escape me that easily?
Explain yourself
The suspect, we can't let him escape
Cut the crap!
I don't trust you anymore
You crazy women!
Today I'll put an end to our conflict
What conflict?
What are you doing?
Stop it! I'm trying to trackdown a dangerous suspect
Stop lying!
(Help!)
(Someone has died on the street)
(She was fine a moment ago)
(She suddenly collapsed)
Excuse us, move aside
Another case of zombiefication
Did she notice something?
Hey, what's up?
Where are you going?
She normally dosn't act like this
Hello, It's Yeyan
Yan bro, I've found the guy you're looking for
He match's the drawings perfectly
He's heading north on People's Street
It looks like he's following two girls
I'll be there shortly
Yeyan?
What's he doing here?
Dahm it
So he really is the culprit
He's definitely behind the zombiefications
(so annoying)
(coming from you)
(did you forget your meds?)
(lol)
(this is for real)
(prove it)
(geez, you never believe me)
Good thing I reacted fast
Die you monster!
YEYAN!
President!
Mr. Secretary?
Move aside!
President, I'm coming to save you!
Asshole, what are you doing?
What have you done to the president!
President?
To ambush the president, how vile
He is Xiahou Middleschool's Student Council President, Ximen Guanren
The president is away for a mission, he is an active member of the night command
You must listen to his every order
Also,
He's quite a meticulous guy, make sure to treat him with respect
Or else, you'll suffer badly
President I am so sorry
He's awakened!
President, please feel assured to give me your inheritance
Don't let them escape!
Zombie!
So she is the culprit
Chaos Beast!
Wait! You shouldn't use that here, it'll damage the city
It can't be helped, she's about to escape
The costs are too high!
Watch it, take this!
Vicious Lotus Blast!
Whiplash Phoenix Sweep!
Oh crap! Another building!
Why must you harm the buildings?
Now! Catch her alive!
Yes sir!
Not good, it's zombie gas
Crap, there's too many spectators
(what's that)
(I think it's forced eviction?)
(ooh, interesting)
(hold on tenants!)
Dahm it
Zombie gas
Leave it to me
Hey! This isn't time to exercise!
Shoulder excercise
Health is priority
So strong
This zombie gas sure is...
Poisonous
Fuck! You sure you can handle this?
Out of his way!
Sir, what are you doing?
The president is strong and is usually very calm
But now...
Zombie babe, want to come play?
Babe
Where are you going?
Don't leave yet!
You can't escape!
Babe, this is when the magic happens
Complete transformation
(what was that?)
(so gruesome)
(blood!)
When, president gets serious, he loses all reason
He becomes a complete savage!
Fortunately I'm here
Amnesia Inducing Punch!
This guy and the president sure are odd
(why is my stomach growling)
(you probably caught a chill)
Amnesia Inducing Punch can make someone forget a shocking moment
The mind will fill the blank with a logical explaination
They'll forget everything by tomorrow morning
You sure it's not caused by the concussion
You think your tough then come again
I'm the fiercest censorate, Ximen Guanren
My name is $#%
&@%#$
President
It's over
So it was a zombie
What's this?
A stray spirit's seal
This is...
There's dark energy
Ehya
I forgot that censorates can see dark energy
I miscalculated