Don't talk to me anymore!
I don't want to have anything to do with you!
I'd never thought we'd meet again so quickly
It's a hit and run
Where are public morals?
What a tragic women
But good thing you found me
I'll personally carry you to the hospital!
And yet you said we're ill-fated!
I'm clearly your saviour!
A manhole without a cover?
Crap! I was thinking too much that I forgot to look in front of me!
I'll definately protect big sister from the impact!
Safe landing
Also you're...
Why do I get hurt everytime I see you?
Our encounter must be ill-fated
She's covered in blood!
Excuse us! Emergency patient!
Serious head injury! Prepare for surgery!
The sewers were really cold
Not good! The patient!
It seems...
We're ill-fated after all
It'd be better if we stopped seeing each other
Did you not see what happened that day?
Really?
Even the SWAT team was deployed
SWAT team?
Too bad that Yeyan kid got away
That day... What really happened?
He... He clearly turned into a bear
And then there was a gang of monsters
Who is that kid anyways?
Did he summon those monsters?
Also that scary women...
She effortlessly defeated buff bro
She's also after Yeyan
That sinister feeling
What is it?
Not good! I saw too much!
Would she try to silence me?
I'm just hallucinating, hallucinating...
Student, do you know where is classroom 3A?
Bro!
He's passed out?
City people are so cowardly
Beauty, he's probably just too excited
3A right? I'll lead the way
Thank you very much
Take good care of bro!
This way
Based on experience, this should last for a while
I better get to class!
Quiet, quiet!
Listen up, This is our new beautiful girl student!
Please welcome her!
(she's our goddess!)
Student, why don't you introduce yourself?
Hello everyone, I just transferred here...
Who's knocking on the board?
New student? Don't you know it's nap time?
It's been a while since I had a good nap
It's all your fault!
So who is this new student anyways?
Is she really that exciting?
The heavens must be corrupt...
We meet again...
(do they know each other?)
You!
Did those things to me!
(those things?)
Caused me those types of harm!
(those types of harm?)
Do you think you can get away with this?
Um...
BYE!
Are you just going to run away?
As a man you must take responsibility!
(dahm you yeyan! go to hell!)
(how dare you violate our goddess)
I'm wrong big sis, please forgive me!
At least spare my underwear
Lowly commoner
I wasn't even supposed to notice you
But you hospitalized me twice in one week
The second time wasn't my fault!
SHUT IT!
Do you know the cost of medical treatment?
I've used up all my savings!
I don't even have enough to eat!
Maybe it's...
I think it's the doctor who's at fault...
The punishment is...
Allow me to live with you!
Huh?
I have to take care of you?
(I'll take care of you!)
(why does it have to be this way!)
(my goddess! die yeyan!)
(I'll kill him!)
(why can't it be me!)
Come in
Headmaster, the new Stray Spirit has arrived
That's great, the heavens have finally responded
This generation can be saved
Then I'll find some one to show them around
Wait, don't rush, we'll observe them for a while
A censorate must adapt to all environments
Bring order to all worlds
They must be able to fit in on their own
Newer censorates must learn the ways of the present
If they can't even do that, then they'll just have to be replaced
(laowang, it's your turn)
Sigh... this is troublesome
When everything is wrong, only art remains pure
Hey, can you eat this?
Big sis, you should wear more, it'll be troubling if people saw us like this
I'm used to this
(laowang, what happened?)
Old people can't withstand stimulation
(laowang, you have to hold on!)
It's a Xiahou student
He's got quite a bit of life force, he'll make a nice component
This is...
Urine?
I'll have to look into this
Where am I? So thirsty...
F*ck! What are you doing!?
Your awake?
This student is all grown
How could you pee in public?
MONSTER!