Woah, Big bro must be the main character, he gets featured in the first scene!
It's only one of my passive abilities
No matter what the plot dictates
Whenever I pee
The camera will always be focused on me
In broad daylight
Yet you... Commit crimes and hurt people!
Where did this old hag come from
Watch me slap...
Woah, big bro is so godly!
Just as I said
I'll kill you is one blow!
I'll kill this monster!
I don't want this!
Who is this person?
She even found my weak point
Go to hell!
You're... A stray spirit?
The naturel enemy of monsters for thousands of years
Any encounter would result is a brutal death
Destroying our soul
Those killed have no chance of revival!
Oh shit! It really is a spirit
This time we're screwed
Look at how scared he is
It's like he doesn't have an owner
Yes, yes, yes
When our owners here, we don't even have to be scared of full spirits!
Bro, it's decided
Miss spirit, please spare me!
I'm wrong
I'll never do it again!
There is no again
Monster
Go die!
Huh? Who's there?
I'm just passing by, don't mind us, continue what you're doing
Hey, your fly's open
Oh no! How embarrassing!
Shit, I fell for it
Leg it!
As I suspected
It's that dahm mushroom!
Master!
We better run as well!
Retreat!
So fast, are they finished work?
I've finally found you
Dahm mushroom
You're not getting away!
Yan-bro! Please take me in!
I gave you an opportunity, and you come back again
Your outta luck
Spirit-sis seemed fine at first
But now she's a raging monster!
Maybe she knows you or something
Bastards! Stop right there!
I'd rather die than to endure this!
Please take me in!
If it's like that, then I'll have to test you
Big bro,
To fulfill your orders I'm willing to die a thousand times
Please be my meat shield!
I've been the top dog for so long
I've finally realized the suffering of my underlings
Outta my way!
This actually feels pretty good
Stop it!
It's over
What should I do?
I've started to become a masochist
I suddenly feel scared yet sad
Stop running!
If you stop chasing me then I won't be running!
Last time was an accident
Get slashed!
Where'd he go?
Dahm it
If I catch him
I'll definitely cut him down!
What is this?
First a night watcher and then a stray spirit
And then I've become an M
This anime is too dangerous
I'll have to find another role
Hey!
Spirit-sis...
Please kick me again!
Tell me
What's your affiliation with the backpack kid
What's his name?
He... He's called Yeyan
Yeyan, so that's what it was
She has a young calabash on her head
Mother
It's summoning it's mother!
This is... The 800 year old armament
The trans dimensional calabash!
The sacred treasure sealed within the Tiantai palace!
A weapon that can defeat immortals!
At least you know
Lift!
Alright
My side job is completed
Time to collect my boxed lunch
Yeyan!
Who's calling me?
Huh?
What?
Look, the trash can kid is flying!
Humph
Lets see where'd you run now
So this is the inside of the calabash
It's like a sauna in hell!
It seems like this steam is highly corrosive
Dahm it
If this continues, the moisture from my body won't last
I'll be reduced to liquid fertilizer
I have no choice
I'll have to do it!
Spirit-sis, I'm wrong
There are other things to worry about
Negotiate instead of violence
At least you're tactful
I'll spare you for now
So all I had to do was apologize?
Hey! Where's your clothes?
They've been corroded
Nonsense!
If your clothes are gone, then why is your underwear intact?
If you insist
I can take them off
Not necessary!
Don't think I've forgiven you
You must compensate accordingly
If you don't want to be grudged
I knew it! There was no way you'd let let me go that easily
I want you...
To kneel before me!
Pride is a man's gold
Although it's devious
But...
What?
You've knelt so easily! Are you really a man?
I'm wrong
Your majesty
Get out! You queer!
May I kiss your feet?
What perverted game is this!
Didn't you want to play master and slave
Why do I have to meet someone like you
What an ill-fated relationship
How is this ill-fated?
We have a lot in common
You also like to wear funny outfits is public
And get excited when people look at you
Who's getting excited?
Woah, historic clothes, so pretty
Is she a show girl?
Why don't you go break the ice?
You go first
Darn it
I've trained in the mountains for all my life
It's the first time I've been in a city, do I really have to explain this?
Let me tell you, I definitely don't get excited when people look at me
We're just trying to clear a grudge
This will never happen again!
Quickly I depart
Wait, big sis!
Don't talk to me!
I don't want to have anything to do with you!
Woah! Big bro is amazing!
He appears at the most important moment!
Of course
If I don't stop, then the show can't end!
Woah! Is it for real?
Don't believe me? Just watch