These two chicks sure are charming
I'm I hallucinating?
I didn't drink "that" much
Humans and Monsters once coexisted equally
Humans lived during the day
Monsters came out at night
But when lights were invented, humans started to take over the night
Disrupting the Yin Yang¹
Causing the monsters to rebel, and harm humans
Because of this,
Those who could defeat monsters became important in society
And my goal is
To become the ace of censors²
[19:00 Internet Cafe]
Little brother,
Playing by you self late at night, how depressing
How about you play some more stimulating games with us?
The key to a women heart
Is a man who is confident
Don't show your weakness
Your brother here is the master at picking up girls
Heh, okay, okay,
So how are we going to play?
Don't get too exited
First answer our question
Which one of us do you think is prettier?
Men,
They must have a sharp mind and raging courage
I think your face is prettier
But her body is better
So that means your equally amazing
You really know what to say
Then how about this?
My body along with her face
Does that make us prettier?
The secret to conquering girls
Is to leave an unforgettable impression
He already fainted
Sis, we can properly enjoy him
Eww,
What's that smell?
It really spoils my appetite
Oh gawd!
He's wetting himself!
It's out of control!
Sigh,
Finding food to eat is sure difficult for monsters
Firstly,
It's better for us if the prey has a stronger Qi³
Qi is determined by age
The older the prey, the weaker the Qi
We were lucky to find one with a strong Qi
But he ended up wetting himself
I guess we'll have to test our luck elsewhere
[Xiahou Middle School, First Years Building]
There's someone here this late?
Is that what they call a nerd?
Nerd or dweeb
As long as we've eaten
His strong and robust Qi really is making my mouth water
Dinosaur?
I guess it's hard to be a nerd
You've even lost your identity
Male Student,
Huh?
How did you tell I was a man from behind?
Because we specialize in eating men
Wah! So scary!
Now that you know, just give up, and let us eat you!
I don't want to
Why, why can't we move?
This, this gong⁴ is?
You are?
A night-watcher⁵?
The job of night-watchers is to find monsters that harm humans
Of course, there are times that the monster cannot be defeated
Please let us go!
We just came her, and didn't know any better!
No way
If you kill us, then our toxins⁶ will spread throughout the school
That way, more people will die
We know that night-watchers can't avoid this
It's true that I have no way to vanquish you
But that's why I prepared a different way to deal with you guys
Huh?
The Eight Sided Demon Hunting Flag?
We're screwed!
You've waited a long time for this
Come out!
(I can finally go pimping again!)
(Bro, thanks for letting us out again)
(What beautiful ladies!)
Bro, if your going to catch them
Then save one for breeding
Close the doors and windows
Don't disturb me as I cast the spell
Sis, what are we going to do?
His familiars are going to absorb our souls
We don't want to live our lives with these old pervers!
Let clouds scatter the mortal body
Primordial spirits I summon
The blood of my Soul
I command thee!
Didn't I tell you to close the windows?
Huh? Where'd my Familiars go?
[Dude, watch your back]
Who dares steal my prey?
NOOO!!!
It's that stray spirit again!
I've been after these two for a couple of days
How could I let them escape
The job of spirits is to kill monsters
None will be spared
Take us with you!
Let go! I don't want to face a Spirit
Night-watchers and stray spirits both serve to protect humanity
They just do it differently
You gong beaters really like to mingle with monsters
Although we're not as extreme as you
But,
Shut your mouth!
I'll never let anyone insult the name of night-watchers!!
You impure Spirit
What did you say?
So what? All Spirits are impure anyways
You stupid gong beater!
Bro! We support you!
Headmaster,
The two new censors are fighting on school grounds
Kekeke,
The new students sure are lively
These two sprouts are pretty impressive
Headmaster,
This looks like a one sided fight
Seeing the youthfulness of two students
It reminds me of an ancient poem
I look up
The moon is in the sky
How many dreams?
Are floating in freedom
Dahm it,
I can't beat her in hand to hand combat
[Bro, fight on! You fight well!]
So unfaithful! They left already!
I've already predicted the ending
A night-watcher's Familiars are terrified of Spirits
He can't fight back
The night-watcher has no chance
I have no choice
Chaos Beast!
Headmaster,
I think the stray spirit is the one in trouble
Actually, I already predicted that the Protectors strength is much higher than the Spirit
A poem goes
A big headed son, and a small headed father
No matter how big the son's head is
He still can't beat his father
Million Spells!
Headmaster,
It looks like...
Shut it!
Spell Blast!
Demon Flags!
Hit!
Open!
Close!
Don't think of escaping
Chaos Beast! After her!
Look at these young people fighting
It reminds me of the time when I was in the heart of my youth
Another poem wells up from my heart
Headmaster,
Bed...
What is it now!
If this continues, the school will be finished
They're destroying our school grounds
How about I go to stop them
Leave it to me
I haven't exorcised for a while
Headmaster! If this goes on, the school...
Children
Stop fighting
Listen to your elder
Poems are like clouds
Who the hell are you?
The headmaster has fallen!
She started it
He started it first
Why are you so annoying?
Your the one that's pissing me off
So what?
Come at me!
You think I'm scared?
Our battle haven't been decided yet!
Enough!
This is the student council
I think you already know what you've done
Assaulting the headmaster, destroying the school, and fighting in class
These events are plenty to expel you from the school
Listen up night-watcher Ye Yan
Pay attention, stray spirit, Huangxiao Ying
The headmaster has given you an wonderful opportunity
I have a task
You must complete this together
Huh?
A task for the both of us?
Where am I?
Sis,
Let's get out of here
Yes, yes
AHH!
Hey,
Beautiful ladies
Where do you think you're going?